[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT,
Giru's quick thinking saved
Goku from a gruesome fate!
How dare you betray me when
it is I who gave you life,
you insubordinate bot?!
[GIRU] Betray? Giru never betray
his friends. Giru, Giru.
What?
[TRUNKS] I'm all right!
I'm up here! See?!
Everything that
happened was thanks to
the careful planning
of Giru and myself.
I bet you didn't
see that coming.
[NARRATOR] As everyone
celebrated the victory,
Dr. Myuu made a break
to try and stop his most valued
secret from being exposed.
But Trunks was one step ahead.
S-Stop! Don't open that!
[NARRATOR] Behind this door
lies a mystery so dark,
that even Trunks had to
deceive his closest friends
for it to be discovered.
Find out what terror awaits them
right now on Dragon Ball GT!
[DR. MYUU] Stop it!
Don't get any closer!
My Baby, my baby. I'm sorry.
Please forgive me for
allowing them to see you.
[machine pulsating]
I didn't want to expose you
to the eyes of such
filthy creatures
before you attained
your complete form.
[machine pulsating]
[DR. MYUU]
I'm sorry, baby.
I know how long
you've been waiting,
how frightened you
must be in there.
Uh, what's that
thing in the water?
It looks
like a robot baby.
You're close, Pan.
It's called Baby,
an infant machine that
was created by Dr. Myuu,
only he applied a
restructuring method
not used on any other
robot on this planet.
[TRUNKS]
When that thing is full grown
its power could surpass us all.
Maybe even before then,
if he develops a workable body.
There's still a lot of questions
we don't have answers for.
You've got to be kidding?
Can he really get that powerful?
How did a bunch of
rotten Saiyans like them
learn the secret of my baby?
Even among robots, rumors can
spread like fire. Right, Giru?
[GIRU]
Giru heard story.
Dr. Myuu build greater
machine mutant.
When new Baby is born, all other
robots to be dismantled! Giru...
[DR. MYUU]
What?
[TRUNKS] When Giru told
me this, I had him show me
where the main computer
was and I shut it off.
It's over.
[DR. MYUU] But--
How could he do this?!
Oh, Baby! My beautiful baby!
Please wake up!
Please, don't die! My baby!!
What did you do
to my baby? You animal!
Simple. I re-routed
his life support
into the unit's
plumbing system.
[TRUNKS] Your baby will stop
functioning soon.
And then we'll be safe.
No! You can't!
You can't die on me! Baby!
[pained groaning]
If I can find the
internal power switch,
I can still redirect the
power in time to save him!
Just like Rilldo said,
Dr. Myuu's sole aim
is to control
the entire galaxy.
If he wants the whole galaxy,
then he had those beady little
eyes set on the earth, too.
[TRUNKS]
Of course he did.
[PAN] Who does
this guy think he is?
[GOKU] He's just like every
other villain out there, Pan.
[TRUNKS] Right.
He's greedy.
That's why, while he continued
with the research on Baby,
he began mobilizing the older
models of robots on this planet
using a military
style of control.
It's all practice for the day he
finally takes over the galaxy.
[GIRU] Giru and robots forced
to do bad things. Bad things.
Yeah, but if it
wasn't for you, Giru,
Dr. Myuu might have
taken over the galaxy.
I think that shows a
pretty healthy good side.
[GIRU]
Is that true?
You're my hero.
[GIRU] Giru have much concern
over homeland and Dr. Myuu,
concern over bad stories.
Know he must change!
Then met new friends.
When we found Giru
in the desert,
an abnormality in his
data was activated,
probably due to
the shock of his journey.
He experienced what we would
refer to as a loss of memory
or amnesia.
So he really is
a defective little robot.
[GIRU]
What?!
I'm just kidding, Giru.
And when we drifted
close to his planet,
the abnormality
repaired itself,
and his memory started
working again.
[GIRU]
Giru told Trunks everything.
And Trunks help Giru. Giru...
[ANGRY BOT] Doesn't
look so tough to Bot K58.
[ANGRY BOT]
Ah, whatever.
--Trunks! Trunks!
--Giru, you did a nice job.
Now where's that baby?
[GIRU]
Giru could not find.
But Giru did locate Dr. Myuu's
hidden laboratory. Giru.
Even better! That way we can
stop this problem at the source.
How do we get there?
Hey! What a
handsome young devil.
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru.
[both laughing]
[TRUNKS] It's good we found this
before he was finished with it.
I wouldn't have wanted
to stare that thing down.
How could anybody even think to
create such a horrifing thing?
[TRUNKS] But you have to
recognize the genius it takes...
--You Fools! What have you done?
--...an idea so radical.
No! You can't die on me!!
My life's work, blown away,
disintegrated in an instant.
You cannot die, baby.
Remember all that
we're trying to achieve!
[DR. MYUU] Think about yourself,
your life, what you will be
when you finally ascend
to your true form.
Remember, the power given to you
through the sacrifice of Luud.
Remember, you are
made of the galaxy!
Energies from all across it
pulse through your body,
giving you life!
This power is greater than
any the galaxy has ever known!
Do you understand?
That means the galaxy is
yours for the taking!
Live, Baby! Please!
You're my only baby. My only...
Don't leave me. Don't leave me.
[PAN] I'm, uh, I'm kind of
feeling sorry for him.
It's too bad. I really wish I
could have fought him just once.
Goku!
Do me a favor and
please try to stay focused.
But I am focused!
I guess you're right.
What do you think?
Has that little guy
stopped functioning yet?
[GOKU] Wow!
Look at that! Impressive!
You can't turn his power back
on for just a little bit?
Oh, Grandpa.
Goku, please!
You!
Don't you dare put your
hands on baby's capsule!
[DR. MYUU]
You disgusting, vile Saiyan!
Ah! My baby!
What happened?
[GIRU] Danger, danger! Run!
Get away! Get away!
[DR. MYUU]
Live my baby!
Baby! My darling baby!
[PAN]
Look!
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru...
That's impossible!
Trunks, how is
this all happening?
So the little guy
didn't die after all?
I, I don't get it. His breathing
apparatus and computer
should be off-line by now.
[DR. MYUU]
Oh Baby, I'm so happy!
I knew you couldn't die
that easily my baby!
Your power is too deep
in your circuits!
And now you can show everyone
what you're truly capable of!
I can't... I mean it's... Whoa.
His power keeps growing.
Stay sharp.
[TRUNKS]
Huh?
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru...
That thing is
giving me the creeps.
Well, I'm ready
for whatever it's got!
[GIRU] All will die!
All will die!! Run! Run!
[PAN]
Giru, don't start panicking!
[maiacal laugh]
Ah!
Ugh!
Ow!
[clacking]
Pan! Trunks! Giru! Watch out!
[screams]
Incredible!
And he's not even
fully developed yet!
[screams]
[DR. MYUU]
That's right.
You must become strong, my baby!
You must rise up and destroy
those who have disturbed you!
Kill the Saiyans! Make them
pay for dishonoring you!
[screams]
Kill... Sai... yan.
[DR. MYUU] That's right Baby.
The Saiyans! Kill the Saiyans!
Sai...yan.
Sai... yan.
Kill.
Pan!
Trunks! Now!
[screaming]
[Baby screaming in pain]
No! Baby!
So did we get him?
[GIRU]
Danger has passed.
[DR. MYUU] Now I understand
the true nature of a Saiyan.
[single beep]
[PAN] That's a spaceship!
He's going to try
and fly out of here!
He can't--
Farewell.
Hey! You can't leave now!
I haven't even started
warming up yet!
I am so sick of
cowards running away!
[GOKU]
Pan, calm down!
[PAN]
Let go of me, Grandpa!
The next time I get my hands
on him, I'm gonna rip him ap--
[TRUNKS] Pan, we can't worry
about Dr. Myuu any longer.
But, he got away.
Right, but Baby is dead.
And without him,
Dr. Myuu doesn't have
any hope of taking
over the galaxy.
So, the best thing for us to do
is get back to finding
the Dragon Balls.
You're right. But,
what about our ship?
How are we gonna fix it?
That's no problem.
[GIRU] Giru fix ship well,
back to normal.
How convenient!
You're quite the handyman!
[DR. MYUU] Saiyans!
Disgusting Saiyans!
They're mucking up my entire
operation to conquer the galaxy.
Though, I'm not the type
to give up that easily
because of a setback.
If I can learn
from these mistakes,
I'll be ready for
the resurrection
in a few short months and
then my baby will be reborn!
"My baby." Every time I hear
that it makes my insides boil,
so much I want to explode!
[BABY]
You fool.
You have no idea who
the boss is do you?
You are nothing but
a simple machine mutant.
For it was I who
programmed you to gather
the energy needed
for my resurrection.
And it was I who gave you
the plans for creating Luud
and the other machine mutants!
Yet, you had no idea,
you feeble shell of a machine.
Your time on
this planet is over.
But my time is just beginning.
I will be the one to bring
Planet M2 to completion.
[evil chuckling]
[NARRATOR] After having
Dr. Myuu construct him,
Baby used and destroyed the
doctor to make a quick escape!
Will he be as merciless
when it comes to
the Saiyans who disturbed him?
I know three disgusting
creatures who have to die today.
And I know they
won't be expecting me.