[NARRATOR]
Previously on GT...
Goku and Pan had the first
four Shadow Dragons on the run
as each one of them met
their untimely doom!
But the fifth one was
considerably stronger!
[NUOVA SHENRON]
...ultimate game of survival,
without any distractions!
I see. Well, I'd rather
settle this without fighting.
But if I have to...
[GOKU]
Solar Flare!
Someone of your strength being
knocked out by a Solar Flare?
I don't think so, Nuova Shenron!
I'm not buying it!
[NUOVA SHENRON]
Goku was right!
In a flash,
the deadly dragon
shattered his old persona
to make way for the new!
[GOKU]
Impressive.
So this is your true
form I take it?
[NARRATOR] The stakes had been
raised, but Goku was ready.
He, too, assumed his
ultimate fighting form!
The battle is far from over,
and another Saiyan is
anxious to enter the fray.
Vegeta prepares for his
biggest challenge yet,
today on Dragon Ball GT!
[NUOVA SHENRON growling]
[SS4 GOKU yelling]
[BOTH yelling]
[BULMA]
Vegeta, no! Wait!
[VEGETA] I can't just leave
things to Kakarot! I have to go!
[BULMA]
You'll die!
Who cares?
[BULMA]
I care! Your children care!
I'm going!
If you stay, I think I
can help you transform!
[VEGETA]
Ah! You call this help?
[VEGETA grunting, groaning]
How dare you!
Leaving me behind,
expecting me to sit back
while you go back and fight!
Like I'm some sort of weakling!
[VEGETA]
I refuse to be a spectator!
How did this happen?
How did the gap between
our powers get so big?
[VEGETA] With Nappa gone,
I could use a good man.
There's no one in the
Universe that could touch us.
We could rule the planet
and you could have
anything you wanted!
Anything! Nothing would
be out of your grasp!
Well? What do you say, Kakarot?
Look, I've got everything I ever
wanted right here on Earth!
All I need is my family, Vegeta.
Besides, I've seen how
you treat your partners!
There's not a lot
of job security!
All right then! So be it!
[VEGETA]
You had your chance!
The first time I fought you,
you were no match for me!
I was superior in every respect.
Try this on!
Man, he's good.
Far better than I expected.
I'll get him though!
Kakarot...
What's wrong? I was hoping
for a more interesting fight.
Oh, you'll get one! I promise!
[GOKU]
Kaioh Ken!
[GOKU grunting]
[VEGETA groaning]
[VEGETA grunting]
Don't tell me
that's all you've got!
Cause if it is,
you'd better quit!
[GOKU]
Alright, I'm ready.
Please body, hold together.
[GOKU grunting]
[VEGETA]
Hm?
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU]
Triple Kaioh Ken!
[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA grunting, groaning]
[VEGETA]
Even though I was stronger,
some inexplicable force
seemed to be guiding you.
You were taking huge
gambles with your energy
and they were paying off.
I couldn't take it anymore!
Live or die, I was willing
to do anything to destroy you!
[VEGETA cackling]
[VEGETA] Say goodbye to
your planet, Kakarot!
I... I don't have any choice!
[GOKU]
It's now or never!
Triple Kaioh Ken!
Now!
Kamehameha!
Ka... Me...
[VEGETA yelling]
Ha...
Me...
Let's see what
you've got, Kakarot!
Gallic Gun, fire!
Ha!
[VEGETA] It can't be! His beam
is as strong as my Gallic Gun!
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU yelling]
Aaaahh! No!
[VEGETA yelling]
[GOKU panting]
[VEGETA groaning]
I am Vegeta! The strongest
warrior in the Universe!
This can't be happening!
[KRILLIN]
Not so fast, Saiyan!
You! No! When is
this going to end?
[KRILLIN]
Right now!
[KRILLIN yelling]
[GOKU]
Krillin! No!
[KRILLIN]
Goku? Is that you?
Yes Krillin,
listen to me, please!
Don't be like him...
Show him mercy.
I beg you.
But Goku. He's done
nothing but hurt.
[GOKU] I-I know, but
I too, am a Saiyan.
I was just like Vegeta
when I first came here.
And it wasn't hate that
changed me, Krillin.
It was love.
[GOKU] He's the last
of my kind, Krillin.
Please, let him go.
I'll acquire the strength
that I'll need to beat
him if he returns.
I promise. I'll take
full responsibility.
[VEGETA] You let me go.
I couldn't believe it.
I thought it was the act
of a sentimental fool.
But later I realized
that being spared by you
was worse than
dying, Kakarot,
because now I couldn't
get you out of my mind!
I had to live with you
every second of the day!
That one act challenged
everything I'd
ever believed in,
everything that
I'd ever known!
You were unraveling my
reality from the inside out!
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU]
Oh, no!
What's your problem?
He was no threat to you anymore!
He couldn't even
defend himself!
There's no honor in that!
[VEGETA gasps]
You're going to have to get over
your soft heartedness, Kakarot!
Do it! Forget about
your feelings!
You have to!
They'll get you killed!
They'll get you killed, Kakarot!
Please. No more.
[GOKU]
Save your strength.
[VEGETA]
Kakarot! Destroy Frieza!
He made me what I am!
Don't let him do
it to anyone else!
Whatever it takes!
Stop him! Please!
[KRILLIN yells]
Frieza, stop this!
Help me!!
[VEGETA] I begged you to
forget about your feelings!
I thought they
would get you killed!
But it was your feelings
that helped you transform!
[GOKU yelling]
[VEGETA] It was the rage
you felt when Frieza
hurt your loved ones that
pushed you over the top!
Listen Kakarot!
Just because we've agreed
to fight together this time
doesn't mean that anything
has changed between us!
Do you understand me?
Once this mess is over, it'll
be you and me, head to head!
Sure.
[VEGETA] And now you're making
light of me again, aren't you?!
How dare you!
[BULMA] Just leave
everything to me, Vegeta!
[VEGETA] I changed
because of you, Kakarot.
You showed me that
ruthlessness wasn't the key
to acquiring power.
I tried to be good like you,
but the Saiyan
in me would not die!
I wanted my old edge back,
my killer instinct!
[GOKU]
Vegeta!
You'll fight with me, Kakarot!
Unless, of course,
you'd like more bodies to
pile up on your conscience!
Please, Vegeta! Tell me
you wouldn't do that.
How sad. I didn't think you were
weak enough to be controlled.
[GOKU gasps]
Tell me! Tell me what has more
meaning than your own strength!
[VEGETA] I have the blood
of a Saiyan Prince in me!
He is nothing but a joke!
Yet I had to watch him
surpass me in strength!
My destiny thrown
to the wayside!
He's, he's even saved my life as
though I were a helpless child!
He has stolen my honor...
...and I want it back!
[GOKU] Babidi! Transport us
to a place away from people!
If you give me that,
then I'll fight Vegeta!
Papararapa!
[GOKU]
The more time we spend fighting,
the more energy will
go to fuel Majin Buu!
So if it's alright with you,
let's just skip the warm-up!
Have it your way!
I'll go straight to
the part where I kill you
if that's what you want.
[VEGETA yelling]
It's quite a shame. I considered
you my friend, Vegeta.
Wake up! This is it!
Our destiny!
[BOTH grunting]
[VEGETA panting]
I'm amazed, Vegeta.
These last seven
years in Other World
I've been through the most
intense training sessions ever.
But we're still
completely even.
I guess this whole time
you've been pushing yourself
even harder than I have!
[VEGETA]
That may be true.
I've pushed myself to the
edge of my limits and beyond.
But you were born with a natural
talent far beyond my own.
No amount of training could
have closed the gap between us.
[VEGETA]
I realize that now.
It was made painfully
obvious to me today
as I watched your fight
with Babidi's monster!
I finally grasped
the undeniable truth
that no matter
how hard I tried,
I would never be
able to catch you!
That I was destined to live
forever in the shadow
of a low level clown!
So that's when I
secretly made up my mind.
You mean you, please no!
You deliberately let yourself
fall under Babidi's spell!
I'd say the end more
than justifies the means!
Vegeta, I don't understand!
You've never allowed anyone
to help you before in your life!
Why start now?! Why Babidi?!
[VEGETA] Because I wanted him to
reawaken the evil in my heart!
I wanted him to return me
to the way I was before!
I was the perfect warrior!
Cold and ruthless!
I lived by my strength alone!
Uninhibited by foolish emotion!
But slowly,
over the years...
...I became one of you!
My quest for greatness
gradually giving way
to this life of mediocrity!
[VEGETA] I awoke one day to find
that I had settled down
and formed a family.
I had even grown
quite fond of them.
Would you believe that I almost
started to think the Earth
was a nice place to live.
Do you understand
now, Kakarot?
That's why I needed Babidi!
To set me free!
By releasing the
evil in my heart!
He has freed me of
my petty attachments!
And I must say it
feels pretty good!
Do you really believe
what you're saying?
I thought I believed. Yes.
But you were right, Kakarot.
[VEGETA] Suddenly I was up
against insurmountable odds!
Death was immanent but I
didn't care about myself,
I could think only of my son!
I decided to shed my
mortal coil in an attack
that would rid the Earth
of that monster for good,
so that my son could live on.
But even my sacrifice failed!
And, once again, it was you
who had to come to the rescue!
And as a Super Saiyan 3 no less!
A level that I didn't
even dream was possible!
The greatest battle that was
ever waged was taking place...
...and I was reduced
to being its witness!
[VEGETA]
Is that my lot in life?
To bear witness
to your strength?
To be the only one strong
enough to be able to fathom
the depth of your might?
I refuse to play that role!
Aren't you the busy woman?
[BULMA] Come check it out!
It's a Blutz Wave generator!
[VEGETA] Blutz Wave
generator? What's it for?
[BULMA]
It's for you, silly!
To help you transform
to Super Saiyan 4!
What?
Are you serious?
This device can help me
become a Super Saiyan 4?
Now you know I wouldn't kid
you about something like that!
It's still just a theory,
but I think it'll work!
We learned quite a bit about
Blutz Waves on Planet Tuffle
and I just happen to
have a copy of the files!
[VEGETA] Whoa! I don't want
to be reminded of that face!
[BULMA]
I've had better days.
Okay, this should be
Goku's transformation.
[BULMA]
Wow! Look at him!
[VEGETA]
Kakarot, always showing off.
[BULMA] This initial
transformation was triggered
by the Moon's Blutz Waves
reflecting off the Earth,
but Goku just became
a wild beast.
He was out of control.
It was Pan who helped him
remember who he was!
Grandpa,
you wouldn't hurt me, would you?
[BULMA] Once Goku became fully
conscious of himself again,
it sparked this transformation.
Of course, he was also
still absorbing Blutz Waves.
[VEGETA]
That's it! Super Saiyan 4!
Now, here's the thing!
[BULMA] Since you're already
fully conscious of who you are
when you become a giant ape,
you should be able to
go Super Saiyan 4
if we flood your body with
enough Blutz Waves!
I don't know.
Don't you remember?
I did transform into a
giant ape on Planet Tuffle,
and I was exposed to Blutz
Waves, but nothing happened.
Yeah, I have that
file right here,
and it's true, you didn't
turn into Super Saiyan 4.
[BULMA]
But the part that confuses me
is that you're both Saiyans.
So if Goku did it, you should
have been able to do it, too.
There must have
been some condition
that was present for him,
that wasn't present for you.
Perhaps. Yes. It could
have been that Kakarot
was a pure blooded
Saiyan and I wasn't.
After all, I did have
that despicable creature
living inside my
body at the time!
Another variable was
your physical condition.
Your body might
not have been able
to withstand
the transformation.
[VEGETA]
Could that be the reason?
Was I simply not strong
enough to handle it?
But that was then,
and this is now!
I know you're ready! I can tell!
You've been training
like never before!
Okay, now we just need to get
the conditions right for you.
After that, you might
even reach Super Saiyan 5!
[VEGETA]
Super Saiyan 5? Are you serious?
You really believe that
I can surpass Kakarot?
You are the Prince of
all Saiyans, aren't you?
Yes I am!
So, Kakarot! The race
isn't over yet! Is it?
The day of the dark horse
is coming to an end!
The true thoroughbred
is making his move
to the front of the pack!
What about me? I think I
deserve a little recognition!
Well, if you're a Prince, that
makes me a Princess, right?
[NARRATOR] Can Bulma really help
Vegeta realize his dream
of surpassing Goku's strength?
Oblivious to anything
except the task at hand,
Goku prepares to
battle Nuova Shenron!
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next GT!