[GOKU yelling]
Grandpa!
[GOKU]
Something huge is on the way!
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball GT...
General Rilldo,
the strongest of the machine
mutants on planet M2,
stepped out from
the shadows and attacked!
The General froze Trunks
in a metallic slab
and sent him to a place far
worse than a battlefield.
You beast! You bring him
back here right now!
[PAN yells]
[PAN gasps]
[PAN] Oof!
[RILLDO] Your friend is
being transmitted to Dr. Myuu
where he will become
the doctor's newest guinea pig.
Consider it an honor.
So, where is this
Dr. Myuu hiding?
The tower behind me.
Trunks! Hold on! I'm coming!
Now, stand still!
[GOKU] Hiyah, hiyah, hiyah!
Yes. Do your worst, Saiyan!
[NARRATOR]
The battle raged on
between Goku and
the fierce General Rilldo.
But with each seemingly
successful attack from Goku,
the smoke would clear
and the General would be
left standing, unscathed.
[RILLDO growling]
[NARRATOR]
Trunks has fallen
into the hands of
the evil Dr. Myuu.
And General Rilldo
has transformed
into a new,
stronger Meta-Rilldo!
Is one Super Saiyan enough
to fight this battle?
Find out right now
on Dragon Ball GT!
[GOKU and RILLDO growling]
[GOKU and RILLDO panting]
[GOKU yells]
Hyper Meta-Rilldo Punch!
And here I was hoping
you were going to try
some different
fighting techniques.
Okay, that's different!
[RILLDO drill spinning]
[RILLDO laughing]
[explosion]
[GOKU gasps]
[zoom zoom]
[GOKU yells]
[RILLDO gasps]
[GOKU growls]
[zoom]
[RILLDO growls]
[explosions]
[wind blowing]
[machines humming]
That darn Giru!
When I find him, he's gonna
wish he was never manufactured!
Giru, Giru, Giru!
There you are!
Pan, danger... Pan, danger.
Now...
Giru, Giru, Giru...
[alarm beeping]
[INTERCOM] Warning Coersive
Removal System Activated.
Not again!
Wait!
Giru!
[RILLDO chuckles]
I've got to admit,
your strength has risen
more in your newer form
than I thought it was going to.
But I've matched you
blow-for-blow this far.
So, don't think that I
can't rise to the challenge.
[RILLDO laughs]
What an unexpected pleasure.
Quite interesting.
This, before me now,
is the Super Saiyan power
Dr. Myuu is seeking?
You can admire
my Saiyan Power later.
Right now it's time
for us to finish this!
[RILLDO chuckles]
[electricity charging]
[alarm beating]
[GOKU]
Uhh...
[alarm beeping faster]
Time for the big one. Ka...
Me...
Ha...
[power charging]
Ha!!
[GOKU yelps]
[RILLDO growls]
[PAN] Ow! I hate
that stupid wall!
It's like it's
alive or something!
[ALARM SYSTEM] Warning!
Warning! Warning! Warning!
[PAN] You sound
your annoying alarms,
but as long
as I can walk,
I'm gonna keep getting
back inside this place!
[alarm continues]
[ROBOTS] There she is.
Registered enemy. Processing...
You're in my way,
which is fine by me,
'cause I can't get enough
of beating up robots today!
[ROBOTS] Registering. Out
of the way. Does not compute.
[ROBOTS] Hold on! Attack!
Get her! Hold On.
Some robots just never learn,
do they!? Don't mess with Pan!
Yikes! Ow!
[ROBOT] I'm sorry.
Goodbye!
[PAN growls]
No, please, Miss Pan!
Wait a sec! You're the scientist
from the dump. You're alive!
I thought they were
going to dismantle you.
Miss Pan, that hurts!
Can you tell me
what's going on here?
First, I'm in the
room where Giru is,
then the walls
start moving around
and I'm back outside again!
The Space-Time Transmission
Machine on the top floor
runs all systems,
including Coercive Removal.
Space-Time Transmission?
Correct. It is the single
piece of equipment
connected to
Dr. Myuu's research.
But you mustn't go there.
That means it's got to be
the Space-Time Machine
that sent Trunks
to Dr Myuu's place.
I've got to find that machine!
But, it's dangerous.
Well, then, could you help me
find a way to the top floor
that won't get me
spit back outside
by those moving walls again?
You could try deactivating
the Coersive Removal System.
Well, duh.
But how do I do that?
You can figure it out, Miss Pan.
You're very smart.
Thank you, but why
don't you just tell me?
T-Tell you?
You know...
The deactivation method.
I don't know it.
Now I know why you
were in the trash heap.
[GOKU gasps]
[RILLDO laughs]
It seems you still cannot
fathom the extent of my power!
[GOKU gasps]
[RILLDO laughs]
[RILLDO growls]
No way!
[RILLDO] Have you put
it together yet, Saiyan?
The mighty Meta-Rilldo is
not just a superior fighter,
but a part of the
very planet itself.
That figures.
[RILLDO] I can manipulate all
the metal of planet M2 at will.
Everything you see here
exists as part of my body.
And I have every intention of
using it all to finish you off!
[GOKU yells]
I caught on to your control
of the metal on this planet
a long time ago.
I've fought enough guys
like you in my day
to know what's going on.
But I don't have the time
right now to deal with this,
so quit hiding
and get out here!
[DR. MYUU laughing maniacally]
[DR. MYUU]
A legendary Super-Saiyan
actually right here
in front of me!
This is one of the days that
makes life worth living!
[DR. MYUU laughs maniacally]
I'm quite excited, Trunks.
I can't wait to get
a good look at your data.
You see Trunks, it's your Super
Saiyan ferocity that I admire.
And I bet that ferocity
is boiling right now.
It's a good thing
we have you contained.
Soon, the time to release
your full Saiyan power
will be at hand.
General Rilldo
should be delivering
your two other Saiyan
friends any time now.
Registering...
There they are! Get them!
Go...
[PAN] What is wrong
with your dumb robots?!
Look how crowded
it is in here!
If you don't get off this
elevator right now--
Ouch, that hurts!
Stop it! Cut it out!
This is so annoying!
Get off me! Let go!
What's that smell?
Ouch!
Giru! You dirty traitor!
Get over here, I've got
a bone to pick with you!
I knew you had
some rotten wiring
the moment we found
you in the desert!
From the second you
swallowed the Dragon Radar,
you've been nothing
but bad luck!
All those times we had
to defend ourselves,
you never helped!
After all, you're the one who
said to come here. Didn't you?!
Wait!
You rescued us just so
you could bring us here!
You used yourself as bait!
All you ever wanted
was to put us in the hands
of that Dr. Myuu guy, right?
Giru.
Warning! Warning!
Giru!
Giru, you better be ready
for me when I get back!
Warning! Warning! Warning!
[PAN yelling]
This won't keep me out for long!
[electric shock]
Warning! Warning! Warning!
Miss Pan, I've deactivated
the removal system!
[PAN] You work pretty
well under pressure.
Ya' know ya' could've
done that earlier.
The chase ends here,
double-crosser.
So why don't you just give
us back the Dragon Balls?
Without them there's no way
to stop the earth
from being destroyed.
Giru, Giru. Giru not know,
Danger, danger! Giru, Giru...
You know the emergency
removal system
has been deactivated,
don't you?
Giru, Giru, Giru!
Giru know nothing!
That's okay. 'Cause I gotcha!
Giru!
No you don't! You're not
getting away this time!
[PAN growls]
Then I'll use a Kamehameha Wave!
Giru, you have so
picked the wrong day
to try and mess with me!
Okay, you asked for it. Ka...
Me...
Ha...
[ALARM] Initiate
Backup Removal System!
[PAN]
Huh? What?
I thought we stopped this!
[PAN yells]
Pan.
I wish I was back
at home right now.
Having homework is better
than dealing with this.
That looks like a Dragon Ball!
It is a Dragon Ball!
[PAN cheers]
And I found it!
Or did it find me?
Gotcha!
[RILLDO chuckles]
See you in the next
life, Super Saiyan!
[GOKU growls]
You've got abilities,
but you don't know
how to use them right.
If I were judging you off
appearance, I'd call you a liar.
And it seems that
you've already forgotten
the most important
point of all.
You can fight me all you want,
but until you rid this planet
of all the metal covering it,
I will always have a body
to bring to the battle.
Now, if you don't know, this
is the part where you concede
and make the smart
decision to hand yourself
and the other Saiyan
over to Dr. Myuu.
[NARRATOR] General Rilldo
divulged the secret
of his awesome power, making
him even closer to invincible.
Can Goku find
some way to destroy
all of the metal on the planet?
And with the three Dragon Balls
that mysteriously
appeared next to her,
will Pan find
a way to save Trunks
from the clutches of
the sinister Dr. Myuu?
All these questions and
more will be answered
in the next action-packed
episode of Dragon Ball GT!