It's Giru's home!
[GIRU]
Giru born on that planet.
[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragonball GT...
Emperor Pilaf used the power
of the Black Star Dragonballs
to transform Goku
back to childhood size.
With Trunks and Pan
along for the ride,
Goku blasted off into the
far reaches of the galaxy
tracking the Dragon Balls
with the handy Dragon Radar.
But the Saiyans
were left speechless
when the radar was consumed
by a bizarre little robot who
seemed to be at death's door.
Giru convinces his new friends
to stop by his homeworld,
the incredible
machine planet, M2.
But the Saiyans found
themselves surrounded
by thousands of robots
and dead in the sights
of the Sigma Force,
who revealed Giru's treachery.
[NEZI] And, we are the least
of your problems.
So I was right about you.
I don't think for a second that
you guys are telling the truth!
[NEZI]
Now Bizu.
[NARRATOR] The Sigma Force
quickly captured Goku and Trunks
with an order to transmit
their bodies to Dr. Myuu,
who desires their Saiyan powers
for his twisted experiments.
[GIRU] Giru, the other
two important, Giru.
Giru! What are you saying?!
[GIRU] General be happy
about Dragon Ball.
Giru, you're one
of them?! Aughhh!
You've deceived us
all along! You traitor!
I really thought you
were my friend, Giru!
[NARRATOR] With Giru's
deception in the open,
Pan realized
the terrible truth,
that she is alone
on a strange world
and that the lives of Goku
and Trunks rest in her hands!
[GOKU snoring]
[RILLDO] Look at them. Sleeping
like helpless, little babies.
It's hard to believe
they're as powerful
as Doctor Myuu says they are!
[RILLDO growling]
[RILLDO] All right!
Take these two specimens
to the laboratory for testing!
[ROBOTS]
Yes, Sir!
[PAN] This place is huge, but
there's not a soul around!
How creepy!
[PAN] Huh?
[ROBOT A] We are to report
[ROBOT A]
for mainframe duty!
[ROBOT B]
Roger that!
[PAN groaning]
[ROBOT A] Is there another
glitch in the system?
[ROBOT B]
Affirmative!
[PAN] Oh Brother!
I can't take this anymore!
[ROBOT C]
Hey, wait for me!
I am falling.
Are you plant or animal?
I'm the end of
the road for you, Jack!
[punching]
[ROBOT C muffled]
Intruder! Intruder!
[PAN gasps]
[PAN]
What am I going to do?
They'll spot me for sure
if I go down there!
I'll never find Grandpa
and Trunks at this rate!
[PAN gasps]
[clanging]
Yikes! Aaaah!
[ROBOT] What's the big idea? Who
did that? Why isn't anyone here?
This situation doesn't compute!
Why me? Ow! My head!
I want to go home!
[PAN]
That did not tickle! Aaaah!
Grandpa? Trunks? Anyone?
[PAN] Well, it's not
my style! But it'll do!
[PAN] Awesome! They really
think I'm one of them!
[ROBOT D] Greetings!
[PAN monotone] What's up?
[ROBOT E] Greetings!
[PAN monotone] Howdy!
[PAN giggling]
[PAN] Well, I'd love to get
to know you guys better,
but I've gotta boogie!
[ROBOTS]
Hail, General Rilldo!
[PAN] I guess he's the big
cheese around here!
Approach T-20-O-6!
[PAN gasps]
[RILLDO]
As you know,
T-20-O-6 has acquired
three Dragon Balls
as well as some valuable
specimens for experimentation!
I hold in my hand
something very special!
To laud his meritorious deeds,
I am awarding T-20-O-6
the Medal of Honor!
[ROBOTS clamoring]
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
[PAN] If I ever get my hands
on that little, lying twirp,
I'll make a toilet
seat out of him!
[GIRU] Long live Doctor Myuu!
Long live General Rilldo!
[ROBOTS] Long live Doctor Myuu!
[PAN]
How could I have been so stupid?
It was their plan to
lure us here all along!
They must have been tracking us
ever since we picked up Giru!
And I talked Trunks
into coming here!
What a fool I am!
What have I done?
[ROBOT] Hey, you! What are
you doing there?
Change the guard! What are
you waiting for? Quickly!
[PAN]
M-me?
[ROBOT]
Affirmative!
[SCI-BOT A]
You never know
what you're going to
see next in here!
[SCI-BOT B] Yes! Organic life
forms are infinitely peculiar!
[SCI-BOT A] They must be
some kind of primates!
[SCI-BOT B]
Agreed!
[SCI-BOT C] Initiating
Energy Configuration Scan!
[SCI-BOT B]
Proceeding with specimen one!
[SCI-BOT A]
Scan complete!
Running Power
Analysis Diagnostic!
[SCI-BOT C]
Proceeding with specimen two!
[SCI-BOT A]
Scan complete!
Running Power
Analysis Diagnostic!
Impossible!
This does not compute!
[GIRU munching]
Thanks to you,
all of our dreams
are that much closer
to becoming a reality!
Soon all life forms will
be robot mutants! Just like us!
[SCI-BOT A]
Excuse me, General!
[RILLDO]
What is it?
[SCI-BOT A]
Take a look, Sir!
Huh? What's this? How much
power does this boy have?
No! There must be
some mistake! This can't be!
His power levels
are off the charts!
[SCI-BOT A] That is correct,
sir!  There is no mistake!
Great mega-bots!
How can a little body like that
harbor such enormous power?
This is something we've
never encountered before!
Not even our
Mega-Cannon Sigma Force
is equipped to handle a
power of this magnitude!
If it were me, I'd
terminate them right now!
But no! Doctor Myuu's
orders are to keep them alive!
[GIRU]
General Rilldo!
I have stored and analyzed
all of Goku's fighting data.
I believe he can
be beaten, Sir!
Giru! Giru! Giru!
[RILLDO cackling]
You are useful
beyond words, my friend!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
[SCI-BOT B]
Download 90% complete!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
Giru!
[SCI-BOT A] Goku's fighting data
download is now complete!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru!
[SCI-BOT A] Commencing transfer
of Trunks Fighting Data
and Pan Fighting Data Files!
[RILLDO cackling]
Mmm! With this the Sigma Force
will be able to anticipate
their every move!
[GOKU heavy breathing]
[PAN]
I need to ditch these guys!
Where's he taking us?
[PAN gasps]
Oh, no!
[ROBOT F]
Error! Never stop! Never stop!
[PAN] What am I going to do?
I can't walk through walls!
[ROBOT F] You are impeding
forward progress!
This behavior does not compute!
[ROBOT F] Never stop.
[ROBOT G] Instruction: Speed up.
[ROBOT F]
Must progress forward.
[PAN]
Ohh! All right! Here goes!
[ROBOTS]
Defective unit...!
[PAN whimpering]
Where are you taking me?
[PAN] We can't all be
perfect, you know!
Come on, guys!
I can learn! I promise!
I was just having an off day!
[PAN yelling]
Thanks a lot, you bums!
Great! Now where am I?
[SMALL ROBOT] Where am I? Who
am I? Where am I? Who am I...?
[SCHOLAR-BOT]
I can't tell you who you are,
but I can tell you
where you are!
[PAN]
Where am I?
[SCHOLAR-BOT] You are
right here, in robot hell,
with all of the other
defective mutants
that didn't fit into
Doctor Myuu's dream!
We are the outcasts!
[PAN]
Just because you're not perfect?
[SCHOLAR-BOT] Yes, but that's
how this empire was founded.
The original inhabitants
of this planet
were not acceptable
to Doctor Myuu.
He believed that they were
worthless and inefficient.
So one day he ordered his robot
commandos to destroy them all.
In no time, Doctor Myuu's
empire was built!
It is so complex that
efficiency is vital!
Defective Units
can not be tolerated!
Can not be tolerated! Can not
be tolerated! Can not be--
[PAN]
Hey!
[SCHOLAR-BOT]
Goodness! Where was I?
[PAN] You were talking
about Doctor Myuu,
but then you got stuck
saying the same thing!
[SCHOLAR-BOT] Alas! Yes! That's
why I'm here! That's my defect!
[PAN]
But it's so small!
It's nothing that a little
shake won't fix...
[SCHOLAR-BOT] Why thank you.
That's very kind of you to say.
I'd tell you where
your friends are,
but I'm afraid it
won't do any good!
[PAN] You mean you
know where they are?
[SCHOLAR-BOT]
On the second floor!
In the laboratory where all
of the specimens go for testing!
[PAN] Oh, thank you!
Thank you so much!
[SCHOLAR-BOT]
You're welcome!
But I'm afraid
that it's too late!
[PAN]
Too late?
[SCHOLAR-BOT] I'm afraid so!
Listen! It's started!
It was nice knowing you!
I'm sorry that you had
to get thrown down here!
[PAN] What do you mean? We can't
just sit here and get crushed!
Get off your can!
We're getting out of here!
[alarm blaring]
[SCHOLAR-BOT] Bless you!
You saved our lives, miss!
You got it!
[COMPUTER] Intruder alert!
Intruder alert!
Onscreen! Right away!
[RILLDO] Mmm! That rat needs
to be put in a cage!
[SCI-BOT A] Download is
complete, Sigma Force!
Pan is on Level Two!
I want her alive!
[SIGMA FORCE]
Yes, Sir!
[NAT] Comander Nezi!
Please, leave it to me, Sir!
One of us should be sufficient
to trap a common
animal like her!
[NEZI]
Very well, Nat! Do it!
There it is!
[PAN yelping]
[NAT cackling] You're
outclassed, little girl!
Take my advice and surrender!
Never!
[PAN grunting]
[NAT laughing]
[PAN growling]
[NAT]
It's useless, you fool!
Over here, Pal!
[NAT] The hand is quicker
than the eye!
[PAN yelps]
You! Trash compactor!
[NAT cackling] That was a sneaky
little trick that you tried!
I guess you're wondering
how I knew exactly what
you were going to do next?
Well, you can thank the
one you call Giru for that!
He recorded all of your fights
and stored them in his files!
It's all been downloaded
into my memory banks!
[NAT cackling] I know every
move that you make!
Oh, no!
[PAN] Giru! How could you?
I trusted you!
[NAT cackling]
Why did you do it?
I was your friend!
[NAT]
What? Error! Error!
[PAN yelling]
[NAT] This does not compute!
Where did this power come from?
There is no record
of this in the files!
Yeah, I know why!
Giru never saw
me that mad! Hmm!
Giru! How 'bout this?
Do you like these?
Don't be silly! He's a robot!
He can't, taste things!
[TRUNKS]
Robots can do anything!
As long as they've been
programmed to do that thing!
[PAN]
What? Give me a break!
[NEZI] Dopes! They think
they're superior to robots!
And yet they can't
tell that T-20-O-6
has been deceiving
them the whole time!
[PAN]
Well, you think you know
everything thing
about robots, huh?
Mister Capsule Corp Executive!
[TRUNKS]
Well, we do make
the most sophisticated
robots in existence!
[SIGMA FORCE laughing]
Giru! Our first Dragon Ball!
And you led us right to it!
[NEZI] Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Of course he did, you fool!
Using you ignorant humans to
help him gather the Dragon Ball
was his plan all along!
[GOKU]
Is that so?
Well he just lost
some good friends!
And as for you three,
you're heading straight
for the scrap yard!
[NEZI] Somebody shut
his insolent mouth!
[GOKU groaning]
[NEZI] That will teach
you the proper respect!
[GOKU] Trunks believed in him!
They were friends! And Pan, too!
They both truly liked Giru,
and Giru truly liked them!
I don't understand!
[NEZI]
Heh, heh, heh! Sentimental fool!
T-20-O-6 isn't even capable
of such silly affection!
Friendship! Trust!
What can these things
mean to a mutant robot
strictly programmed
to do his duty?
[SCI-BOT A]
Danger! Energy waves!
[PAN]
All right! Where's my Grandpa?!
[NEZI]
How did you find this lab, girl?
[PAN] You defective
robots are easy to find!
Pan! Look out!
[PAN yelps]
Pan!
[GOKU grunting, yelling]
[NEZI]
Huh?
I won't let you do this! I won't
let you hurt my friends anymore!
[GOKU]
It all ends right here!
[NARRATOR] Heart afire,
Goku has laid down the law!
But does his boyhood
body have enough power
to topple General
Rilldo's Sigma Force?
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next GT!