[NARRATR]
On the last Dragon Ball GT,
a routine space flight
turned into a harrowing
quest for survival.
The loss of a small
part during take-off
led to a much bigger problem.
[BULMA]
A perfect match! Finally!
And the mystery part is...
[screams]
No! Of all the parts,
why that one?!
[NARRATOR] Without the use of
the missing stabilizer jet,
the ship was doomed to
break apart during flight.
Attempting to crash-land
was the only option.
[TRUNKS] We'll make
an emergency landing.
[NARRATOR]
Disaster was averted,
but being visitors on Imecka
posed its own problems.
The money-hungry merchants
were determined
to take the Earthlings
for everything they had.
I'll just charge it
to your account.
[NARRATOR] Victimized by
a greedy ruler,
the locals can't even afford
to keep a roof over their heads.
But Pan, Trunks, and Goku
had their own worries.
[GIRU] Giru! Giru!
Giru! Giru!
[NARRATOR] And when they came
across a hungry little robot,
they had even more.
Without that radar our
whole mission is history!
There goes our ship.
[NARRATOR] Avoiding the locals'
problems was the plan,
but by a twist of fate,
Goku, Pan, and Trunks
were being drawn
--into the heart of Imecka!
--Hey! Come back here with that!
[TRUNKS]
Well, there she goes.
[GIRU]
Giru.
Man, what else could go wrong?
We can't just stand
here, that's our ship.
If we don't get it back
we'll be stranded.
Yeah. Right.
No sweat.
I'll get us there in a flash.
Huh?
Oh, I get it.
Instant Transmission! Right?
[PAN] And just where
do you think you're going?
Not so fast there!
Until we figure out how
to extract our radar,
you're part of the family!
So get used to
hanging out, buddy-boy!
[PAN] This is just a precaution.
A little insurance policy.
[GIRU]
Stop. Tickles.
There! That ought to keep
you from running off again,
you little sneak!
[GIRU]
Giru!
Entering maximum security.
Here! You hold him, Trunks!
Gee, Pan... thanks a lot.
That dumb robot has wasted
enough of our time.
Let's go get our ship!
Whatd'ya say, Grandpa?
All right. Just grab on
when you're ready, guys!
Here goes!
Ooh!
[screaming]
Are we there yet?
Wait a second! I recognize
that rock formation!
We're in the same spot as
before, you knuckle head!
Yeah, I thought it looked
familiar. How strange!
I've never had any
problems in the past.
Huh. Weird. What now?
Well, I'd like to
give it one more shot!
[GOKU] All right!
Here goes!
Hold on!
[whimpers]
We went a little further.
[PAN] Grandpa, if I live, please
remind me to kill you!
[screaming]
[painful bounce]
[thud]
I don't understand. I'm doing
it the same as I always have.
Yes, that may be so. But your
body's different! Remember?
You've never done Instant
Transmission as a child before!
It might not work!
Well, whatever it is, you're not
using me as a guinea pig again!
So let's go get our ship...
the old fashioned way!
[ATTENDANT]
Your mid-day meal, my Lord!
If it pleases you, Sire!
Yes, it's fine.
My compliments to the chef.
[LEZICK]
Your scouts have returned.
[DON KEE] Yes.
What is it, Gale?
[GAIL]
Aye, Lord!
That spaceship that was found
in the desert-- we've got it!
It's all yours now!
Finders keepers!
[DON KEE]
Show me.
[DON KEE] Sheila,
what's your evaluation?
[SHEILA] Lord, whoever designed
it had function in mind,
but not fashion!
It may work well, but as you
can see, it's an eyesore!
It's not going to
fetch anywhere near
what the sleeker models are
getting in the marketplace.
In a word, it's ugly.
Well, then what good is it?
There's no rare treasure inside,
no crew members for slaves!
So, why have you brought
me this ridiculous ship?!
Sire, you're the one with the
good taste; I'm just a grunt.
Only a refined person like you
can truly know if a thing
has any value or not.
You're not as stupid
as you look, Gale!
Now tear that ship apart
and sell it as scrap!
[DON KEE] That's my word!
Make it happen!
[PAN] Are you crazy?
We aren't sightseeing!
We're supposed to
be avoiding the lights!
[GOKU] I was
trying to see the ship!
This is the Royal Palace.
I thought the guys that
stole our spaceship
were like poachers
or merchants.
Maybe it's not really here.
Maybe there's been some mistake.
[TRUNKS]
No, the tracks don't lie.
They led us right to the gate.
Then our ship
must be down there.
[PAN] Well, the evidence
definitely points to it,
but what would a wealthy
king want with our ship?
He might want to sell it.
It's a pretty nice ship.
I mean it was designed
by Capsule Corp.
I'm sure it would go
for a good price.
We're talking about a
man who has everything.
Why would someone with all that
money care about our ship?
I'm a CEO back home, Pan.
I've seen two millionaires fight
over one Zeni on the floor.
Well, if it's here,
it's gonna be hard to
find without being seen.
I've already found
the ship, silly.
Grandpa, please!
Wait! What?!
Yeah, it's right there.
Hmm?!
[TRUNKS] I'll be darned.
There it is.
You weren't kidding, Goku.
It was right under our
noses the whole time!
Thanks a lot, Grandpa! You
could have told us, you know!
What a jerk!
But I tried.
You weren't listening.
Whatever. Next time the joke's
on you. Now, let's go get it.
[GUARD] Did you see that
outfit Sheila had on?
[GUARD WITH DRINK] Yeah! But I
wouldn't say that too loud.
Gale might hear you.
He gets jealous.
Huh?
[TRUNKS]
There she is!
And I bet we're not gonna get
her back without a fight.
Um... So, should
we go in head on?
Huh? This is a stealth
operation, you numb skull!
There are thousands of
armed guards in this palace!
We don't want them all swarming
around us like bees, do we?
No, I guess not.
If we have to blow our cover
to get out then we'll do it!
But only as a last resort!
Okay? Now, let's go!
[groans]
Sshhh!
Yeah! I forgot!
[GUARD] Yeah, so I got extended
leave comin' up in a few days.
I can't wait to
get out of this dump!
[ARMED GUARD] So check out this
new Vetron 2000, man.
This thing weighs
more than I do,
you know what
I'm talkin' about?
Ready!
[GUARD WITH DRINK]
What a day, huh?
[metallic clanking]
[whimpering]
[screams]
Hmm?
[muffled noises]
[deep exhale]
[loud thump]
[crash]
--Huh?
--Intruders, men!
Hangar B! Sound the alarm!
Busted! Now what?!
[GUARD] Over here! We've got 'em
cornered! Ready! Aim! Fire!
[gunfire]
Now what?
I say we kick their rear-ends
and take our ship back!
What? I thought you said
we were trying to avoid
a big confrontation!
It's too late!
That was then and this is now!
We tried to get the honey
without disturbing the hive,
but it didn't work!
I think we're on the same page
now. But where's the honey?!
It was just an expression!
The ship's the honey!
Now let's get it!
[COMMANDER]
Hold your line, men!
They've broken through
the perimeter! Get her!
Grandpa, help! Up there!
Got it!
[crash}
All right!
Get out, or you're dead.
[giggles]
[GUARD]
You heard me, get out!
[GUARD] Hey! What are
you doing? Stop! No!!
What's going on?
We've got three intruders
trying to steal the ship
that you just brought in.
How dare they!
Unlicensed driver
coming through!
[PAN] Hey!
Earthlings ride for free!
We're on, Pan!
[PAN]
You can do this, Pan!
[TRUNKS] Whoa! She almost
took our heads off!
Hasn't she ever driven before?!
Well, no, come to think of it!
Joy ride's over!
[battlecry]
[GAIL]
No way!
[explosion]
[LEZICK]
They're... Saiyans!
[GUARD]
Close the gate!
[loud collision]
[electric buzzing]
[thumping]
Well, I guess they're
not coming after us.
Now, it's time to fix our ship
and kiss this crazy
planet good-bye!
[TRUNKS]
I don't know about that, Pan!
We might have to turn you in
for wreckless endangerment.
This is the thanks
I get for saving the day?
[groans]
[laughing]
[DON KEE] Well, what
a beautiful, happy ending!
But for who? For me?
No! The great Don Kee is
left looking like an idiot
while they ride off
with my ship!
And all of this happens
right under the noses
of my most highly paid
military experts!
What a bunch of useless twits!
[LEZICK]
I resent that.
No! Not you, Lezick
You're impeccable!
It's these other twits
I'm talking about!
We made a big mess
out of this! I admit it, Sir!
[DON KEE]
Take a look at this number!
This is the number of Gametz
that I'm docking your pay
for the damages to and
the loss of one hover craft!
[DON KEE] Do you even know
who the thieves are?
Yes, of course, Lord Kee!
We've got the whole
thing on tape!
[DON KEE] You've got to be
kidding me! Bandanas!
Ratty clothes! They look
like hired hands!
Well, at least
this one knows how
to make a statement
with his hair. Interesting.
I want their heads
on a platter!
All right!
Some breakfast! I'm starv--
[buzzing]
Hey!
[PAN] Is this going to take
all day, Trunks, or what?
I'm ready to go!
Sorry, your highness!
But your great escape caused
some additional damage!
[PAN] Well, I got us
out of there, didn't I?
Hey, if I'm that good
of a driver now,
just wait 'til I'm
actually old enough!
[GOKU] With a positive
attitude like that,
things will sure go quicker.
Sorry... Did I hear something?
[TRUNKS]
That was the voice of wisdom
from your ten-year
old grandfather!
[PAN] Ten? You think he's ten?
That's ridiculous!
[GOKU]
Well, how old do I look?
I don't know... Three or four.
I hate to interrupt,
but I'm ready to go to
town to get our parts.
[MERCHANT]
One more, no? Perfect!
That will be four
hundred Gametz!
Be careful, Trunks.
We don't want them to
push something on us
that we don't need!
Right.
Don't worry, I think I've got
the hang of this place now
after our first fiasco.
[PAN]
Hey, do you sell parts?
Of course!
[hysterical scream]
[locals chatter]
[scream]
What's wrong with them?
Well, I don't want to hurt
anybody's feelings, you guys,
but it seemed to me like they
were all terrified of Pan.
Now why would
they be scared of me?!
[TRUNKS] Oh, great! Goku!
Pan! Get a load of this!
What? Why are we up there?!
[TRUNKS] I guess were some of
Imecka's most wanted criminals.
[PAN] Criminals?! That's absurd!
We haven't done anything wrong!
[TRUNKS] Well, I'm sure it has
something to do with
us taking our ship
from the palace.
[PAN] But they stole it
from us first!
We just took what
was rightfully ours!
This is ridiculous!
And look at this picture!
It doesn't look
anything like me!
[distant sirens]
[CHIEF]
Over there, men!
What should we do?
I say we get out of here.
If we beat up
a bunch of police,
then we'll really
look like criminals.
[CHIEF]
Faster, men!
It seems like
nothing is going right.
I'm starting to wonder
about this mission.
Once again, we're out
in the cold and rain
and our ship is still broken.
[TRUNKS] Well, let's try
not to lose faith.
Everything happens
for a reason.
Would you rather
go back to the ship?
Then we'd just have to walk
all the way back here
again to get the parts.
Mmm. I'm really hungry.
What else is new?
Come to think of it, we haven't
eaten since yesterday, have we?
[GIRU] Giru! Giru Giru!
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru...!
What an annoying robot! I tied
everything up except his mouth!
[GIRU]
Giru.
Easy! I think he's trying
to tell us something!
[beeping]
[TRUNKS] Guys, we better get a
move on! We've got company!
Huh?
Just follow me! Come on!
[siren]
[crash]
[CHIEF]
Atteeeeeention!
Step back!
[NARRATOR] Marooned on a strange
world, without food or shelter!
Can the most wanted
criminals on Imecka
keep from being discovered?
Find out on the next
Dragon Ball GT!
Come out now!
We have you surrounded!