[GOKU]
This is for Krillin!
[GOKU yelling]
Super Dragon Fist!
[NARRATOR]
Last time on GT...
Super Android 17
was finally beaten,
but the Earth was left in
a state of instability.
Natural disasters were wreaking
havoc across the globe
and it was decided that only
a wish to the Eternal Dragon
could restore the
planet's natural harmony.
But when the first
Dragon Ball was found,
an unnerving discovery was made.
[PAN]
Oh, no! Grandpa! Trunks!
You're not gonna
believe this! Look!
[NARRATOR] The Dragon Balls were
cracked-- a bad omen indeed.
But it was hoped that the
wish to restore the Earth
to its normal state would
mend the balls as well.
[GOKU]
Okay! Arise, Shenron!
[GOKU] Gosh. The sky isn't
changing at all. Is it?
[PAN]
What's happening?
[TRUNKS] I don't know, but
I think we made a mistake!
Whoa! I'm sensing
an enormous power!
[GOKU]
It's evil, whatever it is!
[NARRATOR]
A black cloud of smoke
spewed from the Dragon Balls,
and took on the form of
a mysterious new dragon.
[PAN]
That's not, Shenron!
[NARRATOR] What dark curse has
been let loose upon the Earth?
Wait! What's going on?
Where's Shenron?
Well, he came out of the
Dragon Balls. Didn't he?
[PAN] Maybe he's
filling in for Shenron.
Like maybe Shenron's
on vacation!
[GOKU]
It's possible.
Hey! Did you come
to grant our wishes?
Oh yeah. I came here
to grant your wishes!
I don't know, you guys.
Something's fishy.
I don't trust this dragon.
Mom! Have a little respect!
He's an Eternal Dragon ya know!
The fresh outside air!
So delicious!
It's been far too long
since I've wielded my power!
The world is born anew!
Hey, this is not the way
that Eternal Dragons behave!
Well, at least not Shenron.
Look, dragon!
For your information,
you should be asking us
what we wanna wish for!
What?
Our wishes.
Wishes! I've no intention
of fulfilling any wishes!
[PAN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Goku! Beware of that
Dragon! Do you hear me?
Why? Isn't he nice?
[GOKU]
Uh oh!
[TRUNKS] Alright, you!
Where is Shenron?
[ALL coughing]
Hey! He's taking
the Dragon Balls!
[PAN yelping]
You just give those
back right now!
[ALL screaming]
[PAN]
The Dragon Balls! They're gone!
What are we going to do now?
[BLACK SMOKE DRAGON cackling]
[GOHAN]
That was... weird.
[VIDEL]
What just happened?
[BULMA] We were robbed!
That's what happened!
Huh? Look! In the sky!
[ALL gasp]
[PAN]
Isn't it magical?
Cool, huh?
[CHI CHI] I've never
seen anything like it!
It's absolutely beautiful!
I can't believe that
dragon did that!
Maybe he was good after all!
I'm afraid not. Not that
dragon, he was bad.
Yeah, I sensed it too, Dad.
There was something wrong.
[KING KAI]
Goku? Can you hear me?
King Kai! What in the
world's going on down here?
I don't know.
Idiots!
Who was that?
How obnoxious can you get?
[OLD KAI]
Didn't I warn you about using
the Dragon Balls so much?!
Didn't I tell you
that interfering
with the natural
evolution of things
could have serious
repercussions?
Well, didn't I?
Yes sir, I remember that.
But I just thought, well,
that it was because
you were old fashioned.
It's the generation gap.
Gap? Did you say gap?
It's a stinking
canyon, not a gap!
Now you listen here!
[OLD KAI] That creature and the
creatures that it spawned
are not only capable
of destroying the Earth,
but the entire Universe as well!
What? Him?
I know he's bad,
but is he that strong?
[OLD KAI] Yes, he's that
strong! Thanks to you people!
He was born because you
misused the Dragon Balls!
You couldn't even
tie your shoelaces
without calling the dragon!
Hey! You don't have to
keep yelling like that!
Hasn't your generation ever
heard of manners? I mean--
[OLD KAI]
How dare you!
If there's any one
person to blame
for this terrible situation,
that would be you, Bulma!
[BULMA] Me? And just how
did you arrive at that?!
You invented the Dragon Radar!
And you sought out
the Dragon Balls
for your own selfish purpose.
Does any of that ring a bell?!
Old Man! Why don't
you show yourself?!
Or are you too chicken?!
Is that it?! You spineless
old goat! Fight like a man!
Mom, settle down.
Really, it's okay.
Trust me, Mother.
You do not want to fight
with one of the Kais.
To think that one time
I almost let the fate
of the entire Universe
rest on a kiss from that woman!
[OLD KAI] What she needs is a
good old-fashioned spanking,
and if she doesn't watch it,
I'll come down and do it myself!
Hmm!
That won't be necessary.
Besides, Ancestor,
we need you to focus on
solving the problem at hand.
If I may then, sir.
Listen all of you, please.
[KIBITO] You all know that for
every Yin, there is a Yang.
So even though you
used the Dragon Balls
for positive things,
negative energy was
introduced into the world.
It was stored inside
the Dragon Balls.
I had no idea.
But it makes sense.
I don't get it.
What happens to
the negative energy?
Does it just stay in
the Dragon Balls?
Hmm. I guess it's
just like anything else.
They would hold as much
energy as they could,
then, one day, when they
exceeded their capacity,
they would burst.
[KIBITO]
That's exactly right.
They can only hold so much.
The negative energy does
dissipate over time,
but for every wish,
it takes about 100 years
for that to happen.
[KIBITO] In truth, the
Dragon Balls were never meant
to be used more than
once every 100 years.
This allows time for
the negative energy
to seep out harmlessly,
as it was intended to do.
But the balls were used
much more often than that.
[SHENRON]
Your wish has been granted!
[KIBITO] They couldn't
hold it any longer,
and all of the negative
energy was released at once,
in the form of this dragon.
And he is pure evil.
[PAN]
This is serious.
You don't know
how right you are, Pan.
[GOHAN]
Mister Popo!
[GOKU]
Dende!
Many years ago,
I heard of an evil dragon
appearing on the Planet Eros.
Shortly after, Eros and
every star and planet
in its galaxy were destroyed.
Unbelievable.
That's why the Dragon Balls
are scattered after every wish!
It's supposed to take
centuries to find them
so the negative energy
can't have time to accumulate.
[OLD KAI] But then someone
invented the Dragon Radar
and ruined everything!
Oh, so it's all
my fault, is that it?
Well, why don't you just say it?
There were those that were
aware of the dangers of overuse,
but no decision was ever made
to warn the people of the Earth.
Well, how in the world
was I supposed to know?
[BULMA] It's Dende's fault
if we were never warned!
So you see, it's
not all my fault!
We're all a little
to blame, actually!
[GOKU]
Hm?
[GOTEN]
Huh?
[BULMA]
Well, aren't we?
[TRUNKS nervous laughter]
[BULMA sighs]
Ha! I know!
Even though
I invented the radar,
I still wouldn't have been
able to find the Dragon Balls!
I was just a
little girl of 16,
trying to find her prince
with the Dragon Balls!
But that was just a
young schoolgirl's dream--
a silly fantasy!
But then this big
shot came along!
Who me? You mean it's my fault?
Well yeah!
[BULMA] I was just a
knobby-kneed adolescent
back then. I could never have
gathered the balls on my own.
You were the one
with super strength!
You're responsible for
gathering the Dragon Balls!
I guess I am.
I see what you mean, Bulma.
I am responsible.
I never really thought of
it that way until now.
[BULMA]
Hey, what are you doing?
Uh, yeah, Dad.
What's up? What gives?
[GOKU ]Well, since I'm the
one who caused this mess,
there's only one
thing for me to do.
I guess I just
don't have a choice.
It seems clear to me!
I have to go slay that dragon!
Just like that?
Aren't you worried?
How can you make light
of a situation like this?
So without any
thought or planning,
you're just going to jump in
there and sock it to him, huh?
[GOKU] Well, I'm going to
finish my warm-up first!
There, that oughta
do it! I'm ready!
[OLD KAI] I'm afraid you don't
have much time to act, Goku.
That dragon is attacking the
nerve centers of the globe.
The planet is already
beginning to suffocate
under the weight
of that beast's evil.
[OLD KAI]
If you don't intervene soon,
the destruction of the
Earth is inevitable!
[GOHAN] Wait a second,
Dad! I'm coming with you!
No! I'll handle this myself!
No, Dad!
Don't worry, Gohan. You saw
me as a Super Saiyan Four.
If that won't do it,
nothing will.
Yeah, but Dad!
Well, see ya later!
Wait! Don't go!
What's wrong, Pan?
Oh, never mind!
Forget it, Grandpa!
Everything's fine!
Okay! Bye, everyone!
Come home soon! I'll have
dinner waiting for you!
Do your best, Dad! Be careful!
Huh? Whoa! He sure
didn't waste any time!
With this trail he
won't be hard to find.
Not with a mess like this one.
[PEOPLE screaming]
[5-STAR DRAGON cackling]
[6-STAR DRAGON]
Ha, ha, ha...
[7-STAR DRAGON roaring]
[1-STAR DRAGON roaring]
[VILLAGE MAN]
I guess a big storm's moving in!
Or not.
[VILLAGE MAN]
What is that thing?!
[VILLAGE WOMAN 1]
It's horrible!
[BOTH screaming]
[VILLAGE MAN]
Get down!
[VILLAGERS yelping]
[VILLAGE WOMAN 2]
Someone help us!
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
How quaint! This is the
perfect little abode!
I doubt the town folk will
mind if I set up shop here!
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
[HAZE SHENRON]
Let it be known!
I am Haze Shenron,
the Dragon of Pollution,
and this is my new home!
Hey! What was I thinking?
I can find the dragon
with my senses,
but not the Dragon Balls!
Huh?
[PAN] Did you really think I
was going to let you go alone?
Well, yeah.
Fat chance. Besides,
I know what you were
turning around for,
and I came prepared.
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
Wow! Giru's just who I need.
I thought as much!
Dragon Ball hunting just isn't
the same without Giru, is it?
No! Thanks for bringing him!
Good thinking!
Not so fast, Grandpa!
This is a package deal! Get it?
Pan, please.
Giru wouldn't go without me,
anyway! Would you, Giru?
[GIRU] Giru go! Danger level
increases if Pan goes!
Pan stay! Giru go!
What are you saying? Having me
along isn't more dangerous!
What kind of bogus
calculation is that?!
[GIRU] Giru! Giru! Pan not
stay. Giru not go without Pan!
See, Grandpa! I have to go!
You really don't have a choice!
I'm gonna regret this.
I'll take you, but you'll
have to do what I say.
I promise!
[GOKU]
I can't believe I'm doing this.
There's only one person I know
that's as stubborn
as you are, Pan!
And that would be your Grandma!
[beeping]
[GIRU] Dragon Ball nearby!
Dragon Ball nearby!
Dragon Ball is below us!
[GOKU] Whoa, look!
What happened down there?
What is that stuff?
[PAN sniffing]
Ew, gross. Whatever
it is, it stinks!
[PAN] So, where is
the Dragon Ball, Giru?
[GIRU]
Down below. Down below.
You're gonna have to be
more specific than that.
[GIRU]
Down below?
A kindergartner could tell us
that much, you lame brain!
[VILLAGERS panting]
What's wrong with them?
[PAN] Pardon me folks, but
what are you running from?
Lake! A monster came out of
the lake next to our village!
What? A monster?
A dragon!
Stay back, you rogue!
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
[VILLAGERS yelping]
Now your lives now belong to me!
[PAN]
Grandpa, look!
The Two-Star Dragon!
Stop that!
Pan, come back!
[PAN grunting]
[HAZE SHENRON coughing]
You creep! Do you know who
I am? You'll die for that!
[HAZE SHENRON screaming]
Grandpa, tell me.
Is this the terrible,
evil dragon? Please say no.
Well, he's definitely
different than the one we saw.
What are you looking
at you little beasts?
Did you think a little foot
pain could hurt Haze Shenron?
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
[NARRATOR] The Two-Star Dragon
has the power
to defile entire worlds
with his terrible pollution,
but does he have the
physical might needed
to tangle with Goku and Pan?
And if he doesn't,
does he have something else
planned for our heroes?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball GT!