Give me some credit!
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT...
Goku was tricked by Doctors Myuu
and Gero and trapped in Hell.
And it wasn't long
before a couple of Goku's
forgotten adversaries were
up to their old tricks!
Little did Goku know
that being trapped
in the one place evil
goes when it's destroyed
would only cause these
powerful fighters
to revive after every defeat.
Meanwhile, the battle on Earth
raged as the doctors' strategy
of a full attack
was put into motion!
But none of these
Saiyans would go
without a ground shaking fight.
[DR. MYUU] Good...
The core temperature of our
Android 17 fighter has
reached it's optimum level.
If our victory is
to be decisive,
we must strike immediately.
Dear No. 18, come to your
senses, and join with me.
[ANDROID 17] We belong
together. Deep down you know.
[NARRATOR]
Is Android 17 trying to bring
Eighteen back to the side
from which she came?
Or is this simply another ploy
to weaken the knees
of our heroes?
Find out on today's
episode of Dragon Ball GT!
Now, it's time to
come home Number 18.
We're meant to be together.
It's time for me to go home.
It's been so very long.
Yes... You and I are partners.
Don't do it, Eighteen!
[KRILLIN]
You can't do this, Eighteen.
You have a child and a husband!
[ANDROID 17]
Ha. Give me a break, shorty.
Android 18 is just that,
an android, like me. Built
by the brilliant Dr. Gero.
Brilliant? How could
you even think
to call a monster
like him brilliant?
You destroyed Dr. Gero
yourself, remember?!
You resented him so much because
he gave you human emotions.
He gave me... emotions?
And I killed him?
[ANDROID 17] What are you
doing 17? Snap out of it!
You have to find me.
Our time has come.
You can't take her!
She's not part of you anymore!
[ANDROID 17]
You're right!
[KRILLIN groaning]
[EIGHTEEN] Krillin!
[MARRON] Dad!
Krillin! You can't die!
No, Krillin...
[MARRON]
Dad, wake up, wake up!
[EIGHTEEN]
Please, don't leave me.
I love you...
Get out of here Android 18.
I'll take him.
[KRILLIN] I wish for you
to transform Eighteen
into a human being.
Don't go...
Now, do you see? Your ties
to this race are dwindling.
He was my husband...
...and you killed him!
You killed him!
[EIGHTEEN yelling]
I'll kill you!
[EIGHTEEN panting]
[ANDROID 17] I wanted to
give you a way out of this
for old times sake. But
enough sentimentality...
Tell your husband
'Hello' when you see him.
Mommy...
Get out of here, Marron! Run!
No! You can't die, too.
Get out of here, now!
If you want me...
that's fine.
You can have me, but I
won't let you hurt my daughter.
[EIGHTEEN]
I told you. Stay away from her!
[EIGHTEEN yelling]
Stupid human.
[EIGHTEEN groaning]
[EIGHTEEN] My...
my husband... I love you...
[CELL] What an ugly
specimen of a Saiyan.
[FRIEZA] After all of his
self-righteous motivations
and relentless innocence,
he still ended up
frozen in a block of ice
at the bottom of Hell.
Shows what good it all did him.
So here the fighter rests...
...frozen solid and
uglier than ever.
Finally, Cell, we can
exact our revenge.
Cell, look!
[OLD WOMAN]
My goodness... What's this?
Th-The ice is melting.
[SPIRIT B]
This is stupid, man.
It's too hot for me to deal
with this anymore. I'm gone.
There's a funny
concentration to this ice.
It's made from the
dead who were sent here.
[CELL] And? What does
that have to do with it?
[OLD WOMAN] Since they're dead,
their temperature is much colder
than someone who's alive.
And since Goku's not dead,
his high temperature
warms up the ice spirits
and they run off.
If you had killed him on Earth,
this plan of yours would
have worked perfectly.
[GOKU yelling]
[BOTH yelling]
Well, I guess you guys
didn't really want to win.
Because, if you did, you would
have known the weaknesses
of your attacks
before you used them.
[CELL, FRIEZA, yelling]
You still don't get it.
No matter what you do to us,
we'll always rise again.
Really? Cause I heard
what that old lady
was saying about your
freezing technique.
[FRIEZA] So it seems the amazing
Goku can hear through solid ice.
That's just how good he is.
I wouldn't say that.
I just like to know
my enemies weaknesses.
And I know that this thing will
work a lot better on
you than it did on me.
[BOTH]
What are you doing?!
[CELL]
You imbecile.
[FRIEZA screaming]
[CELL screaming]
[BOTH screaming]
[GOKU] You'd think these guys
would have learned their lesson
after all their time here.
Huh. It's really too bad.
[GOKU yelping]
Oh man, sorry about that.
[GOHAN groaning]
[RILLDO grunting]
[RILLDO yelling]
[ROHAN groaning]
Now, your time has come!
[RILLDO screaming]
[GOTEN]
You okay?
[TRUNKS]
Did he hurt you, Gohan?
I'm fine...
It's just a little embarrassing
to have to be saved
by you guys, I guess.
Papa!
[GIRU] Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru!
[PAN] You're alive!!
Oh, no. Giru, will
you fix my papa's arm?
[GIRU]
Giru fix, Giru fix...
Giru...
[PAN]
Giru, you're the best.
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru...
Ha! Your power level is
pathetic compared to mine.
On your best day,
you couldn't fight a cold.
[DR. GERO]
Big words!
Big words from a man who prides
himself on knowing his enemy.
What do you mean?
[DR. MYUU] This android is only
running at half strength.
You mean you didn't know?
And you think yourself superior?
Wait... there are two of them.
What are you doing
with two Android 17s?
[TRUNKS]
Father!
Ah, it looks like
the gang has arrived.
And with them, the
right time to unveil
the final stage of our plan...
...the perfect artificial human!
[ANDROID 17 chuckling]
My dear fools! When these
two androids merge,
they will become the most
perfect being ever created.
Each complete part of one will
fill in the incomplete gaps
in the other's
mechanical structure.
The machine parts will take
on an organic quality,
like a cyborg.
And it will mutate
to become more efficent.
We are but one, split in two.
But that's about to change.
I can't see them...
[TRUNKS]
Just what do you plan on doing?!
[HERCULE]
What's going on up there?
They merged like it was nothing.
This does not look good!
At last the final stage
of our plan is underway!
We have created the
ultimate artificial human!
Super Android 17 is all we'll
need to control this planet.
This one's mine!
[VEGETA yelling]
Your face...
[VEGETA yelps]
[MAJUUB yelling]
He's unstoppable!
[TRUNKS, GOTEN yell]
Out of the way, everyone!
[GOHAN]
Ka...
Me... Ha...
Me...
Ha!
[GOTEN]
He did it!
You've got to be kidding!
Gohan's attack...
...didn't do a thing.
[DR. GERO]
You're not finished, Super 17.
You have a captive
audience ready for you to
demonstrate what
you're truly capable of!
[TRUNKS groaning]
[MAJUUB groaning]
[GOTEN groaning]
[GOHAN groaning]
[VEGETA groaning]
No matter how many of you
try to face this android,
the fact is that your collective
weakness will always falter
in the face of true strength.
If you like, you can
all fall together.
[GOHAN]
We can't let them do this.
They've all been beaten before.
We can beat them again!
[GOHAN yells]
[TRUNKS yells]
[MAJUUB yells]
[VEGETA yells]
[GOTEN yells]
It's flattering to see
the kind of show you put on
for your most dangerous enemies.
But ultimately it's meaningless.
Let me show you want I mean.
Flash Bomb!
[SUPER ANDROID 17 laughing]
Now, that robot has the kind of
power I'd like to go up against.
[GOKU] But everyone went and
left me out of everything.
No one's even trying to
help me get out of here.
Hey?
King Yemma, if you can hear me,
can you get me out of here?
I hear you, but I can't.
Well, why not? You'll be
helping a lot of people.
I've seen you bend
the rules before.
It's not about
bending the rules.
There's an odd force at work
between the next
dimension and Earth.
Frankly, it's something
I don't understand
and don't know
how to get around.
I'm sorry, Goku,
but I simply don't have
the power to get you out.
You're saying...
The only choice I have is
to stay down here forever?
And I'm not even dead yet!
Oh this job would be great if
it weren't for the people.
[PICCOLO]
King Yemma? Can you hear me?
[KING YEMMA]
Piccolo, is that you?
I need for you to
send me to Hell.
Are you crazy?!
I have an idea on
how to help Goku.
But you'll need to send
me to him immediately.
[KING YEMMA] I don't know
what you think you can do,
but I can't send you anywhere.
I'm sorry, Piccolo.
You're King Yemma,
the one who puts order
into the next dimension,
but you don't have
the power to send me?
Of course, I have
the power. I can do it.
But once your
papers are stamped
and sent to one
world or the other,
I can't change
anything after that.
If I made an exception for you,
I'd have to do it for everyone!
Fine... But what
if you made a mistake?
Like... If you sent
someone to the wrong place.
What are you doing?!
You fool! I am the Evil
Piccolo and you made the mistake
of sending me to
the Upper World!
Evil... yes... evil!
Piccolo, you've gone too far
to prove your point this time.
Fine, I'll give you
exactly what you ask for,
and you'll have to deal
with the consequences alone!
Sorry.
[GOHAN groaning]
[ALL groaning]
I have to admire your ability
to stand up after that.
And I admire
your ability to die!
Final Shine...
...Attack!
That's right! That's the last
time you'll underestimate me.
[SUPER ANDROID 17]
What a sad attack.
You couldn't have
survived that!
[GOKU] If things continue like
this up there without my help
those guys will be
wiped out in no time.
[PICCOLO]
That's why I'm here.
P-Piccolo? How in the
world did you get here?
Nice to see you, too, Goku.
Well, it's great to see you.
I'm just surprised. I figured
they would have put
you in the Upper World.
[PICCOLO] They did. But I came
down here to help get you out.
[GOKU] They let you come
all the way down here
just so you could help me?
[NARRATOR] Just when Goku
was about to lose hope,
this unexpected visit
from an old friend
opened up new possibilities
for his escape.
[PICCOLO]
The powers of a Nammekian
have many uncharted avenues.
[NARRATOR] Will Piccolo have
the power to break open
a rift big enough to
send Goku back home?
And if he does, will
Goku make it in time
to save his friends
from a horrible end?
[DR. GERO] Nice work Super 17.
Now, finish them off!
[PAN]
Wake up! Please!
[HERCULE]
Gohan...
Oh please!
You have to come back
or their gonna
kill us Grandpa!