[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT...
the people of Earth
were shocked when a
giant black hole
split open the sky,
and a flood of death
and destruction
poured through at
the hands of Android 17!
[ANDROID 17 yelling]
It seems the first move in
your strategy is a success.
The powers resonating in the
identical Android 17's have
perfectly fused these
two worlds together.
Then, we should have a toast.
[TRUNKS groaning]
[ANDROID 17] You tell Goku that
if he wants to keep this evil
from destroying
his precious Earth,
then he'll come to Hell
alone to finish this!
Dozens of odd creatures have
descended from a
hole in the sky!
[NARRATOR] Goku accepted Android
17's challenge and ventured
through the portal into Hell.
Little did he know,
he was walking into a trap
set by Doctors Myuu and Gero!
[GOKU]
That hole better not close.
This phase is complete.
Goku is locked down
there permanently.
If you feel the time is right,
we can move into phase three.
[DR. GERO]
A full force attack!
[NARRATOR] With Goku now trapped
in the dark caverns of Hell,
Doctors Myuu and Gero
can proceed with their plan
to conquer the planet Earth.
In the meantime,
Goku will have his hands
full as he prepares for an
all out battle against the
deadly duo of Cell and Frieza!
[GOKU] I've learned a few things
since the last time we met.
[CELL chuckling]
[FRIEZA cackling]
It's been a long time Goku.
And you've gotten so
much cuter since then!
[GOKU] My size has nothing
to do with this, Frieza.
Cause now I'm
stronger than ever!
Wow! It looks like it's
gonna get nasty here!
I think I hear
my mom calling.
It appears to be my turn
to show the little man
what he will be facing today.
[FRIEZA yelling]
[CELL laughing]
Just to give you fair warning,
I promise you'll be
leaving in pieces.
[CELL yelling]
[BOTH yelling]
[GOKU] Excellent work on
the light show, guys.
It's very impressive!
But come on...
I know you're trying
to intimidate me
with your theatrics,
but that doesn't mean
you can use them in a fight!
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU yells]
Wow! With power like that,
he'll blow this
place to smithereens.
And he's not even fighting.
Oh, man! Maybe I overdid
it a little there!
[FRIEZA cackling]
Can't control your own
strength can you, little Goku?
That will come to haunt
to you, I guarantee!
I think the runt has forgotten
with whom he's dealing.
[GOKU]
No, but I think you have.
[ALL yelling]
[ALL grunting]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[TRUNKS] Gross! They look
like giant insects.
[GOTEN] Yeah I know. And
there's so many of them!
[MAJUUB]
Hey! It's not that bad, guys!
Don't let their
numbers intimidate you!
[MAJUUB grunting]
[SABAIMEN shrieking]
[GOTEN] Majuub isn't
kidding around, is he?
[TRUNKS]
Nope.
[GOTEN]
Come on!
Gramps, he's right behind us!
[PAN, HERCULE screaming]
[BOTH shrieking]
Pa-Papa?!
Take Mr. Satan to a
safe place, right now, Pan.
[PAN]
You've got it! Be careful Papa!
[HERCULE]
Take him out, Gohan!
[RILLDO chuckling]
Ha!
[GOKU grunting]
So long!
He's gone! Impossible!
Did he block it or something?
Did you see him?
Ha! Poor Frieza.
You were once considered
the fiercest fighter
in the universe,
and now you're just a simple...
Well, nothing but a slouch.
How dare you call me
a slouch, you idiot!
[FRIEZA]
Wait, Cell look above you!
[GOKU] You know Cell, I was
always taught that if your spent
as much time training as
you do criticizing others,
then your fighting
truely suffers.
How dare you!
You little punk, take this!
Hey, what is this?
Are you trying to pass off
one of my friends
attacks as your own?
You stole that
straight from Piccolo!
[FRIEZA yelling]
Frieza! I thought you
were better than that!
That was one
of Krillin's attacks!
[FRIEZA]
Not quite!
What--
[GOKU laughing]
Why you... How dare
you play games with us?!
[FRIEZA growling]
[GOKU laughing]
Come on! Let's see
what you've got!
Allow me to show you...
Ka... me...
Ha... Me...
Ha!
Give me some credit!
[CELL yelping]
Don't get over-confident!
You haven't felt
my destructo disk!
[FRIEZA yelps]
Oh no... He's done already?
[CELL chuckling]
[CELL] Do you think you
just won the match, Goku?
You fool. Here in Hell,
our bodies are immortal.
[FRIEZA] You will never
be able to beat me,
because I'm already dead!
Ha! That doesn't mean
it's not worth trying!
[VEGETA]
You're still the brainless idiot
who knows only
how to destroy!
One would think that a man
with your experience would
know when to call it quits,
you bald-headed buffoon.
I recommend you split town,
Nappa, immediately.
Unless you want to be
killed by me again!
[NAPPA yelling]
[NAPPA screaming]
[VEGETA] You've completely
lost control of yourself.
[DR. GERO]
Long time, no see, Vegeta!
[VEGETA] What is this? A class
reunion of evil losers?
What do you want?
[DR. GERO] Just the usual
genocide and extinction
of your entire race and people.
Arise! Arise, Android 17!
Well it looks like we've got
a new and improved version.
[TRUNKS grunting]
[GOTEN grunting]
[GOHAN grunting]
[RILLDO yelling]
[BOTH grunting, yelling]
[RILLDO cackling]
[RILLDO]
Come on wimp, make your move.
[FRIEZA yelling]
[FRIEZA, GOKU grunting]
[CELL]
Hm!
[GOKU gasps]
Solar flare!
[GOKU]
I can't see!
[GOKU groaning]
[CELL]
You fell right into my trap.
[CELL yelling]
[CELL] I've done it! I've
trapped him inside me,
and there's nothing he can do.
The strength I've
absorbed from Goku
is almost overwhelming.
I could accomplish
anything with this power!
[CELL yelping]
[CELL growling]
[GOKU grunting]
That was a close one.
I almost got digested
while I was in there!
[CELL]
You got lucky!
[GOKU] Luck has nothing
to do with it, Cell.
I simply had a better
plan of attack than you.
[FRIEZA cackling]
[FRIEZA]
Don't let your confidence
blind your ability to see.
Because here in the dapths of
Hell, nothing is what it seems.
That includes techniques you
Saiyans have yet to lay eyes on,
let alone use in battle.
Like this one!
Almighty!
Light Cage!
[GOKU]
Woah, this is a new technique!
[FRIEZA] Scared yet, Goku?
We're just getting started.
Cell are your ready
for the fun part?
[CELL]
Yes, let's do it!
[CELL, FRIEZA yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU screaming]
[GOKU yelping]
[BOTH cackling]
[GOKU screaming]
[FRIEZA] Have fun digging
yourself out of this hole, Goku!
[GOKU]
Where am I?
And who is that?
[GIRL]
I'll take one for my brother,
and another one for my sister.
Hey. Hi. What are you
doing here all by yourself?
You're no kid.
My goodness. You're my first
customer in a long time.
Please feel free to use the
spa and bath at your leisure.
[GOKU sighing]
Wow. This is quite a
place you've got lady.
[GOKU] What-What's all
this food doing in here?
This is the first stop on
the Terrible Torture Tour.
I am not ingredients for a stew!
I call it the
Boiling Cauldron Torture.
It's very popular.
[GOKU laughing]
This spot is known as
the Tickling Torture.
I can't take it!
You'll like the next one...
It will really make you sweat.
Our third stop brings us to...
Scalding Sauna Torture.
I'm burning!
It's too hot? Why,
then, let's move on.
I'm freezing.
[OLD WOMAN] We've come to
the last stop on our tour,
which is a little different.
The Strangling Ice Torture.
Here. Let me show you.
I know! I'll just blow
it away with a Kamehameha!
[GOKU groaning]
What is this?
[OLD WOMAN cackling]
This is not your
ordinary ice, little one.
There's no use even
trying to break free!
The more you squirm,
the tighter it winds around you!
I can't move my body!
[CELL, FRIEZA cackling]
Hey there, Goku.
You look cold...
I warned you about this
place and the tricks it hides.
But don't fret,
there's plenty more
waiting for you when you
thaw out in 20 years!
[VEGETA grunting]
[ANDROID 17] What's taking you
so long? I need you now!
We must merge into one body!
I want to finish this
as soon as possible!
Well, it doesn't look like
this will clear up for awhile.
That's why I told
you it would be
so much faster if
we would just fly.
But I'm scared of flying.
I don't believe it!
[ANDROID 17 cackling]
It's Android 17!
[ANDROID 17] It's been too
long, hasn't it Android 18?
[EIGHTEEN] What in the
world is wrong with you?
These people have done
nothing to deserve this.
[ANDROID 17] Very shortly the
human race will be exterminated,
and this little planet
will become ours!
What do you mean ours?!
Dear No. 18, Come to your
senses, and join with me.
We belong together.
Deep down you know.
[ANDROID 17] It would be
fantastic if you joined us
to destroy these people and
everything they've worked for.
After all, we are best buddies.
We are friends... forever.
[NARRATOR] With Krillin and
Marron watching helplessly,
the Android 17 of Earth
continues to work his
mind games on 18.
Will she be able to overcome
his hypnotic control?
Meanwhile, Majuub,
Goten and Trunks
continue to deal with
a Saibamen threat
that is terrorizing major
cities around the globe.
Gohan has his hands full
with General Rilldo.
The machine mutant
who nearly defeated
his father and
daughter once before.
While Vegeta steps up to face
the unbridled fury
of Android 17.
[DR. MYUU] Good...
The core temperature of our
Android 17 fighter has
reached it's optimum level.
If our victory is
to be decisive,
we must strike immediately.
[NARRATOR] Just when the people
of Earth need him most,
Goku is in Hell, trapped
inside a block of ice.
With Cell and
Frieza not far away,
can he escape from this
trap before it's too late?
Find out next time on
Dragon Ball GT!