[NARRATOR]
Last time on GT...
Majuub continued to give
Baby a run for his money,
while Goku's speedy training
came to a rough conclusion.
[KIBITO]
His tail looks fully grown now!
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[MAJUUB groaning]
Oh, Kibito, it looks
like we got here too late.
Baby is already chewing him up!
[NARRATOR]
With his tail at full length,
Goku returned to
the Tuffle planet
as humanity's final
hope for resurrection.
But this new appendage
proved to be nothing more
than another weakness.
[GOKU]
This is not what I had planned.
How can he always be
one step ahead of me,
like he's reading my mind?
[GOKU]
I miss the Earth so much.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU panting]
[heart beating]
[NARRATOR]
Has the powerful transformation
promised by Old Kai
finally started?
Or has something
much more devious
begun to stir in the
depths of Goku's body?
Find out now on today's
action packed episode of
Dragon Ball GT!
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
No!
[BABY VEGETA] My people
numbered in the millions,
until the day those
filthy Saiyan gorillas
came to pillage our planet.
A day burned into my very being.
[BABY VEGETA] I'll be dead
before I relive that nightmare.
Now, witness the wrath of a
Tuffle reborn in a Saiyan body!
Your time as the
dominant species is over!
[GORILLA GOKU growls]
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
[BABY VEGETA grunting]
[HERCULE]
Pan! Wait up for me, will ya?
What is it? Can you
see what's going on?
[PAN] No. I just got
a real strange feeling!
What's so strange about it?
I'm not sure.
It feels like something's
not right with Grandpa Goku!
[HERCULE gasping]
He could be okay.
[HERCULE]
No, Pan! Come back!
That's how they were defeated.
But while the Saiyans
pull the same old tricks,
my race has the benefit
of genetic engineering!
I'll be wearing a gorilla
coat by the end of the day.
[BABY VEGETA]
He just doesn't stop.
[GORILLA GOKU roars]
[BABY VEGETA grunts]
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
[BABY VEGETA grunting]
[BABY VEGETA] You'll need
a lot more than those
brute-force jungle tactics if
you want to beat me, monkey-boy!
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
[BABY VEGETA yelps]
Grandpa's energy is
coming from over there.
That big gorilla
didn't eat him, did it?
[PAN] No. I think he
is that big gorilla!
But I didn't think Grandpa Goku
could transform
like that anymore!
[MOB shrieking]
[BABY VIDEL] If this keeps up,
we'll all be killed!
[BABY CHI CHI] Don't worry!
Baby will save us all!
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
[MOB screaming]
[KIBITO] Ancestor, what's
going on down there?
Why isn't he fighting?
Yup, that's what I was
worried about happening
if he didn't train properly.
So, what now?
[OLD KAI] He jumped into
the deep end of the pool
before he learned how to swim.
All the boy needs is a
little time to work things out
and get the power
under his control.
He's not in control?
[OLD KAI]
Of course not.
Right now, he's just
a raving mad ape
looking for food like
any other animal.
But he'll learn.
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
[MOB shrieking]
[PAN grunting]
[BABY CHI CHI]
Look!
[PAN]
Get out of here! Hurry!
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
Grandpa, you have
to stop right now
before you kill
everyone on the planet!
Pan, move it! That freak
is gonna tear you apart
and eat you for breakfast!
He is not a freak!
He's my grandpa!
[PAN]
He just needs to remember!
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
[MOB clamoring]
[GORILLA GOKU roars]
[KIBITO] We can't just sit here.
Something has to be done.
What steps can
we take from here?
[OLD KAI] There may be
a way we can bring Goku
back to his earlier form.
We may have to cut his tail off.
His tail? Sugoro?
Yep. I follow you. Go!
[KIBITO] That's bigger
than I had in mind,
but I think I can still manage.
What are you, crazy?
[OLD KAI] I didn't mean we
should just go snipping away!
If you cut off his tail now,
then everything we've worked
for so far will be lost.
Goku must defeat Baby, remember?
To that end, everything
else is second place.
So, what then?
If Goku could gain control,
if he could somehow wrap
his mind around his new powers,
then he would finally be able
to ascend to a Super Saiyan 4.
Super Saiyan 4?
Well there's got to be something
we can do to help him get there.
There is a method.
What is it, Ancestor?
I'll let you know as
soon as I think of it!
[GORILLA GOKU growls]
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
Something about the Earth
caught his attention.
[PAN]
I gotta see what he's up to!
Wait!
[BABY VEGETA]
If Goku has the ability
to turn into one of
these beastly gorillas,
then by all means, I should have
the same power at my disposal.
[BABY VEGETA]
I hope you're ready, Saiyan!
[PAN] What could have
done this to him?
Please be okay, Pan!
[HERCULE panting]
[GORILLA GOKU growling, moaning]
Grandpa!
You miss your home, I know.
I do, too, but
this isn't helping!
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
[PAN]
Grandpa!
Do you remember me?
I'm your granddaughter, Pan!
You came here to defeat Baby
so that we can all go home.
Please, hear me.
You can't do this!
[PAN groaning]
[CROWD cheering]
[YOUNG PAN grunting]
[PAN]
I hope this helps.
Look at me.
Do you remember this?
This is the outfit
that you gave to me when
I made my first showing at the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
See?
It's one of my most
precious possessions.
[PAN] You've got to try
and remember, Grandpa!
[PAN shrieks]
It's useless.
I guess his heart turned into
an animal with the rest of him.
[PAN] That's when we
all went to the beach
when I was just a baby.
It's days like this that
make all of the hard times
we've been through
seem worth it.
Well I have to admit,
I do miss all of the fighting.
But here I get to
be with you guys.
Grandpa...
[PAN]
You can't forget your family!
I'm not going to let you!
[GORILLA GOKU gasps]
[YOUNG PAN]
Look at me, Grandpa!
[GOKU]
Don't go too far, Pan!
[YOUNG PAN screaming]
[GOKU] Ah, what's wrong?
[YOUNG PAN sobbing]
[GOKU] You're not scared of
those little waves, are ya?
[YOUNG PAN] No, the water
tastes terrible, like salt.
[GOKU] Of course it does! Not
everyone who goes in the water
gets out to use the
bathroom, you know.
Do you remember?
[PAN yelps]
[GORILLA GOKU growling]
[BABY VEGETA] What's that
transformation I sense?
[GORILLA GOKU growling]
[PAN gasps]
[NARRATOR] Pan's persistence
has broken through Goku's
primitive mind and brought forth
yet another transformation.
But will Goku again have to deal
with the same lack of control
he had as a giant ape?
Find out on the next
episode of Dragon Ball GT!