Watch out Grandpa!
[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball GT...
the fight between the
small alliance of Saiyans
and the evil Four-Star Dragon
continued with
undaunted persistence.
[GOKU]
But if I have to...
Someone of your strength being
knocked out by a Solar Flare?
I don't think so, Nuova Shenron!
I'm not buying it!
[NUOVA SHENRON]
You don't disappoint, do you?
Alright then! Let's get real!
Impressive. So this is
your true form I take it?
[GOKU yelling]
[NUOVA SHENRON]
So, Super Saiyan Four,
you've come out.
Let's play.
[NARRATOR]
Amidst all this turmoil,
Nuova Shenron transformed
into a better self.
And Goku knew that
only a Super Saiyan Four
could compete with this dragon.
But nearby, a new threat
is bearing down on Pan,
and it doesn't plan
on stopping there.
Stay tuned. It's all coming your
way today on Dragon Ball GT!
What do you say we get started?
[NUOVA SHENRON]
I couldn't agree more.
[BOTH grunting]
[SS4 GOKU yelling]
[NUOVA SHENRON grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
[SS4 GOKU grunts]
[NUOVA SHENRON growls]
[SS4 GOKU grunting]
I'm quite impressed...
It didn't take you very long
to get used to your new form.
It's only new to you.
Okay then, what do you say
I show you something new?
Now let's see how
you handle this!
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
Ha!
[NUOVA SHENRON] Your
Kamehameha waves are a joke.
The time you take to
gather your energy
takes longer than
the attack itself.
Have you forgotten my speed?
Of course not, I just
explore every angle.
So, try catching me this time!
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
[NUOVA SHENRON]
There!
[SS4 GOKU]
Ha--
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
I guess the guy's got a point.
My Kamehameha waves
were too slow.
[NUOVA SHENRON]
Are you ready for more?!
[SS4 GOKU]
Great, no rest for the weary.
So it's come to hiding.
The sign of a truly
powerless fighter...
[NUOVA SHENRON growling]
What?
[SS4 GOKU]
Score one for me!
[NUOVA SHENRON]
Impressive, you got me.
I underestimated you.
Do what you will.
Why are you waiting?
I owe you for something
that you did for me.
That's not what I meant!
[PAN grunting]
Put her down! Now!
[GOKU]
Thank you.
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
Wake up, Pan! Please!
Don't mention it.
I've been awaiting your arrival!
[SS4 GOKU] You had every chance
that day to kill Pan,
yet you decided
to spare her life.
That's why I'm sparing
your life right now.
I have a policy against
killing innocents.
[SS4 GOKU] You see, you do
have some good qualities.
Now that the debts
have been paid,
let's see who leaves
this fight standing.
Now let's go!
[SS4 GOKU gasps]
What happened to my hand?!
That didn't come from me!
Great! It's my brother!
What? He's got a brother?
[EIS SHENRON chuckling]
I thought you'd be done
with him by now, brother.
Having trouble?
Stand down. This is my fight!
So you two are
really are brothers?
Unfortunately, yes.
I had no idea that you dragons
could actually be
related to each other!
How exactly did that happen?
So you're the Goku
I've heard so much about.
I want to thank you for your
gross error in judgement.
The Dragon Balls have
worked wonderfully for us!
Hey, wait a minute.
That's Pan's bag!
What in the world have
you done with her?
[SS4 GOKU]
Pan!
Hey there Grandpa.
Pan, Pan?
I'm sorry.
I lost the... Dragon Balls
from the ugly dragons but I--
Pan! Come on, wake up!
Pan!
How dare you do this to her!
[EIS SHENRON] Nuova, hold on
to this while I work my magic!
[NUOVA SHENRON growls]
[NUOVA SHENRON]
No, Eis. I'm fighting Goku.
So butt out of this if you
know what's good for you.
I don't think so.
If I were you,
I'd be thanking me.
Your fighting up to now
has been an embarrassment.
Times like these call
for action, not talk.
We're dealing with
the most powerful Saiyan
ever in existence,
and a Saiyan cannot be
talked into submission.
[NUOVA SHENRON]
That's enough!
I have my own methods
of fighting this Saiyan,
and they work just fine.
[EIS SHENRON] You can be
such a blithering idiot!
How can there be a certain
style of fighting someone?
Either you get the job
done, or you don't.
It's that simple.
[SS4 GOKU]
Pan!
See Nuova? My way
is much more effective.
Not again!
[EIS SHENRON] See that?
Two simple beam attacks
and he's incapacitated.
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[EIS SHENRON cackling]
Sorry about the foot,
but that annoying laughter
was starting to break
my concentration.
[SS4 GOKU]
I guess I don't need my hands
when my feet are enough
to deal with you.
[EIS SHENRON groaning]
You know, you have a point.
Those feet are trouble.
[SS4 GOKU]
What's that?
[SS4 GOKU yelping]
[EIS SHENRON]
Now for the left one.
[SS4 GOKU growling]
Next I'll get your stomach.
And I'll work my way up.
And finally, I'll
finish with your head.
[SS4 GOKU screaming]
[EIS SHENRON cackling]
[EIS SHENRON]
A Saiyan ice cube! I like it!
What took me 2 minutes would
have taken you 2 days, brother!
So, you big baby, do you now
see what fighting is about?
Or do you want to be
my next demonstration?
[SS4 GOKU] How am I gonna
get out of this one?
My Super Saiyan Four
powers are useless
as long as I'm
covered in this ice!
Now, brother...
You can redeem your
pathetic self, if you wish,
by destroying this
piece of garbage!
So come on, send this
idiot to the other world.
What?
[EIS SHENRON]
What, are you blind?
Do you not see Goku frozen
in that block of ice,
totally open to any attack
we want to unleash on him?
All it will take is
one finishing attack.
He will be blown
into so many pieces
they'll have trouble
finding them all.
[EIS SHENRON]
What are you waiting for?
I'm giving you
the chance to kill Goku
and you're just standing
there like a statue!
It may be hard for you to
believe, but I'm not like you.
I refuse to kill anyone
when they are defenseless.
It's part of my code.
I didn't ask for you to
show up and help me.
I could have beaten
him on my own.
With my own techniques...
...and my own strength.
What a loser.
[BOTH grunting]
All of that childish
nonsense you spout
makes it sounds like
you have a conscience.
[BOTH grunting]
Just look at you, lying
face down in the dirt,
unable to fight
your own brother.
I'm ashamed to
even call you that!
Prove to me you're
a worthy fighter.
Stop acting like a weakling.
Bring honor to
the Shadow Dragons!
Kill him before I kill you.
[EIS SHENRON]
Well?
I understand.
[SS4 GOKU]
Nuova Shenron! Wait!
[BOTH yelling]
[BOTH grunting]
I'm quite impressed.
It didn't take you very long
to get used to your new form.
It's only new to you.
Let's go, while we're young!
Nova Star!
[SS4 GOKU]
Oh great!
[EIS SHENRON cackling]
[EIS SHENRON gasps]
[SS4 GOKU sighs]
I told you to kill him,
not melt him, you imbecile!
Hey, Eis Shenron.
I've been listening to
you belittle your brother
because of his morals.
Don't you understand that
it's going to take his help
if you ever plan
on defeating me?
What are you getting at?
Give me ten seconds, Nuova.
I'll do away with your
hardheaded brother here,
then we can finish our
fight monkey to dragon,
like it should be.
So, you ready?
Ten seconds? You must have me
confused with someone else!
[EIS SHENRON growling]
[SS4 GOKU] The last thing I need
is to be covered in ice again!
[EIS SHENRON yelling]
[NARRATOR] As sibling
rivalry keeps Nuova and Eis
from executing a
combined attack on Goku,
Eis decides to
prepare his own attack
by freezing the entire city.
Does Goku have it in him to
finish off two Shadow Dragons?
[SS4 GOKU yelping]
How embarrassing!
Forget what I said before.
I'll take him out
in five seconds!
[NARRATOR] Find out if Goku
stays true to his word
on the next Dragon Ball GT!