[SCI-BOT B]
Proceeding with specimen one!
[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball GT...
Trunks and Goku were being
analyzed while in captivity!
[SCI-BOT C] Initiating
Energy Configuration Scan!
[SCI-BOT A]
Scan complete!
Running Power
Analysis Diagnostic!
[NARRATOR]
While trying to find them,
Pan fell in with
the spare parts,
which gave her the idea
for the perfect disguise!
[PAN] Well, it's not my style!
But it'll have to do!
[ROBOT] Resume forward march.
Resume forward march.
[ROBOTS]
Defective unit! Defective unit!
[NARRATOR]
After failing as a robot,
Pan's rescue mission fell
into another roadblock--
Nat, of the
Mega Canon Sigma Force!
Thanks to the traitorous Giru,
the powerful mutant-bot had
all of Pan's fighting moves
in his memory banks!
[PAN] Giru! How could you?
I trusted you!
I was your friend!
[PAN yelling]
[NAT]
This does not compute!
Pan's power level is exceeding
the maximum, recorded level!
Error! Error!
[NARRATOR] Straight from
her victory against Nat,
Pan exploded into the lab
where Goku and Trunks
were being held captive!
[PAN yelps]
Pan!
[GOKU grunting,]
[NARRATOR] Seeing Pan
get hurt was all it took
for Goku to make
tatters of his prison!
"Grandpa" is ready to
take on the Sigma Force!
[GOKU]
Pan? Are you okay?
[BIT]
Some rescue party!
[SIGMA FORCE laughing]
[GOKU]
Trunks! Look after Pan!
[TRUNKS]
Right, Goku!
[GOKU]
As for you, guys! You're mine!
[NEZI] It's amazing that
your little friend
was able to destroy
our comrade, Nat!
Never before has a Sigma Force
member been beaten in battle!
[RIBET] Don't get your hopes up!
We're much stronger than Nat!
Oh, well that's good,
because you are going to need
all the help that you can get!
[SIGMA FORCE cackling]
You can laugh if
you want to! Go ahead!
[GOKU] But if you enjoy
causing others pain,
then I have a bone to
pick with you guys!
Trunks, take Pan
back to the ship!
I can take care of
these jokers by myself!
But Goku!
[GOKU]
Trunks! Listen up!
We need to get Pan out of
here right now!
Right! Got it!
[BIT]
Not so fast!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[BIT]
Huh?
He's not your opponent! I am!
[BIT] We should not be
holding hands like this!
Contamination! Contamination!
[NEZI, RIBET laughing]
[GOKU]
Hm.
[NEZI cackles]
Why do organic beings prefer
to die in the sunshine?
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU groaning]
[NEZI]
Foolish child!
He should never have
pretended to be tough
and sent his friends away!
[RIBET] It would
not have mattered!
Not with the data that we have!
Huh? What do you mean by that?
We're not even from here!
What information could
you possibly have--?
[RIBET] All kinds! Thanks
to T-20-O-6!
The one you refer to as Giru!
[BIT] We know all of your
fighting patterns!
All of your techniques
and your moves!
T-20-O-6 recorded your
fights while he was with you!
He did? Well, he's a
bigger jerk than I thought!
[RILLDO cackling]
Your handiwork is
already taking its toll!
[RILLDO] You're going
to be the most decorated
M2 unit in history! Aren't you?
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
[NEZI] Too bad, kid! Your defeat
is imminent! You can't win!
Well, I'm not
quite convinced yet!
[NEZI]
Then we will demonstrate!
[RIBET] Why can't we
kill him, Commander?
It's not fair. It's like having
an itch that you can't scratch!
[BIT] Heh, heh, heh! We can
still beat him to a pulp!
[NEZI]
Well, now you know the truth!
You're only alive right now
because Doctor Myuu
wants you alive!
He's so impressed with you
that he wants to use you
in his experiments...
...as a Guinea Pig!
Me? A pig? I don't think so.
[GOKU groaning]
[BIT]
Bit Barrage!
[GOKU yelping]
[RIBET]
Ribet Rocket!
[GOKU grunts]
[NEZI] Calculating expected
attack pattern, based on data!
Extrapolation complete!
[GOKU groaning]
[NEZI]
I've already told you
that we know everything
about your fighting style!
So why then do you persist?
Well, why not?
[GOKU grunting]
They disappeared!
[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU]
How do they do that?
[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU]
Sneaky devils!
[BIT]
Looking for me?
[RIBET cackling]
[GOKU]
How is that possible?!
[NEZI] Don't tell me that
you're mystified
by such a simple technique!
It's not simple!
Trust me! It's awesome!
[BIT cackling]
[RIBET cackling]
[NEZI cackling]
[GOKU chuckling] I've seen
some neat tricks in my day,
and that one takes the cake!
But... I think I might
have an answer for it!
How 'bout this one!
[BIT groaning]
[NEZI groaning]
[ALL groaning]
Hah! I could've really
shaken the place up!
But I get way
too dizzy doing that!
[NEZI]
Arrhh! I'll kill you!
Well, take my advice!
Get up first!
[TRUNKS]
Aw, man! This doesn't look good!
It would be a miracle if the
Dragon Balls were still here!
[TRUNKS] Giru! I'll bet
you're behind this!
They're gone!
That bum! Darn him!
I'd like to get my hands
on that little twerp!
[PAN]
Owww! What's the big idea?
That wasn't very
nice, you meany!
Well, well! Look who's
up! It's about time!
Whoa, this place is
a mess! What happened?
Giru came and
took the Dragon Balls!
No way! That little jerk!
[NEZI] You will pay dearly
for that impetuous attack!
Oh, yeah? Well, your wall trick
isn't going to work out here!
[NEZI]
We have no need for
such a rudimentary
technique to defeat you!
Only a small fraction of our
power has been displayed so far!
The Sigma Force Cannon
will make quick work
of an opponent like you!
Sounds exciting! Sigma... Force?
[NEZI]
Cannon! Silence! All right, men!
Ready! Sigma Force Cannon unite!
[BIT]
Bizu!
[RIBET]
Ribet!
[NEZI]
Nezi!
Whoa! That's weird!
Hey, uhh! What happened? Where
did the guys I was fighting go?
[MEGA-NEZI]
We have combined to form
one being of
unparalleled military might!
The all-powerful
Sigma Force Canon!
Wow! You guys are
really something else!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru...
[RILLDO] Yes, T-20-O-6!
I, too, am excited!
[MEGA-NEZI]
Pesky, little fly!
One wrong move and the
little fly is going to die!
[GOKU growling]
[GOKU grunts]
[MEGA-NEZI groans]
[GOKU laughing]
Gotcha!
[MEGA-NEZI cackles]
[GOKU groans]
[explosions]
Wow! He really packs
a wallop! That really hurt!
[MEGA-NEZI cackling]
[GOKU grunting]
[MEGA-NEZI groaning]
[GOKU chuckling] Maybe it wasn't
such a good idea to unite!
You have gotten stronger,
that's for sure!
But you're lacking in
the speed department!
[MEGA-NEZI cackling slowly]
Huh? Now what
are you laughing at?
[MEGA-NEZI] At the silly prattle
of a child who thinks he's fast,
but is about to have
a rude awakening!
Super Sigma
Aerial Attack! Engage!
Look at that! He changed again.
[GOKU yelps]
All right! Now he's cookin'!
[RILLDO] He's making sport of
the Mega Cannon Sigma Force!
[GIRU] Giru! Giru! Danger!
Danger! Overload! Giru! Giru!
[RILLDO]
Yes! Danger! Extreme danger!
What speed! Wow!
I Guess I take back what I
said about you being slow!
[GOKU yelping]
[MEGA-NEZI cackling]
[GOKU]
Now where'd he go?
Ow... That hurt!
[MEGA-NEZI]
Flesh and bone creatures!
So fragile and inferior!
Allow me to take the pain
away once and for all!
Killer Driller Attack!
[GOKU grunting]
That would have taken
away the pain all right!
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU]
Being on the ground
doesn't seem like such
a good idea right now!
[GOKU gasps]
[MEGA-NEZI]
Haa!
[GOKU yelling]
[MEGA-NEZI cackling]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU]
Oh, no you don't!
[MEGA-NEZI]
Aren't we daring?
I can feel your hands
sweating! Don't slip!
[MEGA-NEZI cackling]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yells]
[MEGA-NEZI]
No! What have you done?!
[GOKU]
Nothing yet!
[GOKU grunting]
[MEGA-NEZI yelling]
[MEGA-NEZI] That power!
Explain how you did that.
Your energy tripled just then!
[GOKU] That was nothing!
Just the tip of the iceberg!
I can reach levels a hundred
times greater than that!
[MEGA-NEZI]
Come now! You're bluffing!
You expect me to believe that
you've been hiding your power?
What would you gain
from holding back?
Information! The same
kind you had on me
when we started this fight
thanks to your little spy, Giru!
Your fighting style,
your power, and your moves,
not to mention all of your
strengths and weaknesses!
[MEGA-NEZI]
Curse you!
Look! Buck up, pal!
You're the one who
started this game
and now it's time to finish it!
[RILLDO growling]
Why that impudent, Saiyan brat!
[GIRU]
G-General Rilldo?
[GIRU sputtering]
[SCI-BOT B]
Warning! Warning!
[RILLDO growling]
[RILLDO panting]
[RILLDO]
No! No! Don't be frightened
of your General, my
faithful servants! No!
Only one should be worried!
And his name is Goku!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yelling]
[NEZI]
Analyzing!
[BIT]
Danger! Danger!
[RIBET]
Surpasing known speed!
Haaaa! Here! Ready!
[GOKU grunting]
[MEGA-NEZI yelling]
[GOKU] Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
[MEGA-NEZI] No!
[MEGA-NEZI]
We are the Sigma Force Cannon!
...Ha!
[MEGA-NEZI yelling]
[GOKU]
Sorry, about that, guys!
But if you didn't do bad deeds
this wouldn't have happened...
[stomach growling]
[GOKU chuckles]
What are you complaining
about? I did all the work!
[GOKU]
All right! I get the message!
You've got a bigger growl
than some lions I know!
Whoa! That's some wicked
energy I'm feeling!
And powerful!
Incredibly powerful!
Whatever it is, it's heading
straight for our spaceship!
[PAN]
Where do you think you're going?
Do you think I'm
going to let you
go find the Dragon Balls
without me?
[TRUNKS] Sorry, Pan!
If you come along,
you'll only get in the way!
Please, stay here!
C'mon! Me? Get in the way? What
are you talking about?! Huh?
[TRUNKS]
It's coming this way, Pan!
You're going to have to trust me
on this one! Stay here! Please!
Right! I see! Get 'em Trunks!
[RILLDO] You're going to regret
making me come out here!
You are all going to pay dearly!
[NARRATOR] As General Rilldo
speeds toward the spaceship,
Goku flies on
an intercept course!
Can the young Saiyan
survive the impending clash?
Or will the darkness
overpower the light?