[NARRATOR]
On the last GT,
a Dragon Ball was discovered
in a small village
on a remote planet.
[TRUNKS]
Which one do they have?
Four! Five! Six!
[NARRATOR] But the villagers
had much bigger concerns
than to part with
a Dragon Ball!
Well, my peasants! Have you
decided on a bride for me yet?
What? A bride?
That's disgusting!
Fools! I like
when people beg me!
But, only a bride
will stop the quake!
[NARRATOR] The evil Zoonama
was threatening to destroy
the entire community unless
the villagers handed over
one of their young
women to be his bride!
[NARRATOR]
Let the magma flow!
[NARRATOR] Rather
than face total destruction,
the villagers agreed to meet
the monster's wicked demand!
However, the betrothed
wasn't a woman at all,
but a powerful warrior
carefully disguised to look
like the ultimate bride to be!
The plan: to infiltrate
Zoonama's lair
and cut off his
quake-producing whiskers!
Oh, well. I guess things...
[NARRATOR] Wedding bells ring,
today on Dragon Ball GT!
[ZOONAMA] Come closer, my sweet
Laine! Stop being so shy.
[TRUNKS] It's just that
I hardly know you.
Don't be afraid, silly!
I just want to see
your pretty face!
Uh, oh. This could get ugly.
[ZOONAMA]
Something's different about you,
but I can't put my finger on it.
[TRUNKS] Uhh...
It must be the wedding dress!
Ahh? Hmm. Perhaps
you're right. It's your veil.
Why not take it off?
[TRUNKS] Great! What am I
going to do now? I'm sunk!
Come on! You're too stiff!
Be creative for goodness sake!
[TRUNKS]
I'm trying!
What's that, Laine?
[TRUNKS] I'm dying
to remove my veil!
But, it's not proper
'til we're alone!
[DOMA] Wow!
What a close call!
Trunks really came
through with that one!
[PAN] I don't know.
It seems like he's skating on
thin ice to me.
[GOKU] Hey!
Before the ice breaks,
what do you say we
attack Zoonama?
Are you nuts?
He could use a volcano to
torch the whole village!
Let's use our heads!
[ZOONAMA] How cute!
What a refined young lady!
Oh! Why thank you!
Come Laine.
Let's go find some privacy!
[ZOONAMA] I know a place where
you can let your hair down!
[TRUNKS]
Where are we going, Zoonama?
Where else?
To my little love nest!
[PAN] All right! Everything is
working according to my plan!
Now let's go!
We can't lose sight of them.
You smell good!
Oh, you! Please!
Your skin is so soft!
[ZOONAMA] Laine!
Don't ever touch my whiskers!
Do you want me to
cause a volcano to erupt
and destroy your village?
[TRUNKS] But I was only
trying to protect you!
A mosquito landed on your
whisker and was about to bite!
I see. Sorry about that,
you sweet little thing!
Well, we're almost there!
[TRUNKS]
Almost where?
[ZOONAMA] To a place where no
one will ever bother us again!
It's my little secret!
[TRUNKS]
Oh, it's uh, nice!
[ZOONAMA] This isn't it, silly!
Now take a deep breath!
Huh. That's strange.
It's like they just disappeared.
[DOMA]
But we mustn't lose them.
That would put
Trunks in great danger!
[GIRU]
Must find Trunks! Giru!
Hey! No sweat, Doma! We're fine!
I can track anyone, anywhere!
[muffled groaning]
We're here!
[TRUNKS] Oh! Gosh, Zoonama!
It's... It's uh... It's so you!
That's weird. There are puddles,
but it hasn't rained.
What's up with that?
[DOMA]
Goku! Pan! Over here!
Look! This flower!
Isn't this one that Laine picked
out for Trunks' disguise?
I think you're right,
but would they have dove in?
[GOKU]
I'm gonna find out!
Geez! Put some clothes on,
Grandpa! You're gross!
And hurry up with it,
this isn't a locker room.
Who do you think you are
parading around like that?
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru!
Be quiet!
[splash]
[GOKU] I wanted to
take a look under water,
and I never swim
with clothes on.
I don't see
what the big deal is.
We used to take baths
together all the time.
Liar!
I'm not lying.
[PAN] But that was
when I was a baby, right?
Well, I'm a young
woman now, Grandpa.
People grow up, you know, even
though you never seem to!
[GOKU] Well, I don't
want to grow up if it
means swimming with
your clothes on.
I'm not trying to be nosey Pan,
but is Goku
really your grandfather?
[PAN]
Yes! Unfortunately!
Strange. Here we start small
and grow big and then shrivel.
[GOKU]
There's a tunnel down there.
It looks like it
leads to some caverns!
I'll bet that's where
Zoonama took Trunks!
Laine, my dear! You should slip
into something more comfortable!
[TRUNKS] Oh, can you
pick something out for me?
[ZOONAMA]
I'd love to!
Lava! Oh great! That means
we're inside a volcano!
[ZOONAMA] I have the
perfect dress for you, my sweet!
[TRUNKS]
Oh! Thank you!
[confused groan]
[TRUNKS]
How pretty! I love it!
Y-You there.
You're not my Laine. Are you?
[stuttering]
Not good!
[ZOONAMA] How dare you!
No one tricks Zoonama and lives!
But you!
You're a different story!
I can forgive you
because you're so cute!
I love short hair
on young women!
And your physique! How athletic!
What's your name sweetheart?
Name? Oh, I'm Trunksette.
Trunksette! You are the cutest
thing that I've ever seen!
[TRUNKS] Man! This guy
really needs to get out more!
[bubbling]
Lovely isn't it? Don't be shy.
This is our wedding banquet.
Dig in, sweetie!
[TRUNKS] This is my chance.
It's now or never.
But first a toast to
our new found love!
Hmm? Okay!
[TRUNKS] Well,
here's to a long and happy
and healthy life together!
[ZOONAMA] Oh, how sweet!
You go ahead! I'm not thirsty.
Please! Don't let me
stop you, Trunksette!
Bottoms up!
But sweetie! It's our
wedding day! You have to!
No, I don't.
It's part of the celebration.
Hm?
Just one!
If you want it, you drink it!
[TRUNKS]
Think of something, Trunks!
[screams]
[ZOONAMA]
Hmm?
Oh, he's gone!
It was an ugly ol' bat!
Let's not let him
ruin our dinner!
[TRUNKS]
Zoonama!
Hmm?
Try these!
They're really delicious!
Are you going to feed me?
[TRUNKS]
Yes!
How sweet!
[ZOONAMA]
Those are yummy!
[TRUNKS] There's plenty
where that came from! Here!
Have some more!
Just tell me when
you've had enough!
[ZOONAMA] I've had enough,
Trunksette! I've had enough!
[GIRU]
Giru!
[DOMA]
Look, you two! A light!
[PAN] Bingo!
That's got to be them!
One more. Okay?
I'm sorry! Did I give
you too much, honey?
[ZOONAMA]
Well...
[burps]
Yes, but it was tasty!
I feel good!
[TRUNKS] I think it worked!
He seems out of it!
[hiccips]
Trunksette!
I want more now!
But they're gone!
You just ate them all!
No! No! I want more!
That's not fair!
I'll cause an earthquake
if you don't give me more!
[TRUNKS]
This is getting dangerous!
Now I see why he doesn't drink!
[PAN]
Trunks!
How's it going?
[TRUNKS] Bad! I spiked his food
and he's going crazy! Back off!
Who's in here?!
[uncertain groans]
[drunken mumbling]
[hiccups]
I don't know who you are,
but I'm not going to let you
ruin my time with Trunksette!
Oh, they'd never do that.
These are my good
friends, Zoonama!
[TRUNKS]
They just wanted to meet you!
Get outta my face!
[crash]
Whoa! The potion was
supposed to relax him,
but he's going ballistic!
[GIRU]
Get away! Stay back!
Come to Zoonama!
Gladly, wife stealer!
[ZOONAMA]
Wife stealer? How dare you!
[GOKU]
Pan!
[PAN]
Thanks, Grandpa.
Hey, ugly!
You seem to be real good at
beating up on little girls!
Why don't you try me instead?
Okay!
[ZOONAMA]
You'll make a fine snack!
[growls]
[crash]
[laughs]
Boy, he's really out! Isn't he?
[TRUNKS] Good! Now I can
finally ditch the dress!
You know, I think
he actually cared.
He's a strange one, alright.
Well, now or never, Doma!
[DOMA]
Yes! Right!
[DOMA] Zoonama, you have
turned our joy into sorrow,
our day into night! Never again
will you steal our peace!
[giggling]
That's hilarious!
My duty is only half done!
Now for the other half!
[DOMA]
This is for the children!
[sneezes]
[gasps]
Trunksette, whoa, you don't
look right. You look like a...
A man? Yeah, sorry.
We just weren't to be!
What? But I loved you!
I would have given you anything!
[ZOONAMA]
Deceivers!
I'll kill you all!
[ZOONAMA] How 'bout
a quake for starters?
Yeah! Shake! Shake! Shake!
What the--
[screams]
My whisker! It's gone!
You can't stop me!
I still have one! You idiots!
[ZOONAMA] I'll shake this
planet until it falls apart!
[ground quaking]
[TRUNKS]
This is bad!
I'll shake until the walls
come crumbling down
and smash your heads,
and your brains come out
like scrambled eggs!
[silverware clattering]
[glass shattering]
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru!
[Zoonama chanting]
[suits of armor clinking]
It's not working anymore.
Great spirits!
Has his power truly gone?
Huh?
So your reinforcements
have arrived!
Well, big deal! I don't care
how many of you there are!
I'm bringing
the house down, babies!
You're all going to die!
[Zoonama chanting]
Why did it stop working?
Wait! I've got it!
[PAN] Zoonama doesn't have
the power to cause earthquakes,
only the power to predict them!
He just shakes his
whiskers when he knows
a quake is going to start and
he stops when the quake stops!
But now he's too tipsy
to know the quake is over.
For years we have
been living in fear,
too paralyzed with dread
to stand up for ourselves
and realize
the truth in front of us!
[Zoonama's chanting ceases]
Why aren't you terrified?
Trunksette wasn't the only one
who was faking it. Was she?
It's no use, Zoonama!
We know the truth!
[ZOONAMA] If you don't
stop talking nonsense,
I'll make a volcano
erupt right now!
[TRUNKS]
You will...
...not!
That does it! Now I'll make
a volcano erupt for sure!
Go ahead!
It's over, Zoonama! We know
you can't cause earthquakes!
You've taken it too far,
Zoonama! You've hurt people!
[ZOONAMA] So, you
really do know. Don't you?
Mmm, hmm!
Then, it really is over.
Mmm, hmm.
I'm sorry! Please don't hurt me!
I beg of you! Please! Oh!
[ZOONAMA] I never
meant any harm! Truly!
I only meant it as a joke!
[DOMA] Stealing my
fiancée was no joke!
Stop shaking!
You're not fooling anyone!
I'm not doing that.
That only happens when a
real quake is about to hit!
I swear!
You have to believe me!
I'm telling you!
This one is going to be huge!
Nope! Not Buying it!
[GIRU]
Danger! Big shake, Giru!
We're all going to die
if we stay down here!
[ground quaking]
I knew this was coming!
I've been sensing a
lot of quakes lately,
but they were just babies!
This is the mother
of all quakes!
Ow! Man, that's hot!
[steam bursts]
It's erupting!
[lava gurgling]
[terrified screams]
[GOKU]
Let's get out of here!
[ZOONAMA]
Wait for me!
I don't want to die! Help me!
Ha!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
[thud]
[GOKU]
Are you okay, Doma?
[TRUNKS]
We just made it.
[PAN] This is bad! The village
is going to get wiped out!
We've got to do something!
[TRUNKS]
It's too late!
Maybe not!
[DOMA]
He can fly?
Be careful, Grandpa!
[GOKU]
All righty then.
Now that she's let
some pressure out,
we can try to stop
the bleeding.
Maybe I can seal off the wound.
[GOKU]
Ka...
Me...
Ha...
Ha!
[PAN] It's completely gone!
He blew up the whole thing!
[DOMA]
How can this be?
[GOKU] Whoa! Man! I really
overdid it this time!
Oops! My bad!
[LAINE] Here you are! This is
for your bravery and prowess!
It was beyond all expectation!
Thank you, Laine!
Thank you! You've helped us
more than you know!
Yes, the three of you
made the impossible happen!
[DOMA] We never dreamed
that one day Zoonama
would join our village!
[LAINE] He's actually rather
gentle once you get to know him.
We think he'll fit in fine here.
[GOKU] Just don't give
him anything to drink!
Yes! That is good advice.
We will follow it and pray that
your people find peace as well.
Thanks, Doma!
[villagers chattering]
[evil laughter]
[LAINE'S FATHER]
He's taking the ball!
Give that back! It's ours!
[BON PARA] Thanks for
the Dragon Ball, suckers!
[lasers beaming]
[pained groans]
[NARRATOR] Who is this
mysterious alien who confiscated
the Dragon Ball?
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next GT!