Now... rise...!
Shenron!
[NARRATOR] On the first
episode of Dragon Ball GT,
an elderly Emperor
Pilaf and his gang,
showed up uninvited on
top of the Lookout!
[NARRATOR]
Shenron was summoned,
but the Emperor's lack
of attention to detail
caused a most unusual
wish to be granted,
and Goku's body was reduced
to that of a ten year old.
What?! Goku!
The room got a lot bigger.
[GOKU] I had no idea
that the dragon was
there when I walked in,
then Pilaf made the
wish and "poof" here I am.
No, I liked being old...
[NARRATOR] Although Goku's
new look took some adjustment
from his family,
the situation seemed
to be under control...
[CHICHI]
Goku!
[NARATOR]...until
King Kai delivered
some even more alarming news.
[KING KAI] Goku!
Can you hear me?
We sure can, King Kai.
Now that a wish has been made,
the Earth is in
danger of exploding
unless all of the Black Star
Dragon Balls are found
and returned to Earth
within one year!
[gasps]
[cars honking in traffic]
[EMPLOYEES] Good morning,
Mr. President!
Hello, this is accounting...
I'm trusting that this
morning's meeting
went by the numbers, sir.
That was the easiest
deal I've ever closed.
They signed the contract
before I even finished
my first cup of coffee.
You were born to
lead this company, sir!
[TRUNKS]
If you say so...
Hey, he's here! Look!
It's him!
He always looks so... adorable!
[GREEN SUIT] This must be
real exciting for you, sir.
[LADY] No challenge is too big
for you, Mr. Briefs.
[GREEN SUIT] Don't forget that
we have a board meeting
at three o'clock today.
[EXECUTIVE] Mr. Henderson
called wanting to
schedule a golf match
with you tomorrow.
[GREEN SUIT] And we
still haven't heard your
final decision on that
matter of the research budget.
[EXECUTIVE] Yes, if we are going
to approve anything,
it should be done fast.
[EXECUTIVE]
How about we go over this now?
And of course,
there is the matter of
the third quarter budget,
which is something we need to
finalize before we discuss
the annual employee bonus pay--
I'll ride to my office alone.
Uh, but Sir...
[bell rings]
Yeah... Come in.
[EMPLOYEE] Excuse me, sir,
all of these documents
need your approval.
If I don't get this
to legal by two o'clock,
we'll miss all of
our deadlines!
You've got to be kidding me!
[EMPLOYEE]
Uh, no, I'm afraid not...
Okay, let's go over the
schedule one more time.
At two o'clock in your office,
the vice president wants to
discuss the new contract.
Two thirty is your
video conference call
to the investors from
the MechaVoid Corporation.
At three o'clock the
conference room is reserved
for the board of directors.
[ASSISTANT] We will be serving
coffee with your choice
of bagel or muffin.
Don't forget--
Why do I even try?
[TRUNKS]
Oh, yeah!
That was just about as much fun
as I could stand for one day!
[GOTEN]
I mean,
if you're not already doing
something tonight, that is...
Oh... really?!
Yeah, I'm excited, too.
You are one smooth
talker, Uncle Goten.
That's for sure.
Shhh...! Not you! No.
[PAN] If you don't
want me to poke fun,
then keep your voice down.
Do you mind?! I'm trying
to talk on the phone!
It's a mobile phone!
--Uh, hello?
--No...
I'm sorry!... You see my
little niece was in the room...
[GOTEN]
But, hey listen...
How about I pick you
up around eight?
[PAN]
I am not little!
It's no big deal, really.
Tomorrow, Goku can take
Bulma's new ship into space.
Yeah.
It's not like this is the
first time you've gone
Dragon Ball hunting
to save the Earth.
You don't mind going, do you?
Why do I have to
be the one to go?
What do you mean "why"?
You've never balked at this
kind of adventure before!
Yeah, I guess
I'm just a little tired.
Getting shrunk down to
the size of a kid again
really takes it out of me.
But... You have
to go on this trip
or the Earth will be
destroyed in a year.
She's right...
And we just finished the
addition to our house, Goku,
which I do not want to lose.
Yeah, Dad... We could never let
anything bad happen to Earth.
That's why...
I've come to a decision.
I'm going to find
the Dragon Balls with you.
That's great! A father
and son bonding trip!
Papa, you're going?
Uh-huh.
Let me go, Papa! I want to
go into space with you!
[CHICHI] Pan, your
father and grandfather
aren't going just to play,
you know? It'll be dangerous.
That's right, Pan.
I know that. I'm just offering
my help to save the Earth!
If you go up into space, you'll
see scary monsters and aliens
that will try and get you!
I'm not afraid of anything.
Pan... you sleep
with a night-light.
Um...
Sorry Pan, but going to
space is just for adults.
I'm taller than you, Grandpa!
[GOKU] That thing looks
like an octopus!
And it's so big!
[BULMA] This ship carries three
people, comfortably.
But with you being as
small as you are now...
It shouldn't be cramped at all.
You know, seeing you like this
reminds me of
the time we first met.
[laughs]
Uh... hey boss!
I think someone's coming!
[CRIMINAL]
Can you tell who it is?
Well, uh, let's see... He's
got tall spiky black hair,
a widow's peak
and a creepy little mustache.
[CRIMINAL]
You numbskull!
You're supposed to be looking
out for Bulma's daughter!
Not describing every
guy that just walks by!
How else are we going to get the
ransom money from Capsule Corp!
[KNEELING CRIMINAL]
Yes, sir! Sorry, sir!
It won't happen again, sir!
[PAN] Hey, Papa, is there
anything I can help you with?
[GOHAN]
Thanks Pan, but...
Uh... I think Bulma and I
have everything pretty
much under control.
Oh... Can I still help?
Why don't you go see if you can
help mom with something...
Alright?
[PAN]
Alright...
Hi, mama! Papa told me
I should come help you!
Thanks but... not
right now, honey.
I really have to finish
testing this panel.
Well, if it's a test you want!
Don't touch!
[VIDEL] Listen, Pan,
I'm very busy right now.
I can't have any distractions.
But Mom, I...
Now... Why don't you call your
friends and go play outside?
[PAN] I'll just be
walking this way now...
I found her... I see her now!
[CRIMINAL]
Don't just sit there, you moron!
Get on your feet and get her!
Yes, sir!
[GOKU]
Hey, Pan! Wait up!
What?
So, where are we headed?
Who's we?
What? You're saying
I can't go with you?
[PAN] Well, I can't go into
space with you, can I?
How rude.
I heard that...
What's rude is following people!
[PAN] Why don't you go back to
your dumb punching
and kicking practice?
Now's my chance.
Yeah, that's right!
Ha, ha... I've got her!!
[GOKU]
I'm a boy.
[grunting]
[HERCULE quivering]
[blows landing]
[screaming]
[crash]
[PAN] Oh, come on, boys!
Is that all you got?!
Get up and fight,
you little babies!
My word, Pan... We need to
find you a new anger outlet!
This is getting
bad for business.
You want some too, Gramps?
[nervously stifles cough]
[CRIMINAL] Funny how your girl
looks and eats like a boy.
Yeah, that is a boy... The girl
jumped up and flew into the sky.
Flew into the sky? You've
got the brain of a hamster.
This kid might be just as good.
He was hanging around
Capsule Corp.
So they might
still pay the ransom.
Really?!
I get the feeling this
boy's related to Bulma.
Hmmm... That Bulma lady is
getting up in the years...
I wonder if this kid's her
grandson or something.
Does it matter?! She'll pay
even if it's not her kid!
She'll pay.
Mmm... boy! That was good!
[CASHIER] Your total comes
to 700,000 zeni.
I... guess I'll charge it
now, and pay later...
[CASHIER]
Can I see a photo ID?
[CRIMINAL]
Listen carefully,
we have your son and/or
your grandson here with us.
Grandson? Wrong number.
Don't you play dumb with me!
We kidnapped your boy, Goku,
and we ain't giving him
back 'til you pay.
Goku? Are you serious? I'd watch
my back if I were you guys.
Yeah? You watch... your back!
[CRIMINAL] Lady, I ain't messing
around here, you know.
If you don't-um...
What is that?
Hey!... hello?!
[CRIMINAL]
My calling card...
He hung up.
Who hung up?
[BULMA] Some guy
complaining about your father
for some reason.
[GOHAN] Was it someone from
a restaurant?
We get those calls a lot...
I hope he's not
out fooling around.
This ship's gonna
be ready soon.
Surely not everybody is
treating you that way.
Watch this.
Here you go, you two.
You see,
this is exactly the kind of
thing I'm talking about, Gramps.
Everyone thinks
I'm a little kid.
That is rough.
I'm very mature for my age.
So, would you
like cream or sugar?
[PAN]
No, black's fine.
[disgusted groan]
Well, Pan let me tell ya,
I've certainly never
considered you a little kid.
I agree!
My Pan is not a baby!
I'll drink to that!
My Pan is...
Oh, just the cutest angel
ever to set foot on the
face of this green Earth!
[PAN] I'm not a baby, I'm not
little, and I am not an angel!
Oh, I see... Sorry.
Fine! I'll show everyone once
and for all that I'm no kid!
[disgusted groan]
We're going too fast! Make it
stop! I want off this thing!
I shouldn't have had that funnel
cake! I think I'm gonna be sick!
This is not safe!
Somebody's going to get hurt!
I strongly suggest
that you find a way
to get me that 5 billion
zeni right away!
Unless, of course,
you don't care what
happens to little Goku here!
What are you
babbling about? Goku?
[CRIMINAL] And if I even think
you went crying to the police,
there will be no deal!
I trust I'm coming in
loud and clear, buddy.
[VEGETA]
Deal with him as you please.
[dial tone]
Um, hello...
Are you there? Hello?
[CRIMINAL ON ROLLER COASTER]
Let me off of this thing!
Help me! Help me!!!
I'm gonna die!
[GOKU] You guys sure are a lot
of fun to hang out with!
[CRIMINAL]
Thanks a lot...
[GOKU] So, what do you
guys want to do next?
[CRIMINAL] Well, ah, we still
have to run an errand or two.
Then, I think I need a nap.
Man, this whole day
has been nothing
but one big headache
after another!
Um... I should
probably get back soon.
There's no reason for
you to go home yet, kid.
I mean, the fun's
just starting...
We haven't even had a chance to
take you out for dinner yet!
[CRIMINAL] Boss, we cannot
afford to feed this kid again!
Would you be quiet?!
I guess I have enough time
to eat dinner with you guys.
We just have to find a
telephone first... Okay, Sport?
Let's see, now... telephone,
telephone... Don't see one.
Is this some kind of
a game or what?
That's right.
[GOKU]
On your mark, get set, go!
[chuckles]
[whimpering]
[CRIMNAL] Do you think maybe
this car has an exhaust leak
or something,
'cause I've never seen
anything like that before.
Yeah, and you said that
I had the brain of a hamster.
[GOKU]
Hey, guys!
[shriek]
Looks like I win the game!
[shrieking]
[crash]
[CRIMINAL] Forget this!
Let's go get real jobs!
Oh, well... I guess they
had to get home, too.
[TRUNKS]
F-Father?
Son... there's the easy way
and then there's the fun way.
I still don't understand!
Why do we have to go with him?
This is not cool!
[VEGETA]
Give it a rest!
Both of you have begun to grow
unbearably soft in
these times of peace...
And with Kakarot
leading the search,
you'll see trouble in no time.
You do know that
I have a date tonight...
[VEGETA]
Dating is for the weak!
What about me? I am the
president of Capsule Corp!
Then consider
this a hostile takeover.
It's not that I don't want
to find the Dragon Balls,
I just know that my mother
would never let me set
foot on a spaceship.
It was all her idea.
[GOTEN]
You're kidding me!
Main power link...
Check!
[BULMA]
All systems are go for launch.
Hey, Goku! Keep those
two boys out of trouble!
Don't worry, ChiChi... I will.
Oh, man... this isn't the kind
of vacation I had in mind.
[phone rings]
Hey, Valese, did ya get
my message? No, I swear.
I really am going
into outer space.
Gohan, sweetie...
have you seen Pan?
Yeah, I think she's
with Bulla somewhere.
No, Bulla's standing
up there with her dad.
Yeah... I know...
It sounds like baloney,
but I'm not making it
up! It's the truth.
[GOTEN] What?!
Look, I can barely hear you!
If you're gonna yell at me,
you're gonna have to be louder!
Whoa... Wow...
[TRUNKS] So, this is what's
supposed to pass
as our home for the next year?
[GOKU] Is that
the kitchen over there?!
[TRUNKS] No, Goku.
That's the control room.
Hi!
Hi, there Pan!
What's going on?
[PAN] Just making sure that all
systems are go for our journey!
'Bout time you guys got here.
Pan, please... this is no
time for fooling around.
Oh, no? Then let's get
serious! Blast off!
[scream]
What?! Yes! For a whole year!
You still there?
Good... Guess what?
Change of plans...
My schedule cleared up.
[NARRATOR] A most unusual
trio has begun their journey
to the far reaches
of the universe.
What will these three discover
in their effort to find
the Black Star Dragon Balls
and save the Earth
from certain doom?
[clink]
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball GT!