FUSION!
This Fusion of
yours won't happen!
[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball GT,
the only thing
that looked worse
than Goku and Vegeta's
dancing abilities
was their chance of winning
against the ferocious
Omega Shenron.
Vegeta!
The After Image Technique!
Idiots! Don't you get it?
There will be no Fusion!
FU...
Get it through your thick heads!
...SION!
HA!
FUSION! HA!
Curse those monkeys!
Kakarot!
[GOKU laughs]
Whatd'ya know!
I'm a little kid again!
Now we're in a pickle!
[NARRATOR] Unable to pull
off the Fusion technique,
and with Goku reverted
to his younger self,
Omega Shenron seemed
an unbeatable foe.
[OMEGA] You realize
you're destined to die.
[NARRATOR] The bad omens
continued to reveal themselves
with the appearance
of a Dragon Ball
protruding from
Goku's forehead.
What could this
mean for our hero?
Find out today
on Dragon Ball GT!
All right!
Let's get this over with!
Uh, I know I'm getting
old and my eyesight's going,
but does anyone else see
a Dragon Ball growing
out of Goku's forehead?
[HERCULE]
Good. So I'm not crazy.
[CHICHI crying]
I can't take it anymore!
He turns into a child,
he runs off on crazy adventures,
and now he has
a ball on his head!
Uh, Grandma?
She's finally cracked.
[GOKU] Are you just
going to stare at me
or are we going to fight?!
What are you saying you clown?
Look at yourself.
In that condition you
couldn't fight a headcold.
Just because I'm
in my younger form
doesn't mean I can't
put up a good fight.
You are so very
stupid sometimes!
Grandpa! Hey!
Your forehead! Feel it.
My forehead?
Whoa! What's that?!
That's what we've
all been wondering.
Ahh! What is that thing?
It better be a pimple 'cause
I'm not going to the hospital!
I do not want to get a shot!
But it doesn't hurt!
He probably wouldn't have even
noticed if I hadn't told him.
[OMEGA chuckles]
For as insignificant
as you all are,
you've certainly kept
me entertained.
Unfortunately, it's time
I pulled the curtain
on your little comedy act.
Right now!
I've had enough fun for one day!
Wait, Omega Shenron!
Hey, Nuova Shenron!
I haven't had my fun yet.
I suppose I could share.
[OMEGA laughs]
Think about what
you're doing, Nuova!
You know you can't
trust him, remember?
He's already killed you once!
He's just going to turn
on you like he did before!
All he knows is how to betray!
What did you expect?
Once I've absorbed
a Dragon Ball,
it is forever tainted
by my negative energy.
Your strategy of consuming one
was nothing but a foolish
display of ignorance.
I gave Nuova here a small
portion of my negative energy.
And combined with
his natural strength,
you won't last five seconds!
I promise.
And this time, Goku...
...I will not show pity.
Ha! I never asked
for it the first time.
If the three of you are going
to talk as if I don't matter,
then I'm afraid I'm going
to have to interrupt!
Be careful Vegeta!
Nuova Shenron's a lot
faster than we are!
Is that a fact?
Well, I wouldn't mind
putting that to the test!
Die.
[GOKU and VEGETA yell]
[OMEGA laughs]
[explosion]
Boom.
[EVERYONE gasps and yells[]
[TRUNKS grimaces]
[GOKU grimaces]
[GOKU gasps]
Vegeta!
Father!
[OMEGA laughs]
If you're going to
be moving that fast,
I might suggest going in
the opposite direction, boy!
We've got enough
fighters as it is.
In fact, I might just go
ahead and sit this one out
if you don't mind.
Not at all.
It's time, Goku.
Bring it on!
Nuova Death Ray!
No one here is a good
enough challenge for me.
But by giving Nuova
enough Negative Energy,
this battle should prove to be
more than our tiny
Goku can handle.
Ka...
Me...
Ha...
What's this? The little guy
just doesn't give up, does he?
HA!
How long is Nuova planning
to toy around with him?
I just wish he would finish
these two off soon,
so we can get out of here.
Father! Are you all right?
Of course I am!
Something's not right.
He's not taking this seriously!
Nuova wasn't even
trying to hurt me.
He just wanted
me out of the way.
He's out there fighting
like he's putting on a show.
But why would he do that?
What do you say there, Nuova?
Are you done prancing
around this kid like an idiot?
Do it already!
I'm so tired of him.
I want to fight someone worthy!
Well then...
What do you say, Goku?
Should we give
him what he wants?
On three!
One!
[NUOVA and GOKU]
Two! Three!
[OMEGA growls]
That's right! I'm not going
to watch you destroy everything!
We got you good!
What do you think you're doing?
I gave you an ample
amount of negative energy,
enough to power
you for a lifetime.
There are other types of energy
out there just as strong!
It must have been when Grandpa
swallowed the Dragon Ball!
Some of his positive energy
transferred over to Nuova!
You were right about
Nuova Shenron, Father!
I bet Goku has had this
planned out all along.
[GOKU giggles]
For once, he thought with his
head instead of his stomach.
We've tormented this
planet long enough!
This is between you and me now!
NUOVA SPHERE!
No way!
Good luck!
Let me guess, your plan is to
hug me to death. Am I right?
You know what
I am capable of, Omega,
so, if you think you can
just walk right out of here,
be my guest!
[OMEGA growls]
What makes you think
I would come back here,
loyal only to you?
Loyal to the one who killed me.
I know how strong of a fighter
you are Omega Shenron.
That is why Goku and I
worked out this little plan.
We caught you off-guard and
you fell right into our trap.
Fool, for something so smart
you are behaving very stupidly.
I don't think so.
This time, I've thought
everything through.
These flames are moving in
a perfectly sealed sphere.
Your strength won't
make a bit of difference
if your body
can't take the heat.
It's your call.
What is it?
Would you like me to remove
the flame chains for you?
That's right!
Go ahead and shoot!
You'll kill yourself
while you're at it.
Oh, I forgot!
You're not used to shooting
someone face-to-face.
How's this?
Do you feel better now?
Ha! Still don't have the guts?
Allow me to do it for you!
Wait! Think about
what you're doing!
He's right where we want him!
Don't hold back!
Are you actually willing to
risk your own life as well?
I am Nuova.
Heat is not a factor.
The one who's about to
become charcoal is you!
Nuova!
[VEGETA grimaces]
That can't be all
that's left of them.
Hold up, Vegeta!
I sense someone inside there!
Who?
All right! It looks like
Nuova Shenron made it!
Nuova, you're okay!
The plan actually worked!
What's wrong? Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Goku.
It's not him!
No, it's Omega!
Then, what happened?
Surprised to see me, Goku?
You! Nuova!
What did you do to him?
Yes, I guess it is
a story worth sharing,
if you don't mind my bragging.
Are you prepared
to go down with me?
You see, while my body
absorbs the heat,
yours will be incinerated!
If your body comes
so highly recommended,
then maybe I could borrow it!
[NUOVA groans]
I guess I'll see you inside.
[NUOVA yells]
He was right I suppose.
The first time I took him out,
lacked a certain artistic touch.
[OMEGA laughs]
I don't care how
strong you are,
or how much negative
energy you have
because none of that's going
to make a bit of difference!
Ha! And what are you
going to do about it?
I'll show you!
Ka... Me...
Ha...
Don't you ever get enough
of that same boring move?
HA!
[VEGETA]
Kakarot!
That's better.
Now that I have regained
the Four-Star Dragon Ball
my power has once
again reached its peak!
I'm truly invincible!
Nobody in this world
or the next can stop me!
The entire universe will soon
be laid to waste by
my negative power!
[OMEGA laughs]
They're losing?
Well, looks like they are.
What now, Ancestor?
I mean, if Goku and Vegeta
can't stop this guy,
is there anyone who can?
You don't think we're gonna
have to fight him do you?
What's all of this we business?
Why are you always trying
to drag me into things?
Then again, the kind of power
this guy's playing with
is nothing to take lightly.
If Goku and Vegeta
can't stop him,
I'm afraid the entire galaxy
will be polluted
with negative energy.
[ANCESTOR]
Omega Shenron doesn't even have
to lift his little finger for
this pollution to spread.
The planet will
soon begin to rot
and decay at an
accelerated rate.
Life will no longer
be sustainable
as the earth grows
dark and then cold.
At some point it will explode,
and the pollution will expand
outwards in all directions.
Planet after planet will fall
in an endless domino
effect of destruction.
But then, that means
it could reach us here!
I'm afraid it's
only a matter of time.
Then we have no other choice.
We have to run away!
You coward! How can you even
think to call yourself a Kai?
Relax! I was just kidding.
This younger generation
is always making jokes.
Numbskulls...
So, does this planet
have any real fighters?
You tell me!
Darn!
Bulma! The Blutz waves!
I-I can't! It's broken.
And it would take me
a whole day to fix it!
You're kidding me!
Vegeta, why do you have
to use Bulma's machine?
Can't you just turn into Super
Saiyan 4 on your own by now?
Shut up!
I could ask the same
question of you right now,
so don't get on me,
you little runt!
Would you two like to take
a break or do you mind
if I just finish killing
you where I left off?
We can take a break?
That's great 'cause we're
both out of power right now!
Moron!
[NARRATOR] The unlikely hero
Nuova has taken a fall,
leaving Omega Shenron even
more powerful than before.
These two Saiyans
are running on empty,
but they will need
a lot more than energy
to come out on top
of this fight.
Find out who settles the score
on the next Dragon Ball GT.