[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball GT...
Goku, Pan, and Trunks made
their return to mother Earth.
Hi, you guys! We made it!
[NARRATOR]
Disaster had been averted
and the Black Star
Dragon Balls were left
in the capable hands
of Mister Popo.
[GOKU] We'll see ya soon!
[PAN] Bye Giru!
[NARRATOR] The weary travelers
thought they'd be returning
to the safety of their homes,
but they were not prepared for
what surprises were in store.
And the long awaited
family reunion
descended into a bitter
fight for survival.
[GOTEN]
You Saiyans!
[GOHAN]
It's been a while.
[NARRATOR] Mother had
turned against daughter,
and sons against their father!
Taking the two attackers
as evil imposters,
Goku made up his
mind to destroy them!
Goku! Stop it!
Mr. Satan?
[HERCULE] Goku! Baby is
controlling Gohan and Goten!
He got in their heads
and jacked up their minds!
The entire human race
is under Baby's control!
[GOKU]
How could I let this happen?
[NARRATOR] At last,
Goku knew the whole truth.
In his absence, darkness
had taken over the Earth!
[GOKU]
Not you, Vegeta!
[NARRATOR] With Baby in control
of Vegeta and his own two sons,
Goku now faces an enemy
of unparalleled strength!
But how can the loyal Saiyan
attack his parasitic foe
without destroying the
bodies of the ones he loves?
[HERCULE] Go back to where
you came from, you vermin!
You're not welcome here!
Find your own bodies!
[BABY VEGETA] I thought
that we had infiltrated
all of the human life forms
on this miserable planet.
How we overlooked the
loud one, I do not know!
I'll tell ya how,
Baby! I was hidin'!
Right in here!
And you never knew!
Funny, huh? We used
the same strategy!
[HERCULE] Except I didn't go
inside of Majin Buu to lay eggs,
I went inside of him
to hide from you!
How do ya like them apples?
[GOKU laughing]
Wow! Great idea, Mr. Satan!
[HERCULE laughing]
All right! It's time you were
told what's what around here!
I'm the Champion of the world!
You got that, Baby?!
You're nothin' to me!
You're a joke! That's why
I have Goku on the job!
He takes care of the small fish
and leaves the big ones to me!
I see! I misjudged you.
I thought you were
an ordinary man.
Now that I know you're
Earth's champion...
...you're history!
Uh...
[HERCULE yelping]
I knew my mouth
would get me killed one day!
Buu! Get Pan to safety!
Okay!
Goku! Don't hold back! Hit him
with everything I taught ya!
Hey, Baby! Thought you
could outwit the Champ!
Didn't ya, big guy?
[HERCULE laughing]
Buu! I-It's not time yet!
What are you doing? Aaaah!
Yummy! Good! Good! Buuuuuuu!
He's all mine!
Enough!
[BABY VEGETA] No need to
waste your energy on them!
This little prize is
the only one worth having!
When he falls, it's over!
So tell me, do you really think
you'll be able to do serious
harm to your own two sons?
Hm! You tell me! Will I?
[GOKU yelling]
[BOTH grunting]
You won't get away with this!
My friends and I will
find a way to stop you!
Fool! You Saiyans
wiped out my race!
This is merely payback!
But this is Earth! The Saiyans
were destroyed long ago!
They've already
paid for their actions!
Now so will you!
[GOKU grunts]
You don't have a chance!
Haaa!
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU gasps]
[BABY VEGETA yelling]
The last time we met,
he couldn't even stand to be
inside a Super Saiyan body!
Looks like Baby
is a quick learner!
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
Huh? Hm...
[GOKU gasps]
Oh, boy. Bad timing.
[GOKU] It's not safe
for Bulla to be here!
Baby got to Earth
before we did, Trunks!
He's taken over your Dad's body
just like he tried
to take over yours!
Goten and Gohan
have been infected too!
[TRUNKS] How long do you
think you can resist, Goku?
Gosh, Trunks. You, too?
Don't fret. It's actually
a pretty cool feeling!
No worries, no
pressures, no cares!
You'll enjoy it, Goku!
Let go of all that tension!
Yeah! Go with the
flow! It's so easy!
Fight, Trunks!
[BABY VEGETA] Trunks is a
Tuffle. Now he sees clearly.
It's you!
You're like a drop
of oil in water, Goku!
We are a team! You are
but one individual!
Stop being selfish and become
part of something great!
[BULLA]
Come on. Listen to my Dad.
You've been friends forever.
Bulla, your Dad would
never call me Goku!
[GOKU] Don't be a prisoner in
your own bodies! Fight him!
Ha, ha! You fool!
You don't get it, do you?
They're me! I'm them! We're one!
I know you guys are
really suffering inside.
Fight it. Our bond
is stronger than this.
Dad, don't do this.
There's no way that you can win.
He's right, Dad. You'll
die if you fight back!
[GOTEN] We just want
you to be part of us.
[TRUNKS, BULLA cackling]
[GOTEN, GOHAN cackling]
[BABY VEGETA]
Wait, my precious children!
This one is a special case!
I want to handle him
differently than the others.
The other ones, I changed.
They're all Tuffles
now. But not you!
You don't deserve to live!
I'll kill you with my own hands!
Thanks, I'd prefer
that actually.
No offense, but I'd much
rather die than join you!
Then die!
[BABY VEGETA yelling]
[ALL yelling]
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
What incredible power!
Inside Vegeta, he's ferocious!
I have no choice!
Super Saiyan Three!
This could be trouble.
Yeah! He's going all the way!
Super Saiyan Three!
[GOKU yelling]
Yes! Finally! Your true
Saiyan power at last!
You don't know how
I've longed for this!
[GOKU yelling]
[BABY VEGETA chuckling]
[GOKU] Oh man! I had no
idea he was this strong!
He's making it look easy!
[BABY VEGETA] You can't get
any higher, can you?
You've reached your limit!
Ha!
Nice shot! You're good!
I haven't been this excited
about a fight in a long time!
Haa--!
I'm disappointed, Goku.
[BABY VEGETA] I had hoped
that a Super Saiyan Three
would prove more challenging.
No! My body! It can't
take it! It's too weak!
My older body was more
developed, and more resilient!
What am I gonna do now?
[BABY VEGETA]
It looks like your time is up!
Now die, Saiyan scum!
[GOKU screams]
BABY VEGETA cackling]
[GOKU]
Did I miss something funny?
Because if you think you've won,
then the joke's on you!
This fight won't be over until
you've been destroyed!
Even if you manage to kill
me, someone else will come
and take my place! Some
how! Some way!
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[BABY VEGETA]
Believe what you want.
I believe in what I
can see and touch.
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU coughs]
Now, that's real!
Feel it? Pain is real,
and there's only one way out!
[GOKU groans]
[BABY VEGETA] You'll find
it to be much less painful
if you stay down.
I'll end it quickly.
[GOKU groaning]
Thanks, Baby, but
I prefer to fight!
[BABY VEGETA] Hmm! Have it
your way then, Saiyan!
[GOKU groans]
[BABY VEGETA groans]
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU chuckles]
[BABY VEGETA] What? What are
you laughing at? Tell me!
[BABY VEGETA growls]
Curse you!
[BABY VEGETA grunting]
[GOKU groaning]
That should do it!
Well, I'm not dead yet!
Good try though!
[BABY VEGETA growls]
Look. Baby. Stop this.
It's not too late.
For your own good!
Hm! My own good?
You're at death's door and
you're worried about me?
That's awfully touching!
[BABY VEGETA]
Perhaps your ancestors
should have demonstrated
such compassion
before they destroyed my race!
That would have been
nice, wouldn't it?
But they chose to kill instead.
And now, I must choose!
You die! That's my choice!
Now! Slaves!
Give me your energy!
For the glory of all Tuffles!
[ALL]
Yes, as you wish.
[ALL groaning]
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[BABY VEGETA growling]
[TRUNKS grunting]
[GOTEN grunting]
[BULLA grunting]
[GOHAN grunting]
[BABY VEGETA growling, cackling]
[BABY VEGETA screaming]
That's it, sir. We've given
you everything we have.
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
Well done. Excellent
work my faithful slaves.
Thanks to your
collective Saiyan powers,
a Tuffle is now the strongest
being in the Universe!
Amazing, but true.
You're the best, the
strongest in the Universe.
But the victory
doesn't always go
to the one with the most
power. Sorry, Baby.
Oh? Really? Who's
going to beat me?
I am! I'm not sure how yet!
But I'll figure
it out eventually!
You're going down,
Baby. I promise!
Enough of this blasphemy!
[GOKU groaning]
[BABY VEGETA chuckling]
Hear me, Tuffles!
This is your ruler, Baby!
[BABY VEGETA]
The time has finally come for us
to take our revenge
on the Saiyans.
The last of their race
is here before me!
Send me your energy,
my faithful ones!
Send me your spite
and your malice!
[CROWD groaning]
[BABY VEGETA cackling, groaning]
[GOKU groaning]
[BABY VEGETA]
This is for you, Saiyan!
It is all the hatred that has
built up towards your race.
It is the repayment for
the sins of your fathers!
[GOKU]
Let it go!
Find a way to regenerate
and rebuild peacefully!
Peacefully! That's mockery
coming from a Saiyan!
Oh, no! You have a debt to pay!
Revenge Death Ball!
[GOKU] My body! It's too
thrashed! I can't move!
[GOKU]
I will not give up!
[ALL screaming]
Huh?
[BUU]
Goku...
What an extraordinary
attack. It's flawless.
So Dad, have you
finally met your match?
Oh yes! At last! After all
these years, revenge is ours!
All pure blooded Saiyans
have been destroyed!
[BABY VEGETA]
Now it's our turn!
Now the Tuffles will become
the next mighty warrior race!
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
Buu. What's up? It felt like
the planet was falling apart!
What's goin' on out there?
Boom! That's what
Buu heard. Boom!
Then, poof! Buu can't
feel Goku anymore!
[BUU]
Buu thinks Goku is gone!
What? Goku!
No, it can't be!
Never again! Never again will
the Tuffles be a peaceful race.
We were helpless lambs!
Now we will be mighty hunters!
We shall spread like a plague!
[NARRATOR] A wicked curse
has befallen the Earth
and the souls of her people
are being held captive
in their own bodies.
With Goku gone, is there
any hope left of liberation?