[NARRATOR] With the situation
looking as grim as ever,
Uub appeared on the Tuffle
planet to challenge Baby
But the training he put
in for this moment
proved to be inadequate
against the villain's fury.
[PAN]
No! Uub!
Say goodnight!
[NARRATOR] But an unlikely ally
would come to Uub's aide!
Thinking quickly, Buu realized
that he and Uub would be
a more effective force against
Baby as a single fighter.
[BUU]
That's right!
Time now for Buu and Uub
to become one.
[NARRATOR] Will this merging
of abilities be what it takes
to put an end to Baby's quest
for Tuffle vengeance?
[UUB]
What... What happened?
Thanks, Buu. I owe you.
You saved my life back there.
Now, let's go see Baby!
[NARRATOR]
Find out now, on Dragon Ball GT!
[GOKU screaming, groaning]
[ALL groaning]
[GOKU screaming]
Can one of you
check the glass ball?
I get the feeling something
strange is happening.
[KIBITO] Well, it, looks as if
Uub and Buu have merged bodies.
They what?
[GOKU]
Wow! That is amazing!
Old Kai! It looks like
they're getting ready
to fight down there.
Do you think we can make
this tail grow any faster?
If you would put your
concentration here
instead of on the
Tuffle planet, then yes.
Help him, Sugoro.
You got it!
What... What are you doing?
So, how is this
supposed to help?
You were squirming
around so much,
we've barely made any
progress on your tail.
Now, quit whining!
[OLD KAI] One, two... Really put
your backs into it, now! Three!
[GOKU screaming]
[ALL groaning]
Does it hurt, Goku?
Isn't it supposed to hurt?
[OLD KAI]
Well, it just doesn't seem like
you're trying too hard.
[GOKU] How can I try any harder?
You've got me tied to a rock!
That probably isn't
the best place to stand.
[MAJUUB grunting]
It looks like he's actually
gathered enough
strength to fight me.
At least now I can have
some more fun with him.
[MAJUUB screaming]
What's that fool doing?
[MAJUUB grunting]
[BABY VEGETA yells]
[MAJUUB screaming]
[BABY VEGETA grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
[BABY VEGETA]
This punk is really starting
to get on my nerves!
Buu and I have combined powers,
and we're gonna take you down!
Good luck!
Ha!
[CROWD screaming]
[UUB]
I hope you like chocolate, Baby!
[CROWD screaming]
Hey, don't worry down there!
I'll turn you all back into
yourselves after I get rid of--
[BABY VEGETA] You certainly have
very interesting techniques!
Yeah, well, there's more
where that came from.
Try this on for size!
Ha! I've seen this
foolishness before.
Let's see him
escape from this!
Pitiful! Does he think
that I am foolish enough
to fall for his
chocolate trick again?!
[BOTH grunting]
This is the end! The end
of your reign, Baby!
No... It's not!
[GOKU screaming]
[ALL grunting]
[GOKU] Ouch, stop it!
It's hurting too much!
Untie the rope!
No, not yet. We haven't even
pulled out your tail one inch!
[GOKU]
But I have a much better idea!
[OLD KAI] Well, go ahead
and tell us what it is.
Hey you! Now this is ridiculous!
Untie me right now!
Goku... This is no
time for getting even.
I can feel my spleen
pinching my throat
and I don't like it one bit!
Do you understand me?!
[GOKU] Just settle down
a minute and listen to me.
I want you to hold on to
these as tight as you can.
What are you intending
to do here Goku?
[GOKU] Well, what I had in mind,
was you grabbing onto my tail.
[OLD KAI]
But that doesn't make any sense!
All you have to do
is hold on real tight,
then I'll fly away as
hard as I possibly can
until it's nice and long!
Of course! He's much stronger!
Well if you say so,
but don't try too hard
or your spine may
come out with it!
Don't worry, I know
what I'm doing.
[OLD KAI] Should I count
to three or something?
[GOKU grunting, yelling]
[OLD KAI]
Please be careful Goku!
You're about to pull
it completely off!
[KIBITO] So why don't you
just let go of the pliers!
Oh, yeah.
[GOKU groaning]
Hey!
[KIBITO] You, you did it!
You did it, Ancestor!
His tail looks fully grown now!
[OLD KAI] Good. We've
fixed his power issue.
Now, if we could
just fix the whining...
[ALL laughing]
[CROWD gasping]
[MAJUUB yelling, grunting]
[BABY VEGETA cackling, grunting]
Time for bed, little boy!
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[MAJUUB groaning]
[MAJUUB screaming]
[GOKU]
Where's Uub?
Do you see him?
He's right over there!
[BOTH gasping]
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
It's my lucky day. Looks like
I've won a prize for this fight.
Kibito Kai... It looks like
we got here too late.
Baby is already chewing him up!
Goku? So, you're still alive?
You bet I am, and I'm
gonna keep coming back
until I get rid
of you for good!
Well... aren't you...
quite the trooper...
Go ahead and keep
wasting your time
because I'm really
starting to enjoy
kicking you around my planet.
[GOKU]
Not this time, Baby...
I've made a few changes
since our last fight!
[BABY VEGETA]
There's nothing you can do
to hold off my victory!
[GOKU[ Yeah, well
check out my new tail!
Your new tail?
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[BABY VEGETA] What's next? Will
you start flinging your poo?
Oh, no. You'll like this one.
[GOKU yelling]
Let's get this party started!
[BABY VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
Ow, ouch...
Now that hurt.
Wha, What just happened?
I thought I had control of him.
[BABY VEGETA] Your tail
makes you as easy to hunt
as any other animal!
[GOKU]
Hey!
My tail makes me the kind of
fighter that you'll never be!
[GOKU, BABY VEGETA grunting]
[GOKU]
Does it hurt?
You haven't gotten any
stronger at all, have you?
But I don't... understand...
My strength should
have skyrocketed
with my tail being
as long as it is.
[BABY VEGETA]
And it obviously hasn't worked!
[GOKU]
We'll see about that!
Hey! Let go of me!
[BABY VEGETA chuckling]
It's time for me to
remove that tail permanently!
[GOKU yelping]
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
Oh no, I can't stop him!
Old Kai, what's happening to me?
I... wish I knew.
[GOKU yelping]
[BABY VEGETA cackling
It's time for you
to die, Saiyan!
[GOKU screams]
Quite a pathetic effort
from the mightiest
Saiyan of them all.
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU]
This is not what I had planned.
How can he always be
one step ahead of me,
like he's constantly
reading my mind!
[KIBITO] Old Kai, what's
happened to Goku?
He's getting thrown around
like a rag doll out there.
Is it possible that we
pulled out his tail out too far?
[OLD KAI] I doubt it. Maybe it
takes a while to kick in.
[GOKU]
Earth, she's so beautiful.
Just the thought of me not
being able to protect her...
...makes me cringe.
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[GOKU] I have so many
fond memories of home.
I'll miss it so much.
All of my family and friends.
Those who have been at my
side through the worst of times.
I can't bear not being able
to save them from Baby.
Please, give me the power
I need to end this madness.
[BABY VEGETA] It's time finish
this once and for all.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU panting]
[heart beating]
[OLD KAI mumbling]
Old Kai! Come quickly!
It's Goku. He's changing!
[OLD KAI]
He's what?!
[BOTH cheering]
It's beginning! Oh yes,
it's finally beginning!
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU growling]
No! It can't be!
[GORILLA GOKU growling]
[BABY VEGETA] He's changing into
the same kind of dirty animal
that devastated my people.
But... but it makes no sense!
There needs to be a full moon
for this kind of
transformation to happen!
It... can't be!
[BABY VEGETA] He's using the
earth in place of the full moon!
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
[NARRATOR] After an
excruciating training session,
Goku's hidden powers have
finally risen to the surface.
Will Goku's transformation
be the final push he needs
to topple Baby for good?
Find out the fate of
humanity's last hope
on the next Dragon Ball GT!