All right! Are we ready?
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT...
Earth was a mere two
weeks away from exploding.
In a last ditch effort,
Goku and his friends used
every ounce of their powers
to move all the people of
Earth to the Tuffle planet.
[PICCOLO]
It's okay, Gohan.
I know now that it was
meant to be this way.
Sometimes we have to look beyond
what we want and do what's best.
It's time, my friend!
[PICCOLO yelling]
[ALL gasping, yelping]
Piccolo!
Piccolo, don't leave us.
[NARRATOR]
With the noble death of Piccolo,
the Black Star Dragon Balls
became nothing more
than ordinary rocks.
And the Earth was returned
to its previous glory
by a wish on the
Namekian Dragon Balls.
It is a time of
new opportunities,
today on Dragon Ball GT!
[CROWD murmuring]
[CROWD cheering]
Goku! Goku!
The World Martial
Arts Tournament.
Of all the weird
stuff in the world,
I never thought I'd be back
here competing as a kid again.
[CHARLIE growling]
[GOKU giggling]
[CHARLIE chuckling]
[CHARLIE groaning]
[GOKU laughing]
Sorry about that.
Like all kids, I can get
distracted with daydreaming.
Now, let's get started.
[CHARLIE screaming]
[ANNOUNCER] And the
winner of the first round
in our junior division is Goku!
Goku! Goku! Goku! Goku!
That's kind of strange.
I didn't even touch him.
[GOKU] Yeah, now that's
what I call a fight!
Hey! So you guys made it.
[KRILLIN] Yeah, but we already
missed your first fight.
Why didn't you tell us you were
competing in the
junior division, Goku?
I didn't know.
[HERCULE depressed]
Oh...
[HERCULE]
Now that Buu's gone,
there's no real competition
out there anymore.
Man, am I depressed.
Maybe it's time
to call it quits
on this whole
World Champion thing.
[GOKU]
Hey, there, Mr. Satan.
I think something is
wrong with your contest.
[HERCULE]
What do you mean by that, Goku?
Well, I mean Pan is
fighting the adults
and I'm fighting the children.
But I'm not a kid,
and she's not an adult.
Oh, that's right.
Well Goku, the
divisions are determined
by the height of the fighters.
If you were a
centimeter taller,
you'd only barely make
the adult division.
And Pan is just a
little bigger than you.
Yeah, I guess you have a point.
There are height limits,
so I figure I'll just have
to fight at half strength.
Should be fun.
[KRILLIN laughing]
Wow, he really duped you.
Those aren't the rules.
Mr. Satan made them up.
Come on!
He'd much rather see
his granddaughter
win this competition
than you, Goku.
So, if Dad were to
enter as an adult,
Pan would have less of a
chance to emerge the victor.
Of course, that's just like
my father to fix a fight.
[GOKU] It's not that, Videl.
He just wants the best for Pan.
Why don't we watch
the tournament and
cheer on like a good
family should, okay?
[GIANT growling]
You've got to be kidding.
[PAN yelps]
[WOMAN screaming]
[GIANT cackling]
[GIANT gasps]
[PAN grunting]
Didn't your mother teach you to
treat a lady better than this?
[PAN yelling]
[ANNOUNCER]
And Pan is the winner!
Watch out for this
young lady, folks!
She stands a very good chance
of taking home the championship!
I hope that in the next round
you'll find someone who
is more of a challenge.
[PAPAYA MAN panting]
[BOXER yelping]
[BOTH grunting]
[ANNOUNCER]
And Papaya Man is the winner!
[GOTEN]
Sorry about the wait.
Oh, a ham sandwich.
I've never had
one of these before.
It's called a hamburger.
It smells good.
And he just stood there!
[THAT GUY]
Well, of course he did.
He was fighting in the
adult division last time.
[VALESE] I don't see a
knife or fork on the plate.
How do they expect
me to eat this?
Ah, yes. Allow me
to demonstrate.
[VALESE]
Goten, look who's on TV.
There's a rumor floating around
that you're going to retire
after today's competition.
Is this the case?
Well, I'm getting old.
I have to face that.
I can't be World Champ forever.
That's why after today's
contest I will retire
and the champion
will take my place.
[ANNOUNCER]
This is shocking news
that you will only find here--
No! He can't retire!
[THAT GUY]
Ah, you know athletes.
He'll be back in a year or two.
[GOTEN] And as long
as I don't compete,
I don't have to take his place.
[TRUNKS] It is my duty
to inform you gentlemen,
that I retire today!
[EXECUTIVES]
What? Don't quit!
We need you, sir!
[TRUNKS]
Uh, well...
I, uh, I've-I've
given it some thought--
[ANNOUNCER] To recap,
Mr. Satan has announced
that he will retire at the
end of today's championship.
Oh, wow. I had no idea.
[EXECUTIVES clamoring]
As long as that
has them occupied,
I'll slip out of here.
[EXECUTIVES clamoring]
I have to get there
before it's over.
[WRESTLER groaning]
[ANNOUNCER] And Pan moves
on to the semi-finals!
[PAN]
No challenge at all.
Pan, I'm curious.
Of all the entrants today
you are the one person
it seems could come out on top.
Care to comment?
What? About taking over my
gramp's title? I don't know.
Oh no, I don't want
to have a moustache!
[HERCULE]
Oh, yeah. That's the spot.
My back's been killin' me!
So, you're not gonna
watch the bout?
Why would I?
My little Pan's gonna win
the championship for sure.
Right after she pounds
all those other chumps
into the dirt.
Hey, watch it! That hurts!
[knocking]
Ah, Mr. Satan, we have
the lineup for the semi-finals.
[HERCULE]
Ah, let's see here.
We got Papaya Man, Madd Chili,
Super-One, Matt Cat...
Hey! What about Pan?
Huh? Where's her name?
[MONK]
I'm sorry, sir.
But your granddaughter forfeited
her place in the draw.
She said she had a tummy ache.
That really hurts, sir.
Forfeit?
Sorry.
[VEGETA]
No one in this competition
deserves to take
Satan's place.
They better allow late
entries into this contest
or they'll have big
problems on their hands.
So, what was it that made
you forfeit the match?
You knew you were
going to win, didn't you?
Yeah. But this young lady
has bigger plans for her life
than being a multi-millionaire
fighting champion.
Look at Goku,
fighting like a champ
even though there's no
prize at the end of the road.
That's so him.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
the junior division, final bout!
Now welcome, Goku!
And in this corner, Mugley!
[MUGLEY whimpering]
[MUGLEY shrieking]
[ANNOUNCER] Now, boys, let's
get this match underway!
[MONK B] But the deadline to
enter the fight has passed!
[MONK C] If he gets to enter
the fight, then so do I!
[MONK B]
Don't you start with me!
[MONK C]
Get out of my way!
[MONKS groaning]
Oh, hi Vegeta!
Why don't you fight
a worthy opponent?
It's not my job to
pick the opponents,
so I gotta fight him first.
[MUGLEY whimpering]
A crying... boy?
How did he make it this far?
This is the kid's division.
[MUGLEY whimpering]
[MUGLEY shrieking]
[MUGLEY yells]
He's out! Mugley wins!
[GOKU]
Not yet!
Would you give me a
second to hop back up there?
[MUGLEY gruting]
[GOKU laughing, grunting]
[GOKU laughing]
Now that one was out
of the ring for sure!
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mugley wins!
[CROWD chanting]
Mugley! Mugley! Mugley!
Yea! Uh-huh!
Oh yeah! That's right!
He won!
I guess I had to lose sometime.
I can't believe it.
This is simply embarrassing.
We will begin the semi-finals
in the adult division very soon.
Until then, don't forget to
visit our concession stands
to stock up on lollipops,
foot long dogs, and sodas,
all at reasonable prices.
Looks like I made it
just in the nick of time.
[thumping]
Wonder what that is.
[VEGETA]
You're all mine! You hear me?
I'm going to win this fight!
See ya, Dad. This looks like
one of those private moments.
[VEGETA] No one can stand
against a warrior this focused!
[ANNOUNCER] Your first
competitor in the semi-finals
is the masterful Madd Chili!
[CROWD cheering]
Competitor two is the quick
and colorful Papaya Man!
[CROWD cheering]
Oh, hey! Hey, Trunks! Over here!
[TRUNKS]
This is the finals, right?
I don't see Goku or Pan
down there, anywhere.
[PAN]
Surprise!
Care for a lollipop?
What are you doing here?
[TRUNKS] So, who is this
Papaya Man character
I've been hearing about
since I got here?
[KRILLIN]
He's looking good.
Up to now, he's won most of his
fights with a single punch.
[TRUNKS] Sounds like he
would have given Pan
a run for her money.
Let the first round begin!
[MADD CHILI grunting]
[MADD CHILI groaning]
[MADD CHILI]
That was fast.
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] You saw it folks!
Papaya Man is your champion!
[PAN] He's tough, but he
couldn't beat my other grandpa.
What are you talking about,
Pan? He's stronger than that.
He's only using one-billionth
his actual strength.
And I suppose that you
know who he really is.
[GOKU] Hey, Majuub! Cut the
act! Take off your mask!
[ALL]
What a sec. That's Majuub!
[HERCULE]
Papaya Man is the champion?!
Did you see what he was wearing?
A kid with taste like that
can't make this
outfit look good.
And now, the round you've
all been waiting for.
It's time for your World
Martial Arts Champion, Majuub,
to take the stage one last time.
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and Gentlemen,
it is both my duty
and my sheer pleasure
to introduce you to
the one, the only,
Mr. Satan!
[HERCULE]
Mr. Satan is on the scene
and he's ready to rock! Yes!
Where's Papaya Man?
[ANNOUNCER] Majuub is Papaya
Man. He was wearing a mask.
Uh okay.
Majuub, I wish you a good fight.
Thanks, sir. You, too.
[MAJUUB] I've finally done it.
I am going to fight Mr. Satan.
I hope you're
watching this, Mom.
[ANNOUNCER]
The fight is now underway!
[MAJUUB] I'll give him a
fight he'll never forget!
You're starting
kinda fast there--
[HERCULE groaning]
Majuub's pretty intense!
I guess he's really
taking this fight seriously.
Why isn't Mr. Satan moving?
[MAJUUB]
Now to finish him off!
[HERCULE screaming]
You no beat Mr. Satan.
[BUU]
You are fighting Earth's hero.
How would all the people
feel if he lost this fight?
What? What's he--
[HERCULE]
Are you makin' fun of me?
I'll show you!
[HERCULE grunting]
[MAJUUB groaning]
[ANNOUNCER] Majuub is out
of the ring! Mr. Satan wins!
Coming as no surprise to
any tournament fan here,
Mr. Satan is still
your champion!
I actually won against Majuub.
I didn't know I
still had it in me.
I'm the champion of the world!
[CROWD cheering]
With that win
I can truly retire.
[CROWD cheering]
[GOKU]
Why so glum?
You should be proud of
the way you handled
that match, Majuub.
Thanks for letting
my gramps win.
I know it means
the world to him.
It wasn't like that.
Buu came to me and explained
why I should let him win.
It's no use being
modest, Majuub.
We can all see
right through you.
[ALL]
Bye-Bye!
He told me Mr. Satan
is the world's hero.
[HERCULE]
Okay, okay!
I won't retire!
I promise you all!
There will be many happy
returns to the ring for me!
I'm glad I could help you out,
Mr. World Champion.
[GOKU] I gotta say, it was
a pretty good tournament.
But most of the guys out there
would be ten times as strong
if they just trained some more.
Then, I guess I should
train twice as hard now.
I don't want any
of them beating me.
[KRILLIN] You really think
one of those puny guys
are a threat to you?
[VEGETA] Especially when
there's a real threat
standing right here.
I'd say playtime is over.
Okay, it's been a
while since we did this.
[BOTH grunting]
[PAN] We're on a
bridge, Grandpa!
[TRUNKS] Yeah,
Father cut it out!
[growling]
Sorry, but do you mind
if we continue this
after I get something to eat?
[ALL groaning]
[VEGETA laughing]
[NARRATOR] Goku proves once
again that of all his powers,
none can hold a candle to
the power of his stomach.
But these good times
can't last forever.
Somewhere in the universe,
an evil force is looming.