[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball GT...
the build-up of
negative energy from
the overuse of the Dragon Balls
resulted in the creation
of the seven Shadow Dragons.
Goku and Pan took it upon
themselves to seek out
the cracked Dragon Balls
in order to restore balance
to the devastated earth.
But with each Dragon Ball comes
a battle with
a different Shadow Dragon!
[NARRATOR] The heroes
succeeded in recovering
three of the seven
Dragon Balls,
but not before facing down
three of the deadliest creatures
ever spawned by the universe.
[GOKU]
Ka, me, ha, me... Ha!
I will enjoy burying you.
[NARRATOR] There are still four
more dragons to be defeated,
four more fierce
battles to be waged.
The journey to save the
earth continues today on GT!
[PAN]
I got it!
Wow! That was
really impressive, Pan!
Your very first Kamehameha Wave!
[GIRU] Approaching Dragon Ball!
One kilometer below.
Dragon Ball one kilometer below.
Yeah you say that,
but remember yesterday?
[GIRU] Uh, well...
Yesterday... Um, hmm...
You told us there
was a Dragon Ball
just so you could
stop and take a nap.
What is it today?
[GIRU] No mistake,
no mistake! Dragon Ball below!
You better hope you're right.
Even so, we could
use a break, Pan.
And who knows we
might stumble across
the Dragon Ball
while we're relaxing.
So Giru, you have a lock
on that Dragon Ball yet?
[GIRU] Dragon Ball below.
Dragon Ball below.
What? You mean it's been buried?
[GIRU] Dragon Ball buried.
Dragon Ball below.
I don't think that little guy
has it. Should I dig some more?
[GIRU] Dragon Ball approaching!
Dragon Ball approaching!
[PAN] You walking toaster!
I don't know what kind
of game you're playing,
but I'm sick of it!
[PAN]
Ah Grandpa! It's an earthquake!
It doesn't feel
like an earthquake.
[GIRU] Approaching! Approaching!
Dragon Ball approaching!
What in the world is that?
[GIRU] Dragon Ball approaching!
Dragon Ball approaching!
[NATURON SHENRON]
♪ I love digging a hole, yeah, ♪
♪ love digging a hole, when
I'm making earthquakes, ♪
♪ and the ground
starts to shake, ♪
Pan, do you hear singing?
If you want to
call that singing!
[NATURON SHENRON] ♪ causing
panic and destruction's ♪
♪ my goal, dig-diggin' around, ♪
♪ shakin' up all
the loose ground, ♪
♪ where rocks and debris... ♪
[GIRU] Dragon Ball approaching!
Dragon Ball approaching!
[NATURON SHENRON] ♪ and, uh... ♪
[NATURON SHENRON]
And, uh...
Earthquakes rule!
[NATURON SHENRON yawning]
That's one big gopher!
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru.
A giant weasel is more like it!
What a gorgeous piece of work!
Sometimes, I even
impress myself.
Is it me, or does it seem
like he doesn't even see us?
Maybe he just
can't hear too well.
Hello!
[GOKU] Are we gonna fight
each other or not?!
So, I guess you can hear me.
Uh... Yes, I can hear you.
You know it's rude
to not answer
when someone asks
you a question.
And you would be...
[GOKU]
You don't know who I am?
My name is Goku!
You should have known that I was
on my way here to challenge you.
Wow! This guy is
really thick headed.
You have the Seven-Star
Dragon Ball on your forehead.
You have to be the next dragon.
I'm Naturon Shenron. I thought
that was a secret. Who told you?
No one. It's just that you have
that Dragon Ball on your head.
Now that we know you're
the dragon we're after...
...I'll wait right here.
I'll even let you
have the first attack.
So, what are you saying?
Whoa! You're a weird one!
We've been fighting
battle after battle with
all of the other dragons, trying
to get the Dragon Balls back.
Aren't you clued into anything?
Oh man! This is irritating!
Well, sorry.
I'm not much of a fighter.
Fine. Then why don't
you just hand it over.
[NATURON SHENRON] Because it's
mine and I don't want to.
Oh, give me a break!
All I want to do is to dig
and make the earthquakes happen
and watch everything fall apart.
And it's a big job so
I better get to it.
Now, which way
was I going? Oh yeah.
Hey! Wait a second!
Where do you think you're going?
He's gone!
[NATURON SHENRON]
♪ I'm diggin' a hole! ♪
[GIRU] Giru, Giru!
Dragon Ball retreating!
Dragon Ball retreating! Giru!
Wait, Grandpa!
If he digs too deep we
might not find him again.
[NATURON SHENRON]
♪ Causing panic and... ♪
Yeah! Oh yeah!
Grandpa, get down there
and finish him off!
It doesn't feel right...
I'm not the kind of
guy who picks a fight
with someone who doesn't
want to fight back.
Then you better come up
with some other kind of plan.
We need that Dragon Ball.
Yeah, I guess
maybe you're right.
I got it!
I'll go say some things to
him to get him all worked up!
Hey! Naturon Shenron!
When's the last time
you took a bath?
You smell like a pile
of rotting seaweed!
[GOKU] Either that or
a piece of cheese
that's been left
in the sun too long!
Either he's got a lot
of dirt in his ears,
or I'm gonna have to find
another way to
get his attention.
[PAN] Don't worry.
I'll take care of this guy!
What? Do you know a
technique that I don't?
[PAN]
Nothing out of the ordinary!
Ha!
[PAN yelling]
Pan, that's enough!
You could damage the Dragon Ball
by showing off like that, Pan.
[GIRU]
Pan wreckless! Pan wreckless!
[GOKU gasps]
Oh, no!
If he causes an earthquake,
all of the people in
that city could be killed!
We have to get down
there and help them.
We're in a hurry, Giru, so
you better get in the backpack.
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru,...
What's happening?!
[PEOPLE screaming]
We've still got enough
time to save them.
Look out!
Thank you, deary. Would you
mind running me home?
I have to water the dogs
and make Stan his supper.
I'm really sorry, ma'am,
but I'm kind of in
the middle of something.
[BUS DRIVER gasps]
[KIDS laughing]
[GOKU]
There you go!
[BUS DRIVER]
What a nice boy!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yells]
[PAN]
A little help!
[SS4 GOKU] Don't worry.
I'll take care of it!
[PEOPLE cheering]
[GOKU yelling]
Awesome, Grandpa! You did it!
The ground fit right
back into place.
Now, let's see what
kind of destruction
I've caused to that city.
I bet it's been
reduced to rubble.
[SS4 GOKU]
Well, It seems things are doing
alright up here. No
buildings have fallen.
Looks like we did it, huh?
[PEOPLE yelping]
[PAN gasps]
Hey! It was you who
stopped my beautiful rampage!
So... Are you finally
in the mood to battle?
Either that or
he's gonna eat us.
I dug all those tunnels because
I wanted to cause an earthquake.
And then you had to run around
with your good intentions and
ruin everything that I
had worked so hard for!
[PAN screams]
[PAN groans]
[NATRUON SHENRON groaning]
[SS4 GOKU grunting]
[NATURON SHENRON groaning]
[PAN groaning]
Not bad.
[SS4 GOKU chuckling]
[SS4 GOKU]
When you get all worked up,
you're a pretty good fighter.
It's really too bad it takes
so much to get you in the mood.
When I'm angry,
I am ten times the
fighter you just fought.
So... You never told
us which wish it was
that brought you
into existence.
[NATURON SHENRON]
Do you remember
the evil wizard, Babidi?
He took control of Vegeta at the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
I was born of the wish that
restored the innocent lives
that Vegeta stole that day!
Look out!
Eternal Dragon... By your
name I summon you forth!
That sounds kind of dramatic.
The last dragon was born
from a wish for underwear.
You see, that's
exactly the kind of
ignorance I've come to
expect from you people.
[SS4 GOKU shouts]
[PAN screaming]
[SS4 GOKU shouting]
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
See that? That's what I like to
call the Aftershock Technique.
No one can handle a concentrated
blast of energy from below.
Everyone gets blown away!
[SS4 GOKU]
Well, I have to admit it...
As far as dragons go, you're
the most interesting so far.
Why thank you.
And as far a little boys
who turn into grown men go,
you're interesting too.
That technique you
just used couldn't work
if your opponent is
in the air, could it?
[NATURON SHENRON gasps]
[PAN] Oh, my! Guess I hit
the bullseye, again.
Ok, you got me there.
But don't think that flying
people like yourselves
are out from
behind enemy lines!
[NATURON SHENRON grunting]
This attack isn't that bad.
It's kind of like playing
dodge ball at school.
What's wrong with you?
Why do you keep
making fun of me?
I'll show you what kind of
dragon you're dealing with!
We're up here.
Come on Naturon,
give us your best shot!
Get off my head,
I'm trying to concentra--
[NATURON SHENRON yelling]
[PAN] Oh, man! That's the
oldest trick in the book.
I'd love to keep playing,
but it's time to bring
this fight to a close.
To be... beaten... by...
my own technique.
How embarrassing.... it... is.
[NATURON SHENRON groans]
Well, that's a
little anticlimactic.
Do you think he's got
another round in him?
And just like that,
the Seven-Star Ball is ours!
[PAN screaming]
[GOKU]
Pan!
[PAN]
Grandpa!
Pan... Hold on!
Come... on...
[PAN screaming]
Pan, what's going on?
Where'd you go?
[GIRU]
Pan, danger! Giru, Giru...
[PAN screaming]
Pan, where are you?
[GOKU]
You gotta be kidding me.
Whoa! Now that's a dragon!
[SUPER NATURON SHENRON cackling]
You gullible little
muscle-head. You fell for it.
Didn't it seem kind of easy
beating a Shadow Dragon?
I staged it all.
[GOKU]
You staged it?
What... What do you mean?
I saw you blow yourself up.
You can't stand up
to that kind of hit.
Apparently I can.
It was the mole that
couldn't hold up.
He was my transport then,
but now I've got
your precious Pan.
No way!
You mean you're
using Pan... as your body?
That's right. And I'm
not going to fight you
the way the other dragons did.
Oh I'll beat you, but I'll let
you wear out this body first.
But... But why
would you do that?
Because a Super Saiyan Four
would be a much nicer fit!
[PAN]
Grandpa! Help me!
Pan!
[PAN] I can't see anything!
You have to help me! Please!
That's it! No one messes
with my granddaughter.
Well... It must be time to start
that second round. Let's rumble!
The power you had earlier
has all but vanished.
Why don't you turn
back into the red monkey
and we'll really
get this party started.
Stop using my
granddaughter as a shield
and I'll fight you in a fair
battle, you rotten dragon!
[NARRATOR] For a moment,
Goku and Pan seemed to
have claimed victory yet again.
But with his sneaky move,
Naturon Shenron was able
to take over Pan's body.
Will Goku even be able to fight?
Or will this evil dragon accept
the offer to battle Goku
on an even playing field?
Find out on the next
episode of Dragon Ball GT!