[NARRATOR]
On the last Dragon Ball GT...
Super Saiyan Four Goku found
his energy completely used up.
Powerless to defend himself,
the mighty Saiyan lay helpless
before the monstrous Baby,
who had used Vegeta's body
to transform into a giant ape!
[TRUNKS]
That's close enough, Baby!
[NARRATOR] Freed from the
evil Tuffles control,
Trunks appeared in
the knick of time,
but his best efforts
were in vain!
[SS4 GOKU] Hurry! We don't
have much time! Come on!
Even though Kibito
Kai had restored
Gohan, Trunks,
and Goten to health,
Goku knew that they
were no match for Baby!
[SS4 GOKU]
Thanks son.
[NARRATOR] Their only hope was a
fully powered Super Saiyan Four!
But transferring their energy
to Goku would take time!
Something they did not have!
But deep within Baby's body lies
the answer to their problem!
[BABY]
What's happening to me?
[NARRATOR] Majuub
transformed from tasty treat
to gastrointestinal nightmare,
buying Goku the
diversion he needed!
[MAJUUB]
Goku! Hurry!
Stand firm, guys!
Let's do this!
Dad! Are you ready yet?
Almost there!
Just a little more!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[MAN A]
Baby! Protect us, please!
[PAN]
Grandpa?
[HERCULE]
I can't watch!
[BABY] Impressive! But you're
still no match for me!
You don't realize who I am!
You see the stream before you
and mistake that for the source!
This form is nothing, Baby!
Just the tip of the iceberg!
[BABY] Spare me the
mystic mumbo jumbo!
The mightiest will triumph!
Darkness isn't
mightier than light!
[SS4 GOKU grunting]
[BABY GORILLA growling]
[BABY GORILLA panting]
[SS4 GOKU panting]
Could you guys tell
who had the advantage?
I could barely follow
their movements!
They seemed about even
from what I could see!
Yeah, but my dad has
suffered a lot more damage!
That might give
Baby the upper hand!
What are you guys talking about?
Grandpa's going to beat him
no matter what! He has to!
[OLD KAI]
Hm...
[KIBITO] Ancestor! I didn't
miss anything, did I?
They're evenly matched, this
should be the best fight ever!
[OLD KAI]
This isn't a sporting event!
The fate of the Universe
is resting on this fight,
you dimwit!
[OLD KAI] We should be
thinking of constructive ways
to use our power!
Any ideas, Kibito?
I know! We could start by
reviving the Earth's populace!
Yes! The Sacred Water!
Of course!
[OLD KAI] Yeah! Now you're
thinking like a Kai!
While Goku's taking
care of the hen,
we'll take care of the eggs!
[KIBITO] Precisely! I'll make
the necessary arrangements!
[BABY] How can he
be fully recuperated
after being injured so badly?
Light breaks the darkness!
This form is my instrument!
I have no limits!
[BABY]
What are you talking about?
[SS4 GOKU] Your day in the
sun has run its course!
It ends here, like it
was always meant to be.
[BABY] I should have
finished you off before!
You were as good as dead!
This time I'll see it
through to the end!
Super Gallic Gun!
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[SS4 GOKU] Nice shot!
That would have really hurt
if you had hit me!
[BABY] What? Curse you!
How did you avoid that?
[SS4 GOKU]
It's never too late to change!
You could give up this fight
right now and go in peace!
[BABY]
Peace?! Here's your peace!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
Wooo!
Wow! That's some serious
firepower alright!
He must be desperate.
[BABY] No one makes a
fool out of me, Goku!
I'll vaporize you
into nothingness!
Taste the hateful power of
darkness! Revenge Death Ball!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[SS4 GOKU gasps]
[BABY] Can you make
it out, Super Saiyan?
Can you see your death?
[BABY]
Yes!
He's taking that thing head on!
Grandpa, no!
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
I've got to do something!
Pan! Wait!
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[BABY]
I have him! He's mine!
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[BABY]
No one escapes my Death Ball!
You'll lose your sanity
and die of terror
long before your
body disintegrates!
[SS4 GOKU] No! This cannot break
me! I am beyond this pain!
I won't give in to this!
Gohan! Goten! Pan! Trunks!
I love you too much!
I will not let him hurt you!
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[SS4 GOKU screaming]
[BABY]
No! What's happening?
[SS4 GOKU screaming]
[BABY] My Death Ball!
What's he doing to it?
[BABY]
How?! How did you do that?
That was enough power to
reduce this planet to ashes!
It's over! I can't permit
you to harm anyone else!
[BABY] You should be
dead! What are you?!
I am the answer.
The answer to all that is evil.
[BABY]
I hate you!
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me... Ha!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[ALL shriek]
[MAJUUB]
Come on!
[PAN]
Let me see!
Wow, it's kind of sad, isn't it?
No way! You wouldn't be saying
that if he stood up again, Pan!
I knew you could do it,
Grandpa! You're the one!
[PAN] That big, ugly
monster never stood
a chance against you!
You're the greatest!
[GOHAN] Wait, guys. If Baby
dies, that means Vegeta dies.
Huh? Oh, no!
It's okay. It has to be. That's
the way my dad would want it.
It's better than
being used by Baby!
We're prepared to do
whatever Goku wants!
[PAN sobbing]
[TRUNKS]
He blasted his tail off!
[BABY GORILLA groaning]
[BABY] It's no use! Vegeta's
losing all of his power!
How could this be happening?
Together we were invincible!
Darn that accursed Saiyan!
[PAN gasps]
There he is!
Baby! You coward!
Get back here right now!
[HERCULE] Come on, you little
jumping bean! Fight like a man!
[HERCULE]
Oh, no! Not again! B-Baby!
Gohan! Goten! How about
a little help over here!
The Champ's gettin'
a little old for this!
[BABY growls]
[PAN]
Grandpa! Baby's getting away!
[SS4 GOKU]
I'm more concerned about Vegeta!
[TRUNKS]
Dad! Are you okay?
Lie still.
[VEGETA]
Trunks...
I'm right here, Father.
[PAN sniffles]
Lord Baby!
[BABY BULMA] We're prepared
to fight until the end, Baby!
We might not win, but we'll show
them what Tuffles are made of!
[BABY]
Get out of my way!
Idiot!
[BABY BULMA coughing]
Baby! Take me with you!
[TRUNKS] Baby's on there
alright! I can sense him!
[PAN] You're not gonna let him
escape! Are you, Grandpa?
No, Pan. Don't worry.
[BABY] Fools! You haven't
seen the last of me!
[SS4 GOKU]
Perfect, any second now.
Right on schedule!
Ka... Me... Ha... Me... Ha!
[BABY]
What's going on?
No! This-this
can't be happening!
[BABY screaming]
[SS4 GOKU] His energy signal has
disappeared! It's finally over!
[GOHAN]
That ought to do it!
Baby's cells were
destroyed in the Sun.
He won't be able to regenerate.
Woo-hoo!
Grandpa!
[PAN] You just refuse to grow
up, don't you, Grandpa?
Couldn't you have just
stayed as a Super Saiyan Four?
[GOKU] What's wrong
with the way I am?
I guess nothing, I'll take
you any way I can get you.
But not, Grandma!
I'm sure she wants her
full-sized husband back!
I guess you're right!
Oh, well, I can transform into
Super Saiyan Four anytime!
Oh? Is that right?
So, when we have
Grandparents' Day at school,
can you transform
so you're full grown?
I'll think about it!
[ALL laughing]
Hey, before I forget,
we'd better disperse this
to the rest of the Earth!
A light mist ought
to do the trick!
Would you like to do
the honors, Dende?
Sure!
While you're treating
the people here,
I'll go to Planet Tuffle and
get that mess straightened out!
Hey, Gohan! Would you
mind giving me a hand?
No, I'd love to, Kibito Kai.
[PEOPLE groaning]
[KRILLIN groaning]
[MARRON groaning]
[KRILLIN] Whoa! How did I get
here? I must have blacked out!
[GOKU] Ah, now this is the
way it's supposed to be!
What in the world is going on?
I don't know.
[POPO]
It's been almost a year since
the Black Star Dragon Balls
were used!
The Earth is about to blow up!
What?! But we brought
the Black Star balls
back to Earth, Mister Popo!
Remember?!
[POPO] I would never forget
something so important!
[DENDE] Obviously you did
since Earth is still here,
but I just can't remember
what happened next.
[GOKU] I handed
them right to you!
Where did you put them, Dende?
[DENDE]
I-I don't remember!
Are you crazy? How
could you forget?!
You're right!
I must be going crazy!
We must have already
been infected
when Goku gave us
the Dragon Balls!
Yes! I remember now!
I had the Dragon Balls
and I gave them to Baby!
Time must have reset
after Baby's wish!
[DENDE] What have I done?
I've failed the Earth!
I don't deserve to be
Guardian anymore!
It's okay.
But we'd better figure
out exactly how much
time we have left so we
can come up with a plan!
Hang on, I'm figuring it out.
This is bad, you guys!
We've got exactly two weeks
until the Earth blows up!
[ALL gasp]
[NARRATOR] Before our heroes
had time to celebrate
their victory over Baby,
an even greater
threat has emerged!
With just two weeks to
search the entire galaxy
for the
Black Star Dragon Balls,
what hope does the Earth
have for survival?
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next Dragon Ball GT!