[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball GT,
the Doctor was giving Trunks
a dose of evil medicine,
but it was Baby who
wrote the prescription!
Fortunately, Goku was there to
put an end to the malpractice.
You shouldn't have picked
a doctor to hide in.
I'm on guard
against them as it is!
[NARRATOR] But the
scheming Neo-mutant
wasn't about to surrender!
What he lacked in terms
of power, he intended to steal!
And in a flash,
he hijacked the body of Trunks
right before their very eyes!
[BABY as Trunks] I've never felt
anything like this before!
This is the Saiyan
power I desire!
[BABY as Trunks growls]
[GOKU yelps]
Goodbye! Not even you can block
this blast from
point-blank range!
[PAN]
Trunks! Don't do it!
[TRUNKS yells]
Get out of my body!
[GOKU] That's it, Trunks!
Don't give in!
[NARRATOR] Unable to
withstand the sheer magnitude
of the Super Saiyan energy,
Baby made his escape
and Trunks regained control
of his body once and for all!
[GOKU]
He did it!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
The battle for
the body had been won,
but the war for the
world was about to begin!
[BABY]
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
[birds tweeting]
[water running]
[GOTEN] You have one of the
prettiest faces I've ever seen,
and that's the truth!
No, really! I'm serious!
What? Why haven't I told you?
Because this is the first
time since I've known you
that you haven't
had a boyfriend!
[BULMA giggles]
Please tell me!
Why can't he go after a girl
who hasn't had any boyfriends?
I married
my first boyfriend!
Huh? Seriously?
That's really sweet.
Hey! Let's go out!
If you're not too busy,
we could meet up
somewhere right now!
[GOTEN] No! I don't think it's
too sudden! Let's go for it!
Oh, my word! Doesn't this
generation have any humility?
[GOTEN]
Where? I don't know.
You name the place,
and I'll be there!
Yeah. Right. I know the spot.
Sounds good, Valese!
[GOTEN]
I'll see you in a few! Huh?
Yeah! Of course, I do!
Okay, cool! Ciao!
[GOTEN]
Bye, Mom! Bye, Bulma!
Go get her, tiger!
Goten! Be careful how you
act around those city women!
Huh? Mom, gimme a break!
Hey, Vegeta! What's up?
See ya later! I've got a date!
[VEGETA]
Goten! Just a second!
Notice anything...
different? Huh?
Uh, whatd'ya mean?
[VEGETA] Well, hey, uh,
I've really gotta boogie!
This is one girl you
don't want to keep waiting!
[VEGETA growls]
Well, well! Don't you look
especially handsome today, hun!
Why, thank you!
Notice anything different
about Vegeta today, ChiChi?
[CHICHI]
Huh.
I shaved my mustache, you idiot!
He thinks it should
be front-page news.
Huh. Did he shave it
for any special reason?
You could say that.
Look, Dad!
That mustache has got to go!
It makes you look
like a total geek!
Total geek...
Total geek... Total geek...
[BULMA and CHICHI laughing]
You should have seen
the look on his face!
[BULMA] My very own
Saiyan Prince!
Earthling women!
[BULMA] Do you ever
think about them, Chichi?
How they're doing up there?
[CHICHI] Of course. Every minute
of every day. And you know what?
I don't care if they
don't make it back in time.
I don't care if the
world disintegrates!
I just want
my Pan to be okay.
I kind of know
what you mean.
I miss Trunks, but hey...
Goku's up there!
It'll all work out!
I hope so. But he's just
a boy now, not a man.
Remember?
[BULMA]
Yeah, that's true,
but that never stopped
him in the old days.
I'm sure they're just fine.
[GOKU grimacing]
[CAT snoring]
He scored! All right!
[GOKU giggles]
Careful! Hey!
Easy, Grandpa!
[GOKU giggles]
[GOKU yelps]
[TRUNKS and PAN yell]
[CAT yells]
[GOKU stammers]
[GOKU giggles uncomfortably]
Nice kitty!
[CAT growls]
[PAN] Grandpa!
Are you crazy?
You're going to
get us all killed!
[ALL panting]
Trunks! I don't think
we have a choice!
You'd better give
this back to him!
Are you out of your mind?
I'm not giving it back!
You give it back!
You're the one who took it!
[CAT growls]
Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru...
Giru?
[GOKU] Here it is, you guys!
The 7-star Dragonball!
Awesome! Just two more to go!
Two more, then
we're homeward bound!
Yeah! Let's round 'em up!
[MOM]
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
[GIRL] She was like: No way!
And I was like: Get real!
[explosion]
[MAN yells]
[PEOPLE screaming in terror]
[MAN]
My convertible!
Huh?
Who the heck is he?
Are you here to make
a deposit or to die!
Neither!
Now tell me
where the Saiyans live!
Hey! B-b-boss!
Look! I don't
know any Saiyans!
Who are they?
I'll help you find 'em!
Boss! Are you okay?
[CROOKS yelling]
[explosion]
[VALESE]
Be careful, Goten!
[GOTEN]
I will! Don't worry!
Voila! One sugar cone!
You're teasing me.
No spoon?
Uh, it's a cone! You don't
need a spoon, silly!
Oh, I've never eaten
ice cream like this!
Doesn't it make your
fingers real sticky?
You're kidding, right?
You don't use fingers!
Huh? Oh, Well, how
do you eat it then?
Well, you just keep
licking it like this!
Oh, gosh,
I'm really embarrassed.
You lick it, huh?
Oh, okay then.
[GOTEN thinking]
She's so innocent and sweet!
[explosion]
[VALESE gasps]
What's happening, Goten?
I'm not sure!
Maybe it's a festival.
Maybe! I like the way
you look at things, Valese!
[GOTEN giggles]
I mean, it's just
that you're so positive!
Whatd'ya say
we eat our cones?
Sure!
[GOTEN laughs]
[MAN yells]
[glass shatters]
[PEOPLE gasp]
[PEOPLE yell]
[MYSTERY MAN]
Hold it, right there!
[BLONDE DUDE]
Hmm?
[RANDOM GUY]
A voice! From the sky!
[MYSTERMAN] Violence will not
take root in my peaceful city!
Those who sow the seeds
of discord will be punished,
while the innocent
will be protected!
Up there!
I, Hercule,
will drive out the wicked,
while the weak shall
take shelter under my wing!
There's no light brighter than
the limelight, I always say!
[HERCULE whimpering]
[HERCULE laughing]
Kicking me while I was landing!
What a cheap shot!
Wow! I didn't even
see that! Did you?
No! But these guys are on
a whole different level than us!
Whoa! What a
lightning fast kick!
I'm not so sure, man.
It kinda looked like he just
tripped over himself to me.
All right, you!
Where do you get off?
Taking your violent temper
out on innocent bystanders!
How dare you do that in my city!
Leave!
Get out of here now...
or deal with me,
The Martial Arts
Champion of the World!
[PEOPLE chanting]
Hercule! Hercule! Hercule!
Well! Come on!
What's it gonna be, big guy?
Your choice! Leave here
peacefully or face the music!
It depends.
Are you a Saiyan?
What? What do you
know about Saiyans?
You don't know how to fight
using light tricks like them!
Or do you?
Well, you tell me.
[HERCULE yells]
[explosion]
[PEOPLE screaming]
So, your boyfriends never
bought you an ice cream cone?
This is the first date
I've ever been on, you silly!
My parents never let me
go out with my boyfriends!
I was too young!
Really? Wow! I must be the
luckiest guy in the whole world!
[GOTEN] Whatd'ya say
we go get a hamburger?
[VALESE]A hamburger? Do you
eat it with a fork or a spoon?
[GOTEN laughs]
Good one, Valese!
[HERCULE whimpering]
Go on! You're nothing
to me! Beat it!
Y-Yes! Sir!
[GOTEN] Hercule!
Hey! How ya doin'? It's me!
It's been such a long time!
You remember me, don't ya?
I'm Goten,
Gohan's little brother!
[HERCULE laughing]
Now you're gonna get it,
you blue-collared rough neck!
Hey! I'm talkin'
to you, big guy!
My disciple's gonna
tear you apart!
Nice move! You're not as
young as you used to be.
Let your pupil handle
this one! So, where is he?
Yeah. I hope he's well trained,
'cause this guy's huge.
What? No! You mean
I'm your disciple?
What? Since
when? Look...
This guy's nuts.
He's blown up half of downtown.
You can handle him.
Can't you, Goten?
Pretty please!
Listen. First of all,
you didn't teach me, my Dad did!
Secondly, I'm busy
right now. I'm on a big date!
Valese! No!
Are you okay?
[PEOPLE cheering]
[HERCULE laughing]
Good work! That's my boy!
Valese!
You're not hurt, are you?
Did he say
anything improper?
No. Oh, wait a second!
But, he did ask me
where I thought he
could find the Saiyans.
I don't know what Saiyans are!
But I told him to
try the specialty shop!
They have all
kinds of cool stuff!
[GOTEN thinking] Who is this
guy? How does he know about us?
[PEOPLE cheering]
Hercule! Hercule! Hercule!
[GOTEN thinking] There's
something disturbing about this!
What an awesome kick!
What do you expect?
He's been trained by the Champ!
Uh, where you goin'?
Wow, Goten!
You're quite an athlete!
I see! So, you're
with that other fella!
Goten!
Man! What's with these guys?
They're nuts!
Sorry, Valese! Hang tight!
Fancy meeting you here!
Heh, heh! Are you okay?
Oh wow! I've got
goose bumps all over.
In my whole life, you're the
first boy to ever hold me.
Oh, uh, I hope
I didn't offend you!
[HERCULE laughing]
Well, boys!
Hope you learned a lesson.
You beat us to it again.
Nice going, Sir. No problem!
I enjoyed it!
Spread the word!
The Champ is alive and well and
still watching over his city!
And let it be known,
there's still plenty of
mega left in my Megaton Punch!
I don't know how
he does it, I swear!
Right on! Yeah!
[MAN yelling in pain]
[MAN panting]
[MAN yelling]
Hercule... man! He sure knows
how to get a crowd revved up!
Say, did you know
that my older brother
is married to his daughter?
Really?
Uh, huh! My brother, Gohan!
Wait! I'm getting a bad feeling!
What is it, Goten?
I'm not sure!
Look, whoever you are...
Goten! No!
[GOTEN grimaces]
You caught me off guard
there for a second.
Whoa! What's happening?
[MAN laughing]
Huh?
[MAN yelling]
[PEOPLE screaming]
You there.
You're a Saiyan, aren't you?
Maybe, but what business
is that of yours?
Yes, I feel it now.
Your energy signature is
similar to that of Goku.
What? How do you
know my father?
Well, there's a twist!
He's a boy, and yet,
he's your father!
Yes! Very strange!
But hey, I'm not your
average guy either!
Let me be blunt.
I'm here to confiscate
your body. Sound good?
I'd like to use it
to defeat your father.
Hercule! Hey!
This guy's stronger than
anyone that we've faced before!
Do me a favor and take
Valese somewhere safe! Okay?
--Uh, yes! Right away!
--Thanks.
[BABY laughing]
Hey! What's so funny?
I must have missed something.
This is terrible!
How dare you!
I don't know who
you think you are,
but this type of behavior
isn't gonna fly!
If you don't have respect
for the life on this planet,
then I'm going to have
to teach it to you!
[BABY laughs]
[NARRATOR] Unaware that
Baby has made his way to Earth,
Trunks, Goku, and Pan casually
continue their homeward journey!
Goten has laid down the law,
but now that Baby
has further developed,
does he have
the power to enforce it?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball GT!