[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT...
While Goku continued
his training with Old Kai,
Pan, Mr. Satan, and Buu
traveled to Planet Tuffle
in the hopes of finding a way
to defeat the almighty Baby.
[MR. SATAN]
We need a plan!
I've gotcha covered, Gramps!
We're gonna flush 'em out!
[BABY VEGETA] I don't want
her to join us! Kill her!
Dad! Don't do it!
[PAN]
Daddy?
You have to let me go!
[OLD KAI]
I can't Goku! You're not ready!
But she's my granddaughter!
Oh, yes. I'm well aware
of that Goku! I'm sorry!
So, what? We're supposed
to just stand here
and watch those
beasts kill her?
[OLD KAI whimpering]
[NARRATOR] But then, as Pan
was facing certain doom,
someone came out of nowhere
and knocked Baby
Gohan to the ground!
Pan's savior turned out
to be Goku's protégé Uub!
[UUB]
Your conflict is with me now!
That's Uub.
[PAN coughing]
Well, it appears
there is yet another
worthless being that
I failed to infect.
Uub, is it really you?
[UUB] When this
creature came to earth,
everything started to go bad.
So I traveled as deep into
the mountains as I could,
to find a secret place to train.
I had to so I could help
you guys out if you needed.
When I felt Goku's
spirit disappear,
I knew something
terrible had happened.
So I came back. Where is he?
I don't know how to say it.
Say what, Pan?
You're not trying to tell
me that he's dead, are you?
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
Of course that's what
she's saying, you twerp!
I, the honorable Baby,
sent that pathetic Saiyan
to the next world
with my own hands!
What?
I understood him to be the
mightiest Saiyan in the galaxy,
but he died a most
pitiful death.
The poor weakling could
barely stand to put up a fight.
Not Goku...
[GOKU, UUB grunting, yelling]
[UUB]
Thanks, Dende.
Well, Goku,
I can't tell you how much
I appreciate everything.
You've changed my life.
[GOKU]
Hey, don't thank me.
I got just as much out of
it as you did. Trust me!
Really?
[UUB] That's funny, Goku. I'll
see you fellas later. Take care!
See ya, Uub. Let's do this again
sometime! How about next year?
He was my mentor and my friend.
He taught me what he knew
so that one day I could use
it to make things right.
And I will.
Uub, you can't go!
That guy's absorbed the powers
of everybody he's come
in contact with.
He's gonna kill you!
[HERCULE] Pan, no!
[PAN] Let go!
[HERCULE]
Hey, calm down, calm down!
How can I calm down
at a time like this?
[BABY VIDEL]
Relax Pan, it's us.
Now honey,
you know it won't take long for
Baby to get rid of Uub, right?
Listen to your parents.
Now, if you behave
like a good girl,
we'll ask the Honorable Baby
to save you, my dear.
Yes, so why don't you
use your good manners
and come with us
to see Baby right now.
Mama? Papa?
Uub...
[BABY VEGETA] I will give
them points for persistence,
but these constant
heroics are getting boring!
[UUG grunting]
[CROWD yelping]
So, Uub, I hear that
Goku was your mentor.
Is dashing through
the sky to escape
the only thing he taught you?
I killed the teacher, so I can
certainly defeat the student.
Nothing can save you now!
[UUB]
Here goes!
[BABY GOHAN]
Baby!
[PAN]
Papa!
I will avenge my friend's
death and you can't stop me!
[BABY TRUNKS] Honorable Baby,
are you okay? What happened?
We're here. You're safe, sir.
Just what are you
three doing up here?
[ALL gasp]
We saw you were in trouble,
so we came to help.
[BABY VEGETA]
You incompetent...
You think I can't win?
I own this fight!
Our deepest apologies, sir.
[BABY VEGETA grunting]
I'm testing Uub's
strength, you morons.
He may be stronger than
all of you combined!
Which proves something that
I've been thinking about.
You three are useless to me now!
[BABY TRUNKS screaming]
[BABY GOHAN screaming]
[BABY GOTEN screaming]
He's starting to kill his own
creations. This guy's a maniac.
No, Papa!
[PAN sobbing]
Papa! Papa!
You can't expect me to sit here
and watch him destroy
my family and friends.
You have to get me to
the Tuffle planet now!
[OLD KAI grunting, coughing]
I guess training can be halted,
since there's a
state of emergency.
You'll actually let me go?
If you're going to stop
with your training,
then there is only
one possible way
for you to gather enough
strength to beat Baby.
[GOKU gulps]
[OLD KAI] And it will be a lot
more painful than your training.
Goku, you ready?
Yep, I sure am.
I mean painful.
You've no idea.
Let's do it!
[OLD KAI]
Unbelievably painful.
Now!
Right, then. Drop your pants.
What? My pants?
How can you joke at a time
like this? I'm serious!
So am I. This is no joke.
Does this have something
to do with my tail?
Kibito Kai?
Yes.
Find me the biggest
set of pliers you can.
Pliers? What're they for?
The goal of the training
was to grow his tail.
Since we're skipping
the training,
we'll have to do it manually.
Manually?
That's the only way the power
that is asleep inside you
can be called to the surface.
What? Would you two stop
looking at me like that?
I'm wiser than both of you
and I know what I'm doing!
Get me those pliers
so I can get to work!
Well sir, about the pliers, I've
never even seen a pair up here.
Old Kai, you can put
your complete trust in me
when I say that I will
certainly get you the pliers!
Swell! Let's go, kiddo.
'Kay Daddy! Right behind you!
[SHUSUGORO chanting, drumming]
[SUGORO] So, are these the kind
of pliers you need, gentlemen?
Ah, yes. That will do just fine.
[GOKU] I was thinking maybe
you could use a smaller pair.
They have to be this big
to pull out your tail.
It's started to grow,
so it'll be easy to grab.
You have to believe
me when I say
it's the only way
to get you stronger.
Well, if it's the only way...
then I'll do it.
[GOKU] Just try not to squeeze
too hard if you can help it.
[OLD KAI giggles]
[UUB, BABY VEGETA grunting]
That's an impressive fighting
style you've got there.
Better than your
teacher, I think,
but nowhere near what
it will take to beat me.
[BABY VEGETA] What you
fail to realize is that with
every minute we fight, I learn
another lifetime of techniques
from your Saiyan comrades.
[UUB, BABY VEGETA grunting]
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[UUB grunting]
All of your fighting strategies
have Goku's stink on them.
And considering
what I did to him,
what do you think you can do?
[UUB growling, grunting]
[UUB screams]
So, that was his limit.
I was foolish to have
had higher expectations.
[UUB groans]
[PAN]
No, Uub!
Uub, wake up!
You're our last hope. Come on!
First he takes away
my family, and now this?
I can't put up with
this freak anymore!
[PAN grunting]
You monster! You mechanical
freak of science!
Nobody messes with my family
and gets away with it!
[HERCULE]
Buu, Buu! You've gotta help Pan!
She's the only family I've got
that's not infected by Baby,
and I can't stop her.
I wouldn't know what
to do if I lost her.
She's everything to me now.
What matters to you, Buu do.
Miss Pan will be saved.
[PAN]
Ha...
[PAN yells]
[BABY VEGETA]
Enough!
Is Pan okay?
[HERCULE]
Oh, not Pan!
That thing is gonna pay!
You know what, Buu?
Even Uub's not gonna be
able to beat that guy!
The three of us should just get
out of here as fast as we can
while they're still
goin' to town each other.
[BABY VEGETA cackles]
[UUB groaning]
That looks like
it really hurts.
But don't worry,
I'll put a stop to that.
[BABY VEGETA yelling]
[HERCULE] Does anybody know what
the heck is goin' on down there?
All people are sending
their energies to Baby,
just like they did
when he beat Goku.
But, why would they?
Are they crazy?
[BUU] Things will be safe
for you very soon.
Mr. Satan, Buu always like you.
What?
[BUU] Mr. Satan attack
the evil, mean guy
when he shoot the little puppy.
A good thing to do.
Mr. Satan will always
be my close friend.
And you're my friend also, Buu.
What exactly are
you talkin' about?
You very close friend, but Uub,
Buu think a lot about Uub, too.
[HERCULE gasps]
Buu can only think of Uub,
alone and fighting.
We be friends forever.
Buu will never forget.
Huh?
Buu!
[HERCULE]
No! Buu!
[BABY VEGETA] Aw, Goku would
be so disappointed.
I stand above you,
holding your death in my hands,
and all you can
do is look scared.
I thought you would be
a more gifted fighter,
someone to try my new
Saiyan skills out on.
Again, I overestimated
your kind's ability
to hold their own.
So, here, it must
come to an end.
The cleansing of the Tuffle
people is finally a reality.
Say goodnight!
[UUB]
What is that?
What the--
Ha! Just like Goku. Nothing
left but a small pile of ashes!
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[BABY BULMA] Honorable Baby, the
preparations have been completed
and we are ready to move the
operation into the second stage.
We humbly await your orders.
Good, let's go.
Someone saved me,
but who was it?
[BUU]
Uub! Uub!
[UUB] Who are you? Did you
bring me to this place?
I am Buu.
Are you-- I don't
know what it is,
but I get the feeling
we've met before.
[UUB]
I have memories of you.
[BUU] Long ago, Buu and Uub
were one and the same.
This Majin Buu brought
all his energies together
and a good Buu was created.
It was you, Uub,
born of the good inside.
You and I were the
same being? Really?
That's right. Time now for
Buu and Uub to be one again.
Buu's power plus Uub's power.
What? What happened?
[BUU] Buu and Uub
have become the same.
I feel... I feel stronger
than I ever thought I'd be.
Thanks, Buu. I owe you one.
Now, let's go see Baby.
[GOKU yelling, groaning]
Come on! Heave-ho!
[ALL grunting]
[GOKU groaning]
Goku, brace yourself.
Grab hold of something!
I'm doing my best!
Find something
solid and hang on!
I can deal with the pain,
but can you try to
speed this up some?
Okay.
[ALL grunting]
[CROWD clamoring]
[CROWD chanting]
Baby... Baby... Baby...
[BABY BULMA]
Baby! Wait!
You're alive. What luck.
Luck has nothing to
do with it, monster!
MAJUUB] And you won't be rid
of me until you're dead.
[NARRATOR]
After Uub and Buu merge bodies,
the new Majuub seems
confident to stand his ground
in a battle to
the end with Baby.
Meanwhile, Goku continues to
have his tail stretched out
in the hopes that it will
unleash the kind of power
that Old Kai promises.
Which one of these heroes will
be the one to stop Baby's reign?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball GT!