[NARRATOR]
On the last GT,
Goku, Pan, and Trunks arrived
at the Royal Palace of Imecka
like shadows in the night.
Their mission:
To get their
impounded spaceship
back from the corrupt
regime of Lord Don Kee.
[PAN] Are you crazy?
We're not sightseeing!
[NARRATOR] With thousands of
armed guards in the compound,
stealth was the
name of the game.
But their cover was blown
and the fireworks began.
All right! We'll play
it their way. Come on!
[battlecry]
[gunfire]
[various blows landing]
[TRUNKS]
We're on, Pan!
[terrified screaming]
Unlicensed driver
coming through!
[NARRATOR] The ship was back
in their possession,
but the trio from Earth still
needed to buy parts to fix it.
A difficult task for the most
wanted "criminals" on Imecka!
[CHIEF]
Over there, men!
[NARRATOR] The heat is on and
the authorities are closing in!
Can the unlikely fugitives
manage to fix their ship
before the bounty on
their heads is collected?
Find out today on GT!
[sirens]
Come on! This way!
[POLICEMAN] Spread out!
They're here somewhere!
Lost 'em.
I hate this.
Us, of all people, lurking in
the shadows like criminals!
I don't like it either, Pan.
It wouldn't be such a big
deal if we could just leave,
but we have to buy parts.
And that's what
makes it so difficult.
It's amazing what a
little bad PR can do.
[GIRU] Giru! Giru!
Giru! Giru...!
--Will you please shut up!
--Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru...!
[gasps]
[LADY]
Who are you?
We're visitors from Earth.
Even though we're on
your most wanted list,
we're actually
really good people.
[PAN]
Grandpa!
[whimpering]
[PAN] Please don't be scared,
ma'am. We would never hurt you.
[screaming]
[POLICEMAN]
There they are!!
Over here! Hurry!!
Hut, hut, hut, hut, hut!
Let's get out of here!
Hey! Stop!
Yo! Gail!
They're coming your way!
Got it, Sheila!
What's their ETA?
[SHEILA] Any second now!
They're using the rooftops!
[GAIL] You heard her, men!
Keep your heads up!
And don't you be deceived!
They may appear
to be children...
...but they have the
strength of monsters!
Take them out!
Ready!!
[hesitatant groans]
Nice jump, Grandpa!
Thanks!
You're... all fired!
[building crumbling]
[screams]
[crash]
[coughing]
[groans]
What a landing!
I could have broken my
tailbone on a rock that hard!
[GOKU] That's not a rock!
That's my head!
[PAN]
Oops! Sorry.
I'm okay, Pan. But I had no
idea you were that heavy!
Oh, man. I see that Videl is
certainly feeding you right!
What's that supposed
to mean?! I'm not heavy!
[PAN]
All right! Put 'em up!
Freeze! Don't move!
I've got you covered!
You dirty thieves
aren't going anywhere!
[RADIO ANNOUNCER]
Be on the look out.
These three fugitives are
still at large.
Contact the police
if you see them,
but exercise extreme caution!
They are armed and dangerous!
Listen, folks! That's not true!
Hold it, Pan.
Please, forgive us
for barging in.
[GOKU] Yeah, sorry
about breaking your roof.
We'll just go.
[stomach growls]
Grandpa! Please!
I can't help it.
I haven't eaten in two days.
[LILKA] Wait kids.
There's no hurry.
Why don't you stay a while?
You must be brave
starting a ruckus
in the Royal Palace like that!
It's been a long time
since anyone's had the pluck
to challenge Don Kee!
Oh, yes. That's for sure.
I'd like to light a fire
underneath his
you-know-what myself,
but I'm getting too
old for that now.
[chuckles]
Maybe not.
You're very nice.
Please stay a while.
I'll prepare you some food.
Uhh...
It's settled.
I'll make us supper.
So they took your ship.
What a shame.
Don't remind me!
It makes me want to scream when
I think about those crooks!
It's not fair!
No, it's not. Don Kee made
it illegal to own a ship.
Why would he
do something like that?
[LILKA] It's just
his way of making sure
that no one leaves Imecka.
The conditions here
are so unreasonable
that most would leave if
they had the opportunity.
We're slaves.
Not literally, but taxes
and rent are so high
that he practically owns us.
How awful.
There must be other people like
us who had their ship taken away
and are stuck here
with no way out.
Yes, there are many here
like that. Including us.
We landed in
Don Kee's web... long ago.
[LILKA]
He's like a fat spider,
slowly sucking
the life out of us.
Keeping us alive
only to feed his desires.
But look! Our hearts are
still beating, aren't they?
We still have hope that someday
great changes will
take place on Imecka.
Organize a revolt
and stop playing by
Don Kee's unfair rules!
[TRUNKS]
Pan!
I wish we could. But Don Kee
is a cunning individual.
He has trained
fighters for his bodyguards.
[LILKA]
They have frightening powers.
Any one of them could destroy
an entire army by himself.
We saw!
[battlecry]
[GAIL]
No way!
Saiyans??
[LILKA] Ah! So you've seen how
dreadful they are!
It's lucky you were able
to sneak your ship out.
[LILKA] I wish I had seconds to
offer a brave boy like you,
but that was all we had.
Huh? If that was your last bit,
that means we ate your dinner!
Oh, we don't mind.
Skipping one meal isn't going
to hurt two old birds like us!
Right, Eskar?
[coughs]
Yes, of course.
[TRUNKS] Pan?
What are you doing?
[PAN]
I'm leaving!
What? Leaving? Where?
Oh, I'm just
taking a little walk!
Straight to Don Kee's Palace!
[PAN] I've had it! I'm tired of
tiptoeing around this loser!
People can't get food!
We can't get parts!
Someone's got to give him
a piece of their mind!
And that someone's me!
Good idea!
Hey, wait for me!
Please be careful!
Oh, don't worry, we will ma'am.
We're pretty strong ourselves!
Check this out!
Hey! There they are!
[shuddering]
All right, we surrender.
We've had enough of
life on the run.
So, go ahead... Put the
cuffs on and take us away.
[siren]
[ESKAR]
I guess they lost their nerve.
[LILKA] The poor dears!
They must be terrified!
Hoo-hoo! I've got so much money
I could never spend it all!
[phone rings]
Ha, ha, ha! What now?
[MESSENGER]
Good news, my Lord!
The fugitives that stole the
spaceship are now in custody!
Hmm! Well I can't believe it!
You fools actually
did something!
[screaming]
[thud]
What's the meaning of this?
[door shattering]
Who let you off your leashes?!
Sheila, get in here!
Gail, you too!
I hate to say it, but
they're not coming.
[DON KEE]
You're lying!
[gasps]
[groans]
[PAN] Lord Don Kee,
you're a crook!
We know all about
your evil ways!
Fools! I make the
laws on this planet!
[DON KEE]
I've done nothing illegal!
You are the criminals here!
Wrong answer!
No!
Pan!
[screaming]
You three should
mind your own business!
Die!
[gunfire]
[explosion]
What's this? You're
still alive? Impossible!
You can not topple
warriors like these
with conventional weaponry.
Then take care of business,
Ledgic! Destroy them all!
What have I told you
about giving me orders?!
Destroy them, please, Ledgic!
Oh, I will!
But for my own satisfaction.
[GIRU] Danger!
Giru Giru Giru Giru!
Trunks! No!
[TRUNKS]
New... plan.
Trunks, let me
take it alone from here.
What about me?
Take care of Pan.
Right.
[screaming]
[LEDGIC] And who might
you be, little boy?
I'm Goku! And I'm
not a boy! Who are you?
[mischievous chuckle]
The name's Ledgic...
And I must warn you,
I'm a breed apart from these
weaklings. Prepare yourself!
[blasts]
[explosion]
[strained groaning]
Not my palace! Ledgic!
I have to admit...
you are very powerful.
Don't patronize me, I know
you're holding back...
...as am I. Saiyan.
Uh?
Hmm.
All right then! No fooling
around! Let's get to it!
[GIRU] Massive energy build-up!
Giru! Giru!
[groaning]
[screams]
What?
[battlecry]
Ledgic! Oh no!
[blows landing]
[battlecry]
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me... Haaaaa!!
[massive explosion]
Get up, Ledgic!
[GOKU]
What an awesome fight!
You'd been even better
if you trained more!
I wouldn't mind fighting
you again someday for fun!
That way we could both
test our progress!
[GOKU]
Wouldn't that be cool?
You are an unusual child.
I told you already!
I'm not a child!
I couldn't have
beaten you if I was!
Is this a riddle? It must be...
What kind of child
is not really a child?
[stained breathing]
[GOKU]
Hey, are you okay?
[LEDGIC]
I'll be fine.
[PAN]
But he won't!
[screams]
Ledgic, I've been
saving this for you.
Finish them and it
will all be yours!
[LEDGIC]
Didn't your mother tell you?
Money isn't everything!
Mark my words... Next time
I will be victorious.
Oh, yeah? We'll see
about that, Ledgic!
[horrified scream]
[DON KEE] Please! Don't hurt me!
I beg you! I was wrong!
If you spare me,
I'll do anything you say!
And how do we know
you're telling the truth?
Uh! I swear!
I'll do anything!
[PAN] Stop charging rent!
Give your subjects free housing!
Free? But that's impossible!
Guess the deal's off!
All right!
[DON KEE] Okay! I'll do it!
There'll be no more rent!
I'll give you
the contracts to prove it!
[PAN] Lilka! Eskar!
We have something for you!
[ESKAR]
Hmm?
[resounding thud]
[PAN] Hi, everyone! Here's a
little gift from Don Kee!
These are your
rental contracts!
You are no longer bound by
the Don's oppressive rule!
[awes of amazement]
[PAN] Oh, and Don Kee asked us
to make another announcement!
Anyone who has had their
spaceship impounded
will have it returned,
free of charge!
This... This is
a dream come true!
[giggles]
[PAN] Well it
sure was nice of Don Kee
to give us those parts for free.
[TRUNKS] Yeah, I think
old Don is ready to turn over
a new leaf.
Now we can leave Imecka
with a clear conscience
and go find those Dragon Balls!
Uh, you guys,
our radar ran away.
[PAN]
That brat!
[GIRU] Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
[PAN]
Not so fast!
You little crook!
You're not going anywhere until
we get our Dragon Radar back!
[GIRU]
Let go!
[PAN[ If you don't cough
it up right now,
I'm going to pull you
apart circuit by circuit!
[GIRU] No! No disassemble!
Giru alive! Giru alive!
Good grief!
[GIRU]
Giru.
Hey! What's the big idea?! Huh?!
What you were
doing was cruel, Pan.
What are you talking about?
He's just a stupid
little machine!
If he's scared to die then he
must value his existence....
His life might be
different than ours,
but if he's
struggling to survive
then we have to respect that.
Poor little guy...
He's terrified.
And what are we going to
do about the Dragon Radar?
Huh?!
It looks like the Dragon
Radar is still intact!
If I'm right, he's integrated
the radar into his system
as a fully operational part.
[GIRU]
Affirmative!
All right!
Just great!
If the radar is
part of him now,
that means we have to
take him along with us!
Great!
[TRUNKS]
Hey, it's working!
He's giving us the location
of our first Dragon Ball!
[PAN]
Is it here on Imecka?
[TRUNKS] No, these coordinates
are for somewhere
in outer space,
but it's not that far from here!
[PAN] Well, what are we doing
just standing here?
[GOKU] Yeah!
Our first Dragon Ball!
[PAN]
Let's go get it!
[NARRATOR] After their seemingly
ill-fated crash landing,
the three space voyagers
are on their way once again.
The Imeckians have been
delivered from bondage,
but the future of Earth
is still in the balance.
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next Dragon Ball GT!