[GOKU] What do you say
we get started?
[NUOVA]
I couldn't agree more.
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT,
Goku and the Four-Star Dragon
battled fiercely,
laying waste to
everything around them.
[glass shatters]
What?
[GOKU snickers]
I underestimated you.
Do what you will.
Why are you waiting?
I owe you for something
that you did for me.
[GOKU yelling]
[NARRATOR] But suddenly, Eis
Shenron, the Three-Star Dragon,
had to throw his
hat into the ring,
ruining a glorious battle.
[NUOVA growing]
Let's go, while we're young!
Nova Star!
[NARRATOR] Angry with
his brother's interruption,
Nuova shattered
Goku's icy confines,
bringing the fight
back out into the open!
I told you to kill him,
not melt him, you imbecile!
I'll take him
out in five seconds!
If you don't mind,
Goku, tell me again.
You'll beat me how fast?
[EIS laughs]
Well, I'm not quite sure,
but I'll tell you in a minute.
My, you have such
a confident attitude.
But instead of a minute,
I'll give you five seconds.
[GOKU growls]
One.
Two.
Three, four.
Ka...
Me...
Ha... Me...
He's got Pan!
That was a long five seconds.
And you still couldn't get me.
[EIS giggles evily]
[GOKU] Bringing my family
into this is a dirty move, Eis.
But dirty moves work
better than clean ones,
and I'll do anything
to win this.
No, Pan!
[EIS yells]
[GOKU yells in pain]
[GOKU yells]
[fighting noises]
[EIS grimaces]
You didn't see me play dirty.
You and your evil
ways turn my stomach!
Using my granddaughter
as a shield
is the most despicable thing
you could have done, Eis!
So don't think I'm
gonna let you off easy!
I'm sorry if he hurt you, Pan.
[EIS groans]
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
Come get me!
Coward! You just used me
as a shield, didn't you?
Yes, but the truth is you're
no longer useful in that regard.
Now, move so I can
get back to work!
If you're both so
annoyed with how I fight,
then show me a rulebook
for world domination,
and I might consider
changing my style.
Until then...
...hold this for me!
Look out, Goku!
No! How did that happen?
But my ice ray...
It's supposed to be
an impenetrable beam!
You can't use the
same move on me twice.
My body remembers and
compensates the next round.
That's ridiculous.
What's ridiculous
is the creature
that doesn't believe
in respect.
There are certain
things you don't do,
certain things that
are understood.
What do you mean?
[EIS whimpers]
You don't ever mess
with a man's family.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right, I'm sorry.
It-It won't happen again.
I'll give you the Dragon Ball.
I'll do whatever
you want. I promise!
[NUOVA] You brought this
on yourself, Eis.
[EIS]
Just please, don't hurt me.
I've learned my
lesson, like I said.
I'll give you
anything! Name it!
Just please, don't hurt me.
Please, help me out here, Nuova.
I'm sorry, I was so mean to you,
just don't let him kill me!
Please!
[NUOVA]
Goku?
Killing him won't
help anything.
It should be enough
just to get the Dragon Ball
from him, right?
Yeah here.
[GOKU]
Look at me. He's right.
All I'm here for
is the Dragon Ball.
You're lucky to have someone
so respectful stand up for you.
You should thank him, Eis.
And when you're
done thanking him,
I want you to leave.
And I never want
to see you again.
Now, turn over
the Dragon Ball.
Watch your eyes!
[GOKU yells in pain]
[GOKU] I can't see!
What's going on?
[EIS chuckles]
[EIS] The trust
you people put
in a sniveling weasel
is astonishing!
Your body might be
able to learn my moves,
but your brain can't even
see through a simple lie.
[GOKU grimaces]
[NUOVA] Eis, are
you that desperate
that you have to blind him?
[EIS] It cuts his strength in
half. Anything to win, you know.
And with his power resting
nicely at half strength,
I'll finish him.
No!
[GOKU]
I'll finish it!
[EIS gasps]
Taking away my sight
still leaves me with
four very sharp senses.
[GOKU yells]
[EIS growls]
[EIS yells]
My brother...
[GOKU] Nothing helps.
I still can't see a thing.
An antidote. It will
restore your sight.
Is that you, Nuova?
Unlike my brother, I do
have respect for battle.
I won't challenge you
again until you can see.
Seek me out then.
Nuova, wait! I guess you
could say I owe you one.
No Goku, I think I owe you.
[NUOVA and GOKU laughing]
[glass shatters]
[NUOVA grunts]
Nuova, are you okay?
Somebody shot at my hand!
Did anything hit you?
Nuova, where are you?
I wait no more.
Who is that?
Syn Shenron.
It's a pitiful dragon that
gives allowances to a monkey.
[NUOVA yells in pain]
[GOKU yells]
I'm... I'm sorry.
I wanted to settle
this fairly. I wanted...
Nuova...
[GOKU]
That's it!
[GOKU screams]
That was one of your
own kind you just killed.
Don't you have one
ounce of decency in you?
Can't you see what you've done?!
You slaughtered him.
You slaughtered him like
he was nothing but an insect.
[SYN] Of course, I did.
This isn't a game.
And how dare you criticize
your own creation?
We're here, because of you.
What do you mean?!
All of the Shadow
Dragons were born
because you misused
the Dragon Balls, remember?
It all started with you.
Your world is crumbling
because of your actions.
You were warned
about the overuse,
but you didn't listen.
This is all your fault!
Everything we ever wished for
was always for the
good of the planet.
Old Kai warned me,
and I felt bad for doing it.
But I never made a selfish wish.
Every wish made on the
Dragon Balls was important.
Do you hear me?
I did what was right
for the planet then,
and I'll do what is right
for the planet now,
even if I'm blind.
A noble monkey...
If you feel so
bad about it then
maybe death should
be your penance.
[GOKU yells]
[SYN laughs maniacally]
[SYN] Oops!
Guess I used a bit too much.
But now you know
what I'm capable of!
Your power's amazing.
You destroyed the entire
city with one blast!
And now, your time has come.
Oof!
What do you think so far?
I'm not the easy catch
you thought, am I?
No Syn, I don't underestimate
my opponents, ever!
Well then,
I'm going to miss your good
sportsmanlike attitude.
Somehow, I don't think
he saw that one coming.
The Dragon Balls...
Grandpa, Grandpa what happened?
[GOKU]
Not yet.
One more second.
Now!
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
Ha!
I did it.
Oh, you certainly did it,
all right, Goku.
But none of it
seems to hurt me.
Something's wrong.
That blast should have at least
put some kind of dent in you.
Should have...
So what you're
learning right now,
is the fact that you are simply
not strong enough to beat me.
[PAN yelling]
[NARRATOR] With Goku
blinded and unconscious,
Pan is left helpless to face
the supremely powerful
One-Star Dragon.
Will help arrive in time,
or will the heroes be overcome
by Syn Shenron's might?
Help Papa... and Trunks!
Everyone!
We need your help.
Grandpa's in trouble!
Don't miss the next GT.