[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT,
Nuova Shenron emerged
from the Dragon Ball
that appeared on
Goku's forehead
for one more shot at victory!
[NUOVA SPHERE]
Nuova Sphere!
Nuova!
What's wrong? Are you okay?
I'm... sorry... Goku.
[cracking]
[explosion]
Surprised to see me, Goku?
You tell me!
Would you two
like to take a break,
or would you mind if I finish
killing you where I left off?
With Vegeta incapable of
becoming a Super Saiyan 4,
will Goku have another
angle of attack ready?
Find out now on GT!
Quickly gentlemen,
make a decision.
Which one of you
would like to die first?
Kakarot!
Let's quit wasting time
and fuse ourselves so we
can get to Super Saiyan 4!
We can't.
I would have to be
in my adult body
in order for fusion
to work successfully.
There's always a hitch.
Fine then. I'll just
and kill you both
while you make up your mind!
Oof!
Ugh!
[GOKU grimaces]
Hey, Vegeta.
What now?
Did you see how hard he hit me?
No, I guess I didn't.
Because I was getting smacked
around myself, if you recall.
What?
Look, I'm getting sick and tired
of all your senseless bickering!
[VEGETA]
It's mutual.
Earlier you two had quite
an advantage over me.
But now both of
your powers are drained,
and the two of you stand
no chance of stopping me.
Your people,
your culture, your planet,
everything you've worked for,
you can kiss it all goodbye.
Um, Vegeta, I don't
think he's bluffing.
This can't be the end.
Okay. Let's get this
over with! Time to die!
Move it. I'll take
care of this one!
[GOKU growls]
I can't let him
destroy the Earth!
Kakarot!
I'm not gonna let him
get away with this!
[GOKU grimacing]
I know the earth has been
revived far too many times
by exploiting the power
of the Dragon Balls.
Just let me beat
this guy and I promise
we'll survive from now
on without using them.
[GOKU growls]
I need more power!
Dad!
Come on, Grandpa!
Goku!
You can do it!
[GOKU grimaces]
I won't let it end this way.
If I don't do something soon,
the lives of my family
and everyone on this planet
will be lost forever.
Last chance to
give up before I attack!
Yeah, right...
I give up!
[explosions]
[GOKU yells]
Kakarot!
Did... did we make it?
[HERCULE whimpers]
Aww! It looks like he was
able to prevent this trash-heap
from exploding in exchange
for his own measly life.
Where is Grandpa?
Well, he's dead as expected.
And since the negative
energy was released,
it's now a matter of time
before this planet's dead, too.
Hey, Goku. I hope you can
find some joy in your death!
[laughing]
Grandpa!
[thunder booming]
[PEOPLE screaming in terror]
This is awful!
[laughing]
I can feel the planet
dying underneath me!
It is the end.
We just can't beat him.
I've already had to deal with
one home planet being destroyed!
No!
Now it looks like the
Earth will be next to go.
The time is now...
We can't let this
go on any longer,
no matter what
the cost may be!
Even if it means
sacrificing our own lives.
What does it matter now?
I need to take him out!
Vegeta!
Father!
Everybody listen up!
Get away from the Earth
in Bulma's spaceship
while you still have the time!
One more thing...
Trunks, you'll
have to find a way
to kill this dragon if I can't!
And Gohan, Goten...
It's your responsibility as well
to continue the fight your
father couldn't finish!
Now Trunks, you must
take everyone and go!
That's an order!
Don't follow me!
Wait!
Is the reality of
your fate setting in?
Not my fate.
I'm still alive because
you never thought
of finishing me off!
[VEGETA laughs]
Good bye, Mother.
Trunks!
What is it, Gohan?
Daddy?
Pan, take good care of
your mother and grandmother.
Majuub. Go to your village
and get your family to safety.
Make your dad proud.
Vegeta needs your help
right now Goten,
so give it all you've got.
I will.
[BULMA thinking] Vegeta, Trunks,
please come back to me alive!
[thunder clasping]
Attention citizens:
stay tuned for an emergency
message from our King.
This just in!
We are trying to verify reports
that the King's Castle
has been destroyed!
Stay tuned for
the latest news updates.
ZTV will continue our coverage
as long as we're able
to stay on the--
[GOKU] Please everyone,
give me some of your energy.
Any that you can spare.
If you don't, I'll die.
I knew you'd come.
How pathetic!
Try some of these on for size!
[VEGETA]
You're mine!
[OMEGA]
Dragon Thunder!
[VEGETA yells in pain]
[OMEGA laughing]
Hey Gohan, Goten, Trunks!
I sure could use
some energy right now!
I need it!
I can't wait much longer!
[OMEGA laughs]
This is for Kakarot!
Since you've been
so fun, Vegeta,
I'll put you in the
same grave as Goku,
so you can argue for eternity!
Don't speak so soon.
You haven't won yet.
What?
Hey wait!
I thought I killed you!
[GOKU] I'm not ready
to die again just yet.
I've tried to be reasonable.
You've got one last
chance to apologize!
Omega! I'm holding the energy
of every person left on Earth
who's ever suffered at the
hands of evil-doers like you!
This can't be happening!
You're supposed to
be dead! I killed you!
Just die!
King Kai? King Kai,
can you hear me?
I hear you loud and clear, Goku.
You're doing a great job, buddy.
Remember to use the
attack that I taught ya!
You remember, right?
[GOKU] It's not gonna
be that easy though!
[OMEGA]
Die! Die! Die! Die!
[GOKU] I've already used
all of Earth's energy,
and this spirit bomb still isn't
powerful enough to finish him!
I'll need to borrow from the
entire universe for it to work.
King Kai, call to everyone you
can and gather their energy.
It's our only hope!
Pep from the
entire universe, eh?
That's a fantastic idea!
[GOKU] Please King Kai, I need
everyone you can possibly get!
[KING KAI] Okay!
Leave it to me, Goku!
[KING KAI] Kais of the East,
South, and West!
Lend me your strength,
for the fate of the people
of Earth depends on it!
Everybody! Give me
all of your energy!
Bon para para para.
Bon Pappa!
That voice...
Sounded like...
...Goku's!
[GOKU] Come on!
Raise your hands in the air!
You know the drill,
so dance with us!
Shake your rump...
...and put 'em up!
--What was that?
--Oh! Wow!
It's energy from all
over the universe!
I can sense this one
is from the Imeccians,
and another from
the villagers of Gelbo!
It's Grandpa!
King Kai, thank you so much,
and thank the citizens
of the Universe!
Enough!
Impossible!
How did he do that?
Grandpa!
Look at that!
Isn't it beautiful?
This is it!
Wait, Wait! Hold on!
[GOKU yells]
[OMEGA whimpers]
[OMEGA yells]
Dad!
Goku!
Goku, where are you?
Hey, Dad!
Goku!
Show yourself, Kakarot!
Grandpa!
Grandpa, wake up!
Can you hear me?
Look at the Dragon Balls!
[SHENRON growls]
Wait a minute!
What's Shenron doing here?
We didn't call him.
[NARRATOR] With a Spirit Bomb
of universal scale,
Goku was finally able
to defeat Omega Shenron!
Then, suddenly,
without warning or summoning,
the Eternal Dragon himself
appeared in the sky above them,
restored to his
previous majesty.
What does Shenron's
unprompted appearance mean?
Strange occurrences
await Goku and the others
next time on the final
episode of Dragon Ball GT!