Fusion! Ha!
[NARRATOR] On the last GT,
the ultimate warrior was born!
An amalgam of Super Saiyan 4's!
The incomparable Gogeta!
Where are the other two?
They're here.
I am they. We are one.
There's only one
thing left undone!
Big Bang Kamehameha!
Gogeta's new technique blasted
the extra Dragon Balls
out of Omega's control,
and he was forced to revert
to the form of Syn Shenron.
Determined to regain
his lost power,
Syn began to absorb the
Dragon Balls once again.
As the form of Omega Shenron
started to reemerge,
Goku nabbed
the Four Star Dragon Ball!
It seems he has
other plans for it.
I like to keep
the Four Star Ball
to remind me of my grandfather!
I won't let you have this one!
You should have
tried to eliminate me
the moment you two fused.
You idiots squandered
away your only chance!
Hey! How dare
you call us idiots!
He's the only idiot around here!
[GOKU laughs]
And to think you Saiyans
are known as warriors.
You two outcasts
are nothing but a joke.
It was him!
I would have destroyed
you in the first minute!
Hey Vegeta, easy.
Let's not let
him ruffle our fur.
Come on, we were
both responsible.
Speak for yourself, Kakarot!
You were more interested
in playing pranks
than winning the battle!
That wasn't me!
That's just how we act
when we're together!
No! That's how the clowns
act at the darn circus!
Why don't we just
try Fusion again?
I'm a warrior, Kakarot!
Real warriors don't strike
silly poses like that!
It's not all that bad.
Besides, you've already
done it once, right?
Yes! And it was
humiliating enough!
Allow me to settle this for you!
There will be no more Fusion!
You're dreaming if you
think I'd let you have
an advantage over
me like that again!
Face it.
You had one golden opportunity
to win this battle
and you let it slip
through your fingers.
Vegeta! Fusion! Quick!
Perhaps you didn't
hear what I said?
This Fusion of yours
won't happen!
Yes! Come to me,
my Four Star friend!
Make me complete again
so I may rule the Universe!
Sorry! I hate to
rain on your parade,
but it would be
far too dangerous
to let you have this back!
I was serious when I said
that I won't let you have it!
And just to make sure I
don't go back on my word.
I'll just do what you do!
What the heck?
Can he do that?
He's choking!
Kakarot!
Don't be a fool, Kakarot!
Spit it out!
Don't worry!
You could have
been killed, moron!
That was a foolish place
to put the Dragon Ball!
Now I'll have to rip
your head off to get it!
That Ball's not going anywhere!
It's gonna stay
right inside his body!
Wait Vegeta! Get back here!
Vegeta!
Even in my current state,
you're still no match
for me without Fusion!
Huh? Why didn't it fall?
This is our chance, Vegeta!
We've got to try Fusing
while we're still out of sight!
We don't have much time!
Vegeta, where are you?
Let's do it!
There's no room! If I let go,
the whole place will come down!
Huh? Oh, no!
Why don't you both come out?
There's no use in bluffing,
I know that blast
didn't kill you!
Well, I'm happy to see that
there are still two of you!
You had me worried!
We were a little cramped!
But we'll find a way to win!
You can rest assured of that!
We won't let you have
your way with mankind!
But I was born to take revenge
on those that allowed me to be.
It is my destiny.
Dad! No!
Leave him alone!
Kakarot!
He's not much
on down time! Is he?
I'll admit. That one
was slightly effective.
I knew if I used energy
you would have sensed it!
So I decided to attack
the old fashioned way!
I'm just glad I didn't hit
one of those gnarly spikes!
You two are only
prolonging the inevitable!
It makes no sense! You know
I'll kill you both eventually!
Why resist?
It's what I do!
Not for long!
It's no use!
He's got too much on us.
Vegeta, we can't wait anymore!
We've got to fuse now!
Vegeta, did you hear me?!
Yes, all right already! I'll do
it! Stop yelling!
This is the last time,
do you understand?
Fine! I'll never ask again!
I promise!
Hey! They're fusing again!
Fusion...!
When I say no, I mean no!
Vegeta, quick!
We've only got seconds!
Kakarot look!
Oof!
Enough! I've had all
I can take of you!
[OMEGA scoffs]
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA growls]
[GOKU] You know,
I've never understood how people
can delight in hurting others!
That's what will be
your undoing, Omega.
You see, when you take life,
you live in fear because deep
down you know that someday,
your life will be taken as well.
We all have to reap
what we sow, Omega.
There's no way of avoiding that.
When you harm others, you're
really only harming yourself.
It's simple.
If you want good things
to happen in your life,
you have to be good!
You're good, Saiyan,
but that's not going
to save you today!
Die!
I would listen
to him if I were you!
More often than not, the things
Kakarot says come to pass!
But I know that it's going
to take more than talk
to change your mind!
I had to learn
the hard way myself!
Let's show him our Fusion!
What do you say?
On your mark, Kakarot!
Now!
These fools are
becoming too confident!
FU...
Look out!
There we go! That'll keep
him off our tails for a second!
FUSION!
[VEGETA and GOKU yelp]
This is bad!
I can't take this anymore!
Wait! I'm coming, too!
No Trunks!
Goten! Hold up!
I'm going, Gohan!
I'm not sure
I follow you, Gohan!
We've helped them
perform Fusion once!
Shouldn't we be
able to do it again?
Not much has changed.
Your wrong about that, Trunks!
A lot has changed!
Last time Omega didn't
know what Fusion was.
He felt so superior
that he wasn't even
really that concerned.
This time he knows.
He'll do anything to stop it.
Our Dads are struggling
even as Super Saiyan 4's!
He's going for blood this time!
There's nothing
we can do, Goten.
We have to wait.
We will get our chance.
But if you go in there now,
the only one you'll hurt is Dad.
[VEGETA and GOKU
yelling in pain]
It's starting to get ugly, Sir.
They're in trouble!
Ancestor!
I hardly think that this is the
proper time to be grooving down!
This is serious!
If Goku and Vegeta
lose this battle,
the Earth will be lost forever.
I know that...
...but worrying yourself to
death isn't going to help!
Show a little detachment!
You're a Kai for goodness sake!
Huh? But Sir...
I was just... I was just
trying to be vigilant.
Isn't it a good thing to keep
a watchful eye at
all times, Ancestor?
Kibito you're a good Kai,
but you're not above a little
constructive criticism, are you?
Of course not!
Stop being so darn serious.
Do something to take
your mind off work!
Okay! What do you
recommend, Ancestor?
Exercise for one!
Exercise?
Well, back to work!
I know that many lives are
hanging in the balance,
but Goku excels in these
kinds of conditions.
If anyone can do it, he can.
But if I get all nervous
I feel like I'm jinxing him!
That's why I think it's
better sometimes not to watch.
[fighting noises]
[GOKU]
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
[VEGETA]
Final Flash!
[VEGETA and GOKU]
Ha!
[OMEGA laughs]
Child's play!
I'm baffled!
How can the two of you be
so strong when you're fused,
yet so pitifully weak
when you're apart?
It's inconceivable!
Making light of two
Super Saiyan 4's!
I've been going
about this all wrong.
I shouldn't be trying to
prevent you from fusing.
I should just fix it so
that it's impossible to fuse!
By killing you!
What?
You would have died
sooner or later anyway.
Vegeta!
He's trying to finish it!
He's going for the kill!
Goku!
[GOKU grunting]
[OMEGA laughing]
If you want to
die first, that's fine.
I need to extract the 4-Star
Ball from your body anyway!
[OMEGA growls]
He needs help.
[GOKU]
You don't understand!
[OMEGA]
Huh? Understand what?
I can't let you win!
Hey, Vegeta! Quick!
Fusion! Let's do it!
Right!
Kakarot! Look out!
Hit the deck!
What is with this guy?
No matter what we do to him,
he's all over us!
Go figure!
The very day that I reach
the pinnacle of Saiyan strength,
I meet my end at the hands
of this preposterously
strong Dragon!
No way! I don't
care how strong he is!
He's trying to take
innocent lives
and we're not going to let him!
Our destinies have led us here!
This is the test!
We can't let even a shred
of doubt enter our minds!
We must Fuse again!
There's no other way!
How, Kakarot?
[OMEGA] What are you
two whispering about?
Whatever it is, it won't work!
I can promise you that!
But it doesn't hurt to dream!
Go ahead if you'd like!
Dream about Fusion and
beating me while I kill you!
We can do this!
After all, we are both Saiyans!
Wasn't ours the mightiest
race in the Universe
before it was destroyed?
What, you just figure that out?
It's just too easy!
Oh, man. Ahhh.
Hey, pal. I hate to say it,
but you look terrible.
Yes! Thank you!
That just might be
the winning ticket!
Well! So you still have
the power to stand!
Your mind is strong
but your body is not!
Vegeta!
The After Image Technique!
What about
the After Image Technique?
Wait! Of course!
Kakarot! I'll follow your lead!
Prepare yourself!
We're going to show you
our Super 2 Fusion Technique!
Idiots! Don't you get it?
There will be no Fusion!
FU...
Maybe this will help get it
through your thick heads!
-- ...SION!
What the?
HA!
FU...
FUSION! HA!
Curse those monkeys!
Hey! Look!
What? We're not fused!
Hmm!
[OMEGA laughs]
Now that is funny!
I guess you were so intent
on executing your little fusion
that you forgot how to do it!
Aah! Why didn't it work?
I don't get it!
Kakarot! Look at you!
You screwed it all up again!
What the heck happened?
Look! There you
go blaming me again!
I don't know what happened!
Hey! Wait a second! I've got it!
You... you didn't stretch your
fingers out at the very end!
Did you? That's it!
Are you insane?
It was embarrassing enough
doing that stupid pose,
but now you're saying
I couldn't get it right!
Who made you the
Fusion expert anyway,
Mister Straight Fingers?
Maybe it was your toes!
Pointing too far in!
Ever think of that?
[OMEGA laughs]
You dimwits!
Against all odds you
get your second chance,
only to botch it up!
What's wrong with
Grandpa and Vegeta?
Why can't they Fuse?
I'm not sure!
It doesn't make sense!
[TRUNKS thinking] Maybe
it's Goku! Maybe he's too weak!
He has been fighting
much longer than Dad,
taking in so
many brutal attacks!
It's a miracle
that he's even alive!
He probably doesn't have enough
energy left to perform Fusion!
I think he senses it!
He knows that Goku
is at his wits' end!
[OMEGA chuckles]
You know, I think I've had
a bit of a change of heart.
I'd like the challenge of
fighting your Fusion again!
It'll be fun!
Hmm! Okay!
But you are aware that if you
let us go through with this,
you're most likely going to die?
Mm, hmm.
You heard the nice Dragon!
Let's serve up some Fusion!
Right!
FUSION! HA!
He's letting them do it.
[VEGETA and GOKU gasp]
Kakarot!
You're a... You're a...
Whatd'ya know!
I'm a little kid again!
Now we're in a pickle!
This is awful!
Grandpa's little again!
He must be out of power!
Well, your little dance
didn't work, did it?
You should have
known better than
to take on so many
of my attacks.
It was only a matter of
time until you puttered out.
Guess you could say you ran out
of gas right before the finish.
[GOKU laughs]
Hmm? How long before you
suffer the same fate, Vegeta?
You realize you're
destined to die.
Don't fool yourself, Dragon!
Nobody controls
my destiny but me!
I have to admit it,
you're strong,
stronger than anyone
that I've ever faced.
That's for sure!
But as long as there's
breath left in this body,
it's not over yet!
[NARRATOR] Just as Goku
made his fiery declaration,
the Four Star Dragon Ball
appeared on his forehead!
What does this
strange development mean?