[NARRATOR] Previously on
GT, Goku and Trunks
were in an all-out war with
the formidable Mutchie,
whose arms stretch into
deadly whips with amazing power.
[GOKU grunting]
[MUTCHY] What are you
going to do now, boy?
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, the doll-crazy leader
of the Luud Cult, Dolltaki,
still controls Pan.
[DOLLTAKI] ...about you
from my diciples.
[NARRATOR] Dolltaki plotted
the resurrection of Luud
by brainwashing his followers
into believing the machine
was their lord and savior.
Once he had them
convinced, he turned on them
and used their bodies
to fuel Luud's awakening
in a ceremony of slaughter.
[water bubbling]
[TRUNKS]
Pan! Are you okay?
Your suspicions are undoubtedly
correct. This is indeed Pan.
And she's gonna live
with me forever and ever.
Over my dead body!
[DOLLTAKI] Now arise, Luud!
Arise and fulfill your destiny!
[NARRATOR]Luud is only
moments from awakening.
Will he be the
destructive mutant
Dolltaki believes him to be?
Find out now GT!
[water bubbling]
[GOKU grunting]
[TRUNKS grunting]
[GIRU]
Not good! Not good! Giru!
[DOLLTAKI cackling]
[PAN] I don't know what's
going on, but it looks bad!
[camera clicking]
[GOKU grunting]
Ha! Aw, look! Isn't he cute?
That thing is giving off way
too much energy for a machine!
[LUUD growling]
[footsteps thundering]
[GOKU gasping]
Ah! He's huge!
[DOLLTAKI cackling]
Take your time Luud.
I'll be in the other room
playing with my new toy.
[PAN] I don't suppose
there is any chance
he's talking about
someone besides me!
[DOLLTAKI] Have fun Luud!
And don't wear yourself out!
Pan!
[TRUNKS]
We've got to be careful here!
Whoa! I take back
that cute comment.
[BOTH grunt]
[DOLLTAKI panting]
[TRUNKS] Let's hurry!
Dolltaki's getting away.
[GOKU grunts]
[DOLLTAKI cackling, panting]
Now we finally have
some "alone time"
[PAN] I told you I didn't
want to play, didn't I?
You're just disgusting
and really weird,
so leave me alone
you ugly freak!
[BOTH grunting, yelping]
I get the feeling he doesn't
want us to go that way.
[LUUD growling]
Watch.
Huh?
Hey! Up here! Luud!
Goku! What are you doing?
Yeah, come on! Free shot!
[LUUD growling]
[DOLLTAKI humming]
This one, or that? No! This one!
[PAN] He could have at least
turned me into a talking doll,
like one of those where you
pull the string on
the back and...
Oh wait, that might hurt.
This would be nice!
[PAN] This is so annoying.
He can't even hear me!
[DOLLTAKI] Hey Pan, what do
you think about this number?
Oh, Mr. Dolltaki!
That's just lovely!
[PAN] He doesn't really think
I sound like that does he?
Ah! Put me down!
Mr. Dolltaki sounds too formal.
So please, it's just Dolltaki.
[DOLLTAKI] Why thank you
Dolltaki! That's so nice of you!
You're so welcome!
[DOLLTAKI]
You're awesome!
Why thank you!
You're welcome!
[DOLLTAKI] The bandana is more
for "Rebellious Teen Pan,"
so tonight we're going
for "Formal Dress Pan."
Oh! Playing dress-up
is so much fun.
Oh, but we really should
do something about your hair.
Pan, why don't we get the
same haircut? It'd be fun!
[PAN]
If I make it home
I promise to get rid
of all my dolls!
I had no idea they had
to go through all this!
[TRUNKS grunting]
Hey! What are you waiting for?
Come get me!
[GOKU]
Show us what you got, Luud!
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
Missed me! You missed me!
[GOKU panting]
[TRUNKS shrieking]
[BOTH panting]
[BOTH grunt]
[footsteps thundering]
[GOKU panting]
[GOKU whimpering]
[GOKU] Wow! This toy
sure is hard to break!
[GOKU grunting]
I'll handle this guy.
You go look for Pan!
I'm on it!
[GOKU yelping]
[BOTH groaning]
[BOTH grunting]
Tell me that didn't just happen!
[BOTH yelping]
[DOLLTAKI cackling]
Okay, Pan. It's time
to change your clothes!
[PAN]
Someone help me, please!
[VOICE] Dolltaki,
are you there? Dolltaki!
Y-Yes?
[PAN]
Where is that voice coming from?
[VOICE] Report to the
communication room immediately.
Yes, sir! Right away.
[beeping]
[PAN]
What kind of crazy room is this?
Well not any crazier than
the last room I suppose,
but it is different.
It's an honor to hear from
you again, Doctor Myuu, sir.
[PAN] I wonder why
he's talking to his doctor!
Come on, freak! Stand up,
so I can see the screen.
[DR. MYUU]
You have yet to update me
on your search for
the Dragon Balls.
My apologies!
[DR. MYUU] It couldn't be that
you have failed me again,
could it Dolltaki?
That's not it at all, sir.
We actually have two
here in the shrine now!
[DR. MYUU]
Is that a fact?
[PAN] Okay, so he's not
your normal family doctor.
[DR. MYUU cackling]
[DR. MYUU] If the legend
of the eternal dragon
turns out to be
scientific fact,
then my ambitions to
control the universe
could easily be fulfilled.
[PAN] D-Did he say
control the universe?
So that's what
this is all about!
Well I, for one,
refuse to just sit here
while these nut cases
collect the Dragon Balls!
I've gotta do something!
[DR. MYUU] You have done
very well, Dolltaki!
[DOLLTAKI]
Thank you, sir!
I would like to have
both Dragon Balls
sent to me right away!
[DOLLTAKI]
Well, I would but...
But what?
We were having a
slight disturbance,
but it is being taken
care of right now.
I activated Luud to ensure
that nothing further came of it.
What? You mean to tell me
you actually got that
thing working already?
Yes. That is correct sir.
Tell me, Dolltaki.
With the short amount of time
you had to prepare with Luud,
was he ever able to reach
his highest level of power?
No, not yet Dr. Myuu,
but I was certain
that level two would be
more than enough to stop
who we are dealing with.
[DOLLTAKI]
You can see for yourself.
I'll bring him up
on the monitors.
[PAN] Whoa! Is Grandpa
really fighting that thing?
[LUUD growling]
[LUUD groaning]
[BOTH gasping]
Impossible!
[DOLLTAKI whimpering]
[PAN]
All right! Way to go guys!
Now we can finish this
and rescue Pan. Ready Trunks?
Yeah!
[footsteps thundering]
[GOKU, TRUNKS grunting]
[LUUD groaning]
[TRUNKS]
That oughtta do it!
[GOKU]
Nice job, Trunks!
[GOKU grunts]
[LUUD groaning]
[GOKU yelping]
Hey Goku, you gonna be okay?
Yeah.
Did you notice his attacks?
They're like a child's toy!
He has amazing power,
but he doesn't know how
to use it to his advantage.
You incompetent fool!
You're just as inept
as I suspected!
[DOLLTAKI whimpering]
It seems you have
underestimated these children!
Luud's completely
useless at level two.
[DOLLTAKI]
I'm very sorry!
Remind me, who was it that
took you off the streets
when you were nothing more than
a smooth-talking con man? Huh?
[DOLLTAKI]
You good Doctor. It was you!
And who was it that took
that gleam of talent you showed
back then, and molded it,
not only into the First Guardian
of Luud construction,
but also the Leader of
the entire Luud Order?
[DOLLTAKI] You again,
Doctor. It was all you!
[DR. MYUU] And why did I make
you the leader of order, anyway?
Don't tell me that you've
forgotten the reason already!
I haven't forgotten! You chose
me because I could convince
weak-minded people
into believing in me,
so that we could use
their energy to activate Luud.
You know I'm the best
at toying with people's minds!
That's right Dolltaki,
and for the most part, you
did an excellent job.
Luud is truly one-of-a-kind
amongst all other mutants.
He can absorb and exploit
the energy of any living thing.
Of all my creations, he is
easily my greatest masterpiece.
[DR. MYUU]
And you ruined him!
[DOLLTAKI] Oh, you must
forgive me somehow! Please!
[DR. MYUU] Why must you
disappoint me like this?
I raised you like a son!
[DOLLTAKI whimpering]
[DR. MYUU] Just look at that
pathetic machine out there!
[GOKU, TRUNKS yelling]
[LUUD groaning]
Almost!
[GOKU yelping]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[LUUD groaning]
Can't let up yet!
Right behind you!
[PAN]Yeah! Go get him,
Grandpa! Keep it up, Trunks!
That's it Trunks! Hit with
a right! Follow with a kick!
Don't let him get
past your defenses!
Wow! This is a great fight!
How are you planning
to take responsibility
for this mess, Dolltaki?
[PAN] Don't let up guys!
Sneak a punch in!
Wait, watch out!
Protect your left side!
What is that
on your belt, Dolltaki?
Dolltaki?
[DOLLTAKI]
Yes!
That doll you have there
seems to be important to you.
[PAN] Wait. Is he
talking about me?
[DOLLTAKI nervous laughter]
I'm glad you noticed.
She happens to be my favorite.
Whether or not
it's your favorite,
that doll appears to hold
a high-level of latent power.
Really?
What was she before you
turned her into a doll?
Her name was Pan. She was
with those scum fighting Luud.
But she's very different from
them and has a personality,
and is still
the cutest thing ever.
[DR. MYUU] So, she was
with those two punks, eh?
Put her inside Luud
so he can absorb her.
He needs the power
now more than ever.
[DOLLTAKI]
What?
[PAN]
No, not me!
It's the only way Luud will
have a chance at winning.
But I can't! I already promised
Pan that we would live together
in happiness for
the rest of eternity!
[PAN]
For once we agree, freak!
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but I'll be safer with you!
You are in no position to be
questioning my decisions.
You nitwit!
But why do you
have to take my Pan?
I could go find a few
people on the streets
that we could use!
Unacceptable!
[DOLLTAKI sobbing]
No! Pan!
Look. If you want to be
with that doll so badly,
I'll just arrange for both
of you to be absorbed by Luud.
We could use
the extra power anyways.
[DOLLTAKI screaming]
Guten Tag.
[PAN]
What's happening?
[BOTH yelling]
[LUUD groaning]
[PAN, DOLLTAKI yelling]
Pan!
[PAN]
Grandpa?
[PAN] This is not fun!
I want to go home!
[PAN, DOLLTAKI whimpering]
[LUUD groaning]
Pan! Where did you go?
Hey, Pan!
[LUUD growling]
[GOKU, TRUNKS yelling]
[water bubbling]
[DR. MYUU]
Now let's see what you can do.
[DR. MYUU cackling]
[LUUD groaning]
Whoa!
[NARRATOR]
Upon Dolltaki's failure
to resurrect Luud
to its most potent power level,
the villainous Dr. Myuu
found it necessary to step in
and take full control
of the proceedings.
Realizing that Luud would soon
be annihilated by
Goku and Trunks,
Myuu chose to absorb
both Dolltaki and Pan
into his mutant-machine,
giving it more
than enough energy
to advance to Level 3.
Pan!
[NARRATOR]
Find out the fate
of Goku's granddaughter
on the next GT!