[NARRATOR]
Last time on GT,
Doma was poised to cut Zoonama's
quake producing whiskers!
Never again will
you steal our peace!
[ZOONAMA] But before he
could finish the job,
Zoonama awoke and attempted
to conjure a quake!
However, this time his
true abilities were revealed.
[chanting]
[NARRATOR] The mighty Zoonama
wasn't so mighty after all!
He had the ability to predict
quakes, but not to cause them!
Trunks called his bluff
and now it was time to worry
about the real threat:
A temperamental volcano
that was ready to blow!
I don't want to die! Help me!
[NARRATOR] Never one to
back down from a challenge,
Goku decided to meet
the inferno, head on!
Ha!
[NARRATOR] Having quelled
both the forces of nature,
and the threat of Zoonama,
harmony was restored at last,
and payment in kind was
given for a job well done.
Thank you, Laine!
Thanks, Doma!
[NARRATOR] But before
the Six Star Ball was warm in
Pan's hand, an alien
presence made itself known,
and shocked the crowd!
Give that back! It's ours!
[BON PARA] Thanks for
the Dragon Ball, suckers!
[NARRATOR] The chase is on,
today on Dragon Ball GT.
Come on! Hurry!
I hope this crate has
got some speed, Trunks!
Don't worry about that!
[TRUNKS] And she's no crate!
I'll prove it to you!
[GIRU] Dragon Ball dead ahead!
Giru! Giru!
Dragon Ball dead ahead!
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
[PAN] There he is! Good job,
Trunks. Stay with him.
[GOKU] Our ship must
be faster than theirs.
[TRUNKS] I doubt he's played all
of his cards this quickly.
He's probably just testing us.
That is one weird looking ship.
Trunks! Can our ship
match that kind of speed?
[TRUNKS]
It has to!
[BON PARA] You should have seen
the look on their faces!
What a bunch of dopes!
[SON PARA]
Here! Let me see it!
Are you sure that
it's a Dragon Ball?
[BON PARA]
Yes, Son Para.
Well, it doesn't look
that special to me.
[DON PARA]
How could it, Son Para?
You're too skeptical, brother.
You don't know how to recognize
the finer things in life.
Don Para is right. You have
to have trust little brother.
Didn't Cardinal Mutchy Mutchy
assure us of their potency?
[beeping]
What is it?
[CONFIRMED]
A shadow has been confirmed
at five kilometers, sir.
[BON PARA]
On screen.
It's them! Maybe they're
not as dumb as we thought!
Maximum speed.
[COMPUTER]
Warp drives engaged, sir.
[PAN] They're getting away!
Do something!
We're not getting any closer!
What's wrong with this ship now?
Nothing. She's doing just
what she was designed to do.
They're simply faster than us.
And they're basically
reaching speeds
that my engineers
said couldn't be reached.
[PAN] How much are you paying
those guys, Trunks?
My engineers?
They're all making about
eight figures plus benefits.
That's a lot of money.
Well I'd cut their pay in
half with no benefits,
until they do better
than second best!
Man, I'm glad
you're not my boss.
[PAN]
Hello! Yes, I am.
[GIRU] Danger!
Asteroids approaching!
[PAN]
Look out!
[uneasy groaning]
Wow. That was some pretty
fancy flying. Good job.
Yeah, I thought we
were gonners, for sure.
They might be faster than us,
but no one can outrun me
when I'm behind the wheel.
[screams]
Nice Trunks!
If you're such a great pilot,
why don't you try
outrunning a few asteroids?
[BON PARA]
Persistent, aren't they?
What a nuisance!
Can't a person do a little
stealing without being hassled?
Maybe we underestimated them.
What are we going to do?
Computer! Any recommendations
on how to lose our shadow?
[COMPUTER] Yes, Bon Para!
I suggest an ambush!
Lead your pursuers to Beehey!
Therein dwell creatures
known as Moumas!
The Mouma are giant,
bloodthirsty worms
that can swallow a ship
in a single bite!
Mouma will destroy
your shadow for you, sir!
You will not even have
to lift a finger!
Computer!
I like your style! To Beehey!
They're jumping to light speed!
Don't let them get away!
[COMPUTER]
Approaching Beehey.
[BON PARA] Excellent!
I hope the Mouma are hungry!
[evil chuckling]
I guess we'll follow
them in. Here goes.
[PAN] How can you see
where you're going?
[TRUNKS]
I'm using my instruments.
Just a sec. I'll switch
on the spotlights.
[GOKU] Do you really think they
live in a place like this?
I doubt it. But they may
have a secret base here.
[BON PARA] Computer.
What are their chances?
[COMPUTER]
The cave system is a maze.
They have a fifty
percent chance
of successfully
navigating the corridors.
However, these calculations
were made before considering
the threat of the Mouma.
[BON PARA] What if you threw
them into the equation?
[COMPUTER] Their
chance of survival will then
decrease dramatically, sir. I
calculate less than one percent.
Less than one percent. Now those
are odds that I can live with!
How about you, brothers?
For sure! It works for me!
Good! Computer set
a course for Luud!
[COMPUTER] Course laid in, sir.
Destination, Luud.
[BELIEVERS]
Enyaka, Yakayaka!
Luud Dama Lama Sama!
Luud Dama--
[MUTCHY MUTCHY] Silence! One of
our journeymen has returned
with a Dragon Ball!
Don't just stand there!
You did bring a Dragon Ball,
didn't you?
Oh! Yes!
What happens if I didn't?
[MUTCHY MUTCHY]
Then you'll get the whip!
Now. Did you bring
a Dragon Ball or not?
No, Cardinal Mutchy Mutchy.
I searched far and wide,
but the galaxy is so vast,
and I had so little to go on.
I beg for your mercy.
[MUTCHY MUTCHY]
Failure is unacceptable!
Lord Luud has spoken!
H-He turned that
poor slob into a doll!
[MUTCHY MUTCHY] Was
carrying out Lord Luud's will
really so difficult?
Wouldn't it have
been easier than this?
[MUTCHY MUTCHY]
In life he was a failure!
But in death, this journeyman
has achieved greatness
because his vital energy
has been absorbed by
Lord Luud himself!
Let us beg of Luud that our end
might be just as
glorious as his!
Well?
When I say beg, I mean now!
[BELIEVERS]
Enyaka, Yakayaka!
Luud! Sama!
Dama Lama!
Dama Sama Lama!
Enyaka, Yakayaka!
Luud Dama Lama Sama!
Luud Dama...
[DON PARA] Paras!
Let's get out of here!
Brothers!
The one he dealt with harshly
failed where we succeeded!
We have a Dragon Ball!
Oh. Yeah, right.
That's the ticket! Be bold!
We're the ones in
the driver's seat!
That's what I'm saying!
[MUTCHY MUTCHY]
Next! Approach the altar.
Yes. O-Of course.
[MUTCHY MUTCHY] Did you bring
an offering for Lord Luud?
Yes, Cardinal.
My brothers and I have brought
a Dragon Ball as requested.
[MUTCHY MUTCHY]
Oh! Well then, let's see!
Yes. Well,
it's authentic all right!
Para brothers!
You have accomplished what
many others could not!
You are the first
ones to succeed!
See! There's nothing
to fear here, brothers!
He's rolling out
the red carpet for us!
I wonder what kind of
reward we're gonna get!
[MUTCHY MUTCHY] I wish I could
give the three of you a reward,
but sadly I can't.
I'm afraid you've
committed a terrible blunder.
According to a divine
message from Lord Luud,
you Para Para brothers
have let a Dragon Ball slip
through your fingers!
A grave offense indeed!
But we've got it!
[MUTCHY MUTCHY] The cretins that
you took this Dragon Ball from
had another one on their ship!
And you let it get away!
What do you have
to say for yourselves?
Give us another chance
Cardinal Mutchy Mutchy!
I beg you!
[MUTCHY MUTCHY]
I have interceded for you Paras!
You have one more chance!
Thank you, Cardinal! Thank you!
[MUTCHY MUTCHY]
Don't fail me!
Yes, Cardinal!
[BON PARA] Computer!
Set a course for Planet Beehey!
That ship we ditched
has a Dragon Ball on it,
and we Paras will be living in
a shoe box if we don't get it!
[COMPUTER]
Yes, sir! Destination, Beehey!
But! What if it's too late?
What if Mouma have
already eaten them?
I don't want to be a doll!
Computer! Maximum speed!
It's a maze!
We could search through
this rock for a whole year
and never find them.
I have an idea! Giru, locate
the Dragon Ball they stole.
[GIRU] Giru! Giru! Dragon Ball
gone! Dragon Ball missing!
What do you mean missing?
You're a walking Dragon Radar!
The Dragon Ball's signal has
got to be on there somewhere!
Unless you're
defective, that is!
Nothing.
None of the Balls are showing
up. Maybe he has to eat.
I think it's because
we're under solid rock.
Let's get out of here then!
For once, I think we're
in agreement on something.
[GIRU]
Monster! Monster!
Those things are disgusting!
Yeah, and dangerous!
Why can't I sense its energy?
[GIRU]
Monster approaching!
That is one big worm!
Trunks! Look out above!
[SON PARA] Wait! We're not going
further in there, are we?
[BON PARA] We don't
have a choice, brother!
[SON PARA] But what if a Mouma
gets a hold of us?
[BON PARA]
We'll have to take that risk!
[SON PARA] B-But our chances
of survival in there
are less than one percent!
Yes! But we're the
Para Brothers! Are we not?
[SON PARA] It's them.
They're alive.
[DON PARA]
Thank goodness!
[BON PARA]
They're stuck on their back!
[laughing]
[screaming]
[BON PARA]
Computer! Retreat!
[snarls]
Ha!
[GIRU]
Giru to the rescue!
[snarling]
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
[DON PARA]
Look at 'em!
They're standing up to Mouma!
Are they crazy?
[SON PARA] They're going
to die, brothers! It's suicide!
How perfect!
[BON PARA] While those idiots
are being brave
and getting themselves killed,
we'll sneak onto their ship
and take their Dragon Ball!
Ingenious!
It runs in the blood!
[battle crys]
[snarls]
How strong is he?
[TRUNKS] More company,
you guys! Look out!
What amazingly strong creatures!
All alone out here in space!
Who would have ever thought?
Let's hope we live
to tell about it!
[NARRATOR]
As Goku, Pan, and Trunks
stare into the jaws of death,
the Para Brothers take advantage
of an opportune moment!
Who is this
mysterious Lord Luud
and his bewitching
Cardinal Mutchy Mutchy,
who has the power to
turn people into dolls?
Ensnared in a deadly trap,
the voyagers from
Earth are in danger
of losing their Dragon Balls
and their lives
at the hands of a cult that
they don't even know exists!
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next Dragon Ball GT.