[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT...
The tide turned when Goku
transformed into a giant ape,
obtaining startling
levels of power that
surpassed anything
ever achieved by Baby.
However, Goku could not handle
the enormous amount of power
pulsating through his body,
causing the violent animal
instincts within to take over.
Without distinguishing
between friend and foe,
Goku began trampling the Tuffle
planet with all his might.
[PAN]
Grandpa! Stop it!
If you destroy the planet,
you'll kill your family!
[NARRATOR]
But just as Goku was about to
make waste of
everything before him,
his blind rage came
to a quick halt
as he caught sight
of the Earth.
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
[PAN]
You've got to stop this!
I'm your granddaughter
Pan, remember?
[NARRATOR]
And seeing the falling tears
of his granddaughter snapped
Goku back into reality.
[PAN]
Do you remember?
[GORILLA GOKU growling]
[NARRATOR]
With Goku finally back on track,
he focused his new power
at a much higher level,
transforming himself into
the ultimate stage
of Saiyan existence!
The strongest fighters the
universe has ever produced
continue their battle
today on Dragon Ball GT!
[GORILLA GOKU roaring]
No! Grandpa!
[PAN whimpering]
Hey! What is going on?
[PAN] He looks
completely different again!
Grandpa, I need to know.
[PAN] Are you still on
our side? The good side?
Yeah!
Yes! He did it!
All that work
we've done training
has finally paid off
for us big time!
Oh yeah! He's a
Super Saiyan Four!
Oh, wow! That's a
Super Saiyan Four?!
Amazing! You're telling me
that's the same little kid
whose tail we stretched out?!
Did I do all this?
Grandpa, don't you
remember what happened?
You turned into a giant gorilla
and started smashing
everything around you, even me!
Let's just be thankful that
I didn't have to step in.
Because I would have
knocked that Baby
back into the stone age!
However, I did notice good ol'
Goku has gotten much stronger!
But Grandpa, do you think
you'll ever get back
to your normal self?
Well, Pan...
This body and its amazing
powers are necessary right now.
It's the only way
to defeat Baby.
With Goku helping
me fight Baby,
he'll be a big pile of
mush when we're through!
That's right, Grandpa.
It's time you taught Baby that
he can't mess with our family
and get away with it!
Then that's what I'll do.
[SS4 GOKU] I know where
Baby's hiding right now
and if everything
goes smoothly,
Earth and all her people
will be back to normal
by the end of the day.
Mr. Satan, you'll
take care of Pan.
Of course! No problem!
I sense him nearby.
[BABY VEGETA] This is absurd!
I don't understand how
he was able to convert
the energy from the Earth.
I need an answer on this!
It doesn't make any sense.
[GOKU growling]
If he... If he can do that
then why can't I replicate it?
[BABY BULMA] It is puzzling.
The Blutz Waves he received
have only been
recorded from the moon.
I know that already!
What I need to find out is why
it didn't affect me the same.
Why didn't it
affect Vegeta?
I demand an answer
to my question!
[BABY BULMA]
I believe that is because
Vegeta does
not have a tail.
Of course. These putrid
Saiyans and their tails.
[BABY VEGETA gasps]
[BABY VEGETA growls]
He's coming.
I want a solution from you
within minutes, not hours!
Do you understand?
You had better not fail.
Yes, Baby.
[BABY BULMA shrieks]
I found you, Baby.
Heh. Was the gorilla too much
power for you to control?
Yeah. This is just
another costume change
for the weakling Saiyan.
[BABY BULMA shrieks]
Bulma!
Don't call me that.
[BABY BULMA] And don't act
like you know me, Saiyan!
You are my enemy,
and nothing more!
And very soon your
death will be at hand!
Bulma...
[SS4 GOKU] Baby, I will
never forgive you for this.
You fool!
I wouldn't be caught dead asking
for your forgiveness, Saiyan!
[BOTH grunting]
[SS4 GOKU screams]
[BABY VEGETA grunts]
[BOTH grunting, yelling]
[SUGORO] Attack, Goku!
Attack! Look out behind you!
Defense! Defense!
Now punch him some more!
I wonder what's wrong with Goku.
He appears to be holding back.
He should be much more
powerful than Baby.
[OLD KAI]
What are you two yapping about?
Wait a minute. What in
the world is going on here?
This fight should have
been over long ago.
That's what I said!
What are you thinking, Goku?
Take him out as
quickly as possible!
[BOTH grunting]
[BABY VEGETA]
Oo, that felt good!
[BABY VEGETA yelling]
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[BABY VEGETA grunting]
[SS4 GOKU chuckles]
Stop laughing!
[SS4 GOKU groans]
[BABY VEGETA panting]
[SS4 GOKU laughing]
[SS4 GOKU] Sorry about all
that. I'm surprised as well.
Surprised at how
strong I've become.
What do you mean?
Your punches only tickled,
like a tiny feather.
How dare you say that!
You will learn respect!
Revenge Death Ball!
[KIBITO]
Goku!
[SUBORO] He didn't even
try to get out of the way!
[OLD KAI] I hope he
knows what he's doing.
I got him!
[BABY VEGETA gasps]
That's impossible!
Ah! That Goku.
I wish he didn't have to be
so dramatic all the time.
Even I was getting worried
there for a little while.
[OLD KAI] So, anybody
want to bet on what Goku's
next move will be?
[BABY VEGETA] That attack should
have reduced him to ashes
and it did absolutely nothing!
Baby, you can never defeat me.
No!
[SS4 GOKU] My powers have
far surpassed yours, Tuffle,
and you know it.
Die, Saiyan! Die!
Die! Die! Die!
Listen Baby.
I cannot allow you to get away
with the trauma you've
caused to innocent people.
You've gone too far.
Now you've gotta deal with me.
[BABY VEGETA gasps]
[BABY VEGETA groaning]
[BABY VEGETA growling]
[BABY VEGETA screams]
Lord Baby!
[BABY VEGETA groaning]
[BABY BULMA] I can't allow
him to fail like this!
If that Saiyan beats him, our
entire race will become extinct.
I've got to get the
Amplifier up and running.
It might be our only hope!
[BABY VEGETA screams]
[BABY VEGETA cackling]
[BABY VEGETA] It's fitting
for a moronic Saiyan
that your ignorance
is showing again.
Who do you think
you're fighting here?
It's certainly not your enemy.
This is your friend
Vegeta's body.
So you can keep attacking Goku,
but all you will be doing
is killing your friend.
Hm. That's funny,
I've fought Vegeta,
and this is nowhere
near his breaking point.
So, you understand his
limits. That's perfect.
We'll just push
this fight along
until we reach that
breaking point!
[SS4 GOKU] You act like you know
the Saiyans inside and out,
but the fact is your knowledge
is dangerously lacking.
What you don't realize
is the longer a Saiyan
continues to fight, the
stronger he becomes.
Your warrior race...
It's sickening.
[BABY VEGETA yells]
I'm sick of playing
games with you, Baby.
[BABY VEGETA screams]
[BABY VEGETA] This can't be
the limit of my powers!
[BABY BULMA] Lord Baby!
Pull yourself together!
Bulma?
[BABY BULMA] You can't allow
that Saiyan to defeat you.
Not now!
We've almost completed your
plans of galactic development,
and are just weeks away
from changing the entire
galaxy into Tuffles!
Plus, I've solved
your gorilla problem.
I've found a way to
focus the Blutz waves.
[BABY VEGETA] It's about time
I was seeing some results.
[BABY BULMA] Look over
towards our tower my lord.
[BABY BULMA] This is the
Blutz-Wave Amplifier!
Blutz-Wave-what?
That's right! The moon's Blutz
waves, reflected off the Earth
will increase by 1,000%
and be transferred to you
when it's activated.
That will give us
the power needed
to increase your strength
to a level past the Saiyan's
without having to wait
for a tail to grow!
That's fine.
But will I be able to control my
own actions under that power?
I... I don't want to
demolish my own planet.
I just want to kill the Saiyan.
[SS4 GOKU]
Heads up, Baby!
Ka...Me...
Ha...Me...
Right now!
Yes! Do it!
[BABY VEGETA screaming]
What's he doing?
Oh man!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
This is not good
Kibito, not good.
He's going to smash
his own planet to bits
and kill everyone!
Ancestor, how
did he do that?
Even though he
didn't have a tail,
he was still able to
complete a metamorphosis!
If he stays like that, soon
no one will be able to stop him.
I'm afraid the way
things are now,
a Super Saiyan Four
might not be enough.
No way!
[OLD KAI] What will
likely happen is Baby
will lose complete control as
his brain slowly erodes away.
He's becoming so rash that's
he's actually regressing to
a level of zero
conscious reasoning.
He will proceed to eradicate
everything in his path,
until nothing is left.
[BABY BULMA] We did it,
Lord Baby! It worked!
Now go destroy that Saiyan!
Don't stop until he's dead!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[PAN, HERCULE whimpering]
Oh no! Not another giant monkey!
It's not safe here now, Pan.
Let's get out of
here while we can.
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[NARRATOR] Goku has
become a Super Saiyan Four,
and victory seems inevitable.
But witnessing Baby
transform into a giant ape
throws every
ambition into question.
[SS4 GOKU] You're still not
gonna get away with this!
[NARRATOR] As the gorilla rages
on under Baby's control,
his strength continues to grow.
Soon, even Goku's new abilities
won't be enough to contain
this powerful menace!
Find out what happens,
on the next Dragon Ball GT!