[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT...
Goku completed his
transformation into
a Super Saiyan Four,
and it seemed as if he
could finally put an end
to the reign of the Tuffles.
[SS4 GOKU]
Baby! You can never defeat me.
We'll see.
[SS4 GOKU] My powers have
far surpassed yours.
And you just can't handle it.
[BABY VEGETA groaning]
Lord Baby!
[SS4 GOKU]
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
[NARRATOR] Just when Goku
was on the brink of victory,
the Blutz-wave amplifier
focused on Baby Vegeta.
And almost instantly,
he was transformed into
a rampaging gorilla,
much like Goku was before.
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[NARRATOR] As the gorilla
Baby tramples his own planet
with indiscriminate rage,
Goku prepares to fight
back with all he's got.
Your still not going
to get away with this.
Find out if it's enough
right now on Dragon Ball GT!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
Heh. He's losing control and
sight of his objective.
He... He's gone mad. He's not
in control of himself anymore.
[BABY BULMA] Lord Baby,
you have to stop this.
Can you even understand
what I'm saying?
Baby! Stop it!
[HERCULE yelping]
[PAN]
Grandpa Satan!
Are you okay?
Yeah, sure. It was
kinda on purpose.
[PAN sighs]
[PAN gasps]
He's coming!
[BABY GORILLA roars]
[PAN yells]
What? We didn't
even scratch him?
Your fight's with me.
I hope you have enough
energy for a good one.
[SS4 GOKU grunts]
[PAN] Grandpa, You're squeezing
too tight. I can't breathe!
You two held
up pretty well.
Grandpa Goku!
[PAN] So, what's going to happen
to Baby? He's gotten so big.
He could kill us all
with a single attack.
[SS4 GOKU] He might be big, but
with my strength at this level,
I doubt he'll be able
to do that much.
[HERCULE]
No kidding? I'm impressed.
[SS4 GOKU] His power is
pretty great, but in the end
his rage will be his downfall.
He could never understand how
to control a Saiyan's abilities.
The only way we're ever
going to put an end to this,
is if we take Baby
to another planet
using my instant
transmission technique.
[PAN] But to do that, you'll
have to get really close to him.
Do you think you can?
[SS4 GOKU] It shouldn't be a
problem. I'm feeling confident.
[PAN] Make sure it's a
planet where no one lives.
Of course.
But I can't be sure
the planet we arrive at
won't increase his
powers or something.
That's it! I can take
Baby to the Other World,
and then Kibito Kai and Old Kai
can figure out what
I should do with him.
They're gonna love this plan.
[OLD KAI yelping]
[SUGORO]
Here you go.
Oh thank you.
[OLD KAI yelling]
I can't work with that.
He's much too big.
I can't even think under
this kind of pressure!
So instead of
throwing a tantrum,
shouldn't we be trying to come
up with a plan or something?
Does that smart mouth of yours
have any ideas on how
to get us out of this?
Well, we could hide and
not answer when they get here.
[OLD KAI]
Fine, I'll hide first!
Come on!
[SS4 GOKU] I can since that
Old Kai knows I'm coming.
[SS4 GOKU gasps]
[BABY GORILLA growling]
W-What's he doing?!
[BABY]
Flaming death ball!
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
How is it that you
spoke to me just now?
[BABY] Saiyans never learn.
Haven't you followed anything?
But you're not. You're
not moving your mouth.
[BABY]
So, you can pay attention.
Baby! Wherever you are
you'd better show yourself.
Our fight's not over!
[BABY] Please, use what
little brain you have.
Vegeta transformed
into the gorilla,
I did not. I am the parasite.
I control him, and I'm not
limited to just his body.
I can use his feeble
Saiyan mind, if I so desire,
to connect directly to yours.
We're close now.
I feel it.
[SS4 GOKU chuckling]
So if you're the puppet master,
then why did the gorilla
go on a rampage
and kill your Tuffle people?
[BABY]
Part of me did it for the fun.
The other part wanted to know
what it felt like
to be you, Goku.
[SS4 GOKU]
I would never knowingly
harm the innocent, Murderer!
[BABY] I'm not such a bad
puppet master, am I?
[SS4 GOKU grunting]
[BABY]
You're losing it.
You're not so sure you can
beat me anymore, are you?!
You've got doubt and fear
ruling your thoughts right now.
And it's quickly
becoming a reality to you
that your life is almost over.
Ha! Your overconfidence
will be your undoing.
[BABY]
Prove me wrong!
[KIBITO] We can be sure that
Goku is faster than Baby, right?
[OLD KAI] Yes, but in terms
of actual strength,
the balance is not
so easy to see.
This battle could
swing either way.
[SHUSUGORO giggling]
[SUGORO] Well, at least we'll
have good seats for the fight.
[BABY] I could squeeze you
until your bones shatter.
[SS4 GOKU] You always talk
about what you could do.
Why don't you give it a shot?
[BOTH grunting, growling]
[BABY GORILLA growling]
[SS4 GOKU panting]
[SS4 GOKU yelling]
[BABY GORILLA groaning]
No, please Baby!
[BABY] He shouldn't have
been able to do that!
And you shouldn't
underestimate your opponent.
[BABY GORILLA growling]
[SS4 GOKU] This looks bad. Maybe
I pushed a little too hard.
[CROWD screaming]
Videl, where are you? Videl?
Mama! Grandmother!
[SS4 GOKU]
He's aiming for the people.
Why are you taking it out
on them, when I'm right here?
[BABY] So you would know
just how much I hate you,
you worthless slime!
[SS4 GOKU gasps]
[BABY] Take a look at your
family and I'll prove it to you.
What? You can't--
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[BOTH gasping]
What was that?
Mama?
[PAN]
Grandpa!
[SS4 GOKU] Mr. Satan, can you
take care of these two?
You got it, Goku!
I can't do this.
[SS4 GOKU] I can't put
up with this anymore.
Grandmother, Mama wake up.
You have to wake up.
I think for our safety
as well as theirs,
maybe they should
stay like this.
At least for a little while,
until Goku knocks
off that gorilla.
[SS4 GOKU] You're playing
a dirty game here, Baby.
[BABY] No one ever presented
me with a rulebook
on taking over the galaxy.
But I'd say I'm doing quite well
considering that I'm winning.
[BABY]
Super Gallic Gun!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
Not the Earth!
[SS4 GOKU]
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
Ha!
No, it won't
make it in time!
[KRILLIN]
Please tell me this is the last
of what you need to buy today.
We need supplies. When they
call us to the Tuffle planet,
we want to be ready,
don't we, Dad?
[PEOPLE screaming]
[MARRON]
Dad, what is it?
I... I don't know.
[SS4 GOKU] Just what do
you think you're doing?
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[BABY]
What am I doing?
Anything I can to
see that horrified,
confused look on your face.
It's not about me, it's
about the people of Earth.
They may be your followers,
but it's my job to save
them from their leader.
Now, laugh at this!
[SS4 GOKU]
Ka...Me...Ha...Me...
Ha!
[BABY GORILLA groaning]
[BABY BULMA gasping]
[BOTH gasping]
[SS4 GOKU]
I'm sorry, Vegeta.
I had to sacrifice your body,
but it was for the survival
of the Earth and its people.
[SS4 GOKU] Please, I hope
you can forgive me.
I did my best, old friend.
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[GORILLA GOKU]
It can't be!
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[BABY] Well, your best just
wasn't good enough, old friend!
Impossible! How could
he withstand that?
[OLD KAI]
Oh, this isn't very good.
[KIBITP] But Ancestor, what
about Goku's Kamehameha Wave?
Shouldn't that have put
Baby down permanently?
No, something's different here.
Look at his eyes, would you?
There's a strange energy there.
[SUGORO] He just looks like
a big, crazy monkey to me.
I've got it. He went through
such an unnatural way of
achieving his gorilla form
that it may be causing
some adverse effects.
[BABY]
Now, it's my turn.
You can get out of the way
of this blast if you want to,
but first take a look at
what's right behind you.
From what I can tell, only one
more hit at full strength
and that precious planet of
yours will be blown to bits!
[BABY cackling]
And you're willing to
sink that low, Baby?
[BABY]
Super Gallic Gun!
[SS4 GOKU] If I get out of
the way, the Earth is doomed!
Baby! You have not
seen the last of me!
[BABY] Oh-ho! That's going
to leave a bruise!
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[BABY BULMA]
Lord Baby!
He's lost all control. If he
makes an attack like that again,
the force of the Earth's
explosion will send debris and
shockwaves smashing
into the Tuffle planet,
destroying it too.
But then if he does,
he'll kill himself.
Hasn't he thought about that?
[SUGORO] Well it doesn't
seem like there's
much thinking going on at all.
He's out of his gourd
like the old man said.
[NARRATOR] With Baby's mind
poisoned even further
by the his gorilla
transformation,
he has come to act
on only one emotion.
The desire to kill Goku.
But if Baby's rage carries with
it the destruction of the Earth,
then the Tuffle planet falls
with it, and everyone will die.
The Earth, now more
than ever, needs a hero.
Find out the
destiny of humankind
on the next episode
of Dragon Ball GT!