[NARRATOR] As the people
of Earth continue to enjoy
the peace that was
finally returned to them,
an enemy from the recent past
roams the lonely
caverns of Hell.
[DR. MYUU] Is there no end to
the emptiness in this place?
Trunks what's happening?
So the little guy
isn't dead after all.
Your time on this
planet is over!
[NARRATOR] Following
his destruction, Dr. Myuu
was sent to Hell, cursed
to wander for eternity.
But someone was
watching his every move.
[DR. GERO] I've waited a long
time for you, Dr. Myuu.
Who is that? And how
do you know my name?!
[DR. MYUU screams]
I am the great Dr. Gero, and I'm
most impressed with your work.
Oh, really? Then what do
you want with me, doctor?
I want your mind.
The scientific intelligence
from the most brilliant
descendant of the Tuffles.
[DR. MYUU cackling]
You have been banished here and
you think that some
research is going to save you?!
You're such a fool!
Then you must think it foolish
to exact revenge on Goku.
[DR. MYUU] What? You actually
know of a way to find him?
Well, Dr. Gero, it's a
pleasure to meet you.
[NARRATOR]
As these evil geniuses meet
for the first time, a plan of
vengeance is set in motion.
Find out the results of
this devastating union
today on Dragon Ball GT!
[PEOPLE murmuring]
[KIDS laughing]
Wow. This tastes delicious.
Well, thank you.
Now, some of this food might
taste a little different.
It's a fancy new style
of gourmet cooking
I've been playing around with.
All of it looks great.
I've never seen dishes prepared
quite like this before.
So, what's this one?
It looks like sushi.
That one is a
Paoz Turtle truffle.
Did you say turtle?
It's the tail meat,
which has the most flavor.
We also have seven
colored wart toad,
and some centipede eel soup,
to which I added my own
special blend of hot peppers.
Yeah, and you can only get these
awesome foods at Mount Paoz.
I love the seven-colored
wart toad. It's great!
[BULMA]
Well, I'm just not used to
such an exotic array
of foods for dinner.
Yeah, it's kind of
an acquired taste.
Shouldn't it taste
good to begin with?
Isn't Trunks supposed to
have been here by now?
Yeah, he's your son,
Bulma. Where is he?
Uh, I don't know.
He should have left
Capsule Corp a while ago.
[doorbell rings]
[PAN]
It's him! I'll get the door!
What took you so long?
Pan, help me...
Trunks what happened?
It was Android 17.
[PAN grunting]
Whoa!
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU]
Trunks, what is it?
[PAN]
Hey! What is that in the sky?
[BOTH gasping]
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOKU gasping]
There's something evil
about that. I can feel it.
[KING KAI]
And you would be right.
Hey, King Kai? Is that you?
I haven't seen you in ages.
[GOKU] How have you been?
Are things good up there?
I've been sick
with a cold, Goku.
But this is hardly
the time to discuss it.
Something evil is happening.
Earth and Hell have
become stuck together
in some kind of
space-time rift.
[CROWD gasping]
What in the world is that thing?
It's so big!
[ANDROID 17]
You and I are one in the same,
set apart by time and space.
But soon we will be one again.
[ANDROID 17] The gates
of Hell have been opened.
And I will bring forth a
torrent of evil from this world.
[ANDROID 17 grunting, yelling]
[ANDROID 17 yelling]
[CROWD clamoring]
It's the-- It's the
end of the world.
I've just gotta
get out of here.
[MOB shouting]
It's mine!
You... You jerk!!
[THEIF groaning]
[KING FURRY]
Please, citizens.
The best thing for you to
do right now is stay calm.
We don't even know what
we are dealing with yet.
After our scientists can
examine this phenomenon fully,
then we will report to
you all of the findings.
Move it, people.
We don't have all day!
[ANDROID 17 cackling]
I can feel the power of the
underworld pouring over me.
Earth is in for a shock the
likes of which she's never seen!
[GOBLINS murmuring]
[GOBLINS shouting]
[WOMAN shrieking]
[CROWD screaming]
[BOTH cackling]
It seems the first move in
your strategy is a success.
The powers resonating in the
identical Android 17's have
perfectly fused these
two worlds together.
Then we should have a toast.
I am grateful
to you, Dr. Myuu.
Were it not for your theories
on the permutation
of machine parts,
it would have been
impossible to create
these two halves of the
one perfect android.
[DR. GERO]
It's going to be beautiful.
My dream of replacing
the human race with
artificial intelligence
has finally been realized.
[DR. MYUU]
Artificial intelligence?
[DR. GERO]
Of course!
When our Android 17's
have become one entity,
their abilities and strength
will far exceed that of Cell's.
But then...
[DR. GERO] I have had
my particular problems
with him in the past.
[ANDROID 17]
Good morning, Dr. Gero.
[DR. GERO] Your repairs seem
to have taken very well.
[DR. GERO]
What are you doing, Number 17?!
[ANDROID 17]
The days of you controlling
my every move are over.
From this point forward, I
will make of the decisions
concerning myself! You'll never
have to worry about it again,
you rotten old man!
[DR. GERO]
No!
Using your theories, the human
emotions he experiened
should be gone.
So... We have
two Android 17's,
both with equal power
and no human emotions
to slow them down.
[DR. GERO chuckling]
That's right.
[DR. MYUU] But what happens
when these two come together?
They would have to be capable
of some amazing feats. Yes?
[DR. GERO] It was the
androids' lack of completion
that allowed one of them to
slip through to the earth.
That action opened the gap,
and now I have control over it.
When we cross into their world,
bringing these two
Android 17's to form
one perfect artificial being,
no one will dare to defy me!
And then I will order
him to wipe out all those
whoever stood their
ground and opposed my reign!
But, before any of that,
you're going to do away with a
certain little Saiyan, right?
Goku will meet his doom...
But simply killing
with a quick assault
doesn't utilize the kind of
vengeance I have planned.
That pathetic little Saiyan
will never know what hit him...
I know of some old friends
of his who would kill for
the chance to have a
word or two with him.
[TRUNKS groaning]
About time you woke up!
I've been so worried.
I'm okay, Mother.
Just, please,
Don't tell Dad
about this, okay?
It's about time, sleepyhead.
How are you feeling?
Well, I've been better.
Thanks for taking
care of me, guys.
You sure gave me a scare.
I've never seen
you so out of it.
[PAN] So, Trunks, tell me,
did you really fight Android 17?
[VIDEL] Yeah!
[BULLA] And what does that
[BULLA]
big hole the sky lead to?
It's keeps getting
bigger. Will it stop?
[CHI CHI]
Did the Android talk to you?
What did he say before
he beat you up?
Wait! Hold on.
Just give me a second
and I'll explain
everything to you.
I was driving. I had
just left Capsule Corp
and was heading over
here for dinner.
Driver, I'm running
a little late.
There's an extra
twenty in it for you
if you can get me there fast.
I've never let you
down before, sir.
[DRIVER shrieks]
Come on. We've got to
get you out of here!
What are you doing?!
That guy looked familiar.
[TRUNKS] I can't
believe it. That's either
a resurrected Android 17,
or a great duplicate.
[TRUNKS groans]
It's you, you're
Android 17, aren't you?
[TRUNKS groans]
You should have a look.
Do you have any clue what's on
the other side of that void?
You're looking at Hell.
What? That's--
That's not, it can't...
It is. And every enemy you
Saiyans and your little pals
have ever defeated is being
resurrected and brought here.
To finally exact
their revenge on Goku.
No I have to tell Goku.
[ANDROID 17] Yes. You tell
Goku that if he wants keep
this evil from destroying
his precious Earth,
then he'll come to Hell
alone to finish this!
He wants me to go to Hell?
[GOHAN]
Hey there, Dad.
You better take a look
at the television.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you are now watching
a live video feed.
This is happening right now.
Dozens of odd creatures
have descended from
the hole in the sky
and have begun a
rampage across the city!
[TRUNKS]
He was serious.
I guess. There's really no
way to fight them all at once.
I may have do what
that android said.
But what if Cell and
Frieza are resurrected and
come back to earth
with the others?
Well, that's why I'm going
to have to go to Hell,
to make sure something like
that will never happen up here.
How can you say
that so casually?
Because I'm interested.
I think I'd like
to see how strong
Cell and Frieza have
gotten over the years.
I... I bet I could
still take 'em!
Well, if you think so,
then I do, too.
Yes I support you all the way,
but I think you should
take me with you.
Sorry, Pan. But he has to
make this journey alone.
See you guys later! And don't
worry! You can count on me!
[VALESE shrieks]
[PUI PUI, GOTEN grunting]
Goten, that was so cool!
I've never seen
someone fight so fast!
[GOTEN]
Thanks!
[GOTEN screams]
Goten! Behind you!
[YAKON growling]
Hello!
[GOTEN]
Hey, Trunks.
[VALESE]
Goten, are you okay?
Well I hope I'm
not interrupting.
You know...
I was getting ready to take
that guy when you showed up.
Yeah. Sure you were.
[HERCULE panting]
I'm getting too old for this!
[PAN]
Hello!
Pan, what do you
think you're doing?!
[PAN grunting]
Now, that didn't take much!
[GOKU]
So, this is Hell, huh?
Looks pretty much the same
as last time I was here.
Well, at least it's a
familiar setting to fight in.
[GOKU]
I wonder who those guys are.
Why are all of you guys
tied up? Are you prisoners?
[DR. GERO]
No, but you are.
Welcome to Hell. We've
been expecting you, Goku.
Hey, Dr. Myuu. How you doing?
Somehow, I always figured
you'd end up down here.
[BOTH cackling]
[GOKU]
Oh and Dr. Gero, too. I get it.
I don't care what
kind of evil plan
the two of you
have conjured up.
If your business is with me,
you better let me know up front
instead of taking it
out on innocent people.
I'm perfectly willing
to take you on.
I've never backed down
from a challenge.
Unfortunately, we do not have
the time to deal
with you right now.
[BOTH]
So long, Goku.
Get back here! You've
gotta be kiddin' me!
You dragged me all
this way just to run?!
Hey! Wait a second!
That hole's not going to
close behind you, is it?!
Wait!!
This is really playing
dirty, you guys!
Open up the ground back
up so we can finish this!
[DR. GERO cackling]
[DR. GERO]
Seems the brilliant fighter
is not so brilliant a person.
You're just like a
naïve child, Goku,
falling right into our trap,
where you will spend
eternity in those caverns.
Oh, and Goku...
Remember, just
like any prisoner,
you'll have to get used
to your new cellmates!
The hole... It disappeared
in the blink of an eye.
So, how will Grandpa Goku
ever get back to us?
If he's trapped in Hell,
it's the same as
being dead, isn't it?
Uh... Well, that's not true. I'm
sure he'll make it back somehow.
[GOKU]
Hey! We're not finished!
What do you mean cellmates?
There's no one else down here!
You two said all of my enemies
were resurrected just to
get me here, you liars!
[FRIEZA] 'Liar' is such an ugly
word from your mouth, Goku.
[CELL] The doctors have
never disappointed you.
What makes you think
they would start now?
I guess I put my foot
in my mouth, huh?
This phase is complete.
Goku is locked down
there permanently.
If you feel the time is right,
we can move into phase three.
A full force attack!
[BOTH cackling]
[NARRATOR] Will Pan and
the others be able to
defend Earth against this
evil with Goku locked away?
And will the teaming
up of Cell and Frieza
be too much strength
for Goku to handle?
Or does he have another
trick up his sleeve?
[GOKU] I've learned a few things
since the last time we met.