[NARRATOR]
On the last episode of GT...
the earthquake-loving
Naturon Shenron
was reducing the cities
of Earth to rubble.
Though unsightly in form,
the Seven-Star Dragon was not
without his special talents!
[NATURON SHENRON]
See that?
That's what I like to call
the Aftershock Technique.
No one can handle a concentrated
blast of energy from below.
Everyone gets blown away!
[NARRATOR] But Naturon Shenron's
earthbound techniques
proved to be ineffective against
his airborne adversaries!
[NATURON SHENRON]
What's wrong with you?
Why do you keep
making fun of me?
I'll show you what kind of
dragon you're dealing with!
I'm trying to concen--
[NARRATOR]
Outwitted and demoralized,
the giant Mole Dragon
went down for the count!
And when he coughed up
the Seven-Star Dragon Ball,
it seemed like the battle
had been won at last!
[PAN]
The Seven-Star Ball is ours!
[NARRATOR] But Naturon Shenron
was far from beaten!
The conniving dragon had simply
saved his deadliest
attack for last!
[PAN]
Grandpa!
Come on!
[NARRATOR]
Goku could only watch in horror
as Pan was sucked into
Naturon's deadly trap!
Stretched and disfigured,
the young beauty was
becoming part of the beast!
It was a nightmarish
sight to behold.
Pan and the Shadow Dragon
were one and the same!
[NATURON SHENRON]
Time to start the next round!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru!
The power you had
earlier has all but vanished.
Why don't you turn back
into the red monkey
and we'll really get
this party started.
[NARRATOR]
Bolstered by Pan's strength,
Naturon Shenron was more
dangerous than ever!
Can Goku counter attack
without hurting Pan?
[PEOPLE screaming]
[GOKU grunting]
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
[NATURON SHENRON grunting]
Go ahead and admit it!
You love me!
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
Grandpa! Help me!
What have you done
with my granddaughter?
Let Pan go right now!
Whatd'ya mean? There is no Pan!
I'm your grandchild now!
Come here and give
me a hug, Grandpa!
[GOKU]
He's using Pan's power!
That means she's got to be
alive in there somewhere!
Well, Pops, do we fight or hug?
Stop calling me that! We fight!
Then forgive me if I use
an old family tradition!
Ka, me...
Ha, me...
Ha!
[NATURON SHENRON]
Pretty cool, huh?
No! You hurt people!
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
[NATURON SHENRON] So, you
don't want me to hurt people!
Is that it?!
Oh, yeah! Blowing buildings
up is so much more exciting
than shaking them
apart with earthquakes!
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
What's wrong, Grandpa?
Don't you want
the Seven-Star Ball?
Or are you too
scared to get it?
I thought as much!
[LITTLE GIRL sobbing]
[LITTLE GIRL]
Mommy! Come back! Where are you?
Don't leave me,
Mommy! I'm scared!
Naturon! Leave these
people alone!
Your fight is with me!
Grandpa! Don't let him kill any
more innocent people! Please!
Pan!
Don't worry about me!
Follow your heart! Fight!
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
One over here! One over there!
That looks nice!
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
I'm Naturon!
Come on! Try and stop me!
I am the most powerful
dragon on Earth!
[PAN] What are you
waiting for, Grandpa?
You can't let him do this!
I don't want to be responsible
for people getting hurt!
Attack him with
all that you've got!
[GOKU] Thank you, Pan.
I wasn't seeing clearly.
I let my concern for you
cloud my better judgment.
[GOKU yelling]
Sorry! Unfortunately for you,
I'm no longer the
one in charge here.
Pan is giving the orders now.
And she wants
the killing to stop!
[GOKU yelling]
[NATURON SHENRON yelping]
[SS4 GOKU] This is what
you wanted, isn't it?
You asked for the
"red monkey" right?
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
Your power level has changed,
but the situation
remains the same!
I have your granddaughter!
Enough of that!
I know what's at stake!
If you hurt me,
you're hurting Pan!
[NATURON SHENRON groaning]
How could you?
[SS4 GOKU] You know, it's funny.
When I'm at this power level
it's hard for me
to listen to reason.
You see, I just lose control.
[NATURON SHENRON groaning]
See! I can't help myself!
I just feel like
destroying things at random!
You shouldn't have
called me out like that!
There's no telling
what I'm liable to do!
[PAN grunts]
All right! Now that's the
Grandpa I know and love!
Oh, please!
You can't be serious!
Do you really intend to
kill your own granddaughter?
Don't you care about her?!
[SS4 GOKU] Pan would
rather die than sit back
and watch you kill
innocent people.
Sure! That's what you say now!
But you won't have
the heart to do it!
[NATURON SHENRON]
Let go of me!
[SS4 GOKU] You're the one
who started this game!
Why are you afraid
to finish it?
[NATURON SHENRON] You better
hope I don't get loose, Saiyan
or I'll tear your
hairy body to shreds!
[NATURON SHENRON yelling]
[NATURON SHENRON groaning]
[SS4 GOKU] Naturon! I've had
enough! The game's over!
Are you crazy?!
You'll kill your
granddaughter with that!
[NATURON SHENRON groans]
You brought this upon
yourself, you know.
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
Yes! It's clear now!
You can't kill me!
Oh, no? And just what
gave you that idea?
You backed off!
You were gathering energy
for a finishing blast,
but you didn't have the
stomach for it, did you?
[NATURON SHENRON] You can't kill
me because you can't kill Pan!
[SS4 GOKU]
I wouldn't count on it!
You wouldn't, huh?
Then hit me with a
Kamehameha Wave right now!
Do it, Grandpa.
You can't do it! Can you?
I thought as much!
No monkey-brained Saiyan
is going to outsmart
the great Naturon Shenron!
It looks like we've
come to a stalemate!
[NATURON SHENRON]
Now! Step aside!
You heard me! Move it!
Finish me off now or
never bother me again!
Ha! I love it!
Now, Grandpa! Please!
You know what you have to do!
Forget about what you
want and do what's right!
Pan...
[PAN]
Got your nose!
Trunks! Grandpa!
Look! I found it!
Grandpa, be strong. I don't
want to live like this!
Pan!
I'm so sorry!
You wouldn't dare!
Oh, no?
Yeah. We've already been
down this road once before.
It was a dead end.
Did you forget already?
[SS4 GOKU]
Ka... Me... Ha...
Fool! I know you're bluffing!
Me...
[NATURON SHENRON]
You'll kill her!
Life is nothing without freedom!
You've taken Pan's,
but I won't let you
take anyone else's!
Do it, Grandpa!
Wait! Let's not be hasty now!
Ha!
I can't believe this
is happening to me!
[PAN]
Goodbye, Grandpa! I love you!
Tell Mom and Dad
I tried my best!
[GOHAN]
Mm! That tea smells good.
I brought some
fresh spring water.
Great. We're gonna need it.
The faucets won't
even trickle anymore.
[VIDEL] I hope everything's
okay out there.
I'm worried about Pan.
[VIDEL]
I don't know what I'd do
if anything happened
to her, Gohan.
[GOHAN] Yeah well, knowing
our daughter, I'd say those
seven dragons are the ones that
need to be worried, not us.
I guess you're right.
[VIDEL] She's with your dad.
What could go wrong?
[GOHAN]
Yeah, she'll be just fine.
[SS4 GOKU panting]
Pan!
[SS4 GOKU gasps]
Grandpa, it didn't work!
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
What happened?
You... You were hit head on with
my Ultimate Kamehameha Blast!
You should be dead right now!
Not quite! You call that
an Ultimate Kamehameha?
Guess you're not as
strong as I thought!
What are you talking about?!
I released all the power I had!
If that were true, I wouldn't
be standing here right now!
Would I?!
I doubt that was any stronger
then a regular Kamehameha!
You've lost your resolve, Goku!
Hmm, hmm, hmm!
You blew it! I win!
You don't know what
you're talking about!
[SS4 GOKU groans]
[NATURON SHENRON] The great
Goku reduced to a coward
who can't fight
back! What a joke!
You should see
yourself! It's pitiful!
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
[SS4 GOKU grunting]
I want you to feel like warm
mud squishing between my toes!
No! Fight him, Grandpa!
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[NATURON SHENRON]
Head's up, Saiyan!
Bull's eye!
Grandpa!
My body feels like
it's made out of lead.
My energy's almost gone.
[NATURON SHENRON]
So you've run out of gas, eh?
Looks like my keen intellect
has triumphed over your might!
Yes! Your granddaughter has
given me a new lease on life!
Without her, I'd be
in your shoes right now!
Heh. This is crazy.
I never would have imagined
that it would end like this.
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
Grandpa, what are you doing?
[PAN] You can't give in!
Get up and fight!
He's finished,
but before he dies
I will demonstrate
my greatest power!
The power to grant wishes!
Now you will see that
I am a true Shenron!
You wish to see your
granddaughter one last time!
[NATURON SHENRON] So be it!
Your wish shall be granted!
It's me, Pan!
Can you hear me?
Grandpa! Don't give in!
Please fight!
You're better than this!
You're Goku!
You can do anything!
Enough! That is all!
My patience has run out!
[NATURON SHENRON]
I'm finished here now.
Your wish has been granted!
Grandpa!
[SS4 GOKU grunts]
[NATURON SHENRON gasps]
Grandpa!
[NATURON SHENRON]
But I had you!
Well, not quite. I was saving
a little for a rainy day.
[SS4 GOKU yelling]
[PAN yelps]
[NATURON SHENRON groaning]
Gotcha!
No!
[NATURON SHENRON screaming]
Hey.
Did we win?
[SS4 GOKU] So! That's your
true form I take it!
[NATURON SHENRON yelping]
Scared, huh?
Well, I don't blame you.
When you go about
hurting others,
you can expect that hurt
to revisit you someday.
[NATURON SHENRON yelping]
[SS4 GOKU] You can run,
but you can't hide, Naturon!
Even if you escaped from me,
you would still have to
atone for your deeds!
I would?
Yep. That's right!
[NATURON SHENRON]
I feel so naked!
I need to find
someone to absorb!
[SS4 GOKU]
Hey, what's the matter, Naturon?
You've lost all of your
courage, your zest!
You were so bold before!
I guess you're just too
scared to be yourself.
[bird squaking]
[NATURON SHENRON] It's not much,
but it's better than nothing!
Man! Give it up!
[NATURON SHENRON cackling]
[NATURON SHENRON gasps]
[bird squaks]
Naturon, you have zero
respect for the lives of others.
And you have no intention
of changing, do you?
You're just going to
go on hurting people.
Not true! I'm a
changed dragon, I swear!
That was a bird!
I would never hurt a person!
Nice try! But that
will be your last bluff!
[NATURON SHENRON groaning]
[SS4 GOKU] You're finished!
It's over! No more killing!
How does it feel? Now you
know how your victims felt
when you ended
their lives.
[NATURON SHENRON groaning]
The time has come
for atonement, Naturon.
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
...Ha!
[SS4 GOKU]
Got it!
[GOKU]
Okay, Giru! Now!
[GIRU] Pan! Danger! Seven-Star
Dragon! Seven-Star Dragon!
[GOKU mocking] Now that
I've absorbed your Grandpa,
I'll absorb you again!
[PAN yelps]
[PAN]
Grandpa!
[GOKU laughing]
I had to do it. Sorry.
You had to?
Well, I have to hit
you on the head!
[GOKU]
Hey! No fair!
[PAN]
Come back here, you coward!
[GIRU] Goku, run! Pan,
mad! Extreme danger!
Extreme danger! Run!
[GOKU laughing]
[PAN laughing]
[NARRATOR] After surviving
the scare with Naturon,
Pan and Goku fly
into the unknown,
ready to face one
of the three dragons
that are still
roaming the Earth!
Hatched from decades of
accumulated negative energy,
there's no way of knowing
what monstrous potential
these dragons possess.