[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball GT,
General Rilldo lay in defeat,
but the impending threat
of the bone-chilling Baby
was still a reality.
Meanwhile, the
mission to recover
the four remaining
Dragon Balls had begun,
and the voyagers from Earth
had their first ball on radar.
But retrieving it from
the war-ravaged ship
would be dangerous.
The vessel was about
to be engulfed
in the fire of a nearby star.
[NARRATOR]
After finding the Dragon Ball,
another discovery was made!
A young survivor was still
on board the spacecraft!
[GIRU] We have one minute
to leave the ship! Giru, Giru!
We've got a lot of
ground to cover!
Trunks, pick him
up and let's go!
--Hurry!
--Right!
[NARRATOR] The foursome
managed to escape from the ship,
but the gravitational
grip of the star
was pulling them
towards a fiery doom!
Using a Kamehameha Wave,
Goku gave them the
boost that freed them
from the star's deadly gravity.
Planet Vidal was the next stop.
Boasting state of the
art medical facilities,
it was the perfect
haven for recuperation!
But was something amiss
with the mysterious
survivor from outer space?
[NURSE] Please, get back to bed!
You have to have your rest.
[DOCTOR]
What? I'm serious!
[ORDERLY] We need to get
them out of there!
[NURSE] The Fire Department
is on the way!
[DOCTOR] There's no time!
They'll be fried!
[groaning]
[PAN] Excuse me! Doctors!
Where's the little boy?
He's still in there!
It's too hot for us to get past
the threshold of the doorway!
[all choking]
[GOKU] Hey, you guys!
Look what I found!
[laughs]
What an extraordinary child!
--Bravo!
--Truly!
Way to go, Grandpa! Yeah!
I hope this changes your
opinions about doctors, Grandpa!
They're on the same side
as you are! See? Huh?
[TRUNKS]
Hmm?
He's more scared
of them than before.
[PAN]
Huh? No...
Bet?
[DOCTOR] This boy is
either extremely lucky
or extremely unlucky!
[ORDERLY] Yeah. That's the
second time he's almost died
since he's been here!
[DOCTOR] And the second time
that he's been saved!
[Baby laughing in his head]
[PAN] Grandpa!
Stop acting so silly!
They don't want to
give you a shot!
There's nothing wrong with you!
I'm not going in there!
I hate hospitals!
You're acting like a
little baby, Grandpa!
Besides, they have
food in there!
[GOKU] I refuse to eat
any nasty hospital food!
But Goku! This planet
doesn't have restaurants!
You have to eat here!
Then I'll starve to death!
Hospital food has sick
germs, and it tastes bad!
[PAN]
This hospital is different!
[GOKU]
I don't care!
[PAN]
What are we going to do?
[TRUNKS]
I don't know.
[PAN] If you don't climb down,
we'll drag you down!
[GOKU]
Try it!
These pathetic weaklings
don't have a clue!
[GREEN BOY] Childish minds
are so easily manipulated
by outer appearances!
It's a crime, really.
[evil giggling]
Surprise, surprise...
Baby on board.
Those trusting fools are
making this all too easy for me.
[PAN]
Just a little further!
[GOKU]
No! Let go!
In my present state it would
be risky to take them on
all at once, but if
I get one alone...
...I could steal his flesh
and then I'd be unstoppable!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
[GOKU] Giru, when you see
a fish you're not supposed to
start yelling!
You have to be quiet!
[GIRU]
Okay!
Giru!
[GIRU]
Uh, okay.
Darn it!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru...
Giru!
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru...
[GIRU] Trunks!
Help! Big fish!
[PAN] Come 'ere, little guy!
Aw! How cute!
Hey! What are you doing?
[GREEN BOY]
He thinks you're his mother!
He's a little confused.
Boy! I'll say! Hey! It's you!
What are you doing out of bed?
Well, I'm embarrassed to say it,
but I can't stand getting shots!
That sounds oddly similar
to someone else I know!
Your friend, where is he anyway?
Huh? Oh! You mean my Grandpa!
He went fishing, I think!
Hey!
[BABY] This is too perfect!
Her body is mine for the taking!
[PAN] You naughty little boy!
Shame on you!
[BABY] Yes! That's it! Keep
fawning over that fawn, my dear!
[PAN] What do you want from me,
you silly goose?
[GOKU]
Hey, Pan!
Hi, Grandpa! I'm over here!
We were wondering
where you went!
We've been looking
all over for you!
[PAN]
Look who else is here, you guys!
Hi, there. The doctor
was looking for you.
He said you should
still be in bed.
You'd better do what he says!
Grandpa! You're one
to talk, aren't you?
Ohh! There you are!
You should be back
in bed, my boy!
[DOCTOR]
You're not out of hot water yet!
But, I feel fine, sir. Honestly!
Now you see here, young man!
You need to get more bed rest!
[DOCTOR]
Your condition was far more
precarious than you realize!
And that's that!
It's not that I don't
advocate outdoor convalescence.
It's just that we
can't go from A to D.
First we have to go to B and C!
"B" being bed rest
and "C" being check up!
[DOCTOR]
I'm sure you understand!
I don't blame you for
wanting to be outside
on such a beautiful day!
Huh? Mighty Milky Way!
What is this?!
[evil giggling]
[DOCTOR]
Excuse me, nurse.
Would you mind taking this
patient back to his room for me?
Sure! I'd be happy to, Doctor!
[evil giggling]
[TRUNKS] Ahhh!
I don't know about you guys,
but this little rest
has done me good!
I'm actually feeling fired up
about tracking down the
last three Dragon Balls!
We're so close!
Ugh.
I can't wait to sleep
in my own bed again!
Oh, I see! Feeling a
little homesick, are we Pan?
No, that's not it!
[Goku groaning]
I can't take it anymore!
What's the matter, Grandpa?
He's been like
this for a while now.
I think I'm dying, guys!
If I don't get something
to eat, I'll whither away!
Goku! You can't fall apart
every time your
stomach starts growling!
I can't help it.
My body just runs out of gas.
It's been this way
ever since I was born.
[PAN] I thought
you guys went fishing!
Don't tell me you
didn't catch anything!
I caught dozens! But they tasted
so bad I couldn't eat them!
Those were some
nasty tasting fish!
He's not exaggerating!
Don't talk about it!
That was the most
horrible experience ever!
You've been traumatized! Look!
You need some
immediate food therapy!
Let's give the cafeteria
here a chance!
[GOKU] Never! They'll try
to give me a shot!
Oh, ho, ho!
We would never do such a thing!
We could lose our license
for giving a healthy
person an injection!
[TRUNKS] Really?
You wouldn't give me a shot
if I came in to eat? Promise?
Because I'd rather
starve than get a needle!
I assure you, nothing
of the sort would happen!
I swear on my honor
as a medical doctor!
Hmm.
[GIRU] Interesting! Ingoing mass
exceeds dimensions of stomach!
Wooooo! I feel mighty
again! Good food, huh?
One more plate, old man!
Y-Yes. One more.
Please excuse
my Grandpa, Doctor!
He has no manners because
he was raised in the wild!
[DOCTOR]
I see.
[NURSE]
Here you are.
Now that's service!
Trunks, you asked about our
technology... Is that correct?
[TRUNKS]
Yes!
You have a true
interest, don't you?
Might I satisfy
your fascination
with a grand tour of
our fine facility?
Yeah! I mean, yes! I'd like
that very much! Thank you!
That's what my family does
back home! We invent things!
Then it's settled!
I think you'll find the
technology here most intriguing!
[TRUNKS]
No doubt! Thanks, Doctor!
This is turning out
to be a great visit!
[Baby's evil laughter]
[DOCTOR] This is our
Super Electron Microscope!
Wow! I like it!
[DOCTOR]
It's quite different than most
other Electron Microscopes.
I think you'll be
amazed at the detail.
[DOCTOR] Please!
By all means! Take a look!
[TRUNKS]
Thank you!
[TRUNKS] This can't be!
These electrons are enormous!
And it's all
three-dimensional! Wow!
[TRUNKS] You can
move amongst the atoms
as if you're in there with them!
An interactive microscope!
This is pure genius!
It's decades ahead
of any microscope
we've developed on Earth!
How beautiful! It's like
being in a whole new Universe!
And my board members said
that this couldn't be done!
What a bunch of--
Doc! Why?
[BABY] Because I want
your power! That's why!
That voice!
You're not the Doctor!
You're Baby! But how?
[evil giggling]
You thought you could
make Baby go away!
But as long as one of my
cells lives, I can regenerate!
[BABY] From there
it was simply a matter
of leap-frogging
from body to body,
until I gathered enough energy
to develop into
my current state.
But I'm not finished yet!
What about the spaceship?
What happened to all
the people on board?
Well, they became
baby food so to speak!
But at least they all died for
a worthy and historic purpose!
You fiend! How could
you do such a thing?
[maniacal laughter]
If you really want to know,
I'll show you first hand!
The tour didn't turn out
to be what I expected!
[GOKU]
I noticed! Haaaa!
You shouldn't have
picked a doctor to hide in.
I'm naturally on guard
against them as it is!
But how? How'd you
know I was alive?
I was able to sense your energy!
You did a perfect job
of suppressing it,
but you made one little slip!
When you attacked the doctor,
we were able to
feel your energy,
even if it was
just for a minute!
We didn't know who you attacked!
But we did know you were
somewhere on the planet!
We figured you'd hide until
the odds were in your favor!
So, we decided to let ourselves
be put in vulnerable situations,
to try to draw you out!
This time we won't
make the same mistake!
We'll make sure that every
last cell is destroyed!
Hold on a second! Before this
gets serious, tell us one thing!
Where did the Dragon Ball
come from that you used
to lure us to that ship?
Not that it's any
of your business,
but that was the first
Dragon Ball we discovered!
It was digitized
and then transmitted
directly into
Doctor Myuu's head,
where it was then stored in
his memory banks as data!
Digitized! I see!
Do you have anymore like that?
[BABY]
No! I only had the one!
But after I kill all of you,
I'll have four! Won't I?
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
No more body snatching, Baby!
You would be free to go
if you weren't so intent
on hurting people!
[GOKU] You can't go on doing
what you did on that spaceship!
You spared no one!
Not even the children!
Ahhh!
[Baby screaming]
[Baby giggles]
[screams]
We blew it!
Trunks, no!
[BABY] I've never felt
anything like this before!
This is the
Saiyan power I desire!
Hey! Get out of him right now!
All right! That does it!
Get out of my friend's body this
instant or I'll blast you out!
Grandpa! Wait! What do
you think you're doing?
What d'ya mean?
If you hit him with that
blast, Trunks will die!
I'll try to hit him in a
way that he stays alive!
What? Are you crazy?
[BABY] Goodbye! Not
even you can block this blast
from point-blank range!
[PAN]
Trunks! Don't do it!
[BABY]
What happened?
[TRUNKS]
I happened, Baby!
[BABY] What? No!
You shouldn't be able to talk!
I should be in complete
control of this body,
its mind, and all
of its functions!
He's talking to Trunks! Trunks?
Can you still hear me in there?
[TRUNKS] This is my body!
You get out of here! Right now!
[TRUNKS]
Get out!
[BABY]
He still resists!
What kind of absurdly powerful
people are these Saiyans?
[TRUNKS]
Get out of my body!
[Trunks screams]
[GOKU] That's it, Trunks!
Don't give in! You can do it!
[GOKU]
He did it!
[GIRU]
Yee-hoo!
[strained breathing]
I wasn't strong enough!
Taking over a Saiyan
requires more power!
Come on, Trunks!
Let's finish the job!
[GIRU]
Uh-oh! Giru, Giru.
Baby is getting away!
We have to finish him now!
[STEWARDESS]
Ladies and gentlemen,
Flight 1138 is now
boarding on platform seven!
If you are carrying a handset,
tickets are still
available for purchase.
Thank you for choosing Starline
as your intergalactic carrier!
Starline! We fly on the
sunny side of every eclipse!
[LARGE LADY]
Hmm?
Oh?!
[screams]
[STEWARD]
Ma'am! Are you okay?
[LARGE LADY] Yes! I'm just
nervous about flying!
[STEWARD] Well, you have nothing
to worry about. Trust me.
[GOKU]
I sensed him for a second,
but now he's hiding
his energy again!
[STEWARDESS] Please limit
yourself to three pieces
of carry-on baggage!
This is the final call for all
passengers boarding Flight 1138!
Grandpa?
He could be in any
one of them. Couldn't he?
Yeah. We lost him.
Let's get back to the ship.
We'll never find him here.
Have a nice flight, Sir.
[MAN]
Thank you!
[STEWARDESS] Ma'm!
Have a nice flight.
I can't stand the thought that
someone has that sick creature
in their body right now.
That is so nasty!
He could be in anyone!
Who knows who he'll pick next!
[GIRU]
Giru. Giru.
I have a hunch it'll be someone
small and helpless like Giru!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru!
What's he after? There's a whole
Universe he could prey on!
Why did he decide to lure us
to him with his Dragon Ball?
[PAN]
Hmm?
Well, I just assumed
it was because
he wanted to steal our
three Dragon Balls.
What else could it be?
He did seem a little
obsessed with Saiyan power.
Maybe it was our bodies
that he really wanted.
What do you think, Grandpa?
Who? Me? Well, I think
I need something to eat!
Uh! Don't answer this,
but do you ever
think about anything
other than food?
Huh? Yes. Of course, I do!
But not when I'm this hungry.
[NARRATOR] As Goku,
Pan, and Trunks plot a course
to retrieve the three
remaining Dragon Balls,
the insidious Neo-mutant, Baby,
feasts on the unsuspecting
passengers of Flight 1138!
[CAPTAIN]
Ladies and gentlemen,
please notice that the Fasten
Seat Belt sign has come on.
We're approaching
some solar winds
that might cause a little chop.
Thank you, and I hope you're
enjoying your flight so far.
[evil giggling]
Oh, I am!
[BABY] A paltry
meal to say the least,
but it seemed to
raise my spirit a bit!
Besides, it was better
than a bag of peanuts!
[evil giggling]
Now that the Saiyans have
revealed their true power to me,
I know exactly how much
power I need to destroy them!