- ( people chanting )
- Chloe: NOIR.
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE,
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
TO THE DEPTHS
OF HELL'S FIRE,
THEIR BLACK SOULS
LURE THE LOST CHILDREN.
- ( birds chirping )
- ( moans )
- Altena's voice:
"MY DARLING CHLOE,
I REJOICE TO HEAR THAT
YOU HAVE SAFELY ACCOMPLISHED
YOUR ASSIGNED TASK.
I ANTICIPATE YOUR RETURN
FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
HOWEVER, BEFORE THAT
JOYOUS EVENT CAN OCCUR,
I REGRET TO INFORM YOU
THAT THERE IS ONE MORE JOB
THAT I MUST HAVE YOU DO."
- ( stomps, clanks )
- ( door closes )
- ( sighing )
- SOMETHING'S WRONG.
THEY'RE LATE.
- Man: I'M AFRAID YOU ARE
WASTING YOUR TIME WAITING.
- Man #2: Z-- ZELLNER!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- YOUR FRIENDS HAVE
LEFT THIS WORLD
ONE STEP AHEAD OF YOU.
- WH-- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- ( gasps )
- ( cocks )
- DIVERTING SOME
OF MY PRECIOUS PRODUCT
WAS A MISTAKE.
A MISTAKE THAT
YOU WILL NOT MAKE AGAIN.
- WE'LL GIVE BACK THE GOODS!
- NOW JUST HOLD ON, ZELLNER,
WE WERE ONLY--
- ( men whimper )
- YOU WILL FIND
MY MEN ARE WELL-VERSED
IN THE SCIENCE
OF INFLICTING PAIN.
THE TRICKS THEY LEARNED
IN EAST GERMANY
SHOULD AMUSE YOU
BEFORE YOU DIE.
- Man #3: ZELLNER, WAIT!  WAIT!
- Man #2: NO!  NO!
- Man #3: FOR THE LOVE OF GOD!
NO NO NO!
- ( sighs )
HOW IS THE REIMANN SANCTION?
- ROSHMAN REPORTS THAT HIS
TEAM HAS ENTERED SWITZERLAND.
HE SAYS THEY'LL LAUNCH
THE STRIKE TOMORROW.
- MMM.
THE WALL IS GONE,
BUT THE PAST REMAINS.
YOU WILL PAY, REIMANN.
YOU WILL PAY.
- HMM?
AH.
YOU ARE SOLDATS.
- THAT'S RIGHT. GENERAL
DIETER REIMANN, I PRESUME.
- YOU HAVE COME TO KILL ME,
I SUPPOSE.
- YES.
- ( men grunt )
- Reimann:
IT'S ALL RIGHT, HEINZ.
- HUH?
- I'M SORRY.
IT IS THEIR JOB
TO BE MY BODYGUARDS,
AS YOU KNOW.
IT'S BEEN QUITE A WHILE
SINCE I LEFT THE BUSINESS.
BUT NATO STILL FRETS OVER ME,
OR AT LEAST THE THINGS
I HAVE LOCKED IN MY HEAD.
I USUALLY TAKE
A WALK EVERY AFTERNOON
ABOUT THIS TIME.
WOULD YOU CARE TO JOIN ME?
- Heinz: GENERAL.
- DOWN, HEINZ.
SO, YOUNG LADY,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO ACCOMPANY ME?
- SURE.
- YOU WILL.
WUNDERBAR.
- AND WE'LL ACCOMPANY YOU.
- NO.
THAT WON'T BE NECESSARY.
- BUT, SIR!
- LET'S NOT GET BOORISH AGAIN,
SHALL WE, HEINZ?
- SIR!
- Man: WE'RE NOT JUST GONNA
LET HIM GO, ARE WE?
- WE HAVE NO CHOICE. WE'LL HAVE
TO GUARD HIM FROM A DISTANCE.
BUT IF I KNOW THE GENERAL,
HE'LL BE TAKING
HIS USUAL ROUTE.
- HMM.
- THOSE ARE ALPINE ROSES,
MY DEAR.
A TRUE EMBODIMENT OF THE ALPS.
THEY ARE QUITE LOVELY, YES?
- THEIR COLOR IS BEAUTIFUL--
PALER THAN CRIMSON,
YET DARKER THAN PINK.
- INDEED.
AND THE ROSES IN THIS MEADOW
ARE OF AN ESPECIALLY
DELICATE SHADE AS WELL.
YOU HAVE AN EXCELLENT EYE.
- MMM.
GO.
- THE WOODS AND MEADOWS HERE
ARE FILLED WITH LIGHT.
THAT'S WHY I CAME HERE
WHEN I RETIRED.
THE FORESTS WHERE I GREW UP
IN GERMANY WERE DARK--
DARK AND TERRIBLE.
THEY WERE THEN
AND THEY STILL ARE.
OVER THE YEARS,
I SOILED MY HANDS MANY TIMES.
SOMETIMES I DID IT
BECAUSE I BELIEVED IT WAS RIGHT.
BUT THERE WERE OTHER TIMES
WHEN I WAS BLINDLY
FOLLOWING THE ORDERS
ISSUED BY THE SOLDATS,
AND I QUESTIONED
NEITHER THE REASONS
NOR THE MORALITY
OF MY ACTIONS.
THAT'S RIGHT, NEVER QUESTION
THE WILL OF THE SOLDATS.
THAT WAS MY RULE,
YOU KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I MADE IT
ALL THE WAY TO GENERAL.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW THE REASONS
FOR WHICH THE SOLDATS
HAVE ORDERED MY DEATH?
- I DON'T.
- BUT EVEN SO,
YOU STILL INTEND TO KILL ME.
- YES.
- YOU SEEM TO HAVE TAKEN
QUITE A LIKING TO THOSE FLOWERS.
- HUH? ( cries out )
- ( thunks )
- ( groans )
( panting )
- STAY HERE, PLEASE.
- HUH?  BUT WHAT--
- ( gunfire )
- ( gasps )
- ( knife zings )
- ( man screams )
- ( gasps )
- ( knife zings )
- ( screams )
- ( gunfire )
- ( grunts, screams )
- ( Roshman exhales sharply )
WHERE THE HELL IS HE?
( gasps )
- ( knife zings )
- ( screams )
- ( sighs )
( sniffs )
- ( rock music plays )
- ( both gasp )
- WHAT-- WHAT IN THE HELL
HAS BEEN HAPPENING HERE?
- HEY, THIS IS--
- Bodyguard: GENERAL!
- GENERAL, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT!
- YES, I'M QUITE FINE...
THANKS TO THIS YOUNG LADY.
- HUH?
- AH.
- Reimann: THAT ONE WAS
THE LEADER OF THE ATTACKERS.
- THAT'S ROSHMAN.
HE USED TO BE AN ASSASSIN
FOR THE S.G.T.
- I THOUGHT SO.
- THANK YOU, MISS.
I SEEM TO OWE YOU MY LIFE.
- THE FACT THAT I'VE BEEN TASKED
WITH KILLING YOU HASN'T CHANGED.
- HMM.
- THESE FOOLS WOULD'VE
HINDERED ME IN THAT TASK.
IT WAS SIMPLY EASIER
TO KILL THEM.
- ( wind howling )
- THE WIND SEEMS
TO BE PICKING UP A BIT.
I THINK
A STORM IS ON THE WAY.
( sits )
I HAD THOSE ASSASSINS CHECKED.
EX-S.G.T.,
THE OLD EAST GERMAN
NATIONAL SECURITY BUREAU.
AFTER THE WALL
CAME DOWN IN BERLIN,
THEIR LEADER,
CONRAD ZELLNER,
USED THE KNOWLEDGE
HE'D ACCUMULATED
DURING THE COLD WAR TO BUILD
HIS OWN CRIMINAL NETWORK.
HE'S CURRENTLY AMASSING
A HUGE PERSONAL FORTUNE
IN ILLEGAL NARCOTICS.
WHILE I WAS POSTED
WITH NATO INTELLIGENCE,
WE WERE CONSTANTLY AT ODDS.
IT WAS A DIRTY,
NO-HOLDS-BARRED STRUGGLE.
WE EVEN ATTACKED AND KILLED
EACH OTHER'S FAMILIES.
WHAT FOOLS WE WERE.
I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW FOOLISH
UNTIL I LOST MY OWN DAUGHTER.
- MMM.
- YES, ZELLNER KILLED
MY DAUGHTER...
BRUTALLY.
HORRIBLY.
WITHOUT MERCY.
- REVENGE MUST BE
CARRIED OUT PROPERLY.
- THAT IDEA IS ITSELF MISTAKEN,
FOR ONCE BEGUN, REVENGE
BECOMES AN EVER-GROWING WEB
THAT ENSNARES
EVEN THOSE WHO SPIN IT.
I'M SORRY.
ALL OF THIS TALK WAS
NO DOUBT POINTLESS
FOR AN EMISSARY
OF THE SOLDATS.
- ( rain pattering )
- SO THEN...
HOW IS THE WINE?
- DELICIOUS.
HOWEVER,
THE WINE AT THE MANOR
IS EVEN BETTER.
- THE MANOR?
- YES, THAT IS WHERE I LIVE
WITH MISTRESS ALTENA.
- ALTENA.
I'VE NEVER MET THE LADY,
BUT HER NAME IS
CERTAINLY FAMILIAR TO ME.
( gasps )
CAN IT BE...
THAT YOU ARE
THE ONE CALLED NOIR?
- YES.
- I KNEW THAT
THERE WERE ASSASSINS
IN THE PAST WHO HAD
CALLED THEMSELVES NOIR,
AND YET I NEVER THOUGHT
I MIGHT LIVE
TO SEE NOIR MYSELF.
- HEINZ AND THE OTHERS
KNOW NOTHING ABOUT THE SOLDATS.
IF POSSIBLE,
I WOULD LIKE THEM SPARED.
- VERY WELL.
- I AM GRATEFUL.
- ( wind blowing )
- ( glass shatters )
- ( women singing )
- MMM.
- ( breathing shakily )
- I JUST MADE A PERSONAL
PROMISE TO THE GENERAL.
- ( zings )
- IF POSSIBLE, I WOULD
VERY MUCH LIKE TO KEEP IT.
- ( women singing )
- ( gun clicks )
- ( sighs )
- AT LAST,
GENERAL REIMANN IS DEAD.
- YES SIR.
- NATO'S OLD FOX IS
COMMITTED TO THE DARKNESS.
THIS IS THE MOST JOYOUS NEWS
SINCE THE REUNIFICATION.
- ( hesitantly )
UH, YES, EXCEPT--
- WHAT IS IT?
JUST TELL ME, VINT!
- IT SEEMS THAT
SOMEONE ELSE KILLED REIMANN,
ALONG WITH OUR ENTIRE
ASSAULT TEAM.
- WHAT?!
AND WHAT HAPPENED TO ROSHMAN?
- IT SEEMS HE'S DEAD AS WELL.
OUR SOURCES DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED OR EVEN WHEN.
- ( sighs )
I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU WILL TAKE COMMAND
OF IT, PERSONALLY.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?
- SIR!
- A NEW SHIPMENT OF PRODUCT
WILL BE ARRIVING NEXT WEEK.
MAKE SURE
THAT NOTHING GOES WRONG.
- RIGHT.
( gasps )
( footsteps approach )
WHO IN THE HELL COULD'VE--
- ( clatters )
- ( gasps )
- HUH?
NO NO.
IT'S NOTHING.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'LL MAKE ALL THE ARRANGEMENTS
FOR THE SHIP ON OUR END.
VERY GOOD.
I APPRECIATE YOUR COOPERATION.
- ( phone clatters )
- WHO ARE YOU?!
HOW DID YOU GET PAST
MY GUARDS?!
- ( clicks )
- HEY,
IS THERE ANYONE OUT THERE?!
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU?!
SOMEONE PICK UP
THE PHONE, DAMN IT!
- ( clicking )
- Zellner: VINT!
( breathing heavily )
WHO-- WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT?
( whimpers )
- ( knife whooshes, slices )
- ( grunts )
( gags )
- ( clatters )
- ( footsteps depart )
- ( Chloe shouts ) ALTENA!
- CHLOE.
- ( both laughing )
- ( sighs )
- MMM.
WELCOME HOME, PRECIOUS.
- ( sighs )
I AM HOME.
- NOW LET ME SEE YOUR FACE,
MY CHLOE.
LET ME SEE THAT YOU ARE WELL.
- MA'AM.
I HAVE SO MUCH
TO TELL YOU THIS TIME.
I MET HER LIKE YOU SAID.
AND LOOK,
I RECEIVED THIS FROM HER.
- MY.
YOU MUST BE SO TIRED.
COME ALONG.
LET US GO INSIDE
AND YOU CAN TELL ME
ALL ABOUT IT.
- ( women singing )