- ( chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR, IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS WHO
GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE
OF THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ( gasps )
WE HAVE A JOB.
- WHO'S THE TARGET?
- ALBERT DUX.
HE SEEMS TO QUITE
THE NOTORIOUS VILLAIN.
DUX IS A STAR ON THE RISE
IN THE BUSINESS WORLD,
A REAL BIG SHOT.
HOWEVER, WHEN
THE YOUNG PRESIDENT
OF THE VAGNIER GROUP...
- ( camera shutter clicking )
- ...DIED IN AN ACCIDENT,
THERE WERE QUESTIONS.
NONE OF
THE DECEASED'S RELATIVES
THINK IT
WAS AN ACCIDENT.
- ( printing )
( printer beeps )
- SO WHO IS THAT?
- IT'S THE YOUNG
PRESIDENT'S WIDOW,
OUR CLIENT.
- YOU'VE SEEN HER BEFORE?
- YES.
I'D LIKE SOME OF THESE.
- OUI, MADAME.
THE BELLADONNA LILIES,
CORRECT?
- YOU'VE BOUGHT THOSE BEFORE,
HAVEN'T YOU?
- WHY, YES.  YOU REMEMBER
THE STRANGEST THINGS.
- ( gasps )
WE'VE MET BEFORE,
HAVEN'T WE?
- YES, WE HAVE.
A FRIEND OF MINE
IS BURIED HERE.
- WELL, DO YOU COME OFTEN?
- NO, ONLY OCCASIONALLY.
- AH.
- ACTUALLY, WE WEREN'T
ALL THAT CLOSE.
BUT THEN AGAIN,
AT THE SAME TIME,
I DID SORT OF
CARE ABOUT HIM.
- I SEE.
AND DID HE LIKE
BELLADONNA LILIES?
- WELL, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- YOU SOUND MUCH LIKE ME.
- LIKE YOU?
- YES, THE PERSON
I CARED FOR
ALSO LIKED
BELLADONNA LILIES.
I HATED THEM AT FIRST,
YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE I HAD HEARD THAT
BELLADONNAS ARE POISONOUS,
BUT THEN ONE DAY I LEARNED
THAT BELLADONNA LILIES
ARE OF A COMPLETELY SPECIES.
I SUPPOSE
THAT IN THE END,
IT WOULDN'T HAVE MADE
A DIFFERENCE, THOUGH.
THEY WERE ALWAYS THE FLOWERS
THAT HE LOVED THE MOST.
- HMM.
- ( guns cock )
- SO WE'RE
GOING TO DO IT?
- YES, WE ARE.
DUX RECENTLY PURCHASED
A RESORT HOTEL.
HE'S STAYING THERE
IN A SUITE
WHILE SUPERVISING ARRANGEMENTS
FOR REMODELING
BEFORE THE HOTEL RE-OPENS.
IT'S A GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY.
DUX'S SUITE
IS ON THE TOP FLOOR.
THERE ARE THREE ROUTES.
YOU'LL COME IN
USING THE STAIRS
THAT GO TO THE EMERGENCY EXIT,
ALL RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- ( wincing )
- WELL, I MUST SAY
I NEVER THOUGHT
THAT THE GREAT NOIR
WOULD TURN OUT
TO BE A YOUNG LADY
LIKE YOU.
- PLEASE, DROP YOUR WEAPON.
- ( gasps )
SO YOU WERE THE ONE.
- ( gunfire )
- ( gasping )
- ( both gasp )
- ( door opens )
- SEAL OFF THE HOTEL
AT ONCE!
MAKE SURE THEY
HAVE NOWHERE TO RUN.
TO THINK THAT NOIR
WAS TWO PEOPLE.
- ( panting )
- ( frustrated sigh )
- I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS WHOLE THING
WAS A SETUP,
AND DUX AND OUR CLIENT
WERE IN IT TOGETHER.
IT WOULD SEEM THE TARGET'S NAME
HAS BEEN CHANGED.
- THEY WERE AFTER US
TO START WITH.
THEY'RE AFTER NOIR.
- BUT THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
WHY WOULD SOMEONE GO TO
SUCH LENGTHS TO CATCH US?
- THEY'RE PROFESSIONALS,
JUST LIKE US.
SOMEONE MUST BE
PAYING THEM.
- SO YOU THINK
THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE
BEHIND THIS AS WELL?
- YES.
THE HUNTER AND THE HUNTED
HAVE SWITCHED PLACES.
THAT'S ALL.
IT DOESN'T ALTER THE FACT
THAT WE'RE DEALING
IN HUMAN LIVES.
- HMPH.  ALL RIGHT.
BUT THEN WHO IS
THE MASTERMIND?
- THE ENEMY.
- YOU MEAN THE ONES
WHO STOLE YOUR MEMORY?
THEY'VE MADE THEIR MOVE.
LET'S MAKE OURS.
- ( panting )
( panting )
( men panting )
( running footsteps )
- ( gunshots )
- ( groaning )
- SQUAD "C"?!
SQUAD "C," REPORT.
THEY GOT SQUAD "C" TOO.
IT SEEMS NOIR IS CERTAINLY
LIVING UP TO THEIR REPUTATION.
INITIATE PLAN THREE.
- Man: ( through radio )
THIS IS SQUAD B.
BOTH TARGETS HAVE
ENTERED THE CASINO.
- UNDERSTOOD.
ALL SQUADS REGROUP AND
WAIT FOR INSTRUCTIONS.
- LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE BEEN HERDED HERE.
HMM.
WANT A DRINK?
OR IF YOU PREFER, WE ALSO
HAVE SOME POPCORN.
- Dux: ALL RIGHT, CUT IT.
- I GUESS THEY MEAN
TO DUKE IT OUT HERE.
- POPCORN.
- HMM?
- I'D THINK I'D LIKE
TO HAVE SOME.
- UH-HUH.
- LET'S DO IT.
- ( crunches )
- ( gasps ) OH.
- ( gunshot )
- ( yelps )
- ( crunches )
- HUH?
- ( screams )
- ( running footsteps )
- ( gasps )
- WHAA!
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- ( automatic gunfire )
( gunfire continues )
- ( screams )
- ( distant gunfire )
- ( men grunting )
( screaming )
- ( gasps )
( groaning )
THE FIRST TIME WE MET
WAS COINCIDENCE.
- I'VE OFTEN THOUGHT
THAT PEOPLE LIKE US
SHOULD NEVER VISIT CEMETERIES.
WE JUST SEEM TO FALL
INTO THE GRAVES
AT OUR FEET OURSELVES.
- ALMOST AS IF
THE OTHER SIDE
WAS CALLING US.
- I HAVE TO WONDER
IF THE DEAD
WERE BLINDING US AS WELL.
- ( gasps )
MAYBE SO.
- WHAT ABOUT THAT GRAVE?
- IT'S MY HUSBAND'S.
- WHO WAS NOT
THE YOUNG PRESIDENT?
- BUT WHEN I TOLD YOU
THAT HE LIKED THOSE FLOWERS,
THAT MUCH WAS TRUE.
- TELL ME ONE THING.
WHO WAS IT THAT HIRED YOU
TO KILL NOIR?
- IF YOU WERE ME,
WOULD YOU TELL?
- NO WAY.
- ( laughs )
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- ( gasps )
( strains, coughs )
WHAT'S THE POINT
OF ASKING?
NEITHER YOU NOR I
HAVE GRAVES WAITING
ON WHICH
TO COVER OUR NAMES.
( gasping )
NEITHER YOU NOR--
- I DON'T GET IT.
- ( printing )
- THE ENEMY HIRED DUX
AND HIS MEN
TO ELIMINATE NOIR.
BUT DUX HAD NEVER BEEN TOLD
THAT NOIR
WAS YOU AND I.
DO YOU SUPPOSE THAT MAYBE
IT REALLY WAS
SOME KIND OF GAME
AND DUX, YOU AND I
WERE NOTHING MORE THAN
PIECES ON THE BOARD?
- I GUESS SO.
- NOW WE KNOW THE ENEMY
IS ALWAYS WATCHING.
EVEN NOW THEY'RE WATCHING US
FROM SOMEWHERE...
IN THE SHADOWS.
( sighs )
AND IN THE END,
WE HAVE NO CHOICE,
EXCEPT TO KEEP WINNING
THESE GAMES, RIGHT?
- YES.
AND SOMEDAY...
- NOT HAVING A GRAVE
ISN'T SOMETHING
THAT SADDENS ME...
BECAUSE IT IS THE PATH
I CHOSE FOR MYSELF.
I KNOW THAT THIS
IS NOT YOUR GRAVE,
BUT SO WHAT?
SO WHAT IF THAT'S TRUE?
- ( women chanting )
- ( techno music playing )