- ( people chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR.
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE,
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE
OF THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
NOIR.
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE...
Kirika and Chloe:
TWO MAIDENS WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE OF THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE,
TWO MAIDENS WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE OF THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
IT IS THE NAME...
- NO.  KIRIKA.
- KIRIKA!
- ( gasps )
AM I-- AM I...?
MIREILLE?
THE TEA.
IT'S ALREADY GETTING COLD.
- YEAH.
- ALTENA.
( giggling )
- ( sighs )
BUT YOU'VE ALREADY READ
THIS BOOK SO MANY TIMES, CHLOE.
I WANT TO HEAR YOU SAY IT ONE
LAST TIME BEFORE THE RITUAL,
THE WAY YOU USED
TO TELL ME IN BED.
- ( sighs )
IT IS A STORY AS OLD
AS HISTORY ITSELF.
IT WAS A THOUSAND YEARS AGO
AT THE END
OF THE 10th CENTURY
WHEN THE PEOPLE FINALLY SAW
THE TRUE SHAPE OFF THIS WORLD.
THERE HAD BEEN
AN ABOMINABLE PLOT,
AN ATTEMPT TO GAIN POWER.
MANY PEOPLE WERE KILLED.
NEITHER THE OLD AND INFIRM,
NOR THE YOUNGEST CHILD
WERE SPARED.
THE WORST ATROCITIES
THAT MAN COULD COMMIT
AGAINST HIS FELLOW MAN
WERE COMMITTED.
BUT THERE WERE THOSE
WHO SURVIVED THAT HELL,
PEOPLE WHO SAW THE DEPTH
TO WHICH MEN COULD DESCEND
WITH THEIR OWN EYES.
AND THOSE PEOPLE UNDERSTOOD.
THEY KNEW THEN
THE TRUE NATURE OF MAN,
THAT THE EARTH WAS FILLED
WITH EVIL AND DESPAIR.
THOSE WHO HAD SURVIVED
SWORE TO EACH OTHER THAT
THEY WOULD SEEK REVENGE
AGAINST THIS WORLD,
THAT THEY WOULD HELP
THE WEAK AND THE PERSECUTED,
THAT THEY WOULD REALIZE
JUSTICE ON THIS EARTH.
THEY SWORE A VOW
OF SECRECY AND LOYALTY,
AND FROM THAT SEED
THE ROOTS OF THE SOLDATS
FIRST TOOK HOLD
IN THE LAND OF MEN.
THE BLOOD OF THE SOLDATS WILL
SEEP THROUGHOUT THE WILDERNESS
AND FLOW
INTO THE GREAT RIVER.
THE SEEDS OF THE SOLDATS
SCATTERED TO THE WIND,
TAKING UP SECRET LIVES
IN THE DARKENED SHADOWS
OF HUMAN SOCIETY,
IN EVERY PART OF THIS WORLD
WHERE MEN MIGHT LIVE.
- THE BLOOD OF THE SOLDATS WILL
SEEP THROUGHOUT THE WILDERNESS
AND FLOW
INTO THE GREAT RIVER.
- AND NOW, COUNTLESS
MONTHS AND YEARS LATER,
IT HAS COME TO PASS.
THE BLOOD OF THE SOLDATS NOT
ONLY RUNS THROUGHOUT THE WORLD,
IT IS THE WORLD.
- HOWEVER, WE MUST STILL
CONTINUE OUR ACTIVITIES
IN ORDER TO PRESERVE
THIS WORLD.
BUT ALTENA--
- YES, ALTENA,
THE MERCIFUL MOTHER.
IN A WAY,
SHE IS CORRECT.
THE IDEALS OF THE SOLDAT
SHOULD BE REALIZED.
- BUT IN THIS DAY,
NOIR WOULD BE AN ANACHRONISM.
ALTENA'S ATTEMPTS
AT RESTORATION
ARE COMPLETELY DELUSIONAL.
IT'S JUST A FARCE.
- THE GRAND RETOUR
IS IN ACCORDANCE
WITH THE SOLDATS'
COLLECTIVE WILL.
AS LONG AS ALTENA
CHAMPIONS ITS CAUSE,
WE CANNOT OPENLY OPPOSE HER.
- BUT IF WE ALLOW
THE RITUAL TO BE PERFORMED
AS ORIGINALLY PLANNED, THAT
MEANS THAT ALTENA WILL BECOME
THE NEXT HIGH PRIESTESS
OF THE SOLDATS.
- THAT WOMAN DOESN'T
UNDERSTAND ANYTHING AT ALL.
POWER AND WEALTH ARE WHAT MAKE
THE WORLD TURN UPON ITS AXIS.
- ( door closes )
- Altena's voice:
IF LOVE CAN KILL,
THEN SURELY HATRED CAN SAVE.
THOUGH THE AGES COME AND GO,
THE WORLD OF MAN
DOES NOT CHANGE.
THE LANDS OVERFLOW
WITH GRIEF
AND MEN COMMIT WICKED DEED
UPON WICKED DEED.
AND AS FOR HEAVEN,
HEAVEN MAINTAINS
ITS SILENCE.
BUT SOMEONE
MUST BEAR THE SINS.
SOMEONE MUST BEAR THE SINS.
AMONGST THE SOLDATS OF OLD,
THE LEGEND
OF TWO MAIDENS BEGAN.
TWO MAIDENS WHO SERVED GOD,
YET DARED
TO TAKE UP THEIR SWORDS,
WHOSE VALOR WAS GREATER THAN
THAT OF THOUSANDS OF KNIGHTS.
BLESSED WITH THE MERCIFULNESS
OF THE HOLY MOTHER
AND THE GRIM REAPER'S
HEART OF STONE,
TWO MAIDENS
WHOSE BLACK HANDS
PLAYED ATTENDANT
TO THE SOLDATS' HIGHEST PRIEST.
TWO MAIDENS WHOSE NAME
WAS NOIR.
- Mireille:
I'M BEGINNING TO SEE
HOW ALL THIS FITS TOGETHER.
- HUH?
- IT WAS THEIR NOIR
AND NOT THE ONE WE FORMED
THAT WAS THE REASON
THAT THE SOLDATS CAME AFTER
US IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THAT'S WHY
THEY ISSUED AN ORDER
TO HAVE
THE TWO OF US SANCTIONED
YET, AT THE SAME TIME,
HID OUR IDENTITIES
FROM THEIR OWN HITMEN,
EVEN THOUGH
THEY KNEW WHERE WE LIVED.
WHY WOULD THEY DO THAT?
BECAUSE THOSE ARE
SIMPLY THE RULES.
- TRIALS.
THE FATE OF THOSE
WHO ARE TO BECOME NOIR
- THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE THE RULES CALL FOR US
TO DODGE THE TRAPS THEY SET.
MAKING US PLAY THE GAME
WAS THEIR REAL GOAL ALL ALONG.
( sighs )
AND THEN THERE'S YOU.
THERE WAS SOMETHING
SPECIAL ABOUT YOUR ROLE
IN THIS FROM THE BEGINNING.
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT CHLOE SAID,
THAT YOU AND SHE
WERE SPECIAL.
- MIREILLE.
- OH YES, YOU AND CHLOE
ARE DEFINITELY SPECIAL.
DO YOU REMEMBER HOW WHEN
CHLOE FIRST APPEARED TO US?
SHE SAID--
- MIREILLE!
MIREILLE.
PLEASE STOP.
- ( sighs )
WHEN SHE CLAIMED
TO BE THE TRUE NOIR,
I FELT AS IF SHE WAS
A REFLECTION OF MYSELF.
BUT IT SEEMS THAT REFLECTION
WASN'T OF ME, WAS IT?
- ( rock music plays )
- Altena: PLEASE TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF CHLOE.
THE TIME OF THE RITUAL
IS DRAWING NEAR EVERY DAY.
THE TASK OF GIVING HER
THE FINAL GUIDANCE
MUST FALL TO YOU.
- RIGHT.
I WILL,
BUT WHAT ABOUT HER FRIEND?
- YOU MUST KNOW
AS WELL AS I,
THAT THE DAUGHTER
OF CORSICA IS ALSO FIT.
- YES, BUT--
- ( chuckles )
BUT YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO FEAR, CHILD.
JUST AS YOU HAVE
ALWAYS BELIEVED,
YOU AND KIRIKA
ARE MOST SPECIAL.
- ( sighs )
- YOU MUST SHOW
HER FRIEND WHY,
AND TO DO SO,
YOU NEED ONLY THE TRUTH.
SHOW HER THE TRUTH, CHLOE.
- I WILL.
- Mireille: IF YOU AND CHLOE
ARE THE TRUE NOIR,
THEN WHAT AM I?
NOIR IS A PAIR
OF CHOSEN ASSASSINS.
SO IF THE SOLDATS' GOAL IS
TO TEST YOUR QUALIFICATIONS,
WHAT'S MY ROLE HERE?
- ( train rattling )
- Altena:
THE TWO HANDS OF THE SOLDATS
ARE TWO MAIDENS,
TWO MAIDENS WHO HAVE
NO FEAR OF BEING SULLIED,
TESTED BY THE MOST
RIGOROUS STANDARDS
AND BOUND BY THE BLACK THREAD
OF FATE ITSELF
TO EACH OTHER
AND TO THEIR
MOST SUBLIME DUTY.
- CHLOE HAS BEGUN
TO TAKE ACTION.
- THAT IS NOT GOOD.
- IF THEY ENTER THE MANOR,
THEY WILL BE
BEYOND OUR REACH.
- ( thunder crashing )
- TONIGHT WE WILL SET
THE KNIGHTS OF PARIS IN MOTION.
HOWEVER...
- HOWEVER?
- ...WILL EVEN THEY BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT
ALTENA'S CHOSEN TWO?
- HMM.
- AND CAN THEY DEFEAT
THE MERCIFUL MOTHER ALTENA?
ONCE FEARED TO HAVE
GOVERNED DEATH ITSELF?
- ( thunder crashing )
- ( grunts )
- ( panting )
- ( yelps, grunting )
- ( men groan )
- ( cocks )
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( grunting )
( yells, grunts )
( breathing heavily )
- ( silenced gunfire )
- ( grunts )
- ( yells )
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( gun cocks )
- ( gasps )
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts, gags )
- Altena:
IT IS IN THE NATURE OF MAN
TO COMMIT SIN.
AND NO MATTER HOW
HE STRUGGLES...
- ...NO MAN CAN ESCAPE
THAT FATE.
IT IS THEREFORE
OUR DUTY TO SOIL OUR HANDS
FOR THE SAKE OF MAN,
JUST AS THE SINS
OF THE SOLDATS OF OLD,
WERE COMMITTED IN ATONEMENT
FOR THE SINS
OF MAN HIMSELF...
- ( men grunting )
- ...NOIR WILL COMMIT
SIN UPON SIN.
THE HISTORY OF SIN
WILL BE REPEATED
WITHOUT END...
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
- ( thunder crashing )
- ( bullets ricochet )
- Altena: NOIR WILL
COMMIT SIN UPON SIN.
- ( man screams )
- ( sighs )
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
- THE TWO OF YOU HAVE
OVERCOME ALL OF THE TRIALS.
IT SEEMS THE DEPTH
OF YOUR SINS
IS TRULY WORTHY
OF THE NAME OF NOIR.
THEREFORE I HAVE COME,
AS PROMISED,
TO GIVE YOU THE FINAL GUIDANCE
REQUIRED TO REACH THE MANOR.
- AND WHAT'S THIS MANOR?
- IT IS SACRED GROUND.
THE ONE PLACE ON THIS EARTH
LEFT BEHIND
BY THE FLOW OF TIME.
IT IS THERE THAT
THE RITUAL OF ACCESSION
TO NOIR WILL TAKE PLACE.
- ( thunder crashing )
- ( gasps )
- I WOULD LIKE TO THANK YOU
FOR BEING WITH HER UNTIL NOW.
- ( gasps )
- HOWEVER, THE TIME HAS COME
FOR HER TO GO HOME.
- ( breathes shakily )
( grunts )
- YOUR GUN.
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
- THE TIME HAS COME.
- ( cocks )
- ( gasps )
- TIME TO RECEIVE
THE FINAL GUIDANCE.
- NO!
- ( gunshot echoes )
- ( gasps )
- ( casing clatters )
- ( gunshots )
- ( chuckles )
- ( breathing shakily )
- ( women singing )