- ( men chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR--
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE.
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH--
THE PEACE OF
THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
DO IT.
SHOOT ME NOW.
PLEASE, MIREILLE!
SHOOT ME.
MIREILLE!  MIREILLE!
( cries )
MIREILLE.
KILL ME.
PLEASE!
( cries )
MIREILLE.
WHY?
- WHY?
I WANTED TO.
BUT I JUST COULDN'T.
- ( cars honking )
- THE FLOWER
NEVER TURNED BLACK.
IT JUST WITHERED AND DIED.
KIRIKA'S NOT COMING BACK.
- WHERE AM--
( groans )
HUH?
- ( door opens )
- Man: AHH, YOU ARE
AWAKE AT LAST.
- WHERE AM I?
- THIS IS MY HOME.
WE FOUND YOU COLLAPSED
AT THE EDGE OF THE VILLAGE.
I AM KNOWN AS TRISTAN.
AND THIS IS
MY WIFE MARGARET.
- MY NAME...
MY NAME--
- WE KNOW THAT, CHILD.
JUST AS WE KNEW YOU WOULD
COME TO THIS VILLAGE SOME DAY.
- ( gasps )
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW COULD YOU KNOW?
I DON'T KNOW WHERE I WAS
OR WHERE I WAS GOING.
SO HOW COULD YOU KNOW
THAT I'D BE HERE?
- Tristan: YOU WILL KNOW
THE ANSWER SOON ENOUGH.
HMM.
YOU CAME BECAUSE YOU WERE
MEANT TO COME HERE.
- MEANT TO COME?
HOW CAN YOU KNOW SOMETHING
I DON'T KNOW MYSELF?
HAVE WE MET
SOMEWHERE BEFORE?
- BEFORE?  NO.
BUT IT'S NOT AN ISSUE
THAT SHOULD CONCERN YOU.
- I'VE BROUGHT YOU
SOME FRESH CLOTHING.
YOUR BREAKFAST IS READY!
- COMING.
- ( sniffing )
- THIS VILLAGE IS ON THE BORDER
NEAR A CERTAIN PLACE.
YES, THE SAME PLACE THAT YOU
HAVE BEEN HEADING TOWARDS.
THIS VILLAGE GUARDS
THE ENTRANCE TO THAT PLACE.
- AND WHERE SHOULD I GO?
- THERE'S AN OLD STONE MONUMENT
ON THIS TOWN'S WEST SIDE.
I BELIEVE YOU SHOULD
GO THERE FIRST.
- ( children laughing )
( overlapping chatter )
- Girl: HEY, NO FAIR.
- ( boys chatter )
- Girl: I CAN'T RUN
IN THESE SHOES.
- Boy #1: LAST ONE THERE
IS A ROTTEN EGG.
- Girl: WAIT FOR ME.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
- WHY AM I HERE?
HOW DID I END UP
COMING TO THIS VILLAGE?
THEY ALL KNOW WHO I AM.
THE ONLY ONE
WHO DOESN'T KNOW
IS ME.
- ( bell rings )
- ( gasps )
- OH.
- WELL, GO AND GET IT.
- THANK YOU, MISTRESS.  HUH?
OH?
- I-- I KILLED YOUR FAMILY.
I REMEMBER KILLING THEM,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHY.
MIREILLE.
- MY NAME ISN'T
MIREILLE, MISTRESS.
- BUT I KNOW
THAT I KILLED THEM.
- OF COURSE YOU DID.
'CAUSE YOU'RE NOIR.
( giggles )
- WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME!
- BRING THE BALL.
- LET'S GO PLAY
BY THE PASTURE INSTEAD, OKAY?
I'LL RACE YOU THERE!
- HMM?
( groans )
- HMM?  AH, YOU'VE ARRIVED
JUST IN TIME.
SO, WHAT DID YOU THINK
OF OUR VILLAGE?
- I FOUND IT QUITE LOVELY.
- ISN'T IT?
BUT NOW THAT YOU'RE BACK,
YOU MUST MEET
OUR TOWN ELDER THEBALT.
- WELCOME, CHILD.
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
- Tristan:
AND MAY I ALSO INTRODUCE
OUR OTHER GUESTS.
- THERE'S NO NEED.
LET'S FINISH OUR TALKS FIRST,
SHALL WE?
- I'M SURE BY NOW,
YOU'VE CONVEYED
OUR SUGGESTION TO HER, RIGHT?
- NO, I'M AFRAID NOT.
- OH, REALLY?
THEN WE'LL TELL HER OURSELVES.
- IT WOULD BE
RATHER POINTLESS.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- OUR PEOPLE'S BELIEFS
HAVE NOT CHANGED
IN 1,000 YEARS.
( chuckles )
UNLIKE YOURS I FEAR.
- ( gunshots )
- ( men groan )
- ( gasps )
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- ( groaning )
- ( distant gunshots )
- LET'S STEP OUT FRONT.
- BUT WHY?
- I'M AFRAID THAT
OUR LATE GUESTS
WERE AMONG THOSE WHO OPPOSE
"THE GRAND RETOUR."
THEIR INTENT WAS TO KEEP YOU
FROM SEEING THE LADY,
WHICH WOULD OPPOSE
THE CAUSE FOR WHICH
THIS VILLAGE HAS ALWAYS STOOD.
AND THAT WE COULD NOT ALLOW.
- WHAT KIND OF PLACE
IS THIS?
WHO ARE YOU?
- ( chuckles )
I BEG YOUR FORGIVENESS
FOR NOT EXPLAINING SOONER
FOR, YOU SEE,
EVERYONE IN THIS TOWN IS...
A SOLDAT.
- ( gasps )
- Tristan:
FAR BEYOND THE ROCKY MOUNTAINS
THAT RISE ABOVE THIS VILLAGE,
IN THE BORDERLANDS
THAT DIVIDE SPAIN AND FRANCE,
IS A PLACE THAT BELONGS
TO NO COUNTRY.
IT IS A PLACE THAT CANNOT
BE FOUND ON ANY MAP,
A PLACE THAT HAS BEEN
FORGOTTEN BY TIME.
IT MAY SEEM QUITE
HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT THERE ARE STILL
SEVERAL SUCH PLACES
IN THIS WORLD OF OURS.
THE PLACE BEYOND THIS VILLAGE
IS ONE OF THEM.
WHATEVER NAME IT ONCE HAD
IS LOST.
IT IS CALLED SIMPLY,
"THE MANOR."
- ( gasps )
- THE REASON
YOU UNCONSCIOUSLY
FOLLOWED THE PATH
TOWARDS THE MANOR
IS BECAUSE YOU ARE NOIR.
- ( gasps )
- THE LAND BEYOND HERE
IS SACRED GROUND
FOR THE SOLDATS.
AND TO INTERFERE IN
THE AFFAIRS THERE IS TABOO.
THAT IS WHY
THEY WILL STOP AT NOTHING
TO KEEP YOU
FROM LEAVING THIS VILLAGE.
- YOU MEAN, THE ONES
WHO SENT THOSE MEN?
- HMM, THAT'S CORRECT.
FOR EVEN AS WE ARE THE
DESCENDENTS OF THE SOLDATS,
SO ARE THEY.
SO THIS IS THEIR LAST CHANCE.
IN THE 10th CENTURY,
THE SOLDATS SENT THEIR SEED
TO LIE DORMANT
DEEP WITHIN EVERY
NICHE OF SOCIETY,
MUCH LIKE THE GERMS
THAT CAUSE SCARLET FEVER.
THROUGH THEM,
THE SOLDATS WERE ABLE
TO PLAY A GREAT PART
IN ALL ASPECTS
OF HUMAN HISTORY.
- Kirika:
"THE BLOOD OF THE SOLDATS
WILL SEEP THROUGHOUT
THE WILDERNESS
AND FLOW INTO
THE GREAT RIVER."
- Tristan: EXACTLY, BUT AT
THE END OF THAT LONG JOURNEY,
SOME OF THE SOLDATS HAD BECOME
SOMETHING QUITE DIFFERENT.
THEY HAD BECOME
A BLACK SHROUD
THAT SOUGHT TO ENVELOPE
THE ENTIRE WORLD.
"THE GRAND RETOUR"
MEANS A RETURN
TO THE ROOTS
OF THE SOLDATS.
BUT AMONG THE SOLDATS,
THERE ARE THOSE WHO'VE
TURNED AGAINST THE OLD WAYS
BECAUSE TO THEM,
YOU SEE,
THE SOLDATS HAVE
ALREADY BECOME
THE POINT
OF THE WORLD ITSELF.
- Councilman: I UNDERSTAND.
EXECUTION OF THE PLAN
IS APPROVED.
WE'RE ALL AGREED THEN?
- BLOOD MUST ALWAYS BE SHED,
EVEN THE BLOOD OF OUR
BRETHREN SOLDATS IF REQUIRED.
- INDEED.
THAT IS A TRUTH
THAT THE SOLDATS HAVE
ALWAYS KNOWN.
- ( rumbling )
- AND YOU SAY
THAT IT'S BEEN 1,000 YEARS?
- WE HAVE AN ANCIENT TASK
THAT WE HAVE BEEN
CHARGED WITH.
THAT TASK IS TO GUARD
THE MANOR WITH OUR LIVES.
THE SOLDATS ARE
WITH THE TRUTH.
WE KNOW THE TRUE NATURE
OF THE WORLD OF MAN
AND SO DOES THAT LADY.
- THAT'S ALTENA, RIGHT?
- YES.
THERE, AT THE MANOR,
SHE GUARDS THE WAYS
OF OUR LOST HISTORY,
AWAITING THE TIME
OF THE RITUAL.
FOR IN THE DARKNESS
OF MEDIEVAL TIMES,
WHEN THE SOLDATS FIRST
WENT UNDERGROUND,
TWO HANDS WERE LEFT BEHIND
ON THE DARK SURFACE
TO CARRY OUT ITS BIDDING.
- NOIR.
- YES, THE SOLDATS MUST
REGAIN THESE HANDS,
WHICH WE HAVE LOST.
FOR IT IS THE REVIVAL
OF THE RITUAL
OF ACCESSION TO NOIR
THAT WILL TRULY SYMBOLIZE
"THE GRAND RETOUR."
- ( gasps )
- PLEASE, WE MUST GO NOW.
- HUH?
- THEY WILL COME
WITHIN THE NIGHT.
YOU MUST LEAVE IMMEDIATELY.
MY WIFE WILL
SHOW YOU THE WAY.
- BUT HOW CAN I JUST--
- YOU MUST GO.
- HMM?
- ( gunshots )
- Margaret:
THERE IS NO TIME LEFT.
WE MUST HURRY!
- ( gunshots )
( gunshot, gunfire )
- ( groans )
- ( soldier grunts )
- PUT YOUR HANDS
BEHIND YOUR HEAD
AND GET DOWN
ON YOUR STOMACH!
- THE WOMAN'S
GOTTEN AWAY!
THERE WAS ONLY ONE
OLD MAN IN THERE!
- ( pants )
- Margaret:
PLEASE, WE MUST HURRY.
- ( panting )
- Soldier: YOU'RE BLOCKING
THE LINE OF FIRE!
GET OUT OF THERE NOW, ERIC!
PULL BACK!
- ( gun clicks )
- HUH?  AAH!
- ( gunshot )
- THESE PEOPLE!
THEY'RE ALL CRAZY.
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasps )
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
ALL OF THOSE PEOPLE
ARE DYING FOR WHAT?
- THEY DIE BECAUSE
THAT'S THE TRUTH OF MEN.
- I DON'T--
- UNDERSTAND?
BUT OF COURSE YOU DO.
THAT IS WHAT
MAKES YOU NOIR.
- ( gasps )
- MAN COMMITS SINS.
IT'S OUR NATURE.
THE SOLDATS COMMIT SINS
AS ALL MEN DO,
BUT WE WILL ALSO SHED
OUR OWN BLOOD WILLINGLY.
- ( sighs )
- BUT WHY MUST--
- ( growls )
- ( gasps )
- ( man screams )
- ( shotgun cocks )
- ( panting )
( grunts )
- AAH!
- ( gunfire )
- ( screaming )
- ( groans )
- ( barking )
- THE GIRL'S NOT THERE!
- SHUT UP THAT DAMN DOG
SO WE CAN HEAR!
- ( gunshots )
- ( groaning )
- WHERE'S IT COMING FROM?
- IT'S BEHIND US.
IN THE TREE!
- ( men whimper )
- ( screaming )
- ( screams )
- EXCELLENT.
THAT'S HOW...