- ( men chanting )
- Mireille: NOIR--
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE.
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH,
TOWARD THE DARKNESS
FROM THE NURSING BABES,
THEIR BLACK ROBES
SERVE AS SHIELDS.
- YOUR GUN.
- ( gasps )
- THE TIME HAS COME.
- TIME TO RECEIVE
THE FINAL GUIDANCE.
- NO!
( gasps )
- ( shells clink )
- ( gasps )
- Mireille: KIRIKA!
- ( running footsteps )
KIRIKA.
( sighs )
SHE'S ALIVE.
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?!
- IT'S THE FINAL GUIDANCE.
- HUH?
- THE TRAVELER NEEDS GUIDANCE
IN ORDER TO ADVANCE
THROUGH THE WILDERNESS.
IF SHE REMEMBERS NOW,
THEN SHE WILL SURELY
FIND HER WAY HOME.
AND IF SHE DOES NOT,
THEN SHE WILL DIE ALONE
IN THE WASTELANDS.
- BUT WHY?
IT MAKES NO SENSE.
WHAT'S THE POINT?!
- I HAVE FAITH.
SHE WILL SURELY REMEMBER.
SHE MUST.
ALTENA TOLD ME SOMETHING.
SHE SAID THAT
THE BEST COURSE
WOULD BE TO
TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
- ( whimpers )
- "TELL THE TRUTH"?
WHAT TRUTH COULD
YOU TELL ME NOW?!
- THE IDENTITY OF THE ONE
WHO KILLED YOUR PARENTS
AND ELDER BROTHER, PERHAPS.
- I KNOW WHO KILLED THEM.
THE SOLDATS DID IT.
- AND THE KILLER'S NAME?
- THE NAME!
- THE ONE WHO PULLED
THE TRIGGER'S NAME,
I KNOW IT.
- ( gasps )
- ( whimpers )
- ( sighs )
- ( groans )
MIREILLE.
HMM?
- HUH?
( gasps )
- TO BE HONEST, I DON'T KNOW
THAT PERSON'S REAL NAME.
OH NO, BUT WHAT
I DO KNOW
IS THE NAME THAT PERSON
IS KNOWN BY NOW.
- ( whimpers )
( gasping )
- ( gunshot echoes )
- ( Kirika moans )
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- ( cries )
- ( lullaby melody plays )
- ( whimpers )
- ( melody continues )
- Chloe: YES.
THAT PERSON
IS NOW KNOWN AS
YUMURA KIRIKA.
- ( thunder rumbles )
- LIAR.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE LYING.
YOU MUST BE!
- IT IS THE TRUTH.
- AND YOU HAVE
PROOF OF THIS?
- NO PROOF.
BUT I AM CERTAIN.
- ( groans )
( winces )
- I KNOW IT'S TRUE.
- ( melody plays )
- ( child gasps )
- Chloe: BECAUSE I SAW IT.
I SAW IT WITH
MY OWN TWO EYES.
- AAH.
- ( gasps )
WAS IT YOU?
WERE YOU THE ONE
WHO KILLED THEM?
WAS IT REALLY YOU?
( gasps )
- ( cries )
- THE SOLDATS HIGH PRIEST
BLESSES THE NEWLY BORN
AT THE TIME OF THEIR BIRTH.
THOSE WHO ARE CHOSEN
FROM AMONG THEM
GO THROUGH THE TRIALS
AND ARE ACKNOWLEDGED AS NOIR.
- ( gasps )
- AND YOU, MIREILLE BOUQUET,
DAUGHTER OF CORSICA,
YOU WERE ONE OF THOSE
WHO RECEIVED
THAT RARE BLESSING.
- ( gasps )
- OH, YES.  IT'S TRUE.
BUT LAURENT
AND ODETTE BOUQUET
ADAMANTLY REFUSED
TO HAND THEIR YOUNG DAUGHTER
OVER TO THE SOLDATS.
AND IT WAS FOR THAT TREASON
THAT THEY WERE EXECUTED.
- ( gulps )
( shivers )
- ( door opens )
- I WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU
AT THE MANOR.
- HMM.
- OH, KIRIKA.  KIRIKA!
- ( car horn honks )
( sighs )
- ( grunts, groans )
- ( panting )
- ( man grunts )
( chuckles )
( grunts, gargled scream )
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- ( whimpers )
- Kirika: NOIR,
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE.
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH,
TO THE DEPTHS
OF HELL'S FIRE,
THEIR BLACK SOULS
LURE THE LOST CHILDREN.
- ( man grunts )
- I CANNOT ATONE.
- OH!
- ( sighs )
THERE IS NO WAY...
THAT I CAN EVER ATONE.
I WAS THE ONE
THAT KILLED THEM.
IT WAS ME, MIREILLE.
AND I'M NOT...
EVEN CAPABLE
OF ATONING FOR IT.
- ( lullaby melody plays )
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
- ( melody continues )
- ( gunshots )
- ( gasps )
- ( melody continues )
- WE HAD A PROMISE, RIGHT?
THAT WHEN ALL
BECAME CLEAR,
THAT YOU WOULD KILL ME.
THAT TIME HAS COME, MIREILLE.
PLEASE, DO IT.
DO IT NOW.
WHAT'S WRONG?
MIREILLE?
MIREILLE.
PLEASE, DO IT.
SHOOT ME NOW.
KILL ME.
SHOOT ME, PLEASE!
I'M BEGGING YOU!
MIREILLE!  MIREILLE!
MIREILLE.
- I'LL KEEP MY PROMISE!
THE NEXT TIME WE MEET.
- ( gasps )
- WHEN THAT TIME COMES,
I WILL NOT FAIL.
I SWEAR IT.
- WAIT, MIREILLE!
DON'T GO!
PLEASE KILL ME,
MIREILLE.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME!
MIREILLE!
( cries )
MIREILLE.
( sobs )
KILL ME.
PLEASE.
( cries )
NOIR-- IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE.
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH--
THE PEACE OF
THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ( techno music playing )
- ( women chanting )