- ( voices chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR...
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE
OF THE NEWLY BORN
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ( wind blowing )
- ( gunshot )
( gunshot )
- ( meows )
- Mireille: LET'S GO.
- HMM.
- ( meows )
- ( engine starts )
- ( cab departs )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- HUH?
- WE'RE ALL CHECKED IN.
LET'S GET TO THE ROOM.
- ( sighs )
- Man: HEY, GET IN LINE!
- Woman: THERE IS ENOUGH
FOR ALL. WAIT YOUR TURN.
- Man: BESIDES, THE BORSCHT
IS ALWAYS THICKER
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE POT.
( laughs )
- Woman: THANK YOU, SIR.
MAY THE LORD BLESS YOU. YOU
HAVE ALWAYS BEEN SO GOOD TO US.
- Mireille: THERE'S NO ONE HERE
WHO EVEN KNOWS HIS NAME.
AND FOR ALL HIS WORK
HE SEEKS NO COMPENSATION.
HE'S DEVOTED ALL HIS TIME
TO HELPING THE PEOPLE HERE...
FOR YEARS, FOR DECADES.
THE PEOPLE HERE IDOLIZE HIM.
SOME EVEN CALL HIM A SAINT.
BUT WHO HE REALLY IS
IS YURI NAZAROV,
A BUTCHER FOR THE K.G.B.
DURING THE PURGES
IN THE OLD U.S.S.R.
THERE WAS AN ETHNIC MINORITY
CALLED THE TASHKIL.
THEY WERE SLAUGHTERED
ALMOST TO THE MAN
IN A SOVIET DEATH CAMP.
DEATHS ORDERED
BY YURI NAZAROV.
SHORTLY THEREAFTER HE QUIT
THE K.G.B. AND DISAPPEARED,
ERASING HIS TRACES SO
COMPLETELY IT WAS AS IF
HE HAD NEVER EXISTED AT ALL.
NO ONE KNOWS WHY.
BUT NOW HE'S A SAINT
TO THE DESTITUTE.
OUR CLIENTS ARE THE SURVIVING
DESCENDANTS OF THE TASHKIL.
ALTHOUGH IT SEEMS THAT
NAZAROV IS TRYING TO ATONE,
THE HATRED OF
THE FEW WHO SURVIVED
CAN'T BE ERASED SO EASILY.
THAT'S WHERE WE COME IN.
A SIMPLE JOB REALLY.
- MM.
OH.
MIREILLE?
- MM-HMM?
- I'M GOING OUT FOR A WALK.
- HUH?
- ( trash can clangs )
- ( meows )
- ( door opens )
- I'M BACK.
- YOU'VE BEEN GONE AWHILE.
- MM-HMM.
- WHAT'S THAT?
DID YOU BUY SOMETHING TO EAT?
- ( rustling )
- ( meows )
- ( sighs )
PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'RE NOT REALLY
THINKING OF--
- MM-HMM.
- ( crowd laughing, chattering )
- PLEASE SAY YOU AREN'T
REALLY THINKING--
- HMM.
- PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'RE NOT THINKING OF TAKING IT
BACK TO PARIS WITH US, ARE YOU?
- DOES THIS CAT HAVE NAME?
- HUH?
- IF...
IF HE HAS A NAME,
THEN HE'S NOT LIKE ME.
IF THIS CAT HAS A NAME
THEN HE'S ONLY
PHYSICALLY LOST.
BUT I DON'T EVEN HAVE A NAME.
ALL I HAVE IS A LIE
CALLED YUMURA KIRIKA.
- ( sighs )
IT'S ALL THE SAME TO ME.
IT DOESN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE JUST PART
OF A MUCH BIGGER LIE.
BUT THEN AGAIN
IN THE END IT SEEMS
I'M IN THE SAME BOAT YOU ARE.
WE'RE BOTH FLOATING
ADRIFT IN THE DARK
AT THE MERCY OF THE CURRENTS.
IN ORDER TO FIND
THE REAL ANSWERS,
WE'LL HAVE TO ASK
THE SOLDATS.
- YEAH.
- ( ragged breathing )
- ( gunshot )
- ( groans )
- ( music-box melody playing )
- ( gasps )
- Mireille:
"THE MAN WITHIN THE MAN.
THE LOVE
WITHIN THE LOVE.
THE SIN WITHIN THE SIN.
THE HERMIT TOLD
UNTO THE SINNER,
THE SOLDATS IS WITH TRUTH."
THE SOLDATS...
I STILL DON'T KNOW ENOUGH
TO UNDERSTAND WHAT THAT MEANS.
NOT YET,
BUT I SWEAR I WILL FIND OUT.
- HMM.
- ( melody continuing )
- ( purring )
- I WISH THAT AT LEAST
I KNEW WHAT YOUR NAME WAS.
- ( man whispers )
PRINCE MYSHKIN.
- OH.
- DID YOU SAY PRINCE MYSHKIN?
OH.
- ( meows )
- MM-HMM. YOU ASKED
WHAT THIS FELLOW'S NAME WAS.
IT IS PRINCE MYSHKIN.
- SO THAT MEANS
HE BELONGS TO YOU THEN?
- YES, BUT THE LITTLE COSSACK'S
BEEN MISSING FOR A FEW DAYS.
IT SEEMS THAT I HAVE YOU
TO THANK FOR TAKING CARE OF HIM.
- OH NO, IT WAS NOTHING REALLY.
- PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO THANK YOU ANYWAY--
FOR HIS SAKE.
GOODBYE, YOUNG LADY.
- GOODBYE, SIR.
AND GOODBYE, PRINCE MYSHKIN.
- ( meows )
- ( chuckles )
THE PRINCE IS SAYING
THAT HE WILL MISS YOU.
- HMM.
- ( sighs )
( groaning )
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU, SIR?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
PLEASE, SIR,
YOU'VE GOT TO TRY TO STAY AWAKE.
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP.
YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP FIGHTING.
OLD MAN? OLD MAN?
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- ( ragged breathing )
- ( meows )
- ( gasps )
- ( man sighs )
HE HAS BEEN PUSHING HIMSELF
FOR FAR TOO LONG.
( sighs ) OVER AND OVER
I WARNED THE OLD FOOL.
- ( wheezing )
- BUT HE WOULDN'T GIVE
ANY THOUGHT TO HIS HEALTH,
ALWAYS HE JUST KEPT
WORKING FOR OTHERS.
I'M AFRAID THERE'S NOTHING
MORE I CAN DO FOR HIM.
HE DOESN'T HAVE
LONG LEFT TO LIVE.
NOT LONG AT ALL.
- ( crashes )
- ( glass clatters )
- "BALKUTSK,
YEAR OF OUR LORD 1951."
- ( knocks )
- UH.
- Woman: DR. SVENSON TOLD US
THAT YOU SAVED THIS MAN'S LIFE.
WE OWE HIM SO MUCH
AND NOW TO YOU.
THANK GOD YOU WERE HERE!
THANK YOU.
WE ARE IN YOUR DEBT FOREVER.
BLESS YOU.
GOD BLESS YOU
FOR SAVING HIM.
- ( choir singing in Latin )
- HUH?
- ( meows )
- THIS IS MY ONLY CHANCE.
IF I DON'T DO IT NOW,
I WON'T DO IT EVER.
- ( water flowing )
- ( grunts )
- ( choir singing )
- Boy: ARE YOU
FEELING BETTER, SIR?
- Girl: IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT?
- YOU'LL GET WELL
SOON, WON'T YOU?
- Girl: YES, PLEASE.
- WE WANT YOU TO BE ABLE
TO PLAY WITH US AGAIN.
- YOU WILL, WON'T YOU?
- YEAH, AND COOK
FOR US AGAIN TOO. RIGHT?
- OH, I WISH
I COULD HAVE SOME NOW.
- IT'S REALLY GOOD,
SO GET WELL SOON, OKAY?
OH, GUESS WHAT...
- HMM?
- Girl: HUH?
- Boy: WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- Mireille: HMM.
IT'S GOT TO BE
A FAMILY PICTURE, RIGHT?
AND FROM THE LOOKS OF IT
I'M GUESSING THAT
THIS BOY IS NAZAROV.
THAT'S ABOUT THE RIGHT AGE
HE'D HAVE BEEN IN 1951.
( sighs )
ALL RIGHT, BALKUTSK, HUH?
SOUNDS LIKE A PLACE.
( typing )
ON THE OTHER HAND, AT LEAST I'VE
GOT ONE MORE CLUE ABOUT YOU NOW.
- HUH?
- YOU MAY KNOW THE UNDERWORLD,
EXCEL AT ASSASSINATION
TECHNIQUES,
AND SPEAK DOZENS
OF LANGUAGES,
BUT YOU ALSO HAVE NO KNOWLEDGE
OF RUSSIAN LITERATURE.
- RUSSIAN LITERATURE?
- PRINCE MYSHKIN HAPPENS
TO BE THE PROTAGONIST
OF DOSTOEVSKY'S "THE IDIOT."
HE'S THE EMBODIMENT
OF A PURE AND INNOCENT SOUL.
- A PURE AND...
INNOCENT SOUL.
- ( sighs )
THAT'S ODD.
I CAN'T FIND A PLACE CALLED
BALKUTSK ANYWHERE.
- I SEE.
- YOU DO KNOW THAT
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT KIND OF PERSON
NAZAROV TURNS OUT TO BE, RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
- NAZAROV IS A FOOL.
NO MATTER HOW KIND
HE'S BEEN TO THE POOR,
IT DOESN'T CHANGE THINGS.
IT MAY HELP HIS OWN CONSCIENCE,
BUT EVEN THE ONES HE'S HELPED--
- I KNOW THAT.
AND I THINK THAT NAZAROV
KNOWS IT AS WELL.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
HE CAN DO.
I THINK THAT HE'S JUST WAITING
FOR THE SNOW TO FALL.
- SNOW?
- YES.
UNTIL ENOUGH
HAS ACCUMULATED.
- ( typing )
- ( groans )
- ( meows )
- HMM?
( gasps )
( sighs )
MMM.
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
( panting )
- ( gunshot )
- ( yelps )
- ( gunshots )
- Mireille:
BALKUTSK WAS THE HOME
OF A PEOPLE CALLED THE NORGA.
DURING STALIN'S ERA
THE NORGA'S ENEMIES,
THE TASHKIL, RAIDED AND
DESTROYED THE VILLAGE.
NOW NOT EVEN
ITS NAME REMAINS.
- SO NAZAROV IS A NORGA?
- AND IT SEEMS THAT
EVEN AFTER ALL THIS TIME,
THE LAST FEW REMAINING
NORGA AND TASHKIL
ARE STILL SET ON
KILLING EACH OTHER.
THE YEARS CONTINUE TO PASS
AND THE BLOOD CONTINUES TO FLOW.
IT'S GONE ON FOR SO LONG NOW
THERE'S NO WAY LEFT TO TELL
HOW IT ALL BEGAN--
WHAT WAS THE CAUSE
AND WHAT WAS THE EFFECT.
SO MANY MONTHS
AND YEARS HAVE PASSED
SINCE THE MASSACRE
AT THE CONCENTRATION CAMP,
I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE WHAT'S BEEN
GOING THROUGH HIS MIND.
SO THEN, WHERE TO NOW?
DO THE JOB AND BE LEFT
WITH A BAD AFTERTASTE OR...
OR SINCE HE'S DYING FROM A
TERMINAL ILLNESS ANYWAY...
- I'LL DO IT.
IT'S OUR JOB.
- ( inhales )
- I'LL KILL HIM.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( wind blowing )
- ( gasps )
- ( gunshot )
( casing bounces )
- ( meows )
- ( woman singing )