- ( voices chanting )
- Woman: NOIR...
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE
OF THE NEWLY BORN
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ( accordion folk music
playing )
- HMM.
HUH?
( thinking ) "MAKE A PILGRIMAGE
FOR THE PAST WITH ME."
A PILGRIMAGE TO THE PAST?
OH WHATEVER.
THIS IS STUPID.
- ( music-box melody playing )
- ( gasps )
- ( students chattering )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- SHALL WE TALK?
SUPPOSE WE START
WITH WHO YOU ARE?
( grunts )
- ( music-box melody playing )
- ( hisses )
( gasps )
( grunts )
( running footsteps )
- ( music-box melody playing )
- ( wind blowing )
- END OF THE LINE?
NOT MUCH OF A PILGRIMAGE, HUH?
- ( melody stops )
- I'M GOING TO ASK YOU
ONE LAST TIME.
WHO ARE YOU?
START TALKING.
- NOIR.
- NOIR?
- I KNEW YOU WOULD COME.
I'VE BEEN WAITING.
- ( shudders )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( gunshots )
- ( gasps )
- ( yells )
- YOU LITTLE...
( grunts )
- ( men groan )
- ( casings clatter )
- ( panting )
- ( distant gunfire )
- ( thinking )
AREN'T THEY AFTER ME?
OR ARE THEY?
( footsteps )
DON'T TELL ME
SHE DID ALL OF THIS.
( grunts )
( gasps )
- ( man grunts )
- HMPH.
- ( gunshot )
- ( groans )
- ( gunshots )
- ( gasps )
- ( man grunts )
( body thuds )
- ( grunting )
( man gags )
- IT WOULD SEEM THAT KILLING
IS SOMETHING
THAT I CAN DO SO EASILY.
BUT WHY CAN'T I...
FEEL SORROW
FOR WHAT I'VE DONE?
- Noir: THAT SHOULD DO IT.
- YES, IT SHOULD. IT'S AN
EXCELLENT FIELD DRESSING.
DID YOU TRAIN AS A MEDIC?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- SO THIS IS WHERE YOU LIVE.
- MM-HMM.
- BUT IT'S NOT REALLY
YOUR HOME, IS IT?
- YUMURA, KIRIKA.
THAT'S MY NAME.
- AND THAT ISN'T
YOUR REAL NAME EITHER.
- MM.
- I'VE DONE SOME
CHECKING UP ON YOU.
- HUH?
- IT SEEMS THE YUMURA FAMILY
OF THREE
BOUGHT THIS HOUSE
HALF A YEAR AGO.
THREE PEOPLE MOVED IN.
BUT WITHIN A FEW MONTHS,
BOTH OF THE PARENTS
HAD LEFT FOR AMERICA.
NEW JOBS SUPPOSEDLY,
WHILE THE DAUGHTER STAYED
BEHIND TO ATTEND SCHOOL.
- MM.
- BUT IT WAS ALL JUST
AN ELABORATE WORK OF FICTION.
AND THE DOCUMENTS SUBMITTED
TO THE SCHOOL AND PUBLIC OFFICES
WERE FORGED, RIGHT?
( huffs )
THE FAMILY REGISTER,
THE PARENTS' EMPLOYERS,
NONE OF IT EVER
ACTUALLY EXISTED.
AND THE YUMURA
HUSBAND AND WIFE
DISAPPEARED WITHOUT A TRACE.
- ( gun clattering )
- SO NOW WHY WOULD
SOMEONE HAVE BEEN PRETENDING
TO BE YOUR PARENTS?
- THREE QUESTIONS:
WHO ARE YOU,
WHERE DID YOU COME FROM
AND WHY ARE YOU HERE?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- I DON'T KNOW WHY
I KNOW HOW TO DO
THINGS LIKE THIS.
HOW CAN I KNOW THIS?
HOW CAN I KNOW...
WHEN I KNOW NOTHING ELSE?
WHEN I CAME TO,
I WAS HERE.
WHO AM I?
I AM...
NOIR.
BEYOND THAT,
I KNEW NOTHING.
- ( sighs )
( gasps )
- Noir's voice:
AND THEN I...
FOUND THIS.
THAT ISN'T ALL.
I LEARNED
I KNOW TERRIBLE THINGS.
I DO.
BUT WHY?
- AND YOU DON'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING ABOUT YOURSELF?
- HUH-UH.
- WHAT ABOUT ME?
- MIREILLE BOUQUET,
A MOST TRUSTWORTHY
ASSASSIN FOR HIRE.
- I SEE.
WELL, LET'S MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT TOPIC, SHALL WE?
I KNOW YOU FOUND MORE
THAN JUST THIS GUN.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE THING
THAT YOU'VE BEEN HIDING.
- HMM?
- TAKE IT OUT.
- ( music-box melody playing )
- ( gasps )
- ( ticking, music continues )
- ( ragged breath )
( sobbing )
- ( echoing ticking )
- ( orchestra playing melody )
- STOP IT.
- ( clicks off )
- YOU KNOW, DON'T YOU?
YOU KNOW...
- ( score playing )
- ( gasps )
- ( gunshots )
- Mireille: AND THEN...
YOU CONTACTED ME.
- NOT MUCH
OF A PILGRIMAGE, HUH?
- NOIR...
- NOIR?
- A PILGRIMAGE
TO YOUR PAST AND MINE.
- ( gasps )
- LET'S START
WITH THE SIMPLE FACT
THAT I KILL PEOPLE FOR A LIVING.
I'M NOT IN BUSINESS
TO HELP YOU.
THEN...
THERE'S THE FACT THAT I HAVE
ALWAYS PREFERRED TO WORK ALONE.
AND I INTEND
TO KEEP IT THAT WAY.
- PLEASE LEND ME YOUR HELP,
MIREILLE.
I NEED YOUR HELP
TO FIND OUT WHAT I AM.
I NEED YOUR HELP UNTIL...
UNTIL...
I FIND THAT ANSWER.
- ( sighs )
Mireille: I'VE MADE
THE ARRANGEMENTS
TO LEAVE THE COUNTRY.
- Noir: THANK YOU.
- SO ARE YOU ABOUT FINISHED?
- MM-HMM.
- I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO SAY
GOODBYE IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- HMM.
- "EVEN WHEN I WAS IN A CROWD,
I WAS ALWAYS ALONE."
- HUH?
- I'M AFRAID THAT'S NOT MINE.
IT'S ERNEST HEMINGWAY,
I BELIEVE.
- I'M READY
TO GO NOW, MIREILLE.
- Mireille: YOU KNOW WHAT
IT IS THAT I DO FOR A LIVING.
AND YOU KNOW
THAT MEANS I CAN'T
LET YOU LIVE.
- Noir: YES.
- ALL RIGHT,
I'LL TEAM UP WITH YOU.
THEY'RE SURE
TO COME AFTER US AGAIN.
- ( typing )
- AND WHEN THEY DO,
THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT TO ASK THEM.
ONCE THAT'S OVER,
I WILL KILL YOU.
- I'LL BE WAITING
FOR THAT MOMENT.
- ( woman singing )