- ( men chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR--
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE OF
THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ALL RIGHT,
WHO ARE YOU?
- CHLOE.
- RIGHT, AND YOU ARE?
- THE TRUE NOIR.
- ( gasps )
- IF YOU'D REALLY LIKE,
WE CAN SEE WHO'S FASTER.
- ( sighs )
- I AM THE TRUE NOIR,
YOU KNOW?
- ( phone rings )
- BONJOUR.
- Man: IS THIS NOIR?
- ( gasps )
YOU MUST HAVE
THE WRONG NUMBER.
- I SENT YOU SOMETHING
IN THE POST.
PERHAPS YOU SHOULD
LOOK AT IT.
- ( clicks )
- ( phone beeps )
- THE SAME PHOTOCOPY.
- IS IT?
LOOK AGAIN.
- IT'S BEEN
COPIED FROM A BOOK.
AND THAT'S THE EDGE
OF THE NEXT PAGE.
( gasps )
BUT MOST OF THE DIRT AND STAINS
ARE IN THE SAME SPOT,
WHICH MEANS THAT IT'S LIKELY
THAT BOTH COPIES
CAME FROM THE SAME BOOK,
BUT ALSO THAT
THE TWO COPIES
WERE MADE
AT DIFFERENT TIMES.
- PROBABLY.
AND BY DIFFERENT SOURCES.
- ( phone rings )
- ( gasps )
- ( ringing continues )
- ( phone beeps )
- Mireille: YES?
- Man: HAVE YOU BOTH
SEEN THE PHOTOCOPY?
- Mireille: WHO ARE YOU?
- Man: I WANT
TO MEET WITH YOU.
FOUR IN THE AFTERNOON
IN THE GARDENS BEHIND
THE LAMBERT MEMORIAL HALL.
- OUR CALLER ALREADY KNEW
MY ADDRESS AND
TELEPHONE NUMBER.
WHAT'S MORE,
HE SAID THAT HE WANTED
TO MEET BOTH OF US.
- SOLDATS.
- AND IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE READY TO CONTACT US.
- FIRST, THERE'S THIS
"TRUE NOIR" CHLOE
AND NOW THIS.
IT ALL HAS TO BE...
- RELATED SOMEHOW, I KNOW.
BUT EXACTLY HOW,
I HAVE NO IDEA.
- ( gasps )
MIREILLE.
- HOW GOOD OF YOU TO COME.
- YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO CALLED?
WHEN MEETING A DATE,
PROPER ETIQUETTE DICTATES
THAT INTRODUCTIONS
ARE IN ORDER.
- JUST KNOWING MY NAME
WOULD BE MEANINGLESS.
I BELIEVE IT WILL
BE ENOUGH TO SAY
THAT I AM LOYAL
TO THE SOLDATS.
- ( gasps )
- I AM MOST PLEASED
TO MEET YOU AT LAST.
- IS THAT SO?
AND HERE
I COULD HAVE SWORN
THAT YOU WERE
TRYING TO KILL US.
- AND SO WE ARE.
THE ORDERS TO SANCTION
BOTH OF YOU STILL STAND.
YOU MUST TAKE CARE.
- SO ARE YOU HOLDING OUT
A DAGGER OR AN OLIVE BRANCH?
- THERE ARE NO FRIENDS
OR FOES IN OUR WORLD.
YOU TWO SHOULD KNOW
THAT ALL TOO WELL, CORRECT?
I AM ONLY ACTING ON THE WILL
OF THE SOLDATS.
JUST AS THE TWO OF YOU ARE.
- STOP SPEAKING IN RIDDLES.
- I INTEND TO,
BUT THE TIME
IS NOT YET RIGHT.
- AND WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- THAT YOU DO NOT
YET COMPREHEND
THE ENORMITY OF
THE SOLDATS, MY DEAR.
THINK OF THEM
AS AN ENORMOUS SHROUD
ENCOMPASSING
THE VERY EARTH ITSELF.
I HAVE THE BOOK,
THE SOURCE OF
THE PHOTOCOPY I SENT YOU.
THE BEGINNING OF ALL OF THIS
IS INSCRIBED WITHIN IT.
IN THREE DAYS TIME,
I WILL REVEAL ITS LOCATION.
WE SHALL MEET HERE
AT THE SAME TIME AND PLACE.
- ( gasps )
HOLD ON!
( grunts )
- ( leaves rustle )
- Woman:
"THE WINDS MUST BLOW
IN THE SAME DIRECTION,
MY DARLING CHLOE.
DO YOU RECALL
HOW THE BREEZES RIPPLED
THROUGH OUR BEAUTIFUL VINEYARD?
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN THE WINDS
FROM DIFFERENT
DIRECTIONS COLLIDE?
WHIRLWINDS, CHAOS
AND NEEDLESS EDDIES ARISE.
WE MUST WORK HARD,
MY PRECIOUS CHLOE
SO THAT OUR DELICATE GRAPES
WILL NOT BE BRUISED."
- MISS CHLOE?
I DO NOT RECALL
SUMMONING YOU HERE.
AND AS I AM ACTING UNDER
THEIR DIRECT APPROVAL,
THAT ALSO ENCOMPASSES
MAKING CONTACT WITH THOSE TWO.
"LET US FEED THE SAPLINGS
WITH WATER AND LIGHT."
THAT HAS ALWAYS
BEEN OUR PRINCIPLE,
HAS IT NOT?
AND FOR THOSE TWO AS WELL.
- YES, I KNOW THAT.
- THEN WHY DO YOU
MONITOR ME?
WHAT RIGHT DO YOU HAVE?
JUST WHAT IS
ALTENA THINKING?
- HER CONCERN
IS FOR NOIR'S TRUE FORM.
- ( gasps )
- ( thunder crashes )
- IN THE END,
ALTENA IS DANGEROUS.
WE DO NOT AND CANNOT APPROVE
OF HER GRAND RETOUR.
YOU KNOW I MUST
REPORT THIS.
- OH, THERE IS NO NEED
FOR THAT.
- JUST WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- THE DECISION HAS
ALREADY BEEN MADE.
- THAT CANNOT BE.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THE PROMISE YOU MADE.
OTHERS WILL BE SENT
TO LAMBERT HALL IN YOUR PLACE.
- DO YOU MEAN
TO KILL THOSE TWO?
- ( distant gunshots )
( gunshots )
- ( panting )
- ( grunts )
- RIGHT THEN.
- ( groaning )
- ( groans )
- ( gunshots )
- ( grunting )
- ( panting )
- ( gunshot )
- ( man groans )
- ( gunshots )
- ( men groaning )
- ( groans echo )
- ( sighs )
SO INSTEAD OF
OUR DAPPER FRIEND,
WE GOT A BUNCH OF
HALF-RATE HENCHMEN.
HENCHMEN WHO LEFT NO TRACES
THANKS TO THE RAIN
AS USUAL.
IT REALLY CHAFES
MY DERRIERE.
- BUT THE MAN
WE MET THREE DAYS AGO
FELT LIKE MORE THAN
JUST BAIT TO ME.
- THAT'S TRUE.
THERE WAS DEFINITELY
SOMETHING THAT SAID
HE WAS TRYING
TO TELL US SOMETHING.
- HE DID SAY THAT
WE SHOULD BE CAREFUL.
AND THAT THE ORDERS
TO SANCTION US STOOD.
- WHICH IMPLIES DIFFERENT
FACTIONS WITHIN THE SOLDATS.
AND WHAT'S WORSE,
WE DIDN'T EVEN GET THE BOOK.
ASSUMING OF COURSE
THAT IT EXISTS AT ALL
OR THAT IT'S
REALLY EVEN IMPORTANT.
IT'S JUST MAKING
MY BRAIN ITCH.
- ( knocks on door )
- ( gasps )
( Mireille approaching )
WHO IS IT?
- ( unlocks )
- ( gasps )
- Chloe: GO AHEAD.
TAKE IT OUT.
- ( both gasp )
- REALLY.
THIS IS YOUR HOME, AFTER ALL.
- RIGHT.
THEN WE'LL JUST DO
AS WE PLEASE THEN.
- ( kettle whistles )
- ( Kirika gasps )
UM, WOULD YOU
LIKE SOME TEA?
- ( gasps )
- YES, THANK YOU.
- I ONLY HAVE ORANGE PEKOE
RIGHT NOW.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
- YES, THANK YOU.
- ( exhales )
- EXCELLENT.
- WAIT A MINUTE!  STOP THAT.
AND WHAT IN THE HELL
ARE YOU THINKING?
- THE MOON IS SO BEAUTIFUL.
COULD WE TURN OUT
THE LIGHTS?
- THE LIGHTS?!
ARE YOU CRAZY?
- IT IS...
LOVELY.
- IT'S GOOD.
- YES, ISN'T IT?
I TRIED SOMETHING NEW,
SOMETHING FROM A BOOK.
- SO, JUST WHAT ARE YOU
HERE FOR?
YOU DIDN'T COME HERE JUST
TO HAVE TEA, DID YOU?
- THERE ARE BISCUITS TOO.
- STOP IT.
SO WHEN YOU SAID THAT
YOU WERE THE "TRUE NOIR,"
JUST WHAT DID YOU MEAN?
- THAT I'M DIFFERENT
FROM YOU, OF COURSE.
- AND EXACTLY WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY DIFFERENT?
- IT IS ALL INSCRIBED
WITHIN THE BOOK.
- "BOOK."  THE BOOK
THOSE COPIES CAME FROM?
- YOU KNOW, I WAS
WATCHING YOU TODAY...
AT LAMBERT HALL.
THERE WAS NO DOUBT
THAT YOU WOULD WIN.
- THEN YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO SENT THOSE MEN?
ANSWER ME!
- AN ANSWER...
IS SOMETHING YOU MUST
FIND FOR YOURSELF.
THAT'S WHAT ALTENA
ALWAYS SAYS TO ME.
- ALTENA?
WHO IS ALTENA?
CUT IT OUT, DAMN IT!
THIS WHOLE THING IS TURNING
INTO A MAD TEA PARTY.
- HUH?
A MAD...
- LIKE "ALICE IN WONDERLAND."
- ( sighs )
WELL, AT LEAST ONE OF YOU
HAS HAD SOME
LITERARY SCHOOLING.
- IT REALLY IS SO BEAUTIFUL.
- UM, WOULD YOU
LIKE ANOTHER CUP?
- YES, PLEASE.
- MAKE MINE
DARK WITH SUGAR.
- THANK YOU.
THE TEA WAS DELICIOUS.
- ( gasps )
- COULD I KEEP
THIS ONE, PLEASE?
PERHAPS WE'LL
HAVE TEA AGAIN...
SOMEDAY PER CHANCE.
- ABOUT THAT FORK--
- WHEN I MADE THE TEA,
BUT SHE NEVER LET
HER GUARD DOWN,
NOT EVER.
THE MAN WHO CONTACTED US,
THE MAN WHO SAID HE'D TELL US
THE LOCATION OF THE BOOK...
I'M AFRAID THAT
HE'S NO LONGER ALIVE.
- I AGREE.
- ( techno music playing )
- ( women chanting )