- ( voices chanting )
- Chloe: NOIR...
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
TO WARD THE DARKNESS
FROM THE NURSING BABES
THEIR BLACK ROBES
SERVE AS SHIELDS.
- ( wind blowing )
- ( women singing in Latin )
- ( traffic noise )
- WE HAD A PROMISE, RIGHT?
THAT WHEN ALL BECAME CLEAR
THAT YOU WOULD KILL ME.
- ( clicks )
- THAT TIME HAS COME, MIREILLE.
- ( sighs )
- PLEASE...
DO IT.
DO IT NOW.
( exhales )
WHAT'S WRONG?
MIREILLE?
- ( gasps )
( grunts )
- ( clicking )
- ( gasps )
WHO'S THERE?!
- ( cane tapping )
- YOU HAVE SOME SKILL,
I MUST ADMIT.
- AND YOU ARE?
- A SOLDAT.
ONE WHO WOULD LIKE
TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
- I'LL JUST BET YOU WOULD.
- YES, BUT I PREFER TO TALK
UP ON THE STREET.
THIS COLD AIR
AGGRAVATES MY LEG.
- FINE.
- ( birds chirping )
- AH YES, MUCH BETTER.
FEW THINGS IN LIFE
ARE AS WONDERFUL AS SIMPLY
SITTING IN THE SUN.
YOU MUST BE QUITE TIRED
OF LIVING IN THE SHADOWS.
- JUST WHAT ARE YOU
GETTING AT?
- I WOULD
LIKE TO INVITE YOU
TO JOIN US.
JOIN THE SOLDATS THAT IS.
- ( barking )
- ( groans )
HAVE A SEAT PLEASE.
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO SEE
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE ON THE SIDE
OF THOSE WHO RULE?
- EXCUSE ME IF I DON'T LAUGH.
- OH, ONE FINDS RULING OTHERS
ISN'T SUCH A BAD THING,
ONCE ONE GET USED TO IT.
YOU DO HAVE
THE QUALIFICATIONS,
AND QUITE TRUTHFULLY,
THERE WERE SOME AMONG US
WHO THOUGHT THAT WE
SHOULD HAVE BROUGHT YOU
INTO THE FOLD EVEN EARLIER.
BOTH YOU AND YOUR
FORMER PARTNER AS WELL.
- KIRIKA?
- I BELIEVE SHE HAS
ENTERED THE MANOR BY NOW
AND GONE OVER TO ALTENA.
WHICH UNFORTUNATELY MEANS
THAT SHE IS BEYOND OUR REACH.
- YOU PEOPLE CERTAINLY
DO SEEM TO HAVE
SOMETHING AGAINST
THIS ALTENA PERSON, DON'T YOU?
- YOU MIGHT BE INTERESTED
TO LEARN THAT ALTENA
WAS THE ONE WHO WAS
THE MOST OPPOSED
TO DRAWING YOU IN
TO OUR LITTLE ORGANIZATION
AND SHE WAS EXTREMELY ADAMANT
ABOUT PUTTING THE SAPLINGS
THROUGH THE TRIALS.
THOSE "SAPLINGS"
BEING THE CANDIDATES
CHOSEN
AS POSSIBLE NOIRS--
THOSE WHO HAD RECEIVED
THE BLESSINGS
OF THE SOLDATS' HIGH
PRIEST UPON BIRTH.
- ( gunshots )
- Man: OUR RANK AND FILE
SOLDIERS KNEW NOTHING
OF THE TRUE REASONS
BEHIND THE COMMANDMENT
TO SANCTION YOU.
THEY SIMPLY FOLLOWED
THEIR ORDERS
AND ATTACKED.
- ( gunshots )
- ALL OF THIS FOR NO REASON
OTHER THAN THAT THE TRIALS
HAD TO BE REAL BATTLES,
CONTESTS WHERE LIFE AND DEATH
WERE TRULY ON THE LINE.
OF THE SAPLINGS, TWO HAVE
FALLEN INTO ALTENA'S HANDS.
ALL THAT REMAINS IS YOU.
- WHICH IS WHY
YOU'RE MAKING THIS OFFER
TO JOIN FORCES WITH ME.
- THERE IS JUST ONE CONDITION.
YOU MUST GO TO THE MANOR
AND BECOME A PART OF NOIR.
NOIR HAS TWO HANDS--
LEFT AND RIGHT.
TO BECOME HALF OF THAT PAIR,
YOU WILL HAVE TO KILL
ONE OF THE OTHER TWO--
CHLOE OR YOUR FORMER PARTNER.
WHICHEVER YOU CHOOSE,
IF YOU SUCCEED, ALTENA WILL
BE FORCED TO ACCEPT YOU,
EVEN IF SHE KNOWS THAT YOU HAVE
BEEN INFLUENCED BY US.
- AND THEN...
KILL ALTENA
WHEN I GET THE CHANCE?
- IF ONE PRESENTS ITSELF.
I'M SORRY, BUT YOU HAVE
NO CHOICE, MISS BOUQUET.
YOU SIMPLY KNOW TOO MUCH.
AND THE SOLDATS DO NOT LEAVE
LOOSE ENDS UNCUT.
I WILL GIVE YOU TWO DAYS.
I TRUST THAT YOU WILL COME
TO A WISE DECISION.
- IT'S MORE LIKE THE MAD
TEA PARTY THAN I THOUGHT.
WHAT WAS IT THAT
THE MARCH HARE
AND THE MAD HATTER
SAID TO ALICE?
"NO ROOM! NO ROOM!"
( chuckles )
THREE CANDIDATES FOR NOIR,
BUT ONLY ROOM FOR TWO.
IT'S GOING TO BE
A MAD TEA PARTY INDEED.
- ( women singing in Latin )
- ( dings )
- ( silenced gunshots )
- ( groans )
- ( door creaks )
- HMMM.
I'M IMPRESSED
THAT YOU FOUND ME.
- ACTUALLY IT WAS
EXTRAORDINARILY EASY,
MR. REMY BREFFORT.
HOW MANY PEOPLE DO YOU THINK
CARRY A CANE LIKE THAT?
- AHA.
- ( sighs )
AND THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
THAT YOU'VE FORGOTTEN.
- HMM?
- YOU SOLDATS...
ARE THE SAME PEOPLE
WHO HAD MY PARENTS MURDERED.
AND NONE OF YOUR
INTERNAL SQUABBLES
MEAN JACK SQUAT TO ME.
FROM MY POINT OF VIEW
YOU'RE ALL THE ENEMY.
- YOU CAN SHOOT ME
IF YOU WANT
AND YOU'LL HAVE
ONE DEAD SOLDAT.
HOWEVER...
IF YOU KILL ME, YOUR CAREER
WILL ALSO END HERE AND NOW.
I'M QUITE AWARE
OF YOUR STYLE, MIREILLE,
AND I KNEW THAT YOU
WOULD COME HERE.
- OH? THEN WHY?
- BECAUSE I WANTED
YOU TO REALIZE
THAT THERE'S NO WAY OUT
OF THIS UNDERWORLD WE LIVE IN.
REMEMBER WHAT
YOUR UNCLE SAID?
- HUH?
- HE SAID NOT TO MAKE
THE SAME MISTAKE
AS YOUR FATHER.
- ( gasps )
- IF LAURENT HAD SIMPLY
HANDED YOU OVER TO THE SOLDATS,
THE BOUQUETS' POWER
WOULD HAVE GROWN,
BUT INSTEAD YOUR PARENTS
CHOSE THE PATH
THAT LED TO DESTRUCTION.
- ( sighs )
- WILL YOU REPEAT YOUR PARENTS'
MISTAKE, MIREILLE BOUQUET?
TOMORROW YOU WILL DECIDE.
YOU MUST THINK WELL
UPON YOUR ANSWER.
- ( birds chirping )
- ( gunshot )
- ( music-box melody playing )
- Kirika: I'M BEGGING YOU!
KILL ME,
PLEASE, MIREILLE!
- ( cars honk )
- I WILL KILL YOU, KIRIKA.
THAT WAS OUR PROMISE.
- Man: I SEE.
WE TRUST
YOUR JUDGMENT, BREFFORT.
- YES, I KNOW.
- Kirika: KILL ME,
PLEASE, MIREILLE!
- ( crashes )
- ( sighs )
AH.
- (Mireille reading) "MIREILLE,
I HAVE A VERY BAD FEELING--
A PREMONITION. THAT IS WHY
I'M WRITING THIS TO YOU NOW.
WHEN CHLOE SAID THAT
THE SOLDATS WAS MY TRUE HOME..."
- Kirika:
"I HAD THIS FEELING
THAT I MIGHT NEVER BE ABLE
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
THERE IS ANOTHER ME, MIREILLE.
IT IS SOMETHING THAT
I NOW KNOW MUST BE TRUE.
IT'S STRANGE,
BECAUSE I WOULD NOT MIND
BEING KILLED BY YOU.
BUT IF THAT MOMENT CAME
AND THERE WAS NO TIME
TO EXCHANGE FINAL WORDS,
I COULD NEVER BEAR THAT.
BECAUSE THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT I WANT TO TELL YOU
NO MATTER WHAT ELSE
MAY HAPPEN BETWEEN US.
I WAS ALONE, MIREILLE,
ALONE FOR SUCH A LONG TIME.
I HAD NOTHING.
IT FRIGHTENED ME
AND IT HURT.
AND YET...
AND YET I WAS NOT ALONE.
AND ALTHOUGH
IT CAME AS A SHOCK,
WHEN I LEARNED THAT NOIR WAS
ORIGINALLY A NAME FOR TWO,
MY HEART WAS FILLED WITH JOY.
AND DO YOU KNOW WHY,
MIREILLE?
BECAUSE I FOUND YOU.
AND I KNEW THAT YOU
WERE THERE FOR ME
AND I WAS HAPPY.
I WAS SO HAPPY.
SO HAPPY THAT
I WANTED TO SING.
BECAUSE I--
OH, MY DEAR MIREILLE...
I-- ( sobs )
I'M SORRY,
BUT I JUST CAN'T EXPRESS
HOW I FEEL IN WRITING.
THANK YOU, MIREILLE.
THANK YOU."
- ( gasps, sobs )
YOU IDIOT!
( sobbing continues )
- I WILL GO TO THE MANOR.
- AH. I SEE.
- BUT DON'T MISUNDERSTAND ME.
I WON'T BE GOING JUST
TO SERVE YOUR INTERESTS.
I'M GOING FOR MY SAKE,
NOT THE SOLDATS.
AND NONE OF THIS
CHANGES THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE STILL MY ENEMY.
- ( wings flap, birds squawk )
- DO YOU REALLY WISH TO STAY
A MERE HIT MAN FOREVER?
A FIRST-RATE ONE OF COURSE,
BUT ONLY A TOOL
TO BE USED BY OTHERS?
- AT LEAST IT'S A PATH
THAT I CHOSE FOR MYSELF.
- IF YOU JOINED US COMPLETELY,
YOU WOULD STAND TO GAIN
ENORMOUS POWER,
EVEN MORE THAN YOUR
PARENTS ENJOYED IN CORSICA.
- I UNDERSTAND NOW
WHY MY PARENTS CHOSE
TO GO AGAINST THE SOLDATS
EVEN KNOWING THE COST.
- MMM?
- MY PARTNER HAS BEEN LIVING
WITH A DARKNESS THAT WAS
PLANTED IN HER HEART.
MY PARENTS KNEW
WHAT MY LIFE WOULD BE LIKE
AND THEY SOUGHT TO SPARE
THEIR CHILD THAT TORMENT.
- HMM.
- MY PARENTS WERE
DEFINITELY SOLDATS.
BUT THEY WERE ALSO PARENTS
WHO LOVED THEIR DAUGHTER.
IT'S QUITE SIMPLE REALLY.
- WHEN YOU GET
TO THE MANOR...
WILL YOU SAVE YOUR PARTNER?
- ( sighs )
WHO KNOWS THE FUTURE?
I CAN SAY
ONE THING THOUGH--
THAT THE PERSON WHO HAS
MANIPULATED MY FAMILY
AND MY PARTNER'S FATE
WILL ANSWER TO ME.
- ( bell tolling 12:00 )
- ( tolling stops )
- AS YOU WILL.
GO AHEAD AND TRY.
THE OUTCOME WILL NO DOUBT
BE OF GREAT INTEREST
TO SOMEONE
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
- THAT MAY BE SO.
- THE MANOR IS ON THE BORDER
BETWEEN SPAIN AND FRANCE.
I WILL EMAIL YOU
WITH THE PRECISE LOCATION.
THE MANOR IS A PLACE
LOST IN THE DARKNESS OF HISTORY.
AND EVEN IF YOU ARE
ABLE TO SAFELY RETURN,
THAT SAME DARKNESS STILL
ENVELOPS THE REST OF THE WORLD.
TELL ME, DO YOU INTEND TO
FIGHT THE ENTIRE WORLD ALONE?
- NOT NECESSARILY...
ALONE ANYHOW.
- HMMM.
IN THAT CASE,
ALTHOUGH IT MAY
SOUND STRANGE,
MAY I WISH YOU
THE BEST OF LUCK?
- HMM.
- WELCOME HOME, LITTLE ONE.
- I AM HOME.
- ( wind blowing )
- ( women singing )