- ( voices chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR...
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE
OF THE NEWLY BORN
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ( grunting )
- ( grinding )
- ( Mireille groaning )
- ( chuckles )
- HMM?
- MM, SUCH SPIRIT.
- ( chuckles )
- BUT YOUR TIME HAS
NOT COME QUITE YET.
- JUST KILL HER.
WHY NOT BE DONE WITH IT NOW?
- BECAUSE THERE IS STILL
ONE MORE.
- CLEVER.
SO YOU'RE GOING TO USE ONE
AS BAIT FOR THE OTHER.
- ( gasps )
- Chu: NO WONDER THEY CALL
YOU THE COLD-BLOODED KILLER.
- ( chuckles )
- ( metal clangs )
- ( screams )
( coughing )
- ( clicks )
- ( blade snicks )
- ( yells )
- IT SEEMS I'M JUST IN TIME
TO HELP YOU.
- IF YOU'RE REALLY HERE
TO HELP ME,
I'D LIKE TO KNOW WHY FIRST?
- THIS MOMENT...
IS NOT THE TIME FOR TALKING.
- MIREILLE!
- HMM?
- ( snorts )
- ( grunts )
- ( women vocalizing )
- HMM.
OH.
- ( soft gasping )
- IT SEEMS THE BAIT WORKED
FASTER THAN WE THOUGHT.
- GOOD.
SHE'S SAVED US THE TROUBLE.
- HMPH.
IT WOULD SEEM SHE'S MAD.
- NO!
- DON'T MOVE!
- HMM.
- ( blade snicks )
- ( yells )
- ( groaning )
- ( growls )
- ( yells )
- THERE ARE THREE? BUT OUR
SOURCES SAID THERE WERE--
- ( blade snicks )
- ( yells )
- ( distant gunfire )
- HMPH.
- ( clicks )
- ( gasps )
- TIME TO DIE!
- ( blade snicks )
- ( yells )
- ( gunshots )
- ( groans )
- Kirika: MIREILLE!
- AHH.
- YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
- ( sighs )
THAT WAS THE STUPIDEST STUNT.
SHE SAVED ME,
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA WHY.
- AND THEN SHE DISAPPEARED?
OH.
- ( phone rings )
- ( gasps )
- YAN, THIS IS CHU!
TELL YOUR MEN TO FALL BACK
AND REGROUP!
I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU
AT MASTER WU'S ESTATE.
NOW THAT WE KNOW
WHO NOIR IS,
THERE ARE PLENTY OF WAYS
TO DEAL WITH THEM.
HEY, ARE YOU
LISTENING, YAN?!
YAN!
- ( beeps )
- YOU ARE A DISGRACE.
PITIFUL.
- THIS IS NOT OVER YET, HO.
I'LL IT MAKE UP
EVEN IF IT COSTS ME MY LIFE.
- YES, YOU WILL.
- THIS NOIR, THEY ARE
TRULY THIS FORMIDABLE?
- YES, ELDER.
- WHEN THE SOLDATS' AGENT
CONTACTED NOIR THERE WERE TWO.
YET ONLY A SHORT TIME LATER
A THIRD APPEARED
IN AMBUSH.
THERE IS MORE HERE
THAN MEETS THE EYE.
- Ho: I WILL
INVESTIGATE PERSONALLY.
- THAT SOURCE OF YOURS?
- YES.
- SHAOLI.
I HAD NOT BEEN INFORMED
THAT YOU HAD RETURNED.
IN FACT, I HAD HEARD
THAT YOU WERE DEAD.
- HMM.
- YOU ARE A DISGRACE TO THE NAME
OF THE COLD-EYED KILLER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE HIRED YOU FOR?
- HMM.
( footsteps )
- ( grunts )
- ( casing bounces )
- AND THAT'S HOW IT WAS.
- HMM.
HMM?
- LOOK OUT! IT'S THE BLON--
- ( silenced gunshot )
- NO, WAIT!
- ( body thuds )
- Kirika: MIREILLE!
OUT HERE.
- Mireille: HO LISHIN.
HE'S ONE OF THE OFFICERS.
THIS IS SHAOLI'S WORK.
BUT WHY WOULD SHE DO
SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- ( honking )
THE HONG YIBAN'S HIGHEST-RANKING
OFFICERS ARE ALL DEAD.
IT WILL TAKE THEM QUITE
AWHILE TO RECOVER
FROM A BLOW LIKE THAT.
- AND SO AFTER ALL THAT,
WE ENDED UP DOING THE JOB
THE SOLDATS WANTED ANYWAY--
WITHOUT LEARNING A THING.
AND TO MAKE THING WORSE,
SHAOLI STILL KNOWS OUR FACES.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND
AND ELIMINATE HER.
THAT'S OUR TOP PRIORITY
RIGHT NOW.
- HMM.
- ( baby crying )
- ( laughs ) OH PLEASE!
THIS IS A MEDICINE SHOP!
- Man: I'M SORRY,
BUT I COULDN'T FIND ANYTHING.
- THANKS FOR TRYING.
- LATER.
- HMPH.
- ( typing )
- Kirika: HERE.
- THANK YOU.
- YUN SHUTONG.
- I HAVE BEEN
WAITING FOR YOU.
PLEASE SIT.
- THIS IS QUITE CLOSE ENOUGH.
THE CLAN OF THE COLD-EYED
KILLER'S CLAWS
HAVE TREMENDOUS REACH,
SO IT IS SAID.
- HMM.
YOUR UNIFICATION-FUND ORIGINS
ARE SHOWING, MR. YUN.
- YOU HAVE OUR GRATITUDE
FOR A JOB WELL DONE.
SILENCING HO WAS
AN UNEXPECTED BONUS.
- AS HO WAS THE ONLY ONE WHO
KNEW YOU WERE THE INFORMANT,
IT SEEMED
THE NEXT LOGICAL STEP.
- MM-HMM, A VERY
ASTUTE DECISION.
- YES, I HAVE
STUDIED THIS CAREFULLY.
- HUH?
- FOR EXAMPLE,
HOW YOU WORK FOR THE SOLDATS,
WHILE AT THE SAME TIME
LEAKING THEIR INFORMATION
TO THE TRIADS.
THE WILL OF CHINA
IS A MYSTERIOUS THING.
- THE SOLDATS MAY HAVE THE PARTY
UNDER THEIR THUMB FOR NOW,
BUT IN TIME,
THERE IS NO DOUBT
THAT WE WILL SWALLOW
EVEN THE SOLDATS WHOLE.
"ALLY WITH THE STRONG,"
IT IS SAID.
AN ANCIENT WISDOM WHICH YOU
HAVE MOST CERTAINLY MASTERED.
YOU HAVE THE RUTHLESSNESS
TO SURVIVE IN THIS WORLD.
- ( chuckles )
- I SHALL EXPECT
GOOD THINGS FROM YOU.
I WILL BE CONTACT--
( gasping )
- ( chuckling )
THAT'S RIGHT--
THE INCENSE BURNER.
TO ME, IT IS BUT A SWEET
HEAVENLY FRAGRANCE.
BUT TO NORMAL PEOPLE,
IT IS THE BRINGER OF DEATH.
- T-TRAITOR.
- OH, NOT A TRAITOR.
JUST A GIRL WITH THE
RUTHLESSNESS NEEDED TO SURVIVE.
- THEN WHY KILL ME TOO?
- TO "ALLY WITH THE STRONG."
IF I COME BEARING
YOUR HEAD AS A GIFT,
THE SOLDATS ARE SURE
TO WELCOME ME WITH OPEN ARMS.
- ( choking )
- MMM. ( chuckles )
- ACCORDING
TO MY INFORMATION,
YUN HAS A PRIVATE RESIDENCE
SOMEWHERE NEAR HERE.
- ( both gasp )
- NOT AGAIN.
- ( gasps )
- HMPH.
- I ASSUME YOU ARE THE ENVOY
FROM THE SOLDATS.
- YES.
I HAVE BEEN GIVEN FULL AUTHORITY
ON THIS MATTER.
I SHALL NOW HEAR YOU OUT.
- HMM, VERY WELL.
DID YOU RECEIVE THE GIFT
THAT I SENT?
HE WAS LEAKING INFORMATION
FROM THE SOLDATS.
HIS NAME WAS YUN SHUTONG
OF CHINA'S UNIFICATION
OPERATIONS FRONT.
- AND YOUR POINT IS?
- MY POINT IS THAT
I ELIMINATED A TRAITOR
FOR THE SOLDATS!
I TOOK CARE OF HIM FOR YOU,
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT?!
- ( blade clatters )
- Both: MM-HMM.
- Chloe: THE SOLDATS HAVE
NO NEED FOR ONE SUCH AS YOU.
THAT SHOULD TELL YOU
ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW.
GOODBYE.
- ( ragged breathing )
- ( inhales, bones crack )
( yells )
( gasps )
- SO THIS IS YOUR TRICK.
INTERESTING, BUT DIRTY.
- ( bones crack, hisses )
- ( blade snicks )
- ( groans )
- POISONOUS INSECT.
- ( soft moaning )
- ( gun clicks )
- THE TWO OF YOU HAVE
ACCOMPLISHED YOUR TASK.
- OUR TASK?
AND WHICH ONE WOULD THAT BE?
I THINK IT'S TIME YOU TOLD US
WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON.
- ( snorts )
- UH.
- PLEASE, CHLOE.
PLEASE TELL ME THE TRUTH.
- ( gasps )
- WHO AM I?
PLEASE.
- THE GRAND RETOUR.
- THE GRAND RETOUR?
- IT IS CALLED
"THE GREAT RETURN."
BOTH YOU AND I
MUST ENDURE THE TRIALS
IN PREPARATION FOR IT.
- ( door slams )
- ( women singing )