- ( men chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR--
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE OF
THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- WELL, THAT'S ONE MORE
LEAD SCRATCHED.
THE ALEXANDER
TRADING COMPANY IS CLEAN.
IF THERE WAS ANYTHING THERE,
THERE'S NO TRACE LEFT.
- ( computer beeps )
- HUH?
- ( double clicks )
- ( beeping )
- AHA.
- "A SINNER
ONCE PASSED AWAY
WILL NEVER RETURN.
HOWEVER, THE SINS
WILL NEVER VANISH.
AND AS FOR THE LOVE,
IT WILL NEVER DIE.
THE BLOOD OF THE SOLDATS
WILL SEEP THROUGHOUT
THE WILDERNESS AND FLOW..."
- I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE HOME.
- THE TWO HANDS
OF THE SOLDATS--
THE TWO HANDS
OF THE SOLDATS?
- HEY, ARE YOU
LISTENING IN THERE?
THIS GUY SAYS HE HAS INFORMATION
REGARDING THAT BOOK.
KIRIKA.
KIRIKA?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- OH, IT'S NOTHING THAT'S
WORTH MENTIONING, I GUESS.
- ( people chattering )
- THAT EXAM WAS SO HARD.
- ( chattering continues )
- ( Kirika pants )
THERE I GO AGAIN.
- MM-HMM.
PROFESSOR CHATELLE
IS AN AUTHORITY
ON ANCIENT
HISTORICAL DOCUMENTS.
I'D ACTUALLY SENT HIM THE VERY
FIRST PHOTOCOPY WE CAME ACROSS,
BUT HE ONLY JUST RESPONDED
TO THAT QUERY.
OF COURSE THIS COULD BE
JUST ANOTHER DEAD END.
- Professor: THERE'S
NO MISTAKE ABOUT IT.
THIS IS PART OF
THE LANGONEL MANUSCRIPT.
- THE LANGONEL MANUSCRIPT?
- UH-HUH.
HERE.
- ( rustling )
( papers rustle )
- JUST LOOK AT THIS.
THIS IS A REFERENCE BOOK
OF ARCHAIC DOCUMENTS
FROM THE MIDDLE AGES
WHEREIN ONE OF THE PASSAGES
IN YOUR TEXT
IS QUOTED DIRECTLY.
SEE?
"THE MAN WITHIN THE MAN.
THE LOVE WITHIN THE LOVE.
THE SIN WITHIN THE SIN."
- Mireille:
THAT'S IT, ALL RIGHT.
- IT'S FROM A MANUSCRIPT
SECRETLY TRANSCRIBED
AT THE MONASTERY OF LANGONEL
IN THE 13th CENTURY.
NO EARLIER VERSION
OF THIS TEXT
HAS BEEN FOUND TO DATE.
THAT'S WHY IT IS CALLED
THE LANGONEL MANUSCRIPT.
HOWEVER, I AM AFRAID
THAT LITTLE ELSE IS KNOWN ABOUT
THIS SECRET BOOK,
EXCEPT THAT IT'S VERY OLD.
BUT TO HAVE LAID MY EYES
ON EVEN A COPY OF
THE LANGONEL MANUSCRIPT,
WELL, LET'S SAY I WAS
QUITE SURPRISED.
- ARE THERE COPIES?
I MEAN, ONES WE COULD READ?
- HMM, AT ONE TIME,
THERE WERE TWO.
IN PARIS AND BERLIN.
UNFORTUNATELY, BOTH WERE
LOST IN FIRES DURING THE WAR.
- FIRES.
- BUT THE FACT THAT
YOU HAVE THIS PHOTOCOPY
PROVES THAT ANOTHER COPY
MUST EXIST SOMEWHERE.
PERHAPS IT IS EVEN THE ONE
FROM WHICH THE LANGONEL
VERSION WAS TRANSCRIBED.
- ( printing )
( printing continues )
- ( sighs )
- ( clock tower chimes )
- ( clicking )
I FOUND ONE!
CASPER EDLINGER,
AN AUSTRIAN MULTI-MILLIONAIRE.
THIS IS IT.
( mutters sleepily )
THANK YOU.
- HUH?
YOU CAN'T SLEEP EITHER?
- YOU MEAN WHEN WE'VE
FINALLY GOTTEN THIS FAR?
- MM-HMM.
- IT'S IN VIENNA,
THE BOOK THAT COULD
HOLD ALL OF THE CLUES
THAT WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
- AND SOON--
SOON THE TWO OF US
WILL BE THERE,
OPENING THE DOOR
TO OUR PAST.
- KIRIKA?
- HMM?
- THERE WAS A PROMISE
THAT WE MADE.
- I REMEMBER.
- WHEN EVERYTHING
BECOMES CLEAR,
I PROMISED THAT
I WOULD KILL YOU.
- THOSE TWO MUST
BE TAKEN CARE OF.
I MEAN CERTAIN DEATH,
NOT THESE RIDICULOUS TRIALS.
- ( frustrated groan )
IT SEEMS THAT'S
THE ONLY CHOICE.
- I WOULD HAVE LIKED
TO DRAW THOSE TWO
INTO OUR FOLD IF POSSIBLE.
- IT CANNOT BE HELPED.
ALTENA'S INFLUENCE HAS GROWN
MUCH FASTER THAN EXPECTED.
- HMM.
WE WILL DISPATCH
OUR BEST KNIGHTS THIS TIME,
BUT THE PRETEXT WILL REMAIN
THAT IT IS A TRIAL.
- AND SINCE THE SANCTIONS
FOR THE TRIAL
HAVE ALREADY BEEN APPROVED,
THEY'LL BE NO PROBLEM.
- IF THAT'S TO BE THE CASE,
SHOULD THE SANCTIONS
APPLY TO CHLOE AS WELL?
- YES, OF COURSE.
- Old man: IT WAS JUST
TWO YEARS AGO
THAT THE EDLINGER
FAMILY LIBRARY
BURNED TO THE GROUND
ALONG WITH
THE ENTIRE COLLECTION.
- I AM AFRAID THAT
THE LANGONEL MANUSCRIPT
WAS LOST AS WELL.
EVERYTHING OF VALUE
WAS DESTROYED.
SO WE LEFT THE BURNT REMAINS
WHERE THEY LAY.
GO AND SEARCH IF YOU WANT.
BUT NOW NOT A SINGLE COPY
OF THE LANGONEL MANUSCRIPT
EXISTS ON THIS EARTH,
NOT UNLESS
IT IS IN A PLACE
THAT HAS BEEN
FORGOTTEN BY TIME.
- SO AFTER ALL OF THAT,
ALL WE FOUND
IS A PILE OF ASHES
AND BROKEN RUBBLE.
THE BOOK THAT WE CAME FOR
NO LONGER EXISTS.
SO DOES THAT MEAN
ALL THOSE COPIES
WERE MADE BEFORE THE FIRE?
- Chloe: "A SINNER
ONCE PASSED AWAY
WILL NEVER RETURN,
BUT THE SINS
WILL NEVER VANISH
AND THE LOVE
WILL NEVER DIE.
THE HERMIT ALSO SPOKE THUS."
- CHLOE.
- "THE BLOOD OF
THE SOLDATS WILL SEEP.
IT WILL SEEP THROUGHOUT
THE WILDERNESS
AND FLOW INTO THE--" WHAT?
GREAT RIVER?
- WHY, YOU--
- BUT I BELIEVE
YOU KNOW THAT MUCH.
THE REST OF IT
GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"THE TWO HANDS
OF THE SOLDATS
ARE TWO MAIDENS,
BLACKER THAN BLACK,
BURDENED BY SIN,
REACHING OUT WITH MERCY.
NOIR.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE TITLE OF NOIR HAS ALWAYS
BELONGED TO THE SOLDATS.
- ( gasps )
- THAT IS THE TRUE NOIR.
TWO SUPREME BLADES
THAT, TOGETHER,
MAKE UP A SINGLE ENTITY,
THE SOLDATS TWO HANDS.
HOWEVER,
KNOWLEDGE OF THE RITUAL
OF ACCESSION TO NOIR WAS LOST
IN THE PASSAGE OF TIME,
UNTIL ONLY THE TERROR ELICITED
BY THAT NAME REMAINED.
AND IN THE YEARS SINCE,
COUNTLESS OUTLAWS HAVE
CLAIMED THE NAME NOIR.
MANY NOT EVEN KNOWING
ITS TRUE MEANING.
- I CHOSE THE NAME NOIR
TO HIDE THE FACT THAT
KIRIKA AND I WERE A TEAM,
BUT NOW YOU'RE SAYING
NOIR WAS A NAME FOR
A GROUP OF TWO ALL ALONG?
- ( sighs ) YES.
- THEN IT SEEMS THAT
THE THREAD THAT BINDS US
MUST BE AN ESPECIALLY
TWISTED ONE.
HOW ELSE TO EXPLAIN
SUCH A CHAIN OF CHANCE,
UNLESS THESE
UNTANGLING THREADS
ARE THE BLACK WEB
OF FATE ITSELF?
- ( running footsteps )
- ( grunts )
- SO EXACTLY WHY ARE
YOU TELLING US THIS?
- LET US FEED THE SAPLINGS
WITH WATER AND LIGHT,
BUT ONLY WHEN ALTENA
DESIRES IT TO BE SO.
- HMPH, THIS ALTENA--
SHE'S THE ONE WHO HOLDS
YOUR LEASH, RIGHT?
- ALTENA IS STRICT,
BUT A KIND MISTRESS.
SHE HAS BEEN ANXIOUSLY WAITING
FOR THE TWO OF YOU
TO OVERCOME THE TRIALS
THAT HAVE BEEN SENT.
- TRIALS.
- YES, FOR THAT IS THE FATE
OF THOSE WHO ARE
TO BE NOIR.
- THAT'S THE FATE OF
THOSE WHO'LL BE NOIR?
- RIGHT.
- IT WOULD APPEAR THAT YOU'RE
NOW BEING TARGETED AS WELL.
- BATTLES AGAINST
ABLE-BODIED KNIGHTS,
THE SUCCESSFUL EXECUTION
OF THE ASSIGNED TASKS
AND MISSIONS,
AND TRAPS LIKE
A SPIDER'S WEB--
ALL OF THESE ARE TRIALS
IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE ANCIENT
RITUAL OF SELECTING NOIR.
- AND WHAT IS-- OH!
- ( blades slashing )
- ( gags )
- ( gunfire continues )
- OH!
( groans )
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
- ( gunshot )
( gunshot )
- KIRIKA.
- ( gunshot echoes )
- IS THIS REALLY KIRIKA'S PAST?
COULD IT BE TRUE?
- Chloe: YOU KILL PEOPLE
SO EASILY
WITHOUT ANY HESITATION
OR REMORSE.
- ( blade slashes )
- ( man screams )
- ( chuckles )
YOU AND I
ARE THE TRUE NOIR,
BORN AND RAISED
IN THE NEST OF THE SOLDATS.
THE TWO OF US EXHIBITED THE
GREATEST APTITUDE AS ASSASSINS.
- ( gasps )
- THE SOLDATS
AREN'T YOUR ENEMY.
THE SOLDATS IS
THE PLACE YOU BELONG.
- ( gasps )
- YOU LOST YOUR MEMORIES,
BUT THINK.
WHY ELSE WOULD IT BE
THAT YOU WOULD LOOK AT ME SO?
- NO.  STOP.
- DO NOT WORRY.
YOU DO REMEMBER EVERYTHING...
BOTH AS A NOIR
AND AS AN ASSASSIN.
- DON'T SAY IT.
- YOU CAN ACCOMPLISH
YOUR TASK SO EASILY.
- PLEASE, STOP IT.
STOP TALKING.
- BECAUSE, EVER SINCE
YOU WERE A CHILD--
- LEAVE ME ALONE!
- ( gasps )
- NOIR, IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
TO THE DEPTHS OF HELL'S FIRE,
THEIR BLACK SOULS LURE
THE LOST CHILDREN.
- NOIR, IT IS THE NAME OF
AN ANCIENT FATE...
- Both: TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE OF THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
IT IS THE NAME OF
AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE OF THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
( continues )
- NO, KIRIKA.
KIRIKA!
- ( gasps )
AM I--
AM I...
- I WILL RETURN
IN THE NEAR FUTURE.
JUST ONE TIME MORE,
I PROMISE.
AND I WILL GIVE YOU YOUR
FINAL GUIDANCE TO THE MANOR.
- "THE HERMIT ALSO SPOKE THUS.
THE BLOOD OF THE SOLDATS
WILL SEEP THROUGHOUT
THE WILDERNESS
AND FLOW INTO
THE GREAT RIVER.
THE TWO HANDS OF THE SOLDATS
ARE TWO MAIDENS.
BLACKER THAN BLACK,
BURDENED BY SIN,
REACHING OUT WITH MERCY,
THEY ARE NOIR.
- I KNEW.
I DID.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
BUT I JUST...
- ( inaudible )
- Kirika:
I JUST WANTED TO BELIEVE
THAT A NORMAL ME
EXISTED SOMEWHERE.
THAT WAS ALL.
THAT'S ALL IT WAS.
I DIDN'T WANT TO KNOW.
BUT I KNOW NOW.
PLEASE, MIREILLE.
PLEASE DON'T LOOK
AT ME LIKE THAT.
- ( techno music playing )
- ( women chanting )