- ( people chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR.
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE,
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE
OF THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ( phone rings )
- Man on phone:
Uh, is that you, Mireille?
It's Vanel.
I have some information.
Yes, it's about that.
No, I'll tell you the details
when we meet in person.
Why don't you come
to my house tomorrow?
At noon, perhaps?
Yes, my wife would like
for you to come as well.
- UH...
- ( cocks )
- ( gasping )
( breathes shakily )
- ( footsteps )
WE'RE TOO LATE.
- ( gasps )
- Mireille: IT WAS MY FAULT.
I WAS CHECKING OUT
EVERYONE DUX HAD RECENTLY
COME INTO CONTACT WITH.
I'D ASKED VANEL TO TRACK DOWN
SOME INFORMATION...
AND I'M SURE
THAT HE WAS KILLED FOR IT...
ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY.
- IT'S NO USE.
- HMM?
- JUST THINKING ABOUT IT,
I MEAN.
- ( sighs )
YOU'RE RIGHT.
- ( beeping )
- Mireille:
THEY'RE TRYING TO KILL US.
THEY'RE TRYING TO KILL NOIR.
- ( gunshot )
- ( groaning )
THE FIRST TIME WE MET
WAS COINCIDENCE.
- TELL ME ONE THING:
WHO WAS IT THAT HIRED YOU
TO KILL NOIR?
- IF YOU WERE ME,
WOULD YOU TELL?
- ( chuckles ) NO WAY.
- ( laughs weakly )
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- ( gasps )
( coughing )
WHAT'S THE POINT OF ASKING?
NEITHER YOU
NOR I HAVE GRAVES WAITING
ON WHICH TO CARVE OUR NAMES.
( gags )
( weakly )
NEITHER YOU NOR...
- VANEL MUST'VE FOUND
A CLUE AS TO WHO THEY ARE.
AH.
- GOOD MORNING.
- ( sighs )
- OH.
- WATERING THE FLOWERS IS FINE,
BUT DON'T FORGET THAT THEY
MIGHT BE TURNING BLACK, ANYWAY.
NOIR.
I'D HEARD THAT NAME BEFORE.
IT'S ONE OF THE
OLDEST DESIGNATIONS
IN OUR LINE OF WORK...
AND YET NO ONE KNOWS
ITS ORIGINS.
IT'S LIKE A PUZZLE MADE UP
OF ODD-SHAPED PIECES.
THERE'S THE PIECE
WE CALL NOIR,
YOU'RE ANOTHER PIECE...
AND THEN THERE'S ONE MORE.
I'M GOING TO CHECK OUT
SOME OF VANEL'S OLD HAUNTS.
- ( pants )
- YOU NEEDN'T COME.
- ( door closes )
- ( distant siren )
- Man:
IT'S SO BRUTAL.
THE ENTIRE FAMILY
SLAUGHTERED LIKE THAT.
VANEL WAS A GOOD MAN
WITH A STRONG SENSE
OF HONOR.
EVEN AFTER
HE BECAME WELL-KNOWN,
HE STILL CAME BY
AND PAID HIS RESPECTS TO ME,
HIS OLD SUPERIOR.
TO MANY
HE MAY HAVE SEEMED RESERVED,
BUT HE WAS
A DOTING FATHER.
OUR FRIEND LOVED
HIS SON AND DAUGHTER
AS DEARLY AS LIFE ITSELF.
AND HIS WIFE--
NOW THERE WAS A FINE WOMAN.
SO TRAGIC.
- YES, IT WAS.
VANEL AND HIS WIFE
WERE AMONG THE FEW PEOPLE
IN THIS WORLD
I COULD TRUST.
- FINE FOLKS INDEED.
AND NOW YOU ARE
ASKING ABOUT...?
- ABOUT LAST WEEK, SIR.
- AH YES.
AS YOU SAID,
HE CAME INTO THE SHOP
RATHER UNEXPECTEDLY.
IT WAS THE FIRST TIME
HE'D STOPPED BY
IN NEARLY TWO YEARS,
SO I REMEMBER IT WELL.
- AND DID HE SAY ANYTHING?
- NOT REALLY.
HOLD ON.
HMM.  HMM.
NOW THAT I THINK OF IT,
HE WAS LOOKING RATHER PALE.
- I SEE.
- OH!  NOW I REMEMBER!
HE LEFT A BOTTLE
WITH YOUR NAME ON IT.
- ( gasps )
A BOTTLE?!  WHERE IS IT?
- HERE.  THIS ONE.
HE SAID HE WANTED
TO SHARE IT WITH YOU NEXT TIME.
- ( gasps )
- Vanel's voice:
"MIREILLE, TO OUR MEMORIES
OF SAINT GALAN'S CATHEDRAL."
- ( grunts )
( grunts )
- ( cocks )
- ( gun clicks )
- ( sighs )
- ( rock music plays )
- WHAT MEMORIES
OF SAINT GALAN'S CATHEDRAL?
- I'VE NEVER BEEN THERE.
- AND THIS?
- I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THAT'S ABOUT EITHER.
- CIRCLES AROUND "D" AND 5.
TRIANGLES AROUND "G" AND 7.
- I THINK
VANEL MUST'VE DISCOVERED
SOMETHING REALLY BIG,
SOMETHING THAT
SCARED HIM SO BADLY...
THAT HE FELT
HE HAD TO HIDE IT.
- IN SAINT GALAN'S CATHEDRAL.
- IN THE CHAPEL?
IN THE BELL TOWER?
- THE MONASTERY?
THE CLOISTER?
- NO, NOT THERE.
THE HERB GARDEN?
- THE CATACOMB?
- ( gasps )
- HUH?
- ( switch clicks )
- ( electrical humming )
- Mireille's voice:
"D," "DROIT," RIGHT?
FIVE.
ONE, TWO,
THREE,
FOUR,
FIVE.
FIFTH TO THE RIGHT.
"G" IS FOR "GAUCHE."
SEVENTH TO THE LEFT.
ONE...
TWO...
THREE...
FOUR...
FIVE...
SIX...
SEVEN.
- ( switch clicks )
- ( rustling )
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
- ( bird cawing )
- ( sighs )
- ( gun cocks )
- ( gasps )
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE HERE.
- YOU WHAT?
- I KNEW THAT I WAS BEING
FOLLOWED OUT HERE,
AND I KNEW
THAT YOU WERE AFTER THAT.
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- BUT WHAT WE'RE AFTER IS YOU.
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL US
EVERYTHING YOU KNOW.
LET'S START
WITH WHO YOU WORK FOR.
- ( groans )
YOU THINK
IT WILL BE THAT EASY?
- ( gunfire )
- ( gasps )
- ( man grunts )
- ( rock music playing,
woman singing )
- ( gasps )
- ( cocks )
- ( grunts )
- ( man grunts, thuds )
- SO WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL ABOUT
THE PHOTOCOPY IN THAT FOLDER?
- ( sighs )
IT'S PRECIOUS.
MORE PRECIOUS THAN THE LIFE
OF ANYONE ON THIS PLANET.
- YOU'RE THE ONES WHO KILLED
VANEL AND HIS FAMILY,
AREN'T YOU?
- SUCH WERE THE ORDERS
THAT WERE GIVEN US.
THEY SAID THE SECRET
MUST BE MAINTAINED.
- "THEY SAID"?
AND WHO ARE THEY?
- WHO ARE THEY?
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO KNOW.
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE,
AN ABSOLUTE PRESENCE.
ONLY A HANDFUL
EVEN KNOW THEY EXIST.
BUT I KNOW THE TRUTH.
SHOOT ME
AND YOUR KEY IS GONE.
- ( breathing angrily )
- ( chuckles )
- ( gunshot )
- ( groaning )
( chuckles )
( groans )
- ( breathes shakily )
- Mireille's voice:
"THE MAN WITHIN THE MAN.
THE LOVE
WITHIN THE LOVE.
THE SIN WITHIN THE SIN.
THE HERMIT TOLD
UNTO THE SINNER,
THE SOLDATS IS
WITH THE TRUTH."
THE SOLDATS.
SO THAT'S THE NAME...
OF OUR ENEMY.
- HUH?
- BACK HOME...
IN CORSICA,
MY PARENTS AND OLDER BROTHER
WERE ALL MURDERED.
TO THIS DAY I HAVE NO IDEA
WHO KILLED THEM OR WHY.
THAT WAS THE LAST TIME
I SAW THIS WATCH...
UNTIL YOU BROUGHT IT TO ME
FROM MY PAST.
- BUT NOW I HAVE NOTHING.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY, MIREILLE.
- ( chuckles )
I WILL OPEN
THIS DOOR TO THE PAST.
I SWEAR I WILL.
- ( woman singing
in Japanese )