- ( voices chanting )
- Woman: NOIR...
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
TO WARD THE DARKNESS
FROM THE NURSING BABES
THEIR BLACK ROBES
SERVE AS SHIELDS.
- ( rain pattering )
- ( gasps )
- ( gunshots )
- ( groans )
- ( whimpering )
- ( birds chirping )
- ( child laughing )
- Man: MIREILLE.
- ( laughing continues )
- MIREILLE!
MIREILLE...
MIREILLE.
- HUH.
- HELLO, MIREILLE.
- ( gasps )
UNCLE CLAUDE?
- THAT'S RIGHT, MIREILLE.
- IT IS YOU!
UNCLE CLAUDE!
- 10 YEARS SINCE
WE LEFT CORSICA.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME, HUH?
- AND I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
FOR NEARLY HALF OF THAT.
- YEAH.
- SO HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN BACK IN PARIS?
- NOT VERY LONG.
I FOUND MYSELF MISSING
ALL SORTS OF THINGS
SO HERE I AM.
YOUR LATE FATHER,
HE WAS A GREAT MAN, YOU KNOW?
- UH-HUH.
- LAURENT BOUQUET...
HE WAS A TOUGH SYNDICATE LEADER
AND CARING FAMILY PATRIARCH.
- I KNOW.
- CORSICA WOULD BE A BETTER
PLACE IF HE STILL LIVED.
AND NEITHER YOU NOR I WOULD
HAVE BEEN DRIVEN INTO EXILE.
SO ARE YOU STILL
IN THE BUSINESS?
- I GUESS YOU COULD SAY THAT.
- I SEE.
- SO, AND YOU?
- ME?
- ARE YOU WORKING
HERE IN PARIS?
- WELL, THAT IS THE PLAN.
- ( foghorn blowing )
- Mireille: WITH THE DEATH
OF MY PARENTS,
THE BOUQUET FAMILY
AND SYNDICATE COLLAPSED.
THE DOMINION OF CORSICA
FELL TO THE HANDS
OF A RIVAL SYNDICATE,
AND HAVING LOST
MY HOME AND FUTURE,
I FLED THE COUNTRY
WITH MY UNCLE CLAUDE.
CLAUDE FEYDER...
MY UNCLE
ON MY MOTHER'S SIDE.
( sighs )
HE PLAYED WITH ME AND TOOK
CARE OF ME WHEN I WAS YOUNGER.
AND LATER HE TAUGHT ME
MY TRADE.
HE WAS QUITE A TASKMASTER.
HOPEFULLY I'LL GET
TO INTRODUCE YOU TWO.
- HE DOESN'T...
KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE SOLDATS, DOES HE?
- ( scoffs )
OF COURSE HE DOESN'T KNOW!
IF HE KNOWN ANYTHING AT ALL,
HE WOULD HAVE TOLD ME
LONG AGO, WOULDN'T HE?
- OH, I GUESS THAT'S RIGHT.
UM, MIREILLE?
- YEAH?
- I AM HAPPY FOR YOU, HONESTLY.
- Man: SO HOW ARE THINGS
IN MARSEILLE?
- OH, YOU KNOW.
IT'S COMING ALONG.
WHAT ABOUT THINGS HERE?
- HMM?
- ( gasps )
- ( silenced gunshots )
- ( groaning )
- ( gunshot )
- ( moans )
- DO YOU REMEMBER
THAT WEEK AT THE LAKE?
- OH.
YOU MEAN THE ONE THAT
WE WENT TO WHEN I WAS LITTLE?
OF COURSE.
THAT WAS BACK WHEN
WE FIRST ARRIVED IN PARIS.
I WAS IN SUCH LOW SPIRITS.
BUT LIKE THE GOOD UNCLE
YOU WERE,
YOU WERE ALWAYS TRYING
TO CHEER ME UP, WEREN'T YOU?
- Claude: I WAS JUST THINKING
WHY DON'T WE GO BACK THERE?
- HUH?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
DON'T YOU WANT TO?
- OH NO,
IT SOUNDS WONDERFUL!
- WOULD YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT NOIR, MIREILLE?
- I'M AFRAID I DON'T.
- NOTHING, HUH?
- UM, BY NOIR,
YOU ARE REFERRING
TO THAT NOIR, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- SO WHY DO YOU ASK?
- OH, IT'S NOTHING.
YOU DON'T NEED TO KNOW.
- ( voices chanting )
- ( ship's horn blowing )
- ( panting )
- ( person whistling )
- GO!
- CUT HIM OFF!
- RIGHT!
- THERE WE GO.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, IT'S NOTHING.
( sighs )
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT ANYWAY.
REALLY,
IT'S NOTHING AT ALL.
- WOULD YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT NOIR, MIREILLE?
- ( thinking ) WHY?
WHY WOULD HE WANT TO KNOW?
- ( knocks )
- YES?
MIREILLE, THESE JUST ARRIVED.
- THEY'RE A GIFT FROM MY UNCLE.
I THINK THAT THEY'RE FLOWERS
THAT HE GREW HIMSELF.
- HOW NICE FOR YOU.
- YEAH.
- HMM.
- YO,
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
- THANKS FOR COMING, FEYDER.
I'M GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT.
- AND I'M GLAD TO SEE
YOU'RE IN GOOD HEALTH, DUPOIS.
- GREAT GREAT.
PLEASE HAVE A SEAT.
SO WOULD YOU LIKE A DRINK?
- NO, I'M FINE.
- JUST HOW LONG HAVE
YOU BEEN BACK IN TOWN?
- OH, NOT LONG.
- HEY, WHAT ARE WE, STRANGERS?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT YOU DIDN'T
CONTACT ME SOONER?
- I HAD A LITTLE BUSINESS
TO TAKE CARE OF FIRST.
- AND WITH YOUR SKILLS,
YOU MUST BE WORKING QUITE A LOT.
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
I HAD A LITTLE FAVOR
TO ASK OF YOU AS WELL.
- HMM, SUCH AS?
- WELL, AS YOU
PROBABLY KNOW...
( sighs )
THERE'S BEEN A RASH
OF ODD MURDERS RECENTLY.
- YEAH, ALL THE HITS
HAVE BEEN LOCAL BIG SHOTS.
- WELL, THE FACT IS
I'VE HAD A LOT OF DEALINGS
WITH THOSE PEOPLE,
SO I WANT YOU TO FIND OUT
WHO KILLED THEM.
- I SEE.
- WILL YOU DO IT?
- EASILY.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE TO CHECK.
- REALLY?!
YOU MEAN YOU ALREADY
HAVE SOME I--
- MM-HMM.
I'M THE ONE WHO KILLED THEM.
- THAT'S A CLASSIC, FEYDER!
I NEVER THOUGHT YOU HAD
A HUMOROUS BONE IN YOUR BODY,
BUT--
- ( gunshot, casing clatters )
- I'M SORRY, BUT THEIR ORDERS
WERE QUITE SPECIFIC.
- ( groans )
- ( glass shatters )
- AND THERE WAS
ONE MORE THING...
I'M AFRAID THAT YOUR NAME WAS ON
THEIR LIST AS WELL, MY FRIEND.
- ( phone rings )
- Mireille: YES?
OH, UNCLE!
THANK YOU FOR THE FLOWERS.
YES, THEY'RE WONDERFUL.
UH-HUH.
I LOVE THEM!
HUH?
YOU MEAN RIGHT NOW?
NO NO, I CAN MAKE IT.
- ( people chattering )
- ( car honks )
- Mireille: WOW!
- WELL, NO NEED FOR CEREMONY.
COME ON IN.
THIS WAY, MIREILLE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
AREN'T THEY SOMETHING?
RAISE THEM WITH LOVE
AND FLOWERS WILL RESPOND.
THOUGH I MUST ADMIT,
SOMETIMES I FAIL.
- UNCLE CLAUDE,
YOU DIDN'T BRING ME HERE
JUST TO SHOW ME
YOUR FLOWERS, DID YOU?
- THEY SAY THAT IF YOU TALK TO
FLOWERS, THEY'LL OFTEN GROW--
- ANSWER ME.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'M WORKING ON A BIG JOB
RIGHT NOW.
- AND YOU WANT ME TO HELP YOU,
IS THAT IT?
- NO.
I WANT YOU TO STAND BACK
AND WATCH.
- JUST WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
UH.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
YOUR LITTLE ROOMMATE.
- WHICH MEANS YOUR RUNNING INTO
ME WASN'T AN ACCIDENT, WAS IT?
YOU MUST HAVE HAD THIS IN MIND
RIGHT FROM THE START.
SO YOU LIED...
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
- BUT YOU LIED TO ME
AS WELL, MIREILLE.
NOIR-- YOU SAID YOU
DIDN'T KNOW HER.
YOU KNOW, I COULD HAVE
TAKEN CARE OF THIS
WITHOUT TELLING YOU,
BUT I FELT I OWED YOU THE
PROFESSIONAL COURTESY.
- YOU'RE WORKING
FOR THE SOLDATS.
- YOU MEAN YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE SOLDATS?!
- ( gasps ) YOU ARE.
AREN'T YOU?
- IT'S IN OUR BEST INTERESTS.
FOR YOUR SAKE AND MINE,
I HAVE TO.
IF I DON'T FINISH THIS JOB,
THE SOLDATS WILL CRUSH ME.
JUST AS THEY CRUSHED
YOUR FATHER.
- ( gasps )
- THAT'S RIGHT.
LAURENT BOUQUET WAS KILLED
FOR DEFYING THE SOLDATS,
TOGETHER WITH HIS WIFE
AND SON.
- AND YOU KNEW THAT?
YOU KNEW THAT ALL THIS TIME
AND YOU NEVER TOLD ME?
ANSWER ME!
- YOU MUST NOT
TRY TO LEARN MORE
ABOUT THE SOLDATS.
I SWORE AN OATH
TO THEM, MIREILLE.
I SWORE THAT I WOULD
ALWAYS FOLLOW THEIR ORDERS
WITHOUT QUESTION.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
I WAS ABLE TO LEAVE
CORSICA ALIVE WITH YOU.
WE LIVE BUT BY THEIR GRACE.
- ( gasps )
- SO NOW YOU KNOW THE TRUTH
AND HOW TERRIBLE THEY ARE.
OH.
THIS ONE'S
NO GOOD ANYMORE.
WE ARE MUCH FRAILER
THAN THESE FLOWERS, MIREILLE.
ONCE THE SOLDATS SINK
THEIR ROOTS INTO YOUR SOUL,
YOU CAN NEVER ESCAPE.
NO ONE HAS, NOT EVER.
PLEASE DON'T MAKE THE SAME
FOOLISH MISTAKE
YOUR FATHER MADE, MIREILLE.
TRUST ME.
- ( voices chanting )
- I UNDERSTAND.
- DO YOU?
- I'LL BRING HER BACK
HERE WITH ME TONIGHT.
- THAT'S PERFECT.
AND ONCE ALL OF THIS
HAS BEEN TAKEN CARE OF,
LET'S GO TO THAT LAKE.
THE WATER'S NEVER CLEARER
THAN IT IS RIGHT NOW.
- ALL RIGHT.
- ( zips )
I'M GOING OUT FOR A BIT, OKAY?
- GOING WHERE?
- JUST A LITTLE ERRAND.
YOU DON'T NEED TO TAG ALONG.
- ( door opens )
( closes )
- ( sighs )
DIDN'T I JUST SAY
NOT TO TAG ALONG?
GO HOME, OKAY?
- NO.
- I SAID GO HOME.
- AND I SAID NO.
- ( huffs )
- SO YOU'RE STILL GOING?
WHY?
- YOU'RE A LITTLE LATE.
- WHERE'S MY UNCLE?
- OH, HE'S IN THE GREENHOUSE.
- DO YOU WANT ME TO CALL
MR. FEYDER FOR YOU?
- NO THANKS,
I KNOW THE WAY ALREADY.
- GO RIGHT AHEAD THEN.
( chuckles )
- HMM.
- Man: HMMM.
- ( grunts )
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
- ( groaning )
- YOU LITTLE BITCH!
- ( gunshot )
- ( birds chirping )
- UNCLE?
- HUH?
- WE CAN'T GO
BACK TO THAT LAKE.
I'M SO SORRY.
- IT WOULD SEEM
THAT YOU'RE LAURENT BOUQUET'S
DAUGHTER TO THE END.
- ( sighs )
( woman singing )