- ( voices chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR...
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE
OF THE NEWLY BORN
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ( bells tolling )
( birds chirping )
- HMM?
- OH.
OH.
YOU'RE VERY GOOD.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- HMM.
WELL, THIS ONE'S NICE.
UH, BUT THIS ONE'S NICE TOO.
DECISIONS, DECISIONS.
HEY.
WHAT IS IT?
A SKETCHBOOK, HUH?
YOU MEAN THAT YOU WANT ONE?
- MM-HMM.
- FOR SKETCHING, RIGHT?
- HMM.
WELL, I SUPPOSE
MAYBE IT IS TIME
THAT YOU TOOK UP A HOBBY
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE.
BUT IF YOU WANT IT,
LET'S HURRY UP AND GET IT.
- AH.
- HUH?
HELLO.
- ( gasps )
OH, I'M SORRY.
I-- I MEAN...
I GUESS I'M IN YOUR SPOT.
- MY SPOT?
- UH-HUH.
- I DON'T BELIEVE
THIS SPOT BELONGS TO ANYONE.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO DRAW HERE,
YOU'RE CERTAINLY WELCOME TO.
AH, WHAT A GREAT BREEZE.
ISN'T IT GORGEOUS TODAY?
- UH-HUH.
- IN ANY CASE,
DON'T LET ME BOTHER YOU.
- SURE.
- HMM.
UH, HEY,
YOU'RE STARTING
WITH A BRUSH FIRST?
- HUH?
- I MEAN MOST PEOPLE
SKETCH IT OUT BEFOREHAND.
- THAT'S HOW IT'S DONE?
- UH, WELL, DON'T MIND ME.
I'M SURE IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
THEY SAY THE BEST WAY
IS THE WAY THAT YOU WANT TO.
- OKAY.
( brush strokes continue )
- ( scissors snipping )
- Mireille: IT SEEMS YOUR SHOP
IS AS POPULAR AS EVER,
RIGHT, PAULETTE?
- OF COURSE.
THE BEST BUZZ COMES
AT A STEEP PRICE.
- SO TELL ME,
JUST WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD?
- CHRISTIAN GALLE.
INTERESTED?
- I ASSUME YOU MEAN MORGAN'S
OLD RIGHT-HAND MAN.
I THOUGHT HE WAS SERVING TIME
IN SOUTH AMERICA.
- WELL, HE'S BACK IN PARIS.
PARDONED THEY SAY.
THEY ALSO SAY
THAT YOU DID MORGAN.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
THERE WAS QUITE A BIT
OF BAD BLOOD BACK THEN.
- A TYPICAL TURF WAR.
- HMM.
GALLE'S BEEN GATHERING MEN.
HE THINKS HE CAN TAKE YOU.
THIS SESSION WILL BE
RATHER PRICEY.
- ( sighs )
I THOUGHT IT WOULD.
- UGH, YOU'RE SO FORTUNATE
TO HAVE SUCH BEAUTIFUL
HAIR, MIREILLE.
JUST LIKE I DID
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE.
- THANK YOU.
- ( chirping )
- WELL, THE SUN'S
STARTING TO SET.
IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO CALL IT QUITS.
SO YOU'RE GOING
TO KEEP AT IT?
- HUH?
- UH.
UH, NO, IT'S JUST THAT
YOUR PAINTING IS
VERY DISTINCTIVE.
- IT'S DISTINCTIVE?
- I'M NOT VERY GOOD MYSELF,
BUT THAT'S REALLY
SOMETHING UNIQUE.
LOOK, DON'T MIND ME.
I'M JUST TALKING.
WHAT'S BEST IS
TO PLEASE YOURSELF.
- OKAY.
- IF YOU EVER NEED ANY SUPPLIES,
THIS IS THE BEST PLACE.
THE QUALITY IS GOOD
AND THE PRICES ARE REASONABLE.
- THANKS.
I'LL DO THAT.
- AH, SOLD OUT AGAIN.
- HUH?
- THE OWNER OF THE SHOP
MAKES THOSE TILES HIMSELF.
EVERYONE WANTS ONE,
BUT HE REFUSES TO PRINT
ANYTHING MORE THAN LIMITED RUNS.
HE'S SO STUBBORN.
- HMM.
- WELL, LATER, OKAY?
- ( sighs )
SO HAVE YOU LOCATED
THE WOMAN YET?
- HMM, DON'T WORRY, BOSS.
WE'LL FIND HER.
- ( chuckles )
OH, I'M COUNTING
ON IT, MON AMI.
- OH.
- ( engine stops )
- ( sighs )
- OH.
HUH?
- ( chuckles )
THERE WE GO.
- SO DO YOU SEE HIM OFTEN?
- HUH?
- THE MAN THAT YOU WERE
PAINTING WITH.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- UH-HUH.
YOU SHOULDN'T
SEE HIM ANYMORE.
- UH.
- ( gasps ) OH.
- LIKE IT?
IT'S YOURS.
THE LEGION GAVE ME THAT.
THE FOREIGN LEGION, THAT IS.
FOR DISTINGUISHED SERVICE
IN GUIANA.
( groans )
MY NAME'S MILOSH HAVEL.
I'M CZECHOSLOVAKIAN.
OF COURSE I'VE BEEN AWAY
FROM THERE SO LONG.
IT'S NOT THE SAME PLACE NOW.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- MY...
NAME?
- HEY, NO STRESS.
WE'VE ALL GOT THINGS
WE DON'T TALK ABOUT.
IT'S FINE.
HALF OF THE FOREIGN LEGION IS
FROM EASTERN EUROPE, YOU KNOW?
IT'S AND UGLY PLACE FOR MEN
WHO'VE DESERTED THEIR COUNTRIES.
OR WHOSE COUNTRIES
HAVE DESERTED THEM.
AND YET...
THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT WHILE PAINTING HERE--
WHETHER TO JOIN UP AGAIN.
( sighs )
SORRY.
I CAN'T EXPECT SOMEONE LIKE YOU
TO KNOW WHAT MY WORLD
IS LIKE, CAN I?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
- YOU'RE STILL SEEING
THAT MAN, AREN'T YOU?
- YES.
- ( sighs )
I COULD HAVE SWORN I TOLD YOU
NOT TO SEE HIM ANYMORE.
- WHY NOT?
- ( exhales )
- HUH?
FOLLOWING US?
- UH-HUH.
IS HE STILL BACK THERE?
- YES.
- COVER THE PARK EXITS.
I WANT THAT BLONDE ONE DEAD.
( chuckles )
- RIGHT.
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
( moans, thuds )
- ( gunshot )
- HUH HUH?
- ( grunts )
- DAMN!
( gasps, exhales )
- THE LAST TIME WE MET,
YOU SURVIVED BY RUNNING AWAY.
- ( growling )
YOU BITCH.
- BAD MOVE.
LOOKS LIKE CHECKMATE.
- ( car approaching )
- ( grunts )
- COME ON, GET IN, QUICK!
- WATCH WHERE
YOU'RE DRIVING, DAMN IT!
ARE YOU TRYING
TO GET US BOTH KILLED?
- I SAVED YOUR DERRIERE
AND YOU CAN'T EVEN SAY A
WORD OF THANKS, CAN YOU?
- HUH!
( sighs )
- WELL, THAT WAS
A TOTAL SCREW-UP.
I'D HEARD SHE WAS TOUGH,
BUT I HAD NO IDEA.
- DAMN THEM,
I SWEAR I'LL KILL THEM
NO MATTER WHAT.
- HEY.
- HELLO AGAIN.
- I'VE DECIDED TO RE-ENLIST.
SHOOTING PEOPLE
AND GETTING MEDALS...
I'D GOTTEN SO SICK OF IT.
BUT I CAN'T SEEM TO FIND
ANYTHING ELSE THAT I'M GOOD AT.
I GUESS I SHOULD
HAVE KNOWN, HUH?
YOUR PAINTING'S
TURNED OUT WELL.
IT'S QUITE BOLD,
BUT IT'S TASTEFUL TOO,
EVEN IF, STILL A...
LITTLE CLUMSY.
- ( laughs )
DO YOU THINK SO?
- I GUESS THIS IS GOODBYE, HUH?
- UH-HUH.
- EVEN IN AFRICA,
I PAINTED WHENEVER I COULD.
YOU SHOULD
KEEP PAINTING TOO.
- I WILL.
- WELL THEN.
- ( bells tolling )
- ( soft gasp )
( running )
MR. MILOSH!
- HUH?
- ( tires squeal )
( soft sobs )
- ( moans )
- A GUN?
NO, IT'S OKAY.
PLEASE DON'T--
( groans )
- RIGHT. I SEE.
THANK YOU, PAULETTE. PUT IT ON
MY BILL FOR NEXT TIME, OKAY?
I KNOW WHERE
GALLE'S HIDING.
- All: HUH?
- WHO ARE YOU?
HOW DID YOU GET IN HERE?
- ( gunshots )
- MMM.
- ( gunshot )
- ( screams )
( moaning )
- ( gunshots )
- ( running footsteps )
- ( moaning )
- HEH.
- ( body thuds )
- THIS IS WHY I TOLD YOU!
( huffs )
( sighs )
THAT'S WHY...
THAT'S WHY I TOLD YOU.
( woman singing )