- ( men chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR--
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE OF
THE NEWLY BORN,
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ( man laughs )
- ( classical music plays )
- ( people chattering )
( chatter continues )
- UNBELIEVABLE...
( speaks indistinctly )
DID YOU SEE THE LOOK
ON HIS FACE?
- YOUR EXCELLENCY,
CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR APPOINTMENT
AS MINISTER OF DEFENSE.
- OH, TANNER!
THANK YOU FOR COMING,
MY FRIEND.
- AS REPRESENTATIVES OF
THE ATRIDE CORPORATION,
WE CONGRATULATE YOU.
- BUT THIS IS ALL THANKS
TO ATRIDE.
- Tanner: NOT AT ALL, GENERAL.
OUR CORPORATION BELIEVES
IT IS A DIRECT RESULT
OF YOUR INNATE VIRTUES.
AND I THINK YOU WILL FIND
THAT IS ALSO THE BELIEF
OF THE CITIZENS
WHO CONSIDER
THE PRESIDENT'S FACTION
TO BE A SOURCE OF THEIR
FINANCIAL PROBLEMS.
- ( laughs )
THAT MAY BE.
BUT YOU CANNOT DENY
THAT THIS IS
A BIG STEP FORWARD
FOR YOUR PROJECT AS WELL.
ULGIA HAS A NEW LEADER
AND YOU HAVE GAINED
A FORTUNE, MY FRIEND.
- AND WE ARE MUCH OBLIGED.
- IT APPEARS NEXT YEAR
WILL BE FRUITFUL FOR ALL OF US.
- Tanner: YES, SIR.
- HMM.
THINK OF THIS AS
A CELEBRATION IN ADVANCE.
ENJOY.
- Tanner: WE WILL.
AND THANK YOU, SIR.
- ( music continues )
- WELL, BY THIS TIME
NEXT YEAR,
THIS COUNTRY'S POPULATION
WILL HAVE BEEN CUT IN HALF.
- ( woman giggles )
- HMM?  MMM.
( chuckles )
HEY.
( gasps )
- ( screams )
- WHAT THE HELL?
- ( people scream, shouting )
- TANNER!  HUH?
- ( screaming continues )
- General: TANNER!
- Mireille:
THE ATRIDE CORPORATION
PROMOTES ITSELF AS AN
INTERNATIONAL SECURITY SERVICE,
BUT WHAT THEY REALLY DO
IS COORDINATE COUP D'ETATS.
THEIR USUAL MODE OF OPERATION
IS TO LOCATE A REGION THAT'S
RIPE WITH POTENTIAL FOR CONFLICT
AND APPROACH ONE
OF THE LOCAL PARTIES
WITH AN OFFER
TO HANDLE EVERYTHING
FROM PLANNING AND
TRAINING SOLDIERS
TO BUYING WEAPONS.
IT'S QUITE A BUSINESS,
DON'T YOU THINK?
HEY, DID YOU BRING
A SWIMSUIT?
- HMM?
- I UNDERSTAND,
YOUR EXCELLENCY,
BUT WE'VE ALREADY INVESTED
A LARGE SUM IN THIS.
THERE CAN BE
NO TURNING BACK NOW.
YES, I CAME TO ULGIA
FOR THAT PURPOSE.
AND IF YOU STILL INSIST ON
BREACHING OUR CONTRACT, SIR,
WE WILL BE FORCED TO DISCLOSE
THE NATURE
OF OUR INVESTMENT.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD
HAPPEN THEN.
YES, I SUGGEST THAT YOU DO
RECONSIDER THAT, GENERAL.
GOOD-BYE.
- ( phone clicks )
- IF CANORA LOSES HIS NERVE,
IT'LL THROW OFF OUR SCHEDULE.
- OH, I WON'T LET HIM CANCEL.
WE'VE INVESTED OVER
THREE YEARS ON THIS PROJECT.
THAT'S FAR TOO MUCH
TO BE MADE UP
BY THE RIGHTS TO WORK
A COUPLE OF MINES.
- DO YOU THINK THAT
TANNER AND FOSTER
WERE KILLED BY
THE PRESIDENTIAL FACTION, SIR?
- IT'S POSSIBLE, BUT...
LET'S NOT FORGET
THAT THE ATRIDE CORPORATION
HAS DONE WORK
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
I IMAGINE WE'VE GOT
A LOT OF ENEMIES.
- THAT'S PART OF OUR BUSINESS.
TANNER AND FOSTER
WERE SIMPLY UNLUCKY...
BUT BAD LUCK
IS ALL THAT IT WAS.
THERE ARE ALWAYS
ANNOYING PESTS
IN NOXIOUS HELLHOLES
LIKE THIS
AND WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO SWAT EACH ONE OF THEM,
BUT WE WILL
CRUSH THIS ONE.
- ( sighs )
THREE TARGETS LEFT.
THERE'S THE PRESIDENT HAMMOND
AND HIS AIDES
BURKE AND WELLMAN.
THE SEA'S SO QUIET HERE.
- YES.
- IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
- ( panting )
- ( gunfire )
- ( men grunting )
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( engine whirs )
- ( chatter )
- Woman: EXCUSE ME, MISS.
IS THIS GATE...
- Mireille: IT LOOKS HE'S
WAITING FOR SOMEONE.
- HIS GUARDS
ARE WELL HIDDEN.
- I COUNT FOUR.
- NO, THERE ARE SIX.
- HMM?
- HEY, DAD!
HAVE YOU BEEN
WAITING LONG?
AH!
- ( gasps )
- WHY DID YOU COME HERE
UNINVITED?
I CAME TO ULGIA
ON BUSINESS.
WHATEVER YOU HAD TO SAY
COULD HAVE WAITED
UNTIL I WAS BACK
IN NEW YORK.
- IT REALLY DOESN'T
MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE
WHERE YOU ARE, ANYWAY.
I STILL WON'T
GET TO SEE YOU.
YOU'RE NEVER THERE
WHEN WE NEED YOU!
WHY DO YOU THINK
MOM LEFT?!
- YOU'RE GOING HOME
ON TOMORROW'S FLIGHT.
- CAN'T I AT LEAST STAY
UNTIL THE DAY
AFTER TOMORROW?
- NO!
- ( sighs )
I KNEW IT.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER.
- REMEMBER WHAT?
- THE DAY YOUR
DAUGHTER WAS BORN, DAD.
- HUH?
JUST BE ON
THE FIRST FLIGHT TOMORROW.
- Mireille:
ROSALIE HAMMOND, AGE 15.
THE ONLY DAUGHTER
OF THE DIVORCED HAMMOND COUPLE.
SHE CURRENTLY LIVES
WITH HER MOTHER JULIA
IN NEW YORK CITY.
THAT'S MADE IT
HARD FOR HAMMOND.
IT SEEMS THAT
HE'S BEEN SO OCCUPIED
FANNING DISPUTES
IN OTHER COUNTRIES
THAT HE RARELY
SEES HIS DAUGHTER.
- SCHOOL.
WHEN I CAME TO,
I WAS HERE.
WHO AM I?
I AM... NOIR.
BEYOND THAT,
I KNEW NOTHING.
( cries )
- ( knob jiggles )
- Rosalie: HEY, DAD.
- DID I WAKE YOU?
- NO.
- ROSALIE.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
I'LL GO HOME
ON TODAY'S FLIGHT
LIKE A GOOD GIRL.
DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
I'LL BET MOM'S PRETTY
PISSED OFF AT ME TOO.
- I'VE ALREADY
CALLED YOUR MOTHER.
I TOLD HER
YOU'D COME HOME NEXT WEEK.
- ( door closes )
- HUH?
- ( traffic sounds )
- ( birds twittering )
- ( car horns honking )
- IT MAY TAKE A WHILE
BEFORE WE FIND OUT
WHO DID IT, SIR.
OUR PEOPLE ARE CURRENTLY
GOING THROUGH OUR RECORDS,
RESEARCHING EVERYONE
THE ATRIDE CORPORATION
HAS EVER WORKED WITH
IN THE PAST.
HOWEVER, I ASSURE YOU THAT
BOTH THE ASSASSIN AND HIS CLIENT
WILL PAY FOR WHAT THEY DID.
- HUH?  STOP THE CAR.
- ( knocks on door )
- THE DOOR'S OPEN.
- EXCUSE US.
- ( door closes )
- WELL, WHAT IS IT?
- A STRANGE LETTER.
IT JUST ARRIVED, SIR.
- A STRANGE LETTER?
"NOIR."
- Wellman: WHAT'S IT MEAN, SIR?
- Hammond:
NOIR IS AN ASSASSIN,
ONE OF THE BEST.
- SO THEN IT'S A TIP, SIR?
- OR IT COULD ALSO BE
SOME SORT OF TRAP.
- YES, BUT EVEN SO,
IF IT IS A TRAP,
IT'S STILL AN IMPORTANT
CLUE FOR US.
- HMM.
I THINK IT'S TIME
WE CALLED IN SOME FAVORS.
THERE'S AN ULGIAN MILITARY BASE
NEAR THAT POINT.
CALL CANORA AND HAVE HIM
SEND IN SOME TROOPS.
- Both: YES, SIR.
- ( gasps )
ULGIAN TROOPS.
- WE'RE SURROUNDED.
- HOW DID THEY FIND US?
YEAH, IT MUST BE THEM AGAIN.
OKAY, THEN,
CAN WE HANDLE THIS?
- HMM?
- ( growls )
- Soldiers: HUH?
- SHE DOESN'T HAVE
ANY WEAPONS, CAPTAIN!
- Soldier #1:
THERE'S NO ONE INSIDE, EITHER.
- SO, TELL ME THEN...
WHAT'S A LITTLE GIRL
LIKE YOU
DOING OUT HERE
ALL BY HERSELF?
WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
WHERE'S YOUR PASSP--
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- ( men gasp )
- ( soldier grunts )
- ( soldiers grunt, groan )
( screaming )
- Soldier #2:
RETREAT!  PULL BACK!
- ( gunfire continues )
- ( screaming )
- ( soldiers scream )
- THEY GOT AWAY?!
- FROM WHAT WE CAN TELL,
IT SEEMS THE SCOUTING PARTY
THE ARMY SENT AHEAD
CHARGED IN WITHOUT
WAITING FOR BACKUP, SIR.
- WE STILL DON'T KNOW
ALL THE DETAILS, SIR.
THE ULGIAN TROOPS
ARE IN TOTAL DISARRAY.
AND NOBODY DOWN THERE
KNOWS WHAT'S GOING ON.
- HMM.
I WANT THE TWO OF YOU
TO GET OUT THERE RIGHT NOW.
I'LL BE EXPECTING A FULL REPORT
IN ONE HOUR.
- Both: YES, SIR.
- ( door opens )
- ( door closes )
- ( sighs )
- ( urinating ) DAMN!
HOW DID WE GET STUCK
DOING THE DIRTY WORK
THIS TIME?
- ( zipper zips )
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT'S ALL PART
OF DOING BUSINESS.
WE WOULDN'T HAVE ANY JOBS
IF THERE WEREN'T ANY CLIENTS.
BUT WHY BLAME US WHEN IT'S YOUR
OWN DAMN GOVERNMENT'S FAULT
IN THE END?
- ( faucet squeaks )
- IT'S A LITTLE LATE
TO COMPLAIN NOW.
LET'S DO IT.
- ( engine turns over )
- ( gun cocks )
- ( both gasp )
- ( glass shattering )
- ( women chanting )
- ( knocks on door )
- IT'S OPEN.
- ( electric guitar riff plays )
( electric guitar continues )
- ( music stops )
- ( chanting resumes )
- ( chanting stops )
- OH.
HMM.
- HERE.
- ( giggles )
HUH?
- ( chanting resumes )
- ( techno music playing )
- ( women chanting )