- ( voices chanting )
- Kirika: NOIR...
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
THE PEACE
OF THE NEWLY BORN
THEIR BLACK HANDS PROTECT.
- ( women singing in Latin )
- GO ON, MIREILLE. DO IT.
THANK YOU
FOR PUTTING UP WITH ME.
- ( ragged breathing )
- Man: BALSAN IS DEAD.
MURDERED!
SLAIN IN HIS BED.
BALSAN THE GREAT REVOLUTIONARY
KILLED BY THE ASSASSIN
THAT YOU HIRED!
HOW COULD YOU KILL THE GLORIOUS
LEADER OF OUR CAUSE?
AND WHO DID YOU GET TO DO IT?
- HMMM.
- ( growls )
- ( man grunts, body thuds )
- TALK!
I'LL KEEP KILLING THEM
UNTIL YOU GIVE ME A NAME.
- NOIR.
- ( gasps )
- A NAME ON THE HIGHEST LIST
OF ALL ASSASSINS. THE DEATH
THAT COMES IN THE NIGHT.
BUT THAT IS ALL WE KNOW,
THE NAME AND NOTHING MORE.
- NOIR?
- BUT NOIR IS
THE SERVANT OF GOD.
YOU HAVE DEFILED THIS LAND WITH
BLOOD IN THE NAME OF REVOLUTION
AND BALSAN HAS PAID
THE PRICE!
- ( growls )
- ( grunts, wheezes )
- ( ragged breathing )
( whimpers )
- WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO WALK
ONCE WE PASS THE RIVER.
JUST HOW DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
GOING TO MAKE IT LIKE THAT?
IF WE DON'T CROSS
THE ARAMERA BY 4:00,
OUR CHOPPER IS GOING
TO LEAVE WITHOUT US.
BEING A PRO IS MORE THAN JUST
BRINGING DOWN YOUR TARGET.
MAKING A CLEAN GETAWAY IS
THE MARK OF A PROFESSIONAL.
YOU KNOW THAT AS WELL AS--
( gasps )
- ( chiming )
- ( sighs )
- ( whimpering )
- ARE YOU--
- NO, I'M FINE.
- STILL, ON THE BRIGHTER SIDE,
IF YOU HAD BEEN KILLED, AT LEAST
I WOULD HAVE BEEN FREE OF YOU.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- ( woman singing in bathroom )
- ( silenced gunshots )
- ( singing stops )
- ( gunshots )
- ( moans )
- YES, I'VE HEARD OF THIS NOIR.
- WHEN YOU WERE WORKING
UNDERGROUND IN PAKISTAN, HUH?
- YEAH, THEY SAY HE'S SCARIER
THAN THE GRIM REAPER.
- HMM?
( groans )
THE REAPER?
DEATH HIMSELF.
I SEE.
THEN SO BE IT.
I'LL FIND THIS NOIR
AND PUT HIM THROUGH
THE TORTURES OF HELL!
WE'LL DRAG THIS REAPER
INTO THE DESERT SUN
AND STAKE HIM OUT TO DIE!
- ( panting )
- MIREILLE,
MY I.D. CARD.
- HUH?
- I THINK I LOST MY I.D.
WHEN I GOT SHOT.
- WHAT?
- I KNOW IT WAS STUPID.
BUT I COULDN'T
THROW IT AWAY
EVEN THOUGH I KNEW
IT WASN'T REAL,
THAT IT WASN'T THE REAL ME
OR ANYTHING. I...
- JUST BE QUIET.
- ( grunts )
- THIS ISN'T THE TIME
FOR THAT NOW.
- Kirika: WHEN I CAME TO,
I WAS IN THIS PLACE.
MY NAME AND ALL MY RECORDS,
ARE LIES.
WHO AM I?
WHAT I AM IS NOIR.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
BEYOND THAT.
BUT THIS...
EVEN IF IT IS A LIE,
IT WAS IN MY HANDS.
IT BELONGED TO ME.
- ( water trickling )
- ( thinking ) I MIGHT
STILL BE ABLE TO MAKE IT...
IF I GO ALONE.
- Soldiers: DID ANYONE
SEE ANYTHING?!
- HURRY UP AND OPEN THE DOOR!
SHOW US YOUR I.D.! DO IT!
- PUT YOUR HANDS IN THE AIR.
- OPEN THE TRUNK!
- ( shouting )
- GO ON, MIREILLE.
DO IT.
THANK YOU
FOR PUTTING UP WITH ME.
- ( music-box melody playing )
- ( ragged breathing )
- NOW. HURRY.
( inhales )
- ( silenced gunshot )
- ( melody continues )
- DID YOU REALLY THINK
I'D LET YOU TAKE
THE EASY WAY OUT?
NOT THAT I COULDN'T
CARE LESS ABOUT YOU
OR WHO YOU REALLY ARE,
BUT YOU'RE MY KEY
TO FINDING THE SOLDATS.
SO UNTIL I FIND OUT
WHO THEY ARE,
I'M NOT GOING
TO LET YOU DIE.
BUT ONCE I'VE FOUND THEM OUT...
I WILL KILL YOU.
- I'D FORGOTTEN.
- HEY, LOOK AT THIS!
- DID YOU FIND SOMETHING?
- WHAT IS IT?
- ( phone ringing )
- ( laughs )
- HMM?
( gasps )
- ( men scream, grunt )
- WE'VE GOT HIM!
- IT'S A GIRL.
- IT'S HER, LOOK AT THE WOUND.
- BUT SHE'S JUST A KID!
- HUH?
WHAT'S THIS?
- ( whimpers )
- TAKE HER TO IZUDDIN.
- YES, IT WILL BE DONE, SIR!
- DAMN, SHE'S HEAVY.
- ( engine starts )
- ( grunts )
- GET IN THERE, YOU!
- ( music-box melody playing )
- ( ticking )
- ( ticking echoes )
- ( melody continuing )
- Kirika's voice:
A PILGRIMAGE
TO YOUR PAST AND MINE.
- ( melody stops )
- CAN'T YOU SEE?
THEY'RE NOT SPENDING
THEIR MONEY RIGHT.
- WHAT? WHAT'S WRONG WITH OUR
COMMUNICATION SYSTEM?
- I'LL TELL YOU-- MY GIRLFRIEND,
SHE HAS THIS CELLPHONE.
- A CELLPHONE?
- YES.
AND IT'S REALLY GOOD TOO.
A LOT BETTER THAN HQ'S.
- ( both grunt )
- HMM.
- ( engine starts )
- ( choir singing in Latin )
- IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
TO THE DEPTHS
OF HELL'S FIRE,
THEIR BLACK SOULS
LURE THE LOST CHILDREN.
- ( flames crackling )
- THIS IS THE REAPER?
- OH, SHE IS CONNECTED TO NOIR.
THERE IS NO DOUBT.
- WHAT, THIS LITTLE GIRL?!
- I AM SURE. SHE REEKS
OF THE SCENT OF DEATH.
- ( footsteps )
( gasps )
IT'S HER!
- WHAT IS THAT?
- I FOUND IT
IN THE EAST CORRIDOR.
IT'S YOUR PICTURE I.D.
YUMURA KIRIKA.
I HAD THE TEXT
ON THE CARD TRANSLATED.
SO IS THAT YOUR REAL NAME
OR AN ALIAS?
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU ANSWER?
ARE YOU AN ASSOCIATE OF NOIR?
- YOU ARE BRAVE,
BUT YOU'LL CONFESS.
YOU'LL CONFESS AS YOU ROAST
IN THE FIRES OF HELL ITSELF.
( chuckles )
( stomps )
- ( yelps )
- SO THAT CARD'S
PRECIOUS TO YOU, IS IT?
HUH? YOU FILTHY
BASTARDS KILLED HIM.
OUR GREATEST LEADER--
THE GREAT BALSAN!
( blows striking )
SICK DEMON!
- ( Kirika moaning )
- I'LL MAKE YOU PAY
FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE!
- ( groans )
- ( gunshot )
- ( groans)
- NO, THERE'S NOTHING
UNUSUAL OVER HERE.
- HUH?
- ( sultry ) HI!
- IS SHE DEAD?
- DON'T BE A FOOL.
I WON'T GIVE HER
THE RELEASE OF DEATH
UNTIL THE BURNING SAND
CONSUMES HER.
- AND WHAT ABOUT HER FRIEND?
- THE FRIEND WAS SPOTTED
IN TOWN AT 17:30.
THERE'S A SQUAD ON THE WAY.
- LET ME CHECK.
- ( phone ringing )
- ( groans )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- NO ONE'S ANSWERING.
- EH?
- ( cocks )
- ( growls )
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- COULD IT BE GOVERNMENT TROOPS?
- THERE'S NO WAY!
OUR INFORMANT IN THE ARMY
WOULD HAVE ALERTED US.
- LET'S GET UP THERE.
- NOIR...
NOI...
- HMM?
- ( groans )
- ( hyperventilating )
( yelps )
( grunts )
- ( gunshot )
- ( wheezing )
- A LITTLE SECRET--
THE CODENAME NOIR
REFERS TO MORE THAN ONE.
- NOIR...
- YES, AN ASSASSIN UNIT
MADE OF TWO.
( casing bounces )
- NOIR...
IT IS...
THE NAME OF...
TWO...
- WHAT IS SHE TALKING ABOUT?
- NOIR...
IT IS THE NAME
OF AN ANCIENT FATE--
TWO MAIDENS
WHO GOVERN DEATH.
- WHAT IS SHE SAYING?
A PRAYER?
- THE PEACE OF THE NEWLY BORN
THEIR BLACK HANDS
PROTECT.
- ( whimpering )
- HMPH.
- IN THE END, A LIE IS
ALWAYS A LIE.
I THOUGHT I KNEW THAT
FROM THE BEGINNING, BUT--
( moans )
MIREILLE...
- HUH?
- WHO AM I?
- ( women singing in Latin )
- ( Mireille thinking )
THE THREAD THAT BINDS YOU AND I
IS THE COLOR BLACK.
OF THIS I'M SURE.
BLACKER THAN PITCH,
BLACKER THAN NIGHT,
BLACKER THAN
THE DARKNESS ITSELF.
- ( women singing )
- ( airplane approaching )
- ( woman singing )