Okay, I'm going to activate it.
[breathing shakily]
This is it, guys. We'll show
those cosplaying freaks!
[beeping]
[PEOPLE chattering]
[GARM caws]
[pants, chuckles]
[bicycle approaching]
[NORIKO]
Here we are.
[breathing hard]
[spray paint can
rattles, hisses]
[gasps]
Excuse me, could you please stop
that? Those don't belong to you!
[NOZOMI crashes, groans]
[FUMI] Hey, what're you doing,
you nut job?
--[camera clicks]
--[NOZOMI groans]
[YUKINA] Huh?
Oh, huh! That's weird.
Oh, hey! I know you.
You're Yukina, right?
[YUKINA gasps] Noriko!
[NOZOMI] I don't understand
what that means.
What's "Communal property"?
Any unattended vehicles
are confiscated.
We repaint them to match
the vibe and the scenery
here in town,
and then they become
rental vehicles for sightseeing.
No fair! We only left them
because some people thought
we were thieves
and had us wrongly arrested.
Come on, Mom. I told you
what happened, didn't I?
Please give their bikes back.
They need them more than we do.
If they're gonna run, repainting
them is their best bet.
[BOTH] Huh?
The way they look now,
they stand out
and they'll give em away.
I can fix that.
I think she's got
a pretty valid point there.
I think she just wants
to paint them.
Another bowl, please!
Noriko. I've been
wondering something.
Why do you believe
we're innocent
when no one else seems to?
Mmm. If you ask me, there's
no way you could've stolen
that stone from the captain.
Nobody could.
Anyway.
How do you know this kid?
And why'd you take your sweet
time coming to help us out?
She looked so different
from last time,
I didn't realize it was her.
She's changed a lot.
When we met before,
her hair was longer,
and she wore glasses
and a cute dress.
[YUKINA] Thank you, by the way,
for helping me before.
What happened? You seem a little
gloomier than you did back then.
[YUKINA]
Oh, I do? Really?
[CHIAYA]
Hey, what is that?
[GIRLS] Huh?
[YUKINA]
Oh, I drew that to thank them
for their help
last time I was here.
Who knew we were traveling
with an artist?
So, what's it of?
What do you mean?
It's a portrait.
Of who?
Well, of these guys, obviously.
[nervous chuckling]
[NOZOMI] So, that must be
your dad, then?
[NORIKO] Oh, that guy?
He's a novelist
who was crashing
at our place for a bit.
It's hard to believe, but he'd
been a vigilante squad captain,
and he was the first pilot
of the Tokyo Tower Robot.
[AI and NOZOMI] Wow.
[YUKINA] You know, it does
look like you're related.
[NORIKO] Yeah.
He's not here anymore?
No, he left on a journey.
As the founder of Always Comima,
he was treated as a god,
but really he was
a terrible writer.
I don't know if he ever sold
a single one
of his novels, honestly.
[gasps]
What is it, Mom, what's wrong?
Wait just a minute,
don't tell me that he's the one.
--What do you mean?
--The person who took the stone.
Do you think it could
possibly be him, darling?
--[GIRLS gasp]
--Mr. Akutabi? No way!
I know it sounds crazy,
but think for a second.
The warnings were written
on gridded paper, right?
Remember how he wrote
his manuscripts by hand?
--He was always scribbling.
--[NORIKO] Uhh...
Uh. Yeah, you're right. He was.
Maybe he joined up
with the Bombers.
He could be lashing out because
of how badly his novels did!
Well, honey. I don't know
if I would go that far--
No! It makes perfect sense, Mom!
Anyway, this has nothing
to do with you four.
We know
that you guys are innocent.
You should get outta here
before they catch you!
--Why?
--[NORIKO] Trust me on this.
You don't wanna get caught.
They'll torture you
'til you confess.
[NOZOMI] But, what happens
if we don't confess?
[NORIKO]
Oh, you will.
You don't understand.
Stealing is as serious a crime
as murder, here, anyway.
In consumer-driven
Always Comima,
things are as important--
[scoffs]
no, things are more important
than people's lives.
So you mean, "capital
punishment" is actually...
[whimpers]
[NORIKO]
As decreed by the Knights,
those given capital punishment
are sent into the building
where the festival began.
[TRIO]
And then what happens to you?
Once inside,
you're condemned to servitude.
You work every day:
the men dressed up as butlers
and the women as maids.
--[TRIO whimper]
--[NORIKO] To this day,
no one has ever returned.
Lucky for you,
I'm friends with the girl
at the south checkpoint.
I can have her hide
your departure,
at least 'til morning, anyway.
That should give you time to--
--No! Thank you, but no.
--You're kidding!
What are you saying?
Go if you want,
but I'm gonna stay here.
I don't intend to leave
until the captain believes us.
I can't just let her keep
Chi's stone. It isn't right.
I don't think
that's going to happen.
We should accept
whatever help she'll give us.
Yeah, forget about it.
We'll find a new stone
for Chi-Chi someplace else.
We can't run away like that!
It would be as good
as agreeing that we're guilty.
Like I said,
don't think of it as running.
We're just leaving until
I get stronger, and--
And if you don't get
any stronger? What then?
Why can't you just believe
that I will, huh?
that we'll prove our innocence?
That's so naive!
We can't give up!
I know Masa wouldn't!
'Cause she's strong enough
to fight back!
Determination's more important
than strength!
[whimpers]
Anyway, that's probably how
she got stronger, you know?
[CHIAYA crying]
I didn't...
I didn't steal it.
But even though it's mine,
she won't give it back.
[sighs]
[no discernible dialog]
[MOMIYAMA]
So this is what it was all for?
It must be something
you wanted very badly
to sell those stones, but you
don't look all that happy.
You're wrong. I am happy.
You may not get it,
but I love him.
His story and hairstyle
were pretty strange,
so he wasn't all that popular.
But he kept on working hard,
and he refused to lose heart.
He risked his life
protecting people who needed it,
accepting no reward in return.
That's fascinating.
He sounds like a good guy.
And that's not all, either!
He only ever lied
about something one time,
so his partner
wouldn't take the girl he--
[gasps]
He's a good guy,
but still, he lied.
I'm sorry about this,
I really am, but I can't.
I'm not one
to casually break a deal.
The original agreement
was for one stone, right?
[AKI] Huh?
[panting]
[gasps]
It'll be close quarters,
but you can use this room.
There are
extra blankets in the closet.
Oh, hey, this is the room
I stayed in before.
This is where we're going
to sleep? All four of us?
Why not? We can have
a pillow fight if we want.
A pillow fight?
I've never heard of that.
No, you gotta be kidding!
Pillow fights are
the best part of school trips!
Oh, wow!
This is like a school trip?
Let's calm down. We're guests
at somebody else's house.
Listen, I'm happy
to help you all out.
[CHIAYA]
With the pillow fight, you mean?
Not the pillow fight. I was
talking about with the captain,
about convincing her to let us
keep looking for the lost stone.
Mmm. Mm-hmm.
I'm fine, really.
Everything's going great.
There's no need to be worried.
Yeah. It's not like
I'm by myself.
Huh? Three other girls my age.
Why do you ask?
Dad? No thanks.
I don't see what I need
to talk to him for.
More importantly, I wanna know
how Masa's recovering.
Mmm. Mm-hmm.
What? Aw, jeez!
How could you guys tell her?
--Uh?
--[sprays]
--[chuckles]
--I said no!
--[rattling]
--[BOTH] Huh?
Hey, hey! Where are
you sleeping, Yukippe?
--Oh!
--[laughs]
There! You see how fun it is?
--[laughs, grunts]
--[chuckles]
Pillow Machine Gun!
U-tan, that's no fair!
--[BOTH laughing]
--Yeah. Hey!
--Hmm?
--Uh...
That's something
I still don't understand.
How do you know
our childhood nicknames?
--Huh?
--Yeah, What's with that?
Did you live nearby
or something?
[YUKINA]
I don't think that's it.
[CHIAYA]
I just found out, that's all.
But how?
How did you find out?
Oh, well, I... hmm...
Oh no! No! No, no, no, no!
The captain--
[grunts]
[panting]
I'm sorry, Captain. I brought
them here without permission.
But I believe them!
They're really innocent.
--[AKI] I know they are, Noriko.
--Huh?
--And I apologize.
--[GIRLS] Huh?
I never should have
suspected you of stealing.
[CHIAYA]
You found it?
[YUKINA] Is that what happened?
Did you find your stone?
[AKI] As it turns out,
it was my mistake.
[scoffs] And you think
"sorry's" gonna cut it?
[NOZOMI]
That's fantastic!
And, since you found yours,
you'll give Chi
her stone back, right?
--[AKI] I...
--[gasps]
[AKI]
I can't believe I did this.
That stone was a promise...
to protect the people
of Always Comima.
To safeguard their treasures,
and to ensure their happiness.
I carried that promise
deep in my heart.
It was so important to me.
I can't believe I forgot it.
--[bangs]
--[NOZOMI] Oh!
[YUKINA]
Oh, are you all right, Nozomi?
Did I break it?
Man, I'm so clumsy!
[CHIAYA] The insides
are on the outside now.
--[AKI] That's it!
--[BOTH] Huh?
[beeping]
[KEN]
Hey, maybe we shouldn't do this.
[TATSUHIKO grunts]
What? Why not?
It's just that...
I don't like thinking
about all the people
we're going to scare, ya know?
We're retaliating against them
for wrongs done to us!
This is payback.
Besides, it's not that bad.
[beeps]
[TATSUHIKO] Think about the
suffering they inflicted on us.
Compared to that,
this is nothing!
I just want some revenge.
Is that wrong? Is it really?
[CROWD chattering]
Hey, man, you're thinking
about that girl, aren't you?
What? Who're you talking about?
The chick who thought we were
fellow cosplayers and helped
us out. Akaru, I think.
What if she's there
when the thing goes off?
[scoffs] Well, I think
it would serve her right!
We had to leave
our home because of them.
Look at what
they've done to Tokyo!
--How can we ever forgive them?
--[SUMIRE gasps]
Know what? That costume
looks pretty good on you.
--[grunting]
--Dude, just shut up!
--[AKARU giggles]
--[TATSUHIKO groans]
I won't think about her!
This is for Tokyo!
Hey, guys. You need
to come look at this! Quick!
[MEN]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
An explosion?
[no discernible dialog]
[AKI]
A mobile explosive?
And the perpetrators
are the ones who warned us?
Is it the Dynamite Bombers?
They didn't call
themselves that, no,
but they were
from Higashi Murayama.
The bomb was made
by the evil Takumi.
Apparently, all these guys
ordered was a prank toy,
but the manufacturers
threw in a bomb for free.
What?
There's a bomb in the city?
They said that it looks
exactly like a cleaning robot.
Unfortunately, it doesn't look
like we're gonna be able
to disarm it.
[AKI] I'll find it.
All of you, wait he--
--[grunts]
--[NORIKO] Captain!
[AKI] The armor's too heavy.
Without the Drom Berserker,
I'm just an ordinary
cosplaying girl.
--[YUKINA and NOZOMI] Huh?
--What do you mean "ordinary"?
[AKI]
That's the power of the stone.
It maximizes the potential
of a person's latent abilities.
--Whoa.
--It can do that?
Oh, wow. That's an easy way
to get stronger!
So then...
Is that why you're trying
to collect the stones?
Hmm? I didn't know.
Wait. I know
you lost your stone,
but I thought you found it.
[AKI] I did,
but I don't have it anymore.
Why not?
[AKI] I sold it to an agent
from another country.
--[AI] Huh?
--Momiyama.
Recall all the cleaning robots
to the charging booth.
--[NORIKO] Mom?
--We want the one
that doesn't respond
to central command.
Look for anything out of place.
Hurry, people!
[AKI] I want a search
conducted by area!
Everyone here, come with me
to the charging booth.
[phone ringing]
--[MOMIYAMA sniffles]
--[banging]
Hmm?
Yes, hello, it's Momiyama.
I'm on my way back, ma'am.
[HARUKA]
She's gone! Chiaya is gone!
What?
[CROWD chattering]
--[radio crackles]
--[NORIKO] Oh.
[FUMI on radio]
The bomb has been located.
Port Zero-Two-J. It's heading
in the direction of the Towers!
Three minutes 'til detonation!
[sneezes]
[FUMI]
Two minutes remaining!
[thinks] Come on. Come on!
I need that stone!
--[GARM caws]
--[girls gasp]
--[FUMI] One minute!
--[TRIO gasps]
[GARM caws]
[AKI] Garm!
[AKI grunts]
[yelps]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[RICK humphs] It's okay.
[grunts, shouts]
[TRIO gasp, whimper]
[CROWD gasps]
[AKI] Take them
to HQ for interrogation.
They were probably the ones
behind the bombing
six months ago, too.
It's time to tell the truth.
Go on, dear.
[GIRLS] Huh?
[NORIKO]
Captain.
I'm them.
I'm the Dynamite Bombers.
--[CROWD gasps]
--No way!
[AKI]
I don't understand.
[NORIKO] The explosion
that started all this
was an undetonated shell
from the war.
I was on the investigation team,
and I decided to hide the truth.
Instead, I invented
an anti-Comima organization.
Why would you do
something like that?
[NORIKO] Because... I didn't
want the captain to quit.
I wanted to keep protecting
Comima together forever.
I was so scared
when the captain's stone
really did get lost,
but it was too late.
I'm so sorry.
Well, there you go.
You saved me. Thank you.
--I will not be retiring!
--[gasps]
As for you, Noriko,
I've decided your punishment
is to serve as the captain.
--[gasps]
--There's only one way
to be sure I remember
who I'm doing this for--
to be one of them!
And so from now on,
I'm just a squad member.
[SQUAD MEMBERS] Oh. Yeah!
[NORIKO]
Whoa! Hold on! "Captain"?
Oh! So this baby
makes you stronger, huh?
[CHIAYA grunts]
--Take it.
--[shouts] What?
[NOZOMI]
Really? Are you sure?
[giggles]
Yeah. I am.
[GUARD]
Let's see yer passports, then.
[NOZOMI]
Is that the same guard?
[AI] Hi again!
Don't know what yer sayin'.
I never seen you before.
[YUKINA]
But you look so familiar.
Weren't you
at the north entry gate, too?
Ya do this job long enough
and all the faces look the same.
Hey, kid, put that away!
No picture takin' allowed!
The dadgum dispute
with Shizoka over Mount Fuji
seems to have started up again.
So you be careful, ya hear?
[gasps]
[moans, sighs]
Huh?
--[CHIAYA] Mom? It's me.
--[HARUKA] Chiaya?
It's so good to hear your voice!
You're okay, right?
Where in Tokyo are you?
[CHIAYA] It sounds like
you were worried about me.
[HARUKA] Of course I was!
Stay right there.
I'll send Momiyama
to get you immediately.
Just tell me where you are.
If you're not sure, you can
give me a landmark or something.
Mom, you know what?
Don't do that.
I've made some friends
since I've been away.
I'm with them,
so I'll see you later, okay?
--[stammers]
--[CHIAYA] Don't worry about me.
Hold on just a minute,
young lady--
--[CHIAYA] Hey, Mom?
--Yeah?
[CHIAYA] Those stones.
Why are you collecting them?
Do you love them more than me?
[gasps]
How can you think that?
I'll explain everything!
Please, just come back!
--Chiaya? Chia--
--Don't worry, okay? I'm fine.
--[receiver clicks]
--[grunts, gasps]
[sighs]
[breathes deeply]
Yeah. Everything is fine.
[AI whistling]
[NOZOMI] My plan
is to keep visiting
the countries
that hired Maccha Green.
What do you think you'll do?
[YUKINA]
Well, I thought I'd stay
with you for a while longer.
[NOZOMI]
Sure, that sounds great.
I wonder
if I'm reading these right.
Huh? What do you mean?
What they're offering in return
for Maccha Green's services.
They all seem to call it
by different names,
but I think they might be
talking about those stones.
Oh, yeah? You really think so?
If you're right,
we just need to keep working.
Peacebroker jobs can help us
with Chi's request, too.
Hey. Tell you what.
I'll help you with this
substitute peacebroker stuff.
If I do that,
will you give me a stone?
Sure, why not?
What about you, Nozomi?
Don't you want one, too?
Hmm. No.
It doesn't seem right for me.
Oh, I meant to ask you.
That song you were
whistling earlier.
--It was Momi-Ham, right?
--Dude!. Yeah, it was!
You know their stuff?
They've been around a long time.
I love their music! My mom and
dad got me listening to them.
Oh, really? My uncle
got me into those guys!
"Empty Field" and that song
you where whistling,
"Stones,"
are two of my favorites.
And "Song of the Beginning"
is really good, too!
Yeah! [giggles]
[gasps] Uh...
Oh, sorry.
We're going on and on.
Do you know Momi-Ham?
[AI] Short for
Momiage Hammers.
Yes, actually.
I really like "Stones," too.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh no way!
Chi-Chi, is that Momi-Ham
you're rockin' up there?
What? What about them?
[NOZOMI]
It so is!
[YUKINA] It's the rare
collector's version
with the phantom members!
[humphs]