[GIRLS sigh]
[NOZOMI]
I needed this!
[AI]
I've never been happier
about getting lost.
[CHIAYA]
Pretty.
[YUKINA]
Talk about taking
the scenic route!
Try to watch the map, okay, Ai?
We don't want this
to happen all the time.
All right.
[NOZOMI]
And Yukina,
try not to get separated.
It's hard to find you
when you wander off.
Okay.
I mean, we should be
in Kyoto by now.
[sighs]
You have to admit, though,
this isn't so bad,
and it's not like we're
in a hurry or anything, right?
We are in a hurry, though.
There's a client out there
who's waiting for us!
See, that's where you're wrong.
Last I checked, they were
waiting for Maccha Green.
Well, it's not like we're
totally useless as peacebrokers.
I mean, Nagoya went well,
didn't it?
Yeah. Kinda, I guess.
Yukina made that
weird shachihoko.
That seemed to help
move things along a little bit.
You thought my
shachihoko was weird?
[AI]
Anyway,
I'd like to know
why you gave back
the stone
we worked so hard for.
[NOZOMI]
Mmm.
I just wouldn't have
felt right keeping it.
It seemed like it was something
really important to her.
[AI]
Yeah, of course it's important!
They turn Rests
into Bests, don't they?
If you keep bein'
all soft like that,
you aren't gonna
gather very many.
[NOZOMI]
I thought maybe
that would be okay, though.
The President of Tokorozawa
doesn't know that we're
subbing in for Masa,
so it's not like
she'll be expecting
anything from us, will she?
Ugh! Wait, what about me?
I'm only here 'cause
I want one of those stones.
[NOZOMI]
Oh. I didn't realize that.
[AI]
I told you!
First, we get all the stones
Chi-Chi wants,
and then when we're
done with that,
I'm supposed to get
one of the leftovers.
[NOZOMI]
Oh.
[YUKINA]
Gathering stones for Chiaya
was what started this, remember?
Oh! Of course! I know that!
[NOZOMI laughs]
As if I would forget! Please!
I don't need them anymore.
[AI AND YUKINA]
Huh?
Really.
I don't need the stones.
Uh.
You don't need them anymore?
When did that happen?
Deer sure seem to like her.
Don't they?
I want to help.
That's why I'm here.
It's not for the stones.
[ALL]
Huh?
That's what friends do, right?
They help each other out.
[NOZOMI]
That's right, Chi.
In that case, the next time
we find a stone,
you should use it, Nozomi.
[NOZOMI]
Huh?
'Cause it'll make you a Best,
and then it'll be easier
for you to take Maccha's place.
Uh, well, right,
but it's just, that's
not really what I'm after.
Let's get going, okay?
[NOZOMI and AI humming]
♪ When the world
kicks you around ♪
♪ Throws you to the ground ♪
♪ You may feel like giving up ♪
♪ Then it's you that suffers ♪
[YUKINA] Ah!
♪ So keep rolling and laugh ♪
[NOZOMI]
Ai's so obsessed
with the Moonlight Stones.
If only one fell
out of the sky for her,
that would be perfect,
wouldn't it?
Mmm.
[CHIAYA]
Nonsuke?
[NOZOMI]
Hmm?
[CHIAYA]
U-tan,
when she finds
a stone that she can keep,
will she go away from us?
[NOZOMI]
Yeah, probably.
She's determined
to become a Best
one way or another
for some reason,
even though it looks painful
and seems like a lot of work.
[AI]
Those other two
don't want the stones.
What about you?
No, not to keep or anything.
I am a little curious
about them, though.
If not for the stones,
why are you traveling
with Nozomi?
Oh! Um.
I guess I just--
I'm hoping to get
more experience,
so I can make
my dream come true.
[AI snoring]
Huh?
Ugh.
I'm going to bed.
Cool if I turn out the light?
Oh, sure.
[CHIAYA]
Oh, wow.
She's asleep already?
[NARRATOR]
The holy land of rock, Kyoto.
Inheriting a long
musical tradition,
this city has gone
beyond the times
and fused with the beat.
These days,
young people flock to Kyoto,
singing their very souls out
into the music-filled air.
Two vigilante squads are
in charge of keeping order,
their responsibilities
neatly divided.
The live concerts held
at the famous old temples
are operated and policed by
the Kamogawa Rockers.
Meanwhile, the squad
Maikos, We Are
keeps the peace
in the old capital
and its surrounding areas.
The two groups
are very different
and operate
completely separately.
[MAN]
Cor!
So Maccha Green
is finally here!
No, sorry. I'm not Maccha.
[MAN]
Ah, then it's you.
No way. Don't look at me.
[MAN]
Then...
No, sir.
It's not me, either.
[MAN]
Blimey, don't tell me it's--
No. I'm not her.
Well, come on then!
Who is she?
[GIRL]
She's with one of those
fighting squadrons, right?
She looks normal,
but she's wicked strong.
Ah, so you're in disguise, like.
Why'ncha you say
something sooner?
[NOZOMI]
Well, no. That's not it, either.
Let me explain. You see...
[MAN]
Hmm?
[NOZOMI]
We're here for
the Kiyomizu Temple
Rock Expl-- ugh!
Who named that?
[MAN]
The Kiyomizu Temple
Rock Explosion, isn't it?
The most rockin' rock festival
ever, I reckon!
Anyway, we came to make sure
no one stops the festival.
We're filling in
for Maccha Green.
[door opens]
All right, mates, let's go!
[MAN]
Right! In a minute, Captain.
There are some birds here
from Tokorozawa
who say they're here
to help out.
Yeah, help as what?
Support staff for the festival?
Naw, naw! This kinda help!
Oh, wow! I can't believe
four of you came. That's great!
About that, we're actually
more like substitutes.
People will totally let their
guard down around you. Perfect!
Anyway, we can
talk details later.
Why don't you come
listen to the concert first?
Oi, Shido.
Let 'em ride with you.
Right!
[CAPTAIN]
Excellent!
[NOZOMI gasps]
So much like Masa!
[crowd cheering]
I'd like to thank everyone
for coming!
This is the kind of enthusiasm
I want to see for this year's
Rock Explosion, too, okay?
[ALL THREE]
Yay!
All right, let's wrap this
show up with one last song...
by the legendary rock band
Momi-Ham.
You guys know what song
I'm talking about, right?
[CAPTAIN]
"Stones"!
No way!
She's covering Momi-Ham!
And she picked
the perfect song, too!
[CAPTAIN]
Momiage?
[ALL]
Hammers!
[cheering]
[CHIAYA giggles]
Ah!
[gasps]
[MAN 1]
It's Shuten!
[MAN 2]
And he's brought his gang!
[ALL screaming]
[BOTH chuckling]
And why would
the infamous Doji Shuten
grace us with his presence?
I don't remember this being
a battle of the bands.
I came here for you,
Misa Ichijo.
Really, now!
A fan of my music, are you?
I had no idea!
[chuckles]
[screaming]
Why would you carry around
something so unlucky?
It can be hazardous
to your health.
You should put it
in a jinxed stones box.
Thanks, but I don't need you
looking out for me!
[screaming]
Beam the lights, Professor!
Right.
--[MEN laughing]
--[MISA screams]
Sweet song princess,
carried off by a ruffian!
Oooh, that's so exciting!
Huh? Oi!
What's with the box?
[PROFESSOR]
Okay, and off you go.
What? What do you mean?
Go where?
No! Wait! Put me down!
[cries]
I like to arrive empty-handed
and leave the same way.
Captain, no!
[ALL gasping]
[SHIDO]
That was Shuten's gang.
The gits.
They live up on Mount Oe
and cause all kinds of Barney.
We didn't mind them
running a little mad
during the meat-and-potato-stew
fight with Hiroshima,
but before we knew it,
they made some sort of deal.
Now they run wild
in the city, too.
We thought they might
try to target the festival
for some of their
madness this year,
so we've stayed good and ready.
Kidnapping the captain, though.
I didn't see that one coming.
The captain is the only
Best we've got,
so we're really
counting on you, okay?
Please get her back for us!
[GROUP]
Please! You gotta!
Oh, well, you see,
the thing is...
--[YUKINA] It's just, um...
--[AI] We're not really, uh...
Hey, what is that?
Huh?
[SHIDO]
That's it!
Come out right now,
Doji Shuten!
We're tired of dealing
with your rubbish!
Yeah, and we've got
four Bests here with us,
so things could get right ugly!
Now give us our captain back!
You think we're joking?
Just try us!
--[door opening]
--[gasping]
[GIRLS whimpering]
Right! Tokorozawa squadron,
you're up!
So, what do we do now?
[AI]
Maybe we're
not being clear enough.
[NOZOMI]
Mmm.
Uh, you give their captain back
right now!
[YUKINA and AI gasp]
--[SHUTEN] No problem.
--[GIRLS gasp]
All you lot have gotta do
is help me kill some time.
What do you say?
[gasps]
[AI]
I want that stone!
I'm going in!
Cover me, 'kay?
[ALL]
Huh?
I want you guys to flank 'em!
[YUKINA AND NOZOMI gasp]
While you do that,
I'm going after the stone!
How're we supposed to
flank them?
[AI]
Here I go!
Ha!
Well, looks like
one of 'em's down,
Maybe if I ask nicely?
Ah!
--[ALL] Huh?
--[YUKINA] Are you okay?
Here, let me help y--
Uh, they're not really
doing very well, are they?
There's one left standing!
[sighs]
[BOTH]
Bests, are they? No bloody way!
--[SHUTEN yawns]
--[laughing]
Over already, is it?
I'm off, then.
[GIRL]
Stop at once.
[ALL gasping]
Enough, Shuten.
You will return the Rockers'
captain to them immediately.
Oi! The Maikos are here!
I thought you might come.
And if I refuse, what then?
Then I shall have to
resort to force.
[ALL screaming]
This is not at all
what I had been led to expect.
I was under the impression
that you did things differently.
Fancy seeing you here.
You and the captain
aren't exactly mates,
and yet you came to her rescue.
I fail to see what that
has to do with anything.
There's no need to
work yourself into a tizzy, luv.
[MISA]
Hey, you wankers!
You get this
bloody thing off of me!
[ALL]
Captain Misa!
Hey, she's okay!
Let's have some fun, shall we?
Life is all about
finding ways to kill time.
[JOHNNY]
That's Maikos, We Are.
They're a veteran
vigilante squad
that protected all of Kyoto
during the war between states.
Each and every member
of the squad is a maiko,
from apprentice birds to ones
just about to become geisha.
Their current captain,
the one you saw,
is the 19th Mamechiyo.
[SHIDO]
But what I can't brain
is why they're helping us.
[SHEENA]
They usually pretend
we don't exist.
[NOZOMI]
What do you mean? Why's that?
[JOHNNY]
Well, we're not exactly
the best of mates, are we?
[SHEENA]
That's right.
Neither captain
can stand the other.
Our captain
flat out ignores theirs,
and Mamechiyo has
her own style of harassment.
Couldn't tell ya
what happened with those two,
but they've got a past,
that's for sure.
[ALL]
Huh.
[car horn beeps]
Yo! What are you Rockers up to?
[ALL]
Hello, sir!
[GIRLS]
Huh?
Come here, Sheena, my pet.
How I've missed you!
Oi, easy, old man!
Hands off, all right?
Oi, ladies. So, Johnny,
where's Misa?
[JOHNNY]
Well, uh...
[MAN]
By Doji Shuten, huh?
[JOHNNY]
Yeah.
[SHIDO]
We were just about to stage
another rescue attempt.
Maybe I'm crazy, but,
is that Han-chan and Ma-bo
from Momiage Hammers?
[NOZOMI]
Huh?
Just look.
Check out the sideburns.
The faces do look similar.
[SHIDO]
Whatcha starin' at?
I'll bet I can guess.
Momi-Ham fans?
[HAN-CHAN and MA-BO]
Hmm.
[JOHNNY]
Han-chan and Ma-bo
started a record label
here in Kyoto.
Come back here
every year, they do,
to help out with
festival operations
and promotional-type things.
Ah!
[NOZOMI]
Thank you! This is amazing!
So, um, what about
your lead singer?
Is Momizo doing well?
--[groaning]
--[NOZOMI gasps]
Shut it.
We don't talk about that.
Uh...
Bloody stupid chit, are you?
Don't you know why
Momi-Ham broke up?
I heard they had hammer
differences. Serious stuff.
Because Momizo was the only one
who shaped his sideburns
into pickaxes, right?
They're still a touch sensitive
about the whole thing, right?
So I'd shut your gobs
if I were you.
So, what're you
going to do about it?
[ALL]
Huh?
You could launch an attack
on Mount Oe right now,
but you wouldn't have time
to prep for the festival.
And besides that, you still need
to replace the band members
who landed themselves
in those hospital beds.
If the Maikos are already
taking care of it, well,
why not just leave it to them?
Because then we'd owe them.
And stuff that, yeah?
Don't worry!
We'll figure out something,
I know we will!
You can concentrate on
preparations for the festival.
Whatcha mean by "something"?
That's not too specific.
Well, you know...
[SHEENA]
Haven't even got a plan?
Oh, hey! The stone!
Give it to us now!
Uh--
[AI]
It'll just be like you're
paying us in advance.
That's no problem, right?
[MOMIYAMA]
It took awhile,
but I caught up to them.
It appears that
Chiaya passed through
the checkpoint yesterday.
I got a look at her
customs clearance history.
For now it looks like
she's still travelling
with those other three girls.
[HARUKA]
The ones who like to say they're
filling in for Maccha Green,
even though they don't seem
to accomplish anything?
If that's the case,
then they should be with
the Kamogawa Rockers in Kyoto.
Bring her back.
[MOMIYAMA]
Yes, ma'am.
One more thing.
If you're in Kyoto, anyway...
[MOMIYAMA]
Do you want yatsuhashi?
[HARUKA]
Mmm.
[MOMIYAMA]
I'll also touch base
with our operatives in the field
to see if I can figure out
why we have
no Cores in our possession.
We should have accumulated
some of them by now.
[HARUKA]
Be quick about it.
Why won't she come back?
[CHIAYA]
I've made some friends
since I've been away.
[WOMAN]
I'm afraid I can't accept
what happened last night.
We involved ourselves
in a confrontation
at a concert hall,
an area outside our purview.
I can see your point,
but kidnapping is
rather a serious crime.
Not truly serious.
T'isn't as if
Doji Shuten is a murderer.
The only thing he
ever wishes to kill is time.
Anyhow, you're
forgetting the issue.
It's absurd that Kyoto is
the "holy land" of rock!
I don't know, I rather fancy
rock and roll, myself.
Ugh!
Right. I take it back.
And what about you,
Captain Mamechiyo?
Do you hate rock, as well?
Uh...
Well, yes!
Of course I hate it!
Care to fill me in
on what you're planning?
Everybody knows Doji Shuten
enjoys a good fight now n' then.
You never did
strike me as the sort
who would want to do
any real harm before, though,
or was I wrong?
What's your game?
You're right, luv. I do enjoy
watching a good fight,
and a match between the captains
of the Maikos and the Rockers
is a good way to kill time.
[MISA]
Well, I can't say
I share your opinion on that.
[SHUTEN]
I was wondering
what she would be like.
And I can't say
that I'm disappointed.
Huh?
Just talking to myself.
You came all this way.
Won't you sing a song for us?
Huh?
Okay, so we just ask them
to give it to us
instead of dropping it in.
What, are you talking about
the jinxed stones?
Maybe. What are those?
[SHIDO]
There aren't any about now,
but nights after a good concert,
they rain right down.
There are even boxes
set up around town
for people to put them in,
matter of fact.
What a waste! Why's that?
[SHEENA]
They might be pretty to look at,
but those stones have been
considered unlucky
in Kyoto for a long time.
Not many people besides
the captain hang onto them.
All right! Let's get one!
What would you want
with one of those, anyway?
[yelling]
[SHIDO]
Oi, wait!
He said a whole bunch of them
come down after a good concert.
I wonder why.
Besides that,
I'd really like to know
what exactly the stones are.
[ALL]
Hmm.
[YUKINA]
So, let's say that
the stones enhance
neuron synapses.
Noticing the activation
of sympathetic nerves,
the basal ganglia
cancels signals
inhibiting body functions
sent to the muscles.
This allows people to exhibit
more than 100 percent
of their potential.
Additionally, to prevent
substantial damage
to bones and muscles,
the stones may also put
a coating on the cells.
Ugh.
I have no clue
what you're talking about,
but how would that help anyone
make super cool shachihoko?
Uh--
[YUKINA]
Uh, well,
I'm not sure
how to explain that.
We need to keep
an eye on that box.
Hey! There are
stones coming down!
Really? I don't see them.
Oh, um...
What about over that way?
Oh, hey, we've got a live one!
[ALL gasp]
Wait, sir! Please come back!
[whimpering]
[AI]
Nozomi!
Get him!
[HAN-CHAN]
So, Johnny,
you wanted to be
a guitarist, right?
[JOHNNY]
Too right!
But I can't play an F chord.
[MA-BO]
And Marukome,
you wanted to be a drummer?
Love to.
Except I haven't got any rhythm.
[SHIDO]
I know, maybe the captain
can play bass while she sings.
[SHEENA]
Not a bad idea, that!
Momi-Ham style!
[SHIDO]
Are we sure
those girls will be okay?
[SHEENA]
Now that I think about it,
you know who's managing
the jinxed stones?
Wait, this place is...
[AI]
It's the Shuten gang's hideout!
Uh. Hey, do you hear that?
[CHIAYA]
It sounds like music.
[SHUTEN GANG cheering]
[cheering]
Mmm.
[SHUTEN]
Well, captain,
looks like your ride's here.
Go home, then.
What? Why bring me here?
Did you just want
to hear me sing?
Don't worry, I'll see you again
at the Rock Explosion.
I'll be the one
stirring things up.
[SHUTEN]
I hear that you have
some interesting things planned.
Oh?
[SHUTEN]
Involving the captain
of the Kamogawa Rockers.
Indeed. You know about that?
[SHUTEN]
There's been speculation
for a long time now
that Maikos, We Are
hate the Kamogawa Rockers,
but for your part,
I think it's personal.
Are you harboring
a private grudge or something?
The captain...
is not a nice person.
If you'd like,
I can get involved.
[MAMECHIYO]
Huh?
However, you should know
I don't hold back
when it comes to killing time.
[SHUTEN]
Is that all right?
That sounds acceptable, yes.
[SHUTEN]
Well, evil Takumis,
is your work here complete?
You took care of the other
Takumis without anyone noticing?
[chuckles]
I'll give you this much.
You blokes don't mess around.
I wager even Buddha
would be surprised
that those are
missiles up there.
I think this should prove
a satisfactory cure for boredom,
don't you?