[NARRATOR]
It's tough to tell
who will win a race this close!
The businessman
from Nakamura District 4
takes the lead!
No, the high schooler Satomi
has overtaken him!
Holy smokes!
Did anyone else see that?
It's the mysterious, unnamed
taxi driver!
The first ever to get
a license
for passenger transport
on two wheels,
and the official circuit best!
[WOMAN]
Excuse me,
I'm not in that much
of a hurry.
[MAN] Doesn't matter,
I can't drive slowly.
[AI] How could you forget
to fill up?
That's pretty important,
you know.
[NOZOMI]
It's not usually my job.
My dad or Masa
takes care of it.
Same for me.
It's my brother's motorcycle,
so I'm not used to it.
You sure you should be driving?
I mean, if you can't even
remember to get gas.
With no license, you get no say
so shut it.
What about you, Chi-Chi?
Yours borrowed too?
Oh, yeah. This belongs
to Momiyama.
Who's Momiyama?
[humming]
Birds really
have a thing for her.
What's that about?
She's so lucky.
Scooters are easier to push.
[sigh]
[AI]
We've got a long way to go.
Well, thanks for the ride.
What do I owe you?
--There's no charge.
--Oh, yeah, why's that?
--Because I'm adorable?
--No.
Mmmh!
It's part of my
friendship project.
Wow, you're with Mie Motors?
That's surprising.
Anyway, I gotta go.
[coughs]
That was fast.
Well, look who's home.
Hi, Daddy.
How've you been?
I'm really sorry
I haven't called in a while.
I meant to.
There, ya see? Didn't I tell you
it was Hime?
Finally decided
to come back home, huh?
I can't believe
how much you've grown!
You've been taking
good care of yourself?
Oh. Long time no see, everyone!
[ICHIZO] Isn't it great
to have her back, Mamoru?
[OTHERS agreeing]
Yeah.
--About time she came home.
--So, Daddy...
if you have a minute.
There's something here
I kind of wanted to show you.
Come on, Mamoru, aren't you
at least gonna say hi to her?
Your only daughter's
finally come home,
and you're just gonna
sit there?
How long?
Three or four years?
At least turn around.
She's turned into a real beauty
since she's been gone.
[HIMEKO]
Now you're just
making things up!
Oh, come on, you stupid,
stubborn old man!
Too proud to turn around,
what kind of father are you?
Well, this isn't
gonna be easy, is it?
Tell you what, Hime,
you can come by my house
for some tea
till he cools off.
Oh, no, come to my house,
it'll be a lot more relaxing.
My place is closer.
She can have tea and sleep over.
--[sighing]
--[KANTARO] Don't be an idiot.
we can't let a young woman
like that spend the night...
Anyway, like I was saying,
I wanted to show you--
[KOKICHI] Why not?
Mamoru's a widower, too!
[HATSUE] Mamoru is her dad,
you foolish man!
[KOKICHI] Well, I'm basically
like her uncle,
--so it's no big deal.
--[MAMORU growling]
Right? Right.
Shut up!
[HIMEKO]
Oh, no! Daddy!
[camera beeps and clicks]
[ALL sighing]
[humming]
[CAT]
Meow.
The cat says to look out.
[ALL THREE]
Huh?
[screams]
[NOZOMI]
Jeez! What is that thing?
[CHIAYA]
A dorsal fin?
[YUKINA]
It's a shachihoko.
At least, I think.
[AI]
More to the point,
why is it falling
from the sky?
[HIMEKO]
That was lucky.
I'm glad you weren't hurt
too badly.
--What about the others?
--A few scratches is all.
It could've been a lot worse.
Right now, they're doing
what they can
to put the workshop
back in order for you.
Oh! The kiln wasn't damaged.
Although... the shachihoko
around town were all broken.
The one on the castle, too.
I wonder if it was the people
from Mie who did it.
[MAMORU]
Who knows?
Well... wasn't there something
you wanted to show me?
Huh? Oh, uh...
no. It's fine.
I know! Why don't I get
some coffee?
How's the owner of Machountain
doing these days?
I haven't seen him in a while,
so I think I'll-- Hey! Stop!
--What are you doing?
--What do you think?
I'm going home.
Wha? But the doctor said
you should stay the night!
No time.
I have a deadline to meet.
--A deadline? For what?
--For a shachihoko, of course.
And it sounds like
the golden one on the castle
will need to be remade, too.
Right. Of course.
Seeing them for the first time
in a while,
I remember just how amazing
your shachihoko are.
--Himako.
--Yes, Daddy?
Nothing.
Forget about it.
All right, then,
here ya go.
There's a ton of folks around
for the Tenmusu Grand Prix
this weekend,
so be careful, ya hear?
--Whatcha lookin' at?
--Oh, uh, nothing, sorry.
There was also a big hullabaloo
earlier with all the shachihoko
in town bein' blown
to smithereens.
The residents of old Aichi
have their britches in a twist.
That explains the falling fish.
Seriously? Bombs again?
Steer clear
of their vigilante squads' HQs!
That's the Aichi Tenmusus
and the Mie Motors, okay?
[camera clicks]
[ALL]
Huhhhh...
Welcome! Come on in!
Interesting rule
you guys have.
[YUKINA]
Get hit by a restaurant's food,
and you have to eat there?
Competition for customers
is fierce around here.
[AI]
Worked out this time,
since we were already hungry.
Do you think
I could get another tenmusu?
And I'll take some miso cutlets.
--A red bean toast for me.
--Takoyaki, thank you!
Hey, that's my parfait!
Oh... sorry.
Yeah? Well, sorry
isn't good enough!
Jeez, take it easy.
I mean, it was sticking out
--onto our side of the tab--
--In that case...
What are you doing?
That's my spaghetti!
Oh, sorry.
Ugh!
So what brings you here,
the Tenmusu Grand Prix?
Oh, actually...
maybe you can help us.
We're looking for somebody
called Himeko Uotora?
Hey, Himeko, these girls
are here for you.
I don't know anything
about this. I'm sorry.
Huh. That's weird.
Uh... hey. Could you tell me,
have you been to Tokorozowa
--before?
--Huh?
Chest! Strike!
You okay, Nozomi?
Hey, Masa! Let me see
your Moonlight Stone, 'kay?
[NOZOMI]
S'cuse me! Could I?
Here, let me take a look
at that.
Huh?
Here you go! Did that happen
to fall from the sky?
Yeah! Pretty, huh?
I call it the Moonlight Stone.
The Moonlight Stone, is it?
Cute name.
Check out this!
--Whoa...
--Mine has a name, too,
it's Star of the Circuit.
I do my best work
when I have this stone with me.
Ohh! The little girl!
You sure have grown up, huh?
Anyway, it was really
nice of you
to do that for me.
My friend Masa really liked it.
That's all that matters, then.
No, sorry.
I didn't write this.
I've been traveling all over
for a while now,
so I don't even know
who this Maccha Green person is.
Oh! Masa, um, the friend
I mentioned before.
Hey, the stone you offer
as payment.
Is it that "Circuit Star"
thing you were talking about?
Like I told you,
I didn't write the letter.
I don't know what that's
all about.
I can't give it away.
It's not mine.
[gasps]
--Huh?
--I'm sorry,
but I've got bigger problems
to deal with right now.
Maybe you should lay off.
You look like
you're gonna throw up.
Stress eating, huh?
Not healthy.
Well, it's how I cope,
so there ya go.
Hmm.
[door knocked open]
[MASCOTS]
Dandy, sir! Incoming!
[screams]
[engine revving]
What are you talking about?
[DANDY]
A plot? That's ridiculous.
[engine revving]
[tire squealing]
So, it's a duel you want?
You don't have to do that!
Are you crazy?
Yeah, you are.
Let us help you!
We're here as peace brokers.
We came from Tokorozawa
in Maccha Green's place.
The people of Mie and Aichi
don't have to fight.
It's best if you stay back.
You could get hurt.
[tire squealing]
[screams]
I can't accept your challenge,
vice-captain. It is invalid.
[engine revs]
The Twin Tower Declaration
specifies
that vigilante squad captains
can settle disputes
with a fair fight.
But the duel you propose
doesn't meet those conditions.
As I see it,
there are two problems.
First of all,
you are not the captain
of the Mie Motors.
Secondly,
you taunted a peacemaker,
which shows a lack of fairness.
I cannot possibly
engage in a duel
with somebody like you.
--He's so dandy.
--He really is, isn't he?
[engine revving]
[tires squealing]
Those punks!
They think they're so cool.
Haven't we put up with them
long enough?
Let's just give 'em
the fight they want.
I'm sure they're the ones
who blew up the shachihoko.
Without proof,
we can't be certain.
I don't need proof!
How can you still be so dandy
at a time like this?
Do you really think
we'll all be better off
if one of the regions
takes over the other?
Do you truly believe that?
I heard that the captain
of the Mie Motors
wants a reconciliation.
He's trying
to convince his squad
and the residents of Mie
that peace is best.
And we're just
supposed to wait?
We should
settle it with a race!
--I'll represent us!
--No, I'll do it!
--I'm the obvious choice!
--What about me?
[SQUAD MEMBERS]
Come on, captain!
We can do this, captain!
You've gotta let us
do something!
--I can bring it home for us!
--Are you kidding me?
--Come on!
--We have to do something!
Seems like everyone here races,
what about you?
What? No,
I'm not into racing. Why?
I don't know. Your stone's name
is Star of the Circuit.
Oh... that's something else.
[NOZOMI]
Well, we're heading back
to Dandy's cafe.
There's still a lot of work
to be done there.
[HIMEKO]
You guys are gonna help out?
--That's cool.
--We didn't have
anywhere to stay,
so he's letting us crash
in a spare room.
We figured helping him out
was the least we could do.
[KOKICHI]
Hey! Are you friends of Hime's?
Why don't you
come in for a bit?
[HATSUE] It would help
if we could at least
decide on the country's name.
[NOZOMI]
But how can a country
not have a name?
Nobody could agree on one.
It's "Aichi-Mie"
or "Mie-Aichi,"
but who gets top billing?
If there's one thing
we have to stand firm on,
it's the name.
That's right, Yasuo.
They want us to feel guilty
for not compromising,
but we've given enough ground.
We can't let them do
whatever they want
with the name, right?
Compromise, how?
[ICHIZO]
Well, you see, we were fighting
over the roots of tenmusu
and miso cutlets
That's why we decided to merge.
Better that than fighting.
Actually, both dishes
have their origins in Mie,
so Aichi compromised
on a few things.
Like letting public roads
be a race circuit, for one.
They may've come up
with those dishes,
but we were the ones
who put the spin on 'em
that made them popular!
Invented in Mie, but then
perfected right here in Aichi!
Exactly what I've always said!
That's what those Mie folk
--don't understand!
--Right you are, Ichizo!
Right you are!
Well... maybe.
But that's the sort of thing
Dandy and the vigilante squad
can handle.
In my opinion,
fixing the shachihoko
is more important
than laying blame.
[ICHIZO]
We'll show 'em there's no use
breakin' them
in the first place!
The castle's golden shachi
comes first, right, Mamoru?
Uh, Mamoru?
I don't know
if that's going to happen.
[OTHERS]
Huh?
What are you talkin' about?
[MAMORU]
My arm. Looks like
it's out of commission.
[gasping]
That can't be true!
I've actually been having
a strange numbness in it
for a while.
I've made do with it
for as long as I could.
But it looks like
the feeling's gone from it
entirely now. I can't do
much of anything with it.
But Daddy, all the shachihoko
in town have been broken!
I know, and I don't think
I can fix them.
Here, let me take a look at it.
Maybe you slept on it funny,
I do that sometimes.
If he can't do it,
you'll have to.
--What?
--He's right about that, dear.
You're the only one who can.
[YASUO]
Uotora carpenters
have been making
the Nagoya Castle shachihoko
--for generations.
--Hey, now,
--let's slow down a sec.
--What've you been doing
these last five years
if not training?
--You can handle this!
--I don't think you understand.
I ran away from home
because I started
to hate shachihoko.
I was playing around,
not training.
I got bored
and came home, that's all.
No one else
thinks shachihoko are weird?
A tiger and a carp? Not cute!
You can see
where I'm coming from,
can't you? Mmhh...
We'll go back
to the doctor tomorrow.
[OTHERS]
Mmmnnnhh...
It's a family thing.
We should probably just lea--
Excuse me! If there's anything
we can do to help,
we'd be more than happy to.
We received this note.
It has Himeko's name on it.
[KANTARO]
"Please help bring peace
to Mie-Aichi.
We need your strength."
[KOCHIKI]
Shouldn't it be "Aichi-Mie"?
[HATSUE]
You sure Hime sent this?
Well... she actually
didn't know anything about it.
--No, but I might...
--[OTHERS] Huh?
[KANTARO]
Did you send it, Mamoru?
Of course not. Young lady,
are you the Maccha person
--from Tokorozawa?
--No, I'm not.
But I came in her place.
My name's Nozomi Moritomo.
And I'm Yukina Kosaka.
I see. At any rate,
if it's answers you want,
you should look for a guy
riding around town
on a bike taxi.
There's only one,
so it shouldn't be too hard.
How does a bike taxi work?
Yeah, who would
even have one of those?
Tomoki Suzuka.
He's the captain
of the Mie Motors squad.
You're free to set up
the back room
however you'd like.
Great, thank you. Oh, but
where are you gonna sleep?
Do you not live here, too?
No, I live somewhere else.
Nothing fancy.
Oh, okay.
Hey! What do you say?
Do you think I could get a look
at your stone?
--Stone?
--You know...
the stones Nozomi
and that other girl
were talking about.
The pink ones?
I do not possess such a stone.
I won't tell! Come on,
I know you're a Best and all,
but trading blows
with a motorcycle?
I just want a little look.
Oh! That girl has a stone,
so does she have
mad skills, too?
You're speaking of Himeko?
Yes, actually.
I think it's possible
that she does have mad skills.
That's amazing! Those stones
are really worth hanging onto,
--huh?
--I'll see you tomorrow, then.
Oh, would you mind
putting that thing
--in the fridge?
--Yeah, no problem.
Thanks again! Good night!
You stingy old man. I just
wanted to look at the stone.
It's not like I was asking him
to give it to me.
Sheesh! Right, Chi-Chi?
Chi-Chi?
Mmm?
Maybe she's off somewhere
taking pictures again.
[clock ticking]
--I knew it!
--Huh?
You were lying
about the numbness in your arm.
You can move it just fine!
What are you trying to do?
Were you faking the injury
so you could force me
to make the shachihoko?
Because you think
that's the only way
I would ever take over?
If something happened to you
and you
couldn't create them anymore?
Come on... it's not like
I'd ever be as good as you.
It doesn't matter how many years
I'm away to train.
It won't change anything!
I'll never amount to much.
--Himeko...
--I wish all the shachihoko
would just disappear!
[slap]
[crying]
Wait. Come back.
Himek-- uhh...
Hey, look.
What is Ai doing?
--Maybe something's wrong.
--Oh, hey.
I can't find Chi-Chi anywhere.
[bike screeches]
Do you see what I see, Nozomi?
Do you think
that's what Mamoru meant?
[coughing]
[engine revving]
[muffled]
You should be doing it, too.
[engine revving]
Oh! Is that it? I thought
things looked different
around here.
[engine revving]
I'm not gonna do that.
Didn't I tell you
to start getting along
with old Aichi?
[engine revving]
I've taken some steps, okay?
Just be patient
a little longer.
[engine revving]
Huh?
What else was there to do?
And you're right, I don't think
I'm cut out to be captain.
--He said captain.
--If Mamoru's right,
then he's the one
who sent the request
for Maccha Green.
I guess I missed something?
For me, racing isn't about being
captain of the squad.
I race because
it's what I like to do.
I just enjoy the competition.
I've wasted enough time
listening to you.
Give me the go ahead,
and I'll take care of it.
[engine revving]
But will a race bring us peace?
No, sorry.
Permission denied.
[tires squealing]
[engine revving]
Good! We've been looking
for you.
Give your permission
for a decisive battle
between the squads.
Or are you too chicken
to race us?
[SQUAD MAN] No problem.
We'll take these guys on first.
[engine revving]
Look. That's the guardian god
of the new country.
[YOUNG HIMEKO]
Guardian god?
That's right.
They're called shachihoko.
They have the power
to call down rain,
and protect houses from fire.
As long as that's
where everyone can see,
this country
will be peaceful and safe.
Something you made
can do that?
Wow, Daddy, you're amazing!
I'm gonna make
shachihoko, too!
--Oh, yeah?
--I'll be just like you
when I grow up!
[grunts]
Huh?
[giggles]
Oh! Tomoki!
Hi.
Hey.
[screams]