[NARRATOR]
What was once mainstream
has been far surpassed
in the holy land
of personal expression.
The capital of
the former nation,
known now as Always Comima.
Ha!
[NARRATOR]
After the disbandment
of the legendary vigilante squad
of the Third District,
Tokyo Always,
a cosplaying state vigilante
squad was created
to restore the public order.
They're known as...
Knights of the Twin Towers.
[MAN 1]
Hey! Stop, thief!
[MAN 2]
Get back here!
[WOMAN]
Won't somebody stop him?
[NARRATOR]
And leading the squad,
a knight in shining armor!
That sword is
a truly unique weapon.
Its targeted attack
doesn't cause collateral damage
or harm nearby Rests.
The captain of the Knights is
a small Best with a big name.
People call her... Thunderoad!
These are
the guardians of Comima.
[RICK AND SHAW]
Fighting Buddies, Rick and Shaw!
[NARRATOR]
On or off duty,
they are always Comima.
[whistling]
[NOZOMI]
That looks like--
Is that a Moonlight Stone?
[CHIAYA]
Core.
[NOZOMI]
Uh... Core?
[AI]
Oh, wow! It's really pretty!
Y'know, I feel like
I've seen this somewhere before.
[grunts]
Possible.
There are more.
[YUKINA]
And you want what?
To gather them all up?
[CHIAYA]
Yeah.
[NOZOMI]
Hold on. this looks just like--
[MASAMI]
Nozomi! [crying]
[NOZOMI]
How can these things
even be gathered?
[YUKINA]
Yeah.
[AI]
That's totally cool.
Where'd you buy it?
[CHIAYA]
I didn't buy it.
I found it.
Okay, then
where did you find it?
In the window.
What?
[ALL gasp]
[AI]
What the--?
Pretty morning.
Huh?
[YUKINA]
Do the birds always come
hang out with you like that?
[NOZOMI]
That's what I thought.
[AI]
What?
That the stone just sort of
appeared in the sky
floating in the middle
of the air, like this.
Or a sparrow
picked one up somewhere.
What, and mine too?
I think I read about
things like this somewhere.
About power stones that rain
down mysteriously from the sky.
--[NOZOMI] Really?
--[AI] Power stones?
In fact, I think the Tokorozawa
captain had one, didn't she?
Yeah.
That's what I was talking about.
I gave it to her.
Well, the Higashi Murayama
leader had one, too.
Huh?
Oh yeah, that's right!
The stone on Shigyo's neck
did look like this.
[grunts]
[YUKINA]
Maybe what I read
actually had
a little truth to it.
I've seen something similar
in Tokyo.
I don't know if they're
the same thing, though.
[ALL gasp]
'Kay, so that's
what we're doing, then?
Works for me.
I don't mind going to Tokyo.
[NOZOMI]
We'll just follow you.
Sound good?
Uh... Uh-huh.
[NOZOMI]
Uh, Yukina?
What's up?
Hey, uh, Tokyo's that way.
[snoring]
[gasps]
Mmm.
--[CHIAYA] Mmm?
--[NOZOMI gasps]
Uh...
[NOZOMI screams]
[crow caws]
Don't be so sulky, Garm.
We have more
squad members now.
They've gotten really good
at keeping things organized.
Crime prevention
is on the rise.
The fact that I have
less work now,
it's actually a good thing
for Comima.
I have one more job
as captain to complete.
One more criminal element
to subdue.
[caw]
Once that's done,
I'll come back here and buy you.
My dear Prince Rick!
[gasps]
Garm, you crazy bird!
What are you doing to him?
Come down here!
Get your pecky beak
off my prince, you hear me?
[GIRL]
Captain! I've got bad news!
Hey, Noriko. What is it?
[NORIKO]
It's the Dynamite Bombers!
We've had another
warning note from them.
I brought it for you.
Another one?
[NOZOMI]
I'm starting to get
a little nervous now.
Tokyo's a scary place, right?
According to my brother,
the countries are all
pretty similar
when you get right down to it,
so I'm not sure.
Oh, I didn't know
you had a brother.
He's older.
Anyway, Tokyo.
I can say that
the people who helped me
when I collapsed on the street
were very friendly.
[NOZOMI]
Does this "collapsing" thing
--happen often?
--[YUKINA] Yes.
Sometimes I find
I have no idea where I am.
I know where I'm going,
but I just can't seem to
get there for some reason.
[NOZOMI]
Oh, really?
Strange, right?
I mean it's not like I'm
bad with directions or anything.
[NOZOMI]
No. No. Of course not.
Ah!
My neck hurts.
I musta slept on it funny.
Wait. What the--?
Where am I?
What's going on?
Who're you?
Oh, right.
[NOZOMI]
And this chick's
all over the place.
[groans]
[CHIAYA gasps]
[NOZOMI]
And what's the deal
with the mask?
[AI whistling]
[NOZOMI]
I guess everybody's
a little strange
in their own way.
[gasps]
Hey, Ai,
is that song you're whistling--
[YUKINA]
Are you going to go?
The light turned green.
[gasps]
[NOZOMI]
I'm sorry.
[AI]
You're a terrible driver,
y'know that?
Yeah? Then maybe you'd
like to drive instead.
[AI]
I already told you.
I can't drive.
[groans]
Well, then shut your mouth
and quit complaining.
[MAN 1]
Did you find it?
[MAN 2]
No.
[MOMIYAMA]
Stolen? That's unfortunate.
[AKI]
By the time I received
the warning note,
it was already gone.
Looks to me like
this was written on
old-fashioned gridded
writing paper.
I take it it's from
the Dynamite Bombers again?
[AKI]
I won't let them
get away next time!
Yes, well,
regardless of your intentions,
until these people are caught,
you won't be able to give us
the stone as per our agreement.
If you manage to
retrieve it from them, however,
I'm prepared to keep
my end of the bargain.
Those dirty bastards.
It's time I put a stop
to their mischief!
[FEMALE GUARD]
Lemme see yer passports.
Hmm. Huh.
You seem nervous.
Y'all wouldn't happen to be
Dynamite Bombers, would ya?
[NOZOMI]
Huh?
You know, those guys
that caused all the fuss
about six months ago.
The Knight Squad captain
had somethin' important
stolen from her this mornin',
so we gotta be extra careful
about what kinda folks
we let in here.
Interesting accent
for someone in the city.
Probably because
she's a checkpoint worker.
Most of them are
assigned from countries
that have no vested interest
in local affairs.
Huh. What's the Knight Squad?
[GUARD]
Here.
[sighs] This'll give ya
all the information ya need.
Their full name is
the Knights of the Twin Towers.
They're the state
vigilante squad
who do the peacekeeping
in Always Comima.
Wow!
Is their captain really strong?
[GUARD]
Well, yeah. Of course she is.
A Best with a backbone of iron,
which ya wouldn't expect,
given how tiny and cute she is.
[AI]
Ugh.
It's kinda hot
and gross here, huh?
[grunts]
Strange cloud.
[YUKINA]
Oh, that?
Around here it's called
the Comima Cloud.
The festival is a non-stop,
year-round thing.
I heard the Cloud is created
by all the body heat.
It keeps growing.
In the past,
the festival was only held
in that big building there.
I can see why
people would want to leave.
I mean, come on.
You have to admit, though,
it is a little cute.
Hey, Nozomi, look! Over there!
Huh?
[GIRL 1] Did you see that
they're making a movie?
[gasps] Come on, Chi, let's go!
[gasps]
[NOZOMI]
Hi! Excuse me!
[BOTH GIRLS]
Huh?
I wanted to ask you about that
heart-shaped stone
you're wearing.
[GIRL 2]
Stone?
Oh wait, are you talking about
her security charm?
Cute, right?
They have them on sale
for general use, too.
[NOZOMI]
Security charm, huh?
I guess I jumped the gun
on that one.
I'm sorry about that.
It's okay.
Chi, go ahead
and show them your stone.
[NOZOMI]
We're looking for these.
That's why I asked
about your charm.
Have you seen them before?
[BOTH gasp]
[alarm blaring]
[GIRLS gasp]
What'd we do?
[MAN]
They're here!
It's the Dynamite Bombers!
[gasps]
[GIRLS gasping]
[NOZOMI]
Whoa!
[AKI]
So you four ladies
are the Dynamite Bombers,
are you?
We're not, actually.
[AKI]
Why do you threaten the peace
of Always Comima?
Think you're tough enough
to take on Tokyo?
Where are your headquarters?
How big is your organization?
[AI]
We have no idea!
[AKI]
Since the bombing,
you've only given warnings
about your intended crimes.
Why haven't you acted on them?
[YUKINA]
We don't know!
[AKI]
Hmm.
I see they've trained you well.
No one trained us!
Is that so?
Then would you care to explain
how you came to be in possession
of this Drom Berserker?
What are you doing with my Core?
Maybe your intention was
to thumb your noses at me
or the Knights with your theft,
but this isn't just an orname--
We didn't steal anything!
That stone really does
belong to Chi!
[NOZOMI]
We weren't even in Tokyo
until shortly before
you picked us up.
Right, guys?
[YUKINA]
Oh, yeah.
[AKI]
We're making inquiries
into your passports,
but even if you
aren't the thieves,
the fact that you have this
makes it clear
that you're aligned with them.
We told you we have
nothing to do with this.
That's the truth.
Now stop being a bully
and give her back her stone!
Oh, and one more thing.
I heard you were really strong.
Will you make me your disciple?
--[NOZOMI] What?
--[YUKINA] What?
See, the thing is,
I wanna be a drifter Best.
What d'ya say
if I can lay a finger on you,
you agree to train me?
Huh. You intrigue me.
If you can touch me,
I will not simply
make you my disciple.
I'll call you master
and yield the stone.
All right! Let's go!
Wait, Ai!
Ah!
[ALL groaning]
[NOZOMI]
So, what do I do now?
Think like Masa.
What would she do?
[MASAMI]
Give that stone back,
you little brat!
That's a no go.
Mmm. Mmm.
[NOZOMI]
Um, do you think it's possible
that your stone
wasn't really stolen?
Maybe it got lost
and you didn't realize it.
[AKI]
What's that?
[cawing]
[NOZOMI]
I'll look for it for you!
[cawing continues]
[AKI]
Be quiet! That's enough, Garm!
[AI]
How do you plan
to look for it, exactly?
Well, I haven't
figured that out yet.
The city's huge.
It could be anywhere.
Yeah, maybe,
but that stone
rightfully belongs to Chi.
I've got a request to fulfill.
Except instead of
finding more stones,
we lost the one we had.
[AKI]
A request?
[NOZOMI]
Chi is my first client,
and my job was
to gather these stones.
See, Maccha Green
is temporarily unavailable,
so I'm taking on her duties.
Yes, I've heard of her.
Maccha Green,
the notorious peacebroker.
I know she can be reached
through the Tokorozawa
president's office,
but I didn't know she took on
little personal jobs like this.
These two.
I suppose they're
also here to facilitate
during Maccha Green's
temporary absence?
Huh?
Well, I don't know
about that, really.
I'm not. We're just
traveling companions.
That's all.
Yeah, me neither.
I was just hitchhiking.
Pretty much.
Hmm.
[AKI]
Very well. Find it if you can.
[GIRLS]
What?
[AKI]
You have until sundown.
If you are able to
locate my stone by that time,
I will return this to you.
[GIRLS gasp]
[AKI]
However, if you do not find it,
then all four of you...
will receive
capital punishment.
[cawing]
[CHIAYA ]
Capital?
[HINAYO]
If all you're going to do
is worry,
why did you let Nozomi go
in the first place?
[whimpering]
[TOMOMORI]
Well, because
she's getting to that age where
girls start to hate their dads.
I was trying to
rack up some points with her
while I could.
You know
you're impossible, right?
You let our daughter
go traipse about the world
so she would like you?
I don't see how
you can be so calm
at a time like this, Hina!
Who knows what's happening
to our Nozomi right now?
[HINAYO]
Take a breath.
She made a brave decision
to take Masami's place
and travel the countryside
to help people.
We supported her,
and that's that.
[whimpering]
[MASAMI]
Ma'am, is that really true?
[HINAYO and TOMOMORI]
What are you doing here?
[MASAMI]
You don't have to worry.
I'll bring her back to you.
You can't do that!
You're still badly injured!
Ah, nah, I'll be fine.
Really, I feel like I'm
completely healed already!
Here, y'see?
[gasps]
[HINAYO]
What are you doing?
--[TOMOMORI] Masami!
--[HINAYO] Masami, wake up!
[TOMOMORI]
I think she lost consciousness!
Masami!
[MASAMI]
I can't believe this!
If only I still had
my Moonlight Stone,
I'd be better already.
Hey, Shigyo! You had a stone
like mine, didn't you?
I know we're not buds,
but could you lend--
[gasps]
[OTONASHI]
It's no use!
I'm so sorry!
I swear I've looked hard,
but I can't find your
Heroic Garnet at... all.
[MASAMI groaning]
[AKI]
Those girls
are definitely Rests.
They're probably pretending
to search for the stone
to buy time until their friends
can come and save them.
That's why I let them go.
We can tail them and catch
them all in one fell swoop.
[YUKINA]
I really don't think
we'll be able to find it.
I mean, she did say
it was stolen, remember?
[NOZOMI]
We have to
at least look, though.
I am really sorry I got you guys
involved in this mess, too.
[AI]
Why are you being so stubborn
about the whole thing, anyway?
I made a promise...
even if it was just to myself.
She can't do this, so I will.
[gasps]
[AI]
You can't expect to search
the entire city.
[NOZOMI]
I don't know
what else to do at this point.
[CHIAYA]
Bushy bush.
[NOZOMI/AI/YUKINA]
Huh?
[YUKINA]
I'm sorry,
what are you talking about?
That's what
the crow was saying.
"Inside bushy bush.
Look bushy bush.
Red bushy bush."
'Kay.
Tell me something, Chi-Chi.
What's with these rocks?
Why do you wanna gather them?
Uh...
I want them
because they're so pretty.
[AI]
What? That's it?
[YUKINA]
Hate to break it to you,
but you might have to
give up on this one.
[NOZOMI]
No way!
As Maccha Green's
representative,
I can't let you do that!
We're not
anyone's representatives.
At any rate,
the sun's about to set.
[AKI]
I don't see
any sign of their allies.
[NOZOMI]
Uh. What was that?
[ALL]
Huh?
[whimpering]
[gasping]
[MOMIYAMA]
The agent's recovery fee.
There's a case where it's of
particular sentimental value
to the owner,
so the price is inflated,
which makes it
extremely over budget.
[HARUKA]
That can't be helped.
There's no time
to worry about it.
We still don't have all we need.
[MOMIYAMA]
Unfortunately, we were depending
on Maccha Green's efforts,
so now...
[sighs]
Yes. Her injuries were
exceedingly ill-timed.
Having clients pay for
peacebroker activities
with the stones
was an excellent gambit.
Now we'll just have to
hide the fact
that she's beyond recovery
and have them
send the stones first.
I suppose you're right.
[HARUKA]
You think me contemptible,
don't you?
No. It's not that.
Believe me,
I know that there are
exigent circumstances.
If I may, ma'am.
You should have a meal
with your daughter sometime.
She seems like such
a lonely little girl.
[HARUKA]
You're right. I should.
She needs to be
told about this, soon.
[ALL groaning]
[caws]
[MOMIYAMA]
Very well, then.
We have a deal.
I'll buy your stone
for 100,000 Comima.
Pleasure doing
business with you.
Once I've officially resigned
as captain of the squad,
I'll contact you.
[alarm blaring]
I still want to
honor our deal, Momiyama,
but will you wait until
I catch the Dynamite Bombers?
Huh?
[AKARU]
Hey! Excuse me!
I'd like to buy this statue.
Are you the person
I should talk to?
Huh?
[AKARU]
I was waiting for
the price to go down.
Well you have perfect timing!
Right now I can give you a
special price of 50,000 Comima!
No way! That's great!
Whoa, wait just a sec!
Sell it to me!
I'll pay 80,000 Comima.
[MAN]
Oh. Uh...
No, wait! I'll pay 90,000!
I'll give you 100!
110!
Uh, then I guess I offer 120.
[AKARU]
150!
Ugh. 160. I offer 160.
[AKARU]
180,000!
[groans]
200,000 Comima!
[AKI]
Uh! Wait, please don't tell me
she's working with him!
Huh?
[cawing]
[AKI]
Troublemaker!
How'd you get out of your cage?
Come back here right now.
That's my stone!
But what is it doing in there?
Bird, were you
playing a trick on me?
Caw?
You weren't, were you?
It was my own
stupid mistake all along.
[cawing]
[MAN]
Thanks for your purchase.
I hope you enjoy it!
[NOZOMI]
I can't believe
it's night already!
"Capital punishment."
Do you really think
they'll execute us?
But that would be
ridiculous, wouldn't it?
I mean, just for
stealing a rock?
Um, hello, we didn't
actually steal anything!
Right, but we're dealing
with someone
who doesn't believe
anything we say.
That's the whole problem.
Yeah, it's hopeless, isn't it?
Hey! What if we escape for now
and try again another time.
That could work, right?
I don't understand.
[AI]
Simple!
We come back
after we get stronger.
Then we defeat that
pint-sized captain of theirs
and get Chi-Chi's
precious stone from her.
So, what do you say?
I think it sounds good!
And in this plan,
who fights the captain?
[AI]
That'd be me.
And how are you going to get
strong enough to do that?
[AI]
I'll go train somewhere.
[YUKINA]
Um.
Well, I'm all for
the escaping part, at least,
but they took our passports away
when they grabbed us.
and we don't know
where our motorcycles are.
Don't worry.
We'll figure it all out somehow.
It doesn't work like that.
[NOZOMI]
Besides, I don't want to
run away when
we haven't done anything wrong.
[AI]
I wasn't talking about
running away.
Maybe if we just ask her
for a little more time.
I don't think ten years would be
enough time for us to find it.
There's no way if it was stolen
by those Dynamite Bomber people
she was talking about.
[NOZOMI groans]
[YUKINA]
So, what are we going to do?
Mmm!
[CHIAYA]
Nonsuke. Yukippe. U-tan.
Anyone else hungry?
[stomachs growling]
[ALL groaning]
[door opens]
[ALL]
Huh?
Hey, you four, come with me.
[ALL]
This is it! We're all gonna die!
[groaning]
[NORIKO]
Um, what are you guys doing?
Hurry up, okay?
I'm not going to hurt you.
Just come with me.
[MOMIYAMA]
There's no doubting
that they're both authentic,
but why is it that
you have two now?
Anyway,
I was kinda hoping you could
give me the payment in advance.
Why's that?
Has the situation changed?
Well, yes.
It's not that I don't trust you,
but unfortunately
I can't do what you're asking.
Huh?
It's a matter of urgency
on our end.
In fact, I would ask that you
give me both stones right now
if at all possible.
What?
[MOMIYAMA]
If you insist on
waiting until after you've
eradicated the Dynamite Bombers
to close the deal,
then the price,
actually the entire agreement,
would have to be reconsidered,
I hate to say.
Why?
Mmm.
[BOTH laughing]
Okay! You can have them!