[tires screech]
A good little girl
would have been in bed by now.
A good girl wouldn't beat you!
You've got some spunk.
[BOTH grunt]
[shouting]
Your form is stiff. You leave
too many openings that way.
You should try to relax a bit.
[grunts, shouts]
[grunts]
I know you're
probably stronger than me...
but I still have to find
a way to defeat you.
I'm doing this for everybody!
But especially for my mom,
'cause she deserves better!
[OSSIE grunts]
--[MOMO] Get her!
--[CHI barks]
[MOMO] Ossie!
[squawks]
--[URA] Hey!
--Mr. Slo!
[shouts]
[yelps]
[grunting]
[MR. SLO grunts]
Give this up and go home.
Your life may be poor,
but it's peaceful.
[footsteps approach]
[gasps]
Mom?
Time to go home, Momo.
I didn't teach you to wield
a sword so you could engage
in this sort of foolishness.
[gasps]
Don't try to stop me, Mom.
I'm going to defeat her
if it kills me--
Momo! Hey, is she all right?
Why did you knock her out?
You see her?
That's Momo's real mother.
[BOTH gasp]
[HARU] She's too young
to understand.
I couldn't tell her.
[sighs]
No. That's not it.
I just wanted more time.
A little longer
to be her mother.
[URA] If it isn't master fencer
Haru Fujiwara. It's been while.
This troublemaker is
your daughter, then?
What can I say, Ura?
She takes after her mother.
[URA]
It seems so.
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Stay calm, everyone.
These dolls may look scary,
but they can't hurt you.
I can assure you of that.
They may appear threatening,
but they're harmless.
--[VILLAGERS gasp]
--Is that really true?
[MAN]
They sure look dangerous.
[HARU]
The state vigilante squad,
the Okayama Demons,
does not exist anymore.
The only one living
in this demon castle is you.
You were the Best
who protected Okayama,
defending it
from Hiroshima's attacks,
keeping it safe
from those pirates
without honor or humanity.
Until you turned your back.
I demand to know the reasons
for thy betrayal, Ura Kukino!
[laughs] You always were
old-fashioned, weren't you?
All right then,
let's see if I can put this into
words that you'll understand.
Don't waste thy breath,
'tis a lost cause!
[grunts]
[motorcycle approaches]
[gasps]
[NOZOMI running]
Um. Hold on! Kaguya!
Uh...
Sorry, but there's
a visitor here
from Okayama...
looking for Fuhito.
He wants Kuramochi?
Then he can go to the hospital.
It sounds like it's really
important, though!
--[sighs]
--[NOZOMI] What's your plan?
Going to get back at them?
--[grunts]
--Oh!
I won't let you do that!
You're not even a real
peacebroker, so why try so hard?
[NOZOMI]
I don't like it!
Sounds silly, huh?
But that's how I feel.
I get that I'm nobody.
Not a Best.
Just a lame stand-in.
A stupid, meddling outsider.
But I can't just do nothing!
[gasps]
[MAN] I am the former captain
of the Okayama Demons.
My name is Kibino.
[KAGUYA] An agreement between
Hiroshima and Okayama?
[KIBINO] Ura Kukino wanted
to protect the country
even if it meant becoming
an enemy of all its citizens.
So she made a secret pact
with Hiroshima, got rid
of all the squad members,
and became a demon.
But that charade will not
be useful much longer.
If Kuramochi makes
everything known to the public--
not for retribution,
but for justice--
he could save everybody
from the depredations
of the Ishizukuri Stones.
[KAGUYA]
Shima Ishizukuri is
from a former
branch family line.
If Okayama acknowledges
the secret agreement,
then the former head family
will bring about justice.
[KIBINO] Yes. However, the
captain does not agree with me.
And since the citizens
have begun an uprising,
I thought I would come here
to explain the situation
and convince Kuramochi
to lend us his help.
[KAGUYA]
I guess I shouldn't be surprised
he never said
anything about this to me.
[chuckles]
He's always like that,
carrying everything
on those broad shoulders of his.
Doesn't he know
he's not the only one
who can serve this family?
--Let's get going.
--[gasps]
[chuckles]
Justice awaits.
[BOTH grunt]
Okay, wait.
That walking cupcake over there
is actually Momo's mom?
That's nuts!
There's a reason the president
was always so busy.
She's been working hard
for years,
trying to return you
to your home planet,
to get you back
to your real family.
Real family. What about Mom?
What's that make her?
[grunts]
Well, she's your mom, too.
She always will be.
He was right.
[BOTH grunt]
The way I see it,
they're both her moms, right?
Uh... they're both--
yeah, you're right!
Let me borrow this a sec, Momo.
[grunts] Okay!
--[shouting]
--[VILLAGERS gasp]
--[MAN] What're you doing?
--[WOMAN] You're gonna get hurt!
[grunting]
Hey, what's happening?
[screams]
--That's gotta hurt!
--What was she trying to do?
[AI] Haru!
Don't, Ai! Stay back!
[grunts] If you don't want
Momo to fight her,
you gotta lead by example!
You have to back down
and stop fighting her, too!
I don't know the whole story,
but you're both her moms,
aren't you?
[gasps]
[grunts] Aw, man!
What's up with this thing?
I thought the stone
would make me a Best,
but it's not helping me at all.
I still have to stop them!
--U-tan, no!
--Come back!
[WOMAN]
Really? Again?
[BOTH grunting]
[URA thinks]
Is she really?
You abandoned her!
How could you ever do that?
What was so important
that you could even consider it?
I said not to waste
your breath! Didn't I?
--[screams]
--Are we too late?
--Nonsuke is here!
--Why's Chi here?
Nonsuke! U-tan is in trouble!
--Huh?
--[grunts]
[NOZOMI] Ai?
[grunts]
[NOZOMI]
Whoa! What's happening?
[grunting]
Huh?
[ANIMALS whimpering]
[BOTH shouting]
--[ALL groan]
--Huh?
[CHI whimpering]
A dog! [yelps]
Hold on!
Stop fighting, okay?
There's something
you need to hear!
Uh... Nozomi?
[URA] I'm too stubborn
for my own good.
I never did learn
when to back down.
[KIBINO]
Of course you couldn't.
Only someone with great resolve
could have become
a demon as you did.
And through it all you stayed
by my side, didn't you?
[KIBINO] Of course I did.
It was all I could do.
Please. Tell me her name.
It's Momo.
[URA] Thank you.
You raised her to be strong.
[HARU]
Well, she does have your genes.
[URA] That may be true,
but she also has your spirit.
[MOMO groans] Huh?
She goes after what she wants,
no matter what anyone says.
[sighs]
And people like that only become
stronger, the more they learn.
[winces] Huh?
Well, I think
that's all you need me for.
Is there anything else
I can do to help?
Yeah, me too.
I want to do what I can
to help the people of Okayama.
Ura Kukino has given me
her word of honor.
Now there's an upstart
branch family to deal with,
and that's going to be my job.
Thank you.
[giggles]
[truck departs]
Uhh...
Uhh... [laughing]
Hey, what're you laughing at?
At your face.
You look really terrible!
Huh! You don't look
so good yourself.
[laughs]
So, uh, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, too.
Glad you're back.
[NOZOMI and AI laughing]
Hey, Nonsuke. Where's Yukippe?
--Huh?
--Ah!
I have to get that stone back
for Shigyo as soon as possible!
She can't return
to normal without it.
I don't know whether
or not she can be a Best again,
but she could
at least leave the hospital.
Without the stone,
all I can do
is stay by her side
and comfort her.
But I can't even do
that much for her
when I'm stuck
inside this stupid cell!
Stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid cell!
[chuckles]
♪ Nameless stones,
we're all rolling along ♪
♪ Through the seasons
of the sun ♪
♪ When the world
kicks you around ♪
♪ Throws you to the ground... ♪
Hey, that's Momi-Ham
you're singing.
That song always
helps me feel better,
like I can make
a difference in the world,
even though
I'm just one little person.
I know how you feel.
My friends and I sing it
together all the time, too.
--[MOMIYAMA] "Stones," huh?
--[gasps]
I can't believe
girls as young as you
would know a band that old.
Well, my parents
introduced them to me.
Yeah, there were a lot of kids
who listened to them growing up.
That long, huh? Hard to believe
so much time has passed.
[gasps] Oh my gosh!
You're Momizo from
Momiyake Hammers, aren't you?
No!
"Kuranosuke Momiyama." Momizo.
[MOMIYAMA] Sorry, kid, not me.
--Think you can guide us out?
--[YUKINA] Huh?
You got here yourself.
You weren't dragged in,
so you know best where we are.
Think you can do it?
[gulps]
Yeah, sure!
[OTOMO] There's something about
this relic of the evil Takumis.
I know we agreed not to expose
that it was
in our possession, but--
Why? What is it? Did you
remember something from before?
What? Oh, no.
I have no memories from before
I woke up here that day.
It's all a blank.
[SHIMA]
I see. It's fine, then.
[grunts]
--[SHIMA] What's wrong?
--It's nothing.
[FATCHO on P.A.]
Pardon, ma'am.
There are messengers
from Tokorozawa.
[MASAMI]
Whoa! What is all this?
[SHIGYO]
Maybe they're trying to start
an archipelago conquest project.
[MASAMI] Huh?
[SHIGYO]
There are groups out there
who've started doing
exactly that,
like a reaction against
what the world's become
--in recent years.
--Seriously?
Things seem to be
snowballing out of control.
I think there's more going on
than anybody knows.
[SHIMA] As I'd expect
of the woman called
the Trigger
of the Great Tokyo War.
You're very perceptive.
I certainly hope that's
a real octopus pot engine unit
you've got.
It's not like
we had a lot of time
on our hands
to whip up a fake one.
First return the hostage,
then you can have it.
[SHIMA]
Unfortunately, she's gone.
--[BOTH] Huh?
--I know, what a drag, huh?
I'll be taking that unit now.
[grunts]
We had a deal!
You don't think
we can put up a fight?
If you want the octopus pot,
return Otonashi now!
Don't forget. We have
to push the button first.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
[grunts]
Crap! Shigyo!
--[GUYS laugh]
--These chicks are pathetic.
--Let's get them!
--[GUYS shouting]
--Charge her!
--Knock her out!
[GUY]
Think they're really that weak?
[GUY 2] Nah!
I think we're just that strong!
[GUY]
Yeah, that's right!
[BOTH moan]
Good, now mount it
onto the Stonefish.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Hurry up.
With this, we can expand
Okonomiyaki Village
to the surface of the moon.
I guess you wanted to go,
too, didn't you?
--Huh?
--Oh, come on.
I see how you stare up at night.
I didn't realize.
--[explosion]
--[BOTH gasp]
Shima Ishizukuri.
I'm here as a descendant
of the Nayotake family.
You're guilty
of severe misconduct.
I've come to make you pay.
Kaguya Nayotake.
Have you come to avenge
old Kuramochi?
I've come to punish you!
[NOZOMI] Where do you think
Yukina could have gone?
I don't know.
Maybe she went back to the shop.
I doubt it. I don't think
there'd be any reason to.
[AI] Hey, can we talk
about that stone?
--Yeah! Let's stop a sec.
--[grunts]
--[AI] Well?
--[NOZOMI] My stone.
I've had it with me
this whole time,
but I never came close
to being a Best.
Yeah. I think
that's pretty obvious.
--Uhh...
--Here's the thing.
Those stones are--
oh, is that Yukippe?
[NOZOMI and AI] Huh?
[NOZOMI gasps]
It's Kuramochi!
Hey. I'm really
starting to think
that you have
no sense of direction.
You're wrong. That's not it.
I'm fine with directions.
Okay, so you're absolutely sure
this is the way you came?
Uh, maybe we should take
a quick break.
Maybe you should answer
the question!
--[clangs]
--[engine powering up]
[GUYS scream]
As the Nayotake successor,
it is my duty to see
that you pay
for your wrongdoing.
You backed Okayama's Best
into a corner.
You made people suffer!
Apologize and return
the money you exploited.
Finally,
relinquish the squad license
to which you have no right.
No, I don't think so.
Hiroshima used to be united.
Do you remember that?
The main family,
the branch families,
and the respectable folks--
everyone rough around the edges,
but all of 'em good people.
You were one of them!
Or have you forgotten?
What are you talking about?
I may've been young,
but I remember.
You played with me!
You weren't always pirate scum.
[laughs]
Sounds like a nice memory.
Would you like to know
what I remember?
Because I'm happy to tell you.
I remember how all those people
who looked after
the Nayotake family treated us
once it was ruined
by the family war.
They all pretended
not to know us.
[shouts]
Do you remember that?
Is that some kinda excuse
for what you're planning?
Whatever it is, I'll stop you.
[SHIMA] Think long and hard
before you try anything.
You really believe
you can defeat me?
You don't stand a chance.
Want to know what I'm planning?
I'll tell you. I'm gonna make
this whole archipelago
without honor and humanity
part of Okonomiyaki Village!
[gasps]
[powering up]
[groans]
[grunts]
[KAGUYA grunts]
"The only people who matter
are ourselves and our own.
Everybody else is
just part of the Rest."
That's how most people think.
But not everyone.
There are still people
out there who want to help,
who ask nothing in return
but a stupid stone.
[gasps]
[KAGUYA] Who haven't
given up on the world!
Sounds to me
like those people are idiots.
Stop! What are you doing?
I have no use
for moldy scraps of paper.
What I really wanted was this.
[KAGUYA gasps]
[chuckles]
How sad,
for a descendant
of the main family not to know.
During the Great Tokyo War,
there was a robot with abilities
that surpassed those of both
the Tokyo Tower Robot
and the Tokyo Skytree Robot.
The chivalrous robot, Daimon!
[breathes shakily]
There they go.
I believe they're all finished.
Hey, wake up! It looks like
the ship has been completed,
so half of this has gone
according to plan.
Huh?
Once we have control of it,
we'll get Otonashi.
And next time, be sure
to press the button, okay?
[clicks]
--[sproings]
--[BOTH gasp]
[SHIMA]
Excellent work, men.
Next, why don't I have you
mass produce this robot?
I am still in possession
of the sacred Takumi object
that you brought out
during the turmoil.
I'm assuming
that you would like it back.
--Now. Move!
--[MEN shouting]
[gasps]
It's the end of Hiroshima's
false chivalry! Say good bye!
--It's a chivalrous...
--Robot...
Called Daimon?
It was made
when Hiroshima was in crisis
and is intended to be ridden
by successors
to the Nayotake name.
I heard that, during
the family war, it was stolen
from the storehouse
by the Abe branch family,
and then taken by the Isonokami
before finally ending up
in the hands
of the pirate Shima Ishizukuri.
But it won't run on its own.
It needs another component.
That's probably why she wanted
the squad license so badly.
--[GIRLS] Huh?
--Thanks to me,
Kaguya's rushed
into this situation blindly.
You said your name was Nozomi?
[NOZOMI]
Yes. That's right.
Please help us.
Bring this to Kaguya Nayotake.
So much depends
on her right now.
[GIRLS gasp]
[CHIAYA] Takoyaki?