[gasps]
[whimpering]
[NOZOMI]
Oh, wow!
What's going to happen next?
Well, I would guess that
we're going to derail.
Oh and then what, do you think?
After that,
I imagine we'll fall.
Wow! Cool!
And then what, and then what?
Mmm.
[grunts]
[ALL]
We're all gonna die!
[ALL screaming]
[MASAMI gasps]
[ALL]
Captain! Save us!
All of them?
[gasps] Nozomi!
Masa's here!
[MASAMI]
Who are they?
[OTONASHI]
Unless someone
stops that roller coaster,
things are gonna
get ugly, Masami.
And it doesn't look like you
have time to get Maccha Green.
I really figured Maccha would be
the one to come
in the first place.
This is playing dirty!
Remember the Declaration.
Time and place must be decided--
Alas, communication
isn't what it used to be.
Messages don't always
get delivered these days.
What I'd like to know is
how you're going to
handle this situation
without a Best around.
Yeah? It's not like we're
helpless without Maccha Green.
I'll call in backup.
I've got some lined up,
you know!
[OTONASHI]
Oh, really?
Are you talking about the Hyper
Maccha Robot from yesterday?
Huh? Yes! I am!
You're in luck.
It's right over there.
[MASAMI]
Huh?
[gasps]
Come on,
it's just a cheap balloon!
If you really wanted to fool us,
you should have ponied up
for a better product.
[MASAMI]
But yesterday you were all--
We were just
pretending to be scared!
[snoring]
[ALL whimpering]
[gasping]
[sighing]
What're you going to do?
Since you can't
get Maccha Green,
it looks like your options
are limited.
Do you want to save
your precious Propellers?
If so, then you better surrender
to the Dangers right now!
Hmm.
They tricked her.
I get it now.
The sneaky jerks
are using us as hostages.
[sighs] Yeah. Looks like it.
[sighs]
Instead of helping Masa,
I'm only causing
more trouble for her!
Please! Where's Maccha Green
when we need her?
We're gonna die!
Huh?
[SHIGYO]
On the off-chance
you don't want to surrender,
that only leaves you one choice.
It's time to suck it up.
You have to fight me.
A headache, a stomachache,
family commitment,
a slipped disk,
a freaking inflatable robot!
You've always put off our fight
for one reason after another.
Ugh! That ends now!
I won't let you forfeit today,
Masami Utoku!
No! Maybe I should call you
Maccha Green!
[grunts]
Huh?
What?
[gasps] No.
[OTONASHI]
Oh, just give it up.
It's no secret anymore,
'cause yesterday
I finally confirmed
that you were
the one inside the suit.
I figured that out
a long time ago.
Uh-huh. Yeah, me too.
--So did I.
--Same here.
[gasping]
Yeah, who didn't know?
[ALL talking over each other]
I--
No, you're wrong!
I'm not Maccha!
How could I be?
I can't fight you!
[ALL]
What?
[talking over each other]
[SHIGYO]
Ha. Oh?
I guess your squad members
are doomed, then.
Their captain has
just handed them
a one-way ticket
to the afterlife.
Enjoy your front row seat.
I hope this was worth it.
[ALL gasping]
[NOZOMI]
All this time, Masa is Maccha.
Now that I think about it,
it kinda makes sense.
[ALL whimpering]
Nan man dabu, nan man dabu,
nan man dabu.
[whimpering]
[MASAMI]
What should I do?
I have to save them, but...
[OTONASHI]
Why won't she accept it?
I mean, I've got
one or two hobbies
I wouldn't want
the whole world to know about,
but put in this situation,
I think I would
just deal with it.
You know, if she is
just a regular chick,
then that suit of hers
really does enhance
the wearer's strength.
It's going to be
the star of my collection.
Just wait.
[gasps]
[OTONASHI]
Strength-enhancing powers?
Any way you look at it,
it's just a skintight bodysuit.
Shigyo actually seems to think
it could be for real.
A tough exterior,
but the heart of an innocent.
How irresistibly adorable!
Say goodbye!
They call this
the roller coaster to hell!
You can still put
a stop to this, Masami,
but you have to decide!
[ALL]
It's too late! We're gonna die!
[screaming]
Mmm.
[gasps]
Huh?
[ALL whimpering]
Masa!
[ALL screaming]
[screaming]
Wait, what's going on?
We're not falling.
Ah! Well, not yet.
This is kind of fun!
[grunts]
[OTONASHI]
Wow, their construction
really was impeccable.
Even I was terrified.
For a second,
I thought they were gonna die.
[SHIGYO chuckles]
How pathetically naive.
Huh?
An explosion? What was that?
I didn't place an order
for any pyrotechnics.
[SHIGYO]
Don't you get it?
Those weren't
ordinary carpenters.
They're the evil Takumi
of the black coats.
[OTONASHI gasps]
They do special orders.
You were right before.
This really is
the roller coaster to hell.
This isn't cool.
No one was
actually supposed to die.
[ALL screaming]
[MIITAN]
Okay, this really
isn't fun anymore!
[HITOSHI]
There's someone
trying to stop it.
[DEN-SAN]
You mean she wants to save us?
[NOBORU]
Not everyone from
the Dangers is bad.
[YUMI]
You can do it!
[ALL]
Huh?
[ALL groan]
[screaming]
Help me, Masa. I'm scared.
[MASAMI grunting]
[OTONASHI]
We're in real danger
of violating the Twin Tower
Declaration with this.
We're not supposed to
harm non-combatants.
Oh, get over it.
How many people do you think
actually adhere to that?
[OTONASHI gasps]
Well, Maccha?
Coming to the rescue?
[grunts]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[screams]
Damn that mask!
Crocodile!
[grunting]
[screaming]
Hey, whoa!
No way!
[ALL screaming]
Oh, no!
Help me!
Yukina, catch!
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH screaming]
Somebody stop this thing!
Maccha... Stopper!
Please... just... stop!
[sighs]
[whimpering]
That's Masa? Really?
[MASAMI]
Nozomi.
[BOTH gasp]
Well, isn't this
an interesting development?
Your incredible strength
doesn't come from the suit.
Where does it come from?
Let's find out!
We have to help her!
[gasping]
[retching]
[ALL]
Captain!
You guys didn't die?
That's great!
[CROCODILE]
Yeah.
[DEN-SAN]
This kinda thing
happens to us a lot.
[ALL]
Captain!
[MASAMI gasping for breath]
No. I'm not the cap--
I don't get it!
Why would you
go through all this
just to hide the fact that
you're the one in the suit?
I'm Maccha Green. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Quit acting like you're some
kind of cartoon character!
Let it go already!
Shigyo, look out!
She's gonna blow!
Huh?
[ALL gasping]
[MASAMI whimpering]
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
[NOZOMI]
It's really you?
But why?
Why hide it?
I don't understand.
[MASAMI]
I'm sorry, Nozomi,
but ever since
you were a little girl,
all you wanted to do
was help me.
I mean,
just think about that time
I pretended I was drowning.
You almost died
trying to save me.
So that's why?
[MASAMI]
Well, yeah.
You can see, right?
I wanted to keep it
so you wouldn't know
I was the one fighting.
If you did know I was doing
something so dangerous,
you would want to--
Seriously?
[gasps]
You thought I was stupid enough
to force myself into
a fight between Bests?
I'd never even try that!
I know I'd die!
Huh?
[ALL talking over each other]
[MIITAN]
How could you
even get close enough?
Masami,
can't you see
I'm not a kid anymore?
[gasps]
You're right. I'm sorry.
[NOZOMI]
You should have told me.
I know I wouldn't have
been able to help.
But still, I deserve the chance
to worry about you!
Insensitive jerk!
[NOZOMI]
Huh? Who's she?
Think about how she feels,
why don't you?
Of course your captain
wants to protect you!
To her you'll always be--
Huh?
A crocodile?
--[DEN-SAN] What was that for?
--[NOZOMI] Are you okay?
Whoops. I didn't mean to--
Poor thing!
Not cool!
What do you think you're doing?
You know fighting's against
the rules if you're not a Best!
I'm sorry!
It was an accident. I swear!
[talking over each other]
Looks like our newbie's
gotten herself in trouble.
What was she thinking, anyway?
[gasps]
[OTONASHI]
Shigyo?
Masami's little speech
reminded me of something.
I don't know what, exactly,
but I feel like it had
something to do with a promise.
A promise I've
already forgotten, apparently.
It's right there,
but I can't quite remember.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
And we aren't so little anymore.
[MASAMI]
Tell me what it was, Shigyo.
Huh?
The promise that you made
all those years ago.
What was it?
[MASAMI]
I remember.
A slew of vigilante squads
descended on Tokyo.
To my childish eyes, they looked
like a bunch of villains
straight out of a nightmare.
I was scared.
That's why I cheered for you.
You stood in their way.
Now, think!
You weren't obsessed
with fighting back then,
so why did you do what you did?
I... I don't know.
Don't listen!
I, um, let me think.
I guess I, uh...
[MASAMI]
You're close! Please remember!
Hey, shut up!
Stop talking to her!
Ah!
[OTONASHI gasps]
[SHIGYO]
That's right.
I remember now!
I learned the superhero
I'd idolized
wasn't actually real,
so it became my job,
protecting other people
from bad guys.
Huh.
Why did I...
No!
Oh, no!
Stop, Shigyo!
There's no need to remember!
[SHIGYO]
I don't understand!
How could I?
Really!
Just let it go!
[GUY] She wanted to be
some kind of superhero?
--[GIRL 1] No way!
--[GIRL 2] She totally
missed the mark on that one.
[GUY]
She's not exactly
what you'd call
"one of the good guys."
It's not too late.
You can still change!
--[SHIGYO whimpers]
--[OTONASHI gasps]
She can't just wipe away
ten years of her life like that!
[screams]
It's okay. Calm down.
Masami!
[breathing heavily]
Please! You have no idea
what you're talking about.
[gasps] Behind you!
[OTONASHI]
Watch out!
No matter what,
I'll always protect you.
[gasps]
Behind you!
Ow!
Uh, sorry!
What I meant was
"diagonally from above
and behind you!"
Heh.
[NOZOMI]
Masa, I--
Huh?
[gasps]
[MOMIYAMA]
Our reports suggest
Always Comima has postponed
its expansion for the moment.
Which means
the recent disturbance
should die down
for a while, as well.
These were in the possession
of the two Bests?
Given how things worked out,
I'd say so.
It was
an exceptionally fierce duel.
Both only narrowly
escaped with their lives.
They'll need a couple of months
to recover fully.
[HARUKA]
I see.
Maccha Green
was seriously wounded.
You won't be conducting
any negotiations, then?
Why would I?
Considering that I was,
in fact, the original owner.
[HINAYO]
Why should you go?
These letters are
for Maccha Green,
not Nozomi Moritomo.
But Masami can't do
anything to help right now!
What exactly do you plan
to do out there?
How can you solve disputes
between other squads?
I don't know yet,
but people need help.
And they need it soon!
This one says they'll be waiting
at Aviation Memorial Park
tomorrow!
Not another word!
There's no telling what kind of
trouble you could get into!
Finding out that Masami
is actually a Best
has already been
enough of a shock for us.
Let the vigilante squads
take care of it.
The can ask
another Best for help.
[grunts]
[TOMOMORI]
Why not let her go?
[NOZOMI]
Oh! Hey, Dad!
[HINAYO]
Welcome home, dear.
Now, Hina,
we let Nozomi get
her motorcycle license.
There was a reason for that,
wasn't there?
It's true there's
a lot of trouble in the world,
but there are also
great things to discover
and wonderful people to meet.
[HINAYO]
Huh?
[TOMOMORI]
We met because of
that motorcycle.
You haven't forgotten that,
have you?
[HINAYO]
Of course I haven't,
but Nozomi is still young.
[TOMOMORI]
Look, see this picture?
You remember, don't you?
[HINAYO]
Yes.
That's from back from
when we first met.
[TOMOMORI]
All this time
and you haven't changed
one little bit.
Well, darling,
I don't know about that,
but you look exactly the same.
Mmm?
Ah!
[NOZOMI]
I'm tired of being protected.
Let's go!
[grunts]
[squeals]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
[cries]
Mmm.
[MASAMI]
Nozomi.
Oh, is that--
Hey, Yukina.
[NOZOMI]
Really? You want to come along?
Sure. I was hoping to do
some traveling, anyway,
so why not, right?
Sounds good to me.
[chuckles]
Oh! Hi! Heh!
Hey! Think I could get a--
Oh!
[AI]
Wait up!
Huh?
Let's just keep going.
--[YUKINA] Huh? But this--
--[AI] Hey!
Sorry, but we really don't
have any time to waste.
Nozomi! This is
Aviation Memorial Park.
What? Huh.
[NOZOMI]
It's that girl.
[YUKINA]
Do you know her or something?
Yeah. she's a customer of ours.
[AI]
Hey! [breathing heavily]
Oh, good!
Thanks for waiting!
It's me, from earlier.
You remember?
Yeah. I think so.
You're from Higashi Murayama,
aren't you?
That's right!
Well, until they
kicked me out, anyway.
I have no idea
where you're going,
but you don't mind
giving me a ride, do you?
--This spot's open, right?
--[NOZOMI] Huh?
[AI]
So,
is that crocodile guy
doing all right?
And how 'bout your captain?
[GIRL gasps]
I've got this letter here.
Are you the one who wrote it?
You are...?
Um, right, sorry.
I'm Nozomi Moritomo,
from the dango shop.
This is my friend, Yukina.
Hey there.
It's nice to meet you.
What's up? I'm Ai Hibiki.
I'm the newest member
of the gang.
Anyway, Mas-- Maccha Green
couldn't make it today,
so I came in her place.
[ALL THREE]
Whoa!
[GIRL]
U-tan.
Huh?
[GIRL]
Yukippe.
Uh--
[GIRL]
Nonsuke.
Huh?
Hold on! That's my nickname
from when I was little.
How could you
possibly know that?
--[NOZOMI] And mine, too?
--[YUKINA] That's mine, also.
I'm Chiaya.
[ALL THREE]
Chiaya?
Just stay right there!
Uh...
[NOZOMI]
Are you taking a picture?
Okay, well, get on in here.
All done. Let's go.
Go where?
What are we going to do?
Find these. Let's go!
[gasps]
[NOZOMI]
That looks like--
Is that a Moonlight Stone?