[NARRATOR]
Ten years had passed
since the end of
the Great Tokyo War.
The conflict's aftermath
was unresolved.
Most of the country's leaders,
its ruling class,
and its wealthiest
members vanished.
Disappearing, it seemed,
into thin air.
Japan's newly reorganized states
divided themselves back up
into their old prefectures.
Except now,
they were independent!
Each region embraced
its own unique identity,
pulling away from the others.
It was a time of swift and
exciting change for everyone.
However...
the peace of this new age
was fleeting
Countless seeds of unrest
soon began to sprout.
A people who once understood
the value of community
began to prioritize the needs
of the individual.
Unity and cohesion
were quickly replaced
by isolation and exclusivity.
And then,
vigilante groups developed,
ostensibly to promote
peace among
and within the new nations.
But their violent roots
are still evident,
revealed as they slash their way
through the newly divided land.
Well, Peacebroker Maccha Green,
today is an exciting day.
After I'm done
wiping the floor with you,
I'm going to rip off
that mask of yours.
And then
that high-tech battle suit
will have a worthier owner
I think it's going to make
a perfect addition
to my collection.
[NARRATOR]
The Armed Empress,
Kuniko Shigyo.
It doesn't have to end this way.
We can resolve this with words
instead of with violence.
[NARRATOR]
Peacebroker-for-hire,
Maccha Green!
You're not serious, are you?
I am!
As we speak,
my squad members
are preparing a picnic.
We shouldn't waste
such a beautiful day fighting.
Let us drink tea
and discuss peace instead.
You have to be kidding me,
Tokorozawa punk.
You're the one
who picked a fight with us.
It's too late for talking now.
Villain of Higashi Murayama,
you threatened our safety first.
In the interest of justice,
President Misono abides by
the Twin Tower Declara--
[OTONASHI]
Yeah, yeah,
we know what
the Declaration says.
Fighting should be settled
by diplomatic means.
If not, then it's left up to
the representatives
of the state vigilante squads.
Now just shut up
and let Shigyo crush you.
Your time's over.
Higashi Murayama has merged
with the penal colony
of Tokyo kids from the north
of the old capital,
and we're ready
to make Tokorazawa ours!
Just surrender, okay?
Now this is the part
I don't understand.
As far as I can remember,
most people considered
Higashi Murayama
to be part of Saitama,
rather than Tokyo.
Your geography seems
a bit fuzzy.
[shouting]
Whatever!
We still want to say that we're
residents of old Tokyo
We don't want to be known
as some piece of Saitama.
[SUMIRE] You can be
part of old Tokyo, too.
Just surrender Tokorozawa.
Go on, surrender!
There, y'see?
Wait, wait, wait,
that makes no sense!
Aren't you already separated
from Tokyo?
Why can't we just leave
each other in peace?
[shouting]
Well, it's not like
I'm doing this because
I actually care about
what happens
to these other people.
[gasps]
As a matter of fact,
the real reason I'm doing this
is you,
another leader for hire.
A thorn in my side.
I want you gone!
[NARRATOR]
Fighters like these two here
are known as "The Best."
[screaming]
And these others here
are known as "The Rest."
[GIRL] I'm serious.
I heard it was super cute.
[GIRL 2] Oh, really?
I wish I saw it!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
[screaming]
[GIRL 3] Anyway,
like I was saying, I said--
[GIRL 4]
See ya!
[GIRL 3]
Jeez, does she run everywhere?
This sucks!
We're only here
in the first place
because damn "Always Comima"
keeps expanding!
[grunts]
Those comic-obsessed jerks
drove the rest of us
who're originally from Tokyo
into the northern corner.
We had no choice
but to become our own state.
[crying]
Maccha Punch!
Maccha Combo!
Shigyo!
Leave now, Empress.
Tokorozawa isn't yours.
[humming]
[meows]
[HINAYO]
Here you go!
I hope we'll be seeing you again
very soon!
Oh, ah!
[NOZOMI]
Hey, I'm home!
[HINAYO]
Hi, how was school?
There's dango cooking.
I'm fine, thanks.
Why don't you wash up
anyway though, okay?
[NOZOMI]
Was that a customer before?
Huh?
You know, that girl
in the weird mask.
Yeah. She comes by the shop
occasionally for takoyaki.
[NOZOMI]
Oh, yeah?
I wonder why
she wears that thing.
Who knows?
Maybe it's fashionable.
Where's Dad's motorcycle?
Masa take it?
[HINAYO] Yeah.
With the Kitama Dangers
from Higashi Murayama
attacking so much,
it's getting hard on her.
[NOZOMI]
State vigilante squad captains
have a lot to do.
[HINAYO]
She went to pick up
that Best she knows
who's been helping out.
Do you know if her place
is very far away from here?
I'm not sure.
Seems like it.
[HINAYO]
Best or not,
she should really
take the train.
She's not the only one
who's busy.
That's why
I'm helping out, starting today!
Masa finally said I could.
Isn't that great?
Look!
My squad jacket and ID!
[giggling]
I want you to be careful, okay?
Without the
Twin Tower Declaration,
you wouldn't even be able
to walk outside.
[NOZOMI]
I know, I know.
[HINAYO]
And make sure
you do what Masami and the other
squad members tell you to do.
You're just an apprentice,
after all.
[NOZOMI] Not an apprentice, Mom.
A trainee.
[HINAYO] Don't get too close
to fights between Bests, either.
[NOZOMI]
Calm down. I won't.
Nozomi, are you doing all this
just because you
want to be near Masami?
No, not 'cause
I want to be near her.
Because I want to help her.
Yet you just can't bring
yourself to cook
a single dango skewer,
can you?
[MAN]
Thanks, that was great!
Thank you for coming!
We'll see you again soon, okay?
Ow!
I thought you said
you didn't want any.
Well. Let's see what
the damage is this time.
Spectacularly average.
As usual.
[giggles]
Oh hey, I need you to make
more dango and taiyaki.
And some takoyaki, too!
[screaming]
[HITOSHI]
Hey, Nozomi.
Nozomi Moritomo,
reporting for duty!
Hey, everyone!
[NOBORU]
Nozomi, hey!
[YUMI] What are you doing here?
It's dangerous.
I thought you guys
could use some snacks.
[MIITAN]
Oh! Dango from Moritomo!
[MACCHA GREEN]
Maccha Bomber!
[screaming]
[MACCHA GREEN]
Nozomi?
Now, let's see
what this mask is hiding.
C'mon.
Show me your real face!
[MACCHA GREEN]
Stop it!
I can't breathe in here.
It's so stuffy.
This fancy suit of yours
is going to be all mine!
Otonashi, come help me.
Right!
[MACCHA GREEN]
Can't last much longer.
[laughing]
Hey, stop!
That isn't fair!
Tickling so isn't cool!
[OTONASHI]
I'm coming!
[MACCHA GREEN]
Need to get out.
But I can't, everyone's here,
and I thought I heard Nozomi.
This is Maccha Green!
Do you copy?
Hm? What now?
She could be calling
her other squadron members!
--Huh?
--I think it's possible.
It's pretty unusual to see Green
working without the others.
[MACCHA GREEN]
Hyper Maccha Robot.
Initiate attack!
[robot voice]
Roger.
She's got a robot with her?
There was no information
on that!
Well apparently the thing's
in "hyper" mode!
[robot voice]
Will be arriving shortly
at Mount Hachikoku.
I'll take care of them.
Uh, what should we do now?
We'll deal with them
some other time.
Right, got it.
Retreat!
[MASAMI]
Nozomi. You alive?
Hey Masa.
You were supposed to be at HQ.
I said you could help
with the beautification
of the city, remember?
Yeah, I thought I could do more
here, though.
[MASAMI]
You should always stay away
from where the Bests
are fighting!
--Captain!
--Are you okay?
--Glad you're all right.
--Where's Maccha Green?
Oh, she's already
on her way home.
She did ask me
to tell everyone "hi," though.
[NOZOMI]
Where does Maccha Green live?
You went to pick her up today,
didn't you?
[MASAMI]
Huh?
Oh, it's, uh, near Kusunokidai,
or around there.
Oh!
That's really close!
I can go and get her
for you next time!
Yeah. Except she's really shy
about that kind of thing.
Really?
That's weird.
Well. Okay, then how about
I drive you to your house
right now? We can switch!
[MASAMI]
I'm fine.
That's more excitement
than I was after.
[NOZOMI]
That's mean!
I guess I am a pretty awful
driver though.
I really want you
to stop going to
dangerous places all the time,
'kay?
Fine. I mean, you got
Maccha Green and all
the other Propellers, so what
would you need me for, right?
Some puny Rest
who's no good for anything.
Hey, that's not what I mean.
I'm okay out there because
I have this with me.
The Moonlight Stone!
You still have it?
You kidding?
'Course I do!
After all,
it's my good luck charm.
[WOMAN]
We all really appreciate
your hard work, dearie.
Just doing our job!
[HARUKA] More jobs for you.
They just keep coming in.
I think it was the cease-fire
in the Mount Fuji ownership
rights case that really did it.
Brokering that arrangement
is what got Maccha Green known
in the west, as well.
Oh, that? Yeah, I heard it
was a feud between two girls
who were practically sisters,
so that one was kinda
second nature to me.
Anyway, will you see to
these new jobs?
Once you're done dealing with
the Kitama Dangers, of course.
I, uh, I'd really prefer
to focus on peace
in Tokorozawa if I can.
Look at the big picture
It amounts to the same thing
in the end.
I hope you know
I expect great things from you.
And your devotion to Tokorozawa.
Yes, ma'am.
[phone ringing]
[CROCODILE]
Um, hello?
[YUMI] The station roundabout
and Propel Street are all clear!
--Oh, hi, yeah, sure.
--Nothing to report.
Aviation Memorial Park
is clear, too.
[MIITAN]
Sayama Lakeshore and
Yamaguchi Kannon Temple
look beautiful!
All right.
You can take turns eating lunch,
but I want somebody on guard
at all times, okay?
[MARIO] Den-san.
Here's the bill from Takumi Co.
That was fast. And expensive!
We got the cheaper one, too!
Uh, excuse me! I can go
on patrol, too, if you'd like!
[CROCODILE]
The captain says she got hungry
on the way back
from the president's office,
so she's going to
stop by Maboroshiken.
[crash]
[NOBORU]
Is someone attacking HQ?
Hey, are you okay?
That was rough!
I need water.
Thank you. It's been three days
and three nights now.
I'm looking for the headquarters
of the vigilante squad
the Hiyoshicho Propellers.
[ALL]
Huh?
No! What is it?
Do I still have far to go?
Nope!
It's here. Right here.
[HITOSHI]
Good job! You did it!
You made it safe and sound!
So, it's really over!
[YUMI]
Congratulations!
[MIITAN] Yay!
You can relax now!
Thank you all so much!
So where'd you come from?
It must've been a long way!
Keyakidai.
[ALL]
Wait! What?
[RIKAKO]
That took three days?
[SHOP OWNER]
Here. Eat up.
Don't mind if I do!
Welcome to--
[gasps]
Hi there, boss.
I'll take a ramen
with miso and beef tendon.
Please! You think I'd serve
ramen to the hired leader
of Higashi Murayama?
Oh, add some onions, yeah?
Sure.
Coming right up.
Is that all it takes, wuss?
Hey. Could you clear
something up, Masami?
I've been wondering.
Are you Maccha Green?
[MASAMI]
Did she see?
Otonashi from my squad says so
and now that I think about it,
there is something
similar about your voices.
Besides which, I've never seen
the two of you
in the same place.
Seems kind of strange to me.
Oh, that's just a coincidence.
She's really impatient.
She leaves me behind,
that's all.
Uh-huh.
Here's your ramen.
It looks amazing, boss,
thank you.
[explosion]
[MASAMI]
Okay, good!
It doesn't look like anybody
saw anything.
Still, I need to eat as quick
as I can and get out of here
before Shigyo does.
[SHIGYO]
Oh, yeah?
Good stuff, gotta-- huh?
[SHIGYO] Thanks, boss.
I'll take another, too.
[DEN-SAN]
Here you go. Your squad ID.
Here!
Your jacket.
--Oh, I...
--So Yukina,
I'm glad you were able to
find us.
My name's Nozomi Moritomo.
I'm a new squad trainee, too.
It's nice to meet you.
Uh, you, too.
[CROCODILE]
Just one thing.
Minors need permission
from their parents to join up.
So think you can
get this signed?
Well, uh, actually,
that's not why I'm here.
[honking]
Hey you guys? I think that bus
is out there for us.
I may vomit.
Thanks for the food.
[shouts]
Don't worry,
I don't count that
little contest as a win for us.
Give Maccha Green a message.
You can tell her this--
whoever's inside of it--
that precious little battle suit
of hers is going to be mine.
Soon.
Well,
see ya at the amusement park!
[engine revs]
No.
There's no way.
[screaming]
So, how did it go?
Went off without a hitch.
--That was amazing!
--I've always wanted to see
what this one was like!
I can't believe
we never come here.
It's so close!
I wish the captain
was here with us, though.
[CROCODILE]
Don't worry, she'll be along.
The two rookies
stayed behind to make sure she--
Wa-hoo!
Do you want to ride it again?
Sure,
sounds like a great idea.
--Nope. They're right here.
--It's okay!
I left a message back at HQ.
Oh well. What I'd like to know
is who the heck planned
this fancy amusement park
visit for us, anyway.
Yeah.
I guess maybe the captain did?
Hey! Check it out!
Hey, doesn't that look like?
Those are the guys
from Higashi Murayama!
The enemy Rest are now
entirely at our mercy.
This is totally the perfect bait
to trap Maccha Green.
[explosion]
[gasps]
Hey, what's going on here?
[screaming]
No matter how often I see it,
it's still beautiful.
This, you mean?
My good luck charm.
It's very precious to me.