Ah! [screams]
[whimpers]
[MAMORU] You're ten years
too early to put
--a shachihoko on the roof!
--[whimpers]
That's how we advertise
the quality of our work!
Oh, calm down.
What's the big deal?
Everybody in this town
already has confidence
in the Uotoras' skill.
Well, I think it's cute.
Like father, like daughter.
Right, Hime, dear?
She has to start off
somewhere, I guess.
I wouldn't call
that thing a shachihoko.
How about we go
with "shachipoko" instead?
"Shachipoko," huh?
That's pretty good!
[laughter]
[DANDY] Don't worry.
It'll be good as new.
[YOUNG TOMOKI]
I don't care. I'm done.
[DANDY] Hmm?
I'm through racing.
I don't like it anymore.
[DANDY] Some days are like that.
I don't get it. You really like
shachihoko that much?
Yeah. I love them!
I'm gonna make the gold shachi
for the castle one day.
It's everyone's guardian god.
Did you know that?
Hmm.
You love them. Huh!
Hmm!
[gasps]
Wow! It's so pretty!
--Hey, I know! Here, have it!
--Huh?
You saved me when I fell,
so I want you to have
this stone. Thank you!
All right, then. I guess
I'll give this one to you.
No way! They look the same!
Go on, take it.
You helped me remember
something important,
so thank you.
--[giggles]
--By the way,
I call it Star of the Circuit.
What's yours called?
Uh... hmm... ah!
I'll call it Shachipoko Stone!
[HIMEKO] You're the captain
of the Motors?
That's surprising.
We weren't the ones who
broke the shachihoko, promise!
But I guess
it makes total sense
that we're being blamed
for it anyway.
Oh, and... I'm sorry.
Huh?
I used your name
without asking
to request assistance
from a peacebroker.
I couldn't let my squad
find out about it.
Guess that was
a waste of my time, though.
My plan was
to pay the peacebroker
using this stone.
I thought maybe,
with some luck from that
guardian god you mentioned--
Sorry. Since it was
a gift, and all.
It's okay.
You should have said something
when you gave me a ride
on that bike taxi of yours.
--Hello, and welcome!
--[TOMOKI] Oh. Yeah.
I just couldn't believe
how pretty you'd gotten.
--Huh?
--Oh! I mean,
not that you weren't pretty
before. It's just, you know.
--Right. Of course!
--Thanks for waiting!
It's so nice over here!
Getting cozy, I see!
You should skip the dating part
and go straight to the wedding!
Uh, yeah, please just
leave us alone, okay?
So, uh, it must be
a hard job being captain.
The rule is whoever's fastest
has to be the captain.
I'm just a figurehead,
that's all.
Fastest racer?
Then you were able to become
the Star of the Circuit,
after all?
Mmm. Oh, yeah.
Why isn't the star
riding any races lately?
--That's what I'd like to know.
--Yeah, tell me about it!
When you were
competing regularly,
it kept those guys
in line a little bit.
--[sighs]
--Enough about me,
do you know all about
making a guardian god now?
You went off on a journey
to train, right?
Uh, yeah.
[switch clicks]
--She's here!
--Where were you?
[shivering] So cold.
[AI]
We've been looking all over!
When I woke up, I was...
[sneezes]
What's going on?
Oh my goodness.
You're like ice!
Why're you so cold?
I'll go and get a hot bath
started for her.
Listen, Yukina, do you think
you can bring something ho--
Oh, Lord. Did we lose her, too?
I mean, I'm worried
about Chiaya, too.
But don't you think you've been
driving a little fast, Nozomi?
I mean, we don--
What's that you're sayin'?
[YUKINA] Whoa, hey,
what's going on? Who're you?
[MAN] I could ask you
the same thing, sweetie.
[sighs]
[NOZOMI] Okay, you hold down
the fort here. I'll be back!
Yukippe's the one
who's gone missing now?
Won't she find
her way back eventually?
[phone rings]
Who'd be calling
the café this late?
Yeah, hello?
This is Dandy's place.
How can I help you?
[MEN groaning]
It's those Mie guys again.
You can bet they're to blame!
[scoffs]
[MEN arguing]
We've gotta find Dandy
and tell him what's going on.
--[tires screech]
--[gasps]
[NOZOMI]
Himeko! And, uh...
[TOMOKI]
Are you the peacebrokers
who came here
in Maccha Green's place?
[YUKINA]
Where am I? I can't tell!
Maybe if there was
a landmark or something.
[sighs]
Oh, hey, is that...?
[TOMOKI]
I'm sorry about this.
I really never thought
they would go so far.
[DANDY] Our people
were just as culpable.
[TOMOKI]
They want me to agree to a race
so we can decide this
once and for all.
[DANDY] A race fueled
by anger and hatred
won't help anyone in the end.
It would be futile.
[DANDY] I can't believe
that boy grew up to become
captain of the Mie Motors.
I was there. I cheered you on.
[TOMOKI]
That was nice of you.
It's been a while now
since you've raced.
Without you in it,
people don't get as excited
about the Grand Prix.
Racing just started
to feel so empty.
No one could compete
with me, you know?
Yeah, that is a shame.
Um, excuse me.
From what I can tell,
you two seem
to be on good terms.
If that's the case, why don't
you sit down as captains
and discuss how to make peace
between the people
in your regions?
Then, when everyone's happy,
--you can give us the st--
--Shut up!
What? That's how
these things work, right?
[BOTH grunt]
Is this the payment
for your services?
Um, apparently,
that was what was promised.
Then here,
go ahead and take it.
--I hope you can help them.
--Score!
[TOMOKI] What are you doing?
I'm the client here, aren't I?
So it's up to me.
Anyway, that stone
isn't something
I think I'm going
to need anymore.
[HATSUE]
That you, Hime?
[HIMEKO] Uncle, Auntie,
what're you doing here?
Your father. He was admitted
to the hospital last night.
[BOTH] Huh?
[HATSUE] They're saying
he strained his back.
Will you bring these to him?
Sorry, no.
Could you do it, Auntie?
[DANDY] Himeko, wait.
You're a shachihoko artisan,
a maker of our guardian gods.
Maybe there's something
that you can do to help.
You must feel the same.
Isn't that why
you returned home?
Well, I guess
I got ahead of myself.
[motorcycle approaches]
[engine revving]
There's no choice. It would be
too dangerous for us to hold
the race with everybody's
emotions running so high.
[engine revving]
I told you,
I won't sign off on it.
Um. Hey guys? Before any talk
about racing, what if we all
helped come up with
a new name for this country?
[engine revving]
If you could decide on a name,
don't you think everyone
would get along better?
Something neutral
to both sides, maybe?
Yeah, like, uh-- well, um...
The Let's All
Be Friends Republic.
Or The Smile Federation?
Or how about the Land
of Shachihoko and Circuits?
[engine revving]
Very well, then.
I accept your request.
Oh, no! Not you, too?
[engine revving]
Oh! It's Yukippe!
[gasps] I found everyone!
It's finally over.
[AI] See? I told you
she'd find her way back to us.
Right. Sure I did. I have
a way with directions, you know.
[MAN]
It's a lost cause.
The captain's never gonna
give his okay for this.
[engine revving]
[TOMOKI]
This is him?
[engine revving]
Yeah, but no one's seen
Motoya in a long time.
[engine revving]
I dunno. I can't see his face,
but yeah, maybe a little bit.
[engine revving]
[engine revving, AKOGI laughs]
Huh?
[engine revving]
You were lying?
[grunts]
[REPORTER on TV] Tomoki Suzuka
is withdrawing, you say?
As vice-captain, will you be
racing in his place?
[engine revving, crowd gasping]
[CROWD] Oh!
[REPORTER 2] Dandy, do you have
a response to this statement?
[DANDY] People of Old Aichi,
people of Old Mie,
I would like to find
a better solution
for our coexistence.
That is why I race.
[AI] Hey, we've got
the stone already, don't we?
Let's just move on
to the next city.
Besides, Dandy said
not to get involved any more.
[NOZOMI] We can't
abandon them like that!
We have to help them
make peace
somehow before we even think
about leaving.
And what exactly are we supposed
to do to make things better?
[NOZOMI]
I don't know yet.
The order's up for table three.
[NOZOMI] We can't take the stone
unless we actually do something.
It's not right.
Oh no, it went everywhere!
[AI] She's too honest
for her own good.
[KOKICHI] Here's a question,
can Dandy even ride
a motorcycle?
[YASUO] Don't think I've
ever seen him on one before.
[REPORTER] Looks like it's going
to be a one-on-one road race.
They'll start at Matsusaka
and ride to the reclaimed land
of Kisosaki at the old border,
where they'll pick up the items
they wish to place
on Nagoya Castle.
First to the castle wins.
[REPORTER 2] Whoa.
Hold on. You said "items."
Does that mean it's possible
they won't be shachihoko?
--[GROUP] Huh?
--That's the craziest thing
I've ever heard! The castle
tower has to have shachihoko!
But the Uotora artisan is out
with an injury, isn't he?
If he can't do it,
then who else could make them?
[GROUP] Mm-hmm.
[GIRLS sigh]
[gasps]
I almost forgot.
I found this when I was out.
[AI] Why does it say "fish"?
[NOZOMI] I think I know
who this belongs to.
Let's go to the hospital.
--Is that you, Himeko?
--[gasps]
I'm sorry
for slapping you before.
[NOZOMI] Huh?
[MAMORU]
Was it my fault somehow
that you started
to hate them so much?
[MAMORU] I don't understand
what happened.
You loved shachihoko
since you were little.
Always sitting there
beside me in the workshop
like my shadow,
copying what I did.
My Himeko.
The soul of the artisan
lives in the shachihoko,
did you know that?
It's why they're all different
from one another.
No one else can make the
shachihoko with your soul in it.
Only you can create that.
--[muffled crying]
--[MAMORU] Everyone is waiting
to see your shachihoko.
I believe in you.
Just do your best.
[crying]
[MAMORU]
Huh? Who are you?
[AI]
I'm so sorry!
[BOTH grunting]
Hmm. What's going on?
Those girls again.
They're working in Hime's place.
[CHIAYA grunting]
[GROUP] Hmm.
We're finally done!
[ORCA calling]
[GROUP] An orca?
[gasps]
[AI] What? Did
we get it wrong?
It should be more of a fish
and less of a whale.
[NOZOMI and AI]
Seriously? Are you sure?
It's alright, guys. I think
I can take it from here.
[AKOGI speaks muffled]
[GUY] Personally, I think
shachihoko make the most sense.
--How about you?
--[GUY 2] Same here.
[engine revving]
[REPORTER] I think everyone'll
want to take a look at this.
Exclusive coverage of the shachi
that will be used
in the upcoming race.
Everyone's sleeping.
They must be exhausted!
It looks like they literally
just finished it.
--[distant siren]
--[HIMEKO] Hmm?
[REPORTER] Let's all take
a moment to admire
the completed Uotora shachihoko!
What?
--[ALL] Huh?
--You can't be serious.
This is quite a creation.
I wonder
if the Aichi Tenmusus plan
to put it
on the Nagoya Castle tow--
No, stop! Don't show it! Please!
--Get out!
--This isn't it, people!
--Go on! Scoot!
--[AKOGI] That decides it.
[grunts]
[snoring]
Mmm.
Someone else has arrived
and begun working.
Let's get an interview. Miss?
[REPORTERS shouting]
--[motorcycles revving]
--[countdown beeping]
[AKOGI] What?
Uh...
[AKOGI]
How is he going so fast?
Oh!
Wait!
[CROWD chattering]
[MAN] Hey!
Check out that number!
[MAN 2] Seventy-four
was retired years ago!
[MAN 3]
Is it really Daijiro Motoya?
There's no way, is there?
[moans, gasps]
[gasps]
[cheering]
This is crazy!
--[TOMOKI] Hey.
--[BOTH] Mmm?
There's something I gotta do.
Think you could untie me?
[AKOGI] Whoa!
[CROWD]
[MAN]
Hey! It's Suzuka!
[MAN 2]
It's Tomoki Suzuka!
--[GUY] Motoya and Suzuka!
--[GUY 2] No way!
This is a cross-generational
dream match!
[cheering]
[NOZOMI]
A little more! That's good!
[inspirational song playing]
[HIMEKO thinking]
I loved shachihoko.
It was that simple.
But as I grew, all I could
think about was how
to live up to Daddy's work.
I got tired.
[TOMOKI thinks]
I loved racing.
It was that simple.
But over time, things changed.
It became empty,
and maybe that'll happen again.
[BOTH think]
But still, I love this!
Hmm.
[gasps]
--You can't leave yet, sir!
--[grunts]
[AKOGI] Damn it!
I gotta do something!
[TOMOKI screams]
[CROWD cheering]
[AKOGI] I'm gonna win this
for old Mie!
[DANDY]
Looks like you're not hurt.
--Huh?
--Go on then, take my bike.
But I'm the captain
of the rival squad, I can--
[DANDY] Do you really think
that stuff matters?
Go on, kid. This is a feeling
I'd like to savor for a while.
[humphs]
[GIRLS]
Drive safely!
[MAMORU humphs]
[gasps]
[HIMEKO]
What are you--
Himeko, you lost your nerve
at an important moment,
didn't you?
Come on. Let's get started.
The usual shachihoko
isn't suited to become
the guardian god
of this country's future.
[gasps, grunts]
[grunts]
[AKOGI grunts]
[TOMOKI] Hmm?
[TOMOKI grunting]
[AKOGI] Huh? Passed
by a bicycle? No way!
[shouts]
[AKOGI gasps, shouts]
[AKOGI] Damn it!
[gasps]
[grunting]
[gasps, grunts] Go!
[CROWD cheering]
[grunts]
[shouts]
[screams]
[cheering]
[grunts]
[CROWD] Huh?
Look at that. They've varied
the color pattern a bit.
--Looks like a checkered flag.
--[murmuring]
[screams]
[gasps]
[KANTARO]
I can't see! What is it?
[HATSUE] A motorcycle
and a jumbo fried shrimp?
[YASUO] Not sure how much
I like that, really.
[KOKICHI] Looks weird,
but it conveys
unity and friendship and stuff.
[groans]
[cheering]
We did it. I guess I really did
need your help in the end.
Yeah. Well, I had
a promise to keep.
[HIMEKO] Huh?
[YOUNG HIMEKO]
I'm gonna make shachihoko, too!
[MAMORU]
Oh, yeah?
[YOUNG HIMEKO] I'll be
just like you when I grow up!
But I don't wanna make
a guardian god alone.
We'll do it together, 'kay?
[sighs] A long time ago.
I'm not surprised
if you don't remember.
[cheering]
[chuckling]
[CHIAYA and AI laugh]
[gasps]