[music playing]
Oh, hey. Who're you?
[WOMAN]
Pardon me, Mamechiyo.
--Mmm?
--It appears that the captain
of the Kamogawa Rockrs
has been returned.
[MISA] A bit of a treat
for saving me.
Ah!
Guys, we didn't
actually do anything.
True, Shuten said
you could leave.
--It wasn't anything we did.
--Ah!
What she means to say is,
it may not
have looked like much,
but we rescued you
from Shuten's gang
and basically saved
the festival, right?
Mm-hmm.
That means one stone
for us! Woo!
[MISA] Doji Shuten
is still up to something,
but it'll be all right.
Concert security
should be able to--
Mmm. Mmm!
Nice bracelet. What's that charm
you have on it?
Is it a Moonlight--
sorry, I mean a jinxed stone?
[chuckles]
A jinxed stone, yes.
People say
they bring illness and death
to the ones who possess them.
--Really?
--[chuckles]
Only superstition,
I'm sure.
--Look over there.
--[NOZOMI] Huh?
Oh, hey. Doesn't that
look like Mamechiyo?
[YUKINA]
She's kinda staring at us.
[AI] Do you think
we should invite her over here?
Hey, there! If you wan--
Please pretend
you didn't notice her.
She actually thinks
she's being quite stealthy.
Wow, it's a maiko!
Oi, mates!
We could use some help here.
Are any of you good at drawing?
[SHEENA] This is all that's
finished on the program cover.
Ebisu, the guitarist,
was working on it,
but he's gonna be out of
commission for a while.
Yukina, why don't
you finish it up?
With the sketches
already done,
it shouldn't be
too difficult to do!
[BOTH]
Oh, really?
A clean-up job?
I think I should be able
to handle that for you guys.
[grunts, pants]
-Um. Mamechiyo, was it?
-What are you doing here?
Uh... ooh.
[gasps, grunts]
Are you trying
to become friends with Misa?
--[GROUP] Huh?
--[breathing angrily]
No! I most certainly am not!
[sighs]
[YUKINA] I don't understand.
I thought it looked pretty good.
[ALL] Uh...
Well, we could always go
with a silhouette.
Maybe they just wanted you
to follow the sketch more.
Yeah, I figured.
That's what I was trying to do.
--Uh...
--Don't worry about it.
I'm used to this
kind of thing.
[BOTH laugh nervously]
--Come on, Yukippe. Let's go.
--Go where?
--[AI] Whoa, look at me!
--[NOZOMI] I know! Totally cute!
[clicking]
[MOMIYAMA] No. Unfortunately,
I couldn't find Chiaya.
But I did notice the Shuten gang
on Mount Oe acting suspiciously.
The Hall
of the Lotus Queen, huh?
[MOMIYAMA] I thought
you'd want me to look into it.
[HARUKA] I can't imagine
what they would be doing.
I don't think anyone else
knows how to use the stones.
[MOMIYAMA]
Whether they do or not,
I'm sure they're gathering them.
If I play my cards right,
I may be able to bring
them all back with me.
[HARUKA] There's not much time
left until the full moon.
Just hurry, all right?
[MAMECHIYO] There's still
something I don't understand.
Why kidnap
the Kamogawa captain?
[sighs] I told you,
I was only killing time.
And did she, perhaps,
say anything about me?
--No, not a word.
--[whimpers]
Well. Tell me, Shuten,
what surprise have you
prepared for us? Or need I ask?
One of your clever toys,
I suppose?
You'll just have to wait
and see like everyone else.
--Boo!
--[chuckles]
Scaring Misa
isn't my only objective.
I intend to blow
the entire festival away.
Blow it away?
Takumi Co.'s
greatest masterpiece,
the Kiyomizu Temple's
fan-shaped stage.
I've joined forces
with some blokes
who are interested
in destroying it.
[humphs]
We've modified
the Hall of the Lotus Queen's
Thousand Armed Kannon a touch.
[MAMECHIYO]
What's wrong?
I told you I don't hold back
when I'm killing time.
This should be interesting.
[BOTH laugh]
You're quite the joker!
That sense of humor will
get you in trouble some day.
Your plan is impossible.
Not to mention dull.
--[gasps]
--[echoing] Not to mention dull.
[SHUTEN thinks]
"Dull"? Me? "Dull"?
Well, we'll see about that.
Tell Takumi we need
something more sensational!
[SQUAD]
Yes, sir!
[GIRLS moaning]
[TSURUHA] This is unacceptable.
We can't have impostors
wandering about.
It will undermine the dignity
of the geisha district.
[NOZOMI]
We didn't mean to.
[CHIAYA] We were
just looking for somebody.
[MAMECHIYO]
What is the commotion about?
They were
sitting around in Gion.
We thought it best
to bring them back here.
[CHIAYA gasps]
That looks just like
the other Core.
Did you and the Rockrs' captain
have a falling out or something?
--No, why?
--She completely blew you off.
And what is that to do with you?
Well, was it a misunderstanding?
Maybe there's a reason she--
What sort of reason?
Oh. I don't really
know that, exactly.
It's just a feeling I had.
[MAMECHIYO]
No. I don't think so.
[rock music playing]
[no discernible dialog]
[pants] I'll need a sec
to catch my breath.
I think you need more
than a sec for that.
It's too bad Momizo
isn't singing.
Then it would be
a Momi-Ham reunion!
[MA-BO] Misa! Stop that.
We don't talk about him.
Be honest, Ma-bo. You want
to perform again, don't you?
[MA-BO]
Who said that?
[MISA] Han-chan has told me
a few things about the band,
like the real reason
that you guys broke up.
He said that there was bad blood
because of a member who hit the
road before your major debut.
[MA-BO] Why're you
telling people about that?
Momizo fired him
without asking us.
There was no good reason to.
Dude would have improved,
given a little time.
I'm sure he would.
[HAN-CHAN] "A real rocker will
come back and prove his worth."
That's how Momizo felt about it.
[MA-BO]
And I disagreed, but whatever.
In the end, I still wanted us
to play together.
There you have it.
That's why I could never
get rid of these sideburns.
[humphs]
[BOTH snoring]
I miss you, too.
[AI]
Whoa!
Are these
really Misa's memories?
--Yeah.
--No way.
Where did you get that camera?
It looks like they used
to be really good friends.
They sure aren't anymore.
What happened?
Hey, how much did it cost?
There must be something we can
do to help them reconcile.
[GIRLS snoring]
[AI moans]
Oh!
[JOHNNY] Blimey!
Someone stole your pick?
[moans]
[SHEENA] It was important
to you, wasn't it, Captain?
[grunts]
Yeah, but I'll be okay.
How's everybody else?
Ready to go, I hope.
We've got a big day.
--[SHIDO] Captain!
--[JOHNNY] Oh no!
[NOZOMI]
We'll look for it for you.
We saw it taken. We can help!
--[GROUP gasps]
--You saw who took the pick?
Well, no. It was dark,
but we did see them fall
and hit their forehead.
So, one look at their face,
and we should be able to tell.
[NOZOMI] You guys please keep
getting ready for the festival.
--You sure you got it?
--Yes!
--[rock music playing]
--[CROWD chattering]
[CROWD cheering]
[sighs]
[thunder rumbling]
[BOTH gasp]
Beautiful, aren't they?
And now,
we'll always be best mates!
Yes.
[MISA] Even your maiko training
won't change that.
If this is to be
my only contest,
I just want us
to perform our best.
Yeah, me too.
--[CROWD cheering]
--[gasps]
She's never coming back to me.
She has forgotten me entirely.
Oh, hi, Mamechiyo.
[GIRLS gasp]
Hey! What did
you just throw in there?
Were those the stones?
Why?
I was tired of looking at them.
Without that, the captain
won't be able to do anything!
Isn't it the same for you?
And you know,
there are people
who would have been happy
to have that!
Around here, you think?
Mmm, little more
to the right, maybe?
Wait, what did you mean?
[rain pattering]
[humming]
[beeps]
[humphs]
You said the captain
can't do anything
without the stone.
Can you explain?
She's not going to be able
to be a Best now!
I actually think
it's pretty self-explanatory
Oh, hey! I'm gonna
go look in the boxes.
Who knows, right?
Maybe we'll get lucky
and find one in there!
Sure hope so.
Huh?
[panting]
Hey, give me a ride, will you?
[NOZOMI] Huh?
Why don't we all look together?
[gasps]
--No, thank you. Why should I?
--[NOZOMI] Don't be like that!
You just have to make up!
Real friends fight
all the time, you know!
[CHIAYA]
Please help us!
--[rock music playing]
--[CROWD cheering]
That rock you always wore.
Was it your sideburns?
[gasps]
[SQUAD chuckles]
[SHUTEN] Hello there.
You're the fellow
sniffing around
about the jinxed stones, eh?
Sorry to tell you, my friend,
but there aren't any here.
What do you want those
so-called "jinxed" stones for?
Did you know they're--
There's somebody
who's collecting them, you see.
Oh, wait. Are you looking
for a trip into space, as well?
[grumbles]
[KERUO] Excuse me, sir!
Only-- it's the countdown.
What's wrong?
[crackling]
[MOMIYAMA] It looked
like it could be dangerous.
I thought maybe
I should stop it.
[SHUTEN]
You ruddy bastard!
Now we'll have to fix it!
Bring the user's manual.
I'm not going
to let you ruin my fun.
[AI] Hmm.
Ooh! I think I got one!
[grunts]
Fantastic! Now I'm stuck!
Just a thought, but you might
try opening your hand.
Right, I got good news!
There's a manual button
for emergencies.
--[gasps]
--Well, where is it?
[grunting]
Oh, hey, maybe this button
will open it.
[BOTH shout]
[laughs, gasps]
Score one for the old guy.
[grunts]
[clicks]
[MOMIYAMA] Uh...
[rumbling]
[SQUAD gasps]
[high-pitched humming]
[engines start]
Gimme a break!
Why isn't it opening?
Is it broken?
--[clicking repeatedly]
--C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
--[gasps]
--[groans]
--Hey, stop for a sec, Ai.
--What's up? [yelps]
[MOMIYAMA]
Where's Chiaya Misono?
--She's over there?
--[grunts]
[gasps]
Why's Mother here?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[BOTH] There they are!
[grunting]
[screaming]
[BOTH scream, grunt]
[moaning]
[KIKUSHINO] I was worried
that little friend of yours
would lead you away
from your true calling.
I spoke to her about it.
[gasps]
T'was my duty.
Making you into a full geisha
is my priority, not looking
after your social life.
True, but still--
[KIKUSHINO]
That said, I did not imagine
that she would distance herself
from you so... thoroughly.
A rather simple girl, that one.
[crying]
[splashes, sobbing]
Now I believe this
to be my path.
I know I was meant
to be a geisha.
But, when I was younger,
honestly, I wished to run away.
If Misa hadn't abandoned
our friendship,
I probably would have
remained half-hearted
in my dedication to the art.
[sobs]
Still, surely there was
another way!
Could she not
have explained herself?
She refused to say
even a single word to me.
She's been waiting all this time
for you to become a geisha.
That pick is
all the proof you need.
She has kept it close
throughout these past years,
hoping for your success.
Does that mean nothing to you?
Mamechiyo? Let's go.
We can bring it to her.
[grunts]
[loud boom]
[rockets shrieking]
[gasps]
--Nozomi!
--Big problem!
--[rock music playing]
--[CROWD cheering]
--[loud boom]
--[alarm blaring]
[CROWD screams] Huh?
[CROWD screaming]
[GROUP screams]
--[panting, grunts]
--[beeps]
[CROWD screaming]
[gasps]
--[rock music playing]
--[gasps]
[CROWD] Huh?
[gasps]
Isn't that Ma-bo from Momi-Ham?
Han-can's there, too!
[grunts, gasps]
[gasps]
[MAMECHIYO] Misa.
[music stops]
Uh... [sighs]
[CROWD] Huh?
[gasps]
Hey, is that...?
Looks like Momizo.
It looks like him, but...
[CROWD]
He's gotten fat!
--[MAMECHIYO] Over here, Misa!
--[gasps]
[MISA]
Is that Chiyo?
Misa, I'm-- I'm so sorry!
[grunts]
Huh. [grunts, shouts]
I hope you forgive me, Chiyo!
I'm sorry, too!
[BOTH gasp]
Han-chan, count us off.
--[HAN-CHAN humphs]
--[MA-BO humphs]
[rock music playing]
[CROWD gasps]
[CROWD cheering]
♪ Valleys low ♪
♪ Mountains high ♪
--[CROWD chanting]
--♪ We all go ♪
♪ Far and wide ♪
♪ We will roll ♪
♪ Like a stone ♪
♪ Rivers flow ♪
♪ As we move on ♪
♪ With my empty ♪
♪ Mind I try to think
about what's next ♪
♪ Trying hard to find
what's missing ♪
♪ In that emptiness
of our lives ♪
What do you think?
Not dull, at any rate.
Now let's give them
a good cheer, shall we?
♪ Knowing we could lose
our way so easily ♪
♪ But sometimes loss ♪
♪ Is how you get found ♪
♪ Nameless stones ♪
♪ We're all rolling along ♪
♪ Through the seasons ♪
♪ Of the sun ♪
♪ When the world
kicks you around ♪
♪ Throws you to the ground ♪
♪ You may feel like giving up ♪
♪ Then it's you
that suffers most ♪
♪ So keep rolling ♪
♪ And laugh harder this time ♪
♪ Let your voices ring out ♪
♪ We'll sing out loud today ♪
♪ To tomorrow ♪
♪ Nameless stones buried
deep within the ground ♪
♪ Motionless
and free from sound ♪
♪ Though we may choose
different paths ♪
♪ Will our choices last? ♪
♪ Don't you think
it's early still? ♪
♪ Setting down
and sitting still ♪
♪ I can tell
you need to move ♪
♪ Nameless stones,
we're all rolling along ♪
♪ Through the seasons
of the sun ♪
♪ When the world
kicks you around ♪
♪ Throws you to the ground ♪
♪ You may feel like giving up ♪
♪ Then it's you
that suffers most ♪
♪ So keep rolling ♪
♪ And laugh harder this time ♪
♪ Let your voices ring out ♪
♪ We'll sing out loud today ♪
♪ To tomorrow ♪
[CROWD cheering]
[BOTH] Hmm.
--[crashes]
--Huh?
[humphs]
[GIRLS giggle]
[sighs]
[BOTH giggle]
Uh... [gasps]