[NARRATOR] The land without
honor and humanity: Hiroshima.
The Nayotake Moonlight,
the vigilante squad
that had been responsible
for the land's protection
for many years,
fell victim to internal strife.
During the fight
over the succession
between the head family
and five branch families,
the squad weakened,
and public order degenerated.
[ISHIGAMI CLAN GUY]
Die, ya dirty bastard!
[OTOMO CLAN GUY] Think you
can mess with us, you scum?
Keep screwing with me,
and I'll tear ya to pieces!
There's no other way!
This is how it's gotta be!
[BOTH grunt]
[NARRATOR] As the sun
was setting on the old days,
a young woman appeared,
ready to change
how things were done.
Spitting on the chivalrous ways
of the yakuza,
this pirate girl gathered
her reckless crew
and soon governed
Okonomiyaki Village.
She is the captain
of the Ishizukuri Stones,
Shima Ishizukuri!
Meanwhile, the former
main family, Nayotake,
languished on the fringes
of the village,
struggling to keep
their name alive.
To top it all off, they were
in danger of being evicted.
--[laughing]
--U-tan, wait!
--[AI] Catch!
--[grunts]
Jeez!
--Uck! [coughing]
--[CHIAYA laughing]
The beach is nice and all,
but I'd like
to get going to Hiroshima.
We're headed
to an okonomiyaki shop.
That's the new client, isn't it?
Yeah, and they seemed to need
help sooner rather than later.
--[CHIAYA] Hey, Nonsuke.
--Huh?
[whimpers, screams]
[BOTH laughing]
[giggles, gasps]
You jerks! Ah!
Uh... [sighs]
It's pretty out here.
[NOZOMI]
Like being at a planetarium.
[YUKINA] It'll be a full moon
before much longer.
We're getting to the end.
There's just one stop left
on the peacebroker's list.
--[CHIAYA sighs]
--[AI] I hadn't planned
on going with you
the whole way though, you know?
If only Nozomi
hadn't held back in Kyoto.
Do you mean the stone?
I couldn't have taken it
after what happened.
I mean, come on.
You were the one
who launched
the missiles, remember?
It's not like
I meant to or anything.
And it just made
the festival more exciting--
For something valuable,
there sure are a lot
of those stones around.
You'd think
it'd be the opposite.
Somebody did tell us the stones
were bad for your health.
[AI] I thought that was just
a silly superstition.
Hmm.
It'll all be over soon.
[GIRLS] Huh?
Sorry, talking to myself.
All right, guys.
Let's get to sleep!
We're heading out
at 6:00 a.m. sharp!
[AI] What? That's basically
still nighttime.
[HARUKA] Do you have an update?
Do you know where she is?
[MOMIYAMA] Unfortunately,
I still don't know.
All I can tell you at the moment
is that she entered Okayama.
--[HARUKA] You're lying.
--Huh?
[HARUKA] You're lying to me,
aren't you? I can tell.
You're right, ma'am,
I apologize.
What do you think you're doing?
Encouraging her
to get her license?
Buying her a motorcycle?
[MOMIYAMA] Well, to be fair,
it was actually a hand-me--
That isn't the point,
and you know it.
[sighs]
Momiyama.
I get where you're coming from,
but she seemed
like such a lonely little girl.
She's doing so well
with new environments
and new people, but above all--
well, in all honesty,
I've never seen her
having so much fun.
[sighs]
The next full moon
is almost here.
This happens
once every 415 years.
[MOMIYAMA] I understand.
I hadn't forgotten that.
[HARUKA] Gather as many stones
as you can as soon as possible.
And bring Chiaya back,
you hear me?
[MOMIYAMA]
Yes, ma'am, I do.
[BIRD cawing]
[SHIMA] Hmph. He's cunning,
I'll give him that.
[OTOMO]
What did Shuten do this time?
[SHIMA] Seems he's increased
the price per stone,
and he's not interested
in joining the project.
I'm not surprised.
That's how he is. Ah.
Well, ma'am,
looks like they're here.
A good deal, as always.
Such a pleasure
doing business with you.
You've checked out
the spot, I take it?
--Yes, ma'am!
--And who's going to do it?
I was planning
to take on that responsibility.
Well, let's have a look,
shall we?
From what I can tell,
the hidden room's
in the basement.
[SHIMA]
Yes, so I see.
[GIRLS snoring]
[CHIAYA moans]
--Hmm?
--[GIRLS] Huh?
[CHIAYA whimpering]
[NOZOMI]
Aw man! It's already noon?
Why'd you sleep so late, Ai?
[AI] Not just me! You went back
to sleep, too. Hey, can we stop?
We were in such a hurry,
I didn't eat any breakfast.
[NOZOMI]
Jeez!
[AI] Ah! I'm so full,
I could explode!
All right, let's get
this show on the road!
[gasps] Guys!
We almost left without having
their famous Kibi-dango!
That was a close one!
[GIRLS] All right, everyone!
Let's dig in!
--[AI eating noisily]
--[NOZOMI] Mmm!
--[CHIAYA] Um, Yukippe?
--[YUKINA] Hmm?
I was just wondering
how the rest of you can bear it.
Bear it?
What do you mean?
Do I have to say it?
Come on, you know.
Huh?
That thing
you turn into sometimes,
you know,
when you're not focusing.
It's something you're not
supposed to show other people.
Um... I'm so sorry.
What are you saying?
[sighs]
But we're friends,
so it's not really
that big of a deal, is it?
[chirps]
Uh...
[NOZOMI] Uh...
They're smaller than I expected.
Kind of a let-down.
Sure, go ahead.
Taking the last one never seems
to bother you, does it?
Huh?
Oh, did you want it?
I didn't know that.
Whatever. No big deal.
Uh. I would've let you have it
if you'd said something.
[NOZOMI, angrily]
Like I said, it's no big deal.
What's with you?
You could've eaten it
if you wanted it so bad.
[sighs] Well, Ai, we can always
count on you to be selfish.
--What?
--I mean if you hadn't played
so much at the beach yesterday,
you wouldn't have overslept,
and we'd probably be
in Hiroshima by now.
Hold on, what's that
got to do with anything?
Besides, you were playing
at the beach, too.
Well, maybe,
but that's not the point!
And why bring it up now?
It's not fair
to ambush me like that.
Mention it
when I can change something!
[scoffs] It's not like it's new.
You just do stuff like that!
--[AI] Stuff like what?
--Like, you know. I, um--
well, it's hard
to pin down one thing.
Oh, forget it.
This is getting stupid.
I'll just buy you another one.
Stop! This isn't
about the Kibi-dango!
If we're just airing out
our grievances, I've got one.
You act like your opinion is
the only one that matters,
like you're
the boss or something.
--[gasps]
--You're not my leader.
I didn't come along
to be your lackey. Seriously.
Sometimes you can be really
irritating, you know that?
I... [grumbles]
Um, you guys okay?
Maybe we should go.
U-tan, you shouldn't
say stuff like that.
Here, you can have
my Kibi-dango.
You've got it easy,
just sitting back,
enjoying the ride.
Oh! Oh, well,
sorry for not having my license.
But I still help out by looking
at the map some of the time.
Yeah, until you fall asleep,
and then you just get us lost!
At least I'm not
as bad as Yukina!
[gasps]
I thought you were
better than that, Ai,
but it's becoming pretty obvious
I was wrong about you.
Oh, yeah? What's that
supposed to mean?
Ever since you found out
the truth about the stones,
that's all you ever talk about.
You're the one
who's being unfair.
You wanna get stronger
the easy way!
Fine! But in that case,
all Bests are unfair!
You should have become a Best
from the beginning of all this!
Then maybe you could've been
a half-decent peacebroker.
It doesn't matter
how hard you try!
As a Rest, you'll never
accomplish anything!
[grunts] You don't know
what you're talking about
[CHIAYA] Hold on.
What are you doing?
[grunts] I'm gonna find
a stone by myself. See ya!
[YUKINA and CHIAYA] Huh?
Uh... [humphs]
Don't just stand there!
You have to do something!
--She's going to leave!
--So let her go. I don't care.
Obviously, I'm too irritating
for her to be around.
[AI growls, humphs]
[NOZOMI]
Let's go.
[GUARD] Just you three?
Where's your
other friend at, then?
[NOZOMI] I thought--
how did you know--
[GUARD] Bout yer numbers?
I can see here, plain as day.
You've been traveling
together awhile now.
So, didja get in a fight?
Little verbal rasslin' match?
[NOZOMI] Well, that's not
how I'd put it.
--[YUKINA sighs]
--[CHIAYA] Just three.
[GUARD] Well, welcome to the
land without honor and humanity.
You want my advice?
I'd tell you to eat your
okonomiyaki and move along.
--Come on in, have a taste!
--Best in Hiroshima, guaranteed!
[laughs] Ooh.
[sighs]
[NOZOMI]
Well, here we are.
--[door opens]
--[NOZOMI] Good afternoon!
--Come on in. Hello!
--Welcome. Have a seat.
Thanks,
but we're actually looking
for Ponta, Yasu, and Tsune.
Do those names
sound familiar at all?
We've got some young people here
by those names, in fact.
Mind telling us who you are?
[sizzling]
--It's so good!
--[CHIAYA] Mm-hmm!
There's more if you'd like it.
Kuramochi, don't you think
that's a little much for them?
Oh, it's fine! We've got someone
who can pack it away--
[CHIAYA and YUKINA] Mmm.
Uh. [gulps]
Well, not anymore,
but I'm really hungry.
[FUHITO] You just eat as much
as you want. There's plenty.
You've traveled so far,
you deserve
to be well looked after!
That's them there.
Asked Maccha Green to come, huh?
Probably wanted her help
with a raid, I would say.
[NOZOMI] A raid?
[FUHITO]
Yeah, like a surprise attack.
[GIRLS gasp]
[FUHITO]
Things weren't always like this.
In the past,
a chivalrous yakuza family
called Nayotake
hung their crest here.
Additionally,
it was the headquarters
of the state vigilante squad,
the Nayotake Moonlight.
[NOZOMI]
Oh, yeah? Really?
[FUHITO] They were forced
to relinquish control, though.
Unfortunately, pirates called
the Ishizukuri Stones
are trying to get that license
for themselves now.
They want to force us out
of this location,
so they can build a new landmark
for Okonomiyaki Village,
and Hiroshima's head of state
is allowing it by tacit consent.
--[gasps]
--That's not honorable.
When times change,
you have to change with them.
As you can see,
this young lady has been raised
to show respect
for ways of the past.
However, it is a good
opportunity to move out of here.
But your food is so delicious.
Ha! A takoyaki fan!
Want some more?
--Mm-hmm!
--[FUHITO] Coming right up!
Excuse me, is there anything
we can do to help you?
[FUHITO]
I don't think so, young lady,
but we do appreciate
you asking.
In the letter I think it said
the payment was this stone?
--Oh, um...
--A Core.
--We can't take it.
--[door opens]
[MOMIYAMA] Hello.
Pardon the intrusion.
--[FUHITO] Good afternoon.
--[KAGUYA] Please, come in!
--[gasps] It's Momiyama!
--[YUKINA and NOZOMI] Huh?
--Excuse me.
--[grunts]
Not so fast. There's something
you have to hear, Chiyaya.
Oh, ten orders of pork
okonomiyaki, please.
[door opens]
[MASAMI]
Hey, Shigyo. You doing okay?
I'm healing up. They said
I can leave once this is off.
Still in pretty bad shape?
[sighs]
[MASAMI]
She's faking it?
[OTONASHI] Her injuries
have already healed,
but she doesn't want them
to discharge her.
[MASAMI]
But why not?
I'd think it would
be obvious to you.
--She lost her stone, remember?
--Oh.
[OTONASHI] It wouldn't be good
for Shigyo if it became known
that she wasn't a Best anymore.
The people she hurt
in the past might decide
now's a good time
to settle some scores.
Uh... I'll see if there's
something I can do about that.
[whispers]
I'll talk to the president.
I bet she has some extra.
[OTONASHI]
President Misono?
She seems to be collecting them.
That's what she asks
people for as payment
whenever I do work
as a peacebroker.
[OTONASHI]
There's that many stones?
Enough for her to be making
a collection of them?
Well, just think about it.
At the very least,
there must be
as many as there
are Bests, right?
[OTONASHI] I guess you're right.
I wonder what they are.
[MASAMI]
I couldn't say.
All I know is they're mysterious
stones that fall from the sky.
[OTONASHI grunts]
[YUKINA] Chief Secretary
of the President of Tokorozawa?
I still can't believe Chi's
the president's daughter.
It's crazy.
[MOMIYAMA]
You've been gone awhile now.
Your mother's worried about you.
Well, I'm not going home yet.
How did you find out about
the Cores in the first place?
I wasn't spying or anything,
but I overheard you and Mom
talking about them.
You said you needed
to gather a lot.
Then one morning
I found one, too.
I wanted to give it to her.
[MOMIYAMA] You thought
you'd help collect them?
Mm-hmm, but if we got
the stones, the trip would end.
I was having a good time,
so I changed my mind.
--Hey, Momiyama.
--Mmm?
Is having one of those stones
really what makes
somebody a Best?
And why does Mom want
to collect them so badly?
--You do deserve the truth.
--Huh?
There's so much
I need to explain,
so please just listen for now.
[KAGUYA]
Thank you for stopping by.
[MOMIYAMA] I've arranged
a place for you to stay tonight.
Please wait there
until I pick her up.
I'm entrusting you
with the safety
of the president's daughter.
Don't give me cause
to regret that.
Right. Of course not.
There was a fourth girl,
wasn't there? Where is she?
Oh! Oh, we had a little fight.
It was nothing major, really.
[AI eating noisily]
--[rustling]
--Hmm?
[rustling continues]
[screeches]
[whimpers, screams]
--[beeps]
--[wooshes]
Uh?
--[punch thwacks]
--[body thuds]
[GUARD] Hey, Fatcho.
Time to switch.
Worried about
what's gonna happen
to that old man
and his store?
Hey, listen, you guys
should go on without me.
There's something
that I have to do.
--[BOTH] Huh?
--I have to go back
and look for U-Tan!
--[NOZOMI] Chi!
--[YUKINA] Chiaya!
[HARUKA] Chiaya? What are
you doing up there, young lady?
[YOUNG CHIAYA]
You didn't come home, Mommy.
I wanted to see you.
[HARUKA] You know how busy I am.
Sometimes I have to work late.
Run along
and play now, all right?
Mommy, I want to go to school.
[HARUKA] We've already hired
all the private tutors you need.
You have
a delicate constitution, dear.
--It's best for you to--
--I want to make some friends.
--I don't have any!
--Uh... [sighs]
You do have Momiyama.
He doesn't count!
He's an old man.
[groans]
--[footsteps approach]
--[YOUNG CHIAYA] Huh?
Hey Mom, look at this.
It'll just take a second.
--[HARUKA] I'm sorry, Chiaya.
--[sighs]
Can this wait until later?
Mom's busy now.
[CHIAYA] Mom, you know what?
Don't do that.
I've made some friends
since I've been away.
[NOZOMI]
She didn't go back to Okayama.
[YUKINA] Maybe she got lost
somewhere in Hiroshima?
Yeah, maybe. But how do
we even start looking for her?
[BOTH gasp]
[pencil scribbling]
This oughta be more effective
than just looking around
at random.
Yes, it should... in theory.
[KAGUYA] I think you've
really captured her there.
[FUHITO]
You're pretty good at this, huh?
Huh? Wow!
That looks totally normal!
Good job, Yukina!
Hmm? Oh, well this isn't a work
of art. It's just a drawing.
[NOZOMI] Is that how it works?
Good to know.
There we go! Now I'll just take
it and get some copies made.
--Um, you know where to go?
--Yeah!
--[tire hissing]
--Mmm. Hmm?
The truth is
that you're an alien, Chiaya.
The time is coming for you
to return to your home planet.
Shigyo needs that stone,
and I'm going
to get it back for her,
no matter what I have to do.
--[planes passing overhead]
--Huh?
[gasps]
[GUARD] Hey!
We don't tolerate trespassers!
Stop! You hear me?
--[punches thudding]
--[gasps]
[breathes heavily, grunts]
--[OTOMO] Hold on.
--[MEN] Huh?
There seems to be one missing.
[rustling]
--[door opens]
--[gasps]
Tell me where
the other octopus pot is.
--[OTONASHI] Huh?
--It's pointless to hide
the information from me now.
We've located seven,
but I know
there should be eight.
Now tell me where it is hidden.
[OTONASHI]
I-- I don't know!
--[footsteps approach]
--[breathes shakily]
[humphs]
What country are you men from?
I'll have you know
I'm the president's daughter!
If any harm comes to me,
you'll have an international
incident on your hands.
Is that something
you want to risk?
[MEN] Huh?
This is perfect. Bring her.
Huh? No! Wait! I--
[muffled shouting]
[gasps]
Even though our country
may have forsaken us,
we cannot give the license
to those who don't carry
the way of chivalry
in their hearts.
--[grunting]
--[screeches]
--[whimpers] Help me!
--[shouts]
Must stop and rest.
Where am I? [thuds]
I can't tell.
Maybe if there was a landmark?
[CHIAYA] I'm an alien.
[door closes]
[sighs]