[ANNOUNCER]
Scramble! Scramble!
Type-2. Rise over.
Remove castering device.
[MATAYOSHI]
These mass-produced machines.
They aren't gonna
cut it anymore.
Our enemies are
learning and evolving.
[MORIKO] Type-2 is
warmed up and ready.
[MATAYOSHI]
Will it work?
[SORIKO] It's passable,
but I should warn you,
the pilot's particle
oscillation has been acting up.
[MATAYOSHI]
We have no choice.
Send it out!
[ANNOUNCER]
Starting preparation.
Ready.
[SEWASHIKO] Daimidaler Type-2,
Kiriko. Standby for launch.
[SEWASHIKO] Thrusting Route 4-4.
[ANNOUNCER] Opening gate 3-5
[SEWASHIKO]
Positioning for Chidori.
Position achieved!
[ANNOUNCER]
Three, two, one, zero.
[SEWASHIKO]
Daimidaler entering shaft!
[SORIKO]
Daimidaler Type-2, Kiriko.
Range up!
[SEWASHIKO] Route 4-4,
Chidori hatch released.
Daimidaler shoot out!
[MATAYOSHI] The particle
compartment's unstable.
Think you can handle it?
[KIRIKO]
I'll give it a shot.
[KIRIKO grunts]
[KIRIKO gasps]
[KIRIKO grunting]
[KIRIKO]
Come on, move!
[MORIKO]
Muladhara and Svadhishhana down!
[SEWASHIKO] Manipura, Anahata,
and Vishuddha are out, too!
[SORIKO] Arjana, Sahasrara,
all generators are dead.
[KIRIKO screams]
[NARRATOR]
The mysterious army
that suddenly
appeared overnight,
wrought great
destruction upon mankind
with its incredible robots.
However, the enemy's intent
remains, for the
moment, unclear.
[CHIEKO] Hold it right there,
Kouichi Madanbashi!
Huh?
[KOUICHI]
What now, Miss Chieko?
Busted.
But what a bust it is!
[CHIEKO]
Well, well.
Look who thinks school
rules don't apply to him.
Why should I be surprised?
[KOUICHI]
Rules?
[CHIEKO]
As guidance counselor,
my patience for you
is wearing thin,
much like that whole bad-boy
routine you've got going on.
[KOUICHI]
Hey, wait a minute! Not cool!
Gonna give some
lame excuse now?
Oh, come on! Since when
is it against school policy
to sneak a peek at a pair of
ginormous sweater stuffers
in broad daylight?
[CHIEKO] Stare any harder
and your eyes'll fall out!
But no, the rule that you're
breaking is the dress code!
Dress code? Sleeves aren't
too long, pants aren't too short
and crotch leaves just
enough to the imagination.
What part of this outfit
violates the dress code?
All of it!
[CHIEKO] Why can't you wear the
uniform like the other boys?
Am I gonna have to get
physical with you here?
Here or the janitor's closet.
[CHIEKO]
Ew! I will make you wear this!
[KOUICHI]
Oh, please!
If I wore that jacket,
I'd look like a boob!
Hey, you get your butt
back here, Kouichi!
Real men always wear black,
not whatever ugly-ass
shade of green that is!
Real men don't
grope women and run!
[KOUICHI gasps]
[GIRLS giggling]
All right!
Special attack!
[GIRLS gasping]
[KOUICHI] Two-handed
quadruple skirt-flip!
[GIRLS gasping]
Oh, it's that gross
creeper again!
Even elementary kids don't
flip up skirts anymore!
[GIRL 1C]
You better run, sicko!
[KOUICHI cackles]
[CHIEKO growls]
[KOUICHI pants]
[MATAYOSHI] Your mission is to
find a new particle accumulator.
In order to do that,
you'll need to track down
and make contact with potential
Factor candidates, then test
their power and skill to see
if they're worthy specimens.
Be warned, the enemy is also
hunting Factor candidates.
So don't let your guard down!
[KYOKO gasps]
Damn!
[KYOKO] I can't afford
to scare him off.
Maybe I should try
direct contact?
[KYOKO gasps]
[KYOKO]
There he is!
[GIRL 1D] Do you ever feel
like you're being watched?
[GIRL 1E]
You're just imagining things.
[GIRL 1D]
Yeah, you're probably right.
[KOUICHI] I don't care
what the guidebooks say.
This is the best view
in the city! And now!
Reverse angle!
Wait!
[KYOKO gasping]
[KOUICHI pants]
[GIRL 1D]
Still, glad I remembered...
[KOUICHI]
Made it just in time.
[KYOKO panting]
Kouichi Madanbashi!
You're Kouichi
Madanbashi, right?
Yeah, who's askin'?
Hi. My name's Kyoko Sonan.
Do you maybe have
just a minute to talk?
I'm waiting on
friends right now.
So, whatever you're sellin',
I'm not interested.
[KYOKO]
No, that's not it.
Please, just listen
to what I have to say.
I have an important job for you!
Oh! Yeah, I think I get it now.
You want me loose
in your caboose!
[KYOKO]
I what?
[KOUICHI] You're huffin' and
puffin' like a dog in heat.
[KYOKO]
You idiot!
I ran, so I'm just
catching my breath!
[KOUICHI] Huge knockers flopping
around and those long legs.
You're a walkin' wet dream!
How rude!
Is that any way to speak to
a lady who you've just met?
Spare me! I compared
you to a dream!
That's a compliment!
[KYOKO]
What is wrong with this guy?
[JAKE]
Ah, found it!
[JIM] This really is the
second best view in the city!
[MICHAEL]
Isn't it, though?
From here, one can gaze upon
their undergarments perfectly!
[JAKE] Shh! You'll scare
their legs closed!
[GIRL 1D]
Trig class was so fun today!
[GIRL 1E] Yeah, I know,
right? I love tangents!
[MICHAEL]
Bravo! Good show!
[JIM]
Encore, encore!
[KOUICHI]
Hey, jerks!
[ALL gasp]
[KOUICHI] That's my
peepin' spot, get lost!
[MICHAEL]
Very well.
That's quite enough
tomfoolery for now.
[KOUICHI]
Who the hell are you freaks?
[JIM] Beauty Salon Prince
Intelligence Agent Kyoko Sonan!
[MICHAEL] Hand that boy
over to us at once, please.
[KYOKO] Ah, so you see
something in him, too, huh?
[JAKE]
Of course!
Factors are important to us
in a variety of ways.
[KYOKO growls]
[KOUICHI] Hey, creepy weirdoes!
Aren't you embarrassed to be
ganging up 3-to-1 on a lady?
[JAKE]
Nope!
[JIM]
Not really.
[MICHAEL]
Not even a little!
[ALL]
Because...
[JAKE]
We're all stark naked right now!
[MICHAEL] And compared
to waltzing around town
entirely in the altogether.
[JIM] Picking on a girl is
hardly embarrassing at all!
Yeah, all right.
Can't argue with that.
[JAKE] By the way
you're staring I'd say
there's been a misunderstanding.
What?
[MICHAEL]
These ample bulges protruding
from between our legs.
[JAKE] I do not think they
are what you think they are.
I know exactly what those
are and I'm kinda jealous.
[JAKE]
These are our trademark!
[MICHAEL]
Our pride, our joy!
[JIM] Our most
resplendent front tails!
What? No way he
just said "tails."
[JAKE]
That's right, it's a tail!
[MICHAEL]
Definitely a tail!
[JIM]
It's most assuredly a tail, so.
[ALL]
Not embarrassing!
I guess not.
Even a cold shower can't
help ya if they're tails.
Enough about their dick-tails.
[JAKE]
Fireworks!
[MICHAEL]
So sparkly!
[JIM]
Front tail!
[JAKE]
Huh?
[KOUICHI, KYOKO panting]
[KOUICHI]
Hang on!
Who the hell were
those guys anyway?
[KYOKO]
They're part of the commando
from the Penguin Empire.
And right now,
they're coming after you!
[KOUICHI]
But why me?
[KYOKO]
Because of what you are--
[JAKE]
Hello!
There's no use
trying to run from us!
[MICHAEL] This world is round!
We'll catch you eventually!
[JIM]
And now we have you surrounded!
[JAKE] Trapped like rats
in a bag of rattraps!
Step aside.
I don't get any of this crap.
But if there's one thing I love,
it's fighting for no reason.
Oh, Kouichi!
[KYOKO]
This is the perfect chance.
Now I can see his
powers in action.
[KOUICHI]
Heh.
Let's--
[KOUICHI groans]
He sucks!
[KYOKO]
Kouichi!
[JAKE cackles]
Oh my.
He's not even a
little bit impressive.
[MICHAEL] That guy was
supposed to be a great Factor.
Eh, least we got
to tour the sewers.
Hey, are you all right, Kouichi?
[KYOKO]
I don't understand!
According to headquarters,
he's supposed to be--
[KOUICHI laughs]
We're up close and personal.
[KYOKO] Huh?
[KOUICHI] So soft!
[KYOKO]
What do you think you're doing?
This is the first time I've
ever given a girl's boobs
the thorough fondling
they so richly deserve!
Let go of me,
you dirty little horndog!
[KOUICHI]
Hold on, I'm almost there!
[KYOKO screams]
[JAKE]
That brilliant light!
[JIM]
Oh no! He's going to awaken!
[KYOKO gasps, screams]
[MICHAEL]
What?
[JIM] This is a tragedy!
An absolute horror!
[JAKE]
Are you folks all right?
[MICHAEL] We weren't the
bad guys here, were we?
We couldn't know
this would happen!
[JAKE] You shouldn't play
at a construction site!
It's not safe!
[MICHAEL]
I don't believe it!
[JAKE]
That light!
[KYOKO]
Hi-ERO particles!
[KOUICHI yells]
[MICHAEL]
He's awakened!
[PENGUINS yell]
[KYOKO]
You really are--
[KOUICHI grunts]
[JAKE] Ah-Ugh!
[MICHAEL] Save-Mwagh!
[JIM]
Terri-Blugh!
Amazing...
[KOUICHI grunting]
[KYOKO]
This kid's power is incredible.
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI]
Come with me.
[KYOKO]
Finally, a candidate.
Is he the one?
[KOUICHI sighs]
[KOUICHI]
What in the hell was that?
Did you hear anything I said?
Those penguins are evil
and their existence
threatens all mankind!
[KOUICHI] Those giant robots
that sometimes show up
and terrorize the city.
They're on the local
news from time to time.
Is that their doin'?
[KYOKO]
That's right.
They're an evil empire that
must be defeated at all costs!
They're a rotten,
festering, plague
upon the face of this planet!
They're as wicked as they come,
and we have to crush
them all to smithereens!
[KOUICHI] They must've done
something to piss her off.
Like leave the toilet seat up.
[KOUICHI]
Okay, I get it.
But before you draft
me into your army,
you do know I'm just an average
high school student, right?
I need a fake ID to buy porn.
[KYOKO]
No, don't you see, Kouichi?
You're not just an average
high school student.
You're special.
Someone capable of storing up
powerful Hi-ERO particles.
You're a Factor.
[KOUICHI] Hi-ERO? You mean
the weird pink sparks
that shot out of me
and roided me out?
[KYOKO] Correct. But those
were just side effects of it.
Byproducts. The particles
that you're able to emit.
They can control an
enormous amount of power.
I don't care if they can make me
piss lightning and crap thunder.
This battle? It's not mine.
[KOUICHI]
See ya.
Man, that chick.
What was her name, Kyoko Sonan?
Please, I'm begging you,
Kouichi! Lend us a hand!
For them I'd lend two!
[JAKE]
Greetings.
We thought we'd drop by
and pay you a visit.
[KOUICHI]
How'd you find this place?
[JAKE chuckles]
We have limitless resources.
And Google Maps.
[MICHAEL] It's our job to
squash any potential threat
to the Penguin Empire.
Except for global warming,
'cause who has the time?
[JIM] Plus we have to pay you
back for our last encounter.
[JAKE]
Brace yourself for battle!
[KOUICHI] If we throw down
in here and so much as
peel some paint off the wall,
I can kiss my security
deposit goodbye!
[KOUICHI]
See ya!
[JAKE]
Don't let him get away!
[MICHAEL] But we have to
clean up these dirty magazines!
[JIM]
True.
If one peruses another
individual's pornography,
it's only proper to return
said smut to its rightful place.
[JAKE]
Hurry!
[KOUICHI grunts]
[KOUICHI] I can't believe those
penguins were in my apartment!
And screwed up my
porn filing system!
[KYOKO]
Kouichi!
[KOUICHI]
Whoa, Kyoko?
[KYOKO] I was just on my way
over to your place to find you.
Why are you running?
Those freaks got
into my apartment!
Then they got into my porn!
That figures.
[CROWD screaming]
[WOMAN 1A]
What is that thing?
A robot! I've seen 'em
on the local news!
[JAKE cackles]
[MICHAEL] Even a Factor
such as yourself cannot hope
to defeat our
Antarctic Type 8!
It's a Penguin Empire Robot!
Yeah, a giant robot
attacking an unarmed kid.
Seems real fair!
[KYOKO] Get in!
[KOUICHI] No problem!
[KOUICHI screams] Are you nuts?
You're driving toward it!
Because, Kouichi, you have it
in you to destroy that thing.
Huh? When are you gonna
get it through your head
that I'm just an average, very
handsome high school student?
Yes. Kouichi Madanbashi is an
average high school student.
[KYOKO] But Kouichi plus
Daimidaler can be much more!
You forgot the
"very handsome" part!
It's Kyoko.
We've got a penguin
soldier robot on the loose.
[KYOKO]
Time to release Type-2!
[MORIKO]
Type-2? That's a no-go.
[KYOKO]
What do you mean?
The repairs should've
been done by now!
[SORIKO] They're done,
but it's not moving at all.
[SEWASHIKO]
Oh, but hey, there's still
the Type-3 maintenance robot.
It can move. What about that?
[KYOKO] A mass prototype like
the Type-3 would be useless!
Send over the Type-2 now!
Faster!
[MORIKO] The administrator
isn't here right now,
so I'm not feeling
particularly motivated.
[SEWASHIKO] Sonan, are you
willing to take responsibility?
[KYOKO]
Yes, I'll take responsibility,
I'll take the blame,
I'll even take you out for
a fancy lunch at Juju's!
[SORIKO] Dessert?
[KYOKO] And apps!
[MORIKO] All right,
give me your coordinates.
I sent them your way.
[SORIKO]
Route 23, Butsudangaeshi,
is pretty close to you.
What the hell is that?
This, Kouichi,
is our secret weapon.
It is our great power.
[KYOKO]
Your power. Daimidaler!
[KOUICHI gasps]
That thing's Daimidaler?
[KYOKO] Come on.
Get in there and let's go.
[KOUICHI] You want me
to crawl inside a mummy?
Uh, yeah, no thanks.
[KYOKO] But you have to!
I've already explained
that the particles you emit
are able to control great power.
About that...
[KYOKO]
Only people like you.
People with Hi-ERO particles,
can control Daimidaler.
So get in there!
[KOUICHI]
You're not exactly putting me
at ease here, you know!
That thing looks,
like, crazy-dangerous!
[KYOKO] The fate of mankind
rests on your shoulders!
[KOUICHI]
And yet shockingly,
that doesn't make
me less nervous!
[KYOKO] What if I treat you
to lunch and dessert at Juju's?
[KOUICHI]
I'm not hungry!
[BOTH gasp]
[JAKE]
What is this thing?
[JIM]
Looks suspicious.
[MICHAEL]
Dispose of it!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KYOKO]
Daimidaler!
Flightless bastards!
[KOUICHI] Do you really need
that giant mummy? Really?
[KYOKO gasps]
[KYOKO]
Yes. It has to be Daimidaler.
Only it can defeat their robot.
Who'd have thought
that this power
I was somehow born
with would turn out
to be such a big deal?
Might be fun being more
than just an average,
very handsome, charming
high school student!
Do you really mean that?
[KOUICHI] I don't know
if it'll do any good,
but I'll give it a shot.
Hatch open!
[KYOKO]
Come on!
[KOUICHI]
With ya!
[KOUICHI laughs]
Oh man, this is sick!
[BOTH grunt]
What was that?
I'll teach you how to
fight as we go along.
Why don't you start out
by grabbing the controls!
Uh. ike this?
[JAKE]
What? What's happening?
[JIM]
Impossible!
[MICHAEL]
It's Daimidaler!
[JAKE]
They revived it?
[KYOKO] It moved!
Just like I knew it would!
So this is...
Daimidaler's battle mode!
This is the true
form of Daimidaler!
To go forward just press your
foot down on the right pedal!
I like how this feels!
[KOUICHI]
I'm gettin' amped up!
[KOUICHI] You want a
piece of me, bro-bot?
All right, now push down on
that lever to attack, okay!
[KOUICHI grunting]
You can't just keep
punching him over and over!
Try some attack combos!
Whoa, attack combos?
I'm more of a button-masher!
[KOUICHI grunts]
[JIM] You've had your fun,
now it's our turn!
This is bad!
[KOUICHI groans]
[KYOKO yells]
Wait, do we have
any weapons like that?
[KYOKO] Yeah, but they
require Hi-ERO particles.
And we don't have
enough now to use 'em!
Well, that seems like a
pretty damn big design flaw!
[MICHAEL]
Fire the Antarctic missiles!
[KOUICHI]
Damn it!
There's no way we can
handle all these torpedoes!
[KOUICHI]
That's it.
You said we didn't have enough
of those "EROs" things, right?
Yeah, right. Hi-ERO particles.
[KOUICHI]
So if I make some of those,
will this thing be good to go?
Sure will.
That's all the Daimidaler
system needs to operate.
[KOUICHI] Okay, great.
Kyoko, help me out here.
Of course, I'll do anything!
Just tell me what you need!
[KOUICHI]
Let me touch your boobs!
Hm?
How can you think about
that at a time like this,
you sick pervert? Seriously.
You've got a real
problem, buddy!
[KOUICHI]
Just hear me out, all right!
I think the only way
for me to unleash
my Hi-ERO particles.
Is to do perverted, degrading,
sexy things to girls!
Yeah right!
I'm telling you the truth.
Yeah, but earlier--!
I honked those honkers good.
[KYOKO gasps]
No, this. This can't be right!
[KOUICHI] And I bet if I
do some really sick stuff,
I'll be able to shoot out
even more particles.
[KYOKO]
Please, just stop talking, okay?
Although...
It is true that earlier...
But no, I can't!
[KOUICHI]
Kyoko.
How about fewer "no we can'ts"
and more "yes we can's"?
And speaking of "cans,"
it's grabby-grabby time now!
No!
[JIM cackles]
It's not moving at all!
[JAKE]
Victory is ours!
[MICHAEL] Shall we hit it
once more, just in case?
We've got no other choice!
Our backs are up
against the wall here!
Would you rather die than have
your headlights adjusted?
[KYOKO]
No. You're right.
So here! Go ahead. Objectify.
Oh yeah, awesome!
You know, I can tell
you got a lotta heart.
Even if it is buried under
those tig ol' bitties!
Oh, just shut up and grope me!
[KOUICHI]
Yes, ma'am! As you wish!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI]
Their size. Their bounce.
Their sheer heft!
Everything about them
is pure perfection!
[KYOKO]
Isn't. Isn't that enough?
[KOUICHI]
No, not yet! Not yet!
Not yet!
[KYOKO screams]
[KOUICHI]
There it is!
[KYOKO] It's the same
pink light as before!
[KOUICHI]
I feel so much power!
[JAKE]
It's erect!
[KOUICHI grunts]
[KYOKO]
Amazing!
I can't believe
the Hi-ERO particles
are already fully charged!
[KOUICHI]
Let's do this! Special attack!
Finger beam!
[PENGUINS]
What?
[PENGUINS scream]
[KOUICHI panting]
Wow! You did it, Kouichi,
you really did it!
[KOUICHI] No, not yet.
I haven't finished.
But, you destroyed their robot
and the penguins are gone.
It's over. What could you
possibly still wanna do?
I want you!
[KYOKO screams]
[KYOKO]
Those bastards have a lot more
firepower in their arsenal.
[KOUICHI]
I thought they might.
So, whadda ya say, Kouichi?
Will you join us in our fight
against the penguins?
Hell yeah!
I'll do whatever it takes
to help you beat 'em!
[KOUICHI] Even if I have to
glue my hands to your yabbos,
I won't back down!
[KYOKO]
Can't we find some other way
for you to spew your
pent-up particles?
[NARRATOR] At last,
Daimidaler has been revived.
But the fight against
the Penguin Empire
has only just begun. Do us
proud, Kouichi Madanbashi!
Never give up!
Win this war, Daimidaler!
[NARRATOR] Recognizing
his weakness, Kouichi learns
of true EROs as yet another
page of his youth is turned.
Next time:
Danger! The Stolen Sun.
Please look forward to it.