[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
We filled up a Penguin Commando
with Hi-ERO Particles secreted
from an excited Ritz,
but even that wasn't enough
to defeat Daimidaler.
And while Ritz is
obviously powerful,
she lacks battle experience.
How can we narrow
the technology gap
between the Antarctic
series and Daimidaler?
[MICHAEL]
So frustrating!
Especially because Daimidaler's
a copycat of our models.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Copycat?
What are you talking about?
[MICHAEL gasps]
[DENNIS] Well, a long time
ago we accidentally left
one Antarctic series robot
in town and the humans
sort of absconded with it.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
What?
[MICHAEL]
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Then the humans reverse
engineered our robot
and used that stolen
alien knowledge
as the basis for Daimidaler.
[DENNIS] That's what you
meant by "copycat."
[MICHAEL]
Precisely.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Wait.
Why is this the first time I'm
hearing about any of that?
[MICHAEL]
Oh! Raspberries!
[DENNIS]
I forgot we promised each other
to keep this secret between us!
[MICHAEL laughs] Well, we're
telling you now, aren't we?
[DENNIS]
Look, what's done is done.
And I'm sure His Highness
isn't so cruel
that he'd discipline us for a
tiny mistake made years ago.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
So, to summarize:
It's fair to say that
Daimidaler was built
off of our hard work
and technology?
[MICHAEL, DENNIS]
Mm-hmm!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Before we
arrived, the humans' preferred
weapons were tanks and planes.
I should have known
something was up
when they suddenly had
their own giant robot.
[MICHAEL] Hey, I don't
think he's scolding us.
[DENNIS]
We dodged a bullet.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] So if
their giant robot is basically
just our giant robot,
how is it that a penguin-built
Antarctic series still can't
seem to destroy Daimidaler?
Idea! Dennis! Michael!
I want you to study Daimidaler
down to the very last nut
and then give me a full report!
[MICHAEL, DENNIS]
Yes, sir!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Oh, and one more thing.
There will be no food
for either of you
until that report's in my hands.
Never keep secrets
from me again!
[DENNIS, MICHAEL] We were
wrong. He is scolding us!
Ah! You guys, I can't take it!
[SEWASHIKO]
He's coming.
And he's so banged up!
Um, Professor Sewashiko,
please stop moaning like that.
[SEWASHIKO] I can't keep up
with the pounding you're taking!
Don't blame me!
It's the penguins
who like to play rough.
When Kouichi pilots Daimidaler,
the whole robot becomes
engorged with his particles.
[SEWASHIKO] Yeah, and all
that raw, throbbing heat
is pushing the
frame to its limit.
[MATAYOSHI] So, in other
words, this worn out 'bot
is proof that you're
a huge pervert.
[KOUICHI]
Yes, sir. That's me!
[KYOKO]
Uh, Kouichi?
Your school sent a letter
saying they're going
to hold you back because
you're always absent.
Alright! Leaves me more time
to fluff those pillows!
[KYOKO yells]
It's not even 10AM!
[KOUICHI]
Uh, I was just testing you.
Your reflexes are much
improved, grasshopper.
Oh, can the "wise master" act.
That was clearly a boob grab!
[MORIKO] Their conversations are
getting really sexually charged.
This could get tricky.
[MORIKO] We can't afford
long refractory periods.
Kouichi's gotta make the Type 2
last without busting its nuts.
[SORIKO] Yeah, the new model
is incredibly expensive,
hard to maintain,
and basically a black budget
WMD program with zero
political oversight,
but it'll be way stronger
than the Type 2,
and with kick-ass
special attacks!
I can't wait until it's done!
[KYOKO] I'll get down on my
knees if that's what you want!
[CHIEKO]
I'm sorry, my hands are tied.
I mean, Kouichi's only
attended class four days
in the last three months.
His GPA is a 0.2!
I know it's bad!
But, my Kouichi-- I mean,
Mister Madanbashi here,
has had extenuating
circumstances
that keep him from attending!
Like what?
[CHIEKO]
Oh, wait. Don't tell me.
Kouichi's the guy who pilots
that giant robot, Daimidaler?
[KYOKO] Yes! He's devoted
his life to fighting penguins!
Fighting to save the world
has to count for
something, doesn't it?
[KOUICHI yawns]
[CHIEKO giggling]
I was being sarcastic,
but you ran with it!
No it's the truth!
He really does!
You sound insane!
Like I'm supposed to believe
that hair gel-loving truant
can pilot a giant robot?
[KOUICHI gasps]
[CHIEKO]
A good lie should be realistic!
Hold on a second,
Mrs. Chieko, please!
[KYOKO]
Kouichi!
You're right; me in a
robot does sound ri-donk.
'Fact, I can hardly
believe it myself.
But still, like her rack,
the story's all real.
if you just give me a second,
I'll even prove it to ya.
All right.
Here goes!
[CHIEKO gasps]
[KOUICHI]
Grope charge!
[CHIEKO gasps]
[KOUICHI grunts]
[CHIEKO]
Hey! Get off of me!
[KOUICHI] You wanted proof
of my skills, well here it is!
[KYOKO] Student-teacher
relations are frowned upon!
[KOUICHI] She's about
the same size as Kyoko,
but the consistency's
way different!
They're pouring through my
fingers like warm cookie dough!
Wow you have the bedroom skills
of an international businessman!
How about it?
You believe us now?
Um, and how does this prove
you pilot a giant robot?
Wait! What the hell is this?
Not fair! This explosion's
way more intense
than when you're pawing at me!
[KYOKO] So, you just have
to pass a make-up exam,
and pay for the clothes
you ripped off her body.
[KOUICHI] Well, getting
expelled sounds like
it would have been easier.
[KYOKO]
No, Kouichi don't say that!
You have to get your diploma.
So I would like to offer
you my tutoring services.
[KOUICHI]
No thanks.
Come on, it's all free.
Your school problems
are my fault
because I got you
involved in this.
I don't care about that.
Why give a damn about
high school exams?
I'm better off here
learnin' the ins and outs
of Damidaler and oinking
your sweater pigs!
Please! If you're as great
as you think you are,
you can do it all.
My dumb education
is none of your business!
[KYOKO]
We've gotten too intimate for me
not to have a say, Kouichi!
Why can't you take
"get the hell out of my face"
for an answer?
You prick dick!
[KYOKO] Don't you dare
walk away from me!
[SEWASHIKO] Kyoko and Kouichi
were really going at it earlier,
and not in a fun way, you know?
[MORIKO]
It's so juvenile.
Honestly, this is why I'm
glad I don't have a man.
Doesn't Moriko sound
like a character
who missed her one chance
at love and is super bitter?
Yep. She sounds totally jelly.
Bitches! What's that
supposed to mean?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] This Antarctic
Number 8, Ritz Custom,
is no normal Antarctic robot!
It has a secret.
Oh, yeah? What is it?
Tell us what it is!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] If I did,
then it wouldn't be a secret,
now would it, Ritz?
Lame!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Fine, since you're the pilot,
how about I tell you
the secret, in secret?
Are you sure you
can keep a secret?
[RITZ]
Yay!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
The secret is...
[PENGUIN EMPEROR whispering]
[RITZ]
Amazing!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Right?
[KOUICHI]
Kyoko. I know you care about me
because I'm so damn
hot and awesome.
But school?
Daimidaler's way more
important to me than
any exam right now.
I can't focus on anything else
until I destroy
Rikantz Seaberry.
But, if all you
ever do is fight--
I have better reason to fight
than I have to go to school.
And what's that?
[KOUICHI]
It's you, Kyoko.
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI] Piloting Daimidaler
lets me be closer to you, girl.
[KYOKO]
You're just saying that.
That's just how I feel and crap.
Oh wow. That's so heavy.
So you're telling me
that you're-you're
truly in love with me?
[KOUICHI]
Doing perverted stuff to you
--is like a dream come true.
[alarm blaring]
[KOUICHI]
Let's roll!
[KYOKO]
Huh? Oh. Right!
[SORIKO]
Sorry!
You're late!
[PROFESSORS panting]
I don't remember today being
"Wear a Towel to Work" Day?
Yeah, we're sorry, sir!
We weren't expecting this now!
Of all the times for an attack.
My hair is gonna be so frizzy.
[KOUICHI] Daimidaler Type 2,
Kouichi, departure standby.
Whoa! I didn't know it was
"Wear a Towel to Work Day"!
No! Don't look!
[MORIKO]
Professor Sewashiko, stand by!
Daimidaler entering shaft!
[WOMAN 5A] Get out of here,
before Daimidaler shows up!
Well, now we begin.
[PENGUINS]
Huzzah!
What are those?
Aw, hell no!
It's a new low!
[MORIKO gasps]
[MORIKO]
They're passing out flyers!
[RITZ giggles]
We're boosting the
Penguin Empire's likeability.
by handing out glossy flyers
listing our accomplishments!
We call it Operation:
"Flightless Birds Ironically
Handing Out Flyers."
[PENGUINS]
Fly Girl Ritz!
[MORIKO]
Oh, no! This op is bad news.
All that paper!
Flapping like old lady parts!
Their flyer plan will
litter the town with litter!
All that garbage
will hurt sight lines
and decrease property values!
It'll do worse than that!
[MATAYOSHI] There are
too many flyers to ignore!
That propaganda!
It won't be long
before it brainwashes everyone!
[GIRLS gasp]
[KOUICHI]
Damn! Those sick penguins
have no regard for human life.
[KOUICHI]
All right then, Kyoko.
It's time to kill them all!
[KYOKO grunts]
[KOUICHI]
What's wrong now?
[KYOKO gasps]
I'm good.
[KOUICHI] Piloting Daimidaler
lets me be closer to you, girl.
Are you sure
you're feelin' okay?
[KYOKO]
Huh?
I'm okay.
[KYOKO]
Why he'd have to say that?
Now I can't stop
thinking about him.
[KYOKO]
Block him out!
[SEWASHIKO] Route 21,
Matsubakuzushi hatch released!
Daimidaler shoot out!
[KOUICHI]
Daimidaler, ready to rumble!
Heh! Well someone's
an eager beaver today.
What a dummy.
[KOUICHI] I hope you
signed your will, Ritz.
Because, this time,
there won't be a next time!
[RITZ]
Same to you, human jerk.
We're giving you a
penguin curb-stomping!
Well let's grope from the front!
[KYOKO gasps]
[SORIKO]
Tandem Seat, Front Attack Mode.
Transmutation!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI]
Grope begin!
[KYOKO gasps]
No!
Ooh today your moans are
even hotter than usual!
Don't... Don't read
anything into it.
[KOUICHI grunts]
[SEWASHIKO]
Hi-ERO particle levels stable.
[KOUICHI]
Finger Beam!
Rapid-fire!
[RITZ yelps]
[KOUICHI]
No girl hides from me!
[RITZ gasps]
[KOUICHI]
Finger punch!
[RITZ screams]
[KOUICHI laughs] We're puttin'
the hurt on this squirt.
[MATAYOSHI]
He's a cocky young man.
Confident, too.
Yes, and at this rate,
that cockiness
will have split Ritz in half
by the end of battle.
[RITZ] Ouchie! Oh, you've
gone and done it now!
So. We're through
messing around with you.
Time to show off our
new robot's true form!
Okay! Penguin Transform!
[ALL gasp]
[RITZ]
Complete!
Antarctic 8, Ritz Custom,
Beautifully Strong Form!
The hell is that?
It's a whole new robot now!
No! This is impossible!
We didn't plan for this!
That is one big weiner gun!
It might as well
slap us in the face
with this gross new form!
Hi-Ero Particle Power
Generator, Initiate!
[KYOKO] All of that's
sparkling. That's Hi-ERO.
She's got them, too?
[MATAYOSHI]
Give me a status report!
The robot's particle levels
are equal to Daimidaler's!
My worst fears confirmed.
It transformed!
Like giant robot puberty!
[KOUICHI]
Whoa, whoa, stop the clock!
What's that have to do
with Hi-ERO particles?
[SORIKO]
I'll explain.
We developed Daimidaler...
[KYOKO] Particles don't matter,
she's just powerful.
[KOUICHI]
Eh, she don't scare me!
Whole thing's smells
like a bluff, anyway.
[KOUICHI grunts]
[RITZ]
A bluff?
Now does this feel
like we're bluffing?
[SORIKO] There are seven
chakras, located within
the perineum, genitals, navel,
chest, throat, forehead,
and vertex of the skull.
The Generator draws out
the Hi-ERO particles...
[SEWASHIKO] Watch out!
[MORIKO] Kouichi!
[SORIKO] This is the
reason Daimidaler's form
roughly resembles that of a
human, although such a form
does present the pilot with
control issues in battle.
If it resembles
humans, how the hell
did it get stuck with
such a gimpy right arm?
Talk about crummy
design philosophy!
You may surrender to us
whenever you're ready.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
The Hi-ERO particle generator
you created for the Ritz Custom
is working splendidly.
Dennis! Michael! Good job!
[DENNIS]
Huzzah!
[MICHAEL]
Now we can eat again!
[KOUICHI]
Finger Flash!
[RITZ gasps]
[RITZ]
Huh? Hey! What happened?
[RITZ gasps]
[KOUICHI]
Finger beam, maximum power!
Well! Is she destroyed?
No.
[MORIKO] Rikantz Seaberry
shows no damage.
[KOUICHI gasps]
--Wait, Is that a...
...Type 2 Hi-ERO
Particle Barrier?
[KYOKO]
No. It's stronger than that!
The game's up, Daimidaler!
If you don't surrender,
you will die hard.
[JAKE]
Oh, heavens no!
Sam's buried alive under rubble!
[JIM]
Take short breaths!
[RITZ]
Sam!
Please tell us Sam is okay!
[NELSON] His front tail
now hangs flaccid.
[JAKE] It'll be a long time
before it rises again.
No. Tell us...
...this didn't happen!
[RITZ]
No. No!
How dare you hurt our Sam!
We will never forgive you!
[KOUICHI, KYOKO scream]
[MORIKO gasps] Admin.
You have to look at this data!
Oh, my God.
[RITZ] We will kill
anyone who lays a hand
on our penguin family!
Right arm destroyed?
This is bad!
[KOUICHI] I admit she's strong,
but I'm not sweatin' her yet.
[MATAYOSHI]
Both of you, get out of there!
It's no big deal; that arm
was useless anyway!
[MATAYOSHI] We finished
analyzing her new robot!
[MORIKO]
Kouichi, listen!
This robot is five times
stronger than Daimidaler
in all areas of combat!
Oh, fudge me!
Five times stronger?
[RITZ growls]
[KOUICHI groans]
[RITZ]
More like ten times!
[RTIZ cackling]
[MATAYOSHI] Beating
Rikantz Seaberry is impossible.
You have to pull out!
I never pull out.
Kouichi...
[KOUICHI screams]
[NELSON]
Ooh, grisly.
[JAKE] You think something's
wrong with Ritz? Like, mentally?
[JIM]
Funny you should mention that,
because today it has
crossed my mind.
[RITZ cackling]
[MICHAEL]
Dennis!
The Antarctic Number 8's
chest is blinking!
[DENNIS]
Is that a bug or a feature?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
This isn't good!
[MORIKO] Hi-ERO generator levels
have dropped drastically.
[KYOKO]
I can't reroute power!
God dammit all!
Piece of crap! Come on!
[RITZ] Aw, what's wrong?
You spent already?
Well, in that case...
Die.
Die!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Extract Ritz at once!
That's an order!
[NELSON]
Uh, right now?
[JIM] Yeah, she only needs
a couple more minutes
to completely
vanquish Daimidaler.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Ritz is fraught with emotion,
and the Antarctic Number 8's
Hi-ERO Particle Generator
is feeding off that energy.
She risks being
absorbed altogether!
[DENNIS]
Well that's not good.
It sounds like Ritz doesn't
have enough experience
controlling her
Hi-ERO particles.
[MICHAEL] So the robot's
completely out of control?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] It could
self-destruct at any moment.
You must release Ritz
from its infernal bowels!
Sometime today!
[JIM]
Understood! Penguin jump!
[JIM grunts]
We're gonna kill you!
That's what you'll get for
hurting our little friend Sam!
We'll avenge his
flaccid front tail!
[JIM]
I'm sorry to do this.
[RITZ whimpers]
[JIM]
Ritz, extracted.
[JAKE]
Behind you!
[JIM]
Hm?
[NELSON] Antarctic Number 8's
moving on its own!
[MICHAEL] Well, that's an
unexpected and creepy twist.
[DENNIS]
How's it doing that?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] The particles
the generator harvested
from Ritz possess
enough emotional charge
that they're able to propel
the entire Antarctic Number 8
on their own. What a
terrifying, but colorful,
weapon of war we've created.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Evacuate the area!
I wasn't kidding about that
robot self-destructing!
[PENGUINS]
Understood!
[MORIKO]
Daimidaler's paralyzed.
[MATAYOSHI] Sonan!
Madanbashi! Leave on foot!
[SEWASHIKO]
Emergency eject!
Right. I'm on it.
I have got the worst
friggin' rogues' gallery.
[KYOKO]
No!
What's happened now?
[KYOKO] The computer
won't let us bail out!
Well, can we reboot it?
[SORIKO]
It's melting down!
[MORIKO] At this rate,
the whole city stands to become
an irradiated wasteland!
Eject! Eject!
The hatch is stuck,
too. What now?
I guess we've reached
the end of the line.
[KOUICHI grunting]
[KYOKO gasps]
Kouichi, no! Please don't!
Move!
[KYOKO screams]
This is it. Bye, Kyoko.
[KYOKO gasps]
[KYOKO]
Kouichi, no!
You should know.
I'm so in love with...
[KYOKO gasps]
...your tig ol' bitties.
[MORIKO]
Daimidaler Type-2, Kouichi...
Destroyed.
[MATAYOSHI gasps]
[MORIKO] I'm afraid there
are no signs of life.
It can't be.
Kouichi, gone. And Kyoko.
[MORIKO]
Wait, there's a life signal!
[MATAYOSHI]
What?
[KOUICHI]
You should know.
I'm so in love with...
[NARRATOR] If you can
accept a girl's emotions
melting down a robot.
Then you shouldn't
be thrown for a loop
when our main
characters suddenly change.
Next time:
"Arrival! Shouma and Kiriko"
Please look forward to it.