[KOUICHI]
Kouichi's back in the heezy!
[RITZ]
That doofus Kouichi is alive?
[RITZ yells]
Oh, no!
[KOUICHI grunts]
[KOUICHI]
Suh-weet!
Right on the money!
[RITZ]
Ouch!
He's way stronger
than we remember!
[MATAYOSHI]
Madanbashi!
You sure it's him?
[SEWASHIKO]
Our pervert pilot's back!
But what's
that candle all about?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
A candle!
That can mean only one thing.
I kept believing
that you were still alive.
'Sup, Kyoko.
I swear.
I heard your voice
and sex puns.
[KOUICHI] Well that explains
why you rushed to me
in nothin' but
an ass-flashing blouse!
That's not why!
[KOUICHI] We'll talk later about
the signals you're flashing.
For now, we got
a Seaberry to squish.
Hey. Why am I all
the way up here?
Just leave everything
to me, sugar tits.
[KOUICHI]
Finger Beam!
Kouichi!
[RITZ] We killed you once,
we'll kill you again!
[RITZ]
Fiery Blast Penguin Thrust!
Not fair! He's got
the weaker bot!
Hey, Kyoko!
What's up?
[KOUICHI]
Let's do this!
Yeah, every girl's dream:
Grabby groping instead
of a nice romantic reunion.
[KYOKO gasps]
What?
When did you add this?
While I was on
the other side,
I had some aftermarket
tweaks done.
And I did it all
with these in mind!
Hey! I know it's been a while,
but don't be so rough--
Ah!
I missed hearing
you make those porno moans.
Don't you ever get tired of
being horny all the time?
Hands outside the clothes!
[KYOKO gasps]
I know what I'm doin'.
I'm totally naked!
[KYOKO moans]
Alright!
That's enough!
Hold on, we're almost there.
[KOUICHI]
Almost there!
[RITZ gasps]
[KOUICHI]
Hi-ERO particles, full burst!
[MORIKO]
His particle load.
It's 20 times that
of the normal Type-2!
No wait, it's way
more than that!
Oh, crap!
[PENGUINS]
Wha...!
[RITZ]
Our evolt.
[RITZ screams]
She's all wet!
[NELSON]
What's that?
[JIM]
Looks like HI-ERO particles.
[MICHAEL] Jeez, he's
spraying 'em everywhere.
[DENNIS] What a waste
of life-giving energy!
[JOSEPH]
Oh, no! We have to save Ritz!
Come on, let's roll!
[SHOUMA] Um, would it
be okay if I came, too?
[JOSEPH] I did just say
"we" have to save her.
And that's because you're a part
of the Penguin Empire family!
[KIRIKO crying]
[KIRIKO]
Why? Why?
Shouma's gone.
Well, at least we won.
[MATAYOSHI]
"Daimidaler, Super Thermal
Power System Mounted
Type, Kouichi."
That's catchy.
[KOUICHI] You can shorten it
to Type-Super, if you fancy.
It's one bad mo-fo.
[SORIKO] So you have
a thermal power system
responsible for your
Daimidaler's physical movement.
Which then allows you to
stockpile your Hi-ERO Particles
and use them only for fighting.
So that big cloud at the end
was unused particles
being emitted.
Cleaning the pipes,
so to speak.
Yeah, I don't get it.
What the hell, Master?
You can't wrap your head
around this concept?
All we're really getting at's
this robot has
two energy sources.
What I don't get
is where this robot
was repaired and modified
if not here at the Beauty
Salon Prince, under my orders!
[KOUICHI]
Well, there was the explosion.
And the next thing
I remember is waking up
in some weird place
with a wrecked Daimidaler.
[KYOKO]
Weird place?
[KOUICHI] Yeah. Like here,
but just different enough.
I couldn't contact
any of you.
So I wandered around
clueless for a while,
until another
human-piloted mech found me.
Luckily, they
were as friendly
as they were
smart with robotics.
They're the ones who rebuilt
and tricked out my Type-2.
They also took care of me.
Saved my life.
[MATAYOSHI]
What did you say?
You let some strangers
touch your Daimidaler!
What was I
supposed to do?
So? What kind of group
were these rescuers?
Corporate, military,
or what?
Oh, yeah,
they were, uh...
Wait a minute.
Hm... They were...
What's wrong now?
I don't remember who they were!
Or even the faces of the
people who took care of me!
If you're too lazy to give us
a full report, just say so.
They told me I could
return to this world,
so long as
Daimidaler's left arm
was still here
and in one piece.
I spent my days
alone in that cockpit.
Thinking of things I never
had the chance to do with Kyoko.
Somehow, she must
have felt these feelings
across time and space.
You were thinking about me?
No, he was thinking
about how he wants
to stuff your body
like a turkey.
Wow.
What are you doing up?
You're supposed to
be on strict bed rest!
[KIRIKO] You're the new pilot,
Kouichi Madanbashi. Right?
Yeah.
And you must be...
not wearing a bra!
Wha--?
I've been recuperating
in the sick bay!
F-Y-I, that's Kiriko Kiyuna.
She's a senior Daimidaler pilot,
so please be respectful.
Wait.
You're that pervert!
All this time you two have been
attending the same high school.
[KIRIKO, KOUICHI]
Huh?
[KYOKO] She's a third year
student, and Kouichi's a second,
so at school Kiriko
is his senior as well!
[MORIKO]
Well, that's when he attends.
Anyway, Kiriko, your Type-6.
[KIRIKO]
What's up?
[MORIKO]
The damage was all superficial.
The combat chassis
is still intact.
[SORIKO] We just need
to swap a few parts,
and you'll be back in
the fight in no time.
[KIRIKO] Great! One less
thing to worry about.
Our long wrestling match
with the Penguin Empire
is heating up to its climax.
Now with the upgraded Type-2--
No Type-Super!
We can shred those
tuxedo-wearing
flightless birds into
chicken noodle soup.
You know, when you use
that kind of language
you make this whole war
sound like a joke!
[KOUICHI]
I take it seriously!
I'm not taking your tits
for granted again!
My hands are ready to grope!
[KYOKO gasps]
No! Not like this, Kouichi!
[KOUICHI]
Stop playin' hard-to-get!
[KYOKO]
Stop being pervy!
[KIRIKO] I'll die saving Shouma
if that's what it takes.
Being a penguin
must be horrible!
[SHOUMA]
Being a penguin is awesome!
[NELSON laughs]
Glad it suits you!
[JAKE]
Nice to meet you, brother!
[MICHAEL]
Pinochle? 4:30? You in?
[JOSEPH]
With outstretched flippers,
we welcome you to
your new family, Shouma.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Penguin transfer!
[JIM] Your Highness,
you shouldn't call
for a transfer
while in the bath.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Did you see that candle
that appeared over
the new-old Daimdaler?
It's not just decoration.
It means it was running
on thermal power.
That's a system
of limitless energy
the humans in
the other world created.
[RITZ]
Hold on.
You mean to tell us
that Kouichi has spent
this whole time in
the same world as Humboldt?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Normally,
it takes a Penguin Device
using a massive amount
of Hi-ERO Particles
to transfer things
between dimensions.
But the Hi-ERO
Generator that blew up
was so overloaded with them,
it functioned in the same way.
Its blast catapulted Kouichi
to the parallel world.
Now, the strong
Hi-ERO particles
powering the
new Super Antarctic
must have acted as
a kind of tractor beam,
pulling him back to this Earth.
And that left arm that
survived the Shinjuku Blast
probably served as
an inter-dimensional beacon.
Building the Super Antarctic
made the Penguin Empire
more powerful than ever.
But it also revived that
sex crazed, lunatic pilot.
[RITZ]
Hmm.
Most of that sounds like
gobbledygook to us.
But we do like the thought
of curb-stomping Kouichi.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Unrelated, but I see the boy
who goes by Shouma excreted
all his Hi-ERO particles
and became a penguin commando.
While Henry, whom we injected
with Hi-ERO particles,
became human.
Why is it so hard to figure out
the rules to this stuff?
My brain can only
handle so much
before it starts
giving me a headache.
[ALL]
Your Highness!
[RITZ]
Your Highness?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
I think this is the end.
No, you can't leave us!
[JIM]
It's just heatstroke.
[MICHAEL]
Eh, he had a good run.
Shall we break
for lunch then?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR groans]
Would somebody please
get me a glass of water?!
More Daimidaler damage.
That robot is
incredibly troublesome.
Indeed, and this
isn't the only location
I wanted to show
you today ma'am.
[WOMAN] I could swear
we had the city
shut down this
adult book store.
[WOMAN]
How disgusting.
At this rate, all
the promising boys on the block
will become degenerate perverts!
They tell me this
entire area of the capital
became unhealthily
pornographic overnight.
[WOMAN] I assume we know
what's causing this shift?
[MAN] It's likely
due to them, of course.
I'm coming, Shouma.
[KOUICHI]
You're overreacting!
[KYOKO]
No! I'm not wearing it!
[KOUICHI]
Don't be selfish!
Kyoko, you're my partner,
that means it's your duty.
Now come on, it's
a co-pilot battle suit!
[KYOKO] How in Antarctic hell
is that a battle suit?
[KOUICHI]
It's got support?
[KYOKO growls]
[KIRIKO]
Kyoko, you're so lucky.
[KYOKO]
Kiriko?
Your boyfriend's human.
[KYOKO]
Boyfriend? Who told you that?
That's a strong word!
We're Daimidaler
co-pilots, not lovers!
Oh, who cares what we are,
just try on your new uniform!
Alright.
[KYOKO]
But only for a second.
[KOUICHI]
Yeah, yeah, sounds good.
But let me watch!
[KYOKO]
See you later, Kiriko.
Uh, yeah.
[KYOKO]
I'm just trying it on.
I'm not doing
anything else with you!
[KOUICHI] But that won't
help with our training!
[KYOKO] Two seconds ago,
you said that was fine!
[KIRIKO]
What is their relationship?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] The new
thermal powered Daimidaler.
As I suspected he--
[RITZ] You worry too much,
Your Highness.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Hmm? Ritz?
We're confident we'll
smash his face next time.
'Cause we can use the Hi-ERO
particle generator
without it blowing up!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Ah, the high-risk, high-reward
Hi-ERO Particle Generator.
Mankind's idea to use them as
a force in battle is impressive.
In the end, though,
Daimidaler is nothing
but a reverse-engineered
knock-off
of Penguin Empire technology.
With you and the power
of your Hi-ERO particles
leading the charge,
we have little to fear.
[RITZ]
Yup!
Or the short version,
they're toast!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
But originally, Hi-ERO particles
were not something
to be used as weapons.
Huh?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Ritz.
I have made a huge mistake.
For a guy who loves talking,
the Emperor can be
really vague sometimes.
[MICHAEL]
What's wrong?
Sad? Confused?
Constipated?
[RITZ]
Oh, hey, Michael.
So, get this, the Emperor
poured himself out to us
and said he'd
made a huge mistake.
[MICHAEL]
He did what?
Hmm...
What do you think
he means by that?
Huh? Michael?
No biggie! We can't
worry about the past
when there are
Daimidaler's out there.
Whatev!
[MICHAEL]
I have terrible news!
[JIM] Oh, Michael. It's always
something. What is it?
[MICHAEL] His Highness
"poured himself into Ritz,"
then said it was a "mistake."
[JIM]
Oh my god.
[DENNIS]
What happened?
[JIM] Our Emperor
sexually assaulted Ritz
then tried to apologize.
[NELSON]
You can't apologize for that!
That's fifth degree
sexual harassment!
[JAKE]
His Highness did what?
[SHOUMA]
Sexual harassment?
[JAKE] What's worse:
Sexual harassment
or trying to apologize for it?
[ALL]
Hmm.
[SHOUMA] He should have just
busted out the Gulliver Stick!
[DENNIS] Sorry, pal,
but that's your front tail.
[JAKE]
Yes, again, it's a tail.
Not genitals.
A tail on our fronts.
[SHOUMA]
Sorry. It's hard to get used to.
[NELSON] You're the
Penguin Empire class clown!
Is it true that
we've found the location
of the main
Penguin Empire base?
Yeah, their address
popped right up
when we searched online.
That's crazy.
I know, that's what we said.
I mean searching
for secret bases
hidden in hollowed-out
volcanoes or under the ocean
or on the moon is
really hard work.
Googling's way easier.
Kyoko, you are totally giving
it up tonight, aren't you?
Huh?
[KYOKO gasps]
I forgot to change back
to my normal clothes?
Silky intimates, huh?
No, it's a battle suit
Kouichi made me!
[KOUICHI]
Kyoko!
Now let's put
that battle suit
through its paces
with some test gropes!
You guys hear that?
Kouichi called it a battle suit.
So... Wait.
Did he say, "grope"?
[KYOKO yelps]
Hah, nice fit!
I said no!
[MORIKO]
Wow, he's already engorged...
...with particles!
Hell, yeah.
I don't care if I'm fighting
Penguins or Ritz,
with you dressed like this,
I can't lose again!
Good job!
I love seeing you training
so hard before battle.
He's not training.
Stop him, someone, please!
[KYOKO moans]
[MINISTER 11A] This isn't just
scandalous. It's depraved!
[MAN] This is real time
video from a hidden camera.
[MINISTER 11B] I can't watch
anymore. Turn it off.
[MAN]
Well, since my boss,
the Minister of Art,
is traveling abroad.
I'll be presenting
the report in her absence.
We found a steady
uptick in the sales
of morally unsound magazines,
games, movies, comics,
and self-published
erotic slash fiction.
The amount of exposed breasts
and barely-obscured genitalia
in anime has also
reached new heights.
And all in the
last three weeks.
[MINISTER 11C]
The perversion's spreading
faster than a flu epidemic.
[MAN]
Yes, and it all started
only after the appearance
of this Daimidaler.
Beauty Salon Prince.
We should have eliminated
them when we had the chance.
After that robot
blew up West Shinjuku.
To think, when the
penguins first showed up,
I thought that stupid
Salon would emerge
as the saviors of our world.
[PRIME MINISTER]
The saviors who actually
cleansed the world
of all the filth,
however temporary,
were the Penguins!
[MINISTER 11A]
It's very ironic, yes.
[PRIME MINISTER]
I want immediate measures
in place to stop
this epidemic.
Before we become a land
of pillow-humping perverts.
[KYOKO moaning]
[KYOKO]
Isn't this enough?
[KOUICHI]
Not even close!
I still have to show you
all the special
features I had thrown in!
Open top!
You asshole!
[KOUICHI] Now I have
naked boob access
in the middle of
the most heated battles!
[KYOKO moans]
The Hi-ERO Particle
load is maxing out!
Wow.
With this much
power in his hands,
I like our odds of killing
every last Penguin on Earth.
[KIRIKO]
Administrator!
[MATAYOSHI]
What is it, Kiriko?
I want in on this
battle, too, sir!
[MATAYOSHI]
Two Daimidalers at once.
Well I do like
the sight of double Ds.
Alrighty, then!
Thank you, Administrator!
I'll go give
the Type-6 a once-over!
[MORIKO]
There's one problem, sir.
To move the Type-6, Shouma
needs to be in the cockpit,
regulating Kiriko's power.
[Sewashiko]
They gotta get dir-tay.
[MATAYOSHI]
That's true.
Otherwise, there's a chance
Kiriko goes berserk again,
which would be
balls-to-the-wall cool
if we could channel that
energy into killing Penguins.
Actually, her melting down
right on top of their
base would be perfect!
[laughing]
[ALL]
Uh...
[KYOKO] Kiriko! I heard
you were healed up.
So now the three
of us can do it!
Fight, that is.
[KIRIKO]
Sure, no problem.
[KOUICHI] We should
probably think of a plan.
Yeah, like what?
Like, I'll start by
fondling your tits and then--
No way!
Once I've got her in
"Full Burst Mode" I'll jump over
to the Type-Super
and start working on your ass.
Why my ass now?
Fondling boobs doesn't
give me enough variety.
Alright, that's
enough sex talk!
Now listen up!
I'm a strong
independent woman
who don't need
no man to save my man!
I can go into Full Burst
Mode using nothing
but my imagination.
[KYOKO, KOUICHI]
Your what now?
Just forget I said
anything, all right?
The point is, I won't
let anyone touch my body
other than my true love
and white knight, Shouma.
Well, she's weird.
We're trying to team-up,
but she keeps goin' on
about her lame ex-boyfriend.
Poor Kiriko.
[KYOKO] Sorry for all
the trouble, this year.
[CHIEKO] Yeah, speaking of,
I'm glad you came to me.
It seems that Shouma Ameku
hasn't attended class, lately.
Uh...
It's my ass in the fire if
even a single student flunks.
That's... That sounds bad.
[SHOUMA]
Heyo!
He's gone.
[CHIEKO]
Gone?
Yeah, he's gone
to the Pentagon.
In Washington DC, to train.
[CHIEKO]
The Pentagon?
So you Beauty
Salon Prince people
also have ties to the American
military establishment?
Yeah, we're that important!
[KYOKO laughs]
[KYOKO]
Forget having ties with America.
Lately, we're not
even on good terms
with the Japanese government!
Thanks for talking to her.
I was worried
I'd missed too many days.
You know, with all
the head trauma.
[KYOKO chuckles]
Miss Chieko and I figured
everything out right
before you returned.
Your days missed due
to "the penguin war"
won't count against you.
Man, school is stupid.
Why's the city so dead?
That's weird. There should
be people outside.
[KYOKO gasps]
[tires screeching]
Hey, where'd you
learn to drive?
What the hell?
Where'd that thing come from?
[KYOKO]
Why is it out here?
Kyoko, turn on the radio,
maybe there's some news!
Right, yeah.
[RADIO ANNOUNCER] In response,
the national government
has announced an
emergency evacuation
of the Edogawa District.
Please follow all police dire--
[KIRIKO]
Emergency evacuation?
[KOUICHI]
The hell's happening?
[RADIO ANNOUNCER]
An armed terrorist group
known as the
Beauty Salon Prince
has barricaded
themselves in a building
in the central
Edogawa District.
In response,
the national government...
Why does that
name sound familiar?
That's our beauty salon!
I know, someone's
out to get us!
I want a report, now!
[MORIKO] All I can tell
you is that multiple
Type-3 Daimidaler's are
heading this way!
[SEWASHIKO] It's like a
whole army of Daimidalers!
[MATAYOSHI]
That's the mass production model
we gave the government.
[SORIKO]
They said they destroyed it.
Clearly, that was a lie.
[MORIKO] They've churned 'em
out on an assembly line.
Plus normal people
can pilot the Type-3
because it runs on plasma.
[SORIKO] That explains why
they kept the prototype
and lied about destroying it.
[MATAYOSHI]
What is their angle here?
Attention terrorist mastermind.
Matayoshi.
We have an ultimatum for you!
Terrorist, what?
Mastermind?
[COMMANDER] We have your
lady barber shop surrounded.
Lay down your
weapons and surrender!
What can we do?
How are we the bad guys?
[COMMANDER]
With the Penguin Empire's help,
we were able to
halt the epidemic
of perversion and porno
addiction in our young men!
But your continued
existence threatens
to make them all
re-harden and relapse
into masturbatory madness!
[ALL gasp]
Idiots!
Have you forgotten
everything the Penguin Empire
has done to us with
their warmongering ways?
I know their attacks
don't hurt us
as much as yours!
You should see what
we spend rebuilding
after Daimidaler battles!
Right now, the greatest
threat our country faces
is you, the Beauty
Salon Prince!
[MATAYOSHI]
What?
[SEWASHIKO groans]
I guess he does have a point
about the destruction thing.
[COMMANDER]
I take it you'd rather die
as martyrs than surrender?
What?
That makes my job easy, then.
How did it come to this?
Hold on!
We haven't even
responded yet!
[MATAYOSHI]
Forget it.
Admin?
[MATAYOSHI] They never
intended to let us live.
No matter how we
answered their demands,
the end result was always gonna
be them attacking the salon!
That blows.
[SOLDIERS]
Ready to attack!
[COMMANDER]
Ready, aim.
Fire!
[NARRATOR] Everyone sets
forth on their own path.
But no matter
where life takes you,
these days will
never be forgotten.
Front tails forever!
Next episode, "Showdown! Sound
Robots versus Daimidaler!"
Please look forward to it.