And this is the hanger
where we service Daimidaler.
[KOUICHI]
Whoa, even his room kicks ass.
[MORIKO]
Sonan.
Professors!
[KOUICHI]
Professors?
[KYOKO] Yes, Kouichi,
girls can be scientists, too.
In fact, these three
built Daimidaler.
This is team leader,
Professor Moriko Tomoyose.
[MORIKO]
Hello.
Nice titles.
Up next.
You'll see, without leering, I
hope, Professor Soriko Majikina.
She handles Daimidaler
maintenance and repair.
Hello.
[KYOKO] And last, and least,
because she's short,
is Professor Sewashiko Goya.
She does operations
and control guidance.
How-dee-doo!
[MORIKO] So I take it
you're the new Factor
we've been hearing about, huh?
Well, you certainly look
like a leading man.
[KOUICHI laughs]
[KOUICHI] How did you
pass engineering school
with those D's? I must squeeze!
So horny.
[MORIKO] But the objects of
your affection are over there.
Oh, yeah!
[KYOKO]
Huh?
Yeah, time to charge!
[KYOKO] Hey! This wasn't
the job I signed up for!
No! Stop!
[KOUICHI]
Here it comes!
[KYOKO whimpers]
[SORIKO] He really does have
a lot of potential backed up,
just waiting to burst out.
We might even be able to
call him an S-Class Factor.
[KOUICHI]
S-Class?
Yup. For "strong," like
a horse. Right? Like a horse!
Behave.
Having hot chicks
compliment me on my hair
and compare me to a horse.
Imma have my hands full!
Stop it!
[KOUICHI]
Don't mind me, just loitering!
[AUNTIE 2A]
Whatever.
[KOUICHI]
Yee-haw!
[SORIKO] Penguin robot
spotted moving out from
Sector D-11 to Sector C-4!
Roger that! Clearing
traffic on Route 22!
Type-2, ready for lauch!
[SEWASHIKO]
Daimidaler entering shaft!
[CROWD screaming]
[MAN 2A]
A penguin robot attack!
[MAN 2B]
It's marching!
[CROWD screaming]
[KOUICHI yells]
This new seat feels amazing
on my golden boy haunches.
[MORIKO]
This is the Daimidaler 2-seater.
[SORIKO] We made some
mechanical enhancements
to make it easier for you
to get a full power release
from Kyoko's
natural enhancements.
This is so humiliating.
It's like I'm a hood ornament.
[KOUICHI] Alright, you penguin
bastards, let's throw down!
It's on!
[KOUICHI yells]
[KOUICHI]
What the hell?
[NUMBER 9]
Penguin. Penguin.
[KOUICHI]
You're giving me a headache!
So I'm giving you my fist!
[KOUICHI]
You are so cheap!
[NUMBER 9]
Penguin.
[KYOKO] It isn't moving
like a normal robot!
[PENGUINS cheering]
[PENGUIN EMPEROR laughs]
That's one for the good guys.
Before going into battle,
Number 9 received a
firmware upgrade with new
combat tactics derived
from our deadliest
pair of penguin commandos.
Michael and Dennis!
[NUMBER 9]
Penguin.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Can you keep up with their
grace and whimsy?
[KYOKO screaming]
[KOUICHI grunting]
[NUMBER 9]
Pen...
...guin.
[KOUICHI groans]
I'm not goin' down that easily!
I'll show you what my
Daimidaler is packing!
[SORIKO]
Tandem Seat Front Attack Mode!
Transmutation!
Huh? What? You're not serious.
Sure am. You ready
to rub him out?
Fine. Make it quick.
[KOUICHI] Oh, mama!
That hits the spot.
That, huh--?
[KYOKO]
Hm?
[KOUICHI]
Twist and squeeze.
What's wrong?
[SORIKO] There's just a 2%
rise in Hi-ERO particles.
[SEWASHIKO]
How embarrassing for him.
I lost it.
Not now! We're right
at the climax!
[KOUICHI]
You're making me tense!
He's still a mere novice.
[KYOKO gasps]
[MICHAEL]
Hey, that looks like--
[DENNIS]
Pornography!
[ORSON]
All the newest releases!
In Blu-Ray and 4K!
[JAKE] Even the barely-legal
American cheerleader stuff!
[JIM]
Their pink bosoms are as wide
as the heartland's
great prairies!
[DENNIS]
Let's have Number 9 collect them
for our common area bookcase!
[MICHAEL] Ooh! Now that's
thinking on your feet, Dennis!
[NUMBER 9]
Penguin.
[KOUICHI grunts]
[MICHAEL]
No! Number 9!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] We have
no other choice: Retreat!
[ORSON]
Oh, the pornography!
[JIM] It's a day
that'll live in infamy!
[NUMBER 9]
Penguin.
[SORIKO]
Return on Route 26.
With two seats, you can
use the carpool lane!
Why? Of all times.
Who dropped all that porn?
[RITZ sighs]
So, today's fight.
Daimidaler got worked.
[MORIKO] I wonder why
Kouichi went soft on us.
[SORIKO] I inspected all his
equipment thoroughly
this morning. Maybe he
just needs a pill?
[MORIKO]
So, where's our grabby duo now?
[KYOKO] Give it a rest!
The battle's over!
You should stay calm, and gently
talk about your problem.
That sound good?
But talking only
makes things worse!
[KOUICHI] Who the hell are you?
Shouldn't be down here, weirdo.
And this is no
place for cosplay!
[MATAYOSHI]
Beauty Salon Prince!
[KOUICHI gasps]
[MATAYOSHI] This place began
as a mere beauty salon.
But over time,
it evolved into
an electrical engineering
and robotics think-tank.
One that contributed to society
and various political campaigns.
In turn, the beauty
salon attracted
an international assortment
of top scientists and engineers.
In the blink of an eye,
it became a massive
secret society that
you may have seen
paranoid videos about online.
And then there's our
greatest creation yet.
Daimidaler.
A superweapon to fight
the Penguin Empire.
It is our first and
best line of defense.
And so, in conclusion,
it's you who shouldn't
be here, softie!
[KOUICHI groans]
Kouichi, no!
Administrator Matayoshi!
[KOUICHI]
Asshole.
No one cock blocks Kouichi
and gets away with it!
[MATAYOSHI] You couldn't
get your juices flowing
out there, boy! If I hadn't a
stepped in to save your ass
then those Penguins
would have shut you down
like a prom night chaperone.
Am I wrong?
So you did the big porn drop!
[KOUICHI]
You got some nerve.
I don't care what's written
on your business card, pal.
You're gonna stand there
and see my power!
Kouichi, no! Not now!
[KOUICHI grunts]
[KOUICHI] Feel my mighty
grope flow through you!
[KYOKO]
Knock it off, idiot!
What do ya think of that!
[MATAYOSHI]
Sonan.
Uh, yeah?
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI gasps]
[KYOKO sighs]
[KOUICHI]
What?
That dude turned
Kyoko into a wet noodle
without even touching her ziti!
[MATAYOSHI]
There's more to it than that.
[KOUICHI]
Think. He sort of grazed it.
Wait, that's it! Her nipples!
With just a flick of the wrist
he tickled the tip of her tit!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI] And here I thought
I knew all there was to know
about violating a
girl's personal space!
[KOUICHI]
My whole life has been a lie!
When it comes to
grabbing breasts.
I'm like a kid in the lunchroom
without any milk money!
Understand? No two pair of
casaba melons is ever alike!
Fondling bazongas is a science
that demands respect!
Please help me out,
Administrator.
Please educate me.
[MATAYOSHI]
There's more under their shirts
than what you currently grasp.
[KOUICHI gasps]
You must grasp that.
[KOUICHI]
Whether that's supposed to be
a riddle or a metaphor,
I don't get it.
[MATAYOSHI] I don't explain my
vague sayings, I just say them.
You must figure out
the rest for yourself!
[alarm blaring]
[MORIKO] Administrator,
we have a problem!
The firewall for our internal
comm's been breached!
[MATAYOSHI]
What?
I can't believe
those creeps hacked us!
[KYOKO growls]
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] It's been
a long time, Kazuo Matayoshi.
So you're behind this hack.
Penguin Emperor.
Wait, Penguin Emperor?
You're the leader of
the Penguin Empire!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Yes, that is
the definition of "emperor."
Any-who, I'm sure you've
realized from our last scuffle
that you are
clearly outmatched.
Like hell!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
In the interest
of letting bygones be bygones,
we're open to the idea
of a ceasefire or truce.
All we've ever really wanted
are the Hi-ERO particles.
We have no wish to
see more bloodshed.
Hey, what exactly are
HI-ERO particles, again?
I'll explain it!
These bits of matter flow freely
within the microscopic cells
of all living creatures
in the Universe.
I'm surprised you don't
already know this. Anyway...
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Perhaps, we can even work toward
a formal peace treaty--
[KYOKO]
That's a lie and you know it!
Kyoko?
[KYOKO]
Negotiations? A peace treaty?
After what you did to my Father!
You vile birds gave
a good man a stroke!
Like a rub-and-tug?
Not cool, Sewashiko.
[KYOKO]
Two long years ago...
My father was a representative
at the last peace conference.
But you monsters betrayed him,
and committed an atrocity!
[PENGUINS]
Five, six, seven, eight.
With our strong legs we kick,
while we thrust our tails!
Front tails, not gen-i-tails.
Some curve left some curve right
all will go where
space is tight!
You heard right
where space is tight!
[ALL gasping]
[ALL screaming]
They did a dance
about their tail boners!
[KYOKO]
It was just too much for Dad.
Hey, Daddy, you wanna
eat some breakfast?
Banana? They're ripe.
[KYOKO]
Here.
What? Take it.
[KYOKO'S FATHER screams]
No! No! Not that!
--Don't thrust it at me!
--[KYOKO] Daddy, no!
[KYOKO] I'll come visit again
when you stop screaming.
[MATAYOSHI]
You hate the penguins.
[KYOKO]
They're demons.
Never! I will never make
peace with the penguins!
Their tail cocks
dicked-up my life!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Such rude words. When meeting
foreign dignitaries,
the front tail dance
is the Penguin Empire's most
respectful form of welcome.
[MATAYOSHI]
There will be no "peace" talks.
We're not, biting.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Communication
between cultures is never easy.
Therefore we have no
choice, but to unleash
the full might of
Operation Shadow Hell!
[MATAYOSHI]
Operation Shadow Hell?
What the hell?
[JAKE]
Read more on our website.
[KOUICHI]
How'd they get that URL?
[SEWASHIKO] Hold on, gotta
download a plug-in first.
They use Flash?
Oh! It's bad.
[MATAYOSHI]
What?
[MORIKO] It looks like a
MyPlace page from 2006.
I have to scroll way down just
to get to the Announcements.
[MATAYOSHI] Everyone knows
that should go at the top!
This is why you don't
out-source web design.
[SORIKO] They got so ripped off.
I almost feel bad for them.
Almost.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Commence Operation Shadow Hell!
What's happening? Why's it dark?
I'm afraid of solar eclipses!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Does this answer your questions,
Beauty Salon Prince?
Behold, Operation Shadow Hell!
[PENGUINS cheering]
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] With the town
under the cloak of darkness,
people will think it's
nighttime and thus,
return to their homes.
And then, they will
do what all people do
in bed in the dark!
Procreate!
The mass shtooping
will fill the air
with Hi-ERO particles
for our harvesters.
And soon after, our plan
will come to fruition!
And that's not all!
This time, our men are ready for
any pornography counter-attack.
[MATAYOSHI] You fish-eating,
flightless perverts.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Gentlemen.
Status report on the shtooping.
[NELSON]
Um, yeah.
[AUNTIE 2C]
Well, husband's dead,
so it's TV watching for me.
[NELSON] Hi-ERO particle
production is at zero, sir.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Zero?
If they don't reproduce
in darkness, when do they?
Man is a savage,
unpredictable foe.
[MATAYOSHI]
Dispatch Daimidaler!
[ANNOUNCER]
Scramble, scramble! Type-2.
Rise over.
[ANNOUNCER]
Remove castering device.
[SEWASHIKO]
Daimidaler Type-2, Kouichi.
On standby for departure.
Catapult Route 18.
Jointing to Karigakubi.
[ANNOUNCER]
Opening gate 1-8.
Type-2 ejection!
[SEWASHIKO]
Position achieved!
[ANNOUNCER]
Three, two...!
[SEWASHIKO]
Daimidaler entering shaft!
[SEWASHIKO] Route 18,
Karigakubi hatch released!
Daimidaler shoot out!
[SORIKO]
Tandem Seat Front Attack Mode!
Transmutation!
Again?
[KOUICHI]
For real this time. I promise.
This is just so gross.
[KOUICHI] Ooh, I like it
when you play hard-to-get!
[KYOKO screams]
Oh come on!
[KOUICHI] Why can't I get a
firm flow of particles pumping
through my main vein?
[NUMBER 9]
Penguin.
[KOUICHI, KYOKO groan]
[SORIKO]
Hi-ERO particles at 15%.
That puts Daimidaler at
minimum functioning capability!
Admin, do you think that he's--
[MATAYOSHI] Yes, it's the only
explanation that makes sense.
That's it!
[KOUICHI]
So obvious.
I've simply gotten
bored with you!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI groans]
You got bored?
I give up my dignity and
let you play grabby hands
with my beautiful breasts
for the good of Earth
and now you tell
me you're bored?
[KOUICHI]
No, it's not like
"They're gross.
I'm bored" bored.
Imagine if every day
you got to drive to work
in a sweet ass sports car.
Eventually it'd start to feel
like a normal ride, you know?
Like an old hatchback!
And you really think
that makes me feel better?
[NUMBER 9]
Penguin.
[KYOKO screams]
[KOUICHI groans]
[MICHAEL]
The lack of human desire
left something to be desired.
[DENNIS] But it'll all be worth
it if we eliminate Daimidaler!
[MORIKO]
Administrator, we should start
an emergency retrieval!
I disagree.
[MORIKO]
What?
To lose this battle against
this weak-ass opponent
means they don't
deserve Daimidaler!
[ALL gasp]
[MATAYOSHI] Don't let me down,
Kouichi Madanbashi.
Show me what you can do!
The key to victory is
about more than a lust
for big, sloppy water balloons!
[KOUICHI grunts]
[MICHAEL]
Countdown begin!
[NUMBER 9]
10! 9!
[KOUICHI]
Come on, wake up!
[MATAYOSHI]
There's more under their shirts
than what you currently grasp.
[KOUICHI]
That's it! Kyoko.
[KYOKO gasps]
Prepare to get extra freaky.
Wait, hold on? I thought
you were bored of me!
[KOUICHI] No! I'm just over
the over-the-sweater action!
[KYOKO]
Kouichi?
No! What are you doing?
[KOUICHI]
Don't worry. I got this.
[KOUICHI gasps]
[KOUICHI]
That's what I needed!
[SEWASHIKO]
But her bra!
[SORIKO]
He just pushed it up!
[KOUICHI yells]
[KOUICHI]
Daimidaler! Full charge!
[MICHAEL, DENIS]
3! 2! 1!
[KOUICHI]
Finger Barrier!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Oh for the love of--
Daimidaler is showing no damage!
40. 50. 60. 70.
Hi-ERO particle surge! Awesome!
Muladhara, Svadhishhana.
All Chakra Generators are
currently reading green!
Right on!
You dumb penguins
think you can do
whatever you want? Only I
get to screw up this town!
[KOUICHI]
Special attack!
Finger Punch!
[KYOKO]
You did it! We won!
[KOUICHI]
Yeah.
We owe it all to your
creamy, pendulous breasts.
Mm-hm!
[KYOKO gasps]
[MATAYOSHI]
I'm glad you figured it out.
It's the creative mind,
always devising
new thrills and sensations,
that is the most erotic organ.
Well, after the genitals,
epidermis, and boobs of course.
[KYOKO]
Hmph.
I understand now, Administrator.
No wait, I'm gonna
call you Master!
I would be honored to
become your disciple, sir!
As long as there are
boobs in my face,
I'll learn to fondle them right!
[MATAYOSHI] That's the
spirit! We'll go hardcore
on the training as
soon as you get back.
Brace yourself.
[KOUICHI]
Yeah! I'll grope them all night
'til their raw, if that's
what it takes. Right, Kyoko?
Ah, come on!
[NARRATOR] Kouichi
Madanbashi's newfound wisdom
on the matters of
mammaries turned a soft
and embarrassing loss,
into a hard-won victory.
This cocky high schooler
is a wretched pervert,
truly worthy of
piloting Daimidaler!
[RITZ] ♪ That you live
in the ice and you dress ♪
♪ real nice is
of no dispute. ♪
♪ Penguin! Penguin! ♪
♪ Why are you so cute? ♪
[RITZ giggles]
[NARRATOR]
Some men love a supple bosom.
While others, a toned buttocks.
So why can't a girl enjoy the
caress of talking penguins?
Next time:
Menace! Fiery Jake Appears!
Please look forward to it.