[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Blast! Foiled again!
And by that infernal Daimidaler!
To think that I would
face defeat at the hands
of a robot designed by humans!
[NELSON]
Uh, Nelson here, sir.
I would love the opportunity
to fight that malicious mech!
[JIM] No, I shall
accept the challenge!
[DENNIS]
Dennis here! I want a rematch!
[PENGUINS]
Huh?
Penguins!
And you're even cuter in person!
[SORIKO] Yoga, derived from
the Sanskrit root word, "Yuji,"
comes to us from ancient India,
by way of
Santa Monica, California.
We use it to reach a new level
of personal enlightenment...
[KOUICHI] Well your poses
are certainly helping me
reach a new level of arousal.
[KYOKO]
Kouichi!
Aren't you supposed
to be training right now?
[KOUICHI] Hey, don't be
so quick to judge, Kyoko.
It may not look like it,
but even as we speak
I'm deep into training.
What?
In order to reach a rock hard
state of super arousal.
I've been peeping on you and the
three professors every hour,
even while you sleep at night!
Stalking is illegal!
No it's natural!
When you become
a cool Factor like me,
this is your fate.
You know, you could
be my personal trainer,
--emphasis on the "personal."
--[KYOKO] Stop it!
I think she's really
warming up to him.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
How in the h-e-c-k
did you get in here, young lady!
[RITZ] Cute little penguin.
So squeezable.
[NELSON] There's a
human girl in our base!
Wow. So many
penguins to snuggle!
[DENNIS screams]
Ah! Your skin feels so smooth
and properly moisturized.
[MICHAEL] Somebody stop her!
Dennis is being violated!
[NELSON] Grab her before
she gives him PTSD!
[RITZ]
Whoa!
[screams] Your flippers
touched our boobies!
[RITZ]
No!
Not funny!
[MICHAEL]
Your highness!
We've completed our analysis
of this girl's specifications!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Tell me everything!
[NELSON]
Her bust is 32 inches!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
I don't care about that!
[DENNIS]
Her waist is 25 inches!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Enough with the measurements!
[MICHAEL]
Her nipples are pink.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Oh, that's good to know.
Oh, wow. You guys are pervy.
We take it you're
the big bird here?
Question for you then.
May we please
merge with you?
[NELSON]
Merge with us?
[DENNIS]
Like, procreate?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] So this is
what daddy issues look like.
Icky, that's not what we mean.
We would like to become
the newest recruit
in your great penguin army!
We think you penguins
are so completely adorable.
Please let us join you,
your majesty!
We'll even sit on
your eggs for ya!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Well, I guess
having a human under me
isn't the worst idea.
Oh you mean it?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
With one condition!
Huh?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
You must prove your worth to me
by passing the penguin exam.
Pink nipples be damned.
[PENGUINS gasp]
[RITZ]
Penguin Exam?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Oh, the
bar to pass is quite low.
Almost a formality, in fact.
Simply fight and
destroy an elite,
hand-to-hand combatant
of my choosing.
[JAKE]
I will fight this depraved girl!
I am the brave
penguin commando, Jake!
[NELSON]
You?
[MICHAEL] Jake, what would
possess you to fight today,
of all days?
[DENNIS]
People could be hurt!
Front tails could be lost!
Okay, that's enough.
We're in it to win it now.
[DENNIS] You silly girl!
You haven't a clue
about the brave health
struggle Jake's fighting!
This man. This brave,
beautiful man
currently has a fever, of 101.2!
[JAKE sighs]
[PENGUINS]
Stay with us, Jake!
That's amazing.
They're brave even
when they're sick!
We love penguins more than ever!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Well, if he's
sick, then just dog pile her.
I don't care.
[PENGUINS]
Sir, yes, sir!
[NELSON] Your merging
shall be most painful!
[PENGUINS screaming]
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Gasp!
She defeated an elite
penguin commando squad
with a single kick!
[RITZ giggles]
Despite our petite size,
we've still picked up
some Krav Maga.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Gasp again!
You have splendid
fighting ability.
We won.
Here, we'll show you
some more moves now,
so you know what you're getting!
[RITZ]
Brace yourself, Your Highness!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR whimpers]
[RITZ]
These are our fighting skills!
What do you think,
Your Highness?
Did we pass your
little Penguin Exam?
Huh, did we, huh?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Don't be ridiculous!
Knocking out the Penguin Emperor
is the highest form of treason
in the Penguin Empire!
Huh?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
You have failed the Exam.
I bid you good day, sir!
[RITZ sobbing]
He's so mean.
We only did what
he told us to do!
We just wanted to show him
our usefulness and
sweet Krav Maga skills.
[JIM]
Stiff upper lip, child.
Throwing around a reigning
monarch is quite the faux pas.
But believe it or not, he's
still taken a liking to you.
[RITZ]
R-Really?
[JIM] Many years have passed
since a human liked our kind
beyond what they saw
of us in cartoons.
Your passion has
moved us, deeply.
That said.
I know a service you can provide
that'd make you really popular.
[RITZ]
What kind of service?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Maybe I was too rough.
Let my temper get
the best of me.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR groans]
Zounds! What's happening here?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
It's blinding!
Rays of light more
brilliant than those
of any sun in the firmament!
[RITZ] Your Highness,
we're sorry for throwing you.
Please, sir.
We beg you to let us join
the great Penguin Empire.
[JIM] This girl got down
on her knees and polished
each one of our front-tails.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
I can't refuse a girl
who's good with her hands.
You have proven your worth.
Henceforth, this handsy girl
is part of the Penguin Empire!
No! Penguin family!
[RITZ gasps]
Oh, your Highness,
we will serve only you!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Okay there. Huh.
Come to think of it,
I don't know your name.
We're so glad you asked!
Our name's Rikantz Seaberry!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Rikantz?
That's strange and
foreign-sounding.
You'll need something cuter.
Ritz!
[RITZ]
Ritz it is!
[MORIKO]
A penguin robot has appeared!
[MATAYOSHI] Ready Daimidaler
for battle, at once!
I guess they want
another good ass-kickin'.
These guys need to learn,
with your boobies here,
there's no way they can
beat me off my winning streak!
You're sure cocky for a guy
who skimps his training.
[KOUICHI]
Everything will be fine, Kyoko.
Now let me work my magic.
[KYOKO yells]
[SORIKO] Connect to Thruster
[KYOKO] Not yet.
[SORIKO]
Route 15, Shumokozori.
Right. Shumokuzori, roger.
I got it all figured out,
and I'm never losin' again!
[KYOKO] As a girl,
I like his bad boy way,
but as his partner,
I don't know.
I'll have to focus
for both of us.
[MAN 3A]
A huge robot! How original!
[MAN 3B] Where are they
getting all this sheet metal?
[WOMAN 3A] Crap. This means
Daimidaler's on the way!
[RITZ giggles]
[RITZ] It's fun to watch
them panic, but,
we don't want them to leave yet.
The real fun is about
to get started.
[RITZ] First, we need
to take out that big,
thickly ribbed hose,
and insert it firmly into the
hole on the front of the body.
[MAN 3C] It just went
from six to midnight!
[RITZ] Now, fish around with
your finger and pull that plug
out of the rear hole,
but be careful
and don't do it too forcefully.
Parts can tear
easily back there.
When it's time to finish,
give it a tug.
Slide it in to release gently!
[MAN 3D] Too young!
She's still too young!
[WOMAN 3B]
I'll have what she's having.
For more hose suction,
try pulling the hose out
of the hole. Then flip over
and firmly re-insert the hose,
using the opposite end!
For best performance,
remember to always adjust
the unit to the thickness
of your carpet.
Especially if it's an
extra-long, exotic rug!
[RITZ] You may need to push and
pull the unit harder at first,
pushing and pulling back
and forth several times
until you reach
that perfect glide!
[MAN 3E]
This feels weird in public!
[WOMAN 3C]
Are these vacuum instructions?
[RITZ]
So what do you think?
We call this,
"Operation Penguin Vulgarity!"
Stupid humans. So easy
to embarrass them.
[KOUICHI] Fight someone your
own size, giant penguins!
Daimidaler is here, yo!
[RITZ]
Oh, wow. So this is him, huh?
Smaller than we thought he'd be.
[KOUICHI]
Wait, they've got a human!
[KYOKO] Great, now
they're taking hostages?
[KOUICHI] Alright,
that's enough of this crap.
I already knew you guys
were major league assholes,
but now you're stealing
teenage girls, come on?
[MICHAEL]
How dare you insinuate that!
We penguin commandos would
never do something so cowardly!
We're "Major league assholes?"
[RITZ]
Hey, jerk-butt!
No one talks bad about
penguins around us and lives!
[BOTH gasp]
[KYOKO] What?
[KOUICHI] That hot chick
just hopped in the robot!
[RITZ] Sanctions Charge.
Antarctic Number 8!
Okay then, I don't think
that girl's their hostage.
[KOUICHI] She's gone commando
for the Penguin Empire!
By the orders of the
great Penguin Emperor.
We will destroy you, Daimidaler!
[KOUICHI]
Get fisted!
[KYOKO screams]
[KOUICHI groans]
[KOUICHI grunts]
[KYOKO screams]
[KOUICHI yells]
This bot is hardcore.
It's got some good moves!
[KOUICHI gasps]
[KOUICHI]
Where'd it go?
[KYOKO]
On your six.
Right behind us!
Damn this girl!
Keep it together, Kouichi!
If you're not focused,
we can't beat her!
[KOUICHI]
Just let me yell!
Come in, Daimidaler pilot.
Can you hear us?
[KYOKO]
It's the girl!
[RITZ]
We are Ritz.
Short for, "Rikantz Seaberry."
And as a girl who loves
"cute, wittle" penguins,
it's our duty to kill you.
Let's grab some boob!
Hold on! Be patient!
Stop bossing me around
and let me work!
I'm gonna give that girl a
face full of special attack!
You dummy!
If you fight angry you'll
play right into her game!
We hope you're ready.
Because we've got
our own special attack
that's just for you.
Prepared by the Emperor himself.
[BOTH gasp]
[RITZ]
Cock-a-Doodle-Doo. Attack!
[KOUICHI]
What in the hell is she doing?
Oh, no! This might be
too much for Daimidaler!
[SEWASHIKO]
Right arm damaged.
Armor integrity is below
acceptable numbers!
[MATAYOSHI]
Madanbashi, retreat!
[KOUICHI]
I can't!
None of the controls
will respond!
[MATAYOSHI]
Oh, fudge.
[PENGUINS]
Huzzah!
[MICHAEL] That pink-nippled
girl is going to win!
[DENNIS]
I love you, Ritz!
[NELSON]
Finish him!
[MICHAEL]
Huh?
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI] Now what?
[PENGUINS]
Why'd she stop?
[PENGUINS gasp]
[DENNIS]
Ritz is puking!
[MICHAEL]
Morning sickness!
[NELSON]
She's pregnant?
No, we're motion sick!
[PENGUINS] Morning Sick-Ritz!
Morning Sick-Ritz!
[KOUICHI grunts]
He's really upset.
[MORIKO] Lucky for you guys,
while motion sickness
had that Ritz girl
barfing up her breakfast,
we were able to
retrieve Daimidaler.
[SORIKO] And the Penguin
robot pulled out, too.
So today was effectively a draw.
[KOUICHI] That sounds like
loser talk ya ask me!
No matter how you
spin it, I lost today.
[MATAYOSHI] If you don't
wanna feel like this,
you should train harder!
[KOUICHI]
More training?
[MATAYOSHI] You can't just
jump into battle half-cocked
and expect it to go,
"wham, bam, moneyshot."
You need to soften your target
first with some foreplay.
You've gotta fight
smarter in the cockpit!
A decent pilot wouldn't
go through every battle
dependent on Kyoko's
hypnotic chest torpedoes!
[KOUICHI]
Yes, sir!
[SORIKO] I was expecting
something like this to happen,
so I'd already
prepared a special
training program for Kouichi.
[KOUICHI]
I need to get stronger.
So I can beat the hell out of
that stupid, annoying girl!
I mean it! Imma
train crazy hard!
[KYOKO]
Kouichi...
[KOUICHI]
Sorry, Kyoko.
Please don't let another
man touch your gazongas
until I return, having
mastered Daimidaler.
See you on the flip-side.
Let's go, Master!
[KYOKO]
If he's committing to training,
then I'll commit to
him and be patient.
Good luck, Kouichi!
I'll think of you every time
I see a pervert on the bus.
[PENGUINS]
A toast to Ritz!
[MICHAEL]
Congratulations!
[RITZ] Thank you!
[DENNIS] Morning Sick-Ritz!
[RITZ]
You guys, you're so adorable!
We love having penguins
all around us, all the time!
We're in a penguin dream world!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
I love these faceless smiles.
[RITZ]
Greetings, Your Highness!
[DENNIS] And now,
we shall begin our Salute
to Ritz Slideshow Spectacular!
[PENGUINS]
Morning Sick-Ritz!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Ritz,
getting the better of Daimidaler
on your very first encounter
was as impressive
as your toned buttocks.
[RITZ giggles]
We're a natural at driving
around giant robots.
[PENGUINS]
Morning Sick-Ritz!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
I look forward to seeing you
fulfill your potential.
[RITZ]
Roger that!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR laughs]
I'm quite the lucky Emperor
to be surrounded by such
talented and loyal subordinates.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
I do solemnly swear.
I shall obtain
the Hi-ERO particles
needed to complete this
penguin super weapon
and take over the Earth.
In a very penguin fashion.
[SORIKO]
Nice strike!
[SEWASHIKO]
Nice stroke!
[SORIKO]
Enough with the sex puns!
[KYOKO]
It's been ten days.
I hope Kouichi's
holding up okay.
Finish your training.
And come back to me!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KYOKO]
Kouchi, you're back!
Administrator, is he done?
[MATAYOSHI] Yes, it was
a hard, rough program.
But he wasn't above
getting down on all fours
and taking it like a man.
This guys's now a fully insured
and licensed Daimidaler pilot.
You did it, Kouchi.
I'm so proud of you!
Don't touch me!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KYOKO]
You don't like touching now?
[KOUICHI]
Sorry.
Oh, it's weird because we
haven't seen each other
in a while, right?
[KOUICHI]
Stop it!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI grunts]
[alarm blaring]
[MATAYOSHI]
Penguin attack!
Launch Daimidaler immediately!
[KOUICHI]
Yeah! Let's go!
[PENGUINS]
Panty attack!
[MICHAEL] Cover the world
with ladies' undergarments!
[STORE OWNER 3A] These panties
have soiled my muskmelons!
[MAN 3F] Does this sign
mean panties are banned?
[MAN 3G]
It's panty-monium!
[MAN 3H] Now this is a
cherry blossom festival!
[RITZ giggles]
Thanks to a large
population of perverts,
our panty attack's turned
this town into a hot mess.
[KOUICHI]
That's enough!
Daimidaler!
I've waited ten
long days for this,
Rikantz Seaberry it's
time I get my revenge.
[RITZ] You can't see it, but
we're rolling our eyes at you.
Stand in the way of
the Penguin Empire,
and we'll beat you hardcore.
Shouldn't you charge
the Hi-ERO Generators?
[KOUICHI]
Not yet!
Okay.
Let's go Rikantz Seaberry!
Yawn!
[KOUICHI yells]
Ha!
[KYOKO] His piloting skills
have gotten way better.
He hasn't even glanced at
me to charge the Generator,
but the chakra
levels are stable.
I guess he doesn't
need me anymore.
[SEWASHIKO]
Daimidaler's hand-to-hand
combat reaction speed
has increased by 30%!
That was part of his training.
I'm actually impressed.
But it's not
the only difference.
[SORIKO gasps]
[KOUICHI gasps]
[KOUICHI]
What's going on?
I didn't feel like this before.
[KYOKO screams]
[KOUICHI grunts]
[KOUICHI gasps] Her shampoo.
It smells so good! Oh, mama.
Has Kyoko always been
such a grade-A piece of A?
What's wrong, Kouichi?
It's nothing!
Don't look at me during!
[KYOKO] Ever since he
came back, he's treated me
like I'm in the way.
[KOUICHI] What did that
training do to me?
It's like I can't even look
at Kyoko in the face now.
The second I get a
glimpse or scent of her,
my whole body feels like
it's gonna explode!
His moves are different!
I'm putting your
stupid penguin robot
right where it belongs,
in a junkyard!
What did you say?
How dare you make fun
of our penguins
and the Antarctic
Number 8! Douche!
We won't let you
get away with that!
[KOUICHI, KYOKO gasp]
Now, Special!
[RITZ]
Cock-a-Doodle-Doo Attack!
[KOUICHI, KYOKO grunting]
[MORIKO]
It's that attack again!
[SORIKO]
This is bad!
No, Madanbashi has the
skills to beat it now!
I don't know why
it's so different,
--but I do know I got a bunch
--Sometime today please Kouichi!
of backed up Hi-ERO particles
just waiting to get out!
All I need is one
spark to get me goin'
and I'll blow 'em sky high!
[MATAYOSHI]
That's the spirit, son!
[KYOKO groans]
I understand.
Fondling my boobs is the
spark you need, right?
Not this time!
[KOUICHI] If I let go of
Daimidaler's controls.
we'll be defenseless.
That's why I need you to...
To what?
[KOUICHI]
Show me your tits.
Huh?
Don't play dumb,
whip 'em out! Come on!
This job is insane!
[SEWASHIKO]
Body damage at maximum.
Structural integrity failing!
[KOUICHI] Seeing those
puppies is the key to victory!
What are you waiting for?
Five minutes ago,
you wouldn't even
look me in the eye,
now you wanna see me topless?
Uh-oh.
Ever since you returned
from your training
you've been so cold and distant.
Your piloting skills
have gotten way better,
and so has your control
over your Hi-ERO particles!
I wish you'd man up
and tell me to my face
that you don't need me!
What? Who said--?
That's not it.
That's not it at all.
My god I suck at talking.
Damn it we don't
have time for this!
I need you more than I've ever
needed anything ever, Kyoko!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KOUICHI]
I can't beat Ritz without you!
So be a good friend
and show me your tits!
[KYOKO] I'm glad my Dad's
not around for this.
If you don't defeat her,
I'll never forgive you!
[KOUICHI yells]
[RITZ]
What the--?
[MORIKO]
Oh, snap!
[SORIKO]
100. 120. Still increasing!
[MATAYOSHI] Behold the explosive
power of the abstinent man!
It's like a wall of
water bursting forth
from a broken dam!
Here I go!
[KOUICHI yells]
[RITZ gasps]
[KOUICHI]
Finger Punch!
[RITZ screams]
It's really working!
That's right. So long,
Rikantz Seaberry!
Penguin Lovin' Freak!
[KOUICHI]
Special Attack, Finger Beam!
Now that's a finger technique!
Damn right.
[BOTH gasp]
[KOUICHI, KYOKO gasp]
You may have taken this
round against us, Daimidaler.
[RITZ] But next time,
your big-armed robot butt
won't be so lucky.
Penguins rule, humans drool!
So, earlier...
[KYOKO]
What you said.
Is that true?
Wait, what did I say?
Oh, you know.
How you need me now
more than anything ever?
[KOUICHI]
Yes. As sure as I'm handsome.
I need you right in front
of me, Kyoko Sonan.
Oh, Kouichi!
Your sweet devil dumplings.
They look so damn delicious!
Huh?
Stop it!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Even though we lost,
the skills Ritz showed piloting
the Antarctic Robot
were astounding.
The key must be
the Hi-ERO particles.
Ones emanating from her
positively affected the robot.
[JAKE] Another genius
discovery, your Highness!
You've unlocked the secret
of Hi-ERO particles!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Oh, I already knew all that.
It simply slipped my mind.
[JAKE]
The only thing greater
than your intellect
is your honesty!
[JIM] Omega-three supplements
could help with your memory.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Anyway, the amount of particles
Ritz released. It means
that she is a Factor.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR cackles]
I see. What a marvelous twist!
To be continued.
[NARRATOR] The pent-up lust of a
teenage boy exploded to victory.
Don't screw this up,
Kyoko Sonan!
And don't get cocky,
Kouichi Madanbashi!
Follow that advice and
Daimidaler will never lose!
[NARRATOR] The chilling,
salty breeze of the dockyard.
Look up, at the wings
that fly toward you!
Are they heavy with
yearning, or with pity?
Next Episode:
Challenge from 6.
Please look forward to it.