[JIM] This feels like the
death march of the penguins.
[MICHAEL] The Antarctic
Number 11 was our ride,
and those lovesick
kids destroyed it.
We have no other way home.
[RITZ]
Hey, speaking of home,
how much longer until we
get to the Penguin Castle?
[DENNIS] Hmm.
At our current rate,
probably two months.
You've gotta be kidding?
[JAKE] Is it just me,
or have we ended up having
to walk back after each of
our most recent deployments.
[JIM] That's why I make sure
to pick up reading material
to make the time pass faster.
[DENNIS} I wouldn't mind
walking forever if it means
having a set of breasts
pressed against my flesh.
See, everybody benefits when
you give us a piggy-back ride!
[NELSON] Dennis gets all
the back-to-rack contact!
[JIM] It's not fair!
We should take turns!
[RITZ] Damn it,
we're wandering around
in the middle of nowhere,
all because of Daimidaler
and that stupid Kiriko!
They'll pay for this!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
We shall now commence
testing of the penguin device.
[COMMANDO] Even though Ritz
and the others aren't back yet?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Well,
there's nothing else to do
with them gone and
I'm getting bored.
All right, then.
Do we have any requests
for what you'd like to
see this device produce?
[COMMANDO]
Pornographic magazines, please!
[COMMANDO 2]
Ooh, adult films!
Something with a story.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Seems simple enough.
Now, let's begin.
Penguin device, activate!
[PENGUINS]
That's not porn!
Huh? No!
Why am I suddenly naked?
What just happened?
Oh, my dress.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
It's you, Macaroni!
Huh?
[MACARONI]
Your Highness, is that you?
Your Highness!
It's been so long!
[MACARONI giggles]
Your Highness!
[COMMANDO] Is this luscious
lady an old flame of yours,
you dirty birdie, you?
[COMMANDO 2] I could not
be any more jealous!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
What are you blathering about?
She's merely one of my
subordinates in the other world.
[COMMANDO]
Wait, "other world"?
I can't believe
it's really you!
We were so worried by your
disappearance, Your Highness.
We held candlelight
vigils and everything.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Aw, that's very sweet of you.
Hmm? Your jubblies!
[MACARONI gasps]
Your Highness,
what's gotten into you?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
The sag, the bounce.
Yes, it's clear.
You're not wearing
a brassiere, Macaroni.
Sorry, but I'm a lady. I don't
leave home without my
over the shoulder
boulder holders.
[MACARONI gasps]
My bra!
It's not there!
Don't suppose you
have one lying around?
[MATAYOSHI]
Mister Ameku.
Now that you're part
of the staff here
at Beauty Salon Prince
it's time you got to
know the lay of the land,
which is why I'm giving
you this free tour.
[KIRIKO]
Oh, Shouma.
Thanks for giving up
your free time
to take this boring tour.
As long as
I'm with you.
Oh! It's a date!
[KIRIKO sighs]
What, will the two
of you stop breathing
if you're apart
for even a second?
[KIRIKO and SHOUMA]
Uh, sorry.
Come on!
As you both already know,
the penguins poisoned
the public's trust
in Beauty Salon Prince
forcing us to take
a temporary hiatus.
[MATAYOSHI] Well, after taking
the necessary measures,
we're finally
ready to reboot.
I present the H-E-P-R 06,
Daimidaler Type-6, Kiriko.
[MATAYOSHI] It's currently
the best, the newest,
and the strongest
Daimidaler in our arsenal.
With this magnificent beast,
Beauty Salon Prince
will never lose again!
Now listen up.
I'm counting on you.
That means the both of you.
With your extraordinary
powers working in tandum--
Oh, Kiriko,
you're so soft and warm!
You smell so good, Shouma!
[MATAYOSHI]
Give it a rest already!
Miss Kiyuna, you are
aware that Daimidaler
is fueled by
the Factor's power, correct?
I know that, yes.
[MATAYOSHI] And Mister Ameku,
it's up to you
to stimulate
Miss Kiyuna's power,
whatever it takes!
If you know what I mean.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
I get what you're saying.
But why are you being
such a grumpy
Gus all of a sudden?
There's no need to be a meanie,
we know what you're asking,
right smoochie?
[MATAYOSHI]
They're so sickeningly sweet!
I want to strangle them!
[MORIKO] Sir, we're in need
of some direction.
Yeah, and I'm in need
of some erectio--
Stop. Please, just stop.
Some building
materials were left
on our bowling lane and
they're getting in the way.
Hmm. That's the material...
Yeah, what is it?
You know, I could give
you a private tour myself.
So why don't we just
sneak off on our own?
Oh, yes, I'd like that!
[SHOUMA] As long as you know
your way around this place.
[KIRIKO whines]
I am so lost right now!
Please don't be sad,
Kiriko, dear.
Oh, but I'm so useless!
[KIRIKO crying]
Huh?
Nonsense, my love.
It'll be like we're on a fun,
exciting adventure
together, right?
[SHOUMA]
And by the way,
you look super adorable
when you get all lost
and flustered like that.
[KIRIKO]
Aw, Shouma, you're too sweet!
[keypad beeps]
[SHOUMA] Uh...
I didn't mean to do that.
What is this place?
[KIRIKO] I don't know,
but it's creeping me out.
[SHOUMA]
Yeah, ditto.
Let's get outta here.
[door closing]
[SHOUMA]
Uh-oh.
Looks like a dead end.
Someone's a serious hoarder.
Reminds me of
my grandma's attic.
Let's turn back.
[KIRIKO]
Okay.
[SHOUMA]
Kiriko!
[KIRIKO and SHOUMA yelp]
You all right, dear?
You hurt anywhere?
No, are you hurt?
Nope, I'm A-Okay.
Even better now that
I know you feel alright.
And I'm happy that you
feel so nice yourself.
But we do have a bit of
a pickle on our hands.
[SHOUMA grunting]
Dang, it won't budge!
Oh no, we've been
buried alive!
[KIRIKO]
What do we do now?
[SHOUMA sighs]
[SHOUMA]
Please forgive me.
Shouma, what
are you doing?
[SHOUMA] Don't fight it.
Just lie there and be quiet.
Well, that's
a little forward.
This isn't the time or
the place to get all handsy.
[KIRIKO] Why is he suddenly
getting so frisky?
[KIRIKO moaning]
Is it the boxes?
Is he that literal?
Gentlemen do not do
those things in public
to the ladies they love!
[KIRIKO]
How does he go from that
to fondling me like this?
I don't understand boys!
[KIRIKO gasps]
No, please don't do that!
Your hands are like icicles!
Holy fudge, Shouma,
that feels so good!
All right, let's do it!
Now?
But I don't know if
I'm emotionally prepared
to go all the way yet.
What are you
talking about?
This has to
happen now!
Use your power to
get us outta here!
Yeah, now this makes
a lot more sense.
Leave it to me!
[KIRIKO moans]
[KIRIKO, SHOUMA grunt]
So this is...?
The command center,
like I planned.
See, I told you
that I knew my way
around this
place. No problem.
What the hell did you do
to my command center?
[COMMANDO A]
Ooh, it's a slingshot!
[COMMANDO B]
Definitely a slingshot!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] It seems
there are no complications
with transporting
inanimate objects.
Whoa, did you just have
a profound epiphany,
Your Highness?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
While the simple particles
of non-living material
make it through intact,
living things experience
some degree of entropy.
"Entropy"? What's that mean?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
It means they lose something
in the transmission.
Cells, fluids, memories,
even their wallet or
an article of clothing.
It's like the cosmic version of
losing your sock in the dryer.
Hold on, so that's what
happened to my brassiere?
[MACARONI] I wanna make sure
I understand, Your Highness.
You're planning
to create
a new empire here
on this world?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Precisely.
And there may come a time
when I require your assistance.
Of course.
We, the five strongest
warriors of the Penguin Empire
will be at your
service when you call.
[MACARONI]
Until then, Your Highness
and everybody of
this world, take care.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Panties?
[DENNIS]
This doesn't look right.
I'm afraid we took
a wrong turn somewhere.
[RITZ]
Umm.
Yeah, we were
thinking the same thing.
Five hours back.
[JIM] What? Why didn't
you say something?
[DENNIS]
Huzzah, I did it!
Look, everyone!
I caught a jumbo shrimp!
[JAKE]
That's a scorpion!
[JIM groans]
My throat is parched
and I can no longer move.
Same here.
We're exhausted.
[DENNIS] Well, in that
case, I have no choice.
I will give the shrimp
I caught to you, Ritz.
Now, eat and replenish thyself!
[JIM] Dude, I'm telling you,
that's a scorpion.
[DENNIS yelps]
This shrimp just stung me!
[DENNIS groans]
[JAKE] Dennis, no!
Hang in there!
Dennis!
[DENNIS groans] A light.
I see a light.
[JIM] The poison has
spread to his brain!
It's making him hallucinate!
That's no hallucination!
[JAKE]
What is that?
--[JIM] A bird?
--[DENNIS] A plane?
[JAKE] Whatever it is,
it's coming right for us!
[ALL yell]
Ouchie, ouch, ouch.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Welcome home, Ritz.
You did a good job
on your mission.
[RITZ] Yay! Boy,
are we glad to see you!
[JIM]
Penguin Castle?
But I don't understand!
We were just in
the middle of the desert!
[DENNIS]
How'd we get here?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
With that.
I teleported you all
using our fancy
new penguin device!
--[RITZ] Badass!
--[PENGUINS] Huzzah!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
There's just one minor drawback.
"Drawback"?
[RITZ gasps] Ah!
Our panties are showing!
And they're not
even the cute ones!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
So Ritz lost her skirt.
What about the rest of you?
[MICHAEL]
The penguin phone strap
I treasured
so dearly is gone!
[JAKE]
Say it isn't so!
[JIM] The pornography
I was reading is gone!
[MICHAEL]
Oh, the penguin-ity!
[DENNIS] The poison from that
shrimp is gone from my body!
[JAKE]
That's great, Dennis!
We don't get it,
Your Highness.
What's going on?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Well, before I get to that.
Please, forgive me.
But why? For what?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] The penguin
device transportation
is close to perfect.
However, when a living
creature is transferred,
something of theirs vanishes,
and we've yet to find
a solution for that.
Well, that explains why
all of our stuff went missing.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
That's right.
Despite knowing
the risks involved,
I still used the device
to teleport you here.
For putting you
in harm's way like that,
I am profoundly sorry.
[RITZ] You can hold your
head high, Your Highness.
We understand why
you did what you did,
and you have nothing
to feel bad about.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
But I must take responsibility
for subjecting
you all to such danger.
No biggie!
[JIM] Well, if Ritz's skirt
has you on high alert.
[JAKE] We can cover her undies
with our fronties!
If all the porno
mags are gone,
we can satisfy every one of
you with our handy God Scrub!
[RITZ] And we can make another
penguin phone strap in no time!
If any one of us
loses something,
we'll work together
to fill that gaping void.
Because when you're part
of the Penguin Empire,
you're part of a family.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
You guys...
That's it!
We're all taking
a bath together!
[ALL]
Yay!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Ritz.
Post-bath, I'd like you
to get a full physical exam.
[RITZ]
Okay.
Are we preparing
for something special?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] The penguin
device has no trouble
transporting
non-living objects,
so we can put that
operation into motion.
Whoa, holy crap! What is this?
What are you boys
going to do to us?
[JIM giggles]
Anything we please!
Now let's see
what you've got here!
[RITZ whimpers]
Don't look at us!
[DENNIS] Her nipples are as
rosy as a pair of pink posies.
And as for her tulips...
No! Someone help!
[PENGUINS, RITZ scream]
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
We're giving her a medical exam!
This is no time
to play doctor!
[RITZ] Why not do both
at the same time?
Can't a girl have
a little fun?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
We're collecting data
for our next operation.
This is serious business.
Treat it as such.
Fine, be a clam jam.
'Kay, Nelson. Size us up now.
[NELSON]
All set!
[RITZ giggles]
That tickles!
[NELSON] Well, we've gone
over every inch of her.
[JAKE]
Wow, her bust is a C-cup?
[DENNIS] Those are some
dynamite breasts, Ritz!
[MICHAEL]
Truly spectacular!
Ahem. Are you
saying we're sexy?
[PENGUINS]
Super sexy!
[JIM]
Though, to be fair,
Kiriko has some
mammoth mammaries herself.
Huh? You think that
girl's busted-ass bust
would best our rockin' rack
in a tit-to-tit competition?
[JIM]
I didn't say that.
I was merely proposing
hers might be larger than yours.
[NELSON] Ah, the sway
of her ample bosoms
is quite a splendid
sight to behold.
[JAKE] Those are some
dynamite breasts, Kiriko!
Okay! Enough!
Jeez, we get it!
Let's put her boobs
up against ours!
Then we can settle
once and for all
which of us has a better
set of sweater stuffers!
[EMPEROR PENGUIN]
In everyone's life,
there is a challenge
they must overcome.
Go measure Kiriko
Kiyuna's breasts
so we can put this
matter to rest.
[PENGUINS cheer]
With pleasure!
We'll win this battle
of the bulges easily!
No contest!
[SHOUMA]
You ready, Kiriko?
Am I ready for
what, Shouma?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock beats scissors!
Oh, you sneaky rascal!
Do-over.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I win this time!
Now to take my
victory prize.
You fill my life with
so much happiness.
I wanna sing in the streets
for everyone to hear.
You make my heart
race so fast
it's like I could win
a marathon in record time!
[COMMANDO] Their
lovey-dovey-ness has increased,
even since the last
time we saw them!
[KIRIKO, SHOUMA gasp]
[SHOUMA] That voice!
[JIM] Penguin Empire-style,
front tail technique!
Erection Cutter!
Great, the penguins are back!
[SHOUMA gasps]
[KIRIKO]
Shouma, help!
[SHOUMA]
Kiriko! You bastards!
Give me back my girlfriend!
[DENNIS] There's no need
for all the theatrics.
[JIM] We didn't come all
this way today to take
your precious
paramour away from you.
Then what did
you come here for?
[KIRIKO gasps]
[DENNIS giggles]
[DENNIS] We just came to take
your measurements, that's all.
[KIRIKO]
Ew!
You perverts!
Let her go!
[NELSON]
Sorry, Mister Ameku,
but we can't
let you interfere.
So I, Miracle Penguin
Nelson, will distract you,
keeping you both
occupied and entertained!
[SHOUMA growls]
[NELSON]
Do you believe in magic?
Pick a card, any card.
[NELSON yells]
[JIM]
Poor Nelson!
[NELSON] My cards!
[DENNIS] How rude!
[DENNIS] Nelson was merely
trying to dazzle and amuse you!
Just shut up and go!
[JAKE]
You uncouth cretin!
If that's how you want
to proceed, so be it!
[SHOUMA gasps]
[SHOUMA groans]
Shouma, no!
[JIM] That's one of the
Penguin Empire-style
front tail techniques!
Hypnosis Tail!
[DENNIS] Well, now that the
interloper's out of the picture,
we can appraise your bust, waist
and hip sizes, your weight,
as well as the color and
circumference of your areolas.
[laughs] I'll "accidentally"
graze your globes.
[JIM] I'll sneak
a discrete teat tweak.
[NELSON] I just wanna play
with your boobies!
My breasts sure are popular!
[KIRIKO] I don't want these
creep-wads feeling me up.
I've got it!
My boobs are all yours,
so have at 'em, you big,
sexy stud muffins!
[JIM]
Pardon?
[JAKE] Why isn't she
playing hard to get?
[DENNIS]
She's bluffing.
She thinks that if she
acts like a wanton harlot,
we'll be turned off.
[NELSON]
In that case...
[NELSON grunting]
Mmm, this girl has
several heaping handfuls!
So supple, so resilient!
[JAKE] Yes, yes, but are
they larger than Ritz's?
[KIRIKO] I don't get it.
Nothing's happening.
I thought if I baited
them into fondling me,
I'd generate some
Hi-ERO particles
and kick their penguin butts.
[JIM] She isn't putting
up any resistance!
[DENNIS] Huh. I guess she
really is just a wanton harlot.
[KIRIKO] Of course! I can only
produce Hi-ERO particles
when my beloved
Shouma stimulates me.
I'm such an idiot!
What do I do now?
[JIM]
Whoopsy!
I got a bit
preoccupied caressing her.
[NELSON]
That's right!
We still need to
measure all of her curves!
[DENNIS]
Good point. Allow me!
Don't do this!
[SHOUMA]
Stop!
[JAKE] You've awoken
from your trance already?
You penguin d-bags!
I'm not just gonna
let you treat my Kiriko
like some kind of sex object!
Special attack,
Gulliver Stick to the rescue!
Grabbing me with your
stick is so indecent!
Why would you
embarrass me like that?
I'm sorry, it was
the only thing I could think of!
[JIM]
Oh no!
The breasts are being guarded
by some sort of crotch-arm!
[JAKE] But that'll skew
the measurements!
What an underhanded trick!
[NELSON]
His stick won't last long.
Tugging himself through
his zipper will soon
make a mess of his pants,
rupturing the seam in two.
His pants can't
sustain the load!
No, not yet!
Sorry, Kirikooooo!
[JIM]
The Gulliver Stick is down!
[DENNIS]
And so are his pants!
[JAKE]
Now's our chance!
[KIRIKO gasps]
[DENNIS]
Marvelous!
[MICHAEL]
Indeed.
[JIM] Kiriko has a surprisingly
bountiful bosom.
[JAKE]
Now to measure it!
No!
[KIRIKO groans]
[SHOUMA grunts]
Oh god, Shouma!
Don't look at me!
No!
[JIM] Oh no, it's a
Hi-ERO particle burst!
Hmmph.
Daimidaler come here!
[JAKE]
Not again!
[DENNIS]
But we're unarmed!
Bringing in a giant robot
seems like overkill,
don't you think?
[JIM] All we wanted to do
was measure your body!
[SHOUMA]
Against her will!
[KIRIKO] Why do you want
my proportions so bad?
Ooh, are you buying me a dress?
[NELSON]
No!
Ritz merely wanted us
to prove scientifically
that she's much
prettier than you.
[JIM]
Isn't she adorable?
[JAKE]
She had some concerns,
but even without
collecting your data,
it's clear who
the winner will be.
[MICHAEL]
Oh yes, her breasts are
definitely much
larger than yours!
[KIRIKO]
Shouma a little help, please?
Uhh...
[KIRIKO]
Here you go!
[NELSON]
Look!
It's all of Kiriko's
measurements!
[KIRIKO] Just bust,
waist and hips!
A lady should never
reveal her weight!
[JAKE]
Hey! Nifty!
[NELSON]
Mission accomplished!
Now His Highness
won't have to spank us!
Well you got what you came for,
so get out of here!
[JAKE]
Thank you, Kiriko.
You are a credit to your race.
[NELSON] I'll show you that
magic trick next time!
Why'd you give in
to those weirdos?
Because I'm a girl.
And I'm not about
to let some other girl
claim she's prettier than me!
[KIRIKO] But, having
you measure me, Shouma.
That was kind of embarrassing.
[SHOUMA gulps]
Oh yeah, I can see that.
I'm really sorry
I had to do that to you.
Maybe, it might even things
out if you measure my--
Huh?
Uh, stick.
But only if you
want to, of course.
Love to!
[KIRIKO]
Hey, we're back.
You arrogant, loathsome,
no good gutter trash!
[SHOUMA, KIRIKO gasp]
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
It's nice to see you, too,
Beauty Salon Prince.
[MATAYOSHI] What do you
want, Penguin Emperor!
Whoa, so that's
the Penguin Emperor.
He's the emperor
of all the Penguins.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
As you're no doubt aware,
we require a vast amount
of Hi-ERO particles.
Thus, we would
appreciate the cooperation
of the Factors you currently
have in your custody.
[MATAYOSHI]
Absolutely not!
There's no way
in Hell we'd ever let
the Penguin Empire have
even a single particle.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
I regret to hear that.
We'll have no choice, then,
but to pursue aggressive
action immediately.
[MATAYOSHI] What do you
have up your sleeve?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Operation New Penguin!
[MATAYOSHI]
Operation New Penguin?
What the hell is that?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR giggles]
Is the suspense killing you?
Then allow me to elucidate.
This operation is
a new penguin operation!
[MATAYOSHI]
That elucidated nothing!
Yo, Kiriko! Let's finish
this once and for all
and see who's
the best of the breasts!
[BOTH gasp]
[KIRIKO] Don't you dare look!
Oh Dennis, please bring us
Kiriko's
unimpressive proportions.
[DENNIS]
Right away!
For you.
[RITZ gasps]
What? No! Bust 33.
Under the bust: 29.
You mean she's
a freakin' D-cup?
[DENNIS]
In case you forgot, you're a C!
[JIM]
Waist? 22 inches.
Hips? 33 inches.
[NELSON] Damn, that girl
got it goin' on!
[RITZ growls]
Ha! How do you like that?
Guess I won the battle
of the bod, beyotch!
Shut up or we will
end you, co--
[MATAYOSHI]
That couldn't have waited?
You stepped on my carefully
scripted declaration of war.
[JIM]
Your Highness!
Per your orders, we have
the device on standby!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
Ah, yes, good work.
Penguin device, activate!
[JIM]
Holy guacamole!
[JAKE]
What the heck is that?
[PENGUIN EMPEROR laughs]
Rest assured,
I'll put your robot to
good use here, Humboldt.
[NARRATOR]
For the Ritz that they love
they would even sell
off their pornography.
That is the true
measure of a penguin.
Next episode,
"Warning! The Closed Gate."
Please look forward to it.