[SHOUMA]
Oh, Kiriko.
I've loved you since I met you!
Would you maybe
be my girlfriend?
[SHOUMA]
I remember the first time I ever
laid eyes on Kiriko Kiyuna.
It was during the entrance
ceremony marking the start
of the new school year.
A beautiful face, silky hair,
and a voice as soothing
as an industrial-size
jar of hand lotion.
All in all, she was
the woman of my dreams.
Man, I wanna get
into her heart!
So that's what I set out to do.
[CHIEKO]
Settle down!
I'm returning your final exams!
For real? This brainiac
got 100% again!
We already knew
you were a genius!
Oh, please stop.
You're embarrassing me!
[KIRIKO]
Wow, that's really impressive.
[SHOUMA gasps]
I wish I could get
close to that score,
but I'm terrible at tests.
Uh. Well, then,
would you like to study
with me sometime?
[KIRIKO]
Uh--
[KIRIKO giggles]
[SHOUMA]
The more time I spent with her,
the more certain I became
that she was the one.
And now that we've grown closer,
I knew that I had
to tell her how I felt.
Oh, please, Kiriko.
I hope you feel the same way.
[SHOUMA]
She's blushing! That's good!
[SHOUMA gasps]
[SHOUMA]
Why are you glowing like that?
[KIRIKO gasps]
Oh no! What do I do?
What do I do? Make it
stop! Make it stop!
[SHOUMA] Kiriko, just
calm down for a second.
[KIRIKO screams]
[SHOUMA grunts]
Uh. Are you all right?
Oh. I'm so sorry!
It stopped. Thank goodness!
Sorry about that!
[KIRIKO shrieks]
Why me?
Are you okay?
[KIRIKO gasps]
This is so weird.
It seems to stop
whenever I touch you.
[KIRIKO] That does seem
to be the case, yes.
Sorry, but would it be okay
if we stayed like this
a little while longer?
Just until it goes away?
[SHOUMA]
Sure.
[SHOUMA] This is the best thing
that's ever happened to me!
[PENGUINS]
♪ Penguin! The Penguin Empire! ♪
♪ Penguin!
The feel-good Empire! ♪
♪ Penguin! We're your
friend-pire! ♪
♪ Penguin! We're so fun! ♪
♪ Pen-pen, guin-guin,
jolly penguins. Penguin. ♪
♪ We're the shiznits. Pen-pen,
guin-guin, such fun penguins ♪
♪ Pen-pen, guin-guin, ♪
♪ And we're Ritz! ♪
♪ Penguin! The Penguin Empire!
Penguin! The feel-good Empire! ♪
♪ Penguin!
We're your friend-pire! ♪
♪ Penguin! We're so fun! ♪
♪ Pen-pen, guin-guin,
jolly penguins! ♪
♪ Penguin! We're the shiznitz ♪
Hey, boss?
Are we really gonna get
rid of the adult section?
[MANAGER 6A] Yeah, it's sad,
but nobody wants to pay
for their smut anymore.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] We penguins
are the latest craze.
It appears the fickle
people of Earth
have finally come around
to loving our kind.
Isn't that grand?
[MICHAEL]
Look at this, Your Highness!
We've already surpassed
our goals for the week!
[PENGUINS cheer]
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
The humans have unwittingly lost
almost all of their
Hi-ERO particles to us.
Proceed with the plan!
[PENGUINS]
Yes, sir!
[MORIKO] Strike!
It's so hot and humid here.
I'm getting moist in
all the wrong ways.
Can't we do anything about that?
I wish, but the AC's
been shut off.
All we've got now
are the emergency
backup generator and popsicles.
Come on, baby.
Give Mama what she wants!
[SORIKO] Ugh. Get your head
out of the gutter, you sicko.
[MORIKO] This place has
really fallen apart, hasn't it?
In case you forgot,
West Shinjuku was
completely destroyed.
This is what becomes
of the people
who get blamed for causing that.
But it wasn't really our fault!
One of those penguin
robots went haywire!
Yes, that may
be true, but somehow,
we were the ones who
wound up taking the fall
for all of that destruction.
[SORIKO] While we were
busy trying to recover
from all of the chaos,
the Penguin Empire
managed to get the
public on their side.
Those guys have really good PR.
And as a result,
Daimidaler Type-3,
which the self-defense
force had been
very generously funding,
was totally scrapped.
Which in turn was a
major blow to our income,
leaving us
financially decimated.
They call it a "blow" because
it really, really sucks!
[KIRIKO] I don't really know
how to explain it to you.
but my body just
starts to glow like that
whenever I get excited.
Oh. So, uh. I excited you?
If word ever got out about this,
I'd never be able to show
my face in school again.
So I'm begging you, please don't
tell anybody what you saw!
I won't tell a single soul.
Your secret is safe with me.
I can't thank you enough!
You're really a
great guy, Ameku.
Anything for the girl
of my dreams. You name it.
[KIRIKO]
So, about before,
when you asked me
to be your girlfriend.
[SHOUMA whimpers]
[KIRIKO]
Is that offer still valid?
Yes, please, very much, it is!
[KIRIKO]
Oh, thank goodness! Then, yes!
I would like to be
your girlfriend, Ameku!
[SHOUMA]
Yes! I'm the man!
[BOTH gasp]
[KIRIKO giggles]
[KIRIKO]
Hey, Shouma!
Oh no! I can't believe I just
called you by your first name!
I like the way "Shouma" sounds
coming from your mouth.
[KIRIKO gasps]
[SHOUMA]
You're okay. Wanna go in now?
[KIRIKO]
Yeah. Sounds good.
Uh, thanks for inviting me.
I've just been dying to see it.
Uh, see the movie, that is.
I'm glad you decided
to come. Your outfit.
It's great to see you out
of your school uniform.
[KIRIKO gasps]
[BOTH sigh]
[BOTH laugh]
[ZOMBIES moan]
[KIRIKO gasps]
God, I'm so embarrassed.
Don't worry, it's fine.
Would it help if
we stay like this?
I think maybe it would.
[KIRIKO]
That was really good!
[SHOUMA] Yeah!
Though if I'm not mistaken,
it seemed like you were
paying more attention to me
than the movie.
[KIRIKO] What? I wasn't
looking at you the whole time!
[BOTH gasp]
[KIRIKO]
I'm sorry that keeps happening.
[DENNIS]
Hi-ERO particle reaction, ahoy!
[BOTH gasp]
[SHOUMA]
Well, that was weird.
[KIRIKO] Maybe he couldn't
squeeze the hand brakes
'cause he has flippers
instead of, you know, hands.
[SHOUMA]
Shoulda worn a helmet.
[MICHAEL] There's more
where that came from!
[KIRIKO, SHOUMA gasp]
[MICHAEL] Michael!
[NELSON] Nelson!
[JAKE] Jake!
[JIM] Jim!
[DENNIS]
Dennis!
[BOTH gasp]
[PENGUINS] The penguin
commandos have arrived!
[DENIS]
You! Hi-ERO girl!
We must insist that
you come with us!
What could penguins
possibly want with Kiriko?
[JAKE] This doesn't
concern you, microphallus!
[SHOUMA gasps]
Please hand the
girl over, tiny-tool!
[NELSON]
Yeah, shrinky-dink!
[DENNIS] Mini-manhood!
[MICHAEL] Teeny weenie!
[SHOUMA]
I hate these guys!
Kiriko's my girlfriend
and I won't just
give her over to you!
I'll protect her!
[KIRIKO]
Oh, Shouma!
[JAKE]
My, what a brave young man.
Perhaps you'd like
to settle this
with a friendly competition?
[SHOUMA]
Whaddaya mean?
[JAKE] If you're triumphant,
we won't lay a flipper
on your little sweetheart.
We shall duel as
gentlemen do, one-on-one.
All right, fine,
I accept your challenge!
[JAKE]
As for the terms.
[KIRIKO]
Huh?
[JAKE]
We will compare front tails!
[SHOUMA gasps]
I can't compete with that!
[NELSON] Look at that.
The ill-endowed boy is scared.
[DENNIS] You know, Jake,
he is but a child.
Perhaps you should give
him a bit of a handicap?
[JAKE]
Like so?
[PENGUINS]
Ooh!
[JIM] Bravo, Jake. It does
appear less intimidating
when it dangles.
Damn it, they're just
mocking me, aren't they?
But how can I possibly win
against his giant front tail?
[SHOUMA'S DAD]
Son, if you ever feel inadequate
in a locker room, remember this.
[SHOUMA gasps]
That trick my father showed me.
Dad. I finally need it!
Uh, Kiriko. Sorry, but I
need you to turn around
and cover up your ears for me.
Oh. Okay.
All right then, let's do this!
[JAKE]
Such confidence!
[SHOUMA grunts]
Now, get a load of...
...my Gulliver stick!
[NELSON] Hold on.
Did he say "Gulliver's dick"?
[JAKE]
Odd name for a fake penis.
[MICHAEL]
Does he think we're blind
'cause we don't have eyes?
[JIM]
Have you no shame?
[SHOUMA yells]
[KIRIKO gasps]
I step way outside
my comfort zone,
and then they mock me!
What's wrong with you?
What happened while
my back was turned
and my ears were covered?
What did you do to my boyfriend?
[JAKE]
We didn't do anything.
[KIRIKO]
This means war!
I'll kick all of your tails,
front and back! Shouma!
Say something to excite me.
I know you're not
in the mood right now,
but please, just try
to make me glow!
They mocked my
Gulliver stick, Dad.
You said it would make
them think I was a big boy.
Not sexy.
[KIRIKO] If he can't
get my heart pumping,
I'll take matters
into my own hands.
[SHOUMA gasps]
[PENGUINS]
What?
Thank you, Shouma!
That's exactly what I needed!
I feel like I can take
on the whole world!
[JAKE]
So many Hi-ERO particles.
[KIRIKO] Kiriko Punch!
[JAKE groans]
[KIRIKO] Kiriko Beam!
[PENGUINS groan]
Kiriko. Cutter!
[DENNIS] Your Hi-ERO particles
are truly impressive.
[KIRIKO]
That's the power of love!
[SHOUMA]
Oh, Kiriko.
I'm so happy you helped
yourself to my tongue
like it was a free breadstick.
[KIRIKO giggles]
I'm glad it's complimentary!
[JIM] I can't bear to watch any
more of this sickening display
of adolescent love.
[NELSON]
Look to the skies instead!
Isn't it a lovely sunset?
[PENGUINS]
Oh!
[JAKE]
Oh yes, quite lovely!
[MICHAEL]
Lovely indeed!
[DENNIS] Let us frolic
in its majestic beauty!
[PENGUINS]
Yay!
My Kiriko, nothing on
Earth can get in the way
of our romantic love fest.
You're right about
that, sweetie.
[MATAYOSHI]
Actually, I'm afraid he is not.
You disappoint me, wasting
precious Hi-ERO particles
canoodling with some boy toy.
[KIRIKO]
Administrator Matayoshi?
How can you just show up
here and say that?
I don't understand!
Well, "canoodling" means
to engage in lustful behavior.
To fool around,
to play doctor, to smooch,
to make out, to hook up
and get busy!
I know what that means,
just not why you're here!
Hey, do you know this guy?
Uh, well, he's kinda,
sorta, maybe a--
[MATAYOSHI] Let me share
something with you, boy toy.
[SHOUMA]
Okay.
Kiriko's nipples are as pink
and perky as a piglet's ear!
[KIRIKO] Oh my God, why would
you ever say such a thing?
[MATAYOSHI]
Would you rather I call them
"brown and misshapen,
like a melted chocolate coin"?
[KIRIKO]
Don't say anything!
[SHOUMA]
Is he your ex?
[KIRIKO]
No, I swear!
I lead a group.
An elite organization
she was once part of.
Kazuo Matayoshi.
So you're like her boss?
Please give it a rest!
I'm trying to forget
that part of my life!
[MATAYOSHI]
Shut up! Miss Kiyuna.
Have you already forgotten
that the Penguin Empire
is hunting you down to get
at your Hi-ERO particles?
[KIRIKO gasps]
[KIRIKO]
But I don't...
I don't want this thing!
[MATAYOSHI]
Believe me.
There will come a day
when you need that.
So hold onto it.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
What happened to you?
[NELSON] We found a young lady
who might be a Factor,
but we failed to capture her.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
What?
[DENNIS] Then we ran off and
didn't stop until we got here.
Except for a brief
ice cream detour.
[PENGUIN EMPEROR]
You were outmatched again?
Oh, penguins!
Hang in there!
[JAKE] We put up a good fight,
but it took a lot out of us.
Perhaps some rest
would serve us well.
[RITZ] Oh no! Jake!
Oh, she'll pay for this!
Nobody messes with our penguins
and gets away with it!
We're gonna go find
this Kiriko bitch
and whoop her ugly ass!
[PENGUIN EMPEROR] Bear in mind,
as a Factor candidate,
she's incredibly dangerous.
Ritz. Please bring the girl
back here in one piece.
You got it!
[CHIEKO]
So, it's come to my attention
that you began dating
Kiriko Kiyuna last month.
Well, now you gotta dump her!
[SHOUMA] I don't see how
that's any of your business.
[CHIEKO]
Okay.
Listen, there's been talk of
scrapping the recommendation
we were planning to send
to MIT on your behalf.
[SHOUMA]
What? But why?
[CHIEKO] Everyone at this
school is grossed out
by your nonstop public displays
of awkward affection.
t's like watching two
emojis trying to mate!
Hey! We have the feels!
I'm sorry if that makes a
few people uncomfortable--
[CHIEKO]
A few? It's everybody!
And by the way, my raise
hinges on your success!
Think about how this affects me!
So it doesn't matter
what I want?
[CHIEKO]
Look, I get it.
You're at that age.
It's natural.
You just want a couple
of lady lumps to grab
and it makes no difference
who they're attached to,
so, grab onto mine.
[SHOUMA]
No, that's not what I want!
[CHIEKO]
Oh, playing hard to get?
Oops.
Why settle for bee
stings when you can
have the whole hive?
[SHOUMA whimpers]
[CHIEKO]
You can touch 'em all you want.
as long as you ditch Little Miss
Training Bra and study hard.
Get it?
[SHOUMA gasps]
I love Kiriko and only Kiriko!
And I won't break up with her,
no matter how many breasts
you shove in my face!
Wait!
[SHOUMA] I can't believe
I almost let Miss Chieko
suck me in with
her feminine wiles!
I'm a disgusting
piece of garbage!
I need to apologize
to Kiriko right away!
I have to tell her
how I really feel!
I have to tell her I love her!
Where are you, Kiriko?
Uh, I think she's
in the locker room.
[SHOUMA]
Thank you!
Why are these so
hard to unclasp?
Kiriko I love you!
[KIRIKO gasps]
No!
[SHOUMA groans]
[KIRIKO]
Oh, Shouma!
[SHOUMA groans]
[KIRIKO]
I'm so sorry! Are you all right?
Sure. Never been better.
Oh, you poor thing.
Show me where it hurts.
No. Really, I feel
swell right now.
Then again, every time
I'm near you it feels like
I'm swelling up with
so much happiness
I could just burst
at any moment.
That's exactly how I feel!
[KIRIKO] From now on, I'll have
Shouma's love in my life.
But, do I deserve it?
[BOTH gasp]
[NELSON]
So, we meet again.
These guys are
totally stalking us.
[RITZ]
Welcome to penguin school!
You must be Kiriko Kiyuna.
Don't be nervous.
We're under strict
orders to bring the girl
who emits Hi-ERO particles,
which would be you,
back to the Emperor, unharmed.
[RITZ]
However...
Don't mistake us not killing you
for us not hating your bony ass!
After what you did to them,
our poor little penguins
ran all the way home,
completely wiped out.
It took three whole days for
their front tails to recover!
And for that, we will
never forgive you, bitch!
Hey! There is no need
for name-calling!
Okay, Kiriko, use your light
and send these guys packing.
Yeah. Let's get my
pistons pumping!
[RITZ] Hey, what are
you guys up to?
[SHOUMA]
This should get you going.
[JAKE] These kids today!
Have they no decency?
[JIM]
This is a public place!
[RITZ] Uh. What's goin'
on over there, kids?
[SHOUMA, KIRIKO]
Uh.
Is something wrong?
Maybe I've gotten too
used to kissing you?
I don't make your
heart aflutter anymore?
[KIRIKO] What do we do?
What do we do?
I can't produce any
Hi-ERO particles!
[SHOUMA] Calm down,
there has to be some other way!
Seriously, you thought
you'd get your rocks off
from just a kiss? Adorable.
What do you mean,
"just a kiss?"
Yeah, how else do boys and girls
please each other
with their mouths?
[RITZ]
That's just sad.
As long as you're
gonna be all gross
and lovey-dovey in public,
you might as well do it right.
Nelson.
[NELSON]
Yes, ma'am!
[KIRIKO]
What are you doing?
[RITZ]
Sex ed class is now in session!
And we're gonna teach
you ripe young virgins
a thing or two about
a thing or two.
First up, the titties!
[KIRIKO, SHOUMA gasp]
Yeah. That's it, Nelson.
Go to town on them
all you want today.
[NELSON]
No prob!
[KIRIKO, SHOUMA gasp]
[RITZ] Nelson!
[RITZ] We said, "Go to town,"
not "Show the town!"
[NELSON]
I'm improvising!
[RITZ]
You dirty dog!
[JIM] Why does Nelson
get to have all the fun?
[DENNIS]
Let us join in, too.
[SHOUMA] She emits
the same light as Kiriko!
[RITZ] 'Kay. Stop.
[NELSON] Yes, ma'am.
So you see? It's all about body,
touch and skinship.
We do this kind of stuff
with our penguins every day
and it still gets
my kitty purring.
[RITZ] We're way past a
couple of kids who get off
on just a little tonsil hockey.
Hey! Don't you look down on us!
We could do that,
too, no problem!
Yeah, I'm not so sure.
Oh, we didn't realize
you were so advanced.
Well, in that case, do you
think you can handle this?
[KIRIKO, SHOUMA gasp]
[RITZ] Take a good look.
'Cause this is how real
grown-ups get freaky
with their bad selves!
It's called God Scrub! Boom!
[PENGUINS]
Oh yeah, there it is!
[KIRIKO, SHOUMA gasping]
[RITZ giggles]
You see how Nelson's squirming?
We'd say it feels pretty
damn good for him.
[NELSON]
Oh, fantastic!
[MICHAEL] Oh my, what
a plethora of pleasure!
[JAKE]
He won't last long!
[DENNIS]
We're so randy!
[RITZ]
Big finish!
[NELSON]
Ah-Ugh!
It's a handy skill to
have in your toolbox.
[KIRIKO]
I can't do that.
Wow, how pathetic.
Well playtime's over.
You've gotta come with us,
Miss Uptight prude!
[SHOUMA]
This is bad!
I have to figure out some
way to get Kiriko excited!
That's it!
[SHOUMA]
Kiriko.
I need you to trust me
and do what I say.
Of course!
Turn around and raise
your arms. Over your head.
Um. Like this?
[SHOUMA yells]
[KIRIKO gasps]
No!
[RITZ]
Hi-ERO particles?
[SHOUMA]
Yes! It worked!
[KIRIKO]
Shouma!
Uh-oh!
[KIRIKO]
You pervert!
[RITZ]
Michael!
Way to go! Let's
make a break for it!
Okay.
Don't let 'em escape!
We have to capture them!
[SHOUMA, KIRIKO panting]
[KIRIKO]
Shouma!
[RITZ] It's cute you thought
you could get away from us,
but as you can see,
you were wrong.
[KIRIKO]
Put Shouma down!
Very impressive. Your Hi-ERO
particles back there
were comparable to Kouichi's.
A power like yours would
definitely be a major asset
to the Penguin Empire. Too bad!
You deserve the death
penalty for attacking
dear Michael like that!
We're making it our personal
mission to destroy you!
[KIRIKO gasps]
Kiriko!
[KIRIKO]
Even with my Hi-ERO particles
I can't win against
a giant penguin robot.
But I've gotta do something.
They've got Shouma!
[RITZ] Hmm, it's not enough
to hurt you physically.
We wanna torture you
psychologically, too!
[KIRIKO]
What are you gonna do to him?
[RITZ] Oh, we are gonna
do dirty, dirty things
to your precious
little boyfriend.
[KIRIKO] Huh?
[RITZ] All kinds of things.
[KIRIKO] What?
[RITZ] Aww, don't worry,
big boy, we'll be gentle.
Hey! Hands off!
Stop it! You leave
my man alone!
[KIRIKO screams]
[RITZ]
Oh man, this is too funny!
You're full-on freaking
out and we love it!
Does this doofus really
mean that much to you?
[KIRIKO] So help me,
if you do that again, I swear.
[RITZ] You swear?
Now we gotta hear that!
No, bad touch! Bad touch!
[NELSON]
Here comes the God Scrub!
[JIM]
Wish that were me!
[DENNIS]
We are so randy!
Oh, Kiriko, I love you!
No matter what this
dirty whore does to me,
it's you that I love! You will
always be the only girl for me!
You sicken us.
[KIRIKO]
Shouma, I...
[SHOUMA]
Huh?
[KIRIKO]
There's something...
Something I have
to tell you, Shouma.
[RITZ]
Huh?
[SHOUMA]
Really? Right now? What is it?
[KIRIKO]
I've been lying to you, Shouma.
[SHOUMA]
Huh?
[KIRIKO] But I can't bear
to do it to you anymore.
I have to unburden myself
and tell you the truth.
About what?
In order for me
to go through life
passing as normal, fitting in.
I was always forced to
suppress this glow of mine.
I lived in constant fear.
Every day, worried that I
would finally be found out.
Then one day,
[KIRIKO]
an awkward boy appeared.
I couldn't believe
there was somebody
who could keep
my light in check.
And on top of that, this
somebody actually liked me.
He was loyal to me
and it was all just so--
Just so convenient.
[SHOUMA gasps]
[KIRIKO] The truth is
I started dating you
so I could use you.
And for that.
I am truly sorry.
[SHOUMA]
I don't--
You're telling me that all of
this was nothing but a lie?
[KIRIKO]
I hated lying to you, Shouma.
It killed me.
All I wanted was to protect you,
but I just couldn't lie anymore.
This sucks. But I don't care!
It won't change the way
that I feel about you at all!
[KIRIKO]
I have one more confession.
Huh?
I love you so much!
[KIRIKO]
You're cool and kind and smart!
I love the Shouma that's
such a good friend to people!
But I also love the
Shouma that only I know!
I'm totally obsessed with you.
I can't sleep at night 'cause
I'm only thinking of you!
[KIRIKO] And then even when I do
sleep, all I dream about is you!
In class, I think about
how when we're married,
my name'll be Kiriko Ameku
and I doodle it
over and over again.
Every time I look at your face,
I feel my heart stop beating.
I love you so much
it hurts! I love you!
I wanna shout it so loud that
the whole world can hear.
Kiriko Kiyuna is completely
and utterly in love
with Shouma Ameku!
[RITZ] Didn't you just finish
saying how you were
only dating this
loser to use him?
[KIRIKO]
Yes, at first I was.
But every day, I fell
more and more hopelessly
in love with this
wonderful, sweet boy.
And now I'm head
over heels for him!
I had to clear the air first.
I didn't want there to be
any secrets between us
because I want us to
be together forever!
[RITZ]
Ah, got it.
Then it should be
especially painful for you
to watch the love of
your life get a God Scrub
so intense he may
never walk again!
Hey, you leave my
ding-a-ling alone!
[KIRIKO]
I don't wanna fight,
and I don't wanna give
up my peaceful life.
But if I have to...
To protect Shouma...
[KIRIKO]
Daimidaler come here!
[NARRATOR] As long as
there are front tails,
I'm sure "it" must exist, too.
A world protected by love.
Next episode: Hurrah!
Antarctic Number 11 Appears
Please look forward to it.