[ENTERPRISE]
We look like humans,
but we are powerful weapons.
This is the Mental Cube.
They are mysterious crystal
substances acquired by humanity
through their battle
against the Sirens.
They are also the foundation
upon which we were created.
Filled with their power,
we have the strength
to fight the Sirens.
It is the power of warships.
Strong enough to tame an
ocean and silence Sirens.
Humanity reclaimed the seas with
the help of the mental cubes.
But, it wasn't enough.
Some people wanted more and
alliances eventually split.
One side was called
The Red Axis,
This included the Sakura Empire
and Iron Blood.
Due to their desire to
acquire the Sirens' power
for themselves, they raised a
rebellion against Azur Lane.
Even when facing our
common threat, the Sirens,
conflict between
human factions continues.
The truth is,
war never changes.
It's exactly the same,
no matter the era.
[SAN DIEGO stammers]
They got us. I didn't expect
them to attack us first.
I'm not surprised that
they joined Iron Blood.
It's to be expected. But...
Perhaps they moved too soon.
They don't know
the Sirens' power.
How dangerous it is.
[ILLUSTRIOUS]
We need to focus on rebuilding.
The main Royal Navy forces
will be arriving soon.
We mustn't be caught
off guard ever again.
[PRINCE OF WALES] Thank goodness
for Eagle Union's Enterprise.
She truly saved us this time.
[ILLUSTRIOUS] Yes. But at great
risk to her own existence.
[PRINCE OF WALES]
Her strength is limitless.
She fights without hesitation,
like an arrow loosed from
its bow. And yet...
You're through.
[ILLUSTRIOUS] Let us not
forget that when a bow
is strung too tightly
it can easily snap.
[sighs] Seems like we all
made it out safe, at least.
Oi! Laffey, are you okay?
I'm sleepy. It's nap time.
Not a good place to
take a snooze.
[gasps]
Hi Javelin! Hi Laffey!
[UNICORN giggles]
Hey there, Unicorn!
Are you alright? Are you hurt?
[UNICORN] Mm. I'm fine!
Thanks for asking!
Great work, both of you.
You kept us safe.
[gasps]
Hold on!
[ALL gasp]
[yelps]
[whines]
Laffey! Why'd you do that?
Sleepy. And so hungry, too.
Night‐night.
[gasps]
I'm sure you're quite tired.
Do go inside and rest, Dear.
Um, wait!
I believe you were
just ordered to rest.
[UNICORN giggles]
[JAVELIN grunts]
[LAFFEY groans]
Wow. I need a drink.
[CLEVELAND]
Keep it steady! Almost there!
And, stop!
[sighs] Can't believe how much
maintenance we still have to do.
[SAN DIEGO]
Look at my ship! No!
[GLOWWORM gasps]
It's bad.
I wish we at least
had a repair ship
to help us out with this mess.
Huh?
[grunts]
[CLEVELAND]
Hey, Enterprise!
You shouldn't be
here right now!
You should be recovering
from how hard you pushed
in that last battle!
I'm fine, thanks.
[CLEVELAND]
How is that possible?
[ENTERPRISE] All emergency
repairs are complete.
I've still got some
fight left in me.
[ENTERPRISE grunts]
[CLEVELAND gasps] See what
I mean? You need to rest!
The enemy hasn't gone very far.
I'm not going to lower
my guard just yet.
[CLEVELAND gasps]
[ENTERPRISE grunts]
[CLEVELAND sighs]
Good grief!
[KAGA gasps]
[AKAGI] There we go.
Just hold still.
But. But why are you
so close, sister?
[AKAGI] Oh no, You have a
cut on your face, too.
[KAGA] It's such a minor injury.
Pay it no mind.
[AKAGI]
No it's not.
A scar left on your beautiful
face would be a tragedy.
[AKAGI] I insist you learn to
take care of yourself.
If something were to happen
to you, I would be very sad.
My deepest apologies,
Dear Sister.
But this body isn't‐‐
I understand. But we are as
close as actual sisters,
And elder sisters always love
their baby siblings deeply.
[giggles]
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[thud]
Oh. Bad time? I can come back.
What do you want?
Well, first I want you to stop
glaring at me. We're allies.
You are part of Sakura Empire
und I am from Iron Blood.
Right?
Absolutely.
We are all very fortunate to
have the same goals and ideals.
Everything we do is to ensure
the victory of Red Axis.
Right. Like the way you
controlled the Siren ships?
That was quite impressive.
Even if they were merely
mass production models.
Or is that part of
the achievement? Ja?
[AKAGI] Well. Everything that
happens is Heaven's will.
[PRINZ EUGEN] Und yet, you're
still being quite cautious.
I'm confused as to why
you didn't go ahead
und destroy that base.
Did the scratch on your
sister's face frighten you?
[KAGA gasps]
[PRINZ EUGEN giggles]
[grunts]
Oh goodness no. A face I love
could never frighten me.
They need to be
teased a bit more.
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Hmph. Sicher.
[AKAGI]
That ship is quite special.
You would be foolish
to underestimate her.
Eagle Union's Enterprise, ja.
Also known as Grey Ghost.
True, she can be troublesome.
[ZUIKAKU]
My elders, I've found them.
A detached force.
[KAGA]
It's just as Ayanami reported.
Well then. I guess we have
another chance to toy with them.
Alright Fifth Division,
they're yours.
I know you're still new,
but this is hardly a
difficult errand. Copy?
[ZUIKAKU]
Understood.
Good. Moving on.
I have a request, Prinz Eugen,
famed warrior of Iron Blood.
The Fifth Carrier
Division found leftovers.
We shouldn't let them go.
I am so embarrassed
to admit this,
but I worry deeply
about my juniors daily.
If they just had Iron Blood's
support on their side,
I know I'd feel more secure
about their endeavors.
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Hm?
Fine, I suppose.
[grunts]
I'll be taking Z23 und that
Ayanami girl from your camp.
Yes, we'd be honored to watch
a display of your strength.
[Z23]
Ayanami!
[AYANAMI]
Hm.
Z23.
We're being sent on a mission.
We'll be heading out soon,
so please follow me.
There's another battle already?
[Z23] Yes. An enemy fleet
is away from their base.
We will strike them
before they return.
[AYANAMI]
Hmm. Enemy.
It's not that I'm
against fighting,
but I don't like it.
Wach auf! This is not about
whatever you like or don't like!
How 'bout what you like?
Do you enjoy fighting?
[Z23 gasps]
It's not about me either.
Our preferences
are not relevant.
We have a duty to
execute our mission.
[AYANAMI]
Hmm.
We don't get to
choose the mission.
We're warships, after all.
Our entire purpose is
to fight when requested.
[sighs] How can that be all
there is? I don't understand.
That girl. I hope she's okay.
[LAFFEY]
Hm? Oh. You mean Ayanami?
Ayanami, right...
I wonder if we'll
have to fight her.
‐‐[wings flapping]
‐‐[JAVELIN gasps]
It's that bird.
[ENTERPRISE]
Mm?
[JAVELIN gasps]
Hello there, Enterprise!
[JAVELIN] W‐Would you
like a bite of my food?
No, but thank you.
[JAVELIN grunts]
[LAFFEY]
Enterprise, are you hurt?
[ENTERPRISE]
Mm? So you can tell?
It seems my healing
has slowed down lately.
[gasps] Then why aren't
you resting somewhere?
All critical repairs
are complete.
There's nothing to worry about.
[gasps]
[JAVELIN] Enterprise is the
strongest Eagle Union ship.
I think that probably explains
her stubbornness. But...
But why? Why would you push
yourself so far in battle?
Aren't you exhausted?
[gasps]
That's a strange
question, considering.
I never analyzed how
much I fight or why.
It's my purpose for existence.
[LAFFEY sighs]
Yeah, it's mine, too.
But I don't like to
fight when I'm sleepy.
Okay, Go back to sleep!
[sighs]
I'm still so tired,
but I don't like it when mean
people pick on my friends.
When they do, I fight harder.
What do you think
about that, Enterprise?
Well, I...
[HAMMANN grunts]
Hammann, calm down.
Are you kidding?! How can
you expect me to be calm
when my entire base is being
threatened right now?
Because. We just told you
the base has reported
that the enemies have
already been repelled.
We have to hurry!
How is she so spastic?
She's been like this
since yesterday.
This ghost is so exhausted.
I need some shuteye.
Thank goodness the enemy
was at least pushed back.
I heard it was
Enterprise who did it.
[NORTHAMPTON] Enterprise? Wait.
Hornet, isn't that your...?
My sister. Yeah, I guess
it is a bit annoying
being related to a champion.
[HAMMANN] Hey! The enemy could
show up here at any moment!
Less chit‐chat!
Let's get focused!
Right. I suppose Hammann does
have a point. It really would be
in our best interest to
hurry this party along.
Everyone, listen!
[ARIZONA]
What's wrong, Helena?
Argh. Well, darn, I guess
we were too slow!
[HELENA]
Sakura Empire carriers.
[LONG ISLAND gasps]
They look really strong.
We're staring at a bunch
of bathtub tug boats.
Let me handle these goons.
[grunts]
[SHOUKAKU gasps]
I feel so faint!
How could the superiors be so
mean and bully me like this?
I didn't do anything.
Right, Zuikaku?
You really shouldn't take it
so personally, Big Sis.
Besides, we have a good
opportunity here.
The First Carrier elders will
finally see our strength.
I see. I admire the way you're
always thinking ahead, Zuikaku.
And I'm giving you my word that
I will always have your back
no matter what.
[ZUIKAKU grunts]
And as long as you're with me,
I have nothing to fear!
We have to go help
Hornet and the others.
Which ships are
ready to move out?
[ILLUSTRIOUS]
There you are!
Something's wrong
with Enterprise!
What is it?
[CLEVELAND] Enterprise, wait!
You're going too far ahead!
Slowing down is a waste of time!
[grunts]
You can't fight like this when
you're severely damaged!
It's irresponsible and reckless!
Hornet's my sister‐‐
I have to.
[CLEVELAND exhales]
Oh, I understand.
I mean, It's great to see you
have a human side after all!
Well, in that case,
I'm with you!
I have many sisters myself,
So I know how you feel.
I just wish we had some escort
vessels to back us up, ya know?
I want to help you, too.
Same here! We've got
quite the team!
[CLEVELAND gasps]
[chuckles]
Let's do it!
[LONG ISLAND]
Oh, no...!
[HAMMANN groans]
Pretty bubbles in the sea.
♪
This melody's a requiem.
Its purpose is to bring
peace to the dead.
♪
[HORNET grunts]
[HORNET] It's not fun being
the only one on defense!
Could I get some back up?
[ZUIKAKU]
I got you!
[gasps]
Aw, damn!
What the...?
[gasps]
When did you get here?
Go on!
Whoa, thanks!
[ZUIKAKU gasps]
Grey Ghost! I knew you'd come!
If it isn't Eagle Union's
strongest carrier!
You are a worthy
opponent, indeed!
Heh. Ready? It's time
for us to duel!
Hey there, Hornet!
We're here to help you!
Nice timing, thanks! I was
starting to get a bit nervous!
Whoa... This is our
chance to come back.
Give me just a second
to bring out my ship.
Und Feuer!
[ALL gasp]
[PRINZ EUGEN laughs]
[ALL gasp, grunt]
Oh great, now what?
Guten tag , ladies. Looks like
you're having so much fun.
Can we play?
You're Iron Blood, aren't you?
Z23, it's your turn. You good?
[Z23]
Mm.
I am Z23, a strong
Iron Blood destroyer.
You're standing in the
place of your final defeat.
No way! It's Ayanami!
[gasps]
Take the others with you
and head back to base.
Why? What are you doing?
Does this mean you're
volunteering to be the breach?
That's an honorable act.
Even by an enemy.
[UNICORN]
U‐chan!
[phone rings]
Hello, Azur Lane base command?
It's been a rather
long time! Wales!
Your Majesty?
[QUEEN ELIZABETH]
The wait is over.
I, Queen Elizabeth, and my
noble fleet have arrived
to make everything splendid!
[PRINCE OF WALES]
Thank you, Your Majesty,
our allies are currently
under attack.
[QUEEN ELIZABETH] Yes, I know
what's going on, Wales!
And I've already made
my brilliant move!
[BELFAST giggles]
[ENTERPRISE grunts]
[ZUIKAKU]
No you don't!
[grunts]
[ZUIKAKU] Plenty more
where that came from!
I expected you
would be stronger.
[gasps]
[grunts, shouts]
Zuikaku! Please stop!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[ZUIKAKU gasps]
No!
[grunts]
You've gotta be kidding!
[gasps] Are we gonna
have to fight them now?
Poor thing. She's morally
conflicted by this.
I can't wait to see
what she decides to do.
What? Hold on.
Hey! What do you think
you're doing now?
[LAFFEY sighs]
I'm sleepy. So, never mind.
What? Nein! You're not
allowed to do that!
Quit messing with me or
you're gonna regret it!
[JAVELIN chuckles nervously]
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
Zuikaku!
I've gotta hit her
at least once.
It's all over.
[grunts]
[ENTERPRISE gasps]
Why am I reaching my limit now?
[gasps]
[shouts]
You're going down!
[BELFAST]
Pardon the interruption.
[ZUIKAKU, ENTERPRISE gasp]
Are you kidding?
What the...? Who are you?
I'm no one, really.
Just a maid passing by.
[giggles]