[FURUTAKA pants]
Is it...?
[FURUTAKA]
Oh! It is! They made it back!
[FURUTAKA giggles]
[BOTH chuckle]
Welcome home, Akagi.
Good to see you. Kako. Furataka.
Did anything important
occur in our absence?
No, not really, although, Nagato
wishes to speak with you, Akagi.
I know, thank you.
I'll report to her now.
[FURUTAKA]
Welcome home, Ayanami!
It's good to be back.
[FURUTAKA]
Are you okay?
[SHIGURE]
Hey! Look who's home!
[YUUDACHI]
Yay, there you are!
[SHIGURE laughs]
I, the great Yukikaze, have
taken the time to welcome you!
Can you believe
how lucky you are?
Go on! Tell us! How many
of 'em did you sink?
[AYANAMI sighs]
Well, it's not like...
Wait! It's only right to listen
to her stories over some tea!
[YUUDACHI]
Yes!
[SHIGURE gasps]
[PRINZ EUGEN chuckles]
As always.
They're so childish.
I admit, I find them
rather charming.
[HIRYUU]
Uh?
We've returned to you safely.
Excellent work out there.
I'm glad you're in one piece.
Oh, you just wouldn't
believe it, Soryuu!
Our elders were such
harsh mistresses.
Why are our leaders
so demanding?
[HIRYUU] What's wrong, Zuikaku?
Why the long face?
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, everything is fine.
Don't worry about me, Hiryuu.
[inaudible]
The Grey Ghost.
[ZUIKAKU]
I'll have you next time!
[BELFAST grunts]
[footsteps]
[ENTERPRISE grunts, gasps]
A very good morning,
Miss Enterprise.
[ENTERPRISE]
What exactly are we doing here?
[BELFAST gasps]
I prefer to have coffee
in the morning.
A cup of coffee can
be lovely, yes.
But too much may
unsettle your stomach.
Especially if your
stomach is empty.
I've already had
enough to eat.
I think not.
Enterprise, we are going to
improve your way of life.
Maintaining a strict and regular
schedule is the key to leading
a proper and elegant existence.
Why are you so anxious to
interfere with my life?
What could you possibly
get out of it?
I'd like to witness
something special.
[ENTERPRISE]
What?
The human soul that I
know is inside of you.
[ENTERPRISE grunts]
Suit yourself, then.
[GIRLS chattering]
How are the Dragon
Empery girls doing?
It certainly seemed like the
elder sister was badly injured.
Oh look!
[GIRLS chattering]
Here's your order! Please enjoy!
[grunting]
Why do I have to be
the one to help,
I can't even make them right!
Jiayou, you're doing
a great job.
Ping Hai, stop eating all
of our merchandise!
They opened a business?
They've shown
incredible resilience
in the face of tragedy.
[ENTERPRISE gasps]
[BELFAST]
Huh?
[PING HAI]
Here you go!
I appreciate it,
but no, thank you.
My sister said you don't have to
worry about payment or anything.
[NING HAI]
Mm‐hm!
You saved our lives, so we
have to thank you somehow.
[BELFAST giggles]
[UNICORN whimpers]
[JAVELIN]
Uh?
[UNICORN gasps]
Delicious.
Ha! Yes, they're wonderful!
[UNICORN giggles]
I hope Ayanami can eat
with us next time.
Really?
Or not.
Oh, no! I hope so, too!
I would love it if one day,
she was able to join us.
[UNICORN gasps]
[NING HAI] The Dragon Empery
detected suspicious activity
by the Sirens. We thought
it might be a sign they were
preparing to launch
a massive attack,
and went out on a scouting
mission to find out more. But...
[NING HAI gasps]
[PING HAI grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
Sounds like some
high‐powered Sirens
are up to something freaky.
Hornet, please, let's not
forget our manners here.
The Dragon Empery is our
ally and risked great loss
to obtain this information.
We would do well not to take any
of their intelligence lightly.
Maybe the Sirens want to strike
while Red Axis and Azur Lane
are at war. When we're
all distracted.
Increased Siren activity and an
attack from Sakura Empire,
which utilized new technology
giving them control over
mass‐produced Sirens.
Those can't be coincidences.
Thankfully, the Royal Navy
has already launched
an investigation.
Really?
[BELFAST] We, the Maid Corps,
are on a mission
that will bring us the
answers we seek.
Alright. What mission?
[BELFAST]
Hm.
[BELFAST] "Cloak and Dagger."
Espionage, of course.
[YUUDACHI] You wanna go?
I'll race you!
[YAMASHIRO] Do you want to go
have some anmitsu with me?
[FUSOU giggles] As long as you
don't overeat again, okay?
[SHIGURE] Where do they
get all that energy?
[SHEFFIELD gasps]
[EDINBURGH]
Uh?
This is the Black Box that gives
us control over the Sirens?
[AKAGI]
Yes, but it is only a byproduct.
[NAGATO]
Hm.
You see, this Black Box
is a kind of Mental Cube.
The same Mental Cubes that
we warships are made out of.
[NAGATO]
Project Orochi.
Yes. Sakura Empire's hope
for a shining future.
Unfortunately, in order
for it to work,
we were forced to
make the first move.
That was inevitable.
Our clashes with the
Sirens were too frequent
and too destructive
for us not to act.
Humanity is barely
holding on as it is.
[AKAGI] Azur Lane's strategy
isn't feasible.
Sakura Empire's survival depends
on us completing this project
at all costs.
I understand.
You may be excused.
[NAGATO] I suppose no matter
the era, war never changes.
[KAGA] She is still hesitating.
Nagato lacks determination.
[AKAGI]
Oh, don't speak too ill of her.
She is driven by a deep,
overwhelming love.
Dear sister, she‐‐
But it's not enough, is it?
My love is strong.
Strong enough to incinerate
the world and burn on.
And that may happen very soon.
My dear Akagi.
[SHIGURE gasps]
Wait, you're telling me
this Enterprise woman
took out Kaga?
Wow, that's intense.
[YUKIKAZE] If I were in charge,
Eagle Union and Royal Navy
would never stand a
chance against us!
[SHIGURE] Calm down and
eat slower! Here, drink this.
Ah! I'm so jealous you got
to see battle, Ayanami.
I can't wait to be
strong enough to fight!
[AYANAMI gasps]
I don't actually like fighting.
I'm just doing what's
expected of me.
"What's expected,"
are you kidding?
I thought you were
"The Demon," Ayanami!
Admit it, you love it.
[YUUDACHI]
Ayanami the Demon!
You have the horns
and everything!
Those aren't horns,
those are just my ears,
so please let go now.
Battle takes way more
than strength.
You also have to be blessed
with fortune, like me,
the famous Shigure!
Oh! I won a freebie!
[ALL gasp]
[SHIGURE]
Enough, Yukikaze!
I'm the lucky one here, let's
settle this once and for all!
Quiet in the restaurant!
You're all insufferable!
[SHIGURE pants]
[TAKAO grunts]
[gasps]
Training hard, I see, Takao.
Zuikaku. It's good to
see you've returned.
Yeah, but, I can't exactly say
I did very well out there.
I see.
[ZUIKAKU] I didn't stand a
chance against the Grey Ghost.
[gasps]
[ZUIKAKU]
I can't stay like this.
I have to get stronger,
or else I won't be able
to protect Shokaku!
[ZUIKAKU grunts, gasps]
Oh, my apologies! I may have
hit a little too hard.
[whimpers]
You must not take on
every burden by yourself.
You must learn to
rely on us as well.
Takao.
We're friends, are we not?
[gasps]
[SHIRANUI]
Hm.
Where's Akashi?
That bumbling fool must be
slacking off somewhere again.
[EDINBURGH yelps]
What's that? Are you okay?
You kind of look
like you're lost.
[whimpers]
[SHIRANUI]
Uh... Oh wait. Excuse me.
[EDINBURGH gasps]
You dropped... your glasses?
[EDINBURGH giggles]
[SHIRANUI]
Mm. Huh.
Why did they have to assign
me to an undercover mission?
I'm terrified, I'm not cut
out for this in the least!
Stay quiet, please.
Our intelligence appears
to be accurate.
Their coordination
suggests they're
building something massive.
The question is... where?
Shiranui doesn't know
how to treat a cat.
She acts like I'm "infurior."
What is this place?
[gasps]
[AKASHI]
Uh?
Well I'm definitely lost meow.
[AKASHI] I have a feline that
this is the Project Orochi ship.
It looks just like a Siren ship.
Is it really okay to build
something like this?
[gasps]
Akagi? What are mew doing here?
[yells]
[gasps]
[OBSERVER]
With so much energy gathered,
we are nearly ready to
launch Project Orochi.
Is that fur real?
At this rate, I'd say
one more, perhaps,
and then we can
really have some fun.
[OBSERVER] The goal of Project
Orochi is not to create
any ordinary ship.
It is, shall we say,
an Ark, meant to carry every
wish across the ocean.
[OBSERVER]
You'll be reunited soon.
Leave this place. Someone could
easily find you here.
I should be going meow.
I saw something clawful,
something apawling.
[KAGA]
You there. What are you doing?
You saw.
Uh... what do you mean?
I just got a little lost, uh,
it's purty dark in here.
[yelps]
Oh dear, she did see me.
Unfortunate.
Well, as they say
curiosity killed the cat.
No, please, don't!
Somebody help me!
[AKAGI]
Halt at once.
I won't allow you to harm a
member of the Sakura Empire.
I understand why you say that,
but you must see that
we can't let her go.
[AKASHI yelps, groans]
Who the hell are you?
That ludicrous outfit
must be Royal Navy.
[AKAGI giggles]
[gasps]
[KAGA]
Sister!
[growls]
Edinburgh, now!
[EDINBURGH gasps]
I caught it, Sheffield.
I did it, I have it!
[OBSERVER gasps]
[SHEFFIELD]
Time to retreat!
You fools!
Oh goodness, what a mess.
This is on you, Akagi.
[gasps]
[sirens blaring]
[ZUIKAKU]
What's going on?
[TAKAO gasps]
[YUKIKAZE] What is this about?
Is everything okay?
[gasps]
[NAGATO gasps]
What's happening here,
who set that thing off?
Furutaka, we have
to stay vigilant!
Hey! Wait, what?
Uh. What was that?
Who were they?
[EDINBURGH] I would prefer
to carry gold ingots.
You can complain later.
Why are you bothering with
the extra load, Edinburgh?
Don't you dare leave me behind!
Won't you quit following us?
What can we do?
They would have put me out of
my mewsery! I'd be hisstory!
Dead cats tell no tales, y'know!
I s'pose we've no choice.
Let's see this through, then.
We're clear if we make
it to that island!
On your right!
[EDINBURGH gasps]
[gasps]
Not so fast!
I can handle this, Edinburgh.
Go on ahead without me.
Save her.
Sheffy, are you sure?
[gasps]
This is ridiculous.
Slow and steady wins the race.
Dripping water wears down stone.
I've spent a long time
training my sword.
There is nothing it can't sever!
[gasps]
[TAKAO gasps]
My enemy. Your skills
have earned my respect.
[grunts]
[AYANAMI shouts]
[SHEFFIELD gasps]
Reinforcements, eh?
[EDINBURGH] What should
we do? What should we do?
[AKASHI] Um, maybe we should
hightail it outta here.
I can't just leave her.
Meow what are you looking at?
[EDINBURGH giggles]
[engines roaring]
[TAKAO]
What?
Edinburgh!
Sheffy! Grab my hand!
[AKASHI yells] It's on fire,
you gotta be kitten me!
Not what I expected.
This could be bad.
No, wait! Don't come this way!
[AKASHI yells]
Someone help me!
I must apologize, dear sister,
it seems the enemy has escaped.
I see. That's disappointing.
Azur Lane operatives now have
control of the Black Box.
Organize a recovery team,
dear Kaga.
But in truth, this could turn
out to be beneficial for us.
How is that?
If Azur Lane is so willing
to nurture the Black Box
on our behalf, perhaps we
should accept their help.
I greatly appreciate your help,
Ayanami, you saved my life.
Don't mention it,
I'm just glad you're okay.
[GIRLS]
Ayanami!
Whoa, Ayanami, we were
so worried that
something happened to you!
Of course nothing happened
to her, she has me,
Yukikaze, the goddess of
good fortune by her side!
I can't believe I'm
late to the party again,
I want to fight next time, too!
It's not a big deal.
[TAKAO gasps]
Wow, they really must love you.
[gasps]
Uh‐huh. These girls are
my precious friends.
So I have to be strong,
for all of them.
[AYANAMI gasps]