[gasps]
[AYANAMI whimpers]
[chuckles]
[AYANAMI grunts]
[LAFFEY gasps]
[JAVELIN gasps]
[JAVELIN]
Ayanami, wait!
[sighs]
[JAVELIN gasps]
[footsteps]
A very good morning,
Miss Enterprise, dear.
[BELFAST]
Breakfast is ready and waiting.
[gasps]
Fine. I'm coming.
[GIRLS chattering]
Did you wind up buying that cute
outfit you saw the other day?
Isn't that too much?
Don't be modest... I owe you
one for helping Oklahoma.
Thank you for that.
[ENTERPRISE]
Uh...
Ah. Good morning, Enterprise.
It's good to see you here.
Oh. Hello.
Morning, ladies! What'll it be?
I heard there's a sale
at the bazaar today,
so I'll go get them later.
[NORTHAMPTON gasps] Hey there,
Enterprise, how are you?
Wow, you must be pretty
hungry this morning.
Oh, no.
That's just, uh, nothing.
[ENTERPRISE sighs] Belfast,
why don't you take a seat, too.
Apologies, but I must attend
to my duties as a maid.
I don't think I can
finish this alone.
[gasps]
Well if you need assistance,
I would be more than
delighted to join you.
[VESTAL gasps]
[gasps]
[HORNET yawns]
Hey. So, what's up?
Nothing.
[VESTAL]
It seems to me...
...Enterprise is starting
to open up a little bit.
[GIRLS chattering]
There's a great shop at
the bazaar. I got 'em there.
Now pay close attention!
I won't repeat this!
[REPULSE pants]
[REPULSE] Hello, Enterprise!
How are ya today?
[ENTERPRISE] Hello Repulse,
I'm doing well, thank you.
[RENOWN] Hey, Repulse! I told
you not to run in the hallway!
[CLEVELAND]
Enterprise! Hello!
[COLUMBIA, DENVER]
Hm?
[ENTERPRISE]
Uh?
[CLEVELAND] I've never
introduced you to my sisters,
have I? Come on, girls, say hi!
I'm Columbia the second sister
ship in the Cleveland class.
It's nice to meet you!
I am Montpelier, the third ship.
Thanks for helping my sister.
And I'm Denver,
sister number four!
It's a real honor to
meet a legend like you!
Thanks. Nice to meet you, too.
See why I'm so proud
of these ladies?
Still, we can't compare
to you. Not yet.
You're number one, Cleveland,
we just try to keep up!
[CLEVELAND gasps]
Come on!
I told you to stop saying stuff
like that! It's embarrassing.
It sounds like you
really love each other.
‐‐[CLEVELAND] Mm?
‐‐[DENVER giggles]
[CLEVELAND laughs]
Oh, hey.
What happened to that thing we
recovered from Sakura Empire?
Right. We've much to discuss.
[BOTH gasp]
[ENTERPRISE]
A black... Mental Cube.
The Sakura Empire's
secret weapon,
based on Siren technology.
[CLEVELAND]
Couldn't we use this?
It might neutralize
those mass‐produced
Siren ships they're controlling.
[AKASHI] The Orochi itself
controls the Siren ships.
The Cube is just extra support.
[HORNET] Our intel said they
were building something.
I guess this massive
warship, Orochi, was it.
What's the relationship between
the Orochi and this Cube?
What we do know, is that a
Siren gave them this Cube.
And that Akagi has worked
closely with that Siren.
[AKASHI whines]
Well, if that's the case,
Sakura Empire is engaged
in a vast deception.
Akagi. This will
be a cat‐tastrophe.
[ENTERPRISE, HORNET exhale]
[ENTERPRISE gasps]
[ENTERPRISE]
Uh...
[gasps]
[BELFAST]
Enterprise?
[ENTERPRISE gasps]
Are you feeling alright?
You seem distracted,
like we lost you for a moment.
Yes... I'm fine... It's nothing.
[SAKURA SHIP GIRL A]
This one's so cute!
[KAGA gasps]
It looks good, doesn't it?
I think it would suit you...
...much better than it
does me, dear sister.
Don't be so modest.
Why don't you take another look?
Now do you see it? This color
is beautiful on you, Kaga.
[KAGA exhales]
[AKAGI]
I'll take it.
[gasps]
Taiyaki. Here I come!
I'm gonna get one of the good
ones made with extra bean paste.
Let's go! They'll sell
out if we don't hurry!
[UZUKI]
Slow down!
[FUMIZUKI] Watch your
step so you don't trip!
Wait for me!
[UZUKI]
Don't leave me behind!
[gasps]
[UZUKI whimpers]
[yelps, gasps]
Careful. Running can
be dangerous.
[UZUKI yelps]
Oh no...
[MIKAZUKI]
Uh. 'Scuse us. We're very sorry.
We didn't do it on purpose!
Are you okay, Uzuki?
We're sorry,
please don't eat us!
No, wait. I'm really not
angry with any of you.
[NAGATSUKI]
Don't make me use P‐kun!
[AKAGI] Oh my, what have
you done, Kaga?
Don't make these
sweet little girls cry.
Sister, I'd never!
[MUTSUKI] Um! I'm, uh...
I'm really sorry!
You can have all of my candy.
Please don't be angry!
But I said... I'm not.
[AKAGI giggles] I see,
we'll take you up on that.
[AKAGI giggles]
Kaga, you can forgive
them now, right?
Uh. Yes.
[AKAGI] And here's a reward
for good little girls
who know how to apologize.
Don't forget to share.
[MUTSUKI gasps]
Bye, ma'am! Thank you so much!
[GIRLS chattering, giggling]
[KAGA] I just said they
should be careful running.
[AKAGI]
Hey. Kaga.
Don't you wish that they could
stay together like that forever?
Sister?
[GIRLS chattering, giggling]
[AKASHI] We've got an
ameowzing sale today!
Don't cat nap through it!
Stop by now!
[AMAZON]
Fledglings!
Pick up one of these and do
some studying for a change!
You're going to need it!
Look around as
long as you want!
I want to bring back some
of these for my room.
There are more shops now.
This place has quickly
grown lively.
You're gonna eat all that?
Not all of it!
I'll share with my sister.
[LONDON gasps] The selection
here is incredible!
[AMAZON giggles]
These could be pretty
useful in our classes.
[BAILEY laughs]
It's like a human city.
Well, we are human.
Don't start this
conversation again.
It just doesn't...
Make sense to me.
Please enjoy our fresh flowers!
[BELFAST] Hm. Enterprise,
I believe the best way to learn
is for you to find
elegance in your heart.
Find elegance? I don't
understand that, either.
Are you saying you want me
to become a maid, like you?
Well, now! Are you interested?
I could certainly discipline
you to become a fine maid
suited for any household.
[ENTERPRISE gasps]
No, I... That was a...
[giggles]
Maid or otherwise, dear.
You might find
your understanding
in exploring something new.
A hobby, some kind of job,
anything other than fighting.
That's not going to
be easy for me.
Then it's a challenge
worthy of you.
Life is about adventure.
Seek and you shall find.
[ENTERPRISE]
I suppose that might be true.
[BELFAST sighs]
Ponder it as long as you need.
Because that's how we got here.
It's what makes us truly human.
[sighs]
[groans]
[LAFFEY]
Ah. Shiny and clean.
We're supposed to be enemies.
[inaudible]
[JAVELIN]
But...
[JAVELIN] But... I still believe
we don't have to fight!
[yelps]
[LAFFEY]
Javelin. Don't slack off.
Laffey!
I'll get you back!
Come at me, bro.
[JAVELIN, LAFFEY laugh]
[GIRLS chattering]
[SHIP GIRL I]
Wow, where did you get those?
[SHIP GIRL J] I want a cute
bra like that, too!
[UNICORN gasps]
[OKLAHOMA] So did you pick up
those skivvies I told you about?
[SAN DIEGO]
You'll have to show me later!
[NEVADA] I can always
count on your good taste.
[UNICORN sighs]
Hey! Hi there, Unicorn!
[UNICORN gasps]
[JAVELIN chuckles]
How did you get all wet?
Oh we were having
a small pre‐soak.
Are you taking a bath, too?
Let's go in together, okay?
I‐I don't know if I‐‐
[LAFFEY sneezes]
Excuse me.
We don't want anyone to catch
a cold. Let's go! I can't wait!
[UNICORN gasps]
Um...
What cute underwear!
I love the color!
Oh wow. Those are really nice.
Hey, sis. Do the Royal Navy
girls all wear such fancy,
grown‐up underwear like that?
[CLEVELAND grunts]
[CLEVELAND]
Sheffield, quick question.
So uh. Is the fancy
underwear like a cultural thing?
It's not. I usually
tend to do without.
I'm sorry, I think
I misunderstood you.
I don't wear knickers.
[ALL gasp]
Oh dear.
[LAFFEY]
Bath, quickly.
[JAVELIN gasps]
There's no need to pull me!
[UNICORN]
Uh.
[LAFFEY]
The water is getting cold.
[JAVELIN] No it's not!
We'll see you inside, Unicorn!
[UNICORN gasps]
[HAMMANN sighs]
[SHIP GIRL K]
Oh, that feels nice.
Yahoo! Bath time!
Hey, don't run, you're going
to hurt yourself!
[SAN DIEGO]
Here we go!
[NORFOLK]
Oh! No, that's‐‐!
[SAN DIEGO yelps]
Wh‐Why? How can a
bath be electric?
Sometimes Eldridge leaks
electricity into the water.
Hey, sis! Aren't the
Royal Navy girls awesome?
[CLEVELAND gasps, yelps]
[ALL]
Hm?
[CLEVELAND] She really
wasn't wearing any...
[EDINBURGH chuckles]
[AKASHI sighs]
A hot spring soak
after work makes me feel
like one divine feline!
[QUEEN ELIZABETH giggles]
A thermae bath
hand‐built by us,
the Royal Navy!
Hot springs aren't exclusive to
Sakura Empire, my dear!
It's quite impressive,
Your Majesty.
[JAVELIN]
Huh?
[JAVELIN gasps] Unicorn,
you're very well‐endowed!
[UNICORN gasps]
[JAVELIN, LAFFEY]
Hm?
[JAVELIN gasps] Oh no!
What's wrong, darling?
Please don't cry!
[UNICORN sobs]
[UNICORN] I'm so small,
but my body looks like this.
I'm afraid there's something
wrong with me.
Oh my, I promise that's
not true at all.
[UNICORN sobs]
[JAVELIN exhales]
Unicorn. Your body is great
and you're awesome.
[UNICORN]
You don't mean that.
Of course I do.
[UNICORN gasps]
But I...
I don't look the same
as everybody else.
Everyone is different.
That's normal.
[JAVELIN]
Mm‐hm.
There's nothing wrong
with any body.
[gasps]
So it's okay?
[JAVELIN gasps]
[UNICORN]
Hm?
[gasps]
Maybe... yeah.
[ILLUSTRIOUS gasps]
[ILLUSTRIOUS giggles]
[PRINCE OF WALES] Mm? You look
rather pleased about something.
Yes, very much.
[UNICORN, JAVELIN giggle]
[UNICORN] Ayanami?
That girl we met before?
[JAVELIN] Mm. We're supposed
to be her enemies.
So this could be
very wrong, but...
[JAVELIN]
I don't want to give up on her.
Truth is... I still want to
be friends with Ayanami!
[UNICORN]
Mm! I do, too.
I want to see her again
and get to know her.
I don't think it's fair that we
have to fight her like this.
Same here. And we haven't
started any fights yet.
[gasps]
[LAFFEY exhales]
[UNICORN]
Hm!
[YORKTOWN] I have faith that
one day you'll remember.
So many people have placed
their trust in your name.
Good evening, Enterprise.
Having trouble sleeping?
I felt the ocean
calling out to me.
[BELFAST]
Huh?
I'm joking.
That seems quite
unlike you, doesn't it?
It is. Maybe I'm just feeling
a little emotional right now.
[BELFAST] Try and keep
yourself warm out here.
You brought coffee?
At this hour of the night?
[giggles]
[gasps]
Thought you taught elegance.
It's very quiet.
Yes.
[ENTERPRISE]
I never mind a quiet ocean.
[PRINZ EUGEN] How pretty.
Must be Akagi's taste.
[KAGA]
You're not welcome here.
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Oh, come now.
Let me join you
for just one drink.
[KAGA] I decline.
You'll ruin the taste.
[PRINZ EUGEN chuckles]
Always playing hard
to get, aren't you?
They took the black Mental Cube.
Are you not at all worried?
What are you and
your sister scheming?
I'm sorry, but that's
none of your concern.
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Are you sure you and Akagi...
...are, in fact,
after the same thing?
[KAGA growls]
That's enough from you!
[PRINZ EUGEN] One‐sided love can
be so painful, don't you think?
[PRINZ EUGEN] Guten nacht.
Have a pleasant night.
[grunts]
[AKAGI] Soon, we'll meet
again very soon.
[AKAGI]
My dear sister Amagi.