[ENTERPRISE]
The truth is...
[AYANAMI pants]
[ENTERPRISE]
...war never changes.
It's exactly the same, no matter
which era it happens upon.
One battle ends and
another begins.
[QUEEN ELIZABETH]
It's about time they showed up!
This is the fleet
I've been expecting!
[PRINCE OF WALES chuckles] It's
not just our own, Your Majesty.
It appears that the
fleet has combined with
Eagle Union's. Fantastic.
This is indeed an
astounding view.
And certainly quite promising.
This fight, I'm sure,
will be decisive.
As the knights of the sea,
you can count on us.
We are second to none.
And there's no way we're gonna
let our big sister down.
Think maybe we could
relax a little bit?
Everyone's so tense, I swear
we're all about to snap in two.
Yeah, she's right.
So, let's try to release
some steam today.
No one wants a break‐down.
‐‐[MONTPELIER, DENVER] Okay.
‐‐[COLUMBIA] Got it!
[grunts]
[HORNET]
No gettin' 'round it now.
Time for a showdown!
What's the matter?
You seem upset.
Do you honestly feel
prepared for this?
We haven't even
completed Orochi yet.
And now we're heading
into a major battle?
What could Akagi
possibly be thinking?
Maybe the fact that we couldn't
get the black Mental Cube back
is getting to her. That seems
understandable to me.
I have no idea what
sort of schemes
Akagi's cooking up out there.
But don't you worry, Zuikaku.
I'm right here. Your big
sister will protect you!
[gasps]
[YUUDACHI]
Oh, boy, I can't wait!
Finally, a real battle!
[YUKIKAZE] And they'll all
bear witness to my great
and awesome power!
What's the matter?
You've seemed gloomy
for quite a while now.
Really? I hadn't noticed.
I feel just fine.
Well, if you weren't fine,
I know I could help
you feel better.
I'm blessed with good fortune.
[YUKIKAZE] Hey, you're not
the only one, you know!
[SHIGURE] Yeah, yeah.
I haven't forgotten.
It's too bad Ayanami's
on their side.
[gasps]
[JAVELIN chuckles]
Thank you, friend. I'll be okay.
I'm just not quite sure
what to do about it yet.
But, at least now
I know what I want.
Good day, Miss Enterprise.
You seem like you're
feeling a bit down.
I'm not. I was actually
enjoying the feel of the wind.
An important battle lies ahead.
I must remain sharp.
Please refrain from
allowing your temper
to take charge of your actions.
I will do my best.
I'm not sure I trust your tone.
[ENTERPRISE chuckles]
Belfast. Stop worrying.
I feel good about this.
Trust me.
[PORTLAND gasps]
Well, isn't that something?
Such fierce determination.
She really is
Yorktown's little sister.
Yorktown's not the only one
with an awesome little sister!
Um. Mine's cuter than
everyone else here!
Did you just create a
rivalry from, like, nothing?
I still can't hear.
My radar's all messed up.
It's been a while now.
I hope it's not a bad omen.
Not good. I have a really
bad feeling about this one.
It's finally ready
for you, Akagi.
I've set it up perfectly.
It's in your hands now.
[AKAGI]
Oh, heavenly wind,
Close off the passage way
that winds within the clouds.
Keep those heavenly
maidens still,
for they must remain on Earth.
[yelps]
[gasps]
Are you okay?
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[ALL grunting]
[gasps]
[BELFAST gasps]
[grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[CLEVELAND] Whoa.
I don't know where we are.
Over there, Big Sis!
Sirens!
[gasps]
Akagi!
If it isn't the
legendary Azur Lane.
Welcome to my ocean.
I've been expecting you.
Time to charge!
Tally ho, soldiers.
Elegance isn't just for show!
It's who we are!
Hope they're ready
for a big surprise!
[NORFOLK whimpers]
I've got this.
[NORFOLK gasps] Wow, Eldridge!
That was so cool!
Yes! Only one left, girls.
‐‐[humming]
‐‐[COLUMBIA gasps]
[grunts]
You've got some great moves.
At least this'll
be entertaining.
What do you say we wrap this
up and go get a drink, Ise?
Sakura Empire battleships.
[BOTH grunt]
[ALL gasp]
Don't move. Allow me
to savor this moment.
[grunts]
[giggles]
Fire!
Let's go! Sakura Empire
must advance!
Heaven's will is on our side!
And so it begins.
Dear big sister, Souryuu.
Where are we? I don't
recognize this place.
Did Akagi do this?
If so, what's the plan?
To be quite honest,
I have no idea.
[gasps] It seems the guest
of honor has arrived.
[ZUIKAKU]
Grey Ghost!
[ENTERPRISE]
Huh?
[ZUIKAKU]
No, wait!
Stand back if you
want to survive.
But why? I want to fight
the Grey Ghost, Kaga!
This fight is meant
to vindicate my honor!
There isn't any role in it
for a novice like you!
Can carriers really do that?
Tell me the truth!
Are you really in an
alliance with the Sirens?
Did Akashi tell you? She needs
to be severely disciplined.
Both you and Akagi are traitors!
To your comrades and
to all humankind!
You don't know my sister,
so don't you dare say
another word about her!
It would be rude of me
to expect Kaga to do
all the work here by herself.
And I thought we were done
with these annoyances.
[BELFAST] Don't mind me, just
thought I might clean house.
[gasps]
Housework? No thanks.
[ENTERPRISE]
Huh?
[gasps]
[KAGA]
You're mine.
[ENTERPRISE gasps]
Enterprise, no!
[grunts]
[YORKTOWN] Look at that.
The ocean is so lovely today.
[ENTERPRISE]
From the moment we were born,
the ocean was a place for war.
I look at it, and the roar
of artillery fills my ears.
I can smell gunpowder as
I feel the flame's heat
and the ice‐cold sting of water.
For me, it's different.
The ocean is...
[gasps]
Now you can finally rest
in peace, gray phantom.
Your tireless will shall
live on inside the Black Box
and become part of a
much greater force.
[gasps]
What the hell's going on?
[JAVELIN, LAFFEY gasp]
[ALL gasp]
Enterprise, what's happening?
[OBSERVER]
So you've awakened?
It seems some things
never change.
You're now the key in this
world as you were in the last.
[OBSERVER]
Welcome, Enterprise.
[gasps]
But why? What did you do?
Kaga!
[shouts]
[ZUIKAKU]
Akagi! Kaga!
[SHOUKAKU]
Zuikaku!
[QUEEN ELIZABETH]
My goodness! What is that?
Damn it, Big sister.
What did you do now?
Move out of the way, Laffy!
Everyone!
Who are you?
And what do you want?
I won't allow you
to stand in my way!
[AKAGI] This is a
manifestation of my love!
A feeling so strong
it surpasses time!
It even overwhelms the gods!
For Sakura Empire,
and for my dear sister!
[AKAGI gasps]
[gasps]
So you... you're afraid?
[ENTERPRISE] Ah.
I understand it now, finally.
It's true. I'm afraid...
of the ocean.
I've finally found you.
My sister, Amagi.
[gasps]
[OBSERVER]
This isn't over, Akagi. Not yet.