[NAKA, HATAKAZE pant]
[AMAGI]
Huh? What's all this fuss?
[HATAKAZE] Oh, Amagi!
I'm so glad we found you.
[NAKA] Akagi and Kaga
started fighting again
and we need your help!
[AMAGI sighs]
Oh, dear.
When are those two
going to grow up?
[EDINBURGH]
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
[laughs]
Seriously?
You're not even gonna try
to make this fun for me?
[grunts]
What?
[gasps]
Siren!
Oh, yay! It's Enterprise!
[gasps]
She did it!
[PURIFIER laughs]
[PURIFIER chuckles]
Alright, that was fun!
Too bad, that's my cue to leave,
but I'll catch you later!
See you ladies at
the final stage!
[SHEFFIELD gasps]
She hit her own ships?
The "final stage".
[ALL sigh]
[BELFAST]
You always do tend to show up
right in the nick of time.
[chuckles]
I've no choice.
I can't just sit by when you're
out here being reckless.
Always the knight
in shining armor.
Thanks for your protection.
Spare me. That's not it.
[SHEFFIELD grunts]
[EDINBURGH, NORFOLK giggle]
[BELFAST chuckles]
[TESTER A] We've outrun
the Sakura Empire fleet.
Of course they were
a little too confused
to put up very much of a fight.
We're close now.
[TESTER A] I have to say, this
is quite a magnificent scheme.
Well of course, a battle like
this one needs to be dramatic.
It's only fair. Battles are
manifestations of will.
It is not just power that drives
them and gives them strength.
[TESTER] You know, it's
difficult to understand you
when you start to
wax poetic like that.
Oh, she knows.
She just loves to be
pretentious, that's all.
[TESTER B] My... Looks like
someone took a beating.
You know I always enjoy a
little bit of roughhousing.
[OBSERVER] Now we begin. Time
to stage an encore of the past.
Or perhaps release our
calculation for perfect future.
Tick, tock, tick, tock.
It's playtime.
Rise and shine, beautiful!
[grunts]
[gasps]
My sister?
[chuckles]
Akagi. My dear sister!
[KAGA gasps]
I'm so glad you're alive!
[AKAGI]
Yes. All as the gods intended.
Look, Kaga.
This is it. The power of Orochi
that we desired for so long.
[DACE gasp]
Huh?
[gasps]
[CLEVELAND]
Wh-what is this?
[HORNET] It's obviously
gotta be a Siren attack.
But, why target a
deserted island?
Perhaps they merely
mean to taunt us.
But they underestimate
our power.
[HOOD] Indeed, Majesty.
But this could be a test.
And if they use whatever did
that to strike this base...
Kaboom! We'll be toast for sure.
[HELENA] I think this
might be what did it.
A few hours before the island
was vaporized, a huge unknown
vessel took off from the
coast of the Sakura Empire.
Its destination unknown.
Sheffy. That ship.
Indeed. It has to be the one.
It has the characteristics
of the ship hidden beneath
Sakura Empire.
[HOOD] So this is Orochi .
What an enormous beast.
[PRINCE OF WALES] The Sakura
Empire port sustained
heavy damage from the
ship as it departed.
I expect that must
have come as a shock.
To them, and to the
Iron Blood as well.
[ILLUSTRIOUS]
If that's true,
then the Sirens were
always the sole threat.
I suppose that will
end our dealings
with the Red Axis for now.
[ENTERPRISE]
Not quite.
[ALL gasp]
[ENTERPRISE] Think for a second.
This is just the beginning.
We aren't done with
any of them yet.
What next, Miss Enterprise?
[ENTERPRISE]
We go after the Sirens directly.
We're going to put a stop to
whatever it is they're plotting.
[BELFAST]
Hm.
Their impact reaches
far beyond just Azur Lane.
The Orochi is a threat
to all of humanity.
Well then, let's not lay
about and get a move on!
We must brush off the
humiliation of our failures.
A stiff upper lip is
the Royal Navy way!
And the Eagle Union way is pure,
cold payback, so let's do this!
[ALL]
Mm-hm!
One last fight. Here we go.
[grunts]
[Z1 laughs] Guess you
didn't see that coming.
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Indeed I did not.
Who would have expected such
rash behavior from Kaga?
She's not acting alone, it's
clear the Sirens are involved.
So Akagi and Kaga were working
with Sirens this whole time?
It's foolish that the
entire Sakura Empire
somehow missed
there was a mole.
[PRINZ EUGEN] How do you know
it was only the Sakura Empire?
We may have spies
in Iron Blood as well.
And, we should consider there
could be Siren influence
in the higher echelons
of all camps.
[Z1]
Is there someone you suspect?
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Nein, never mind.
There's no value in
dwelling on that.
At least for the time being.
[TAKAO] What in the gods'
names have you done, Kaga.
There is no
explanation for this.
[sighs]
I underestimated her.
I never thought she
would go this far.
So, uh. What happens
when we find her?
[FUSOU] If she truly is in
league with the Sirens,
that is a grave betrayal
of the Sakura Empire.
And if worse comes to worst,
we may need to strike her
down along with the Orochi .
No. Please no!
That can't happen,
it's not right.
It's gonna be okay.
[YUKIKAZE] Ayanami, captured.
Akagi missing.
Ever since the start of
this stupid battle.
only horrible things
have happened.
Jeez, pull yourself together!
We don't know for sure yet that
they actually betrayed us!
I know how you feel, but...
[ZUIKAKU] She's the only one
with sense. This is wrong.
We haven't been fighting all
this time to take down a friend.
I know, and yet...
We're bringing Kaga home,
no matter what.
If she won't listen to us,
we'll just have to slap
some sense into her.
You hear me?
She's our family and we're
not gonna play along
with these Sirens' schemes!
[YUKIKAZE]
Thanks, Zuikaku!
[BOTH gasp]
[TAKAO, ATAGO]
mm.
[YAMASHIRO chucles]
How wonderful it is
to see you all grown up.
It's bittersweet,
but I'm so proud.
Dear sister.
You look like you're--
[AKAGI]
Oh, darling...
You don't have to be afraid.
Everything's fine. I promise
I won't leave you again.
No, wait.
Kaga?
You're lying.
You're not my sister,
so who are you really?
[AKAGI grunts]
You know, you can
be so difficult.
[gasps]
Amagi.
[AMAGI]
Hm. It's been a while, Kaga.
No. That's wrong, too.
Explain yourself.
I became Amagi because
that is what Akagi desired.
[gasps]
So you're... Orochi.
[AMAGI chuckles]
[KAGA]
Let go of my sister!
Are you sure you want me to?
After all that Akagi went
through to see me,
you would disrespect
her wishes?
Enough treachery, impostor!
[AMAGI] I'm not the
only fruad here, am I?
[gasps]
Take care of Akagi. Won't you?
Amagi was destroyed,
leaving poor Akagi behind.
Then parts of Amagi were
passed down to another ship.
[KAGA]
Stop this.
[AMAGI chuckles] Surely you
already know this, darling.
[whimpers]
This isn't right.
Aircraft carrier Kaga.
You're a ship that was
retrofitted using
Amagi's secondhand machinery.
[gasps]
[AMAGI] Akagi only ever
loved you because she knew
there was a shadow of her dear
Amagi somewhere inside you.
Of course, that was
just an illusion.
[KAGA]
My sister. That can't be true.
[AMAGI] You were never going
to be her replacement.
You're simply a collection
of decaying parts.
A Ship of Theseus,
broken and unoriginal.
It's a shame you could
never measure up, Kaga.
Are you sure about
your plan, Miss?
Rushing in.
When it appears that you're
as important to the Sirens
as the Sakura Empire.
We may be waltzing
right into a trap.
We'll at least be
prepared this time.
There are no other options.
We can't turn away
from this battle
if we expect to
uncover the truth.
So once again, I will face
off against this ocean.
[BELFAST]
Hm.
As you wish, Miss Enterprise.
My duty, as always, is to see
your convictions through.
You have my support.
[gasps]
It's gonna be fine!
[LAFFEY] We got this.
It's all good.
[UNICORN] And U-chan
will protect us, too!
[AYANAMI]
Mm. Mh-hm.
[gasps]
Where'd that come from?
Who's shooting?
[CLEVELAND]
Hm. Red Axis, maybe?
[HORNET]
I suppose. Could be.
But I can't believe they
wouldn't wait for us
before pickin' a fight
with the Sirens.
No problem.
Guess we better get in there!
[YUKIKAZE gasps]
Alright!
Just leave everything to
the famous Yukikaze!
Rawr! I'm gonna bite 'em!
[SHIGURE]
Don't get too far ahead of me!
[shouts]
[YUKIKAZE] What happened?
Was that a cannon?
[YUUDACHI, SHIGURE gasp]
What cute little guests we have.
Let's see what kind of data
we can collect from them.
Battleship Sirens!
[ATAGO, TAKAO gasp]
[YAMASHIRO yells] I've never
seen this many powerful Sirens
at one time before!
That's a problem. We can't even
get close to the Orochi .
Never say never, Shoukaku.
If our path is blocked,
then we'll make our own way!
[ZUIKAKU gasps]
You're okay!
What is this? Where am I?
You have nothing to
fear now, Akagi.
Your wish has already come true.
Eternal love is
right here with you.
[AKAGI]
My wish. My eternal love.
Dear sister Amagi.
We... Sakura Empire...
You stubborn fool! How can you
show such blatant disrespect?
How dare you?
You're nothing but
Amagi's pathetic lackey!
I can settle all of this
right here and now,
if you think you're ready.
[AKAGI, KAGA growl]
[SAKURA SHIP GIRLS whisper]
[KAGA groans]
Sister Amagi, she--ow!
How many times have I
told you to play nice?
Fighting won't be tolerated.
Come on, give me your hands.
Now shake and be friends.
[KAGA, AKAGI]
Hmph!
[AMAGI gasps]
Girls. Don't make me ask again.
Be friends.
[KAGA, AKAGI gasp nervously]
I won't allow harm to Orochi.
Kaga!
[shouts]
Why are you working
with the Sirens?
You know this isn't right!
My only duty is to make sure
my dear sister Akagi is happy!
[SHOUKAKU]
Hey! Come on!
Where's your cool head,
this isn't like you!
[shouts]
[yells]
Yuudachi, no!
That looked painful, you ok?
[YUUDACHI] Oh yeah,
I'm totally fine, it's cool.
What do we do now? This is bad.
[gasps]
[PRINZ EUGEN] Okay.
Stay sharp, ladies.
Please pull yourself together.
If you don't concentrate,
you'll make an easy target.
I can handle it!
My, it looks like we have
a full house tonight.
[ADMIRAL HIPPER]
What is your plan now?
Even with our combined forces,
we're still vastly outnumbered.
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Oh, sister.
You must still be waiting for
your optimism to grow in
with your breasts.
[ADMIRAL HIPPER gasps]
I'll slap you!
[PRINZ EUGEN giggles] I joke,
of course. But you are correct.
Perhaps we must now stall
for divine intervention.
Here they come.
New reinforcements?
I would certainly hope so.
The enemy of my enemy
is my friend, after all.
Here at last, Azur Lane.
We've been waiting.
Deploy all units.
Glory to the Queen!
[shouts]
Miss Enterprise?
Eagle Union, charge at once!
We can't let those Royal Navy
girls have all the fun!
Am I right? Let's go!
Pull yourself together, Kaga!
Can't you see that the
Sirens are just using you?
It doesn't matter.
I won't allow you to
hurt my Zuikaku!
Brace yourself!
No... Nothing matters.
Not anymore.
[SHOUKAKU, ZUIKAKU gasp]
Aren't you from... Azur Lane?
[AYANAMI]
Of course things still matter.
[KAGA]
Well, well.
Are you here to come between
my dear sister and me?
That's not it. I'm came here
to help save everyone.
[BELFAST gasps]
Miss Enterprise, look. Up there.
[ENTERPRISE]
Mm?
Is that...?
It can't be.
Akagi?
[ENTERPRISE]
Who is that with her?
What did they just activate?
[AMAGI]
Everything's finally in place.
Ready, Akagi?
There. See, you're friends now!
Everything is going to be fine.
The future of Sakura Empire...
is held in these very hands.
Being friends with each other
is the only way to
defeat the Sirens.
Yes...
I think it's about time
we started a real war.