[AYANAMI]
I still don't understand,
or know the right answer.
But so what? I know this
is wrong, and I don't like it!
[BOTH gasp]
[AYANAMI grunts]
[ARK ROYAL] If you're
thinking of leaving, don't.
You're being watched.
Don't worry, we're not
going to bite.
Can you at least tell me
if this is Azur Lane?
You did your research.
Not that I'm surprised.
The battle's over now.
We found you unconscious,
so we brought you back here.
And that means you're
officially a prisoner of war.
[AYANAMI grunts]
What about the other two?
Are they okay?
Your two enemies?
Worried about them, are you?
[CLEVELAND] Talk about reckless.
What were you thinking?
So y'all made an
excessive effort
so you could save an enemy?
Shoot. Y'ain't tryin to earn
any medals, that's for sure.
I apologize.
No, please, wait. There's nobody
else to blame here but me.
I am the one responsible
for allowing it.
That's noble of you to say.
But we need to send the
right message to the others.
[HORNET]
Well, okay then.
Laffey, Javelin, as a
consequence of your actions,
you're on "prisoner
supervision duty."
[BOTH gasp]
We've got a strict rule
that Prisoners of War
need maximum care.
[JAVELIN]
So that means...?
[HORNET]
We're countin' on you.
Okay!
That was a light punishment.
[CLEVELAND] Well, there's no
need to be overly harsh.
[HORNET]
Yeah she's right.
Just like coffee, tea,
and life in general,
sweetness always helps.
I suppose. Anyway,
that's the real problem.
[CLEVELAND gasps]
What's with the Cube?
Ever since the battle ended,
the Cube has been
behaving quite abnormally.
Unfortunately, there's no way
to know exactly what it means.
The Black Mental Cube is
the key to Project Orochi.
I've no doubt that this is
all part of the Sirens' plan.
Well, shoot.
This definitely has something
to do with my sister, right?
What's the update on Enterprise?
We're performing diagnostics
on her body and her gear.
But so far, nothing out
of the ordinary.
I always knew her to be
an exceptional ship, but...
[CLEVELAND]
I was afraid of her back there.
She was terrifying.
[VESTAL] Oh my goodness,
there you are!
We still haven't finished
all of your checkups yet!
I really need you to stay put.
Right... Apologies.
Please be honest with me.
Are you okay?
I am, but we will have to fight.
For now, we have no choice.
Don't you agree?
Get well soon, Enterprise.
I don't understand this.
What does it mean, Yorktown?
The deceptive beauty
of the ocean.
The array of emotions
attached to my name.
Nothing makes sense.
[footsteps]
We've so many things to buy.
Let's do that first.
You're going to be living here
for quite a while, right?
That requires lots of "things!"
Shop has things.
So, we're going to the shop
first! I just love "things!"
[GIRLS chattering, laughing]
[AYANAMI]
Huh?
[BORG] Hey! Can you
throw me that ball?
[AYANAMI]
[GIRLS gasp]
Wow! Looks like we've
got a promising rookie!
[clapping]
[JAVELIN gasps]
[CHARLES AUSBURNE] Hey you!
Aren't you the ship, Ayanami?
How exciting!
There's a new girl here!
Yeah, that's her! She's the one
we were just talking about!
She's that girl from
Sakura Empire!
Hold on, that was her?
[AYANAMI gasps]
[CHARLES AUSBURNE]
I thought so!
Well, well! Everyone knows
how you saved your
Sakura Empire friends!
You put yourself at risk to
save others. That's so cool!
Huh?
And you two. Laffy and Javelin.
Good job as well!
You're great allies!
[JAVELIN chuckles]
[CHARLES AUSBURNE] Anyway,
if you ever need any help,
just let the
Little Beavers know!
That would be us.
And we'll be right there
for whatever you may need.
[AYANAMI]
Mm? Oh. Okay, thank you.
We'll see you soon, then.
Onward! Duty calls!
Um, I'll see you later. Bye!
I hope that we can all play
a game together sometime!
I know what you're thinking.
Nobody thinks badly of you.
You don't have to
worry about that.
Come on! Let's keep moving!
[AYANAMI] This feels weird,
but whatever.
[AKASHI]
Meow and welcome!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
What are you doing all
the way out here, Akashi?
Are you okay?
As long as I have customers,
I can do business from anywhere
in the world that I want.
Hey, is there any chance you
can give me a discount?
[AKASHI]
Not even the slightest!
Rude!
Ever since Akashi showed up,
selections here have
been a lot better!
I'm just glad we
don't have to worry.
Akagi's with the Sirens?
What gives?
She was always a little scary,
but Akagi would never go behind
her friends' back for anything.
Do you know what's going to
happen to Sakura Empire?
I have a bad feline.
[BOTH sigh]
[JAVELIN] Hey Ayanami! Which one
of these do you like best?
[AYANAMI]
Uh...
[JAVELIN]
Come on, pick one!
[LAFFEY]
This one is cutest.
[chuckles]
[YUKIKAZE]
Ayanami, no!
She never had a chance.
I can't believe she was
captured by the enemy.
[ZUIKAKU]
I'm so sorry.
There was nothing I could
do to bring her back.
I know. None of this is
your fault, Zuikaku!
[YUUDACHI] I'm so worried.
Is she going to be okay?
Are they going to
bully her over there?
She was never created to be
one of the lucky ships like me.
I'm so sad for her!
It's not right.
I was the rear guard.
But she's the one who saved me.
Quit being so negative!
What's wrong with you?
What if she goes hungry
because they forgot to feed her?
What if she's eating rice
while everyone else has meat?
If only I could've
been a little stronger!
Where is all this gloom
and doom coming from?
None of this is our fault!
[NAGATO] So Akagi has
still not returned to base.
Unfortunately, we did
lose the commander
of the entire operation.
And the Black Box, it still
remains with Azur Lane.
The situation is quite dire.
[NAGATO] Kaga is currently
making a strong case
for pushing forward
with Project Orochi?
Are you suspicious
of her? Be honest.
I believe it's too dangerous to
move forward with the project.
I never wanted to have
to doubt a friend.
[YUUGURE]
Thank you for being patient.
Things are getting really
serious out here, aren't they?
Sakura Empire's in
a perilous situation.
Maybe this is a good
opportunity for us as allies.
Should we, Iron Blood, take a
chance and help them?
Really? You want to utilize this
chaos und attack our allies?
How very sinister of you!
That sounds nothing like
what I said und you know it!
I'm kidding, calm down.
I know you're anxious
to rescue Ayanami.
Yeah, the two of you seemed
uncomfortably close at times.
What? I don't know what
you're suggesting,
but I know you're wrong.
There's nothing personal there.
I agree that if we're going to
make a move, now's the time.
What should we do?
Hi. I thought you might like
something sweet to eat.
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Aren't you a cutie?
I could just gobble you up.
[YUUGURE]
Miss, please, control yourself!
This is kind of important,
can you please stay on topic?
Of course. What moves
would you like to make?
What a lovely shot.
So impressive. Brilliant.
[EDINBURGH]
Nice shot!
I still don't understand
those Sirens.
I know they're our enemy
of course, but what else?
Where do they come from
and what do they want?
We've all asked the
question many times,
but no one seems to know
how to find the answer.
Why do the Sirens even bother
interacting with humanity?
It doesn't make sense if
their goal is to eradicate us.
They should just do it
instead of wasting time.
Project Orochi is the answer
to everything. And her.
Excellent par!
[HOOD] Pardon my assumption, but
are you referring to Enterprise?
[QUEEN ELIZABETH]
Mm‐hm.
If so, I was just thinking.
Illustrious always had her
eyes on Enterprise as well.
Of course she did,
I recall she's quite an
uncanny judge of character.
That's why I brilliantly
assigned Belfast to Enterprise.
Oh dear. I wonder if Belfast
sees something in her.
[ILLUSTRIOUS] What we had feared
most has become reality.
[BELFAST gasps]
You must've known the truth.
About Enterprise and
her state of mind?
[grunts]
No matter how much mighty
power fills her body,
her spirit is delicate and
she's always been vulnerable.
We all knew she was at risk.
There was nothing we could do.
But it comes with a consequence.
Enterprise has no choice
now but to face herself.
I see. Should we
expect her to recover?
[BELFAST]
I cannot say.
[UNICORN] I think Enterprise
is afraid of the sea,
but she doesn't like to
talk about it. Or show it.
But even though she
was really scared,
it didn't stop her
from saving me.
[chuckles]
Yes, you are quite correct.
[JAVELIN hums]
We're far from the base.
Where are you taking me?
Turns out Akashi already took
care of the necessities,
so we've got some
time to ourselves.
I thought perhaps we
might go to town.
[AYANAMI]
Hm?
Hello! And good day.
Good day, Illustrious!
Oh, and good day, Unicorn!
[UNICORN giggles]
[gasps]
[ILLUSTRIOUS]
This is a surprise.
What brings you out this way?
Right! We were just
on our way to‐‐
A date.
[AYANAMI]
Hm?
Huh?
[SHIP GIRLS chattering]
[JAVELIN gasps, giggles]
There's always something
going on out here!
Um, what did you mean
when you said "date?"
We play together.
[AYANAMI gasps]
[JAVELIN] Hey, Unicorn! Do you
want to come play with us?
[giggles]
[ALL gasp]
[JAVELIN]
Wow! This looks delicious!
Thank you for the food. Yay!
[UNICORN, LAFFEY]
Thank you for the food.
Oopsy.
The demon's awake.
You brought this on yourself!
Bring it. I ain't scared.
[JAVELIN] Hey! Stop fighting!
Don't you have manners?
This is not the time or place!
I mean, honestly.
You would think by now they'd
have learned to have some class.
How priceless.
Your nose, Ark Royal.
It's bleeding.
[SHIP GIRLS chatter]
[JAVELIN] What's the cafeteria
like in Sakura Empire?
[AYANAMI]
Uh... It's the same.
How so?
Everyone sits together,
no matter their age.
They're all nice to each other.
And share delicious meals.
[AYANAMI] Like that.
Everyone's treated the same.
[GLOWWORM yelps]
Are you okay?
It's just a shallow cut!
But don't worry, I'm happy
to disinfect it for you!
Meteor head slam!
[AYANAMI]
Uh...
The Orochi awakens, with the
wills of countless souls
embedded in its body.
The Orochi contains
everything we need.
It has traveled every ocean.
Collecting wills as it passes.
I see.
That's right. Akagi's will
is here as well.
Do you feel it? You can't
let it die, no matter what.
[KAGA] Yes, that's right.
That's why I'm here.
[AYANAMI grunts]
[AYANAMI]
Huh?
[ENTERPRISE]
Mm?
Well, well. Escaping?
[AYANAMI]
Mm‐mm.
[chuckles]
Just a joke.
Having trouble sleeping?
I can't stop thinking
about things.
If Azur Lane is supposed
to be my enemy,
then why are you
all so nice to me?
What is the fighting for?
Is there even a reason?
The more I try to
understand it,
the more confused I make myself.
I'm so torn,
this has been eating away
at my mind for a while now.
[ENTERPRISE] So then,
do you still want to fight?
[AYANAMI]
I don't know that answer.
I'm working it out. All I know
is that I don't like fighting.
I get it. I feel the same.
[BELFAST]
hm.
[AYANAMI gasps]
You found her!
Thank you so much for bringing
U‐chan back that day.
I really didn't do anything
deserving of your gratitude.
I was just an enemy spy, and I
was infiltrating your base.
[LAFFEY]
Yeah but, we got to meet you.
Wow! How did you find
such an amazing spot?
You've got some great
location scout skills!
By the way, I'm Javelin.
And that's...
Laffey.
Unicorn.
What about you?
What is your name?
Huh?
I'm Ayanami. Hi.
Nice to meet you.