[SHEFFIELD gasps]
[sighs]
[YAMASHIRO]
Hm...
Gotcha now.
[YAMASHIRO yelps]
Ouchie.
[AKASHI]
Hm... What a mystery.
You mean to tell me that
you've never seen this before?
Isn't this a Sakura Empire
secret weapon?
How am I supposed to know
about stuff like this?
All I am is just a lowly
repair ship, remember?
[AKASHI grunts]
[AKASHI] Maybe they got it
secretly from the Sirens?
And if they did, it must be
some seriously bad news!
I'm so afraid!
[EDINBURGH gasps]
Hello, I've returned.
[EDINBURGH]
Welcome back, Sheffield.
How did it go?
Scout planes are
still patrolling.
It's safe to assume
they have identified us.
They know that
we're hiding here.
[EDINBURGH, AKASHI shout]
How dreadful! What do we do?
[SHEFFIELD] Not much. The base
already knows our situation.
We should be patient
and wait to be rescued.
Then again, I highly
doubt the Sakura Empire
would sit idly by
if they were us.
[gasps]
Ouch! Hot!
Do you think if we found
a way to give this back,
they would let us go?
What a terribly
ignorant question.
Please don't let them catch me!
I bet they're gonna
turn me into a shamisen!
[SHOUKAKU] Hm. How can we
tell if these ships are safe?
What if the enemy takes control?
[ZUIKAKU] According to Akagi,
that's not possible.
She said as long as the Orochi
is the host, we'll be okay.
[SHOUKAKU grunts]
That's a lot to promise, huh?
What sort of scheme could
Akagi be plotting, I wonder?
You're suspicious?
It makes me uncomfortable.
They're all so sinister.
[gasps]
[giggles]
[TAKAO sighs]
I have failed my mission
and let the enemy escape.
I have to find a way
to restore my honor.
[ATAGO]
What's the matter, Takao?
You've got that
frownie face again.
Atago?
Oh goodness, your shoulders are
so tense. Do you feel that?
[TAKAO gasps]
[TAKAO]
Cut it out!
[ATAGO giggles]
[ATAGO]
Huh?
[ATAGO] Would you
like some, too, Ayanami?
No thanks. I must respectfully
decline your offer.
Stop that! We're on a mission!
What's wrong with you?
Is it that hard to
take this seriously?
[ATAGO] Yes ma'am. How is the
island looking over there?
[ZUIKAKU grunts]
[ZUIKAKU] It's in shambles
with many hiding places.
It won't be easy for
us to search for them.
[FUSOU]
We have to be patient.
We'll wait for the scout
planes to come through.
But Akashi was taken.
Who knows what horrible things
they could be doing to her.
We can't just sit here and
wait around like this.
[FUSOU]
Mm.
[KAKO]
Fusou!
We've received a report
from the Iron Blood fleet!
It's Azur Lane!
Yeah. I can confirm it's them.
What now? Should we plan
to take them out first?
Our only responsibility
is to watch the island.
We can let the Sakura Empire
deal with them.
[OKLAHOMA] That sure is a
whole lot of buildings
on such a tiny island!
That makes sense.
I bet a there was a large number
of people who lived there.
[OKLAHOMA gasps]
[SAN DIEGO]
It looks like it's in ruins now.
Yes, you're right. The island
was completely abandoned
after the Sirens attacked.
[SAN DIEGO gasps, sighs]
[SUFFOLK gasps]
[SUFFOLK]
Those are such lovely seagulls.
As if we don't already
have enough enemies.
[NORFOLK gasps]
Is something troubling you?
Humans battling humans makes
no sense to me. It's maddening.
[NORFOLK gasps]
Looks like they took
the upper hand.
But now we can be certain.
This must be the place where our
undercover scouts are hiding.
Okay, so then what's
your rescue plan?
It's not gonna be easy to
break through that blockade.
[PRINCE OF WALES]
Their safety is our priority.
I don't want to endanger them
by taking unnecessary risks.
I have to wonder what
Belfast thinks of all this.
[ENTERPRISE]
You're very calm.
Am I?
Well you don't seem
to be worried.
Aren't those your
friends out there?
Yes. We all work together
as maids, serving the Queen.
This is all a bit strange.
We're ships, but we're talking
about maids and queens
as if we're trying to‐‐
Trying to convince each
other we're human?
I apologize if that wasn't
what you were thinking.
[ENTERPRISE]
Mm.
It doesn't matter.
Whether we are people or ships,
we all have lives and hearts.
There is no difference.
[ENTERPRISE] I disagree.
We were born to fight.
Humans were not.
[BELFAST]
Yes, Miss.
We were given immense strength,
which comes with
great responsibilities.
[ENTERPRISE] It's our duty
to defeat the enemy.
[BELFAST]
But that's not all.
We're models.
Examples for others. Proof.
Of what?
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[BELFAST] That no matter
how difficult life becomes
in this world, we can still
live a proud and noble life.
We should be a light
for the lost.
What I'm saying is, we must
strive for elegance.
[gasps]
[BELFAST] And provide it
in all aspects of life.
Because, that is the true
purpose of a maid.
[ENTERPRISE] We don't think
like that in the Eagle Union.
Of course not.
That is why members of Azur Lane
must assist each other.
[BELFAST] Royal Navy,
Eagle Union, Dragon Empery,
Iris the Liberty,
Northern Parliament.
[ENTERPRISE] And Iron Blood and
Sakura Empire. But no more.
[JAVELIN gasps]
Where's Ayanami?
Could she be here?
It's possible.
If I see her again, I might...
[ATAGO]
What's the matter, Ayanami?
If you want to talk about
something, I'm glad to listen.
[gasps]
[giggles]
[TAKAO gasps]
Cut it out!
Uh! Stay right there!
I'm just fine!
[ATAGO] You don't have
to be so afraid of me.
Why do you seem so
timid about fighting?
[gasps]
Um. I don't dislike it.
[ATAGO] But you're not
fond of it either?
The thing is. I love all
of the Sakura Empire.
They're my treasured friends.
But... think about it.
On the other side,
it's the same.
They have friends
just like I do.
They laugh with each other.
They're all close.
[sighs]
You know?
[chuckles]
[AYANAMI gasps]
[AYANAMI]
This feels weird.
[EDINBURGH gasps]
[EDINBURGH screams]
[SHEFFIELD] It would
appear we've been found.
[AKASHI gasps]
I don't know what to do!
We have to get out
of here right away!
Where would we go?
The island is surrounded!
No, now is the best
time to escape.
[AKASHI, EDINBURGH gasp]
It's the Sakura scout plane!
They've located the target!
[PRINZ EUGEN grunts] I suppose
that means we ought to
make a bit of an effort.
You're not going to have to work
that hard with me on your side.
[Z23] This fight may not
be as easy as you think.
[REPULSE grunts]
Right. It's time to get focused.
Ready, aim... Pow!
[BOTH gasp]
All guns ready... fire!
Fire!
That's Azur Lane...
making their move.
[YAMASHIRO yelps]
[TAKAO]
It's a diversion.
[ATAGO] They must be trying
to use the fog and chaos
to rescue their friends.
We can't just rely
on Iron Blood.
We have to think bigger.
Ayanami! We're moving out. Now.
[AYANAMI]
Mm.
[ATAGO] I realize it
could be a diversion,
but we can't ignore
the enemy fleet.
[ZUIKAKU]
We'll handle them.
I need to know if the
Grey Ghost is among them.
I'm going to beat her this time.
[ZUIKAKU, SHOUKAKU grunt]
It's already begun.
[CLEVELAND]
Then we should get moving!
[gasps]
[CLEVELAND]
Not good.
[CLEVELAND, TAKAO gasp]
[shouts]
[grunts]
[ATAGO]
Takao!
[CLEVELAND grunts] This is
the worst timing possible.
Laffy! Javelin! Stay sharp!
[JAVELIN gasps]
Ayanami.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[JAVELIN gasps]
[gasps]
Enemy planes!
[SAN DIEGO shouts]
[HELENA]
Watch out!
Grey Ghost! Where are you?
[SUFFOLK] The enemy's strong!
You must fight harder!
[NORFOLK]
I know! I'm trying!
[gasps]
[NORFOLK yelps]
[SHOUKAKU] Apologies! I'm afraid
we don't have any time for you.
Interceptors! So you're here,
Grey Ghost! Come out now!
[SHOUKAKU gasps] Zuikaku, wait!
You can't go in there!
[giggles]
[SHEFFIELD gasps]
[EDINBURGH yells]
[Z1]
Feuer!
[gasps]
Right there!
Sheffy!
[EDINBURGH]
Sheffy, no!
[Z1]
Look at that!
Our combination tactics
are infallible!
[EDINBURGH gasps
[AKASHI gasps]
This is bad.
I wonder if I can
sneak away quietly.
[AKASHI]
Meow!
[grunts]
You can go ahead.
[BELFAST gasps]
Are you sure?
[CLEVELAND] Of course!
I'm pretty strong. It's fine.
Besides, I can tell
how worried you are.
[BELFAST gasps]
[CLEVELAND growls]
Let's do this!
Hold on!
[CLEVELAND] I'll take all
of you down right here!
[LAFFEY gasps]
They're running. Not again.
I've had enough of this!
[JAVELIN, LAFFEY gasp]
What's wrong?
Why won't you fight?
Uh, Laffey?
[grunts]
[JAVELIN]
Watch out!
[AYANAMI grunts]
[gasps, grunts]
[EDINBURGH gasps]
Huh?
[BELFAST grunts]
Belfast!
My, my. How nice
of you to turn up.
Unfortunately, you're one
move too late.
It appears we win this time.
Yeah! We did it!
[KAKO gasps]
[giggles]
[BELFAST]
You're wrong. Victory is ours.
It's you who are
one move too late.
What do you mean?
[gasps]
What?
[SHOUKAKU gasps]
[HORNET chuckles]
Sorry, 'bout that.
You've got the wrong sister.
[ZUIKAKU grunts]
[SHOUKAKU gasps]
It can't be!
Interesting. And after
everything that you said today.
I've learned something.
Your heart is soft, too.
Right, Belfast?
[gasps]
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Enterprise...
[gasps]
[grunts]
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Retreat.
What?
[Z1 growls]
[AKASHI whimpers]
[EDINBURGH]
Here we go!
[BELFAST giggles]
[AYANAMI gasps]
[AYANAMI]
Why? Why won't you fight me?
[LAFFEY] Because I don't
feel like fighting with you.
[AYANAMI gasps]
[AYANAMI growls]
Doesn't matter! We're enemies!
I know we are. So what?
I would rather be your
friend if that's okay?
[AYANAMI gasps]
[JAVELIN] Oh. I see.
And I think I understand.
Because that's how I felt.
I wanted to be her
friend as well.