[ENTERPRISE]
This scene again.
I don't understand. What are you
trying to accomplish by
showing me this vision?
[CODE G]
War.
War across all of time,
whether on land or ocean,
I continue to fight.
Every battle in an endless war.
This ocean engulfed in a flame
is my true, crimson lane.
As it will be for you.
[gasps]
Good morning, Miss Enterprise.
I hope you managed to
get a good night's rest?
Morning, Belfast.
[BELFAST]
Won't you have breakfast first?
No thank you.
Enterprise, I insist.
If you want to lead a healthy
human life, you need breakfast.
It's the most important meal.
[ENTERPRISE]
Just stop.
[gasps]
[ENTERPRISE]
I'm not an idiot, Belfast.
I know I'm not human.
No reason to pretend otherwise.
[PRINCE OF WALES] The Sakura
Empire has taken a bit of a hit.
They're going to need
some time to recover.
Unfortunately, we ourselves
aren't in the best position
to pounce on
such an opportunity.
Let me guess.
You're talking about
the Black Mental Cube
and all of Enterprise's
strange behavior, right?
There are plenty of reasons.
[door opens]
[PRINCE OF WALES]
Did you learn anything new?
Afraid not.
We're completely stumped.
It's difficult to know what
we're looking for when
we don't know anything about
Mental Cubes in the first place.
Huh. I can see quite
clearly that it is
literally a black box.
Okay, hold on.
From here it looks like the
glow is getting stronger.
Since it's related
to the Sirens,
we should assume that
is a very bad sign.
If those Sirens are even
thinkin' of messin' with
my sister, they sure ain't
gettin' away with it.
D'you have some kind of
an update on her?
She's not herself, Miss.
I gotcha.
I just wish she didn't
have to suffer alone.
[AKASHI groans]
Akagi is the worst!
Why did she have to cause
so much trouble for us?
Akagi was the one principally
aligned with the Sirens,
but now that she's gone,
I wonder how Kaga will act?
[AKASHI sighs]
I want answers right meow.
[UNICORN panting]
It's too hot.
[JAVELIN gasps]
How are you doing, Ayanami?
Ready to leave?
[gasps, sighs]
Oh, I'm sorry,
I was just thinking.
I'm feeling worried about
my Sakura Empire friends.
[OTHERS gasp]
I'm not saying that
I don't appreciate all of you
here at Azur Lane.
It's just that Sakura Empire
is still very precious
to me as well.
All I want is to do whatever I
can to save every one of them.
[JAVELIN gasps]
[JAVELIN] Mm‐hm! Yeah,
I'm right there with you!
Will you please let
me help you, too?
If they're important to you,
then they're important to me.
I appreciate that, but I'm
still not sure what to do.
We were able to become friends.
Even though we're
on different sides.
We could do the same
For Sakura Empire.
What do you think?
I hope so. Thank you.
[KAGA]
You want to seal away Orochi?
[NAGATO] Temporarily.
We just want to pause it.
If Akagi is gone, we won't
be able to push forward.
Whose decision was that?
It was mine and mine alone.
Half measures, Nagato.
Sakura Empire has no
future without Orochi.
Akagi's absence has clearly
taken its toll on you.
You should really try
to get some rest.
Separation can be painful.
Take some time and
allow your heart to heal.
How dare you!
[NAGATO]
My decision is final.
You are dismissed.
That's not good.
Things are starting to look a
bit troublesome around here.
We're in a bit of a bind.
The mass‐produced Sirens
are still unresponsive.
So Project Orochi's on hold.
I'm starting to get
a little worried
about Ayanami and Akashi.
I don't want them to feel lonely
or abandoned out
there on their own.
[SHOUKAKU] This whole plan
was doomed from the start.
We should not have
trusted our fate
to something we
know nothing about.
What is the matter with us?
The answer is not quite
that simple, I'm afraid.
You do realize Red Axis is
not a monolithic alliance?
We don't want Iron Blood to
know about our weakness.
Don't forget, the Sirens
are still the real enemy.
[NAKA] I wonder what
our next move will be.
We do what we have to do.
Simple as that.
Nothing has changed.
[SENDAI] Your own power is
the only thing you can trust.
[TAKAO]
How are you feeling?
I'm fine now and ready
to fight at any time.
Well, that's very good to hear.
However, our situation is
certainly less than ideal.
It's worse than we thought.
Sakura Empire is pushing
towards a terrible fate,
but we're only
part of the equation.
Everything is affected.
Well, then I guess it's up to us
to try and change it, isn't it?
[gasps]
[ZUIKAKU] I'm not going to
let them do all the work.
We have to be willing
to change as well.
Something feels familiar.
Is that you, sister Akagi?
Is that my sister Amagi?
[coughs]
You shouldn't be out in
the cold wind like this.
You need warmth to heal.
I'm so sorry.
I woke up feeling a bit better,
so I thought I'd be okay.
Oh, look over there!
See how pretty the
cherry blossoms are?
This is how you can
always find me.
Because even if I'm gone,
my heart will remain here.
Why do you say that?
Is something troubling you?
My powers may not last for long.
They'll go to all
the new children.
It's true, but...
We'll be together
forever, Akagi.
[OBSERVER] At this rate,
the Sakura Empire‐‐
no, the entire world
has no future.
You will need power.
Power akin to the gods.
This black Mental Cube
has the ability to collect
all forms of data.
And it evolves.
Data reminds me of
the will of a soul.
When it evolves,
it becomes power.
This transformation happens
often for beings like us.
You see?
And that is why the ship
created from the Black Box
will possess astounding
powers like no other.
It'll reanimate
the past and create
whatever future you desire.
That is a ridiculous theory.
It's true. You can create
anything you want.
Anything. You can even
bring back the dead.
‐‐[KAGA gasps]
‐‐That's nonsense.
[OBSERVER]
Ouch. So hurtful.
[AKAGI] Even if it had the same
appearance and memories
as the deceased, it would
still just be a reflection.
A shadow within a mirror image.
[OBSERVER] You're wrong.
If the shape and the content
are exactly the same,
then that means it is real.
And if they both exist,
what does that mean?
That newly repaired
ship you have,
is it the same as
the first vessel?
[gasps]
So. Which one is the
true Ship of Theseus?
The only thing that matters
is who's by your side.
Don't you want it to be Amagi?
[KAGA] There is no place
for me beside Akagi.
My sister deserves better.
I have failed. I couldn't
even be a replacement.
But this is not about me.
Dear sister Akagi, whatever you
wish will be my mission.
[ENTERPRISE panting]
What are you? Tell me right now!
When humanity began,
they set sail into the ocean
thirsting for adventure.
But soon, a different
desire took over.
A powerful need to
conquer the seas.
[gasps]
The history of the ocean is full
of tales of war and conflict.
This is what makes up
humanity's true desire.
The drama of what
humanity truly longs for.
What kind of insanity is this?
[gasps]
[ENTERPRISE]
Huh?
What's happening?
You've changed.
You don't fool me.
The looks you've stolen
are nothing but illusions.
The horror of your nature is
unworthy of their likeness.
No, I am quite real.
I stand here before you
as the mirror that reflects
the will of all humankind.
[ENTERPRISE groans]
[OROCHI]
I am Orochi. I am a monster.
I was born from
the will of humanity.
[ENTERPRISE]
Wait!
[BELFAST] It's all right.
I can take over from here.
[VESTAL] Are you sure?
Well, thank you and goodnight.
[groans]
[ENTERPRISE gasps]
[gasps]
What happened?
You were found unconscious
in the hall. You fainted.
You're not taking
care of yourself
and it's starting
to catch up to you.
Wait, is this a dream? No.
[ENTERPRISE gasps]
[BELFAST gasps]
I need some time
alone, all right?
[ENTERPRISE] Something is
clearly very wrong with me.
I cannot possibly be
of any use right now.
It's just...
I'm really not worth anything
if I'm not able to fight.
Uh‐‐
Huh? Uh‐‐ What the?
[ENTERPRISE gasps] Hey! Let go!
What's happening? Stop that!
Belfast! Are you
listening to me?
Hey! What is going on with you?
[JAVELIN gasps]
Is she in danger?
That was strange.
She's never like that.
What's wrong with Belfast?
[LAFFEY yawns]
Morning. Overslept.
[yawns]
Um. 'Kay. What's happening?
[SARATOGA]
Lover's quarrel?
You need to eat.
No thanks. I'm still
not that hungry.
I said eat.
Sure. Fine.
Ah. Good. If you would
eat decent meals regularly,
you wouldn't be so preoccupied
with negative thoughts.
As I've mentioned before,
I don't believe you are
as invested in fighting wars
as you claim to be.
You're right.
In truth, I think I might
actually be afraid of the ocean.
[BELFAST] I know. And yet,
you charge into battle.
Why is that?
[ENTERPRISE]
Because.
Fighting is the entire
reason for my existence.
You need to stop
falling back on easy answers.
[ENTERPRISE gasps]
I know it is difficult
for you to accept the truth,
but you must face it,
to move forward.
‐‐[explosion]
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasps]
What was that?
[CLEVELAND panting]
[DENVER]
Big sis!
[CLEVELAND] There's been
an attack! But from where?
If that's the Sakura Empire,
why would they attack now?
And why aren't the patrols
doing anything to help?
No, the enemy attacking is‐‐
It's not coming from the ocean.
Yes. This enemy has infiltrated
the base somehow! [gasps]
[PURIFIER giggles]
It's them. That's a Siren!
[laughs]
Northampton!
[NORTHAMPTON groans] I'm so
sorry I couldn't stop them.
[SAN DIEGO]
Not my ship again!
Belfast and some others
are already on the way,
but the enemy...
Yeah. Who would've ever
thought one of those Sirens
would dare to come out
here alone. Shoot. Huh?
[HORNET]
Enterprise?
[exhales] It's my purpose.
[PURIFIER laughing]
[NORFOLK]
She's way too fast!
[SHEFFIELD] The enemy has
stolen the Black Mental Cube.
We must not let her
get away, no matter what.
[EDINBURGH] There's no way
we can ever catch up to her!
Look! I think I'm positioned
in a perfect spot.
[PURIFIER gasps]
Oh! You did it! Huh?
[PURIFIER] Hi there!
Does someone want to play?
[EDINBURGH gasps]
[NORFOLK gasps]
Let's party! Tomorrow's
gonna be a big day.
[ALL gasp]
We've got mass‐produced
Sirens, too? [gasps]
[CLEVELAND gasps]
Y'all didn't really think
I'd let my sister
do all the work, now didja?
[JAVELIN yells]
Ayanami!
Huh? Right!
We did it! [gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Oh no!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[gasps] Enterprise!
Hornet! Hold this position!
If I'm really
afraid of the ocean,
then why do I continue
to fight as if I'm not?
[NORFOLK screaming]
I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die! [whines]
[laughs] Seriously?
You're not even gonna try
to make this fun for me?
What?
[BELFAST gasps]
Siren!
Oh, yay! It's Enterprise!
[PRINZ EUGEN]
Oh, darn. It's over.
And there they are,
the secrets of Orochi.
Uh‐‐
Kaga?
It's me, dear sister.
I'll see you soon.
[gasping] What?
[ISE gasps]
Whoa! What is that?
[BOTH panting]
Kaga? Is she behind this?
[gasps]
What is that? What's going on?
Wait, could that be... Orochi?
[gasps]
Kaga, come back!