[Music]
I have a staff...
a longsword, a katana...
and even a knife...
But it looks like the staff
is your preferred method.
Let's finish
them off, Miu!
This is our chance!
While you may be
able to see
what's two steps
ahead of you...
I can see even farther ahead
thereby surpassing you all!
Take this...!
Things are about to
get really sticky!
Once this glue dries you
won't be able to move
and I can't wait to take
pictures of you all helpless!
You won't be able to show
your face on the streets again!
Commander I think we
have a problem, sir!
Huh...? Why? What's
the matter, Matsui?
Nice try, little man.
You're different than
the other fighters...
I've never fought anyone
like you before...
That first round was
fun, Haruo Niijima.
But how... How'd
you get out? !
Too bad we don't have time
for another round right now.
But I got an
Alliance to crush.
This isn't good.
I didn't expect him to be
able to escape from trap 2.
What'll I do now?
This guy is huge!
He could totally crush me!
It's time.
I've failed
you, Kenichi...
I tried to take care of
Berserker on my own
but I couldn't do it!
That was a close one.
It looks like I got
here right on time.
Sieg! How'd you find me.
My driver heard reports
of an alien running naked
through the streets...
I figured it was you.
Let go, you traitor.
I can't leave you here!
Go, now...! I can handle
this weakling all on my own!
You bastard!
Good luck, my friend!
Women naturally have
less power than men...
That's why we have to rely
on weapons to beat them...
I don't understand why
that bothers you so much,
Kisara.
I'm a master of weapons
and I take pride in my skill...
Meanwhile my former disciple
has turned into a traitor.
It almost feels as though
I've been bitten...
by my own dog!
Their fight has nothing
to do with you-
if you girls wanna try
to start some trouble
then you're going to have
to get through me first-
and I'm not gonna
go easy on you!
Thanks, Miu...
Freya... I've
already told you...
I'm gonna walk my own
path from now on...
I'm not going back.
No...! I refuse to follow
in your footsteps
ever again!
Wow...
I liked you better before.
Shinpaku...!
Shinpaku...! Shinpaku!
I'm not letting
you down there.
You'll have to swim
if you want him...
Jump in and give
it your best shot,
but I promise you'll fail.
The Commander can swim faster
than anyone I've ever met.
What the hell? !
La-la-la...
What's the matter Sieg,
can't take the heat?
Guess my punches are just
too powerful for ya, huh?
I can handle the power
of your punches...
It's your sloppy,
untrained fighting style
that I'm not
accustomed to.
It's so unsophisticated.
Oh yeah?
Do-Re-Mi-
Impressive...
Random street fights can be
quite entertaining sometimes.
Yeah... Those two are really
going at it, aren't they?
Hey... Check it out...!
There's something in
the water over there!
What...?
Where?
The big guy's moves
are too flashy.
Reminds me of how
Kenichi used to be.
Why are you talking about
Kenichi in past tense?
He's not dead he's just
doing special training
in the mountains this week.
Somebody misses
his disciple.
I'm just gonna keep punching
you through the fence!
And I'm going to dodge.
Got ya.
Such a powerful
kick with forzando!
How the hell was he
able to kick me
from that position?
I found your weakness.
It seems you can't
block me in mid-air.
He got me good.
It feels like he
broke three ribs...
This calls for
drastic measures.
Jeez Is that
Mozart's Requiem?
I won't let you escape!
Why'd you do it, Sieg?
What made you decide
to leave Ragnarok
and join the
Shinpaku Alliance?
What is it they got?
I'm afraid that you could
never really understand,
my friend.
Whenever the Shinpaku
Alliance comes together
I hear a beautiful melody.
It's unlike anything
I ever heard
while I was
with Ragnarok.
It's allegro and
always con anima!
As long as that melody is
there I will continue
to fight for the
Shinpaku Alliance...
Even if it kills me.
You kidding?
Do these eyes look
like they're joking?
And now... My
ultimate attack...!
Requiem...! Buster!
Normally we'd be falling
towards concrete
but tonight we'll fall
into the water instead!
It's a nice
night for a swim!
Whoa! They fell
into the water!
Eh. The guy in the hat had
a death wish anyway.
I had hoped to hear that
melody of friendship
one more time...
Ah, too be young again.
Those kids'll risk it all
for something they believe in.
"Risk it all?" Ha...!
They may smell like sewer
but I doubt they'll die.
I 'd say that we
should save them...
but we shouldn't get
involved... in a duel.
What the-
You're a dead man.
So much power and
so suddenly...!
This must be his
Berserker mode!
I hope you're okay, Sieg!
If we're not careful the
whole Shinpaku Alliance
is gonna be wiped out!
Damn it, Kenichi!
Come back already!
You saw what happened?
Let's do it! We gotta find
opera boy before he drowns!
I've got a question
for you Sakaki-
where are you planning
on landing?
What...?!
Don't tell me you're aiming for
the top of that sign too...?!
You idiot!
Damn, you're heavy...
Less complainin'
more searchin'.
I found him.
-Catch!
-Apa!
Who's he...? That
opera boy...?
But where's is his hat?
Apachai is thinking dead
man's hat looks better on him!
He's not dead
yet, ya big dummy.
This young man was
quite courageous today.
Let's take him back
to Ryozanpaku with us.
Kenichi, my
friend, hurry...
We really need
your help... now...
Please hurry back before the
Alliance is destroyed...
Not too bad, Kisara...
You always were my
favorite disciple-
you were so talented.
Unfortunately, your attacks
are no match for my staff.
Since you've chosen
not to use weapons...
You've given up any
chance of being victorious
against me.
Why do you insist on
making me the enemy...?
There was a time,
not long ago,
when you looked up to me.
I got you.
Let go of me!
You like to fly,
little girl?
You can kick all you want
but your little woman kicks
are no match for
this big man's muscles.
That hurt you
little bitch!
I was goin' easy on ya
cause you're a girl
-but forget it!
-Shut up!
Holy crap...! That chick
just knocked him out!
How the hell
did she do that? !
She was able to defeat
that guy with one punch!
I don't know who she
is but she's amazing.
You've got a
lot of talent...
How would you like
to join my team?
Here ya go, Freya.
I brought you a drink.
Thank you.
You train so
hard every single day
it's no wonder you've
got such an awesome punch!
How'd you do that? !
I'll show you.
I keep a staff hidden
on me at all times-
it's my weapon of choice-
that way whenever
I end up in a fight
I'm sure to win no matter
who my opponent may be.
A full size staff would
be too hard to conceal
so I shortened it and
then cut it in half...
That way I can hide them
but if I need a longer staff
I can just screw
them together.
It's the ultimate skill...
and I've trained really hard
to be able to attain it.
Now whether I go up
against a man or a woman
at least I'll know
that it's a fair fight.
Amazing...
I simply wanted
you to understand
the importance of weapons...
And back then I really
respected you for that, Freya...
So cool!
So what changed your mind?
What made you decide
that using a weapon
is sign of weakness?
That is why you left the
Wall-keer-ee, isn't it?
You refused to use
weapons in battle.
I know that using
weapons takes skill...
-Its just that...
-What?
I didn't want you
constantly forcing
that skill upon me, Freya...!
I just wanted to
find my own path!
There's this guy named
Kenichi Shirahama
and he said something
I'll never forget...
Oh yeah, he's
her boyfriend.
He's not my boyfriend!
He's more like a
silly younger brother!
Or maybe more like
the family dog!
You know, one of those
stray dogs you take in
cause you feel
bad for him? !
Yeah, that what he is!
Hey come back here!
Do you know what
he said to me?
I've told myself that
I'll never fight a woman.
I'm not going to change my
principles 'cause of you.
I was stronger than him
but he refused to fight me...
It really pissed me
off at the time
but when I thought about it
later I realized something...
He wasn't patronizing me
or trying to be cool-
he was just trying to stick
to what he believed in.
I understand you
have your pride...
But I have my principles!
I realized that if he had
the strength to stand up
for himself then
I should too.
He's the reason I'm
standing up to you now...
I don't feel the need
to rely on a weapon-
I don't have to use one
if I don't want to...
It doesn't mean I think any
less of you because you do...
That's just how I
feel about it...
I won't use a weapon!
I'm sorry you feel like
I betrayed you by leaving
the Walkyrie but
that wasn't my plan.
I wasn't trying
to betray you...
All I wanna do is
walk my own path...!
I want to find my own way!
Go ahead and use your weapon
it's no match for my fists...
Now is my chance to prove
myself to you, Freya!
Kisara!
If only Kenichi knew the
positive effect he had
on the people around him...
It's a rare talent-
and something he's
always been able to do.
What the hell
are you doing? !
We're not done
with you yet!
Her moves are
ridiculously good...
It's almost like she's
light as a feather!
And she's able to take
us all on at once...
She's a lot stronger
than we thought.
I wonder what Kenichi's
up to right now?
Good work, you've finally
made it through level five,
Kenichi.
What's with the angels...?
Hi guys...!
Does this mean
I'm about to die?
You can't die yet we're just
about to start level six.
I'm so proud-look
at all that energy-
I was gonna give
him a break
but I think he's
ready for more.
Here goes level six!
I can't take much
more of this, Elder!
What's the matter...?
Don't tell me that's
all you've got... Kisara!
Her attacks
are relentless.
There has to be some way
I can get close to her.
Long kick!
I got so close but she
still was able to block me...
I can't get close
enough to make impact!
No way- I caught
her staff!
I use this staff as an
extension of myself...
You'll never be
able to stop it!
A weapon is like a fist so
strong it can never be broken!
She's so strong...
You're not going to defeat
me with your fists alone,
Kisara.
You big breasted monster!
What'd you say? !
I'm tired of all
these nicknames-
Dairy Cow, Blondie, Big
Breasted Monster, Big Boobs.
I have a perfectly good
name- it's Miu Furinji-
and you idiots
should try using it!
Miu...
Kisara...! I took care
of her lackeys for ya...
Good luck with
your fight...
Win it!
That's easy for
you to say...
At least someone
has faith in me.
I have to do this.
I have to beat her.
You still have the strength
to stand up, huh...?
That takes some
serious conviction...
Kisara.
If Miu was able to beat
all of those girls on her own
then I should be
able to defeat this one.
She was so light
on her feet-
almost like a feather...
I wonder if I
could do that?
What the hell? !
She's got new moves? !
How'd she do that...?!
She watched me do
that move once
and she figured it out.
What a fast learner.
She's not moving
so stiffly anymore!
It looks like
she's loosened up!
Hey Kisara...!
Don't waste your time trying
to dodge her attacks.
Try following
them instead!
Do what?
Don't concentrate
on kicking-
focus on getting into
her personal space!
Personal space?
She can't protect the
area above her head!
Damn it! It's closing in...!
I can do this!
What did I tell you...?!
My staff is an
extension of myself...
You can't get close
enough to touch me!
Oh yeah...?!
We'll just see
what happens
when I kick with
my other leg!
Double long kick!
Wow, that was the
best fight ever...!
Your first kick
was so strong
she used all her
power to block it
and that left her
wide open for you.
Thank goodness she didn't
have the strength
to counterattack cause
that could've gotten ugly.
It's not over yet...
I won't lose to you...
I can't...
Great... So now her weapon
is even more dangerous.
I can't do this...
You've won this
round, Kisara.
I can't do much of anything
with a broken staff...
I've no choice but
to admit defeat.
What're you
talking about? !
Let's finish this!
I understand...
The pieces of her staff
are like spears now
and that's too dangerous.
Weapons masters are
not out to kill-
that's not their goal...
They simply wanna fight
until they've rendered
their opponent defenseless,
isn't that right?
Correct... If you
want to kill someone
then a gun or a knife
would do the job...
But I'm a martial
artist not a murderer.
I can tell you feel very
strongly about this...
Thank you, Freya.
Why don't you just go
get another weapon...?!
We can still do this!
I'm done for the night...
I don't think I could
beat you right now anyway.
I'm proud of
you, Kisara...
You're strong.
Thanks Freya...
I'm still amazed Kisara
was able to change her
style so effortlessly...
I've never seen
anyone do that before.
I bet if she had
a good master
she'd get even better.
Hey, did you
hear the news?
The Shinpaku Alliance
was almost annihilated!
Yeah, I heard!
Man, that's crazy!
Those Ragnarok guys
aren't playing around.
Yeah but I also heard that
all the members of the alliance
are okay- so no one
really got hurt.
Jeez, boys are stupid...!
It's all they've
been talking about.
I really hope nothing's
happened to Kenichi...
It's been a long time
since he's been
to the gardening club.
I heard that Ragnarok's
patrolling the streets
looking for him!
Oh, poor guy!
I never thought
I'd say this
but it's kinda lonely here
without these idiots.
Captain Tanimoto...!
I'm so happy you've
decided to join us!
Would you let go of me!
You've got the wrong idea!
Jeez... I came to enjoy
the peace and quiet
now that you've
been dispersed.
What are you
talking about? !
The Shinpaku Alliance
hasn't been dispersed!
In fact, we could really
use your help right now!
How many times do I have
to tell you I don't wanna
join your gang of losers-
I'm not interested!
Okay, but...
Whether you join or not
we'll still consider you
a member because we all
think you're pretty awesome!
Here's a map of
the building
where the Commander
is hiding for now...
I know you're not
an official member
but I think I can
trust you with this.
-Why the hell--?
-See ya...
Captain Tanimoto...
Shinpaku!
Wait!
I just came to get
the Commander's PDA...
We're planning
to counterattack
whenever Captain
Shirahama gets back.
-Big nose?
-Gray!
Access granted.
Come on in.
Got your PDA sir...
It was at school.
Who's there? !
Hey...! Koga the
kicker's back everybody!
He's all that's left
of Kisara's squad...
Turns out the little guy was
playing dead the whole time.
I see...
I brought something
for you, Commander.
The guys told me you're
really into Space Cola
so I got you a bottle...
This stuff's hard to find-
it took me forever
to hunt it down.
Why thank you very much-
that's so thoughtful
of you...
Still I gotta wonder
why you were asking
about my favorite soda.
It just came up
in conversation.
Wanna tell me why the
cap's already open...?!
You should give it a
little taste test for me!
Why'd you make me
drink that crap? !
Where's the bathroom? !
Jerk... He put
laxatives in it...
Go lock all the doors
and bunker down, Matsui!
Yes, sir...! But why so
urgent all of a sudden?!
We've got a
big problem...
Ragnarok's found
our hiding place.
Where's the bathroom? !
Over there, you dumb ass.
That kid's a useless spy
he barely bought us any time.
We've got them trapped
like rats in a cage...
That's right...
no gettin' away this time.
[Music]
What's the
matter, Kenichi?
Why are just
staring blankly
at your cell phone like that?
Oh, I'm sorry-
it's just that I got
an email from Niijima
that's kinda
freaking me out.
I don't know what
to make of it.
Let me take a look at it.
Hmm... That is a
strange email.
I wonder what happened.
I don't get it.
He's never leak his plans.
Even if he had to die
to protect them-
he'd take them to the grave.
You know, the more
I look at this
the more it reads
like a will.
A will...?!
Oh no! Don't tell me
something happened to him
while I was gone!
I gotta go back!
Niijima!