[Music]
Tanimoto is Hermit?
I don't understand.
Yeah, I was pretty confused
about that myself...
but it looks like
the friend thing
was just an act
to pull me in.
Whoever he is...
that kid has received
some impressive training.
Yes, I agree...
Such skill is rare
in one so young.
Chalk it up to
experience, I suppose.
Easy for you to say!
What is it?
It's just... Hermit-
I mean Tanimoto-
asked me something...
While we were in the
middle of fighting
he asked me if my master's
name was Sougetsu Ma.
Does that make
any sense to you?
Master...?
What's wrong...?
Let's go...
You've put off your
training long enough.
Right. I'm sorry.
Not fast enough!
Kenichi must be quick
like tiny rabbit!
I've never seen Kensei
look so serious before...
Who is Sougetsu Ma?
I have to know!
Something tells me he's not just
gonna spit it out, though.
For all I know
everyone here
could have some
sort of secret past
they're not letting
me in on...
I'm supposed to be
their disciple
and they don't tell
me anything...!
It's not fair.
Faster, faster, faster,
faster, faster...
A-pa-pa!!
Oh! Tiny rabbit
got distracted!
Your magazine's
upside down.
Is not!
Something is
definitely wrong...
But right now...
Uh-oh! Kenichi,
please don't die!
Another day in hell...
What's he doing sneaking out
in the middle of the night?
I've followed
him this far...
can't let him
get away now...
Ah! Too late!
He's gone!
Man... where the
hell did he go...?
I'm so stupid...
Okay, I'm the worst spy ever.
Did that even count
as espionage...?
I kept expecting you
to do a little dance
and wave a red flag.
This is as far as you should
accompany me, Kenichi...
Have some take
out and go home...
It's on me this time,
don't worry about it.
No, thank you!
I'm afraid it'll be impossible
to guarantee your safety
if you follow me any
longer tonight...
now be a good disciple
and run along home
before things get sticky.
Being your disciple isn't
just about training together
and living under
the same roof,
it's about sharing
your burdens, too...!
I want to go with you, Master!
So you're prepared, then...?
To face whatever may happen?
I am!
Alright-y...
you can come along...
But this means that
if I jump off a cliff,
you have to do it
too, you know...
That's the rule
of following.
Please be joking.
Cool! We get to eat first?
Ahhhh.
I figured you'd show your
face sooner or later... Kensei.
Master Hakubi...
It's been a long time.
What is this place...?
A bald club?
I'm not bald.
No... This man is the strongest
fighter in the district...
Actually, his entire
name is Hakubi Ma Ryou...
And he is my uncle.
A feast...!
I'm in heaven!!
Eat as much as you'd like.
Ah! You're a good man...
And not--bald at all!
Thank you.
Time to eat!
Tell me, Kensei...
I know two reasons you
might have come here today,
so which is it...?
Are you looking
for Sougetsu?
That's right...
Is it true he's in
the country then?
Yes.
Alright. Then I suppose
I'll have to have a
little chat with him.
A chat, huh...?
Do you really think
that's going to help?
Who is this Sougetsu guy?
Sougetsu Ma...
Otherwise known as
my big brother...
What...?! You have a brother?!
Mmm... a troublesome
one at that...
Chaos seems to follow him
around like a puppy...
Right now he's being
hunted by some of the mafia's
most notorious hit men.
That's just who Sougetsu is,
he was born to fight...
He's never been able to control
those brutal tendencies...
But this district can't afford
the surge of violent crime
he'll bring
along with him.
I know...
I will find him.
You really just come
here for your brother?
Oh... That's
the other reason
I thought you might
have for stopping by.
Man. He's fast.
Not a bad attempt for
such a lovely young lady,
but I'm afraid I have
years of experience
dodging similar
attempts on my life.
What...? Who's she?
Really, Daddy?
I don't even get a hello...?
That's nice.
Daddy...? Like sugar daddy...?
So he... and she, they...
-They're like a... ahhhhhh
-Ew! No! We're not!
She's my daughter, Renka,
you disgusting boy!
She's sixteen!
Wha...?!
You mean you have
a daughter?...?
Come to think of it, you've
mentioned that before.
Huh. Don't worry, your
wife and the other two kids
are still far away in China.
That's right, Daddy,
I'm the only one you should
be worrying about right now...
I've had this place
staked out for weeks...!
Knew you'd show up someday!
I'm taking you back
home with me tonight!
We-heh-hell...! Kensei,
I'd say you're in a pickle.
Now come on...!
Just give it up, old man.
Forgive me, dear.
Well... Guess that's a wrap.
Not... funny.
Wait! Don't go, Daddy!
Kensei!!
Get your face...
out of there!
This. Is not. My fault.
Believe me, you're not
who I meant to catch.
Yeah, I got that...
Why are you trying
to force your dad
to come home anyway?
Geez you really don't
know anything, do you?
My dad is the leader of the
Phoenix martial arts sect.
He has over 10,000
disciples waiting for him
back in China.
Really? That's so cool.
Yeah. Well dad said it was
too much responsibility.
He gave all the leadership
duties over to mama,
packed a bag,
and disappeared.
Sounds right.
And now I find
him in Japan,
hanging around with
some loser kid...
so exactly who
are you, again?
Oh... Who, me...?
I'm Kenichi Shirihama...
a sophomore in
high school...
And I happen to be your
father's number one disciple!
You idiot...! Didn't anyone
teach you to dodge a punch?!!
Poor Daddy!
He's sunk so low in life
that he can only find one
scrawny little disciple...!
Oh, it must be humiliating
to have a student who can't
fend off one helpless girl!
He seems okay with it.
Oh... You're up already...
Well, at least you can
take a punch... kind of...
Yeah... The masters are
always saying that...
I have an unparalleled
ability to get beat up.
And that makes you what?...?
Proud?
Please stop hitting me,
Kensei's daughter.
So. Where did my
dad run off to?
How should I know...?
You're his daughter,
aren't you?
Shouldn't you
have some idea?
If I did, you'd think
I'd be wasting time
with his charity project?
So. Not the best part of town.
Lots of scary people.
This whole neighborhood's
under the control of the mafia.
Then whaddaya say
we get outta here
and get ourselves a
latte or something?
You can go. I have something
I wanna ask these guys.
Oh yeah? What's that?
Where I can find
my uncle Sogetsu.
Hold up! You mean you're
not looking for Kensei??
Boy you're slow...!
You see my dad is looking
for uncle Sogetsu,
so if we find him first,
we can ambush him.
Umm... do you know why...
your uncle's being
targeted by the mafia?
Because he betrayed them.
So you're sayin' I
don't gotta hold back?
No reason to.
If we don't kill him
he'll just kill all of us.
You mean like how he
bumped off that whole family
of 14K Triads back
in China, right boss?
Yeah.
But how do you know
he's gonna show up here
and fight me, boss?
A guy like him can't resist
the lure of a good fight,
no matter what...
When he hears our strongest
fighter is waiting here,
he'll take the bait.
And I'll be right here,
ready to take him
out when he does.
We'll show that traitor
what happens in our world
when you don't hold up
your end of a bargain...
You get dead.
I give up.
You can't give up.
We just have to
find one clue.
He's there...? Just keep
him busy, I'm on my way.
You! Where's Sogetsu Ma?
And who the hell are you?
Just answer...!
Where is he?
What's that a sword-belt...?
Well that's a new one.
And you...
That fancy move...
That was no Chinese martial
art I've ever seen.
No... It's Japanese Jujitsu.
-Jujitsu?
-Yeah...
I'm learning a bunch of
different disciplines
at the moment...
Let's see, there's Karate,
and Jujitsu, and Muay...
What is this,
some kinda buffet?
You don't just take
one of everything
and see what tastes good!
You pick a discipline and
stick with it, you jerk!
Oh! 'Scuse me.
What do we have here...?
Trying to sneak something
out of my pocket
or something into it?
I was just testing you...
I heard that
you were fast...
I've got a note
from Hakubi for ya.
Well maybe next time
hand it to me...
I could have broken
your arm, stupid boy.
I'll remember that.
Hmmm...
If Hakubi's right,
maybe I can stop this
from going any further...
So this is where
you've been!
We all waited for you
there for over an hour
and you were off training
again, just like always...
I can't believe I
went to the trouble
to set you up on a blind
date and you no-showed!
Come on, man, I'm just trying to
get my big brother to realize
there might be more to life
than sparring matches
and alcohol, ya know?
I like sparring matches
and alcohol better than girls...
Girls are always
chattering and giggling...
it's annoying.
Trust me, man, the benefits
seriously outweigh the costs.
Yeah, I think I'd
rather bash heads in.
Fine...
Just tell me you
didn't kill anyone.
I don't think I did.
You don't think you did??
You've gotta get a
hold of yourself!
Lately it seems like
you're trying to kill
everyone you fight.
I am!
That's what
martial arts means!
It's the art of death,
used to defeat your enemy.
You're serious.
I don't get it, if Kensei
and Sougetsu are brothers...
then how come they don't
talk to each other anymore?
Twenty years ago,
my uncle killed some
people back in China...
and he had to leave
the country for good.
Really...? He murdered people?
This is the place.
And this is the end
of the line, kid...
Inside that building lies a
world of corruption and violence
you've never seen before.
You'll be putting
your life on the line
if you go any further...
Ask yourself if you're
really up for that.
What would you say if I tried
to stop you from going in?
I'd say 'bite me!'
And that's how I feel...!
I'm not letting a girl walk
into a place like that,
looking for a
murderer, all alone.
Jeez... Is this guy for real?
Who are you kidding?!
I'd be better off
alone than taking you!
You're probably gonna get
us both killed, amateur!
What was daddy thinking,
taking on this puny weakling?
Well, if you
really want to come
I guess I can't
stop you...
But I can't
guarantee your life!
I'm sure we'll be fine,
I mean this guy is
your uncle, right...?
It's not like he's gonna
kill his own family...
Maybe he'll
listen to reason.
Sure. Right.
Sure! Right!
You just have to
be more peaceful.
Fighting isn't
the only answer.
Didn't we just agree
to be more peaceful?!
I am being more peaceful.
I didn't kill
anybody, did I?
I can't let uncle Sogetsu get
away with what he's doing...
He's shaming the Ma family
by dealing with the mafia,
and I'm putting
a stop to it.
Wait...!I'm
coming with you!
Renka!
Oh.
Get down!
Ow...! Man!
-What was that?
-That... was uncle Sogetsu.
Huh...
I thought this one was
supposed to be strong...
What a disappointment.
Sougetsu Ma!
You're done
shaming our family!
Interesting... that kick...
I'd recognize
the form anywhere,
but I don't recognize you.
No, wait...!
Don't hurt her, she's
Kensei Ma's daughter...!
She's your own niece!
I suppose I should've
guessed that...
But no matter
who her father is,
she attacked me as
a martial artist...
Besides...
I said goodbye to
my family long ago.
Weird...
Kenichi hasn't come
back to the dojo yet?
No. Is sad...
He said we'd play the
black and white game.
Kenichi followed Kensei
into town a few hours ago...
..Lame.
Oh... Alright then.
Who knows what den of sin
Kensei's introducing him to...
Brother... I see that
you haven't changed.
Never thought I'd run
into you, Kensei...
I guess this trip
was worth it.
Hang on, Renka.
Kenichi.
I want you to
take her and go.
No! I'm not leaving
you alone with him!
So that runt...
Is he your disciple?
Hah... I'll never understand
why you live this way...
wasting your time
training weaklings
when you could be
a great fighter.
Hey! I'm not weak!
Twenty years and you still
can't see the truth, can you?
We can try to go
back, Sougetsu...
Find the man you
could have been.
No... It's too
late for that.
Then you leave
me no choice...
As your brother,
it's my duty to stop you.
Don't get cocky... Kensei.
That stance...
In a normal fight the left
hand is above the right...
But they both have their
right hands on top,
which can only
mean one thing...
This is a fight
to the death!
Master! Don't do it...!
You'll never be able
to forgive yourself!
I've never seen
anything like this!
I've never watched two masters
in a fight this intense...
It's unbelievable.
It's like...
It's like watching them
duel for their souls.
Fist of Heaven!
Well...
Looks like your defense
is as strong as ever...
Not just anybody can
absorb my attack like that.
Your attack has
no technique.
It can't hurt me...
I'm surprised at how little
you've improved in this time.
But then, I suppose when you
lost your heart as a man...
-your art lost its heart, too.
-Shut up!
Sougetsu the Strong...
and Kensei the Slick...
They were revered
as China's most
accomplished martial artists.
No doubt... Wonder which one's
the most accomplished now.
Let's see you
fight this...
Master Sougetsu.
Do it.
Right.
What happened?
Now you die!
Son of a bitch.
Oh no...
Kensei lost?
I told you, martial
arts is the art of death
used to defeat your enemy...
It's not a tool
for the weak.
It's not the tool
that makes a killer...
It's the spirit of
he who weilds it...
You're a fool to think
strength gives you
the right to kill.
But... I don't understand
how this happened...
how'd you beat me?
I have the strength
of my friends...
all of their training...
When you fought me, you
fought each of them as well...
but you've been
training alone,
so you fought alone today.
We have to go!
This place is collapsing!
Daddy!
'Course... surrounded by people
who're worried about you,
like always.
I never had anyone
who cared about me...
or supported me...
But you...
You were always popular.
I didn't leave China because
I was running from what I did.
I was looking for
my place to be...
Somewhere I might
actually belong.
Brother...
It's not gonna hold
much longer, master!
Go on, Kensei...
Get outta here.
Alright, kids...
Let's get going.
We're just gonna leave...?
But he'll die!
You can try to get him out
the door if you'd like...
I'm sure my brother would
prefer to go out fighting.
He'd rather die?
Is that what a
fighter's world is like?
Hurry!
No better than I
deserve I guess...
At least it's over.
I can't let you do this...
Damn it, he's your brother!
Is this guy freakin' crazy?!
Come on. Let's go.
Why...? It's done.
Because I'm a disciple,
that's why...!
And I can't just watch
a master die like this.
You're not my disciple.
I may not be...
But think I know someone
who feels differently.
You mean, Natsu.
He had the same look
in his eyes I did
when I was a kid.
He called you his master...
And he would
want you to live!
Jeez... Are you for real...?
Kensei really found himself a
weird one this time, didn't he?
Neither the rescue team
nor the cleanup crew
ever found Sougetsu's body...
On the way back
to Ryouzanpaku...
Kensei didn't really
have much to say...
But I could've sworn when I
headed to my room that night,
I heard him whisper...
thank you.
And even though he's
not quite himself yet...
He's slowly getting
back to normal.
So... Are you sure it's okay
you didn't go back
home with Renka?
Of course.
This is my home now...
I'm sure deep down
she understands.
That sneaky rat.
What kind of a father
refuses to come home
with his daughter
when all she wants to do is
take care of him lovingly?!
Now, now... That won't
get anything clean.
And who knows...
Maybe I'll even
drag that Kenichi guy
back home with us, too.
[Music]
Whoa. Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's the
matter, Kenichi?
My locker. There's a
letter in my locker.
It's pink.
And I'm pretty sure...
It's a love letter.
Oh.
Wow. Aren't you
the popular one.
No! I mean, I don't wanna be!
I mean it's not like that
Miu, really! I swear!
Well, don't let me stop you
from reading your love letter.
I'll get out of your hair.
Miu! Wait! I...
Aaaaah! This sucks...!
But I wonder
who it's from...