They are quite the
trinity of skill.
With Koga's swift kicks...
Ukita's throwing strength...
And of course...
Takeda's fearsome fists...
It's safe to say poor Kenichi
doesn't stand a
chance against them.
How sad, things were just
starting to interesting.
So this is Ragnarok, huh?
Even if they're a gang
of vicious thugs,
it's always best to root
for the winning team.
Yup, yup. You're
sprouting just fine.
Izumi?
I always thought you were kind
of quiet and glum, but,
you seem so lively
when you're here.
Sure, well it's
just so relaxing.
It's the one place I don't
have to worry about
some jerk trying to fight me.
It's like a total paradise!
You don't have to be
that lively about it.
If she only knew.
I'm being hunted by that
Ragnarok gang 24/7.
And then every other second
of my life goes to training.
I'm really gonna enjoy
making you bleed!
Here it comes!
He's evil!
Apa!
Although, there are some
good times here and there.
More, more!
There you go. You got it!
With encouragement like that,
I can't just up and quit.
Y'know, Kenichi?
Huh?
I've heard rumors that you're
the most ruthless fighter
in the whole school,
but I don't believe it.
You put so much thought and care
into nurturing these flowers,
and you somehow tolerate
that weird friend of yours.
So you've gotta be a
decent person, right?
Yeah sure, except I think
I've already told you
that I'm not actually
friends with Niijima.
He's more like a demon trying
to possess my friendship.
What's the matter?
I don't know. I just got
this weird sensation,
like I felt an evil
presence or something.
Oh, how sad, Kenichi,
you must be delusional.
Too busy smelling the flowers to
realize your life's in danger.
But if you want to spend
your time pushing daisies,
help is on the way.
It doesn't seem like your
Snow King orchid has grown much.
Nope. I chose it
because I like its name,
but it seems
pretty stubborn.
All of the other plants
are growing though.
Maybe we should try
a different bog moss?
I guess some plants just can't
grow as quickly as others,
no matter how hard they try.
Huh?
It's not like it doesn't
want to grow...
It's not slacking
off or anything...
Please, just one time,
say that it can grow!
No.
No, Apachai, I haven't trained
enough yet to spar with you!
Helllooo?
Right, sorry!
I was just relating to what
this plant must be feeling.
Wow, you must have a
lot in common with it.
But, I kind of feel like I
can relate to it as well.
I'm a bit slow too, y'know.
It just takes me longer
to improve than most.
What, no way! But...
Maybe there are some of us that
aren't meant to do great things,
no matter how hard we try.
Are you ever gonna learn?
Keep your shoulder straight
or you're just asking to
get grabbed and thrown.
And you're gonna be singing
soprano real quick
if you don't keep
your thighs closed.
You're just not gettin' this.
You moron! Didn't you even
listen to what I was saying?!
You need to align your striking
fist with your blocking fist.
Move 'em together.
Try to imagine
they're connected by a
string pulling each other.
Like this.
See?
I can't do that!
Let's take a minute and compare
our arms, why don't we?
Your freakin muscles are
the size of my upper torso!
I mean, c'mon--
For the last time, Sakaki, stop
smashing everything!
So what? You don't
need guns like mine
to throw a proper punch.
Hey, what's up?
You didn't hear
a word I just said.
Happy to help.
You've actually got more
muscle mass than Miu does.
But watch.
Now, how many punches
did you just count?
Wow, awesome, that was three!
Three punches in one second!
Nope, that was six.
Thanks for watching.
There are two primary
elements of karate.
The first, Nahate,
relies on strength.
But the second, Shurite,
emphasizes the speed
of your fists.
You've gotta learn
both to master karate.
But we'll just stick
with Shurite for now.
You know, if you want those
fists to fly faster, then
I've got the perfect Chinese
training method in store.
Back off, Kensei!
Can't you see that I'm
training him right now?
No! I see your time
is up and it's my turn.
What? We hardly
accomplished anything.
That's not his fault.
Try teaching him something
next time instead of just
calling him a moron.
Miu, I need you
for a demonstration.
No way!
Your hands aren't getting
anywhere near me, creep.
Sorry, Kenichi, I've
lost my motivation.
Will you please
take this seriously?!
Now, hold your arms
up like mine.
Do you mean like this?
Drop your shoulders and
let your arms swing
from one side to the other.
Relax them completely as
they make their rotation.
Now alternate while you walk.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
You should be able to feel
your joints stretching,
almost like your arms
are about to fly off.
So, uh, how exactly am
I supposed to use this
to defeat an enemy?
You can't defeat anybody by
swinging your arms at them.
What?!
Then why are you
teaching it to me?
Hey, no need to get excited.
There is a method to the
madness, I promise.
Just keep doing that as
you make a full circuit
and you'll start
to figure it out.
Around the garden?
Around the neighborhood.
You're joking.
Swing your arms in line with
your hips, and no cheating!
Best of luck to you!
This is more embarrassing
than tough.
Hey, Miu?
I know you're not too
familiar with the area.
So, I figured I'd
come with you.
Just to make sure
you don't get lost.
Do you even know
what this is for?
Sure, it's to help you
loosen up your muscles.
Really, but how?
When you swing your arm in one
direction as hard as you can,
like when you punch, you can't
help but tense up the other arm
as well, and that slows down the
movement of your next swing.
It's a basic reaction that
protects your joints
from straining. But it's more
psychological than physical.
So this is going to
help me loosen my arms
so they'll move faster?
Yeah, so it's important that
you visualize your arms
swinging further and
further away each time.
The idea is that once you make
these large swings smaller,
they become compact
striking moves. Make sense?
Whatever you say.
Nobody told me there
was a parade today.
Oh, I'm not in your way, am I?
Lucky coincidence bumping
into you, Kenichi.
We've been looking for
you all over the place.
I've seen him...
I think he's from
the Ragnarok gang.
He's one of the three guys
that were looking for me!
In case you don't know,
my name's Taichi Koga, and
I need you to come with me.
My friend Takeda really
wants to meet you
and I don't wanna
disappoint him.
Hey, check out Blondie,
her boobs are huge!
Huh? Ah!
Okay, Kenichi, you gotta
explain this to me.
How does a dork like you
get such a cute girlfriend?
Nobody said we were dating,
he's my friend! That's it!
She certainly was
emphatic about that.
And I don't enjoy being ogled.
So why don't you go away!
Takeda said he wanted
me to bring you to him,
but I've got a better idea.
I'm gonna beat the crap out of
you in front of your girlfriend
and show her what
a loser you are,
and then I'm gonna
steal her from you.
What is with this guy?
I'm not an object!
I guess I'm just gonna have
to deliver you to Takeda
in a body bag, huh?
We're surrounded.
Oh, man, this is not good.
Nine against two?
Even though Miu's with me,
they're all carrying weapons.
There's no way we can
take all of them!
Alright. Just try and escape.
Hey, it looks like you guys are
having a little party over here.
What's up, Kenichi? I didn't
know you had so many friends.
Sensei, you're just in time!
It seems like you guys
are having a lot of fun.
Well, no, not really.
That little punk there
was harassing me!
Alright, old man! Beat it!
Aw, man! How did he--
He knocked him down
just by glaring at him!
Kenichi.
Sensei?
I'm glad he's on our side...
This guy's not human!
Keep your thighs closed!
There you go, kid,
that's a good stance.
Good enough.
Oh, and Apachai's
been waiting on you,
so try not to take too long.
What?
Hey, wait!
Sensei! Where are you going?
We need your help...?
Sensei, come back!
Kenichi, no!
I wouldn't if I were you.
Koga's kind of crazy.
He'd probably kill you if you
got in the middle of this.
And I'd hate to see a cute
girl like you get killed.
Oopsie, my hand slipped.
You'll regret you have hands.
So stupid...
I can't even count how many
times Sakaki's told me
how important it is to
land the first blow.
And I get punched
while crying for help!
I've gotta land a hit, or
there's no way I'm gonna win!
Alright, how about
this? Yamazuki!
I guess you haven't
heard of me after all.
I'm Koga the kicker. And
you're way too slow for me!
He's dodged every punch!
I can't believe you're
so weak! Seriously!
Tsukuba must have had the
flu when you beat him!
Ragnarok doesn't need any
more worthless losers like you!
Wait a minute!
Wh- what are you doing?
That supposed to scare me?
Okay. Relax my arms
completely as they move.
Visualize them swinging
out of my joints.
And when I pull them into
smaller, concentrated moves...
Quit wasting my time!
...they become compact punches!
No!
It barely brushed
against his chin!
Ha! You just missed.
Huh?
I just didn't eat enough today.
What the--
Did he rattle my brain somehow?
Attack him! Kill him! Now!
Oh!
Uh... I forgot to leave
some for Kenichi.
I guess I got a little
carried away there, huh.
She's a monster!
Huh?
Help me!
Did you hear that, he
called me a monster!
Yeah, but I think he meant
it in a good way, you know,
like the monsters of rock.
He did not! You know
that's not true!
Come on, let's get out of here.
Man, for someone with her
skills, she sure is sensitive.
You hear that, Kensei?
Our golden boy here
defeated their leader,
just like I predicted he would.
I knew that you could do it,
I wasn't worried or anything.
Oh, thanks.
Sure, sure. That's why you spent
all afternoon pacing around
the garden muttering about
how worried you were.
So I guess all those straight
punches and blocking maneuvers
I taught you came in pretty
handy after all, did they not?
What? Yeah, that's it...
Jeez, he seems so proud.
I just can't bring myself
to tell him that it was a
combination of sheer luck
and Kensei's technique
that did it.
So, Apachai's bummed that
you missed his lesson today.
He's been moping
around the house.
He hasn't even said
his own name in hours.
Oh, I'm sorry Apachai!
I got attacked by a gang
while I was out doing
Kensei's exercise.
But you can train me twice
as long next weekend!
I don't care.
Apachai's coloring books
are more fun than you.
Oh, man.
What's the deal?
Aren't any of you idiots capable
of bringing me this freshman?
It's not my fault, Kisara!
We ran into him on the street,
and I was gonna
bring him over here!
But he had this really
hot girlfriend with him,
and I got a little distracted,
but she turned out to be
some kind of monster! For
real! You shoulda' seen it!
She's gotta be a
mutant or something!
Do you know what he's
going on about?
Alright, this is the last
time any of you fail.
Takeda, take Ukita
and Koga with you
and do whatever it takes
to retrieve Kenichi. Understood?
Yeah.
I'm telling you, she's
got supernatural powers!
She's not human--
Kenichi Shirahama...
You're full of all
sorts of surprises.
Too slow! Offense and defense
are not two separate things!
You have to use your entire body
to concentrate two
moves into one form!
Ugh! You haven't
improved at all.
What happened? I thought you
used the technique I taught you
to defeat the leader
of that gang!
I'm gonna have to take
this secret to the grave.
He'd never let it drop.
Okay, Miu listen up.
Next time you notice he's let
his guard down like that,
just go ahead and kill him!
You got it!
No, it's fine!
Go on and kill me.
I'm too slow to live!
That's right!
Now, Kenichi, swivel downward
and take Miu by the arm.
No, your upper hand
is far too weak.
You would normally use
your leverage on her arm
to pull her backwards
for the next step.
But if you grasp
her that weakly...
Well, Miu?
That's what happens.
You've got plenty
of time to learn.
I'm just entirely
hopeless, aren't I?
I haven't made any
progress at all!
Apachai doesn't believe
that, even if it's true.
Stay away!
Apaaaaaaa!
Apapapapa!
Perfect. He's
destroying my statues.
What's going on in here?
Kenichi made the mistake
of showing fear.
And you know what happens
when Apachai smells fear.
Quite a sight.
Well, it's still
pretty good training.
He can witness
Apachai's techniques
without getting killed.
You think so?
Can observing this do
that much for him?
Just go away!
This is not good.
Why haven't I been
getting any better?
It was just a fluke
that I won that fight.
It wasn't skill,
it was just luck.
Hey, I wish you wouldn't feel so
depressed, you're doing great.
All your hard
work and training
is really starting to pay off.
Are you just saying that
to make me feel better?
Yeah.
I know that Miu would
never tell a lie,
but she could've
lied about that.
So there it is.
I won't get any better
no matter how hard I try!
I'm going to the Gardening
Club, I'll see you later.
Maybe I should've lied.
Bad news, Kenichi.
Latest word on the wire
is that those three guys
aren't the only ones
hot on your trail.
There's one more wild beast
trying to track you down.
No!
What happened in here?!
Kenichi...
Yo, Kenichi! I was startin'
to think you'd never show up.
It's you!
Hope you've been working
on your muscles, little guy!
Daimonji!
Oops!
Tell me why you did this!
'Cuz you and me aren't
anywhere near finished.
I can't just accept that you
beat me on some fluke.
And I heard that you
somehow managed
to beat the
sub-captain, Tsukuba.
And you know what people
would say about me
if I took down the guy
that beat Tsukuba,
the strongest member of
the Karate Club?
They-they'd say I'm
number one, that's what!
And once word gets
back to Ragnarok,
I bet they'll ask
me to join 'em.
Do I look like I care about
your stupid plan, Daimonji?
I just want you to let Izumi go.
I'll release her if you promise
not to run away when I do.
I won't run away.
Whatever, fine.
Now I want you to tell me...
Why did you destroy all
of the plants like this?
What, these plants?
I'm asking you a
question. Answer me!
We just got bored waitin' for
you to show up, that's all.
Please stop!
But don't cry yet punk,
we decided to let your
favorite plant live for now.
Of course you'd grow
a puny plant like this.
Shut up!
A plant like this doesn't
even deserve to live,
no matter how much
you want it to.
I'm doin' you a favor by putting
this thing out of its misery.
Come on!
Wait a minute, where'd he go?
You son of a--
Impossible!
He was right there,
then he was gone!
I'll, kill, you!
Oh wow.
I'm sorry. This
is all my fault.
Let's clean up.
We need to repot the
plants that can be saved.
Right.
I don't think this one's
gonna make it.
So sad.
I'm so sorry,
Snow King, I'm sorry.
But we-- we should
still try to save it.
Sure enough, a few days later...
Hey! Kenichi!
What's up, Izumi?
Look at this! Your plant's
grown a new leaf!
You did it buddy,
I knew you could!
You're small, but you've got the
persistence of a heavyweight!
I think it's more durable
because it has such a thick
stem from growing slowly.
It never would've survived if it
had grown quickly and thin.
That's right.
Just because it's slow doesn't
mean it's not actually growing.
Real progress takes time.
I could see all
of Daimonji's moves,
as if they were in slow motion.
They might only
be small steps,
but I'm still making progress!
I'm growing!
Be careful.
Wow, you're really
fired up today, Kenichi.
You've got it! I'm going to
keep on working until I bloom!
Just like my Snow King!
Your... Snow King?
Those Ragnarok guys are getting
more and more dangerous
every time I run into them.
They were even cheap enough to
pull weapons on me today
and I don't stand a chance
against them with just my fists.
Shigure said she's going
to train me in weaponry,
but I think I'm more likely
to die training with her
than fighting the
entire Ragnarok gang!
I admit it, I'm scared,
I don't wanna do this!
Kenichi, don't be scared.
You know the expression
'don't lose your head'?
We are dealing with swords here.
I don't wanna die!