Back to the ol'
strategic withdrawal.
Not the most
exciting of options,
but definitely the safest.
And if you avoid a
problem long enough,
it'll eventually go away, right?
But these Ragnarok goons
are so darn persistent.
I don't even get
Sundays to relax.
Well, look who's
finally bagged the prize!
Me, Takashi Furukawa!
That name don't mean much right
now, but you wait, pretty soon
everybody's gonna know me as
the number-one guy in Ragnarok!
Oh, can it! I don't
care who you are!
Right now you're screwing up
my only day to go
shopping with Miu!
I've been waiting for
this all week!
Not my problem.
If I can manage to drag you
back to Kisara's place,
chances are she'll make me
one of her top go-to guys!
Kisara? Who the heck is that?
Just one last thing.
Fine, what is it.
Call off your crazy
girlfriend, huh?!
Amazing as always...
She's taken out five guys
in less than two minutes
and hasn't even broken a sweat!
Hang on a sec,
maybe I should try to bring this
chick back to Kisara instead.
Nah. I better not start
second guessing my orders.
If Kisara wants the kid,
the kid who she'll get.
Uh oh. If I can't take care
of at least one of these guys,
I'll never be able to look
Miu in the eye again!
My pride's at stake!
Want some more? Free samples.
I'm bleeding!
What the heck you
tryin' to do to me?!
I think-I think you
broke my nose, you punk!
Man, that hurts! I quit!
Are you gonna be alright?
Be careful!
He could be faking it to
try to lure you in closer!
Keep your guard up!
Now you're gonna bleed.
Hey, wait a minute!
That's no fair!
You're not allowed to use
that thing! Are you crazy?!
Someone could really get hurt!
Enough already!
I've gotta get inside his
reach without getting cut.
But how?
Pulling a knife on an unarmed
opponent? You know better.
That's against the rules!
Gotta save face.
I better play it cool,
like it's no big deal.
Whew! We make a
great team don't we.
Huh?
What happened to him?
Someone pee in his Sake glass?
He's been like
that ever since
he came back from
shopping with Miu.
I can't even get him
to start training.
Apachai knows that face.
Kenichi is hurting
on his insides.
Whadda ya know? He's movin'.
Maybe Apachai could
cheer him up?
Nah, let's leave him alone.
It's normal for teenagers to
get depressed from time to time.
He's alright.
Well now, Sakaki, been studying
up on teen psychology, have we?
Why'd he have to pull
that stupid knife?
I'm scared enough
in a normal fight,
and I sure wasn't
prepared for that.
So what am I supposed to do?
Guess I'm gonna
need some help.
Akisame sensei might be able
to teach me a few pointers.
But knowing the way he works,
he'll probably make me
do some freaky exercise
I don't understand.
It'd be too embarrassing
to ask Miu.
But maybe Sakaki...
Yeah, that's it!
I bet you he's dealt with
his fair share of weapons.
Huh? Huh?!
Shigure! Leave him alone! What
do you think you're doing?!
Just practicing, is all.
I could be wrong, but it
looks to me like Shigure's
just offered you some
personal weapons training.
What?
When it comes
to weapons use,
Shigure's skills
are unparalleled.
But I'm not interested
in using weapons,
I just wanna know
how to avoid 'em!
What happened when you
saw that knife today?
You completely
froze, didn't you?
Yeah, that's one
way of putting it.
What you need is experience.
And before you can learn
to avoid weapons in a fight,
you must first become familiar
with the weapons themselves.
I was a little uneasy
with the idea
of leaving Shigure
totally in charge,
so for safety's sake, I
decided to watch this one.
Apachai thinks watching
is a good idea.
Most definitely.
Just promise me!
You won't let her cut off
anything I can't grow back?
Okay then, what
should we start with?
Your first lesson:
using a blade...
...to kill.
What, is something wrong?
'Course not.
You'll get a better chance
to learn this way.
Using a spoon? Really?
Yes, yes! No!
Kensei, you pervert!
Kenichi! Kenichi!
Don't be dead!
What in the world is
going on in here?
I need to go change!
Kensei, you know better.
And Kenichi, you should
know knives and spoons
are just worthless
hunks of metal,
as long as you can
avoid being hit by them.
But, the problem here
is that Shigure's an expert,
and she never
misses her mark.
Your only chance
is to observe calmly,
and wait for an opening.
Isn't there some safer way
I can learn this stuff?
Assume the position.
Okay. Like this?
What, do you want me
to chop your hand off?
You're wide open.
Every vital point.
Stand up straight.
Now shift your stance
so your body's aligned
sideways with mine.
Put your free hand on your hip.
Think you can hit me?
I know I can!
You're dead.
I win.
I'm not dead yet!
Okay then. Now that you're
getting the hang of it,
let's teach you how to
counter an armed opponent
with your bare hands!
You call this getting
the hang of it?!
Kenichi. What would you
say is the most important
characteristic a
fighter can possess?
I dunno. mm...
Strength maybe? Or technique?
Nonsense! It's courage!
If you don't have courage,
you can't stay calm,
and you overlook openings.
Without courage your
strength is limited!
Without courage your technique
is sloppy and unfocused!
Then I'll never
be a great fighter.
My courage, well,
it's a little lacking.
If you don't have it, then
you have to train for it!
Practice is the
key to everything.
Shigure, this time I want you to
push him to the absolute edge.
Shigure...
She really is a
master of weapons,
but otherwise she's
such a mystery.
Most of the time I don't
even know she's here.
Get set. Go.
What happened to "ready"?!
One thing's for
sure, though.
I definitely found the
right person to teach me!
Ah, I think I'm
bleeding internally.
If that was Shigure's
way of taking it easy,
then I can't imagine what
would happen to anyone
who had to fight her for real--
Betcha' he's not
afraid of a knife.
Guys his size probably never
give them a second thought.
With muscles that thick,
I'd be surprised
if most weapons didn't
just bounce right off them.
I've been training for what
seems like months now,
and I haven't gained a
single ounce of muscle.
I'm starting to wonder if
all of Akisame sensei's
weird training techniques
are really working.
Oh, there you are.
I've got some shopping to do
would you like to come along?
Huh?
You know, I said I'd
go shopping with you,
but I didn't think that meant
I'd have to drag you around
like your own personal mule.
Seriously, remind me never
to go anywhere with you again!
Oh, quit being a poor
sport. It's multi-tasking.
We're Killing two
birds with one stone.
Killing me is more like it.
One-two! One-two!
Aw, come on, Sensei,
this is so embarrassing.
How much of this
do I have to do
before I graduate
from basic training?
Graduation? But
that's impossible!
Your basic training
lasts an entire lifetime.
What?! You can't be serious.
So I'm gonna be running
these embarrassing marathons
for the rest of my life?
You don't have to run
marathons necessarily.
But you have to maintain
some kind of training routine.
Back in the old days
it was very rare
that people did any
separate muscle training.
What?
So why am I getting
the special treatment?
They sparred a lot back then.
So they really didn't
need muscle training.
Dry yourself off.
So then, sparring was
their strength training.
Sparring's a great
way to build muscle.
Mostly because it focuses
specifically on all the muscles
needed for fighting, without
adding unnecessary bulk
in places that could
slow the body down.
However, there is
definitely one drawback
to that method of training.
High risk of bodily injury.
Out of every 100 or so
disciples only a handful
ever made it through
training alive.
So how does that sound to you?
We could skip muscle
training and spar instead.
That's not a good idea.
Well, you aren't
quite a master yet.
I suppose you have plenty of
time to work on your courage.
Me a master? Yeah, why not?
You train with masters,
to become a master, right?
Can I ask you a
question, Sensei?
How come your body's not built
up like Apachai's or Sakaki's?
I keep an eye on my figure.
I'd be really curious to see how
he handles himself in a fight.
Normally, I come
here with Kensei,
but he said he had to pick
up something very important
at the book store today.
Girly mags...
So you two usually walk back and
forth between here and the dojo.
Is this part of your
training routine?
Nah. I'm just
saving on bus fare.
Let go, or you'll be sorry!
Calm down little girl,
we're just gonna ask
you some questions.
Hey! I know them...
Izumi, and Makoto!
School friends? They look
like they're in trouble.
We're trying to find a girl
that goes to your school.
Looks just like you, 'cept she's
taller and her hair' and eyes
are different, and
she's not so scrawny.
So you're looking for a girl
that wears glasses, is that it?
That's what I said!
I remember now...
Those are the same thugs that
Miu beat up the day I met her.
I've gotta do something!
There go my weak legs again.
Why is it so hard for me to work
up the courage when I need it?
Hey, that little
punk was with her.
Is that Kenichi?
Go home girls. Your
friend will be fine.
Come on!
Be careful, Kenichi.
What's he doing?
Move, old man.
I got some business
with the kid there.
Oh, is that so?
I'm afraid I don't
quite understand.
Has my disciple caused
some sort of trouble?
Watch out boys.
He's tricky...
Keep both eyes on him.
Hey, uh, dude?
Yeah, what is it?
Um, well--
What the heck you blabbin' ab--
Sorry, that's my fault.
Dislocation is an
old habit of mine.
That's some habit.
There you go,
but you should watch where
you stick that thing.
You're completey insane!
You two, get some
weapons or somethin'.
Hurry! And get the boss
while you're at it!
Yeah, right!
Now that's just rude.
I'm not completely insane.
Isn't that right, Kenichi?
Alright boys, I'm
guessin' this freak here
is like glasses-girl's old man,
and that makes him fair game!
Come on out, Boss!
Let me introduce ya!
That's the guy.
You take care of him, and
we'll deal with the runt.
Oh my. You're certainly
a big fellow, aren't you?
We're in trouble. This guy's
built like a redwood!
Looks like we got
ourselves a bonus!
We were just tryin'
to track down
that brat daughter of yours!
But seein' as how you need to
learn to keep your kid in line,
we'll start with you instead!
I hate to rain on your parade,
but I'm still a bachelor.
What, you call me for this?
He's smaller than anyone here.
Hm?
Next time make sure
he's at least your size
before you think about
wasting my time.
Ah, excuse me, if I may?
I take it that you're the
leader of these men?
We seem to have a bit
of a misunderstanding.
Whatever the problem
is, I'd rather not
have to cause any trouble
for you or your goons.
Perhaps it would be best
if we went our separate ways?
At least if we all
walk away right now,
you won't have to dirty
that fancy white suit
that you're wearing.
Yeah! You show 'im, Boss!
Oh, man, he's gonna get killed!
What did you do that for?
That's government
property paid for
with your hard
earned tax dollars.
It appears that I may
have offended you
in some way, haven't I?
Again, I'd rather not fight
you, but if that's the case,
I am willing to take back
some of what I said earlier.
Yeah, that's more like it.
Not feelin' so
cocky now, are ya?
I don't believe it.
Is he apologizing?
I take back the part about
not wanting to cause
you any trouble.
Did he really just do that?
With one finger?!
Truth is I don't care much
for people like you.
You're overbearing, rude
and always trying
to intimidate people.
So I've decided it's about
time to give you boys
a little taste of
your own medicine.
Hmph! Really? You think
you can bully me?
Kenichi...
Y-Yes?
I'll give you a quick
jujitsu demonstration.
Keep your eyes open, and
try to learn something!
You got it.
Should you find yourself
in a situation
where your opponent is
bigger than you are...
Shut up and fight already!
First, here's what not to do.
You should never face your
opponent directly like this,
because you'll eventually
be overpowered.
But he's not
budging! How come?
I mean it's simple physics, he
should be getting pushed back.
He's hooking his toes
into that manhole cover!
Ouch...
Wait a second! Why are
you screaming? Huh?
Okay, now I'll show you
the right way to do it.
That's it! Now I'm mad!
What you want to do is
make your opponent think
you're moving forward, when
what you're really doing
is moving sideways
into his blind spot.
Then, in an actual
jujitsu fight,
before you did anything else,
you'd attack one
of his vital points!
But that's only
a preparation move
so you can get your
opponent off balance.
Well, it certainly
seems effective!
Now, before your opponent's
punch gets up to speed,
you move a half step forward
and deflect its
power away from you.
And then...
...you throw him!
A-mazing! That was the
coolest thing I've ever seen!
I just hope you
learned something.
Oh yeah!
Let's see you deflect
some bullets, ya freak!
He's got a gun this time?!
What the heck is with this guy?
That is totally
crossing the line!
All right, that does it.
You idiots are far too
reckless for my taste.
What if you'd accidentally
hit an innocent bystander?
Come on. It's time someone
taught you some manners.
Let go of me!
Oh, and Kenichi?
Sit tight for a
moment, if you would.
This won't take long.
Let's get him!
He can't take us all!
Remind me never to get
on Sensei's bad side!
I almost feel sorry
for those thugs.
I didn't know people's
bodies could bend that way!
It's like he had some kinda'
super-human strength,
especially for
someone his size!
Well according to
him, the human body
is made up of three
different kinds of muscle:
white muscle that's good
for fast, sudden moves,
but lacks endurance,
red muscle that's got
endurance but not much power,
and in between those two
is a bit of pink muscle
that's supposed to have
both qualities combined.
They say the ratio
of the 3 muscle types
stay the same your entire life.
But ol' Akisame,
he ignored conventional wisdom
and followed his own theories.
He believed that muscle
type could be changed,
and after 20 years of bizarre
training, he had converted
all his red and white
muscle to pink.
So, while he may not
look all that strong,
what you see
is 100% muscle.
He's like a rock.
I doubt the guy has a
milligram of body fat on him.
You mean, he might even
be stronger than you?
Did I say that?
Don't be stupid, kid.
I don't do all that
freaky training,
but I'm no slouch either.
Tell you this, though,
He's one of those guys,
if I never do have to fight
him that's just fine by me.
If we ever did get into it,
one of us would wind up dead.
Maybe I should walk
you home. It's late.
You never know, they
might still be out there
waiting to catch you alone.
No, that's okay. I can manage.
And, hey, if I run into
something I can't handle,
there's always the old
"strategic withtdrawl", right?
Well, see you tomorrow.
--Bye.
--Okay then, be careful!
No way they'd expect me
to walk down the same street
where they ambushed
me last time.
Gotta stay one step ahead.
I was just about ready
to give up on you Kenichi.
You again?!
Better believe it!
An' this time I'm draggin'
your scrawny butt to Kisara!
Right. I still don't
know who that is.
But first thing's first!
Me an' my little friend here
still owe you some payback
for makin' me bleed
yesterday, don't we?
What do I do?
You should know
knives and spoons
are just worthless
hunks of metal
as long as you can avoid
being hit by them.
What's that supposed to be?
Like a butter-knife
or something?
Don't act like
you're not scared!
You were shakin' in your
boots the last time!
And your posture is pathetic.
Your vitals are wide open.
I'll show you pathetic!
And compared to Shigure,
you might as well be
moving in slow motion!
Shut your mouth, punk!
I'll cut you! You hear me?!
And your grip's bad.
I can just...
In an actual jujitsu fight,
you'd attack one
of his vital points!
But that's only
a preparation move
so you can get your
opponent off balance.
Furukawa! I just realized
that this is all your fault!
Do you have any idea
what I had to go through,
all because you pulled
that stupid knife?! Do you?!
You ever been chased
around for an hour
by a woman with a sword?!
Oh, and what about having your
skin removed a layer at a
time with a sai and a tonfa?!
Guess what--it hurts! I'm
probably gonna have nightmares
now for the rest of my life!
Oh yeah, did I mention
the ten-foot wrestler
that tried to squash me?
Or what about the guy that
pulled the gun on me?!
Not my idea of fun!
Kenichi, I'm glad
to see you're alright.
Hey, are you listening?!
Wake up! I want
you to hear this!
Besides, you can't sleep out
here, you'll catch a cold!
Apa. Apachai doesn't
know what to do!
This sounds serious.
What's the matter? Is
something troubling you?
Mm-hm. Every sparring
time with Kenichi,
Apachai can't make
his punches fold back,
then Kenichi gets
beat up for real.
Hm. I take it you
mean "hold" back.
That's definitely been a problem
for both you and Kenichi.
But, I'm certain it's
one you can overcome
with a little time and training.
Apapapapa! That's great!
Apachai will do his best!
So next time, Kenichi
won't have to end up dead!