Hey, you! Come outta there!
What the heck?
There's only one of you?
No.
There are eight of us.
You'll be fighting
our newest member,
the Eighth Fist, Valkyrie,
the Sixth Fist, Hermit,
and the Fourth Fist, Loki.
I sincerely hope your
men can handle it.
Your level of stupidity
never ceases to amaze me!
If you walk down there,
Tsuji's gonna kill you!
I've gotta go try to
square things with him!
What are you, nuts?! You've
seen him when he gets angry!
You're no match for him!
He's gonna kick your butt!
Don't throw away the win you
earned with that sneak attack!
If you go down
there, you're dead!
I don't care what
you say! I'm going!
If I turn around
right now, all I'm doing
is running away from my
problems like a coward would!
Oh, I want it all right,
kid! Really, really bad!
What are you trying to do
with those lame punches?
Bring it on!
Tsuji, you have something far
greater than 100 henchmen.
It's a rare gift. Do you have
any idea what that is?
Friends you can trust! That's
right! Two of 'em, in fact!
Hey, Kenichi.
What is it?
That friend of
yours, the boxer guy?
I heard that Ragnarok's giving
him a farewell beatdown soon.
But when?!
I don't know the exact
date, but Kisara will be there
along with a witness from
the Eight Deadly Fists.
One of the
Eight Deadly Fists? Who?
The Sixth Fist, the guy
who's also known as Hermit!
I'd watch out for him.
He's bad news.
See ya 'round kid.
Did he say "Hermit?"
Yeah. Do you know him, Niijima?
Uh-Huh.
I saw him fight a whole gang;
it was pretty intense.
Only three of the
Eight Fists fought,
but they took down 50
men in like 30 seconds!
Master Koetsuji!
I've decided! Starting
today, I want to begin
training for the
advanced techniques!
I don't know what happened,
but that look in your eyes
is completely different
from the one this morning.
So, shall we get started then?
Yes!
In any case, you
need to be careful!
Listen, a reliable source told
me that Ragnarok's planning
to punish you for
walking out on them,
and they're not gonna
go easy on you!
Yeah? So what?
Come on, man, you've
gotta take this seriously!
This isn't some joke
you can just laugh off!
It doesn't matter how careful I
am, there's no way to avoid it.
Kenichi, look!
What's that?
Niijima's been passing
these around the school!
Nice shot.
This is totally photoshopped!
How many of these has he
managed to hand out so far?!
Unfortunately, they're
all over the place.
What does that idiot
think he's doing
spreading stupid
rumors like this?
Extra! Extra! Get ya newspapers!
You!
He ran away!
Come back here, you freak!
Man! How the hell does that
guy always get away?!
Woo! Nice footwork!
Anyway, try to keep a low
profile for a while, okay?
And here. Take this.
This is my cell phone number.
If they corner you
somewhere, give me a call
and I'll be right over!
Promise me, okay?
Aw, it's like we're
dating or something!
Am I blushing?
You know, to tell
ya the truth, babe,
I would rather have your
number on my speed dial.
Will you focus?!
It's time.
All right, now we
shall undertake
some real technique training!
Yes, master!!
How 'bout we start
with some karate.
Take a shot!
Right!
First off, you must deflect your
opponent's attack downward,
then using the same hand,
you're gonna strike upwards
at his chin with your wrist.
This allows you stop an
opponent with only one hand.
From here on, the
odds are pretty good
you're gonna find
yourself fighting alone
against more than one
opponent at a time.
If you have to use both hands
to handle each of 'em,
you'll never be able to deal
with them all. Got that?
And now it's Apachai's turn!
I'm ready, master!
Sorry if I kill you.
I try and try, but you always
end up dead after the lesson.
Apapa.
Someone save me! Help! Help!
This really is a dangerous
move, so I'll take your place
as his sparring partner.
Now pay close attention!
Let's go, Apachai!
Apapapapapapa!
Reverse elbow.
Whoa, close one. If that
had been Kenichi,
that would have snapped his neck
in two like a chicken bone.
Uh, reverse elbow?
Yep, that's what
it's called kid.
Yes. It's an extremely
advanced technique.
All right, now let me show
you something as well.
Okay, first,
attack your opponent
with a chop.
When your opponent's open,
you attack his side.
Twist the opponent's
hand around,
then strike his back
and neck area,
while attacking with your knee!
Then throw him,
like so!
Then if you can manage to
pin him down using your leg,
like so.
Now, use your hand
to finish him off.
It's a very useful combination
attack that gives you
four opportunities to
deliver a finishing blow
to your enemy, if
it's executed properly.
Eeeeeeeeeeee!
I pity the guy who's
on the receiving end!
Ah, I've never seen
Akisame so worked up.
Now it's my turn.
Oh, please, master, I just don't
think I can handle anymore!
Please have mercy!
Well, it's true that these
techniques are usually
considered rather advanced for
a disciple of your skill level.
Why don't Shigure and I
hold off on our training
til you've practiced
what you've learned?
As usual. Left out again.
The techniques that
Master Sakaki and the others
have shown me are too hard!
I don't know if I can remember
all the moves! I don't
have the skill!
You needn't worry.
Skill doesn't matter.
You just need to analyze
each technique step by step.
How does he do that
mind reading thing?!
And we'll get things started
by having you practice
each of these moves
1,000 times.
No way! 1,000 times?!
Oh, Akisame, you have a patient
waiting for you at the clinic.
Oh, yes, I forgot. Your
friend Takeda is scheduled
for another check up
with me this afternoon.
I might be a little while,
so I'll just leave Kenichi
in your capable hands, is
that okay with you, fellas?
Yup.
You got it.
Darn it! I told Takeda
to keep a low profile!
Everything looks okay.
Yeah. It feels fine.
So, doc...
Something's bothering
you, isn't it?
I haven't even said anything.
There's no getting
past this guy.
Yeah. I've been thinking,
I've worked so hard to heal
and train my body, and in
the end it's all for nothing.
Makes you wonder what the
point of martial arts really is.
There's a saying: "Humans
are born, then they die,
thus, is it better not
to have been born at all?"
I used to wonder
the same thing.
But you have to ask yourself:
What can I accomplish
during that short
period of life?
I don't care if I
ruin my body boxing!
I have no regrets about that!
But if Ragnarok cripples me...
Don't go into a fight
assuming that you'll lose.
No one has ever
escaped Rangnarok.
Those guys are out to kill me.
If you knew how dangerous
they were, you wouldn't be
acting so casual about it!
Really?
Come with me.
There's something I
think you should see.
What's this place?
Too slow!
Is he gonna be alright?!
How many times do
I gotta tell ya'?!
You have to direct the oncoming
blow downward and then use
the same move to strike
at the opponent's chin!
This is just the
first technique!
If you don't wanna learn,
we can just forget about it!
Please continue, Master Sakaki!
I have to master this technique
as quickly as possible!
Hm. All right, now you're
talkin' like a true disciple.
Get up!
Right!
You see, he's chosen
to undertake this severe
training regimen to learn how
to be able to protect you.
Ah! Attack before your opponent!
Come on, faster!
Kenichi isn't
like you, Takeda.
He has absolutely
no natural aptitude
for the martial arts at all.
But, also unlike you, he
doesn't give up or give in.
Please continue!
Alright
You see what I'm talking about?
You're not as alone
as you might think.
And as long as Kenichi is
willing to go the distance,
don't you think you owe it to
him to hang in there yourself?
You know, he's
an interesting guy,
our young Kenichi.
He comes off as cowardly,
but then he'll surprise you
by turning around and doing
something amazingly brave.
Honoka!
He seems as timid as a mouse,
but then he'll suddenly
turn around and take a stand.
I've decided! Starting
today, I want to begin
training for the
advanced techniques!
At first I didn't know what
to make of him, but now I think
I've finally figured out
what makes him tick.
And? Just what would that be?
Well, simply put,
Kenichi Shirahama...
Too slow!
...will do anything, dare
anything, even risk his life,
to protect the lives of
the people he cares about.
Now I think you got it.
Apapapapapapapa!
Apa!
You mean, I'm not dead?
How'd I make it out alive?!
Yeah, I thought so,
he's completely delirious.
Apaaaa!
Hey! Why did you fold over
a page in my favorite book?
Use a bookmark!
One more.
A hot spring?! Miu, Shigure,
how would you like me
to wash your backs for you?
Isn't that part of a
loyal disciple's duty?
Okay.
Enough's enough.
So you're back in the real
world now, little man?
Hey, Kenichi!
Kenichi...
Takeda's leaving, he asked
me to tell you good-bye.
What? I didn't even
know he was here.
Takeda, wait!
Oh, hey, Kenichi! They
finally giving you a break?
What? You mean you
were watching me?
Hey, next time you're
planning to stop by
let me know or something.
Actually it was my
idea to bring him here.
Ah, I thought I told you to
lay low for a little while--
what are you doing here?
You've gotta be more careful!
It couldn't be helped.
He had an appointment
for a physical at the
bone clinic today.
Yeah, I get it, but still...
Wait a sec! What about my cell
phone number, have you
programmed it into your
speed dial like I asked you to?
Uh, well...
Come on! Okay, wise guy,
hand it over, now!
Seriously. What the
hell do I have to do
to get you to start
listening to me?
Gimme a break!
Here! It's programmed
and ready to go!
Sweet! I'm finally on
somebody's speed dial!
Is this cool or what?
Right! So if anything happens,
remember to call me
right away, got it?
Promise me, will ya?
Yeah, alright.
Hey, thanks for
everything Kenichi, bye.
Watch your back and
avoid any dark alleys!
You're not as
alone as you think.
And as long as Kenichi is
willing to go the distance,
don't you think you owe it to
him to hang in there yourself?
Way to go, kid! I didn't
know you had a cell!
Check mine out, it's
the latest model!
Man, that is cool!
Apachai want to have a
cell phone too! Buy me one!
Please?
We don't have that kind
of extra money right now.
Now, now.
Here.
Knock yourself out
with this mobile phone.
Apa!
You can't just tear the
telephone cord out of the wall!
Wanna trade?
No way!
You can come out.
I know someone's there!
Hm! Well, it's Takeda.
Ah! Hey gorgeous,
long time no see.
The name is Kisara,
you gutless traitor.
What a loser! C'mon,
guys, let's get him!
Hold on. Let me handle it.
Ukita...
That's how it is?
What's wrong?
Are you gonna call your
mommy to come and save you?
I know I promised, Kenichi,
but I gotta do this on my own.
Y' know what?
You've been a weirdo for
as long as I've known you.
After a fight, I've seen you
praise your opponent
to comfort him.
Hey, it was a good
effort, cheer up!
And you'd chew me out
if I fought unfairly.
You had that guy beat
from the start,
there was no need
to fight dirty.
Oh, sure. They liked to call
us the "Take-Down Trio."
But, deep down you
were a sportsman.
'N we were a couple a thugs.
We had no code of honor.
Man! How I hated your guts!
Heh. That's a shame,
'cause y'know, I never hated
you for a single moment.
Ukita! What are you doing?!
What's wrong with you?!
As of right now, I,
Ukita the Thrower,
officially resign from Ragnarok!
So, do any of you ladies
got a problem with that?
Ukita, thank you.
Wha-- idiot! I'm not
doing this for you!
I wanna go back and
do real judo again,
like I did before I was
a useless delinquent!
'Course, I'm sure
you know that no one
has ever left the gang.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know,
no one has ever successfully
left Ragnarok and managed
to walk away whole.
That was what you were
gonna say, wasn't it?
I know we'll take a pounding,
but at least we can
show them what we're made of!
If I gotta go, I'm
takin' them with me!
I'm afraid that I can't go
along with your little plan.
Say what?
You shouldn't go into a
fight assuming you'll lose.
By Akisame.
Man. What is it
with guys like you,
do you just live to
piss other people off?
Aw, male bonding.
That is so touching.
Ukita, since you asked for
it, I'm going to dish out
your punishment for
betraying us right now.
Boys, get 'em!
It's Takeda! Sweet,
he actually called me!
Hello! Give Apachai money
and he teach you how to kill!
Apachai, give it!
Funny, no one is answering.
Hand it over already!
Hey, Takeda, is there
something wrong?
Is everything okay, man?
What's going on? I can't
make anything out!
Here.
Ah, I see, it would seem that
your friend accidentally
hit the speed dial function.
It sounds like he's right in
the middle of big mob of people.
It sounds to me like he's
in the middle of a fight!
Hello! Apachai here!
Sh!
Apa.
Takeda... we'll kill you...
Ukita...
you are done for... yes.
Uh! I knew it!
Hey! Apachai says hello!
Do you think he heard me?
What the hell's your problem?!
Don't you see
they're in trouble?!
Apaaa.
Wait, we may be
able to help him.
--Huh?
--Apa?
Everyone hold still.
Apapapapapa...
I hear what sounds
like a train passing by
on an overpass
in the background.
Miu! Bring me your student
directory and a city map now!
What are you gonna do with that?
I'm going to check possible
routes he might have taken home
from Ryozanpaku and see if they
intersect any train overpasses.
Ah! That's brilliant, Kensei,
I'll get 'em right away!
Oh, I get it now!
Awesome! I didn't
know you had it in ya!
He didn't know I had it in me?
What kind of idiot
does he think I am?
That hurts!
One, two, three, four...
And the ol' "lethal left"!
Ah, the Puncher...
And they called you that even
when you were only using
your right hand didn't they?
What a pity.
Seems like such a shame
to destroy a fighter like you.
You know, I heard about you.
I guess you expect me
to congratulate you
on your promotion, huh?
The Eighth Fist of Ragnarok,
Kisara Nanjo.
She's a formidable opponent,
but I have no intention
of being defeated.
No way in hell.
I know who he's up against.
But not for long.
I'll be seeing you and your
buddy Takeda soon enough
and we'll settle things
once and for all.
Why?! Why didn't he call
me?! Hang on, Takeda!
You there!
Forget about Kenichi.
I'll be your opponent!
Who's this top-heavy bimbo?
Get lost, you dairy cow.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
Dairy Cow?
You asked for it.
I won't cut you any slack
if I see you get in my way.
Get ready to fight!
Dairy cow?
Did you just call
me a dairy cow?
Ohhhh! Now I'm really mad!
You're gonna pay for that!