It was perfect!
I finally got to take Miu out
on a date! Just the two of us!
But Niijima showed up and
the day started to go wrong.
And then those Ragnarok
guys decided to attack me.
Jeez, how did this happen?
Are you people insane?
You used Miu-san as bait so
those thugs would attack me
and I'd have to fight them?!
It's no different
from the lioness
who throws her cubs from the
cliff to make them stronger.
Perhaps cruel but
it's "tough love".
Well, I don't need
love like that, okay!
Hey, whether you like it or not,
those bullies are
comin' for you.
That's right. Remember the enemy
will never stop attacking you.
I get that. But you don't
have to help 'em do it.
Tell me, son.
Have you already decided you're
never going to run away?
Well, sort of...
If that's true, you must
prepare yourself to fight!
Why won't this stupid
thing go straight?!
How did she do that?
Miu is so awesome!
Whoa, yes!
No matter how cute
she is in her uniform,
nothing compares
to a leotard!
Thank you, stupid wheelbarrow,
for steering me
toward this window!
And, man! She's an
amazing gymnast, too!
And flexible!
I've never seen anybody move
like that! Have you, Takashima?
She's-- she's okay.
I'm sure she's just
eating this up.
Just because she's
cute and blonde
and can do a back flip into
splits, everybody loves her.
Oops! What moron would leave
a pin lying around like this?
I nearly tripped over it
and broke my neck.
Oh, crud! I kicked it too hard!
Look out!
--Are you okay?
--I was so scared!
That was amazing!
Why couldn't it have hit her?!
Miu is amazing at
anything she does.
It's like she doesn't
even have to try.
She's gotta be some
kind of genius.
But look at me, I
can't do anything
without six weeks of
intensive training first.
So why me?
Do you know what a punch that
fast could do to a human face?
Nooo!
Why does it have to be my face?
I really like my face!
So that's the jist of it.
To keep my face, I'll be staying
at the dojo on the weekends.
What does that even
mean, keep your face?
Is this a 'respect' thing?
Explain yourself!
Well, then, take
care, everyone.
No, please, Kenichi!
They're only going to hurt
you, I know they will!
Please don't leave us!
This is just silly.
I have to become strong as
soon as possible, otherwise I--
...simply won't have a chance.
According to them.
So, there's no option.
Of course there's an option!
It's sit your butt down!
Right now!
Wait, Kenichi!
Alright, Honoka. I guess
I'll see you on Monday.
Did you see his eyes?! That
boy has been brainwashed!
This supposed dojo
must be one of those
doomsday cults I've read
about where they lure you in
with the promise of
karate but who knows
what they're going to do?!
We have to do something
to save him, Saori!
Please, calm down, dear.
Hey, Dad! Look what I've got!
Yes? What now? Go on.
I snuck into Kenichi's room
and copied the map of the
dojo he's been going to!
Brilliant! Our daughter
is a certified genius!
Quick, calm, and cool,
just like her old man.
Rise, Sebastian!
Well, I'm going for a walk
and might drop by
the dojo to say hello.
With your gun?
Yeah, way to go, Dad!
You told me that you had
to work this weekend.
Oh, dear, work is nothing
compared to my family.
But don't worry, I
already called my boss
and told him I was
undergoing emergency surgery.
Hurry up, Dad, let's get going!
I'll return home with our son
in no time, safe and sound.
What? Dad's not, coming?
Once your father calmed down,
he realized he had a very
important meeting to go to.
Here, take this with
you to the dojo.
And please try to
be polite to them.
One question, do they sell such
a thing as a paralyzing drug?
Now, being polite does
not mean drugging them.
She's definitely her
father's daughter.
I know it seems strange,
but I feel like we
can trust this dojo.
If it was actually dangerous,
then I'm sure Kenichi
would have left by now.
That's not my take on it.
I think he wants to leave,
but they've said they'll
kill him if he does.
But I'll find out one
way or the other.
Just be careful.
Roger!
Nobody thought that I would
last for more than three days,
but here I am!
I've endured their training
now for a whole month!
Willpower!
So are you ready to practice?
Sure am! Let's do it!
Well, some might think I've
only held on for this long
so I could be close to her.
There are a few peculiar
things I've noticed
while getting used to the dojo.
Apa!
Apa! Apa!
These masters never go
a day without training.
They never stop...
I'm starting to wonder if
they even sleep at night.
Hey, Shigure.
Are you going somewhere?
Um, no.
Some people will just
mysteriously disappear
and not return for a few days.
Stay sharp, Miu.
Good morning, Sensei.
It's a nice day, huh?
And there are a few people
that I just can't figure out
no matter how hard I try.
But time after time, this
man has proven himself
to be the most caring and
empathetic of them all.
Alright, Kenichi, it's about
time for some serious training.
At least that's what I thought.
Um, Akisame sensei...
What is this thing?
This device is a
stretching machine
based on my own design.
I call it the
Great Leg Divide.
There.
I'd love to teach you
how to fight right away,
but first we need
to loosen you up.
It's a basic fact,
flexibility is just as crucial
to a martial artist
as his strength.
A stiff body is
restricted within itself.
And frankly, I've
seen metal pipes
with more flexibility than you.
To accelerate your flexibility,
we'll keep you strapped
in for about a day.
Go ahead, Miu, give him a push.
Sure!
I don't believe this...
But I guess it's a little
late to question him.
We'll start nice and slow...
That's too much,
I can't take it!
Oh? If it becomes unbearable,
then call out Ge...
This will be our safety
signal to let you out.
But the machine is designed
so you can't get out
until your legs are fully split.
What was the signal?!
You said it quiet so I
couldn't hear, didn't you?!
What was it?!
Alright, Miu, don't let up no
matter how much he screams.
No problem!
After this you'll be
able to split your legs
a full 180 degrees.
And it should only
take 16 hours or so.
If it starts to hurt too
much, just let me know,
and I'll ease up on it.
What do-- What do
you mean if it starts?!
More, more!
There you go, you got it!
Tres bien!
Look at you!
I'm surprised at how
flexible you are.
Torture and ecstasy, no
wonder Kenichi's confused.
At this rate you can make
180 degrees in just 13 hours!
How terrible! Those
creeps have my brother
strapped into some kind of
medieval torture device!
I've gotta stop 'em!
Just a little farther.
No no no no, yes yes!
Please don't stop!
Wow...
Not bad.
Let's try and take it
all the way in one move.
Ge- Geronimo!
You leave my brother alone!
Whoops...
I-I accidentally slipped, sorry.
Am I hearing things or did
he just shout Geronimo?
That didn't take long.
I'm just surprised he
heard the safety signal.
Really? The safety
word was Geronimo?
It's a miracle!
Kenichi!
Honoka?!
Don't touch, it hurts too much!
Akisame! I think
I broke Kenichi!
He should have listened
to me. Oh, well.
This is what he gets for not
taking the full 16 hours.
There!
What'd you do that for?!
What? It's not still
hurting, is it?
Hey! How about that!
I have a bonesetter's
clinic in the back.
Kensei has an acupuncture
station there as well.
I'm a certified professional
when it comes to bone setting.
So no matter how many
times you get hurt,
I'll just fix you up again.
This man can break me and fix
me like some kind of toy.
What have I gotten
myself into here?
What do you think
you're doing to him?
What's this? We have a guest?
Uh, she's, my sister.
What? She's your sister?
Oh, wow! She's so adorable!
What?
Awww! You have the same eyes!
Now I get it.
Honoka, what are you doing here?
Just stay back and keep quiet!
So, you got your
nails in him, huh?
She looks just like
a little doll.
You're so cute!
Stop right there! Keep
away from my brother!
Don't you even realize?
This big-boobed wonder
has totally got you
wrapped around
her little finger!
Oh yeah?
Well, I'd like to wrap my
fingers around your neck!
She is just too precious!
I can't believe this! I thought
Kenichi was in danger,
but it's just this tramp
stringing him along.
What's with the
uh... little kid?
Apapapa?
She's Kenichi's younger sister.
Younger sister? Just how young
are we talking exactly?
Oh, no! I'm
completely surrounded!
Cutie, what's your name?
Kenichi! Time to go!
Hey, wait! Honoka!
Hurry it up!
Are big boobs really
that important to you?!
Kenichi! I'm disappointed!
Hey! Quit making
a scene, will you?
I don't know what the heck
you're talking about!
I'm here to learn
karate and that's it!
Wow, so this must
be what it's like
to have siblings,
I'm so envious.
Hey, you! Top heavy! My mom
wanted you to have this!
Top heavy? Well...
Okay, thank you.
I'm going home for today!
But don't you think I'm
giving up that easily!
I'll be back! Got it?!
Oh no you won't!
You little freak!
How sweet. I think she liked
me, she gave me a gift.
Do Apachai smells sponge cake?!
Lucky you.
What I wouldn't give to have a
cute little sister like that.
Don't you have
any siblings, Miu?
Actually, I haven't even
met your parents.
Well, I barely knew my parents,
they both passed away
when I was little.
And well, The only family I
have now is my grandfather.
What?
Uh, I've got a lot of
chores to take care of,
so I'll talk to you
later, okay? Bye.
Aaa-pa-pa.
So were you born without
a heart or did you sell it?
What?! No, no, I
had no idea, really!
Please believe me, I
never would've said that!
Oh yeah? Try
telling that to Miu.
Hey, don't say that!
Don't worry, it happened before
she can even remember.
It's the thought of memories she
doesn't have that makes her sad.
I'm a monster! What have I done?
Miu... You're so smart and
beautiful, and always smiling.
And not only are you
talented at martial arts,
but you're an amazing
gymnast as well.
But the truth is that you've
hardly been able to enjoy
a normal life because
you've been stuck here...
...in this dojo.
You've been forced to cook and
clean for these annoying men
in order to keep this absurd
dojo from falling apart!
And you never experienced
the love of your parents.
You do so much but
you receive so little.
Did he say absurd dojo?
And annoying men?
Oh, poor little Miu.
Miu has lived a rather unusual
life, to say the least.
She spent most of her childhood
traveling with her grandfather,
making pilgrimages
throughout the country.
Making pilgrimages?.
You mean she's been
studying martial arts
since she was only a child?
You got it.
Elder knew her life would be
tough without her parents,
so instead of spoiling her,
he chose to train her
for all of the difficulties
she might have to endure.
That's terrible!
How could I just assume she
was some sort of genius
and not think about
how hard she's worked?
I was too busy feeling
sorry for myself!
I've gotta find her!
Not so fast!
You're still in the
middle of training.
Oh. But!
Apachai, why don't you
take over for the day?
Alright! It's
Apachai's turn, now!
S'what you get for
calling us annoying.
I'm back. Hello.
Welcome home, Shigure.
You're back sooner than usual.
It's none of my business,
but I can't help but wonder--
So...
The kid still alive-ish?
Who? Oh. Yes,
he's still kicking.
He probably wishes he
was dead, but he's alive.
Oh.
Not the lens!
Apa.
Hey! It's Shigure!
Hm... He's not dead after all.
Hey! Apachai! I'm like jelly!
Kenichi! I don't think
bodies move like that!
--You jelly-ized me!
--Oh no, that's scaring me!
So, Shigure. Are you
concerned about Kenichi?
No.
I really should be grateful to
Kenichi. His arrival has somehow
managed to lift everyone's
spirits around here,
even Shigure's.
R-really?
You made all of this
by yourself, Miu?
That's great!
Stop it! Flattery won't
get you any extra food.
Here! Hope your hungry.
Um, yeah. Thank you so much!
But, that's not fair.
You know, come to think
of it, where's Shigure?
I don't know why, but Shigure
prefers to eat by herself.
She usually eats
up in the attic.
She's kind of
strange, isn't she?
Speak for yourself, Kenichi,
is that how you
always eat your food?
You're hiding it.
Well, I...
I guess I've just
seen a few too many
of those old kung fu
movies, y'know?
But master!
They'd always say that eating
was also part of the training!
So stay back.
Relax. You can rest assured!
We would never do
such an unseemly thing.
Ah, thank god.
I think it's a great idea!
Now you try to take my food!
It's all part of the training!
Only the truly fit
are truly hungry!
Apa-pa-pa-papa!
Hey, hey, everybody!
Mind your manners and
save some for your elder!
Oh, Grandpa!
No! You ate all my dinner!
Not, a, bite.
And that was Miu's
homecooked meal, too...
It's just not fair!
And now I have to sleep
on an empty stomach!
How am I supposed
to train like this?!
And on top of it all,
I have to sleep on the
floor of the dojo by myself!
Sleep tight and pleasant dreams!
What?! We're sharing
a bed together?
Of course. That's
not a problem, is it?
No, not at all!
I don't mind the slightest
bit, I promise!
Why don't we make
ourselves comfortable.
That's what I was hoping for,
but it'll never happen.
This is reality.
But why can't it collide
with fantasy for once?
Pst!
Miu?!
What does she--
Here's my chance to collide!
Hello, Miu.
What?
Huh?
Hey, is she trying
to mess with my head?
What...
What the heck is going on?
Ta-da!
Akisame told me to
make sure you got fed
and not to let anyone else know.
He doesn't want you doing any
training on an empty stomach.
Wow! Thank you!
Y'know, that guy, he's
actually pretty decent, huh?
That goes for everyone else too,
though it might not
always seem like it.
They aren't very...
...adept with social skills so
they're a little off sometimes.
Here.
--Thanks.
--Sure.
Uh, Miu, you know I'm
really sorry about earlier.
Oh, it's nothing
to apologize for.
Even though I never really
got to know my parents,
everyone here is my family.
And look up.
How can I be sad with that view?
It's almost like I
can touch the moon!
Right, I know!
I think this is my favorite
place in the whole wide world.
I've always dreamed of
bringing a friend up here.
Someone to just sit here and
watch the stars with me.
Honoka! Honoka!
Welcome home, Dad...
What's going on?
Tell me! What's
happening at the dojo?
It's an evil cult isn't it?
No, it's just that big busty--
What do you mean?
Who's busted? Kenichi?
Huh?
Well then, I guess your
dream came true after all.
You're right!
And it's just like I
hoped it would be.
So tell me what your dream is.
Well, it sounds kind of silly,
but, my long-term dream
is to someday become a
novelist and win the Pulitzer.
But, my future seems to be
headed off in a different
direction than I expected.
No, I'm sure you can!
How about you?
Do you have any big
plans for the future?
What?
Hey, that's a secret!
Oh come on! Tell me!
You can't do that, now I
have to know! Spill it!
Why is it such a secret?
It just is, okay?
That's really not
fair, you know!
"My dream for the future is...
Huh?
...to one day get married and
have a big, beautiful wedding."
Signed Miu Furinji,
Class 1-D, 8th grade.
Gimme that!
Aw! That wasn't
very nice, Shigure!
Well, that's kind of
a relief to hear.
It's good to know at least
Miu's dreams are normal.
Kenichi, I'm gonna go
back in from the other side.
If my grandfather
catches us together,
he'll kill you and use
you as a punching bag.
Huh?
I'm not joking.
Wait, Kenichi?
What is it?!
Hurry up and tell me.
I kinda don't feel
like dying tonight.
I hope we can stay good friends
for a very long time, k?
You mean always?
Yeah, forever!
So does that mean that we'll
always just be friends
no matter what?
Yeah, we'll always
be good friends.
You know, I think
she just told me
I'll never have a shot
at being her boyfriend.
Well, I think I can live
with that, for now.
The Ragnarok gang is after me
and I still don't have the
strength to take them on!
I'm just like this flower,
I'll never bloom!
Quit crying. If you give
a plant water it'll grow.
We just have to
give you something
a little more
specific than water.
What do you have to give me?
Rigorous, painful, nonstop
training of course!
But if you give a flower
too much water, it'll spoil!
So maybe too much training
will spoil me too!
What? Did you say
I'm already spoiled?
Y'know, you might be the master,
but there are some things
you really shouldn't say.