Take this!
It's over.
What the hell?!
I'm not quitting 'til you leave.
I understand you
have your pride,
but I have my principals!
Who is this kid?
So even if I pound
you into the ground,
you won't fight just
'cause I'm a "girl".
Right. I won't raise my
hand against a woman!
Are you kidding me?
That's stupid!
Why don't you just get out of
my way and I'll let you live!
That's not gonna happen!
Not until Miu's
performance is over.
I won't let you through,
no matter what!
Hold on. Are you in love
with that cow or something?
No, no, it's not like I'm
in love with her or want
to marry her or date her
or anything like that!
But I, I guess you
could say that,
I have a crush on her.
Wow. That must've hurt.
Aw, hell! There's
something about this joker
that makes my brain
hurt! Let's go!
Huh? But are you sure?
Didn't you want to
confront Furinji?
This guy's stupidity took
all the fight out of me.
I'll do it some other time.
Huh?
So, that kid.
His name's Kenichi Shirahama,
is that right?
Yeah. I understand he's
in Class 1-E at school.
Well, I'll be.
My secret alien powers allow
me to melt into the wall
and remain unseen
and undetected!
Hm. What a strange kid.
At least he's not boring.
Well, at least they're leaving.
Miu has put her heart
and soul into that show!
I couldn't let them ruin it!
Of course, this means
that the kissing scene
between Romeo and Juliet
is gonna happen, after all.
Aw, man. What the heck
is the matter with me?
I mean, I really can't stop
them if Tanimoto and Miu
want to be a couple.
He's a moron! He's
such a complete idiot!
It's heartbreaking!
Oh, happy dagger!
This is, thy sheath!
Wonderful!
I'm impressed.
The freshman were great!
You want a hanky?
No I don't. I was just blinded
by the spotlight, that's all!
Hey.
Just shut up! I am not cryin'!
I'm not talking about that.
Apachai's missing.
He's gone, see?
What a pain. He's never
been to school, so he probably
got curious and decided
to go exploring.
We shouldn't have
taken our eyes off him.
I'll go look for him.
Askin' for trouble...
Who's that?
A pro wrestler?
Man, this school's bigger
than I thought it'd be.
Still, a guy his size oughtta
be pretty conspicuous.
Apapapow!
Ah, there he is.
Apapapapa!
He's fast!
He's huge!
Go! Apachai!
One more basket and we win!
Are you sure that
overgrown monster
is a student at your school?
Yeah, he's one of those
exchange students
from some other country.
You've got to hurry,
we're nearly out of time!
Awoo!
No don't Apachai, hold on!
That's the wrong basket!
Just when it looked like
my pathetic little team
was going to win its
very first match!
No, we're toast, man!
That guy.
I swear can make friends
with anyone he meets.
Apapapapa!
We did it!
Yeah, baby!
Our first win!
Heh. Hey there,
Apachai! Let's go!
Oh, look, it's Sakaki!
I have to get going!
Remember guys,
think like the ball!
That way you can never lose!
Thank you, sir!
Don't worry!
I know you can win
again, even without me!
Oh, yeah!
After that game the Koryo
High School basketball team
became one of the most
successful in the country
and even competed in the
national championship.
And the legend of the
mysterious giant named Apachai
would be passed down
for years to come.
Great performance, Miu.
Thanks for coming
to see me, you guys!
I really appreciate it!
Wow, nice dress.
I've never been
so nervous before.
I couldn't have gotten through
it if it hadn't
been for Tanimoto.
What's that?
Oh hey, Miu, and are these
some friends of yours?
Huh? Oh, right.
This is my family.
A pleasure to meet
you all. I'm Tanimoto.
Congratulations on your
brilliant performance, sir.
Though I think it's
a terrible shame.
It would've been perfect if you
actually enjoyed performing.
Like I said, it's a shame.
Oh, Tanimoto!
Please accept these!
Oh, thank you!
Aren't these cosmos?
My sister just
loves these flowers!
Well, then I guess
we'll see you at home.
Sure!
This sucks. I bet
the play's over by now!
She'll hate me! It's over.
Why do I always manage to
screw things up like this?
Hey! What's the matter?
Why did you do that
to the flowers?
So you saw me.
I hate flowers,
because they fade
and die too quickly.
What's going on?
He's acting like a
completely different person!
I hate acting almost
as much as flowers.
What? Then why'd you
join the Drama Club?
Ha! For practice in
the art of deception.
I have to be able to play the
role of the model student,
the class idol,
the teachers' pet.
In order to rule, you need to be
able to win people's sympathy.
You're the same way.
I bet you get tired playing
the champion of justice.
Acting doesn't really suit you.
But I...
It's very annoying,
the way your heroics have
made you so popular.
You see, this high school
is my proving ground.
Stay out of my way.
Your "defender of
the weak" act seems
to have taken a little bit
of a hit lately, hasn't it?
And it looks as if the lovely
and popular Miu Furinji's heart
will soon be all mine,
Sorry but I don't understand
what you're talking about!
This is just me! I'm not acting!
Don't lie to me!
Everybody is playing a
role, they're all liars!
I don't know what's going on,
but I told you, I'm not acting.
I'll teach that self
righteous fool.
Oh, hey Miu!
Oh, sure, now you show up,
after missing the performance
I've been slaving over for days!
She totally hates me!
Aw man, Tanimoto was right!
He's already captured her heart!
I'm sorry.
Just kidding!
I know you got into
a fight with Kisara
in order to protect the play.
And I want you to
know I appreciate it.
Oh, dear! Look at
your poor face!
Does it hurt alot?
Well, no.
Wait, I don't get it.
How'd you know I had
a run-in with Ragnarok?
Oh, well, Niijima
told me all about it.
Ah, well, I guess I can't
be evil all the time.
Miu's performance was
pretty darn good, wasn't it?
Mm-hm.
Apachai thought the play was
kinda hard to understand.
Now that we've picked up
Miu's favorite dessert,
let's get home, have
some tea, and relax.
Who are those
scary-looking characters?
Okay, just stay cool and
don't make eye contact.
Hey! There's Kenichi and Miu!
What the crap?
It'll take them twice as
long to get home that way!
Nice move, Kenichi! Way to go!
Hey! Kenich--
Now, now, let's
just head on back
and leave those kids alone.
There's no way I could do that!
Even if it's just acting, a girl
has to draw a line somewhere.
Besides, it would
be too embarrassing!
Huh?! What?!
You and Tanimoto didn't--
You mean the big kissing
scene in the play...
...it never happened?
Yay!
Woo-hoo!
Hey, there's something I've
been meaning to ask you.
Is that alright?
That little badge.
Is it very special to you?
Yin and Yang! Yin and Yang!
Uh, what, this thing? I guess.
You know that represents
the Yin and the Yang, right?
They're part of the ancient
Daoist philosophy in China.
Oh, I always wondered
what it was.
I picked it up at a candy
store a long time ago.
I traded a kitty pin for it.
I was just a little kid
back then, so I don't
remember much about it.
But I really haven't
taken it off since then.
Ah, it's pretty cool.
Why? Does it mean
something special?
Well, to put it simply,
the ancient Daoist masters
believed the universe was
composed of a balance between
two basic forces,
the Yin and the Yang.
The Yang meant light,
positive force, justice, day,
Yin was darkness, negative
force, evil, night.
Something like that, anyway.
Oh, wait a sec. Why is
there a small white circle
in the black, and a
black one in the white?
You just noticed something
very important.
It means that the deepest
darkness contains an element
of light, and the brightest
light also contains
an element of darkness.
Nothing in the universe
is without flaw and
everything that exists
is a part of everything else.
I see. It's kinda like
Niijima, sometimes I'd swear
he's pure evil. Then he'll turn
around and do something nice.
Yin and yang. Which
one are you Tanimoto?
C'mon Kensei,
what are you doin'?
Let's go!
Yeah.
Hold on, I want to see if
they're going to kiss or not.
Who are you?
Get down!
Who is this guy?
I'm Hermit.
You're Hermit?!
The Sixth Deadly
Fist of Ragnarok?
You're the one who
attacked Niijima!
He's had some serious
training! Be careful!
Ha!
Kenichi, no!
That hurt!
You're pretty tough.
You should answer me
while you can still talk.
What's the name
of your master?
Is it Sogetsu Ma?
No, it's not! One of my
masters is named Ma,
but his first name
isn't Sogetsu!
My master's name is Kensei Ma!
Miu! What's happening?
One of the Eight Deadly Fists
attacked Kenichi!
It's true! I see them!
Look, they're on
top of that bus!
He caught me off guard and
I couldn't react in time!
What are we gonna do?
Kenichi isn't ready to fight an
opponent of his caliber yet!
It's just a kid's
playground squabble!
I'm sure that he'll come
home when he's hungry!
Well, we should really get
back home and have our tea!
Does two guys fighting on a bus
look like a squabble to you?!
Now, take it easy Miu.
Everything will turn
out just fine.
I'm sure those two will
keep an eye on him.
Well, well, worried about your
little disciple after all!
Don't forget that as
masters we can't interfere!
You moron, this has nothin' to
do with Kenichi's fight, okay!
I just had a sudden urge
to run a marathon and to do
it the fastest speed
I could possibly do it!
You're the worst liar
I've met in my life.
How come you're not chasing
them on your motorcycle?
Are you kidding me,
even if I could get that
piece of junk started, it takes
forever to get warmed up,
it's older than I am!
When I first saw you
fight, I could've sworn
I saw the style of my master
Sogetsu Ma in your own!
But it would seem
I made a mistake.
Why are you doing this? Is
this an order from Ragnarok?
Why would you risk your life
to do something this crazy?
I do it because I
find you annoying.
You, with that pure,
noble look in your eye!
And your naïve faith
that there can ever
be justice in this world!
On the other hand, I've
always had to play a part,
just to survive!
You, with your easy life, want
to tell me that the purpose
of fighting is for justice?
You're wrong about that!
How do you know?
Shut up! I've been playing
a role my whole life so that
I could someday rule over both
the darkness and the light!
What?! No way! You're Tanimoto!
Here he comes!
He did a flip on a moving bus?!
I had hoped to put off killing
you until you'd become
strong enough to present
a real challenge.
But now I've no choice.
Your martial arts
training is incomplete.
You may have true
masters instructing you,
but you yourself are
still an amateur.
Now you'll see,
the real power of
Chinese kung fu!
Prepare yourself!
He's good.
I've never faced an
opponent like him before.
It's like fighting one of
the masters at Ryozanpaku!
I feel like such a failure!
He's amazing!
I mean, we're on top of a bus
and it hasn't phased him--
a moving bus!
Here's a thought. Let's
get off this thing first!
Otherwise we'll both fall
off and break our necks!
What?! That was Piguaquan!
it's an incredibly
advanced technique!
Pigua-what?! I don't
know that style!
It's one of the deadliest, most
sophisticated fighting styles
in Chinese kung fu!
The fighter uses both arms
like they were whips,
his opponent doesn't even have
a chance to counter attack!
It's nearly unstoppable!
He's so powerful!
He bent that steel
cover with his hand!
How the hell did he do that?
He's been taught how to
channel his energy to his arms!
He can make his hands and arms
as hard as steel that way!
He's good! No doubt!
Sakaki!
I know, I know, a master
must never interfere
in a disciple's battles!
I can't keep this up.
Die! And take your
stinking nobility with you!
Ow! Hey!
You know its dangerous to go
for the back of the head!
What? Are you
trying to kill me?!
What's he made of?
You're the first opponent I've
ever fought who could take
that blow and not collapse!
Whatever kind of training you've
undertaken, it's been excellent!
You'd better thank your
masters because they're
the only reason
you're still alive!
Very nicely put.
Whose side are you on?!
When it comes to beat
downs, I yield to no one!
But I can tell that Hermit
is striking to kill.
I'll tell you one more time.
This has nothing
to do with Ragnarok
I want to kill you because
I can't stand you!
Ragnarok is just a way
for me to pass the time
and hone my skills!
Then when I'm ready
the entire underworld
will bow down before me!
Tell me something! Was all of
it an act or was any of it real?
'Cause I believed
you when you told me
that you and I were friends!
It was all an act! It was
a lie right from the start!
I had those guys attack
the Drama Club!
And I was the one
who took them down!
Then I went after
Miu Furinji to increase
my popularity at school!
You thought we were friends?
Don't make me laugh!
A prince must always be alone
as he fights his way to the top!
You're wrong!
What?!
That's a lie and you know it!
I don't know why you think
that way, but I do know this.
You don't really
want to be alone.
You're just saying that
to cover your real feelings.
When you asked me to help
out the Drama Club,
and after that, when you asked
me if we could be friends,
I could see it deep in your
eyes, a sad lonely light!
You had the same look in your
eyes that I used to have!
The eyes of loneliness!
You need friends, whether
you admit it or not!
I don't understand you!
Look, let's end this.
For starters ya think
we can get off this bus?
Sure.
After you!
Careful!
This guy is full
of dirty tricks, kid!
You naïve fool!
What's wrong with you?!
You tricked me again!
But your punches will lose
half their power if
we fight this closely!
Maybe so, but the
same applies to you!
But that's just an uppercut.
An opponent with
a strong neck would
be able to withstand that
blow. It's impossible for you
to put much force into the hit
when you're so
close to your enemy.
Which is just what your
opponent will be thinking.
So, he won't expect
what happens next.
Oh, man! How did you manage to
muster so much force, Master?
This form is the
source of your power.
Once your hand is
placed under his chin,
use your other hand
to strike your elbow.
The strength of two hands
is now behind the one
in contact with the chin.
And since you're already
in contact with your opponent,
he won't be able
to dodge the blow.
Take this! Master Kensei's
secret move!
Alright! I've had all
I can take of this!
Go time!
Master Sakaki, wait!
Huh?
He's right.
don't be childish.
I'm sorry Master,
but I have a feeling I have to
be the person who defeats him!
Kenichi...
It's amazing.
Our little disciple is growing
up right in front of our eyes.
Uh-huh.
Look, Kenichi, I'll treat
you to a bowl of noodles
and then you head home, okay?
I'm not leaving!
This is a personal matter
I must resolve alone.
It has nothing to do
with my disciple!
I told you, I'm not leaving!
Forget about it!
Kenichi, you're too stubborn
for your own good!
I can't guarantee your
safety in this matter!
I hope you're prepared!
As a disciple, I must
follow my master!
No matter what happens,
I won't leave your side!