We'll use that? For what?
How am I supposed to throw
this thing, it's too heavy!
So! Are you finally
ready to do something?
Yes!
Alright then, let's teach you
something worth knowing!
No way!
The Yamazuki of Bassai...
It's an ancient technique
that's rarely used in
sports karate fighting.
How perfect.
Bad news for you, those
guys are with Ragnarok.
What's Ragnarok?
Oh, nothing big,
just the most powerful
gang in the entire city.
You are in some seriously
hot water, old chum.
There's no escaping, Ragnarok.
They're probably waiting
on every street for you
and I bet they already
know where you live.
But this is what you get
for telling everybody
about your fight.
I knew you should have
kept quiet on the subject.
I see. It sounds like
you're in a bit of trouble.
What makes you say that?
Aside from the fact that
I'm gonna get my face kicked
in by a gang of vicious thugs?!
Heh. You couldn't stop bragging
about your win yesterday.
What, did you think
that'd be the end of it?
Well I didn't think I'd
have a whole gang of--
Wait a second! You
guys already knew
what was gonna happen
to me if I won that fight.
You knew that if I beat Tsukuba,
I'd have every thug
in town gunning for me!
And you didn't think that's
something I'd wanna know?
Say we had told you,
would that have prevented you
from standing up to Tsukuba?
Don't chicken out, what you need
to do is to keep on training and
getting stronger until you're
the best fighter at school.
I can be the best fighter
in the whole world
and it still won't help
me solve my problem!
Life is a battle!
You welcome the challenge!
That may be the life you
want but it's not for me!
Fine then. You tell
me what you wanna do.
I... I don't know.
Kenichi!
Tell us where he is!
Those goons are
looking for me.
Man, how did I get
myself into this mess?
I'll get him good.
I'm gonna beat him down and dunk
his head right in the toilet!
Put that little piece of
crap where he belongs!
I-I'm not really running away.
I'm not a coward, after all.
I'm just avoiding getting
into a pointless conflict...
...with a well-timed
strategic withdrawal.
Is someone there?
Are you okay?
Izumi...
How's it going?
Um...
What?
No, it's really
not a big deal.
If you've got something
to say, just say it.
Well...
Tell me, am I getting on
your nerves or something?
What? No, it's
nothing like that.
I was just wondering,
I'm a little bit curious
why someone like you would
join the Gardening Club.
It's just that...
it's not exactly a popular
choice around here.
Well, since I was a kid,
I've always been interested
in flowers and stuff.
But people used to pick on
me and give me a hard time.
They'd say 'flowers are for
girls' and they'd call me lame
but I figure to heck with them,
I'm gonna keep on doing
what I wanna do and I don't
really care what people say.
You surprise me.
I hear these rumors
about you all the time.
I had this idea that you'd
be really intimidating.
Intimidating? What kind
of rumors did you hear?
They say you're the strongest,
meanest kid in the whole school!
Right... Well you shouldn't
believe everything you hear,
especially if it comes from
that freak show Niijima--
There's my best friend
in the world!
I've been looking for you,
you aren't easy to find!
Niijima! You've been
running your mouth
telling lies about me
again, haven't you?!
Maybe I have and maybe I haven't
but what difference
does it make to you?
Just stop spreading
rumors about me okay?!
But a rumor's not a
rumor if it's the truth.
Hey, Kenichi asked you nicely.
So why don't you just leave
him alone, you big meanie!
Who asked you, four-eyes?
Niijima! You told me yourself
that you really hate
twisted information, right?
Well, I don't mind it so much,
as long as I'm the one
doing the twisting.
I've had enough of
your crap for one day.
Get out of here before your
stink kills all the plants.
But aren't you even interested
in what I have to say?
Get lost, Niijima.
Fine, be that way. But
If he knew what I know
about the gang of thugs chasing
him he'd listen alright.
I swear, that guy'll
be the death of me!
You have some really
weird friends, huh?
Take that back! That
moron is not my friend!
If you say so...
Leave me alone you freak!
Miu!
Why would you say that
to me? That's so mean!
I thought we could walk
home together after school.
But if you want me to leave...
I am so sorry.
Please don't cry!
I'll see you later okay?
Apachai's turn!
Now you dodge!
Apa!
So, how come you
no like to dodge?
We try a slow one!
Am I still alive?
So sorry about that, Kenichi.
Next time Apachai
promises to give you break.
He broke me pretty
good this time.
Stop screwing around
and get up kid!
If you lay on the
ground all day,
there won't be any time
left for us to train you.
I don't get it, these
guys are masters.
Why are they so
eager to train me?
Could it be...?
Does this...
...mean you think I could be a
great martial artist like you?
No.
Apapa!
I can't believe you
answered that in sync!
I get it! I'm awful!
I'm a loser!
I'm gonna get killed
by those thugs anyway,
I might as well end
it all right now!
No Kenichi, stop!
You know, no one beats you
at beating yourself, kid.
You've got self-defeat
down to an art.
You're gonna have to fight
and now you're scared
about it, so what?
Best thing you can do at a time
like that is punch a pole!
Punch it hard, punch those
fears square in the face!
Then when you get
some confidence back,
you punch again!
You punch that pole until
you can't punch anymore!
'Cause when the
stuff hits the fan,
your training's the one
thing you can count on!
And if... it's not enough?
Then you'll lose, but what of
it? Martial arts isn't just
about getting strong, it's about
learning to face your fears.
You do that,
and the rest is easy.
Y-Yeah but what if--
Enough with the questions...
Let's get back to
doin' something useful.
Now look. Sometimes
it doesn't matter
how mentally
prepared you are.
When the real fight comes,
you still might find
your punches aren't packing
the power you need.
Right.
If you end up in that situation,
don't feel pressured
to form a fist.
Instead of clinching up, hold
out your hand out like this.
Nice and easy.
Keep it loose like a whip
and aim for the teeth.
If I did, couldn't that end up
breaking the other guy's jaw?
Of course it could! That's how
you know you're doin' it right!
I really do want
to be stronger.
But still, I don't want to
fight anyone. I hate violence!
Punch the pole! Punch the pole!
At this rate, it seems
our young disciple
is going to have some difficulty
finishing what he's started.
Indeed.
The kid needs to suck it up
and find some courage.
Well, maybe we can help...
I brought you a towel, you
wanna take a little break?
Thanks.
That's it!
Oh yeah...
I think this is going to be fun!
Kenichi!
Oh right!
Keep punching the pole!
Why don't you and Miu go
on a little date
together this Sunday?
What?
What part of "go on a date"
don't you understand?
A-A real date?
You mean like just
the two of us?
Of course.
You bet we'll go!
All-right! Yoo-hoo!
This is grea--!
But we don't...
...have to?
Sorry it's a reflex. You
shouldn't sneak up behind me!
Yeah. Got it.
So we're still going
on the date, right?
I'm up for it if you are.
And what do you know?
I happen to have
2 free tickets to the movies!
That's very nice but--
Go on, take 'em!
You kids deserve a little fun.
Sure...
All right! She said yes!
We're goin' to the movies!
Not so fast, kid, you've
still got punchin' to do.
Right!
Punch the pole!
And we're off!
You kids have a great time now!
Come on, let's go!
Hurry up or we're
gonna miss the train!
Right!
Guess we cut it a
little close, huh?
Oh yeah...
Good thing you're so
fast, or this would be a--
OH, I'm sorry about that.
No, that's okay.
She seems pretty excited
about being on this date.
Maybe she likes me...
I'm really excited
about this date.
I've never seen a movie
in a theater before!
What? Are you serious?
She isn't into me at
all, she's just happy
about going to see a movie
at the stupid theater. Figures!
There's my best friend
in the whole world!
Man, I have been looking
for you all over town!
Hello there! How
have you been?
Come on, there are
some more open seats
--at the back of the train.
--What?
Kenichi, wait, where're
you going buddy?
Aren't you even curious
why I was looking for you?
This isn't our stop;
we're supposed to get
off at the next station.
Don't worry about it!
Wait I've got some info!
Don't you wanna hear what I
have to say? No Kenichi wait!
I feel kinda bad we
just left him like that.
He'll be alright.
Besides we're only one stop
away from where we need to be.
I figured we could walk it.
I guess walking there
wouldn't be so bad.
I'll bet you anything that
creep's waiting for me
at the next station.
This is so nice,
it's been a long time
since I've taken the day
off and gone for a walk!
So you think you can dodge
me that easily, huh, Kenichi?
Never underestimate me!
That jerk Niijima's
gonna ruin my date.
How in the world did he know
we were going to be here?
What is he some sort of
mind-reader or something?
What's wrong with you?
We better hurry and get in
there or we'll miss the show.
Well uh...
you see uh...
Man, if I can't figure out
a way to get rid of him,
this date's gonna go
from bad to worse!
Oh, we'd better hurry
or we'll be late!
Miu wait.
What?
Miu, listen.
Uh, yeah?
I'm starved! You
wanna get some food?
Huh?
I'm so hungry!
When we were walking I got
this craving for a hamburger.
What do you say we ditch
the movie and get some grub!
Oh no, but I've never
been to the movies,
and we've got
these free tickets...
I said I'm hungry!
I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
Alright, fine! I get it!
We can go get some food, just
don't eat the tickets, okay?
I know they'll be here soon.
Welcome to the Burger Palace!
What can I get for you?
Let's see... well...
Geez, there are so many options
I don't know what to get
but I guess I'll have the spicy
chili burger and some fries.
No just give me the
master hotdog. No, the burger..
Come on, it's not like
this is your first time
going to a fast-food
place, right?
Actually, I don't get
out to eat very often
to tell you the truth.
Huh. I guess Miu's got it
pretty tough over there.
Then I'm gonna make
sure this is the best day
she's ever had
in her entire life!
Starting now, we're gonna
have a great time!
I think my mouth is on fire!
Meow...
Uh-oh! I'm gonna get you, kitty!
Here, kitty-kitty-kitty!
He should've been here by now,
where in the heck
could that guy be?
Hey! You're friends with
that weak-kneed punk,
Kenichi, aren't you?
Huh?
Do yourself a favor and
tell me where to find him!
Here.
Oh, thanks.
Yep. This sure has
been a lotta fun!
I've really had a nice time.
We never did get around to
seeing that movie did we?
But we did a lot of
other cool stuff, right?
I guess...
I mean "yes," I'm sorry.
I kinda spaced out
there for a second.
Ah, let me guess.
You've never been to an
amusement park before either.
No I haven't...
Grandpa never had
a chance to take me.
We were too busy
training every day.
Sometimes I feel
like I missed out.
I would've loved to try
a ride like that, just once.
Let's do it!
Come on let's go take a spin
on the merry-go-round.
You wanna try it, right?
Well here's your chance!
No time like the present.
But, well the
thing is, I just uh...
When you feel like you
really wanna do something
you should just take
a leap and go for it!
Nice move...
So far so good.
Don't be scared, there's
really nothing to worry about.
Yeah, okay...
These kids' rides
can be pretty boring.
I hope she isn't disappointed...
Wow, so this is how it feels,
to finally be the one waving
from this side of the ride.
That's great. She looks
like she's having fun!
Are you positive you still
wanna see that movie?
Yeah! Besides, aren't you
the one who told me if I really
wanted to do something I
should just "take a leap"?
Yeah...
Except now we're probably gonna
have to dodge Niijima again.
Would you look at that!
I guess he gave up on me!
Where is Kenichi?
Don't make me ask you again
or I promise you'll regret it!
I already told you guys that
I don't know where he is!
You stubborn little weasel!
You better start
singing like a bird!
Please don't hurt me! I swear to
you, I don't even know the guy!
Don't lie to me, a minute ago
you two were thick as thieves,
"best friends in the
whole wide world!"
Niijima?
Let's go, or we'll
miss the movie!
Wait, we've gotta help
him out, he's your friend!
Who's my friend? That guy?
Look, it really doesn't have
anything to do with us.
Are you actually gonna
pretend you didn't see that?
I'll be the hero...
That's right,
Kenichi Shirahama the hero.
I'll beat up the thugs
and defend the innocent.
This is your last chance
to come clean you punk!
Let him go!
Huh?
You came to save me!
I told you guys he
was my best friend,
now teach them a lesson
they'll never forget!
So, you're the one who's
been bragging to everyone
about beating Tsukuba, huh?
I haven't been
bragging about anything!
Oh no! My legs are
starting to shake!
Would you look at that! The
tough guy's a little scared!
Crap! This guy looks
like a monster!
I'm really gonna enjoy
making you bleed!
Calm down...
There's no getting
away from this now.
I just have to
trust my training!
Don't feel pressured
to form a fist...
Here it comes!
Not too shabby, kid.
That kinda' hurt.
Uh, really?
Now I get to return
the favor. You ready?
Here comes the pai--
'Cause when the
stuff hits the fan,
your training's the one
thing you can count on!
I'm so proud of you!
Thanks!
I guess it was pretty awesome.
Hey wait. Who knocked
out those other guys?
You idiots. I told you
Kenichi was my best buddy
but, you wouldn't
listen to me!
This guy is a master of
all kinds of martial arts!
Karate, kick-boxing,
weird Chinese stuff
you've never even heard
of! That's right!
And he's busting his
butt day in and day out,
so you better
watch your backs...
How does he know that
I've been training?
Is he stalking me or something?
My boy's not scared of Ragnarok,
bring it on whenever you want!
That's enough! Put
a cork in it already!
I don't even know who
these "Ragnarok" guys are!
Isn't it suspicious these
thugs somehow knew
you'd be here today?
Well, now that
you mention it...
I did try to warn you.
Huh?
Some creepy old guy with a
weird hat was handing this out
in school to anyone who would
read it, including those thugs!
What? How did they--
"Kenichi's Itinerary"?!
It's not bad enough every
bully in school is after me,
you guys have to
tell 'em where I am?!
Yes well, actually, it
was all Akisame's idea.
It was what I like to call the
"carrot and stick" approach.
Come again?
You see, kid, when I had
you punchin' that pole,
you looked like you were about
ready to throw in the towel.
So we figured we'd try to help
you grow a little backbone.
Are you people insane?
You used Miu as bait
so those thugs would attack me
and I'd have to fight them?!
Well, you already ran away
from those punks once.
We had to find a way to snap
you out of your little funk
before it became
a bad habit.
It's no different
from the lioness
who throws her cubs from the
cliff to make them stronger.
Perhaps cruel, but
it's "tough love".
Well, I don't need
love like that okay?
Hey, whether you like it or not,
those bullies are
comin' for you!
It doesn't matter what you do,
you're gonna have to
fight 'em sooner or later!
That's right. Remember the enemy
will never stop attacking you.
I get that...
But you don't have
to help 'em do it!
Remember, a man doesn't
choose his path in life,
only whether or
not to walk it.
Huh?! Are you forgetting they
used you as a "carrot?!"
That's okay. I can
forgive them...
...for now.
What is all this
commotion about?
Oh, hi, Hayato.
I see. This is quite a mess.
Hey, Kenichi. My grandfather's
had a lifetime's
worth of experience.
We should see what he thinks
what you should do next.
Uh... right.
Now this may surprise you...
When I was a boy, the older boys
at the dojo picked on me.
You got picked on? I never
would've thought that.
Of course I made sure
I paid them back 100 fold
for what they did.
Yes, once you beat one
person, even if you never
want to fight again,
others will challenge you.
I was constantly attacked
until I had no choice
but to wipe out
the other dojos!
And then one day I woke
up and I was an old man!
Oh no!
Alright, look.
He's saying once you're in
a fight you can't just stop.
You can't quit right in
the middle of a battle.
Keep on fighting!
That doesn't help me at all!
Who said anything about helping?
We were wondering
if there was any way
Kenichi could resolve
this peacefully.
Tell me, son.
Have you already decided you're
never going to run away?
Well, sort of...
If that's true, you must
prepare yourself to fight!
They say, a man does not
choose his path in life,
only whether or not to walk it!
Take a look at these, it
should calm your nerves!
What's this?
No way...
Were you following
us the whole time?
I'll never forgive you for this!
You letch! You pervert!
I only took those pictures
because I thought you
might like to have them...
Looks like you struck
out this time, kid.
If you want I can give
you a few pointers.
Next time Apachai want
to come along too!
Long walks and merry-go-rounds
look so much fun!
For the first time in my life
I feel like I'm the normal one.
What are you doing?
I thought I told you to
bring me the Shirahama kid.
Yeah, we tried, but
he was too strong.
Hm...
Then I suppose it's time that
I paid him a visit myself.
Apachai is so happy!
Kenichi is going to spend
the night at Ryozanpaku!
Boy, spending the night
for training, huh?
This stinks. it's not like it's
been a walk in the park here!
What's the matter, Kenichi?
Aren't you happy?
Apachai's happy because we're
training all night long!
It must be nice
to be so carefree.
That's not true at all!
Apachai can be very serious,
Apachai thinks seriously
all the time.
Like, how I should punish
you when you run away,
or what I should do
if you stop breathing
during training exercises!
This is gonna be the
worst night of my life...