[Music]
Please Elder...
I need you to teach me
a death blow technique.
Why are you asking about death
blows all of a sudden, boy?
Because every martial
artist should have one...!
Whether its some kind of
ultimate punch of doom thingy...
or maybe its some kind of
super crazy kicking fury...
or maybe some kind of
awesome combination of both.
You know...
Something special...
Now that I've become
a real martial artist.
I mean, everyone else has
some kind of finishing move
and I should too...
I don't wanna stick
out like a sore thumb.
Now hold on...
A death blow is not
something that can be taught-
you have to invent it...
You have to look deep
within yourself
in order to find it...
Then it will come to you.
But before you
do anything else
I suggest you decide
what kind of fighter you
want to become, Kenichi.
Gotcha...!
I just need to figure
out the characteristics
of my style first.
I'll start tomorrow!
I'll pay close attention
to my training
so I can invent
my death blow!
Is he training by himself?
I knew it, he's totally
helpless without me.
I can't wait...
Wow...
I'm telling you my death
blow is gonna be awesome-
just you wait and see!
I see you're just
as stupid as ever.
What kind of death blow
are you gonna come up with?
The "super pansy
ear flick"?
Who said that?!
Come out here?!
Renka...?!
But what are you
doing here?!
How did you
find Ryozanpaku?!
I got Hakubi good 'n drunk
and he told me all
about this place.
It's nice to meet you- I'm
Kensay Ma's daughter, Renka...
I've come here to bring my
father back to China with me.
So, you're Kensei's daughter-
make yourself at home...
Nice to meet you.
I'm happy you remember me...!
I thought for sure you
would've forgotten me by now.
Don't be silly how could
I ever forget you, Renka.
Yeah... I'm learning a bunch
of different disciplines
at the moment...
Let's see, there's Karate,
and Jujitsu, and Muay...
What is this, a
dinner buffet?
You don't just take
one of everything
and see what tastes good!
You pick a discipline and
stick with it, you jerk!
Well, I'm sure you
wanna see your dad
so I'll go and
get him for ya
Thanks but that's
not necessary.
Just where do you think
you're going Daddy?
Oh no, forgive
me, Renka...
But I'm not ready to go
back to China just yet.
I'll tell mama
about Ryouzanpaku!
No... Please
don't do that...!
You don't want mama
to kill your daddy!
You ditched the Phoenix Alliance
and left mama and Hakubi
in charge of your
10,000 disciples!
When are you gonna
stop goofing off
and come back to China?!
But I'm not goofing off...!
The masters of Ryozanpaku
are training history's
strongest disciple!
Surely you're not
talking about this loser?!
Hey...
I guess...
I can see why you've
been so busy...
I mean, that weakling needs
all the help he can get.
I'm a weakling?
What's with all
the excitement?
Yeah, what's happening?
What?! You're
Kensei's daughter?!
It's nice to meet you...
My name's Renka.
Now I know you told us
that you had kids...
But I gotta admit I never
would've expected
you to give birth to such
a good lookin' girl.
Mama gave birth- not me.
Yeah, but you don't look
like you helped at all...
How come she not
bald with a mustache?
She's a woman.
So I guess you're
really serious
about taking your dad
back to China with you,
aren't you Renka?
Of course I am!
And since you're
his best disciple...
I think you should come back
to China with us, Kenichi!
That is not gonna happen.
Oh I'm sorry I didn't
mean to interrupt.
I swear this isn't
what it looks like Miu-
this girl barely knows me...!
Listen I'm never
gonna leave Ryozanpaku
so you should just
give it up already...!
Now if you'll excuse me
I have to go and think
about my death blow.
What is this
weird feeling?!
I've had a change
of heart, Daddy.
We can hold off on China.
I think a change of
scenery would be nice...
So I'm gonna stay here
for couple of days.
The characteristics of my
style of martial arts...
How the hell am I
gonna figure that out?
You're not gonna
do it alone.
Want some help?
Who knows? Maybe a little
sparring will help inspire you.
I think that's
a great idea...
But I think
it'd be better
if you sparred
with somebody new
cause you just might learn
something about yourself,
you know?
Well, I guess
you have a point.
Told ya.
I'd probably be better
off sparring with Miu.
That's okay. I've got plenty
of other things to do.
See ya!
Go ants go!
What is with this
crazy feeling?!
Hey everybody!
Its time for dinner!
Goodness that looks great!
What's the occasion?
Apa!
Even though she wants
him to go back to China
I thought we should celebrate
Kensei and Renka's reunion...
So I made something
a little bit special.
I'm sorry Kenichi...
but I thought that you might
be trying to grope me...
So punching you in the
nose was just a reflex.
Why are you going
easy on him, Renka?!
Hey Miu why's my dinner smaller
than everyone else's...?
And of a different species?
I'll give you mine...
-Say 'Ah!'
-Thanks...
Ah!
Miu could I have another
bowl of rice, please?
You've got rice
on your face.
Here you go, Kenichi.
Thank you so much
for the lovely meal.
It was no problem at all.
Did you have enough food?
Do you want some rice...?
Just say "Ah!"
Oh, I can get
you your own!
Um... I... don't
want anymore.
Wow I've never seen Miu
in such a bad mood before...
I get the impression
that she doesn't really like
Renka hanging around Ryozanpaku.
I was so scared at dinner
that I didn't
know what to do.
I didn't want it
to come to this...
but... as long as
I have it with me.
Death blows even a
monkey can learn!
If my masters caught
me reading a Daigakukan
"How-to" on death blows
they would kill me.
But something
about reading
always seems to help
to calm me down.
What are you reading?
What's the matter...?
Why are you
trying to hide it?
It's nothing!
Forget about it, okay?
There's nothing to be
embarrassed about-
is that the kinda stuff
you're in to...? Well?
She thinks I'm reading
something perverted...!
Wait, who cares
what she thinks.
That means my
secret is safe.
Come on! Let me see it...!
Just really quick!
Now way...!
Forget about it!
I feel horrible about
acting that way at dinner.
Hopefully these snacks
will help him forgive me.
Ow that hurt!
Don't touch me like that!
Be more gentle!
It's kinda hard
to control myself
when you're on top
of me like this!
Apachai, how would you
like a little snack?
Apa!
There's only one way to
destroy the evidence! Eat it!
I just can't seem
to figure you out.
The masters here took you
on as a disciple despite
the fact that you lack
any kind of natural
marital arts ability...
You must have worked really
hard to get where you are now.
But what made you decide to
start learning martial arts?
Why didn't you
just give up
after the first time
someone beat you?
I have someone
to look up to.
Oh really?
Yeah...
You see, there's
this girl I know
who took on a gang of
delinquents all by herself
without ever giving
it a second thought.
She didn't freak out or get
scared like most people would.
She faced them like
it was nothing.
And when I finally
saw her fighting style,
which is as smooth
as the wind,
something in me
changed forever...
I realized that I deeply
respected this girl...
and I still feel
the same way today.
I know that it's gonna take
me a really long time...
even so... my goal
as a martial artist
is to finally be able to
protect her one day...
I train so hard in the
hopes of becoming half
as good as she is.
That make sense?
See...? Its not that
difficult to figure me out.
Yeah, I think
I've got it now.
Apachai left rice ball for
Miu to give to Kenichi.
Oh, hey. What's up, Renka?
We leave now.
The only reason he cares about
you is he met you first...
You're just lucky,
that's all.
Girls are scary...
What? You wanna go at it...?
Cause I'll take you
on right now.
Aw, Renka you make
the cutest cat ever!
Just look at her!
Isn't she precious?!
I know Miu loves cats
so I'll use that
against her!
Why the hell are you messing
with my head like that?!
Not my fault you
fell for it, bimbo!
You make me so angry!
I hate you!
That's funny I didn't
know cats could talk-
you're not a very
good one, are you?
I ate the whole
"How-to" book...!
My stomach is killing me...!
I can't train anymore.
Well... I can handle this.
I could've told you that
it's not good to eat paper.
Ow... Do you have
to do that...?
I'm already in pain.
I keep thinking about
what the elder said.
I don't know what kind of
fighter I want to become.
What does that even mean?!
I've gotta figure it out if I
wanna create my death blow.
So I'll keep
training until I do.
Watching you train made me
realize something, Kenichi.
While your death blow training
seems pretty thorough
I think its missing one
very important thing...
So if you want me to tell
you what that thing is...
I suggest you come
with me tomorrow
and I'll show you
what you're missing.
What's she gonna do?
Give me a private lesson?
Do you really think that
my training is lacking
something... important?
Yes, something
very important...
Your training needs
to be more fun!
I should be training
at the dojo.
What's the matter, Kenichi?!
Let's go on the
water slide!
Come on!
I'm never gonna come
up with my death blow
if I waste my time hanging
out at the water park.
Take that, bimbo!
Score one for Renka!
I'm gonna get close to him
and there's no one
here to stop me.
Hey...! What took
you guys so long?
Wait a minute, what are
you guys doing here?
A-pa!
Yup. And I'm here too!
But why?!
Why're you so surprised
you're the one who
invited everyone...
And you said it
was Kensei's treat.
I don't remember
inviting you...
And why would my dad pay?
I put a tracking
device in here
so I could find you...
Tochumaru helped
me with it.
Now, I can't let you
have all the fun, Renka.
What kind of idiot father
tries to get in the way of his
own daughter's happiness?!
My dear, I'm simply
trying to teach you
that happiness is hardly
ever easily attained...
I'm sorry but you don't always
get what you want, my dear.
Okay it's time to
begin your training.
Right!
No more training!
Master Ko-et-soo-gee...
Dontcha think everyone
deserves a day off?
I think you're right...
I haven't had a real day
off in a long time...
So I'll let the
others train him.
I'm sinking...!
What's with the dumbbell?!
It'll help you build
muscle in your legs... hush.
Look! She's overworking him!
No, that weight is much
lighter than the norm.
Remember kids...
Don't try any of this
crazy stuff at home!
You have to stay afloat
while keeping your
chest above the water.
Next!
So what are we gonna do
with this water slide?
Climb up it.
Climbing against the current
helps strengthen your legs.
-No way.
-Would someone show him...
-uh, Miu?
-Sure! No problem!
We'll be right behind you.
See you at the top.
I said I'm going second...!
-Let go dummy!
-Stop... it...
What the hell are you
trying to teach me?!
How to be an old,
bald-headed pervert?!
Ahhh!
What now?!
She was moving so
incredibly fast
I couldn't catch up to her!
Are you ready...?
Cause we're gonna do 100
laps of forward kicks
in the 50 meter pool!
My feet are
getting heavy...
Come over here, Kenichi!
C'mon let's play!
Well... I guess it's nice to
have a change of scenery.
Repetition can
make us lazy.
Kenichi!
A new atmosphere
is good...
It keeps us from becoming
complacent and can inspire us.
Check out that woman
in the loincloth!
She's swimming
up the waterfall!
That kinda looks like fun.
Those two...
What are they doing here?
I- I don't think
I can move.
Are you alright, Kenichi?
Get your hands off him!
Who do you think you are?!
I'm the one who's supposed
to be taking care of him
not you, you big,
blonde bimbo!
Stand back and give
him some air, would ya?!
You're gonna suffocate
him like that!
Would you cut that out!
I hate you!
Ree-ewe and Show-kaht-sue.
They work for Hawk-uh-bee!
Oh no!
I bet they're here
to take me back!
So, you understand
the mission... right?
Yeah... We're to bring
her back to China
no matter what...
no going easy
on her either.
Hawk-uh-bee must've told them
about Rio-zahn-pah-koo.
We're gonna bring
Renka back to China...
Even if it kills us.
I've got an idea...
Come with me, Miu. Hurry!
Things are about to
get a little crazy-
for some reason the
Chinese mafia is here.
Since Sougetsu's death
they've targeted Hakubi...
I'm worried they may have
come here to take me hostage.
Don't try anything.
Just come peacefully
now, Renka...
We don't want trouble.
You're not too
bad for a girl.
Look, I don't wanna
fight you guys-
not in my swimsuit.
Then you shouldn't
have gotten involved
in the first place, huh?
Have fun, bimbo.
Those guys are
two of the best.
Good luck.
Had enough yet?
Kenichi!
You lay a hand on Miu
and you're gonna have
to answer to me!
He didn't lose his balance and
fall when they attacked him!
His legs are so strong
he hardly even budged!
Leg strength is crucial
in martial arts...
and it looks like
Kenichi's strength
is at an almost
untouchable level!
I don't know who you are but
I'll take you on anyway...
The name's Ryuu also known
as the Praying Mantis fist.
I'm the wielder of the
piercing leg kick... Shokatsu.
I'm the first disciple
of Ryozanpaku, Kenichi...
I accept your challenge.
I really wish I
could help him.
I'll just cheer him on!
Go Kenichi, I know
you can do it!
Hey, look...!
he's having fun...
He made some
friends at the pool.
But they're gonna fight.
Those guys are Hakubi's
top two disciples...
They must've been sent to
take Renka back to China.
I see...
So they're
Hakubi's men, huh?
I look forward to seeing
which of our disciples
comes out on top.
Kenichi, be careful...!
Show-kaht-sue's known across
China for his powerful kicks-
so watch out for his legs...!
But he'll attack
using his arms too!
About time I pull out
my piercing leg kick!
That all ya got?!
What...?! No way!
Such amazing leg power...
His masters must've
trained him hard.
Well, of course.
Damn you...! I'm
gonna take you down!
Since the first day Kenichi
stepped foot in Ryozanpaku
we've focused his training
on increasing his strength.
It's essential when
learning martial arts.
You gotta watch out for his
one-two combination punches!
You're comin' with me!
You bastard!
That wouldn't have happened
if he had worn a loincloth.
I tried to tell him.
Damn it! This water
is slowing me down!
How the hell
did he do that?!
He kicked me out
of the water!
That's beyond
human strength!
Wow it's like he's a completely
different Kenichi...!
But why is he going so far?
Oh Kenichi.
Even so, my goal
as a martial artist
is to finally be able to
protect her one day...
I've gotta keep
his legs pinned!
My breath!
Helpless runt.
Is he laughing at me?!
Get outta there...!
I've had enough
of the two of you!
Did you just see that?!
Yeah, that was the
coolest thing ever!
Maht-soo-ayy Park has really
stepped up their attractions!
There was even a hot
chick in a loincloth
swimming up the waterfall!
I get it now...
So you guys were sent by
Hakubi to take Renka back home.
I thought you were members
of the Chinese mafia.
I am really
sorry about that.
You don't have to
apologize to them...
I mean, they're just Hakubi's
lackeys so who cares...?!
Ow. I'm sorry my daughter
caused you so much trouble.
You know Renka...
If you spend all your time
goofing off at the pool...
you're never gonna become a
martial artist of our level.
Now, now, calm down...
Well... I must
say I'm surprised,
cuz Master Hakubi made
it sound like Ryozanpaku
was full of a bunch
of crazy people-
but that's not
the case at all...
You all seem
pretty normal.
Anyways, it's you time
to go back home, Renka.
Things have been tough for
master Hakubi since you left.
What...! Really?!
I'm afraid so...
He's been drinking to
ease his loneliness
but in his drunken state
he's begun attacking
any mafia members
he can get his hands on.
Renka... Please... come home!
Wow, the Ma family
sure is scary.
Alright I'll go
back with you.
He's so annoying...
But I guess I really shouldn't
have left him alone like that.
Deep down she's
kinda nice.
Okay Renka,
let's get going.
Hey Kenichi, I just
thought you should know
that you already
have a death blow...
But it seems like you haven't
figured that out, you know?
But... What are
you talking about?
You have these
really awesome moves
that I've seen you use
repeatedly when you're fighting
but I don't know
if you realize it...
I noticed while I was watching
you fight the two of them...
Since you're not really aware
of the moves you're making
you're unable to see their
potential as a death blow...
But I promise
you it's there.
Once you've figured
out what it is
and you've learned
how to use it properly
give me a call, okay?
I need someone to
protect me too.
You haven't seen the last
of me, ya Blonde Bimbo!
Come back again
soon, kitty!
Meow- meow- meow!
One day that boy's
gonna be mine!
So my death blow is something
I may have used before, huh...?
If that's the case, I should
be able to figure it out again.
I appreciate
the hint, Renka.
Um, Shigure...?
Next time we go to the
pool can you wear this...?
It's less revealing.
Yeah, but that
thing looks...
uncomfortable.
Miu shouldn't be pushing that
bathing suit on Shigure...
I think she's looks smokin' hot
in that loin cloth, don't you?
I think you're an old perv
who has a weird obsession with
scantily clad young women.
[Music]
Hey guess what, Kenichi!
We found Thor's lair!
You know, the Seventh
Fist of Ragnarok?
We need to strike
while the iron's hot!
But we can't just go in
there and pick a fight!
That's not the
right thing to do.
Are you sure about that?
Ragnarok keeps
coming after you...
why not beat 'em
to the punch?
Just think about all the
poor, innocent people
who are gonna get hurt
if you don't fight!
Come on, go show him
what a hero you are!
If you don't do
it then who will?!
Alright, alright,
I get it.
But I don't know anything
about the Seventh Fist.
Who is this Thor guy?
Guess I'm gonna find out.