[Music]
I ask you again...
Say you will become
my disciple...
Kenichi Shirihama.
Sorry, I can't do that.
But... But why...?
Don't you want
to be a martial artist?
I do...! But I want to be
one to protect people...
My friends...
And anyone else
who needs someone
to fight for a good cause.
So... I don't really need to
learn how to kill people.
You know?
That's it, laugh...!
I almost starved to
death in that forest
and I was attacked
by a bear...!
And where were you? !
I don't know what I
would've done if Ogata
hadn't saved me...
I told him about
the walnuts
and he told me where
the trees grew...
so I went looking for them,
but I wasn't paying
attention...
and the ledge broke off
and I fell in the river...
and I floated away...
Why didn't you
come for me...?
I thought I was
dead for sure!!
You might've
been scared...
But you still managed to keep
control of your inner rage.
Oh...! I'm angry, don't
kid yourself, old man!
As I thought, he
has a strong will...
and he has chosen the path of
the true martial artist.
Glad you're
back, Kenichi...
good to see you
haven't changed.
Oo-kay... thanks.
I should concentrate on
the radius of my reach.
I see! The reason I
couldn't grab them before
was because they always
swam ahead of my reach!
Then the place I
should be reaching...
Isn't where they are...
It's where they're going!
I got one!
Ryouzanpaku...
And that damn old man.
He used me to
train his disciple.
Makes me itch to leave the
mountains for a while
and pay the city a visit.
I'm gonna die!
Keep calm.
Don't let your heart race.
Remember what
you've learned.
Ow!
That's enough
for tonight!
It's finally over.
Nope... There's
more to go.
Give up... How many times
do I have to tell you, no...?
You're lucky I haven't killed
you yet, you alien bastard.
There's no reason to
be so rude, Hermit...
I just wanted to
invite you to a party.
As Commander of the
Shinpaku Alliance
I'm aware that we've
become the main target
of Ragnarok...
So I thought it would
be nice to have a little
shin-dig to get to
know each other
before we go to war.
There's gonna
be a bingo game.
With prizes!
Die.
You are never gonna
hear the end of it-
at least, not until you join.
I told you I'd kill you if
you asked one more time!
Hey...! Sorry but I'm not the
alien you're lookin' to kill...
Good to see ya...!
But you should really
be more careful
about attacking
outta the blue like that-
could've been anyone...
you know?
Yeah, the last thing we
wanna do is put each other
outta commission before
we have to face Ragnarok.
How dare you even classify
me in the same group
as you worthless trash.
What the hell did you say? !
Now wait a minute...
Let's not start fighting
amongst ourselves.
Why don't you get it? !
I'm not one of you!
That doesn't matter- I
just think the party'll be
more fun the more
people come...
You should join us.
There's no way
that I'm going...
That's the last
thing I wanna do.
So you're going? ! Great!
I'm glad we
cleared that up.
Guess we'll see
you later then!
The party starts at four
so ya better be on time...
Otherwise, you're
first up at karaoke.
Did you dumb asses even
hear a word I said? !
Shin... paku!
How lame.
Kenichi's in secret training
and Hermit's an ass...
so unfortunately neither of
them can be with us today...
Too bad for them...
It's their loss...
Now let's get this
party started
and get to know Kisara
and her people.
Hey... I thought
Shiratori and the others
were supposed to
be here too!
Don't worry about them...
They have their own
party to attend-
this one's just
for the generals.
And who are you...? I'll
have to see your invitation.
My what...?! I was
told to come here.
Oh, you're the guys
with the girly leader.
They called you out, huh?
Would you shut
up, dumb ass? !
Kisara asked me to try
to get along with you
Shinpaku guys...
So... You want some juice?
Hell yeah... Thank
you very much.
Here... Would you like to have
some water- it's filtered.
Sure...
Hey how come everybody
seems so high strung
at this party?
I don't wanna get
to know these guys.
They're weird.
So how about you pour
me a glass flag boy.
Sure - whatever you say...
princess.
Do you carry that flag
with you everywhere?
Our flag is the soul of
the Shinpaku Alliance.
Oh great, we
got a weird one.
Your general can
kick some major ass.
Yeah, well yours
isn't too bad either.
So they're having
some kinda party, huh?
Just so you know... you're
the best of the best...
You're the chosen
few my lads...!
We weren't very
close at first...
because... we saw
things differently.
But now that we can
all see eye-to-eye
I know the Shinpaku Alliance
is destined for greatness!
Wouldn't you agree,
Siegfried? Well? !
In other words, all of my songs
are written from the heart
yet I also want them to
convey my technique.
Come on, Takeda! You'll
back me up, won't ya? !
Okay, yeah...
so your music
is your attack!
And my other cat's
named Gorozen.
He's the lighter one.
Oh wow! I can't believe you
have two of them!
As soon as I saw 'em I
knew I had to take 'em home.
I never would've pegged
you for a cat lover.
Ukita quit showing her
your cat pictures
and Sig quit talking
about music!
Start paying attention-
this is important!
We have to discuss the future
of the Shinpaku Alliance!
Listen...! I'm ordering
all of you...!
Please don't make
me keep screaming!
Ta-da!
Do not fear my underlings!
Your commander has come to
grace you with his presence
and I even brought food!
Are you kids
having fun yet?
Hey girly man...! I got
the booze...! I--...!
Oh my god, what happened? !
Matsui...
Hey... Commander...!
What's going on, sir? !
Commander Niijima...
Kamioka...! Can you tell
us what happened? !
Uh... Berserker.
What? !
He busted in here and
asked me where you were...
but... I didn't say a word.
Because... I will
always remember...
that you saved my life.
Thank you... sir...
Without you I'd be dead...
lying... in a sewer.
No...! No...!
Don't diiiiiiiie!
Calm down... He just
fell unconscious.
How can you be
so calm...?!
Your subordinates have all been
attacked, Commander...!
It's only a matter of time
before they find you too!
You may be right...
But I'll be prepared
with a counterattack.
That was a lot of fun! We
should do it again some time!
Hold on. Where's
Commander Niijima?
He probably went to
check on the other guys.
I had a great time
chatting with all of you-
hope to see
you again soon.
Bye... Sieg!
So thanks for showing
me those pictures
of your kittens, Ukita.
It's no big deal- I
mean, I had 'em on me...
I'm just glad you
thought they were cute.
So what's going on?
You gotta little
crush on Kisara?
What...?! What the hell
are you talkin' about? !
She and I were just
talking about cats!
More members of the
Shinpaku Alliance...
I got good luck tonight.
Ukita!
Nice glasses, pal.
-Hey!
-Wait... aren't you...
Berserker? !
That's right- the
one and only...
and just so you know...
I meant to miss.
I hate not havin'
Kenichi around-
this shopping stuff
gets exhausting!
Well... I see you recognize
the value of your
disciple when he's gone.
Apachai was also very
sad about Kenichi until
Akisame bought him
an ice cream cone!
That was too easy.
Hey, wait a second...
Where's Miu?
You're the cutest thing
ever! Yes, you are!
You're the sweetest little
ball of fluff I've ever seen!
I wish I could take you
home with me, kitty!
I'd hate to see her do jail
time for stealing a cat.
Peel your face off
the glass, Miu-
it's time to head home.
It's useless Sakaki- she
will stay there with face
to glass for at
least an hour.
Apachai has seen
it happen before.
Well I'm not
waitin' for her.
Meow...
What're you doing here? !
I could ask you
that question!
All of a sudden we keep
running into each other.
Like that time I saw
you at the bookstore
while I was looking
at kitty calendars!
They have some great ones
at that place, don't they?
Yeah, and then I
saw you at the park.
Because that's where all
the stray cats go
and I like to feed
them sometimes.
I just feel like you've
been popping up everywhere
I've been this
week- are you sure
that you're not following me?
It's just a coincidence.
We have a common interest
so it makes sense
we'd bump into each
other sooner or later.
We're cat lovers so we
end up in the same places!
Whenever I start
feeling kinda lonely
my cat obsession can get
a little out of control.
You're feeling lonely?
I get it- it's because Kenichi
isn't around right now...
So tell me, do you have
a crush him or what?
What are you
talking about? !
What on Earth would
give you that idea? !
Kenichi is just another
disciple training
at my grandfather's dojo.
No big deal!
I don't have any
feelings for him.
At least not in that way.
I think of him more like a
silly younger brother, you know?
Or maybe more like
the family dog?
But it would be better
if he were a cat.
Hold on- give
the guy a break-
dontcha think you're being
a little hard on him?
I was hoping Kenichi
Shirahama would be with you.
Guess I'll just have to
concentrate on my other targets.
I'm impressed...
You're the first person
who's ever been able
to dodge one of
my attacks...
You're more skilled than
I thought you'd be...
Miu Furinji.
What did she
just throw at me? !
And you... If you knew
what's good for you-
you would've stayed with the
Wall-keer-ee...
Instead of joining
with the Shinpaku.
Stay outta this dairy cow-
this is my fight, you got it?
But cat lovers have to
have each other's backs!
Alright fine, if you wanna
help I guess I can't stop ya.
Then we'll fight
both of you...
Get them!
Pick up...!
Damn it Kisara,
why the hell won't you
answer your phone...?!
Have you gotten through
to anyone, Matsui? !
No sir! Takeda's not
answering his phone either!
Damn it! Then try
calling Ukita!
Yes, sir!
I'll call Sig and we'll
come up with a place
where we can all
meet up, okay? !
Ukita! I'm so glad that
I got through to you!
Where are you right now?
What's the matter...!
What's going on? !
What's up, Ukita? !
Who the hell is Ukita...?
Oh, I think I know
who that is...
I'm steppin' on
his face right now.
Who the hell is Ukita...?
Oh, I think I know
who that is...
I'm steppin' on
his face right now.
Um... May I ask who
I'm speaking with?
Berserker.
What...?! What happened to him?
Is everything okay? !
Calm down- we gotta keep
our cool Matsui-
otherwise we've lost...
This has come as
a surprise-
I didn't expect to get
ambushed by Berserker.
It looks as if the final
battle is upon us...
That means we
need to commence
Operation Triple
O immediately!
So Kenichi Shirahama
isn't here...?
No sense in me wasting my
time with you guys, then.
Get your foot
off my friend.
Takeda the Puncher,
right...?
I've heard stories about
your powerful punches
but I can't say I'm worried.
I said get your foot
off my friend, you punk!
How the hell does
he keep dodging me? !
Ultimate uppercut!
To the left?
No! The right.
He dodged me again!
Thanks. Right side's
better for me anyway.
There's something
weird about this guy...
I've got a
question for ya...
tell me... which martial
arts have you studied?
None of 'em.
I knew it!
He didn't get that strength
through martial arts training.
He's just a
street fighter.
I'm surprised you
can still stand...
I can tell
you're a boxer...
you're tough.
This is bad news for me.
Somehow he's able to
see through my punches.
Most fighters have to go
through years of training
before they can even
dodge a punch like mine...
but not this guy.
He's got some kind
of raw talent
that puts him
ahead of the game.
He's like a street
fighting genius.
I really don't
wanna admit this...
but I don't think I'll
be able to beat him.
I'm getting' tired of waiting-
are we gonna fight or what?
I thought I told you to get your
foot off my friend's face!
All you're doing is
wasting your energy-
you haven't been able
to hit me once.
Didn't your boxing coach
tell you not to do that?
What's the deal, Takeda?
Wanna tell me why
you're so angry?
And don't tell me it's cause
I'm bullying your friend here-
there's gotta be more to it-
I've heard that one before.
That's too bad...
Cause you're about to
hear it one more time...
Now get your foot
off my friend
before I kill your dumb ass.
Well, that's
disappointing...
For some reason
I was hoping
there was a more interesting
reason this time.
Now Takeda!
Now's your chance
to hit him!
Ukita!
He caught my jab!
Only one thing
left to do...
My Illusionary Left!
That kinda stung a little.
What the-...?!
Hw did you catch my punch? !
Now die.
Ah well...
you gave it your
best shot...
I was hopin' for
a good fight
but that was easier
than I thought it'd be.
I suggest you get your
dirty feet off of my
subordinates before I have
to teach you a lesson.
Yeah, right...
And what if I told you
that wasn't gonna happen?
Watch it. I don't
think you know
who you're messin'
with, buddy.
One round and you'll be
cryin' like a baby...
You see...
I'm the secret weapon
they've been hiding.
I don't know...
You do look like the leader
of the Shinpaku Alliance...
I could never forget
a face like that.
That's right... The
name's Haruo Niijima-
leader of the Shinpaku
and an overall bad ass.
What do you say, big guy...?
Ready to take me on?
You may think you're tough
but I got this one-
I bet you won't even be
able to lay a hand on me!
Time for Operation
Triple O...!
Go!
He's running away? !
What's the
matter, Berserker?!
You weren't expecting
that one, were ya? !
I'd like to see you
catch up with me now!
Through the legs!
What the hell? !
Okay... this one's...
interesting.
You have now
completed level two.
Great...! Does that mean
I can control my Seikuuken now?
Not yet!
Level three...
Beehive of hell.
You must dodge the
bees attacking you
while staying
balanced on the rock!
But... This is impossible!
You have to stay calm or
you'll lose your balance
and fall into the water!
Uh, oh...
Damn...
These girls are a lot
stronger than I remember.
We've been in special
training ever since
we fought the
crazy ninja woman
who attacked us
with a rice spoon.
If you're wielding a
weapon to gain power...
you can never become
it's master...
You need to become the master
of your own body... first.
I've had enough
of you two!
Hey don't use me
as a spring board!
Sorry!
Damn you!
She's using some
kinda stick...
Now I've got you!
You're pretty darn
good with a staff...
Couldn't even
see it at first.
I see what she's doing.
She hides the staff
behind herself
so it looks like
she's only punching.
That's kinda clever.
I have a staff...
a longsword, a katana...
and even a knife...
Yeah. I can tell that you're
a master of weapons...
But it looks like the staff
is your preferred method.
Let's finish them off, Miu!
This is our chance!
Do it! I'll leave
the others to you!
You got it!
You're going down, girly!
You're pretty confident...
Too bad this fight is
gonna break both of you.
Hell yeah...! Four
steps at a time!
You can't stop me!
Now I've got ya.
Come back here!
I'm free!
Somebody help me please!
There's a pervert
on the loose...!
I'm being chased by
a big, scary perv!
Hold up Berserker...!
It's not a good idea
to chase me through
the crowded streets!
That's right.
Follow me, ya big lug...
Little does he know-
I'm psychologically
manipulating him!
All I had to do
was piss him off
and he'll chase me to
the ends of the Earth!
You're not gettin'
away this time.
Hold on...! Let's
talk this out!
Here we go!
Everything's going
according to plan.
This is gonna be great!
Just one more step...
Huh... You're kidding...
Did you really think I was
gonna fall for that...?
You have seriously
underestimated your opponent.
Nice try, buddy...
but this is the end.
You figured me
out, Berserker...
I can't believe you were
able to see through
my perfect plan!
Now die!
Oh no...! Don't hurt me!
Fooled ya, didn't I? !
How ya like that...? I've
been digging this hole
since I was a
little kid...
I'm so glad I finally
got to use it...!
I call it trap two-
it's harder to get out
of than the first one.
You jumped right
over trap one
but you didn't see
this one coming!
I lured you
into my trap-
like a game of
Tic-Tac-Toe...!
And that's why I call
it Operation Triple O...
Pretty smart, huh?
You could learn
a thing or two.
Want me to tell you why
I'm standing here at the top
and you're at the
bottom of trap two?
Go ahead and tell me...
Maybe you're right- I
could learn a thing or two.
While you may be able to see
what's two steps ahead of you...
I can see even farther ahead
thereby surpassing you all!
[Music]
I am a master
of weapons.
Who would've thought
my disciple would leave
because I chose to
fight with them?
You've sided
with the enemy.
I feel like I've been
bitten by my own dog.
I'm sorry, Freya
but I can't stand
in your shadow any longer.
I have to walk
my own path.
It's nothing personal.
You talk a big
game, Kisara-
but against my staff
you're helpless.
You may have been
my student once
but I have no problem
destroying you now.
Fine, then let's do this.
We'll just see who
comes out on top.
Here goes!