Kenichi saw an
opening and took it!
Y-you sneaky little
snot-nosed punk!
You waited and struck
me right at the moment
I relaxed my stomach muscles!
Kenichi. A man's worth is
determined by whether or not
he can strike a blow
at the critical moment.
Time to die, punk!
Hey, buddy?
I heard you say you wanted
to challenge a master,
so why are you messin'
with our disciple?
You're Sakaki?!
Sure am. Now how
'bout that challenge?
L-let go! You're crushing
the bones in my wrist!
Hey, Kenichi,
I've been watching you take
care of our guests here.
That was a nice strike.
You barely hesitated at all.
Y-you mean you were here and
watching this whole time?!
C'mon get a grip, it's okay!
You handled it perfectly!
The party's over!
Ow! Kenichi, let go!
You're grabbing me too tight!
I can't breathe and
you're smashing my--
Geez. It's not
over already, is it?
Oh, man, you gotta
be kidding me.
And I thought Crab Head guy
was a ferocious fighter!
Master Sakaki makes him look
like a choir boy in comparison!
These guys have gotta be the
lamest bunch of challengers
I've ever faced in this dojo!
Master, there's something I need
to ask you, and it's a matter
of life or death! Would you
please give me a day off?
A break? Why?
Well, if you haven't noticed,
I've been training like crazy
for three weeks straight
without a single day off!
I need a break,
just for one day!
--Say yes! Please, please!
--Sure. Why not?
I thought you'd say that,
but I had to try at least.
Oh, well. Thanks anyway.
You're serious?!
Of course I am. You're right.
You have been training hard
and you deserve a break.
In fact, come to think
of it, we all do!
Let's all go to
the beach tomorrow!
Master, you're the best! Really!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
You've brightened up my
day in more ways than one!
Alright! The beach! Woo hoo!
It's been three weeks since
I moved into the dojo.
My skills have
definitely progressed,
but my relationship
with Miu hasn't.
But a day at the beach with
her is gonna change all that!
What? The beach? Really?
Yeah, we're leaving tomorrow
morning! Pack your swimsuit!
Oh, I'll have to
buy a new one.
I've outgrown the one
I bought last year.
This top is so tight! I'm
about pop out of this thing!
Oh, God! Thank you for these two
very bountiful, bouncing,
bosomy blessings!
Ah! Kenichi! What happened?!
You're bleeding!
Up until now, I thought
this was a waste of money.
But at long last, I can
finally put this book to use!
I doubt it.
What the-- How did you...
You and her? No way.
I wouldn't get my expectations
up if I were you.
It'll hurt less when
she turns you down.
Thanks for the
vote of confidence!
When she turns you down,
please don't hurt yourself!
Life is worth living!
Were all of you spying on me?
Ah! You're in on this too?!
Well, you're wrong, got it?!
Just wait! You'll
see! You'll all see!
Wow! I've never
seen seagulls before!
There are so many of them!
A-pa!
Wanna find out how they taste?
What?! No, stop!
Seagulls are for
watching, not eating!
Okay then. Whatever.
You guys sure had me fooled.
You live in a dingy dojo
like a bunch of hobos but you're
actually rolling in dough.
If you weren't, you couldn't
have bought this fancy boat!
Fancy? This old thing?
You must be joking!
We didn't buy this
vessel, we built it.
You built it?!
Look. You missed a spot.
Oops! Apachai is bad painter.
Wait a minute!
You mean you guys actually
built this tub yourselves?
You did? I'm too young to die!
Don't worry, little
one! You're safe.
I've been to the island
many times on Sekitoba 2.
Did he say "two?"
Um, so tell me,
if this is "2,"
what happened to Sekitoba 1?
We don't appear to be
picking up any speed.
I'll go see what's
wrong with the engine.
Apachai, what happened
to the first boat?
Miu, can you take over as
navigator for just a bit?
Oh, sure thing!
What's wrong, engine?
We need a lot more horsepower.
At the rate you're going, we'll
never make it to the island.
Our little engine that couldn't
has reached his limit.
The only thing keeping him
from totally sputtering out
is the thought of
seeing Miu in a bikini.
I gotta see some boobies!
Well, then. Do you think we
should switch this clunker
out for a model with
a lot more power?
Hm...
Yeah!
Let's do it!
Go time!
Apapapa!
Wow! This is really awesome!
I guess Akisame must have
solved our engine problem, huh?
At the rate we're going,
we'll reach the island
in just a few minutes, Grandpa.
It's "Captain" Grandpa today!
Ah! Land-ho! We're here!
My favorite vacation spot!
I discovered it myself!
Furinji Island!
What do you think?
Beautiful isn't it?
Hey, has Miu changed
into her bikini?
Whoa! I knew it!
You guys are super-rich!
You'd have to be to buy a
vacation home like that one!
Actually, we built
that ourselves, too.
Apapapapapapa!
♪ Saw the tree,
build the house, ♪
♪ saw the house, build
the saw, saw, saw. ♪
Hold up, big guy.
We already built
the house, remember?
Y-you mean they built
this thing, too?!
Hey! Kenichi!
Come join us! Hurry up!
Yeah! Get a move on!
What's taking you so long?!
I love beach photos!
Well, what are you waiting for?
They're calling for you.
You better get going.
You wanted a face full of
boobies, well there they are.
Yeah, that's true. I do wanna
join her, it's just that...
Why do I have to do it from the
top of this cliff? It's suicide!
Hey, Blondie! What the heck
is he doin' up there?
Uh...
Listen up, Kenichi.
There's one thing that every
martial artist must have.
It's a little thing
called courage.
It's the most important thing
in a fight. If you're too scared
of what might happen,
you've already lost.
If you wanna win, you
have to have courage,
and lack of it is your biggest
weakness right now.
It's affecting your progress.
If you don't conquer this now,
you'll never move
to the next level.
That's why we've planned
out some highly intensive,
courage building activities
while we're here on the island.
What?! I have to train here?!
I've got courage! I beat
up Crab Head, didn't I?
Besides, you told me I
could have the day off!
You can if you pass the test.
Have you ever heard
of Pentecost Island?
It's in the South Pacific. Young
men there test their courage
by jumping from high towers
with a vine tied to their feet.
It's a tribal coming
of age ceremony.
And the origin of
modern day bungee jumping.
Here's the test. If you
can jump from here,
we'll excuse you from any of
the training we have planned.
No way! I'm not here for
a coming of age ceremony!
Those other guys
had a vine at least!
Plus, there could be lots
of sharp rocks down there!
She's nuts! That's dangerous!
Especially dressed like that!
Wh-Why did you throw
your life away?!
Shigure!
No rocks here. Jump.
She jumped right in
without even thinking.
Great. That sucked all
the fun right out of it.
Now you have no
excuse not to jump.
Oh my god! Shigure!
That was a close call! Whew!
She's right! The next
time you do that,
please wear a
proper swimsuit!
That's not what I meant!
But at the beach,
I always wear, this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
If I... If I tell
you two something,
will you promise me that you
won't tell Miu about it?
The truth is...
...I don't know how to swim!
So? That's no excuse.
It just makes
things more exciting.
Enough talk. Jump off the cliff.
Right now. Either that
or you start training.
Th-That's like asking
me to choose how to die.
Now, now. With that
kind of pressure,
even a fearless person
would hesitate.
Do you have any better
ideas, old man?
How would you get him to jump?
I'd approach him quietly
and get as close as I could.
And then what would you do?
Grab him quickly and do this!
If you wanna learn
how to swim,
the best way is to
jump in head-first!
Somebody help me!
While inventive, that
defeats the purpose.
Kenichi really needs to
work up the courage himself.
We were trying to make
him face his fear.
All you did was add to it.
Hm. You're right. He must
jump from that cliff on his own.
We'll make him jump off
again once he wakes up.
And if he can't, it's nothing
but back-breaking
training for two days.
Yes, I agree!
Uh-oh! Not good!
Try dodging this,
you little coward!
Faster, boy, faster!
No matter what I do, at this
rate I will definitely die!
As the saying goes "when
you only have two options,
pick the third". Well,
I'm picking the third!
I'm getting the hell
off this island!
He what?!
He ran away? Are you sure?
Well, it certainly seems so.
It happened when I went
to check on him to see if
he'd regained consciousness.
Kenichi!
Eep!
Where do you think you're going?
Look! I think Miu's
top just came undone!
What? Where? Over
where? Show me!
I've got to get
a picture of this!
And that's how he
escaped from me.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'd be, too, if I were you.
Oh, brother. This
island's small.
Then again, it's big
enough to get lost on.
And it can be dangerous,
too. If you didn't know
where you were going, you
could stumble off a cliff.
What was he thinking?
Well, we don't have any choice.
We'll have to split up
into search parties,
and hunt Kenichi
down like a dog!
This isn't what it looks like.
I am not running away!
It's a strategic withdrawl.
I don't wanna die, so
I'm leaving, that's it!
And that's what we usually
call running away!
Who said that? Who said
that? Where are you?
See? Look, it's a "sand
bongo!" Bom-bom-bom-bom...
Hey, wait! That's weird!
Where did everybody go?
That's funny. I could have sworn
they were all here a minute ago.
Hm. Apachai is gonna
take a quick look around.
You stay put. Apachai
will be back soon.
'Kay!
Hey, wait! Now that I think
about it, I'm on an island.
The only way to get home is by
boat, and there's only one here.
They've probably got it
under armed guard by now!
The only reason I came
here was to be with Miu!
My dream of spending a
romantic evening on the beach
with her has turned
out to be a nightmare.
I guess the only
thing I can do now
is try to make it through
the next two days.
I'll find a place to lay
low, and not worry about
cliff-jumping or training.
And just take it easy in this
beautiful island paradise!
It's Shigure.
Aagh!
She saw me! I'm dead meat!
Why are you running
away from me?
Well, to make a long
story short, if I don't,
I'm going to die on this island.
And then they said
if I didn't do it,
I'd have to train for
two straight days!
All because I wouldn't
jump off that cliff!
Isn't it horrible?
This was after I told
them I couldn't swim!
Totally insane, right?!
Mm-hm.
I'd jump right in if I knew how
to swim, but I never learned to.
It's easy. I could even
teach you how, Kenichi.
If you want. Do you?
Um, I appreciate this and all,
but if your method of teaching
involves me possibly
getting hurt or even killed,
count me out.
This river has a flow.
Do you feel it?
Uh, yeah I do.
Then listen closely.
If you're scared of water,
and you try to fight
against the flow,
there's a good
chance you'll drown.
However, if you relax
and go with the flow,
you have nothing to worry about.
Come on!
Remember what I said.
Relax and go with the flow.
Whoa! I'm moving!
This is amazing!
Just by moving my arms and legs,
I'm able to keep
up with the fish!
Oh, man! I'm swimming!
I don't believe it!
I was actually swimming!
That's good. You wanna learn
how to swim and breathe?
Whenever you're swimming
and need to take a breath,
turn your head to the side
like this to breathe.
Hey, I've heard
of this method.
It's called freestyle
swimming, isn't it?
Yes. Some people call it that.
It was mentioned in
a book I read called,
"Learn How To Swim
In Three Days."
Let's try it again.
Assume the position.
Never inhale underwater.
Exhale instead.
Just breathe out. Not in.
But if I do that, won't I
run out of air eventually?
Why do you think
I taught you those
breathing exercises earlier?
She's right! This
is pretty easy!
That's it. You've got it now.
Alright! I can finally swim!
Not too hard once you
get the hang of it, huh?
That's the same way that
I was taught how to swim
when I was young.
Did Shigure actually just
smile there for a second?
Maybe. I don't know.
I guess it could have been the
way the light was hitting her.
But then again, I could
swear that was a smile.
If it was, that
was the first one
I've ever seen on her face.
Looks like you've learned
the basics of swimming.
Any questions?
No!
Excellent. Then you have
nothing to fear anymore.
Right?
Huh?
W-w-wait a minute!
I can't do this yet!
It's too soon! Don't'cha think
I need some more lessons first?
You said you'd do this if you
knew how to swim, remember?
I meant I'd do it after weeks
of extensive swim
training, not now!
Well, well. What do you know?
Our little lost disciple
has finally been found.
So I guess we scoured the
mountains for nothing, eh?
He's been with
Shigure all this time?
Hey, look where he is.
Maybe he's going to
give it another try.
For his sake, I
certainly hope so.
No! Stop!
There's absolutely nothing that
can make me jump off this cliff!
Hey, Kenichi! This is
the coolest thing ever!
You shouldn't be out
there alone! Oh, geez!
Come back in now!
Hey! Apachai told
you to stay here!
Oh, no! How'd she
get so far out there?
Kenichi, jump into the
water and come play!
Huh? Whoa! Check
it out! Dolphins!
And it looks like a
whole pod of 'em, too!
Look closer! Those
aren't dolphins!
Apa!
They're sharks!
Oh, no!
Honoka!
I'm coming!
Help!
Leave her alone!
Kenichi!
Elder!
There's another one!
It's gonna eat us!
We're going to eat it!
Shark fin soup, anyone?
Thank you for
saving our butts.
Oh man I was so scared!
But your courage
outweighed your fear.
You've impressed
me today, Kenichi.
For some time now, you've also
reminded me of someone.
Really? Who's that?
Me believe it or not,
but back when I was around
your age, of course.
You?
Honoka! Kenichi!
I'm so glad you guys are okay!
I know you've been waiting
for this, Kenichi,
and now it's time.
I hope you're ready to move
on to technique training.
Actually, Master, can it
wait just a little longer?
But why? Is there a problem?
Understand that every
day you put it off,
is another day that
Ragnarok grows even stronger.
If you insist, so be it.
I just hope it isn't too late.
It might be hard for you
to understand, Master,
but there's something I
have to take care of first.
If I don't do it now,
Well, I'll never be able
to go any further!