I'm not gonna beat
around the bush here.
I want you to be
a part of my crew!
Word on the street is
that Kisara's people
have been causing
you problems lately.
And from what I hear, they're
plannin' to take you down.
I'm here 'cause I wanna
offer you protection.
if you join me and my gang those
punks'll never touch you again!
So, whadda ya say?
I could really use a guy
like you on my team.
I'll take good care
of you, I promise.
I don't understand, what exactly
do you want from me?
Isn't it obvious?
A man's true value is determined
by the number of people
he's in command of. I'm gonna
keep expanding my personal army,
so that in the end,
I'll be in charge
of the most powerful
group in Ragnarok!
And what do you plan on doing
after you've gotten to the top
huh? What about once you
graduate from high school?
You can't be a delinquent
forever you know.
Eventually you and
your thug friends
are gonna have to grow
up and get real jobs!
Come on, Boss, take it easy!
Just calm down, okay?
My men and I don't need
your clever logic.
There's no way you
could ever understand
that a man's greatest desire
in his life is freedom.
Everything that my men and
I do is about being free.
I can understand that,
but if you're harming people
to get your way
then that's not right!
You and your gang are
running around town
enjoying your "freedom", but
all you're really doing
is causing other people pain!
That's not freedom!
Don't you see?
That's tyranny!
I wish he wouldn't
say things like that.
It'll just make 'em madder!
You know I should probably
get this thing on tape.
I'm betting that he'll
want to see this later!
Let's go, bring it on!
Way to go, Kenichi!
Boss, are you gonna be okay?
Not bad, that one kinda stung.
You like that? Plenty more
where that came from!
Now it's my turn!
You're gonna pay for that kid!
Keep it up, Kenichi!
You're gonna bleed!
You're doing great, Kenichi,
don't give up on me yet.
Come on over
here, little buddy.
I'll give you one more good
shot right in the face!
Aw, what's the matter?
What are you chicken?
Come on, take your best shot!
What's the deal with this guy?
I knew you couldn't do it,
you're just a coward!
I'm no coward!
My hand!
I think he's hurt. it looks
like he's in trouble!
That one almost
knocked me out.
I even saw the punch coming!
Get up and fight me.
You call yourself a man, right?
Don't tell me that's
the best you can do!
I'm glad you haven't lost
your sense of humor.
I'm amazed you have the
strength to talk smack
after the beating
you just got.
So listen, why don't
you join my gang or,
I'm gonna have to
take you down!
I can't seem to
figure this guy out.
I should've been able
to beat him already,
but my attacks aren't
working at all.
I could really use some help!
I must say I'm a bit concerned.
I don't think Kenichi
is strong enough to
face this guy yet.
Skill is only part
of the equation.
A fighter gains a certain knack
with years of experience.
And no amount of talent or
training can stand up to that.
Then, what are we waiting
for, he needs our help!
Let's give him a chance!
Kenichi...
Is that really all
you've got, kid?
I expected so much
more out of you!
Hey!
Hm?
Who said the fight was over?
I don't remember quitting!
Cause I'm just
getting warmed up!
You really got
some guts kid.
If you keep impressing me,
I might actually start
respecting you as an opponent!
And since you've almost
earned my respect,
I don't have to hold back!
He's swinging big!
I can do this!
I'm losing my balance!
I've got to get my footing back!
Damn it! What now?
That was a mistake!
This fighting by the book will
get you nowhere with me.
It's not a formula.
A fight's only about one thing.
It's about your instinct!
Nailing up another one
of your dolls, I see?
Uh, yes.
We need luck.
'Cause Apachai got a horrible
feeling earlier today.
Apachai picked up the
stuff that Miu asked him to,
then felt worried
for Kenichi.
This time he knows
it's for real.
Yes but Shigure, you
know how Hayato feels.
It's for Kenichi.
He'll understand.
But what I mean is--
It's okay. It's just
a few nails. Only 100.
Apa!
Lucky nail number one!
Keep Kenichi safe, lucky nail!
I'll leave you to it then.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Thank you.
Apachai, that had better
not be you again!
Apa?
I swear, if you're pounding more
nails into my pine trees--!
Well, you're pretty good at
taking a beating aren't ya?
You punk!
We've gotta do something!
He can't handle this!
Give him time!
You 'bout ready
for a break, kid?
I'm not really
feeling that tired.
If you need a break,
let me know!
Why don't you shut your
mouth? Nobody's allowed
to talk to me like that! I will
tear you limb from limb!
What the heck do you
mean "limb from limb"?
Do I look like a tree to you?
Keep it up, I'll show you how
much of a man I really am!
Wha--? For someone who's losin',
you sure like to talk smack.
I hope you can back
it up, you little punk!
Oh? Why don't you come
over here and find out
whether I can back it up?
Who knows, I might surprise ya!
I can't believe he's
still standing.
No one's lasted this
long with the boss.
He's got guts, but if
he keeps smartin' off,
he's just gonna
make things worse!
Tsuji won't put up with it
much longer, he'll kill him!
Nobody disrespects me!
My right hand's numb.
A punch won't work.
Kouho!
Haiho!
Wow, I can't believe it, he's
using the stepping method
I taught him at the beginning!
Not bad!
It worked!
He just missed his chance
to strike. It's over.
I have a feeling
he's lost this one.
So, you didn't really think
you were the only one
who knows how to take
a little pain, did you?
I hate to do this, but
you're being so stubborn
and refusing to
join my gang so,
I have no choice
but to take you out!
I think I'll start
with your leg.
Have you ever broken a bone?
No matter what I try,
nothing works against him.
After all those painful
hours of training...
It's all useless
against this guy.
I'm so sorry, everybody.
I'm so sorry.
That's it!
Not yet!
What are you talking
about? Are you crazy?
That guy is gonna break his leg!
Look at that!
Your fighting style hasn't
changed one bit has it?
You're still sloppy.
Why, you little!
I heard that you were
going after the kid.
So Kisara's got you doing
her grunt work, huh?
I knew that you'd do
whatever she said.
Doing a little recruiting?
Hey! This has nothin'
to do with you. Walk away!
You just raised your fist to an
executive member of Ragnarok!
You're totally out of line, man!
We have rules. There's no way
you're gonna get away with this!
Sorry, but that's
not my problem.
Guess you guys haven't
heard the news.
I quit the gang!
Hold it! You know the penalty
for quitting Ragnarok, right?
You get a "farewell beating"
from the whole gang!
Me and my boys are
gonna make sure
the only way you leave is
on your hands and knees, punk!
You're goin' down!
That does it!
It doesn't matter what you say,
I'm not walking away!
From now on if you mess with
him, you mess with me.
Not only did he save my life,
he saved my boxing career.
I owe him!
Your lethal left!
I thought it was busted!
Oh no. Let's just say my
arm's back in business.
So, unless you want me
to open up shop on ya,
how bout we postpone
the farewell beating?
That you...
...Takeda?
You're a lot heavier than
I thought you'd be.
Can barely hold you!
I'm...
...really sorry.
Stop him! Don't
let him get away!
Yes sir!
Look guys,
you might wanna reconsider this,
'cause I can crush your face
with one punch!
Later!
Why didn't you
guys do something?
The boxer was obviously
bluffing you idiots!
If his left hand was really
100% healthy, don't you think
he would've used
it from the get-go?
Come on!
Let's get him!!
That fool. He's just a
wannabe, that's all he is!
But he sure packs
one hell of a punch!
Kenichi, listen, you're uh,
a lot heavier than I expected.
Damn it! Those punks
are catching up to us!
Don't look back! Keep running!
He's so fast!
What's up with the old man?
Since Kenichi held his own
against your crazy boss,
I think he's earned a helping
hand from his sensei!
Help me! Help!
I'm gonna drown! I don't
swim, someone please help!
Oh my!
Our little secret.
Whaddya know! He
annihilated that bridge
with a simple kick!
He's just like Apachai,
he doesn't even know
his own strength!
I've been looking for
you all over Kenichi.
I wanted to say thanks for
everything that you've done!
Guess what Aksiame told me?
He said that if I give my hand
a little time to heal, I'll be
boxing in no time!
Oh man, I can hardly wait
to get back into the gym
and start training again!
You awake?
Thank goodness, he's awake!
Apa!
Where am I?
You're in the 3rd
circle of hell.
I can't believe you let
that delinquent punk
clean your clock like that.
I promise you this, the
training session we're about
to put you through's gonna make
you wish you were in hell!
Hey, guys just cut
him a little slack!
Kenichi stood up for himself and
did everything he could to win!
But he still lost!
Let me tell you what's
gonna happen to you now.
You're in way over your head.
Since you got your butt kicked,
everyone in the entire school
is gonna be comin' knockin',
lookin' for a
piece of Kenichi.
Your name's gonna be
spread all over town
by the end of the day
and there's nothin'
you can do to stop
what's coming at you.
Once rumor spreads that
this crazy haired guy beat you,
every single person that's been
too afraid to step up to you,
will take this opportunity
to take you down!
'Course now that you've
lost your first fight,
you're bound to keep losin'
over and over again.
True.
Many fighters aren't ever able
to break such a vicious cycle.
If only Apachai knew how
to count straight through
to 100, the good luck charm
might have worked out!
As senseis, we felt it was our
duty to warn you ahead of time,
so be careful,
and protect yourself.
More than careful.
We're not tryin' to scare you,
we just wanna give
you a head's up.
You'd better start watchin'
your back at school tomorrow!
But you are scaring me!
Oh I wouldn't worry about it
if I were you, you'll be fine!
Just avoid the dark alleyways!
You know, that really doesn't
make me feel any better,
in fact, now I feel worse.
Wait a sec, I don't
remember anything,
how did I get back here anyways?
Was I dreaming or did Takeda--
Yep.
You're lucky your friend
showed up when he did.
That guy was about
to break your legs!
Takeda rescued me?
When you face off
against an opponent,
you have to be ruthless.
A split second decision
can make all the difference
between winning and losing.
Remember this? The
moment you were certain
you had him beat, you
let your guard down!
Hey! How'd you get this on tape?
You were hiding in the
bushes the whole time,
and you didn't help me?!
Well uh...
Yes.
Well, I'd better go,
or I'm gonna be late.
I've gotta get to the club!
Okay then!
Try to be careful on
your way home, okay?
Remember, your wounds haven't
had a chance to heal yet!
Right!
I wonder if those guys are
really going to come after me
like everyone said?
Why are you sneaking
around Kenichi?
You scared the crap
out of me you jerk!
What's wrong with you?!
Take it easy there,
buddy I just wanna know
why you're sneaking around.
Why don't you mind
your own business?
That's right, I forgot!
I heard you got smacked around
by one of the Rangnarok guys!
That's a lie, where did
you hear that? Tell me!
And how many people
have you told?
Who would I have told?
The whole school knows!
Guys! Kenichi's here and
he's still kinda beat up
so if you're looking for
a chance to kick his butt,
now's the time to strike!
You shut up! Are you trying
to get me killed, idiot?
Excellent work, Niijima.
We finally found him!
I've heard a lot
about you, kid.
Word on the street
is your head's
getting too big for
your own good!
I wouldn't say that.
I'd say my head's just
about the right size!
Why Niijima?!
We're not best friends but I
didn't think you wanted me dead!
Come back here!
Hmph!
I have such high
expectations for him.
Can the bullied weakling
become the powerful hero?
Can he rise like a
phoenix from the ashes
and be triumphant over
the evil doers?
In all honesty I don't really
care what happens to anyone
else, not as long as
I stay entertained!
Gods, if you hear me,
rain down hell, fire, brimstone,
and suffering upon him!
What a freak!
Looks like your back's
against the wall!
Somebody messed up.
Running away isn't
an option this time!
Who says I was running? I wasn't
trying to escape you guys,
this was just part
of my strategy!
You actually think that being
cornered is a strategy?
What about getting attacked
from both directions?
'Course this was just
a happy accident.
This ain't fair.
There's three of you big fellas
and only one of my friend,
and he's injured.
That's pretty pathetic
if you ask me.
You're Takeda right?
I've heard of you.
I've got Kenichi's back, so if
you wanna get a piece of him,
then you're gonna
have to deal with me!
Go ahead and keep on
talking smack, you punk!
We know you left Ragnarok
so you don't have anyone
to back you up! we heard
they're coming for you, boxer.
If I were you, I'd worry
about my own problems
and keep my nose out of
other people's business!
I'm running out
of patience here.
Are we gonna do
this thing or what?
You're lucky we're lettin' you
off the hook this time, boxer!
Oh, man.
Don't worry about those guys,
they're just a bunch of losers!
Uhm...
I really don't know
what to say.
Thank you so much for
bailing me out again.
It's no big deal. I
owe you big time, kid.
I could stick up for you every
day for the rest of my life
and I would still
be in your debt!
They say my hand's
gonna be fine.
I'm okay'ed to get back into the
gym first thing next month!
Are you serious?
Congratulations, man!
That's awesome!
I've got you to thank.
My career would've been over
if it weren't for you
and your sensei.
Hey, but listen,
'Got a reputation to uphold
so try not to get beat up.
You were the guy who beat me.
If you lose, it makes us both
look like a couple of chumps!
Yeah, sorry about that.
For some reason I
totally lose confidence
whenever I have to face
up to a thug like him.
Hold it!
Oh man, this is not good!
What's up, Ukita?
Hey Takeda. I just heard.
So you decided to quit
Ragnarok and become a boxer?
Yeah.
Come on, you guys are friends,
it's not worth fighting!
To tell ya the truth I've
never really thought
you belonged with us. You
always seemed kinda different
from me and the other guys.
And now I've finally figured out
why you felt so out of place!
Deep down, you've never
been a delinquent.
You're a boxer!
A true sportsman
belongs in the ring!
I'm glad to hear that your left
arm is workin' for ya again.
I'll try to buy ya as much
time as I can with Ragnarok.
but if I were you,
I'd start training.
See ya, Takeda the Puncher!
See ya 'round,
Ukita the Thrower!
You're lucky to have
a friend like him.
He's nothing like my
traitorous alien friend!
Ah-choo!
Someone must be
talking about me.
Attention! I would
like to begin
the Ryozanpaku summit
meeting at once!
It would be nothing short of
a disgrace to the martial arts
to allow Kenichi to
carry on this way.
We've been far too
easy on the boy
and I am recommending
that this change at once!
I'd like to propose a new
approach that will take
his training to the
next level of intensity!
I call it...
"Phase Two: Transform into a
Real Fighter or Die Trying!"
Yay! Self-sacrefice!
That's what I'm talkin' about!
So, how do we go about
executing this new initiative?
It's simple.
First, we force the boy
to move into Ryozanpaku.
After that, we
infuse martial arts
into each aspect of his life.
Once he's reached
the point of exhaustion, martial
arts will be his only solace!
We make him recognize
that he is nothing
but a product of martial arts!
He'll live martial arts
and breathe martial arts,
until he comes
to the fork in the road
where he has
only two options before him!
Martial Arts or death!
It's genius. We'll force
Kenichi to become a resident
of Ryozanpaku and then
bend him to our will!
That is correct!
Finally!
We can stop playing games
and begin the real training!
Ah-choo!
Man, this sucks.
I just got the chills.
You catching a cold?
You better not get me sick!
What the--
How'd you get in here and why
are wearing my pajamas?
Oh whatever, it's not
that big of a deal.
Your pjs are just
more comfy than mine!
I don't care if they're comfy
or not they're mine, got it?
Now go change and give 'em back!
You're gonna catch a cold!
You big stupid head!
I don't wanna wear your
smelly pjs anyway!
I'm gonna go change!
Great! Now I'm gonna have
to wash the girl off of 'em!
Shut your face!
Fine! I'm just gonna keep 'em!
Give me back my pajamas! Mom!
That's it for
today's training.
It's not good to push
yourself too hard, you know?
You've gotta be kidding me!
We just started!
How are you feeling?
Does it hurt anywhere?
Are you in any pain?
Because if you are, I'll be sure
to take care of that right away.
Why is everybody being so
nice to me all of a sudden?
Something's up. What's
going on with around here?
Are you guys
plotting something?
Tell me!
You see, starting tomorrow
you're going to come here
to live and start
your special training.
It wouldn't be
fun for anyone
to hurt yourself before
that, would it?
What are you guys talking about?
I don't wanna live here!
I didn't sign up for this!