Begin!
Apaaa!
Apaaaaa!
Aaa-papapapapapapa!
Aapaaaaa!
Aapaa!
They should've asked if
they could use my statues.
What exactly are they doing,
other than making a big mess?
Well, It was supposed to be
an exercise in self-restraint.
Hate to say it, but I
don't think its working.
Tch!
Stupid, stupid!, Apachai don't
know how to not kill opponent!
My fists won't
listen to my brains!
Hey, look.
Apa?
It lives! Apachai
didn't kill it to death!
I did it!
This is the first time I
haven't made broken pieces
of everything in my way!
I can now teach Kenichi
Muay Thai without killing him!
Apaaa!
Why don't we take Miu
to see a movie, I mean,
that'd be a good way to get
to know her, don't ya think?
What, with both of us?
Hey. You seen
Kenichi Shirahama around?
It's the Take-Down Trio
from Ragnarok!
Heh. Hey did ya hear that?
We're celebrities now.
Then they should know what I'll
do to 'em if they don't answer.
But we-we don't even
talk to that guy!
It's true! We don't
know where he is,
he always runs off and
disappears during lunch!
That's very noble of you to
try and protect your buddy.
Thing is, "noble" starts
to hurt real quick.
Are you protecting him?
What's wrong with you?!
We're talking to
freaking Ragnarok,
of course I'm not
covering for him!
Seriously, I swear to you,
I don't know where he is!
You think I'm dumb enough
to believe that he could just
vanish like that
without anyone noticing?
Don't treat me like
I'm stupid, kid.
We've tried to
follow him before,
but he always gives us the
slip and disappears somehow!
It's true! He and this girl
Miu always take off together!
Hey, I know that girl!
She wears a purple leotard,
She looks sweet and innocent,
She's built like a supermodel
but she's a monster in disguise!
That, doesn't, sound like Miu...
Miu has braids
and wears glasses.
Really? You're telling me this
guy has two girlfriends?
Like I needed another
reason to kick his teeth in.
Your voice is getting in the way
of me telling you to shut up.
Ukita? You think
he's here somewhere?
I've got you now!
Check it out.
I figure he's trying to hide
right beneath our noses.
The hell is that?
This guy's got a serious pair
trying to mock us like this.
Your face! Ukita...
You got all worked up
over a stupid doll!
Way to go tough guy!
Am I missing something or
is Takeda the only person
who thinks this is funny?
That punk's gonna pay.
No one humiliates me
and gets away with it!
Where is it?
Well, that's weird. I hope
I didn't drop it somewhere.
What's wrong, did
you lose something?
Yeah, Apachai made me
this weird voo-doo doll
and told me to keep
it in my backpack.
The whole idea of any kind of
voo-doo really creeps me out
but he said that
it would protect me.
He's actually a pretty
nice guy, y'know?
Yeah, I've gotta agree with you.
He's one of the nicest
guys that I've ever met.
He just doesn't know how
to control his own strength.
Man, this sucks.
How much longer am I gonna
have to sneak around like this?
You just need a
little more training.
Once you're able to show
those bullies who's boss
you'll be able to relax.
Hold on, so you're saying
I can't relax 'til I've
fought every bully in school?
Yup, that about sums it up.
They haven't been able
to find us up here yet
so you can relax a little.
This training is starting
to wear me out.
Miu?
Stop, Miu, please!
Niijima?!
Well, your hair-trigger reflexes
are on the mark, as usual.
You can run, but you
can't hide, Kenichi.
Well, I wouldn't have
to hide if people like you
would just mind your
own freakin' business!
Every time I get Miu
alone, he shows up.
There are severe implications
to my discovery of
your hiding place.
If I can find you,
so can Ragnarok.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Are you their spy or something?
I'm not a spy,
I just work the angles.
But I recommend you
find a new hiding spot.
Information's a valuable
commodity and this hiding place
of yours should fetch me plenty
of worthwhile intel in return.
Don't worry, though. You'll
be long gone and safely hidden
in some new spot by the time
they come looking for you.
This con should work a few more
times before they catch on.
Wow, I guess you really do know
how to work the
angles, don't you.
Let's get out of here, Miu!
There's no need to hang around
and listen to this alien freak.
Don't get too close to him you
don't wanna catch any evil.
Leaving so soon? And I thought
you'd want to hear the latest
information on Ukita the thrower
and Takeda the Puncher.
What kind of info?
Come on, spill it.
I would if you asked me nicely.
Please tell me the info.
Say 'pretty please,
Great God Niijima'.
Pretty please,
Great God Niijima, tell me now!
Kiss my shoe.
Oh, wow!
This must be that "male bonding"
I've heard so much about.
Alright, then.
This fellow here is
Ukita Kozo. He was expelled
due to his highly competitive
and aggressive nature.
His specialty is
the shoulder throw,
which he used on a
teacher who flunked him.
Technically, his fighting
index is around 80,
while yours--
you're just around 62.
In other words,
you don't stand the slightest
chance against this guy.
Come on,
you can't rate a fighter's
ability with statistics.
I'm so proud of him.
He's finally getting it!
Yeah, yeah. But the
worst of your worries
is another senior, Takeda Ikki.
Not only is he ruthless, but
he's a former lightweight boxer.
He's a boxer?
Yep, he's a professional
fighter. Word is he was
the premiere rookie til he
dropped out of the league.
What's a guy like that doing
fighting for Ragnarok?!
How should I know that? What
makes any man give in to evil?
It happens all the time. No
matter the 'cause, you know
the effect, and that's all you
should be concerned with.
What do I do?
There's only one option!
All of that running he did
with Akisame's paying off.
I wish he wasn't running away,
but you've gotta
start somewhere.
Geronimo!
They look so intense!
What are they doing?
--Now rock!
--Paper!
--Scissors!
--Go!
Oh man, this is the
most extreme game
of Rock, Paper, Scissors
that I've ever seen!
There goes my
theory of strategy.
Yeah.
Apachai just stuck his
hand out without thinking.
Apachai never won
paper hand game before!
If you guys hadn't kept
changing your hands
this wouldn't
have happened!
I'm glad you're
having a good time,
but I'm in some serious
trouble over here!
We weren't just playing
some stupid game, moron!
We were trying to
decide which one of us
is stuck with training
your scrawny ass next.
You're playing
Rock, Paper, Scissors
to decide who's gonna train me?!
Uh Sakaki...
I thought we had agreed
to keep that our secret.
Kenichi! Apachai the lucky
one to train you next!
Don't worry, Kenichi.
Muay Thai is extremely effective
in competitive fighting.
It'll definitely help
you against that boxer.
A boxer? That's quite a dilemma.
Uh yeah...
That's why I'm
freaking out right now.
Well, assuming you only have
a short amount of
time to prepare,
Muay Thai's your
most reliable option.
Is that true, Apachai? If
I start learning Muay Thai,
do you think I'll
be able to beat him?
Of course you can!
Muay Thai is the only
way to kill a boxer!
I should trust him.
Through all my failures he's
continued to believe in me.
He trusts me, so
I'm gonna trust him.
Just try and take
it easy on me, okay?
Of course I will!
I'll take it easy on you
as the mountains are high
and the oceans are deep!
The statue didn't die
so you won't either!
What statue?
Okay, Apachai, you're
kinda hurting my hands--
you can let go now.
Kenichi! Are you ready?
Uh, yeah...
Ready as I'll ever be.
Muay Thai is the art
of bare hand man killing.
It'll help you kill
your way out of any fight!
Um, but...
I just wanna learn how to
defend myself against a boxer...
You think about
complicated stuff like that
after your opponent is dead!
Use your thinking for killing
or it'll get you killed!
That was my impersonation
of my master!
So, were you scared?
I'm starting to have
second thoughts about this.
Apachai, before getting
into technique training,
why don't you explain the
history of Muay Thai first?
Well, it was invented
for killing people.
Knock it off with the
killing talk, will ya?
Muay Thai is an ancient
martial art that was originally
developed to train soldiers
in the protection of the
Siamese Kingdom, before
they became known as Thailand.
Wow...
I believe that's what
Apachai meant to say.
Yes, that is what
Apachai meant!
It sounds like it was created
as a very practical
means of defense.
That's right! My master would
tell me story from long ago
when king called Nareswan
was captured by soldiers
of his enemy. But they told
him that if he could defeat
their strongest soldier,
they would let him free.
But not only did he feat
best fighter, he also beat
all their soldiers and
returned to his country.
And he beat them
all using Muay Thai!
That's awesome! Okay, I'm sold!
I wanna learn, please teach me!
Great! I first teach
you Tan Guard Muay!
So, what is this
Muay Guard Tan thingy?
Tan Guard Muay!
It is the basic
stance of Muay Thai.
Like this, right?
That's it! Now...
Tee Sok.
The use of knees and elbows are
very important in Muay Thai.
Which, in fact, is rather rare
as most contemporary martial
arts have banned the use
of knees and elbows
in tournament fighting.
Really? How come?
If you use them wrong you
can kill your opponent.
That's right.
However, in Muay Thai,
they specifically focus
on these moves.
Yeah? And why's that?
Because, if you use them right
you can kill your opponent.
There's too much killing
in this martial art!
You're never gonna be
a man acting like this.
All martial arts are
built upon the premise
of conquering your opponent.
Misused, any of them can become
simply a means for violence.
Their lethal nature is basically
a question of conscience.
Question of conscience?
If one has chooses to use it
for his own selfish desires,
then it becomes nothing
more than brutish violence.
However, if you genuinely intend
to use it to protect yourself
and others, and only when it's
necessary, then even the most
lethal martial art
can be honorable.
You must look deep into your
heart and ask yourself:
do you want your skills to bring
misfortune and pain to others?
No, of course not!
Then you have nothing
to fear from Muay Thai.
It's not the technique
that harms others,
it's the desire in
one's heart to do so.
Now carry on with your training.
Right!
Apa!
What's the deal, Kisara? You
sure are taking your sweet time
trying to recruit new fighters.
This thing is gonna go down
any day now and you're actin'
like it's no big deal.
Shut up, Tsuji.
This isn't a joke, Kisara!
We need a crew of tough
guys ASA freakin' P!
I told you to shut up.
You got my character killed.
Y'know the problem here?
It's him! None of this
would be happening if
you'd let me run things
instead of that boxer--
Hey Kisara! We just found
out that Shirahama kid's
been hiding on the
school roof during lunch.
Give us one more day
and we've got him.
Hey. What's your
problem, lightweight?
You not gonna say hello
to an executive member?
I could've sworn I said
'hey Kisara' when I came in.
You gotta respect
your higher-ups.
You may not work
for me directly,
but I'm an executive member
and you're just a grunt.
Say hello, punk.
I said hello to the
one who matters.
Oh yeah? You really think
you're pretty slick, don't you?
You sure are jumpy, I was
just stretching my arm.
Oh, by the way,
do you need this?
It's the button
from your sleeve.
No thanks I've got plenty.
Not bad, lightweight.
But y'know somethin'.
Just 'cause you're
fast doesn't mean
you can save
yourself in a fight.
Damn it!
If my character
dies one more time,
then you're all dying with him!
Alright, Kenichi! You're
doing basic moves great!
I think you're ready to move on.
Let's practice
with punching next!
Sure!
C'mon, shoot me with
your best hit!
I guess Apachai really did
learn how to restrain himself.
He doesn't seem to be as
crazed as he was before.
What's the matter, Kenichi?
Come on, I can take it!
Punch me with all you got!
I don't care how scared
you may be Kenichi--
you're not allowed
to cop a feel!
My fight or flight
instinct took over.
It told me it was time
for flight. I'm sorry.
What's wrong, Kenichi? Apachai
thought punching was fun?
If it's not fun,
you just hit harder!
Are you sure? You're
positive you can hold back?
You make me so sad!
The statue didn't die!
Apachai try so hard! I practice
so much to control strength,
but I can do nothing
right! I lose confidence.
I can't do it
anymore, I give up!
No way! um...
I was joking, Apachai!
I can't wait to
do some punching!
Really?!
Now you see! Hitting
isn't scary, it's fun!
Yeah! It really, is, fun!
Now, you try to dodge one!
What?
A-pa pa pa pa!
--Ohhhh.
--Kenichi!
You almost kill the kid,
and all you can say is 'oh'?
Please, wake, up!
Oh, dear, did he finally do it?
It looks like it.
Apachai held back, I promise!
My fists were
light as a feather,
I barely even touched him!
Hey guys, I think
he killed Kenichi!
Calm down, I'm sure he's fine.
With all the training
he's been through,
a single punch wouldn't--
Begin cardiac compression!
One two three four...
One two...
Whoa, where am I?!
See? It was nothing
to worry about.
What's wrong with you, people?!
Yay, Apachai!
Let's all climb on Apachai!
Can you throw me in
the air and catch me?
Sure! But I have to feed
the pigeons first, okay?
Come on, pigeons! Eat up!
Oh wow!
You're like a tree
to those pigeons!
Man, that guy.
Kids and animals just
can't get enough of him.
Hey, Apachai?
Is there something wrong?
You don't look very happy.
I'm sorry, Apachai's
thinking about
a tiny big mistake
he made yesterday.
It's tiny and big
at the same time?
That doesn't make sense!
Apapapapapa!
It doesn't, does it?
It was tiny because it was hard
for me to see what I did wrong.
Cheer up, Apachai, it's okay.
Yeah! You're right,
I'm happy now!
No more being sad for me,
let's go play tag!
Yay! Apachai, you're the best!
Well, looks like I've
managed to go another day
without getting into
a meaningless fight.
Yeah.
I think the equipment
shed is the perfect place
for us to eat lunch from now on.
Those Ragnarok guys will
never find us there!
It's the last place
anyone would look.
Kenichi never
ceases to amaze me.
I can't believe he's
in such a good mood
after what happened yesterday.
I guess I don't give
him enough credit.
Maybe he's tougher
than I thought he was.
Now where's Apachai?
I'm ready to roll!
You sure, Kenichi?
I can't wait to get started!
I mean, he taught me so much
yesterday that I can
hardly remember it all!
But you almost--
A-pa pa pa pa!
Do you really think
it's a good idea?
I think it's a great idea!
It's not like I can stop now!
There's so much to
learn! I've just begun!
How could he
forget almost dying?!
A temporary loss of memory,
probably from the concussion.
Don't worry,
happens all the time.
What do you mean temporary?!
It's been a whole day
since it happened!
Akisame!
Hm?
I think that you
need to give Kenichi
a thorough physical exam!
Really, why's that?
Because he has
absolutely no memory
of what happened
to him yesterday!
I guess we dodged that lawsuit.
Hey! I'm worried about him!
I was just kidding.
Believe it or not, Miu,
memory loss is pretty common
in the world of martial arts.
I checked him out
yesterday, though.
He's only slightly concussed.
You're sure?
Would you two quit yappin'?!
I'm more interested in
what Apachai's doing
than your medical concerns.
Just be happy the kid's alive.
Come on and fight already!
I can't believe these people.
Apapapapapa!
I'm afraid that's still too much
Aapaa! Why am I so stupid?
I try so hard but
I can't do it!
Apachai put all of his strength
into trying to hold back,
but his punches
are still too strong!
Listen to me Apachai,
You tend to spend
your afternoons playing
with the children in the
neighborhood park, don't you?
Apachai get along with
everybody especially kids.
I'd like you to try this.
When teaching Kenichi,
try not to think of it
as martial arts training.
Try to pretend that you're
playing with the kids
in the park instead.
Where are you Apachai?!
I don't get it, why is he so
hard to find all of a sudden?
Normally the big lug would be
forcing me to train with him
whether I like it or not.
Hey, Shigure, have you
seen Apachai around?
Yeah, he's over there.
Cool, thanks.
We're gonna do some
more punching practice.
Before you do...
Wear this.
What? Why do you want
me to wear that thing?
It's to protect your brain from
being knocked out your mouth.
That's really nice of
you to offer but, um...
Gotta go see ya later!
The more I get to know her
the more she freaks me out.
Hey, Apachai!
I promise to hold back
with all my might!
Right! Whoa, total déjà vu.
This seems strangely
familiar for some reason.
Come on! Let's get to punching!
Kenichi...
You had better not
be cheating old man.
Oh!
Yeah!
There you go!
And when you get closer,
you go to grab for my neck!
You can do it!
C'mon Kenichi! Finish it off!
Watchin', old man? Don't know
if your advice is gonna hold,
he's starting to get
that look in his eye.
Everything's fine, just fine...
For as long as he can remember,
Apachai has risked his life
fighting ruthless opponents
in the underground
Muay Thai circuit.
He's unable to control
his strength because
any sign of restraint would
have gotten him killed.
Despite this, there is a true
gentleness within him.
That is the defining
quality of his nature.
Yeah, I think you might
actually be on to something
with that one. He's easily
the most carefree person
I've meet in my entire life.
It's nice to see that you care
for your friend so deeply.
What are you two talking about?
Hey! Watch it gramps!
You must be going senile!
Sakaki won't admit it, but he
came to see me this afternoon
with a very concerned
look on his face.
Old man! You've gotta do
something about Apachai.
I've never seen him so
greatly distressed before.
I told you to keep
quiet about that!
I didn't ask for your help
because I was worried about
him or anything like that.
It's just that...
Weird as it sounds, my sake
just doesn't taste right
unless I can hear his laughter.
That's the only reason I asked.
Come on, Kenichi, you
can do faster than that!
Now try to dodge this one!
Try to pretend
that you're playing
with the kids in the park.
Apa?
Whoa-ho... You scared me
there, that was a fast one!
I thought I was a goner!
That punch was so fast
I didn't even see it!
In that case, watch
your opponent's shoulder
and guess the speed.
Okay!
Oh wow! He learned how to
hold back, that's so great!
I'll look for an opening and
throw in some punches as well.
Mitt practice is pointless
unless you practice
dodging with it.
Right!
Okay, start punching!
C'mon, faster!
Try harder!
You can do it!
I think you can
relax now, Shigure.
Now it's time you have to dodge!
Okay!
Apapapapapapapapa!
Oh no...
Kenichi!
Oh!
Oh, Kenichi, I'm so so sorry!
I don't know what happened!
I couldn't control my knee--
Could be worse...
At least his hands
are under control now.
We'll just need to focus on
his knees from here on.
Back to the playground, I guess.
Hey, this is no laughing matter.
Calm down, Sakaki,
he's still breathing.
What are you talking
about, look at him!
Apa.
I tried to warn him.
Well, Kenichi, I'm afraid
you've met your match,
and you're probably gonna
meet your maker as a result.
Your next opponent
is Takeda Ikki,
a former professional boxer.
A single punch from him
and you'll be down for
the count, permanently.
What do I do?
What do I do?!
This guy's a former professional
who does it for fun now?!
There's no way I can beat him!
Calm down, Kenichi, you
don't wanna let stress
ruin the last few
days of your life.
In fact if it'll make
you feel better,
I'll deliver your body
to the morgue myself.
If I can use the techniques
Apachai taught me,
then I just might have
a shot at beating him!