Apachai's not hiding in here,
this room is empty.
Please go away now.
Apa!
I saw the giant again!
He's hiding in the bathroom!
I apologize for her behavior.
It's her first home visit,
and I think she's a bit nervous.
Don't worry. Really.
Yes, but how about
we put an end to this.
Why don't you go ahead
and come clean with me?
You're not Miu's
mother, are you?
She's clumsy, doesn't
like to be alone,
worries about what
other people think,
and tends to be scatterbrained,
but she's a really good kid.
She was afraid you
wouldn't understand
if she told you the truth.
Try not to be too hard on her,
she didn't mean any harm.
I caught him, Yasunaga!
I caught the giant!
I told you he was real!
I'm not crazy!
Kenichi!
What's going on here?
Don't tell me you're the one
that's been living
together with Miu!
No, no, it's not
what you think it is!
Yes, where living together, but
we're not "living together"!
You idiot!
What do you think
"living together" means?!
Oh, my. Am I seeing this?
Oh, c'mon!
Why did I have
to pick this room?!
Uh, are you okay sir?
I've never seen anything
like this before.
As a history teacher, I've
devoted my life to the study
and appreciation
of Japanese culture.
But this is the most magnificent
collection I've seen.
So he isn't living
with Miu, he's merely
residing here as a pupil?
I had no idea this was a dojo.
And I never would have
guessed it was the dojo
of the grand master.
I'm sorry for screaming
and jumping on your back.
And I'm sorry for bursting
through walls with you.
Despite the misunderstanding,
it's been an honor.
We are honored as well.
It's always a privilege to
meet one of Miu's teachers.
Please understand our disciples
were looking out for Miu.
They're a little misguided,
but please forgive them.
And Kenichi.
I'd noticed that you've
seemed more confident lately,
though I couldn't figure out why
But now I think I understand.
You've been training to
become a great artist.
I have to admit,
I'm quite impressed!
I might as well
let him think that.
Thanks for the work-out!
I needed that!
Did you find the
location of our target?
Yessir!
Excellent! Then the
time has finally come!
Ryozanpaku's going down today!
Having problems are we, Kenichi?
You haven't even landed
a single punch yet!
Hey! It's not for
lack of trying!
I just can't find any openings!
"Can't find any openings?"
Are you even looking
at your opponent?
Of course!
It's almost impossible to attack
and defend at the same time,
even for the greatest
martial arts masters.
Well, don't just stand
there! Do something!
If you don't attack,
you'll never score a point!
I can't! You block everything!
In a prolonged fight, your
opponent will eventually tire,
let their guard down,
and reveal an opening.
Oh, man!
An opening! Finally!
If I strike her now,
I'll score a point!
But, should I? What if I miss?
You shouldn't have hesitated!
I was wide open!
She's right, you know.
You blew a perfect opportunity.
And a real opponent would never
make an opening for
you like Miu just did!
Wait?! She did it on purpose?!
She did it on... purpose.
I never had a shot.
She thinks I'm pathetic.
A weenie. A loser.
Lower than a dog.
This is the worst
stinkin' day of my life!
Hey! Why did you
tell him I did that?!
For a martial artist,
there's nothing more dangerous
than being overconfident
with their ability.
Thanks to you, he would have
thought he was stronger
than he really was.
Oh, I hope I didn't hurt
Kenichi's feelings too badly.
I'm so stupid.
Love these new shoes!
See ya later!
Are you going to the dojo?
Yep!
Wow!
Did someone say "dojo?"
What a coincidence!
I've been meaning to stop by
and say hello to the masters!
I'll go with you, sweetheart!
Ahem, Honey?
Is there a reason why you're
wearing a heavy coat...
...in summer?
What?! Summer?
A-Already? I had no idea!
Time sure does fly by
quickly! It seems like
we were celebrating
New Years yesterday!
Having some bubbly,
making resolutions,
and bundling ourselves up in
long overcoats to protect us
from winter's icy chill!
Then what's in your coat?!
If you're going, you're
leaving Sebastian here!
Gotta go! Bye!
Honoka, wait, sweetie!
Don't you need a ride?
Daddy will give you one!
Oh, no, you won't!
Uh, thanks, Dad,
but I've already got a ride,
and it's a fast one!
Apa!
Hey!
That was quick!
Apachai was over at the park,
playing with the
pigeons just now!
Get away from my daughter,
you monster!
Maximilian, come forth!
Say hello to my little friend!
My second favorite
shotgun, Maximillian!
Now back away from my
daughter, or you're gonna--
Huh?
You have fun, dear! Just be
back by dinner time, okay?
Mom, why do you always
treat me like a baby?!
All my friends
have later curfews!
Let's go!
Hi-yo, Apachai, away!
Mom! You don't worry!
Apachai and Honoka will
be back for dinner!
Uh, wh-why thank you.
A-pa!
Apapapapapapa!
Pa! Pa!
Well, he gives new meaning
to the word "jumpy".
Man! It's not enough
I get exhausted in every
training session, but almost
every time I go to my room!
Why aren't there any stairs
in this part of the dojo?
I'll tell you.
Oh, uh, Master Koetsuji.
One night a few years ago,
Sakaki and Kensei got drunk.
What are these things? Stairs?
A true master doesn't need
stairs, do they Kensei?!
No way! Only a weakling
would need stairs!
Do we look like weaklings?
Say goodbye, dumb stairs!
You'll never darken this
part of our dojo again!
For some reason, they took
out their aggression
on a defenseless flight of
stairs and demolished them.
You don't say.
I thought about rebuilding
them, but then I decided
that putting a rope here would
provide a much better work-out.
Master! Wait!
I need to talk to
you about something!
What am I gonna do?
I really need to
talk to someone.
It's open. Come on in.
I will. Than--
Hey, what gives?
This thing's so heavy!
What's all the racket out here?
Is there something
I can help you with?
And then...
Wait. Let me get this straight.
She gave you an opening,
but you still couldn't hit her?
Yeah. Do you have any idea why?
Ah, nope.
Um, couldn't you at least
give it some thought?
Geez kid.
What do I look like,
a shrink or something?
Why don't you go annoy Akisame
and see if he can tell you?
He's gone. I'd ask Master Ma,
but he's not here, either.
Well, since I'm the
sole voice of wisdom
I guess I'll give it a stab.
Ya see there's people out there.
Scared people. Sometimes
they can't attack
because they're afraid of their
opponent's counterattack.
Say they're lined up to deliver
a finishing blow right,
and they start to wonder "what's
gonna happen me if I miss?"
This causes them to hesitate
and instantly puts them
at a disadvantage.
That's never been a problem
for me because I don't hesitate.
The first opening
I get, I take it.
He's right.
Now that I think about it, I was
afraid of her counterattack.
Kenichi. A man's worth is
determined by whether or not
he can strike a blow
at the critical moment.
If he doesn't strike,
he's going to get crushed.
Right!
Apapapapapa!
Apa! Apa!
Nice pitch, son! You're
getting really good at this!
Now let's see your fast ball.
Huh?
Hey! There's Shigure!
Cool!
Here it comes!
Do you wanna play with us?
Uh, sure.
Come on! Let's
see that fastball!
So, what game should
we play today? Any ideas?
Let's play cards!
Oh no!
Dad! Did you see that tall
man jump from the sky?
Son, if you keep
imagining things,
you're gonna have to
back to the psychiatrist.
There was a lady with a
mouse on her head, too!
A man's worth is determined
by whether or not
he can strike a blow
at the critical moment.
If he doesn't stike,
he's crushed.
Since I didn't strike
because I was afraid
of Miu's counterattack,
I must be totally worthless.
Why do I have to
be such a loser?
Open up in there!
I said open up!
Who could that be?
Now!
We're here to see
this dojo's masters!
Uh, can I tell them
who's calling, sir?
Tell them Shiken
Odori dojo's here.
And its master...
The great and terrible
Gonzai Kumatori!
And...
...your reason
for coming? Sir?
Oh, that's a simple one, boy!
We've come to challenge
Ryozanpaku and take its sign!
Miu! Miu! Where are you?
We've got big trouble!
Some guys are here
to challenge the dojo!
Really? Cool. No problem.
Whaddya mean no problem?
There's a big, scary,
musclebound guy in
Kabuki makeup out there,
and he's got henchmen
with him, too!
So it's a big group
of people then?
In that case, I'd better go
let them inside right away.
What?! Are you crazy?
We need some help now.
Hey wait! Master Sakaki!
Oh, he just left a few
minutes ago to buy some beer.
What?! Then we'll just get
one of the other masters,
like Apachai or Shigure!
Well actually, they're
not here, either.
They're on a playdate with
your cute little sister.
Akisame's busy at
his bone clinic...
Kensei's doing acupuncture...
And Grandpa's travelling
on business today.
Talk about your
busy schedules!
Looks like you and I are the
only ones home right now!
Are you kidding me? How come
they're always around when
you don't need them, but when
you do need them, they're gone!
It's not fair!
Come on! It's not polite
to leave guests waiting!
Please have some tea! I insist!
Master, no! Don't drink it!
She might've poisoned it!
No tea?
The only thing we're interested
in brewing is a fight!
You can dispense with
the pleasantries, girl!
We didn't come here
for a social visit!
Very well then, sir.
First, I'll need you to write
down your name, address,
and fighting style
in our register.
Then you'll need to read
and agree to this disclaimer
per our Elder's instructions.
Wha--
It says here that
each challenger
must pay a fee
of 10,000 yen!
Yes, and that's
10,000 per person.
If you all pay, you get
to attack us as a group!
Pay you?!
Are you nuts? Why, I oughta--
Stand down!
But, Master...
No, it's fine.
Thank you for your
business, sir! So, all of you
will be attacking us as a
group then, am I correct?
No, I will be the
sole challenger.
Huh?
There are many strong
fighters here at Ryozanpaku.
However, as a karate master,
it's only fitting
that I challenge this
dojo's karate master.
Therefore I demand to fight
the 100th degree street
fighter himself, Shio Sakaki!
Master Sakaki?!
Sorry, he's not
here right now.
The other masters
aren't either.
So then by default, you'll
just have to fight with me!
If that's alright, it'll
just take me a minute
to go get changed. Wait here
and I'll be back in a jiffy!
How dare you?!
You insolent little brat!
I came here to fight a master,
not some little girl!
What an insult!
No one mocks me like this
and gets away with it!
I'm going to make
you pay dearly!
Stop it!
So you want to play hide
and seek, eh, Sakaki?!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
Get away from her!
Do it! Now!
What the--
It's that puny kid from before!
What is this?
Some kinda joke?!
You shut up!
I'm First Disciple of
Ryozanpaku! Kenichi Shirahama!
And if any of you
lay a finger on her,
you're gonna have to
answer to me, got it?
That goes for you most
of all, Mr. Crab Head!
What? Crab Head?
Kenichi, get out of here!
That's twice now
I've been insulted!
It's time I taught you
little whelps a lesson!
You there! Bring
the bats out now!
Yes, sir!
See that? I'm gonna do
the same thing to you
I did to those bats!
Eep! Not good!
Ha! In the Shiken Odori
style, we forge our bodies
until they're tougher than
the hardest steel, punk!
Ha, ha! So are you
scared yet, kid?
You should be 'cause you're
going up against the master!
This is gonna be good!
Kenichi, let me handle this!
No, Miu! You stay back!
Huh?
I may not look like much,
But I'm First Disciple
of Ryozanpaku!
No, don't!
Die!
I see it!
It must be because I
deal with the masters'
superhuman speed every day!
But...
Being able to see it and
being able to dodge it
are two different things!
Oh, no! Kenichi!
Oh, man, this is bad!
My body can't keep up
with my eyes yet!
Well, boy. Have you
had enough yet?
You're not so mouthy
anymore, are you?
I guess Ryozanpaku's not
all it's cooked up to be.
All this time, it's
been called a legend
when it's really just a joke.
A bad one at that, too.
The masters here are idiots if
they chose a weakling like you
to be First Disciple.
Masters...
Hmph! And Sakaki's
legendary reputation!
It's probably exaggerated and
overblown as well to scare off
any real challengers
who might come along.
Speaking of challengers,
if there aren't any real ones
here for me to fight, we'll take
that sign and be on our way.
Hey, didn't you hear me before?
I said I'd fight you!
Cr-Crab Head!
You want a real challenge?
Fine, you've got one.
From me!
The First Disciple
of Ryozanpaku!
Hm. Managed to get up
after my kick, eh?
A weakling like you?
I'm actually impressed.
Must be dumb luck.
Heh Heh! Nope,
just good training!
All the masters here
have taught me well!
No. Not well enough obviously.
If think you can survive
another hit from me, kid,
you're crazy.
But since you have a
death wish, so be it.
In fact, I'll even let you
take the first punch.
It'll have no effect then you'll
realize how weak you are,
and that's when I
deliver the killing blow!
K-killing blow?!
Well, what are you waiting for?
Come on, kid, strike him!
Hah! I bet he's too
scared to do anything!
I'd be, too, 'cause the master's
counterattack'll kill him!
Oh, Kenichi...
This isn't good!
He's cracking under
the pressure!
Sometimes they're afraid to
attack 'cause they're afraid
of their opponent's
counterattack.
So you're not only a weakling,
but a coward, too, huh?
Huh?!
What the?!
He hit him?!
Kenichi saw an
opening and took it!
Master! Are you hurt?
Y-you sneaky little
snot-nosed punk!
You waited and struck
me right at the moment
I relaxed my stomach muscles!
Brilliant! One might be able
to strengthen their body
until it's as hard as steel,
but that means nothing
if they get struck when
their muscles are relaxed!
Kenichi, you're a genius!
Kenichi. A man's worth is
determined by whether or not
he can strike a blow
at the critical moment.
Time to die, punk!
Hey, buddy?
I heard you wanted
to challenge a master,
so why are you messin'
with our disciple?
Master! Th-that's
him! That's the guy!
The famous street fighter!
Yeah, that's Shio Sakaki!
You're Sakaki?!
Sure am. Now how
'bout that challenge.
L-let go! You're crushing
the bones in my wrist!
Hey, Kenichi.
I've been watching you take
care of our guests here.
That was a nice strike.
You barely hesitated at all.
Y-you mean you were here and
were watching this whole time?!
C'mon get a grip, it's okay!
You handled it perfectly!
So, Crab Head.
You helped our Disciple
learn a valuable lesson,
but now it's time for you
and your friends to go.
Ow! Kenichi, let go!
You're grabbing me too tight!
I can't breathe.
You're smashing my--
Geez. It's not
over already, is it?
Oh, man, you gotta
be kidding me.
And I thought Crab Head guy
was a ferocious fighter!
Master Sakaki makes him look
like a choir boy in comparison!
These guys have gotta be the
lamest bunch of challengers
I've ever faced in this dojo!
Apachai, when are we
gonna play some more?
Apa! After I do a
favor for Sakaki!
He asked me to take all these
people to Akisame's clinic!
We'll play when I'm done, okay?
Okay.
Apachai, why are all
these guys asleep?
What's wrong? Are they
sick or something?
Sakaki put them to sleep
because they have
lots of broken bones that
have to be reset.
It won't hurt if it's done
when they're asleep.
The only thing that will hurt,
is that Akisame is
going to charge them.
I get it. An arm
and a leg, right?
You're getting extra sake
thanks to what we made today!
Alright! Nice haul, huh?
And for your part,
you're getting an extra
special side dish!
You better guard your
plate good, kid!
All this butt kicking today
has made me hungry!
See ya!
So the dojo makes money
by taking on challengers
who pay to fight?
And then makes even more
by sending them
to Akisame's clinic?
Oh, man...
Hey, Miu! Drop what
you're doing! I've got big news!
We're all going to the beach!
To the beach? Wow, really?!
Yeah! The masters said
they're gonna take us!
In that case, I better go
buy a new swimsuit then!
The one from last year
has gotten too tight!
Huh? Too tight?
Oh, wow. Y-you mean you've, um,
filled out more in certain areas
over the last few months?
Oh, thank you, God!
Ah! Kenichi, your
nose is bleeding!
And you're starting to pass
out, too! What's going on?
Say something!
I can't wait to go to the beach!