[Music]
This is phenomenal!
Akisame, I can't thank you
enough for this massage chair-
it does a great job of
loosening up my tension.
It feels
absolutely amazing!
That's good...
Miu's wanted to get
you one for a while
but I knew I could
piece together
a custom chair for you-
I'm glad that you like it.
Little Miu...
I'm honored to have
such a great granddaughter
and such wonderful friends.
I think that you're
overreacting.
If you want me to go
faster don't you think you
should maybe lighten
the load a little??
Sorry Kenichi but training
for the double palm
is serious business......
Now quit whining
and go faster.
Don't forget...... make
sure your foot is making
full contact with
the treadmill-
that'll help build
up your back...
We've gotta get you to
start building up some
more muscle on your body
or you're never gonna be
much of a fighter.
How much longer do
I have to do this? !
Let's make it 2,000 reps.
2,000 reps? !
But you only made me
do 1,000 yesterday!
Well, we've gotta build up
your stamina some how...
Tomorrow we'll
do 5,000 reps
and the next day it'll be 10.
You've gotta be kidding!
Double each day? !
That's insane!
I'm already doing as much
as I can and you want more? !
Hang in there- you'll
be fine Kenichi...
What happened to that
determination
you had the other day??
That was before you
made me do this!
I'm gonna train so hard
that I break the floor!
And I won't give up...
Not until that happens!
I may have said
that before...
But my body's
gonna break down
long before I break
through the floor!
And that's what training
is all about, kid!
Anybody here??
I'm here to take
over your dojo...
You will surrender to me!
Oh, wow... a visitor.
I've got it...
I'll take care
of this one.
Kensei, wait!
Don't worry- it
won't take long.
Damn... He beat
me to it again.
What's wrong.....?...
I thought I told you
to pick up the pace!
How dare you mock me!
I'm not leaving until
I've defied your dojo!
Go ahead and give
it your best shot.
You idiot...
Here I am disgracing
your dojo
and you're not even
gonna challenge me??
I order you to bring
out the master
of your dojo
immediately !
I'm afraid you're going to
have to fight me instead...
The elder just got
back from a trip
and he's resting
inside, right now.
I was gonna let you off the
hook cause you're a shrimp
but now you've
pissed me off!
A shrimp?
Prepare to die!
And now... Double...... palm!
Uh-oh!
No.....!...
My power source!
Sorry... I got a
little carried away-
don't know my own strength.
Please be more
careful, Kensei.
Forgive me. I'll take him
straight over to your clinic.
I got him pretty good
so I'm sure he's gonna
have a hefty bill.
Kenichi... I'll fix this
thing as fast as I can...
Then we'll
continue training.
Isn't that great news? !
Akisame will
have you back up
and training in no time!
They're insane!...
Why can't I just
have a normal life??
Okay everybody,
it's snack time... ..!
I made you all
coconut jelly today.
Coconut jelly?
That sounds
pretty sweet...
Can I make rice
wine with it??
No, you can't.
Seconds please!
I only made one
for each of you.
Akisame, listen...
Do you think maybe you could
add a foot massager this time??
Definitely...
It'll add resistance and
pump up Kenichi's training.
Oh yeah.
Speaking of which,
where did Kenichi go??
50 thousand times,
100 thousand times,
a million times...
They're trying to kill me!
I ran here fast
as I could.
Did Kenichi
really come home? !
Yeah...
He's back home
safe and sound...
He said that he learned
everything there was to know
so the dojo
let him leave!
Yeah.....?... That's my boy!
I thought you were
handling a big business
deal in Osaka
tonight, dear.
You know what I always say-
don't sweat the small stuff...
Kenichi...... come
on downstairs...
I wanna see you!
Honey, tell me
what happened!
Did you just
up and leave??
Congratulations, son.
I'm proud of ya.
Honoka emailed me with the
good news and I came home
as quickly as I
possibly could.
I can't tell you how happy
I am to see ya, my boy.
There's no need
to cry, dad...
I can't tell him that
I chickened out
cause my training
was too hard.
Listen dear......
I hate to nag
but you finished
that meeting right??
Hey I know...
Why don't we go have sushi
tonight to celebrate??
Leave me alone
already.....!...
I gonna destroy
this thing!
That was your coworker,
wasn't it.....!..?
If you lose your job-
Anyway, Kenichi.....!... .
Tell me some wild
stories about the dojo!
Do you think we can do
that tomorrow, Dad.....?
I'm really tired.
Would you answer me? !
What happened with the
business deal.....?
Don't make me hit you!
Man... Now I've
really done it...
I wonder if Miu's
worried about me??
I can finally get some rest.
He ran away.....?...
Are you... sure??
But I wasn't even gone
for very long......
and you let him get away?
Where'd you go Shigure?
Lingerie shopping?
Public bath?
Any details you wanna
give I'll take 'em.
Apachai's sad
Kenichi's gone...
He left because you guys
made him do hard training.
Hey... It's not our fault.
What should we
do now.....?...
Do you think maybe I
should go by his house
and have a talk with him??
No, just leave him alone.
I'm sure, Kenichi will
come back when he's ready...
for now...... we'll wait
patiently for our disciple
to return to his masters.
Poor Kenichi...
Big brother, wake up!
What's up.....?...
What do you want??
Guess what.....?...
I met someone cool that
I wanna introduce you to!
I think you'll like him-
he's a martial arts master
just like you!
Are you talking about the
guy who rescued you
while we were out shopping?
I've heard enough
about him...
Dontcha think it's time
you find something else
to talk about??
Sorry but I've got more
important things
on my mind right now.
But I really wanted the
two of you to meet......
He's rich and he's
got a big house.
I think that he might even
be the same age you are...
Even though he kinda looks
mean when he fights.....
I think he's a
really nice guy!
I don't think he has
any friends cause
he's so scary looking
when he fights...
But he's cool and you
both do martial arts
so you should be friends!
I think it would
really cheer him up.
So will you go with me?
Pretty please? Come on!
Shut up.....!...
I don't have time to worry
about anyone else right now.....
Besides, why would I
wanna be friends
with some stupid
guy you met? !
Uh, Honoka...
You're an idiot,
big brother!
Honoka!
A-pa-a-a-a-a-a!
Hey! Watch out!
I'm sorry...... I can
be so clumsy sometimes.
Whatever... How many
vases does that make?
-That's three!
-And you're proud??
Don't worry,
I'll clean it up!
Hey wait!
I wanted my brother to
come with me today
but he's not in a
very good mood...
I don't know what his
problem is lately...
So I'm gonna see
if Apachai
and Shigure wanna
come with me.
I'm not in a good mood
either, you know......
How 'bout you
stop cleaning...
and don't bring anyone
else over here-
I'm having a hard enough time
getting you to leave midget.
I'm not a midget-
I'm just fun-sized.
Oh well, time
for the laundry.
Would you cut it
out already? !
I don't want your help.
I don't wanna
be your friend.
I just want you to leave!
Why do men always have
to be so dishonest??
I have to get ready for
training this afternoon...
So beat it, would
ya.....? I'm busy.
So what're you gonna do
once you get super strong??
I'll kill all the
people I don't like.
And what're you gonna do
after you've killed them??
I'll find more people I don't
like and I'll kill them.
Well, then what're
you gonna do
after you kill
those people??
I'll find more people
I don't like...
and I'll kill them too.
But, if you keep looking
for people you don't like
you might find that you
don't like anyone
in the whole world.
That's right... I know
who my enemies are-
it's me against the world!
"You against the world"...
You crack me up.
No... someone like you who
grew up in a good home
could never understand.
Nobody understands...
they never will...
Well, Natsu...
From this day forward I will
be your foster father...
I've devoted my entire
life to my business
so I've never had
children of my own...
Therefore, you will inherit
the Tanimoto Corporation
and be responsible for
the company's future.
I'll teach you
everything I know.
If you meet my
expectations
then I will pay off all of
your sister's medical fees.
But if you don't...
then I'll have no choice
but to throw the two of
you out on the streets.
I'm serious, Natsu.
Don't let me down.
Who's there??
Hey... I just
thought I'd drop in
and see how you're doing.
Loki, you bastard...
How'd you get in my house?
You don't seem too
happy to see me...
It was easy getting in-
Number 20's a pro
at picking locks.
Yeah... Easy.
Don't get all worked up.
I'm not here to
fight you, okay?
I just came here because
I have a message.
I'll take care of
Kenichi Shirahama...
so don't you even
bother with him.
Kenichi Shirahama??
Screw you...
I thought I made it clear
that I don't take
orders from anyone.
Now I suggest you
leave this house
before you have to be
dragged out in a body bag.
Now hold on...
this order didn't come
from me or Odin...
It's an imperial
command handed down
by the Saint of
Fists himself.
Hey... You're a bad
guy, aren't ya? !
I can tell just by looking
at your ugly face...
You're not gonna
beat him...
Kenichi Shirahama
is my brother
and he could
kick your butt!
What... You're
Shirahama's sister? !
That's right...
My brother is a good guy-
a champion of justice...
He may be kinda
down right now,
but that won't stop him from
beating up all of you bad guys!
What a surprise...
Didn't think I'd find
that punk's sister here.
What're you doing? !
Hey! Put me down!
I can't move!
You're squishing me!
You're more useful
than I thought, Hermit.
She's Kenichi
Shirahama's sister? !
Hey, is that
Shirahama.....?...
It looks like he's trying
to hide out from someone.
Hey there...
Miu's been looking all
over for you, ya know...
I think she was wanting
you to walk her home.
Mi-Mi-Miu!
Sorry but you've got the
wrong guy! Gotta go!
That was definitely
Shirahama.
He's so weird.
I can't face
Miu right now.
Not after I chickened
out on my training
at Ryozanpaku.
I'm so embarrassed!
I wanna go crawl
in a hole and die!
I gotta find somewhere
to hide until Miu's left
school for the day!
Welcome to another thrilling
Shinpaku Alliance meeting...
Our numbers are low
so I need you guys
to concentrate on
recruiting new members.
Do whatever you gotta do.
Well... I was late so you guys
discuss while I eat my lunch.
Ugh. What the hell
is he eating?
That doesn't look
like lunch...
It looks like some kinda
weird science experiment.
Why are you here, Kenichi-
shouldn't you be walking
home with your honey?
Hey come to think of it...
he's right...
you said you didn't want
anything to do with the
Shinpaku Alliance so
why are you attending
Niijima's
little meeting??
Uh... Just checkin'
in.....!...
You see, I gotta keep
an eye on Niijima
to make sure that
he's behaving.
Miu will never
look for me here.
I just have to wait
till she goes home...
What about the two
of you.....!..?
I never thought you
guys would wanna join
Niijima's silly
Shinpaku Alliance.
It's not... what
you're thinkin'.
We never really
wanted to join
but somehow he was able
to talk us into it.
Please! I'm begging you!
I need a strong
guy like you
in the Shinpaku Alliance...
Just come to one meeting
and see what it's like.
Jeez, you're annoying...
I already said no- I'm
not a delinquent anymore.
Hold on! The Shinpaku Alliance
is totally delinquent-free!
It's a group of students
who are focused on
fighting for peace!
And you're one of the best
fighters in the whole school-
you'd be an excellent
addition to our group.
-No...
-You're an amazing boxer-
don't you wanna
show everyone
how incredibly awesome
you are at it?
I don't know.
Your friends need
you to protect them.
You wouldn't go and
neglect your friends
would you, Takeda?
You can't resist fate!
I'll even make
you a leader...
you in or you out??
I'm in...
It's my fate...
I have to help protect
my friends and my school.
Good to hear.
Then I'll see you at
tomorrow's meeting.
It was the
strangest thing...
I still can't figure
out what kinda voodoo
he used to talk
me into joining.
Whoa... He did the same
thing to me too!
He brainwashed them!?
I gotta get to work...
You ladies can sit here
and chat all day if you want
but I've gotta get online
and make things happen
if you know what I mean.
It's imperative that we get
some new recruits... and fast.
Is that a computer...
Holy crap!
I just threw this one
together using
what I found in the trash-
not too shabby, huh Ukita?
It's the modern age!
We need to have
technology on our side!
This computer has a 3
gigahertz dual core processor
and 2 gigabytes
of RAM!
Whoa... I have no idea what
you're talking about
but it sounds awesome!
What the hell is
Niijima doing?
His stupid computer
can't help us in a fight.
Oh, hey Kenichi...
I got some news for ya.
Word on the street is
that weird guy is back.
What guy?
Natsu Tanimoto...
you know, Hermit.
Tanimoto's back? !
Yeah, and evidently
he's been running around
beating up
everyone he sees.
Rumor has it he's been
doing some serious
martial arts training.
It makes you wonder
if maybe he's randomly
starting fights with
delinquents on the street
as a kind of warm-up
to fighting you.
So he's back...
And I bet he's
counting on a rematch.
Don't worry, kid...
You gotta remember to stay
calm- don't get nervous...
If you start getting too riled
up then you'll lose focus
and they'll get ya...
I've got a
question for ya.
Yeah... What's up?
Is it true that you can meet
hot chicks over the internet?
Cause you know...
that's what I hear.
You can but only if you're
diligent about it-
the internet's a lot like
the real world that way.
I see...
so I have to be diligent
if I wanna meet hot chicks...
now I get it.
That's it! I'm done...
I'm sure we'll get plenty
of new recruits now.
What do you think?
I never gave you permission
to put my picture
on the internet!
That website's not
gonna recruit anyone
or get us hot chicks!
You've got mail!
Look I've already
got new mail...
And I just finished
updating the website...
I'll show all of you
haters what's up.
Let's see... what've
we got here...
"How are you doing,
Commander Niijima?
I was just surfing the web
when I stumbled upon your page.
What a happy accident."
They even put a
little smiley face.
What... Come on, you've
gotta be kidding me?
I can't believe
someone sent an email
to Niijima's creepy
website- how weird!
Hey... is it a girl...
Well, Is it? !
"My name is Loki and I'm
a member of Ragnarok.
Perhaps you've
heard of us?"
So her name's Loki?
That's cute.
Let me reply, Loki is
a pretty cute name.
Wait. No way...
-Loki? !
-The Fourth Fist...
But I thought it
was a hot chick!
Oh no, now he's in
the chat room...
He asks, "Is Kenichi
Shirahama there?"
Yeah, he's here...
He says, "It's about
time we finish this.
I'll be waiting for
you by the church
in the third district.
Show up alone."
Huh... This sounds like a trap-
I wouldn't go if I
were you, Kenichi.
It's an attachment.
Kenichi come back...
It's a trap... Let's
come up with a plan
and go after him together-
You with me, Ukita?
Hell yeah!
Whatever you do don't
lose track of Kenichi.
I finally found you.
Where have you been?
I was worried...
Are you ready to come
back to Ryozanpaku now-
the masters have been
waiting for you.
Kenichi wait!
We just found out
Kenichi's sister
was kidnapped by Ragnarok.
What... Honoka was kidnapped? !
Damn it! How did
this happen? !
What the hell do they
want with Honoka? !
You know now that
I think about it,
I guess we were kinda
hard on the little guy.
We put him through
some intense training.
I know he's been gone for
quite a while but
I have faith that Kenichi
will return to Ryozanpaku
when he's ready.
I don't know what to do with
all this time on my hands...
Thanks for comin' to play
Pachinko with me though-
it helps pass the time-
I had no idea that you
were so good at it.
Well... neither did I-
it's the first time
I've played-
but I got the hang
of it pretty quick.
Yeah...
I feel bad cause you
never gambled before
and I brought you over to the
dark side outta sheer boredom...
Kenichi...
I wish you would just come
back to Ryozanpaku already.
Hold on. Is that him?
I'm impressed- it
seems as though
he is keeping up
with his training.
I don't know- it doesn't
really look like
the kid's out for
a leisurely run.
Yeah, you're right...
He's running
with an urgency
that I've never seen before-
something must
have happened.
I sense fire.
He's incredibly angry.
Wanna follow him?
Who knows? Might
be interesting.
I... can't... run anymore...
TaKAYda... wait.
I'm sorry man but I've
gotta keep up with Kenichi!
I've been trailing
him this whole time
but he's so fast he's getting
farther and farther ahead of me.
Is that...
Master Ko-et-soo-jee?
If he loses this fight
I'll tie him up
and drag him back
to the dojo.
Good idea- it sounds like
someone's been lonely
without their
disciple around.
C'mon! You feel the same!
No wonder Kenichi's
so freakin' fast...
Just look at his
masters go...
I can't believe that
Alien-lookin' freak job
created a webpage for
the Shinpaku Alliance.
He's got guts,
that's for sure.
So what now... You got in...
What're you
gonna do to it?
His security is weak
so we're gonna hack
into the damn thing.
What the-? This is
harder than I expected.
Damn it. What's that mean?
Dummy... You're supposed to
offer a lady tea!
Could ya at least
get me some water...
My throat's all
dry and scratchy
from screaming all day.
And, just where do you
think you're going, Hermit??
I'm gonna go get
the kid some water.
She doesn't need it- the
brat's not gonna die
from a scratchy throat...
I suggest that you
go sit down now.
Stop it, Hermit!
You really don't want
do this, my friend-
remember I have orders from
the Great Sage Fists.
If you know what's good
for ya you'll let me down.
My plan didn't work out the
way I thought it was gonna...
Thanks to you it
worked out even better.
So I'll thank you
by giving you
what you've wanted all
along- another fight...
And this time
Kenichi Shirahama
has no chance of winning.
Consider that an order
from the big man himself-
that means there'll
be no backing out...
You owe him big time Hermit
so you'd better not
go and betray him.
The Great Sage Fists
has put me in charge
so you answer to
me now, got it?
It's you...
Tell me where my
sister is, Hermit!
[Music]
Damn you're naive.
Lemme give you a few words
of advice, Shirahama...
The only way you can
stay alive in this world
is by living a life
full of lies.
That's not true, Hermit!
I know better than that!
As long as you have the
heart to trust others
that's all you
need to live.
"The heart to
trust others"?
That's the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard!
You idiot! Don't you see?
The truth is worth
absolutely nothing!
That's not true!
I'll show you how important
it is to trust others.
Even if I have to use
my two fists to do it!
Prepare yourself, Hermit!