[Music]
It's you...
Where is she, Hermit...?!
Tell me now!
Enough...! Hermit, you bastard,
you'd better hand over
Honoka do you understand.
I swear if you so much as
touch one hair on her head...
You're gonna be a dead man.
Well... looks like they're
gettin' ready to rumble...
I'm lookin' to win back
my Pachinko losses
so what do you say we
bet on the winner?
My gambling days are over.
C'mon you know you wanna.
You hate me, don't you?
Good... That's how
it should be...
Hate your opponent
with all your might.
"Your hate...
will make you... stronger."
That was what Master Sougetsu
always said to me, anyway.
Sougetsu...
Martial arts is
the art of death,
so you should fight
with no holds barred...
Therefore...
Hey! Wait up, Takeda!
Ya gotta hurry up, Ukita-
we gotta keep goin'-
we already lost him...!
Do ya remember what street
that old church is on?
What...?!
I wasn't really
payin' attention.
Damn it! What do you mean you
weren't payin' attention?!
I told ya those directions
were important, didn't I?!
I'm sorry, Takeda.
But someone's
gotta know, right?
It's gonna be the third
street up ahead...
Take a left turn and you should
be able to see it from there.
Not you.
Man, these guys
are helpless...
I knew you dumb jocks wouldn't
be able to do it without me...
Shinpaku Alliance...
let's find 'em!
I hate that guy.
So Niijima told me that
Honoka's been kidnapped
by one of the Eight Deadly
Fists, is that true?
Yeah... the fourth
fist, Loki, has her-
he's the only guy despicable
enough to kidnap a little girl.
Despicable is
such a harsh word
I prefer to think of
myself as ruthless-
a man's gotta do
what a man's gotta do.
Loki!
Sorry...
But this is as far as you
kids are gonna get today.
No... way!
I never go anywhere
without backup-
looks like you're
outnumbered.
What the hell-
he has clones?!
Nuh-uh... They can't be clones.
Take a look at the
big guy on the left.
Yeah... he's kinda round.
They're not my clones but
they're just as strong.
Hope you're ready
for our stun rods!
Wow... Who knew he
had those moves?
What the hell?
He's running away!
Here they come!
What's with this chick?!
Don't worry, Honoka.
Everything's
gonna be alright.
We're coming to save you!
Whoa ...
Looks like Kenichi might
win this thing after all.
See? If we were betting
I'd be up right now.
I've had a change of
heart- count me in.
Alright...
but you know we can't both put
money on Kenichi... right?
I know...
I'm betting it all
on the caped kid.
Winner gets the
other's dessert.
Deal?
Now tell me where my
sister is, Hermit!
This fight'll be
tough for Kenichi.
He still has one
major weakness.
Right?
The kid's too naive.
You figured it out.
Ok, deal.
I'll take you
up on your bet.
Well...?! Where is she?!
Really think a joint lock's
gonna restrain a
fighter like me...?
Lemme guess,
you think my attacks
are only good
long range huh.
Not only did Master
Sougetsu teach me
the importance of
long range attacks
he taught me eight
different punches
to be used at close range.
I let you get close enough
to joint lock me on purpose-
that was my plan...
You've never seen my
close range attack
so you doubted my ability.
Not convinced?
He drew back his
attacking arm.
Was that some kinda feint?
Time's up.
I can see through
your defense.
I'm afraid your attacks aren't
strong enough to get past me.
That makes six down...
Which means there's
only one more to go.
If this guy's
the last one...
is he the real deal?
Certainly looks that way.
Why don't you guys
just leave him to me?
Gimme a break would ya...?
You think you can fight
one of the Eight Fists
just cause you were one of
Key-sar-uh's bodyguards?
That was a long time ago
and I've been training
hard everyday since then...
You have no idea
how strong I am.
All the blood, sweat and
tears I shed through training
have made me
infinitely stronger
than any of you
Eight Deadly Fists.
Yes...! And I'm the genius who's
in charge of this powerhouse-
he doesn't do a thing
till I say the word...
Go...! Vice-commander!
Man, I hate you.
Come on...! Now...! Let's go!
Ultimate uppercut!
Is it just me or was
that way too easy?
Damn... That's
not the right guy.
We have to hurry...!
I'm gonna go on ahead!
The real Loki
is right here.
I knew it! What the
hell were we thinking?
They're all fakes!
I can't believe
they got us again.
They're trying
to distract us!
Hey wait a minute- didn't
anyone ever teach you brats
not to judge a book
by it's cover?!
Oh well... Guess I can't really
blame them- they're right.
You can't even
handle a feint...
High level fighters
can always tell
when their opponent's faking.
How can you be so naïve?!
I'm wasting my time
-you're not on my level!
You... You say you stand
for justice and truth
but don't you see that's
not gonna get you anywhere
as a fighter?!
A martial arts master
has to have the ability
to trick his opponent
and use their
powers against them.
Someone like you would never
be able to pull that off.
You see...
I lived in an orphanage
until I was six years old.
We lived there until the
day he came to adopt us.
He was a cold man
but I didn't care.
He was wealthy so I knew he'd be
able to afford a good doctor
for my sick little sister.
I tried to be
the perfect son-
I was almost robotic.
I never cried.
I would never
whine or get angry.
I did everything my father
asked of me without question.
Even so, I never
once saw him smile.
Now listen Natsu,
one day you will inherit the
entire Tanimoto Corporation.
I didn't adopt you
to "play house".
I'm protecting
my business.
Understand?
But... one day
something happened
that changed all of
our lives dramatically.
He fell in love.
My father fell in love
with and married a doctor
who worked at one of
the clinics he owned.
The next three
years flew by-
everything was perfect...
You love Cosmos flowers,
don't you Kaede?
Yeah, I do!
They're so pretty.
Natsu.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong...
You kids are a blessing.
And that's when
he did it...
He finally smiled.
But our happiness
would be short-lived.
It was all based on lies.
Not too long
after that day
our father mysteriously
passed away.
Brother...
Then my sister became
gravely ill and died.
That's when I realized that the
doctor my father had married
hadn't done anything
to help cure her.
Kaede...! Kaede!
All she wanted was
my father's money-
she only pretended to care.
Everything was a lie.
I didn't poison your father.
I swear!
I'm your mother!
Not-sue!
That how I lost my
father and my sister...
In a web of deceit...
She was quite an actress.
It's so wrong
that it's funny...
Don't you think...?
It's okay, you can laugh...
If I saw her today
I would thank her...
Because now I've realized
what an important
lesson she's taught me.
Lies make you stronger.
Our little chat is over...
You probably don't even have
the strength to stand right now.
Die!
What the...
I've heard enough...
I won't let you trick
me into pitying you
so you can pummel
me into the ground.
I'm ready to fight!
Impossible!
You may have amazing masters
but you're naivety is
gonna get the best of you.
Wow... Didya hear that...?
caped kid just called him out.
Now the question is
can Kenichi defend
himself against his enemy
because a feint may be the
only way he'll be able to.
What now...?!
You're not gonna
be able to get up
so you might as well
surrender, Shirahama.
This is the place, right?!
Be careful... He's dangerous.
I know...
But... we gotta do what
we can to help Kenichi.
We made it...!
Hey... Niijima...
try to keep up, man.
Hey, I'm not so sure
about this you guys...
I'm not very good with
shrines or churches...
they make me
uncomfortable...
know what I mean?
I knew you were a demon.
Sorry about this, Uki.
It's no big deal- just
don't call me that.
You don't like
you're new nickname?
I'm too old for that, man.
Well, I'm your boss and
I wanna call you Uki.
One more time and
I'll kill you.
It seems that the
winner has been decided.
Power and deceit...
Those two things are all you
need to get by in this world.
Your're...
You're wrong.
If you live a life
full of deceit-
constantly struggling
for power...
you'll end up with
nothing but sadness.
My karate master
once told me...
talking with your fists makes
your words hit... harder.
No matter how much someone
tries to put on a façade...
you'll have them
completely figured out
once you fight them.
I don't remember ever
saying that to him.
Well, you were probably
drunk at the time.
I know you aren't the
one who kidnapped Honoka.
After what you've
been through
you'd never kidnap
someone's sister...
I know that you
didn't do it...
but you know that
as her brother
it's my duty to protect her.
But that's impossible...!
He shouldn't even be
able to stand right now-
not after I've attacked
him repeatedly!
What you truly need to
get by in this world
is not power or deceit...
You need a heart that is
capable of trusting others
and deep down
you know that.
Trust your masters.
Trust your friends and most
importantly trust yourself...
because that is true power.
'A heart that is capable
of trusting others'...
I don't think you get it...
Shirahama...
That way of thinking is
what killed my sister!
Well, My sister is
counting on me to save her
and I'm not gonna
let her down!
You're so naïve-
do you really think you'll
be able to protect her?
Double palm!
That's quite impressive...
The Double Palm...
I never thought
you would know
one of the eight... punches...
But if you don't attack
with all of your might
it's very easy
to block it.
That punch was so powerful.
It's so much stronger
than anything
I've ever been capable of.
That's right...!
You don't have to be
deceitful to gain power
all you need is determination
and some good old
fashioned training!
Hey! why are you smilin'...?
You bet it all
on the caped kid
which means I get
your dessert tonight.
I don't understand- how do you
know all these martial arts?
At first I thought
it was just karate
but you also use Jujitsu,
Kenpo, even Moy Thai...!
Just who in the hell do
you think you are, huh?
I'm Kenichi Shirahama...
and I'm history's
strongest disciple.
I don't know what
you're talking about
but it's about
time we end this...
Let's go!
That's enough you two.
That was awesome...
Definitely a great fight.
But you've been rained out
so I think you
should call it a day.
The final victory
always goes to Ragnarok.
Don't forget that, kid.
Big brother!
Honoka!
[Music]
Don't make a move, Shirahama.
You wouldn't want me to hurt
your little sis now would ya?
Please help me!
This guy is creeping me out!
Let her go!
I'm warning you!
Don't worry about
me, big brother.
I want you to go out there
and kick all the
bad guy's butts!
Watch what you
say little girl.
You're not my sister so I
don't care if you end up dead.
Loki...! You'd better
not lay a hand on her!
I'm going to
save you, Honoka!
I swear it!