[Music]
Uh-oh...
Guess I was a little
too hard on you...
You've gotta learn
to dodge, my boy...
Oh my god...!
It's a miracle...!
The good Lord above has
recognized my dying wish
and has granted this lost
soul with a single bar!
Looks like I have to stay
like this or I lose it...
I better hurry
and call someone.
An email.....?...
But who's it from??
Niijima!
There are the wimps
who are bullied
and the bullies
that abuse them.
There are the people
who give orders
and the people
who follow them.
Each person's role has
been predetermined by God
and handed down to them
when they were born.
Or so I thought.
Your existence has shaken the
very foundation of my beliefs...
We'll bust through that wall
of dirty thugs and
head to freedom, sir!
Molotov cocktails??!
Hey Commander...
I don't think we're gonna
get through these guys.
It's a wall of Loki!
Elder...
I have to get back home
immediately, I'm sorry.
I guess he's learned enough
to face any delinquent
he may encounter.
My name is... Thor!
Damn it... Not you.
Now listen up punks-
I'm here here to
protect the commander
at the request of my buddy,
Siegfriedfried...
As of today I'm a member
of the Shinpaku Alliance.
I never thought
he'd actually come!
You never said anything
about running 100 miles an hour
on electrical wires.
Really I am gonna die
before I ever make it home.
Don't worry- as long
as you keep holding on
everything'll be fine.
This is the fastest
way to get there
so just hang tight, okay??
This may be the fastest way
but it's dangerous.....!...
My hands are slipping!
Save me, Elder!
Those two just had
to get in the way...
Ragnarok is now... dead!
Whoa...! Who are they.....?..?
That's a pretty
scary lookin' bunch!
I'd like to introduce you to
the fighters I've trained
to pick up where
Ragnarok left off...
The new Eight Deadly Fists!
And their...
new leader is...
Berserker,
you're the one who's
right for the job.
I'm perfectly fine with
being second in command.
Everyone... I present to
you a fighting force
to be reckoned with.....!...
The reincarnation
of the Fists
and their new and
improved Ragnarok gang!
What?
Now...! Go Niijima...!
I made a promise
to Siegfried
that I would protect
you at all costs!
What now??!
Ow! Man, that hurt.....!...
Jeez, I wish the Elder
would figure out
how to let me
down more gently.
Hey you guys.....?...
You okay??
Its... Kenichi!
Captain Shirahama's here!
Kenichi Shirahama...
You haven't changed-
you're just as stubborn
as you were before.
They're fighting
in that factory.
It is abandoned, right??
Yes, sir.
Where's all that
smoke coming from??
-Picnic time!
-The meat... the meat.
Let me see...
It looks like there's
a lot of people there.
What.....?..?...! Really??!
Yep a bunch of people!
Well... I know it's
hard to see...
So... I brought this for you.
Where'd that come from...?
Huh...?
You wanna tell me what use
that telescope for, Kensei??
I have a passion
for bird watching!
I hope that
everyone's okay.
Please be well,
my comrades...
and my dear, demon king!
It's been a while...
So how is everyone.....?...
Did you all miss me??
Oh... hey...
We're glad you're
home, Grandpa.
Apa!
Who's this old
man.....?..?...!
I've never seen anyone
move so fast before...
How'd he do that??!
I saw you on my way
back to Ryozanpaku
so I dropped in...
I wasn't expecting
such a fancy picnic.
Where's Kenichi; is
he coming too.....?...
How'd training go?
Do you think he's ready
to face his old friend??
Kenichi's back...?..?...!
He should be over there
helping the other Shinpaku!
Kenichi...
I accidentally
dropped the boy...
into a deep ravine.
I'm just messin' with ya...
I dropped him right in the
middle of the battlefield-
he should be there now.
Old man... Joking around
like that isnot cool...
Are you sure the kid
made it over there??
What if you dropped
him in the wrong place?
His life is at stake- do
you want him to get hurt??
Ah... How I've
missed you tea...
So good.
Why don't you guys take
a look for yourselves...
He's across the river by
the smoking warehouse.
How can you
see over there?!
All I can see from
this far are shadows.
He's all pumped up
from his training
and ready for a fight...
Hold on a second...
This is supposed
to be a battle
between the Shinpaku
and Ragnarok...
What exactly are you
doing here, Thor.....?...
I don't really understand
why you showed up.
Start explaining, Niijima!
I told you not to come-
we're in serious trouble.
You should've
listened to me.
What's going on.....?...
Where are all the other members
of the Shinpaku Alliance?
They should be here.....!...
I mean, where the
hell is Takeda??
Killed in action!
No, he's not really dead.
What about Ukita??
Killed in action!
What about Mizunuma.....?...
And Kamioka.....?...
And Siegfried??
They were all...
killed in action...!
We're the only
survivors, Captain.
Just ignore him......
He's being dramatic.
You're the one to
blame for this...
Ryuto!
No... I'm not the
one at fault here...
Do you think I'd waste
my time on your lackeys??
What'd you say??!
You can blame me...
I'm the one who
fought them.
It was just too easy...
Those guys all
had terrible form.
They moved so slowly...
I had to crush them.
Keep your cool, Kenichi.
Remember to stay calm
and stop the water.
No good...
Almost let my anger
get the best of me.
Check it out guys...
It's Kenichi Shirahama!
If we can defeat
him I bet...
Odin'll make us one
of the Deadly Fists!
Let's do it!
Seikuuken??!
That's impressive...
How could he have learned how
to fight using the Seikuuken
in such a short
amount of time??!
That's enough...
This isn't the way that things
are supposed to go down...
Hold on a second,
Berserker.
This isn't your
fight, Kenichi...
Let me handle it.
But I wanna fight him!
Shut up!...
You've been training in
the mountains all this time
so you could 'd
defeat Odin, right??
You need to concentrate
on beating him-
don't waste your energy.
I understand what
you're saying...
But one thing...
-What is it?
-Uh...
What are you doing here??
Well... I came here to
get revenge on Loki...
But then Berserker knocked him
out before I got the chance
so I might as
well hang around
and help you guys,
you know.....?...
Damn it.....!...
Why do you care...?..?
You're so annoying...
I should kill you.
Sorry... just glad
that you're here.
Wait- they're friends??!
Captain Tah-nee-moto has
come to show his support
for the Shinpaku Alliance...
and Captain Thor came
along with him.....!...
I knew those two
would see the light
and join the
Alliance eventually!
Tanimoto...
I don't wanna hear it.
Kenichi... You
haven't had a chance
to recover from
your training...
If you go and fight two of
the Three of Cards now...
I'm afraid... you'll injure
yourself to the point
where you can't study
martial arts anymore.
If that happened...
I'd never be able
to have a rematch
with you in the future...
Besides...
That noisy brat
you call a sister
would never let me
hear the end of it...
I can only imagine...
Thanks, Tanimoto...
Aw. This is a tender moment...
However... When did I ever
agree to fight you, Kenichi??
What??!
I've already defeated you-
I have no interest
in fighting again...
I think Berserker can
handle you both...
He's twice the fighter
you'll ever be.
-Whoa!
-Damn... Watch out, Hermit!
No... Leave him alone!
Wow... That was so predictable
I didn't even bother dodging!
Well... Must say I'm
impressed, Hermit...
You've improved.
Blood??
Kenichi's not the
only martial artist
who's been in intensive
training lately...
Ever Since I left Ragnarok
I've been preparing myself for
a fight like just like this one.
And Berserker...
I think you're the
perfect opponent for me
to test my new skills on.
What you just do?
It's a target...
That way I know exactly
where to aim my punches!
Wow... He's strong.
Yeah well that's probably
why his nickname is
the "Invincible Brawler".
-Really??!
-'Fraid so...
Evidently Berserker
hasn't really
had any formal
martial arts training.
He's defeated a number of
highly skilled martial artists
with his raw talent.
Imagine what he could
be if he trained...
I've heard he's
never lost a fight-
which doesn't bode
well for Hermit.
Tanimoto!
Whoa.....!...
He just beat him!
I'm not surprised...
Hermit's pretty tough
but he's still only the sixth
Fist outta eight, you know...?
That guy i's no match for
one of the Three of Cards.
Wow...
He's taken all of
Berserker's hits
and he's still
able to stand...
Hey... what happened...
I thought the whole point
was to hit the target.
You gotta remember
that I'm different
from the martial artists
you've fought in the past...
Sougetsu Ma trained me...
You may know him as
"The Fighting Demon".
I'm going show you the fury
of a true martial artist!
Too slow.
Yeah!
My attacks are
gonna hit you
whether you can see them
or not, Berserker...
You see, I've
mastered a technique
that counters
the human reflex...
Only martial artists
who've trained diligently
for years can master it
because the technique
is so difficult to learn.
I think I get it...
He's completely in tune
with his opponent's instincts.
He performs the
move they expect
and then he adds another
move to throw them off...
He can get a hit
because the opponent
isn't expecting
the second move.
I can't believe Tanimoto's
even stronger than before.
And back then he lasted
an entire fight
with a serious injury.
So... What'll you do
now, Hermit.....?...
I'm sure your're
master was a passable.
But I'm guessing he never
got around to teaching you
how to dodge an attack
from above, am I right??
I'm not worried.
No! Watch out!
I bet your master
never taught
you how to handle an attack
like this did he.....?...
What's the matter Hermit?
You afraid of fighting me??
Hell... no.
Well, you should be.
Shut up!
You see...
I'm not afraid of
losing a fight-
especially not to
a loser like you...
I just don't want
to be bored...
Every time I think someone's
gonna be a good opponent
they let me down and I end
up yawning through the fight.
It's such a shame...
I thought you were going to
be the one to change that.
But it's over.
-Captain Tanimoto!
-He got him!
Damn it, he's down!
Bulls-eye.
-Hermit!
-Captain Tanimoto!
He got him!
Damn it, he's down!
Hermit!
I'm disappointed...
I expected more but you let
me down like everyone else.
Looks like it's up
to you... Kenichi...
What do ya say??
You think you'd
actually be able
to handle a couple of
rounds against me.....?...
Nobody else seems
up to the challenge.
Kenichi... We have
to avenge Hermit
and you're the only
one who can do it!
No.
What.....?..?
What're you saying-
we can't give up
without a fight!
You see...
I knew he wasn't out...
There's no way Tanimoto
would ever give up
a fight that easily.
You underestimated
me, Berserker.
I'm not some jerk who
goes around fighting
for the hell of it.
I'm a trained
martial artist
who refuses to be
beaten by likes of you.
I swore I'd never give in!
Remember big brother...
Please...
don't give in... please.
I promised!
Not... bad...
He knocked him out.
Now you listen to me...
Your raw talent is
actually your weakness...
You've never learned
what it means
to truly fight for victory.
See... My master
always taught me
losing a fight's
was the equivalent
of a dishonorable death.
I never let my guard
down during a fight...
not 'til my
opponent is dead.
It's not that easy...
Sorry kid...
but your time is up.
Damn... What'd you do to me??!
I didn't even
see him attack!
It seemed like Tanimoto had
the upper hand until now.
Man... That guy's intense.
Sure is...
He's a street fighter that
feeds off of his anger...
This is bad...
If he keeps gaining
strength like he has been...
I'm afraid our boys won't
be able to defeat him.
I'm impressed...
So far this fight 's been more
entertaining than the others.
I wrote you off too soon.
You're a worthy opponent.
I wouldn't be surprised if
you were the first person
to push me to my limit.
Oh, I'm sure I will...
and I'll be
the first person
to show you what it
losing feels like.
So fast...
having a hard time keeping
up with his punches...
There's no rhythm to them
it's just a flurry of attacks.
I can't keep
this up for long.
Whoa... Did you see
that awesome feint
Berserker pulled on him??!
Yeah... He went in
with the a left jab...
but then he got him
with his a right hook.
Berserker's untrained attacks
have no rhythm to them...
So they can't
be predicted...
He can trick his
opponent... see...
When they dodge his attack
he instinctively punches in
the direction of their movement.
However...
He has to be aware of
how often he
uses this tactic
or he'll throw himself off...
He could easily lose track
and leave himself open.
Here you go.
Not bad...
You were able to dodge
my attack by turning...
Well... Then how about this??!
Why'd he turn
his back to me??!
I got you now Hermit!
Why don't you give up, kid??!
He's entered
Berserker mode...
I guess it's
over for Hermit.
Dodge them! C'mon...
Captain Tanimoto!
He can't...
The guy's too fast.
This is bad.
What's the matter, Hermit?!
This fight isn't
exciting anymore...
If all you do is block
it's gonna get boring.
None of these bastards
can keep up with me...
When am I gonna find
someone who's on my level??!
I thought you were the one
but it looks like
you've given up
just like the rest of them!
No way, it can't be...
Hermit has been defeated!
Hang on... I wouldn't go
and write him off just yet.
You're a dead!
Just as I planned.
You're predictable,
Berserker...
Whenever it comes time
for your last attack
you always do
something flashy...
That's when you
leave yourself open.
You just stood there
and took the hits
until you saw an opening?
Most fighters wouldn't
choose to win that way.
Didn't I tell you.....?..?
You and I have different
ideas of what victory means.
It's obvious
that Hermit...
Is my brother's
disciple...
He has the same
style Sougetsu did.
Impressive...
It's a damn good style-
that kid's moves
are unbelievable...
One good hit and his opponent's
pretty much done for.
Well, he certainly won't
be able to stand anymore.
Think not??
Wow... His adrenaline's all
that's keeping him going...
He probably can't
even feel pain anymore.
He got close to him!
I see now...!
I bet he's gonna try to use
one of the Eight Deadly
punches on him!
Once he's that close
his opponent can't
change their attack.
I suggest that you surrender
before this starts to
get ugly, Berserker...
You can't handle a
real martial artist.
I'm not giving up now...
I'm having too much fun.
Yep... Definitely
a Hermit move...
He always wants to gowants
to go straight for the joints.
Dam... You Bastard!
You may not think my
training is equivalent
to your natural talent...
He attacked using
his dislocated elbow!
But I put everything
into my training.....!...
100 percent!
Don't you see that's
how this art form
has been passed down
for thousands of years!
It's because in the
world of martial arts...
Hard work will always
surpass talent!
Yes!
Then again, I've
trained hard
but I also have
a natural talent.
I'll tell you one thing...
Even if you had fought
against Shirahama
you still would've lost.
Bastard!
My body won't move.
I don't understand...
What... What is this
strange feeling??
I never felt
anything like this.
That's what it feels
like to lose a fight.
Al- right.....!...
He totally kicked ass!
I knew it.....!...
Just as I expected- he had
no problem defeating him.
My word... He's so strong...
Our boy's got
great friends.
Yeah.....!...
They're strong.....!...
They're great.....!...
Yay!
Guess it's about time
for the main event.
Tag me out??
Aw man, that hurt!
[Music]
I don't know why you're
so warped, Ryuto...
But I'm gonna
straighten you out!
Take off those glasses!
I can tell you've been
training hard, Kenichi.
That's good- you wouldn't
last 5 seconds against me
if you hadn't.
Are you sure you want me
to take off my glasses??
What?
If I take them off
then you'll finally see
why they call me Odin.
Are you sure you're ready?
I trained really hard just
to be able to defeat you!
Your scare tactics aren't
gonna make me back down!
How foolish you are...
My fist is known as
the legendary spear...
I can't wait to
acquaint you with it.