Hey, Kenichi?
You okay? Hello?
Are you awake now?
From this day forward,
you're officially
a disciple of Ryozanpaku!
Right!
To formalize and honor
this new relationship,
from this moment onward you will
address each of us as "master"!
They're all acting so
different than usual...
This must be serious!
Yes! Master Sakaki!
You maniac!
I call this the Squid Dance.
Giviing it a cute name isn't
gonna make it any less deadly!
You know this is
attempted murder?!
If I don't flip over
to my back in time,
my stomach is gonna
get totally fried!
Is this supposed to
strengthen my back muscles
and my abdominals?!
Don't move.
Don't even twitch.
Maybe I'm overreacting,
but I'm starting to get a
very bad feeling about this.
And what is this training
method supposed to teach me?
It's supposed to help
you overcome your fear.
That's my guess.
Uh, you guess?
Come on, you need to go a lot
faster than that, slowpoke!
Your legs are three times
stronger than your arms!
Why's that? Right! Because
you walk with your legs!
That's how I figure it too!
Stop pushing!
I can't take it anymore!
Finally, it's
Apachai's turn now!
Hey, it's okay! Akisame
said Kenichi needs a break,
so Apachai should go easy
on the dangerous stuff.
Huh? So what exactly
are we gonna do?
Just regular free punching!
That's the most
dangerous thing of all!
Kenichi!
Are you okay? Speak to me!
Kenichiiiiiii!
Those guys are gonna
kill me, I just know it!
If I'm dead, my lovey-dovey
plan will never succeed!
Hey, this is the best
situation you could hope for!
You never know what will happen
when you leave two young people
alone together and let
the old hormones work!
I wish this had happened
to me when I was your age!
Yeah, right. Instead,
they're making me stay
in a separate dormitory
with all the masters!
Miu's in the main house...
That's it! I'm not
going to stay here
and die in this hell hole!
I hope I remembered to
bring that book with me!
Found it! The "How to Break
out of Prison Manual!"
Looks like they're
watching me...
Okay, what am I suppose
do at a time like this?
Maybe dig a hole...?
No, I'm on the second floor.
Dear Son,
Though I don't know how many
days it's been since you left,
if you're reading this, it means
you're thinking about quitting.
Just remember that your
mother and I believe in you.
I know you can triumph
over any obstacle.
Don't run away, Son.
Signed, Dad.
Well...
he's right; it is
only the first day.
Thanks, Dad!
You've reminded me
that I can't run away!
I will not be defeated!
Chocolate, malted milk
balls, cookies, and...
Big Brother's favorite:
cheesy fish sticks!
There. Hey, Mom? Do you think
you could pack me a box lunch
to take to Kenichi?
No problem. I thought you were
just going for a quick visit.
It looks like you're packing for
an expedition up Mount Everest!
That dojo's more isolated
than a desert island,
I have to make sure I'm
prepared for anything!
I know he told us
not to visit him
'cause it would
interrupt his training.
But I've got a funny feeling...
Here you go, Kenichi!
My ginormous boobies
are all yours!
I won't let him fall
into the clutches of that
big-boobed hussy no matter what!
Okay, Honoka!
Make sure you take my
Sebastian with you for--
Huh? I'm sorry,
did you say something?
You must have
imagined it, sweetie.
Wake uuup!
Huh...?
Don't tell me it's time
to get up already...
It's been a week since
Kenichi moved in with us...
What? What is it? Is it a
fire? Is it an earthquake?!
Nope, it's morning, kid.
Morning?
It's only four o'clock,
the sun's not up!
It's like they say,
the early bird catches the worm!
So, you ready to get out
there and carpe some diem?
Well?!
How about we start with three
easy laps around the city
before breakfast?
It feels like I'm getting up
earlier every morning...
...and doing more
laps each time!
Well, see you guys later, then!
He seems to be adjusting
pretty well to life here.
I think he's even
starting to have fun!
You lunatic!
Somebody save meee!
All right, it's
my turn today. Heh.
I'm not gonna lay a hand on you,
just take your best shot.
Right!
His sparring practice
is going well.
You're too slow!
You didn't say
anything about feet...
What'd you expect?
You're small with a short reach.
This'll train you to get inside
your opponent's reach
so you can dodge his kicks.
Yeah, that's great.
Okay, boys it's
time for breakfast!
I've noticed
during meal times...
A-pa-pa!
Why don't you eat
your own food?!
What's that?
Stop it!
Will you two clowns
let the kid eat?
...he's even getting
better at fighting back.
Shopping sure has
gotten a lot easier
since you came
to stay with us.
I really appreciate
all your help.
Aw, it's nothing,
nothing at all.
Anything I can do to help
you out, you just ask.
But you know, I'd probably
be a lot more helpful to you
if they didn't make me drag
these stupid leg irons around
every time we left the dojo.
Well, it's like the
masters told you,
think of those as
"chains of love".
Do you remember when
you used to get winded
just from carrying
the groceries?
Yeah...
I must've seemed pretty
hopeless there for a while,
but I guess all this training
is finally starting to pay off.
If I can just keep up this pace,
then I should be strong
enough to protect Miu soon.
What was that you just said?
Huh?!
Oh, it was nothing
important, nothing at all!
Before you protect anyone,
you're going to need to
build up your leg strength.
Hey! Where did you--?
Oh, man!
I don't need another one!
Every time I come
here, this dojo
looks like it
needs cleaning.
No fair, the gate's locked!
But if they think something
like a dumb locked gate
is gonna keep me out,
then they don't know Honoka!
Apa?
Apapapapapa!
He's gone!
It won't fit!
Hello! Apachai here!
Cookie attack!
Now's my chance.
What the--! How did you?!
Apa!
Chocolate and
potato chip attack!
Hello there! It's me, Apachai!
Oh, no!
What is he,
some kind of monster?!
Hard candy, peach jelly, pudding
snack, candy stick attack!
Hi! It's Apachai again!
He can't be human!
I'm running out of
stuff to throw!
All that's left are my brother's
favorite cheesy fish sticks
and the lunch Mom made him.
I have to protect those even
if this ogre eats me alive!
Time for a strategic withdrawal!
Ahh!
Ahh... paa!
You saved me? I don't get it.
So you're not really a big,
scary monster after all,
are you?
And here I thought
everyone in this dojo
was some kind of an evil fiend.
Sakaki likes to drink,
but he's a good person!
Kensei likes bikini pictures,
Akisame likes some
really confusing things,
but he's a good person!
Shigure likes to
play with weapons,
but she's a good person.
Do you mind taking me
to see my brother?
Oh! He's a good person!
Apaaaa...?
Not here...
Or here...
Not here either!
What is this place?!
Awww....
--he's not anywhere!
--Wait, Apachai have idea!
Apapa!
Apapaaaa!
He's not up here either!
He just...
...flew!
Maybe he's shopping?
Apachai saw Kensei
attach the leg irons.
Leg irons?
For shopping?!
Huh?
Hey! Those are my
brother's fish sticks!
Apa?
That thing is always stealing
food and blaming it on Apachai!
It's Shigure's mouse, Tochumaru!
Who's... this?
Why'd they have to go and leave
me here all alone like this...?
What're they doing?
Apa, apa!
Apapa!
Ah-pahh...?
Alright, where's the tea?
Beats me.
But Apachai saw Miu making
tea just a few days ago.
Hey, everybody,
the tea is ready!
You're supposed to serve tea
when visitors come over, right?
Shigure! I found
some tea cups!
This sounds like
it might be tea...
doesn't it?
Next, we need some hot water.
Wow, making tea is easy!
What did you do to the tea?!
--What's wrong?
All right, you two,
it's time for a tea lesson!
First off,
you gotta do this! See?!
Then, you do this!
And then this!
And there you go!
Tea!
Incredible! And so fast!
You're very skilled.
You think?
You're a genius!
Apachai jealous!
Very impressive!
Oh, wow, and I got a
"C" in home economics!
Well, anyway,
have some tea!
Okay! Thank you!
Absolutely amazing.
Ahhh! Apachai forget
to let the tea cool off!
Hot! Hot!
You doing all right?
Legs getting tired?
Nah... this is nothing.
This gate weighs a ton no
matter how much I work out.
You just have to
know how, that's all.
Well, someone's
having a good time.
Looks like
you're outta luck.
Whoaaaa!
Apa?
It's Honoka!
Kenichi, you're back!
I was looking for you!
Come on, knock it off,
you're embarrassing me!
Awwww, she's so adorable!
I told you,
I'm focusing really seriously
on my martial arts right now,
and you're interrupting
my training!
But, I...
Give her a break, Kenichi,
you don't have to be
so hard on her, do you?
Yeah, I do!
Otherwise, she'll be
here all the time!
Yeah, but...
You know what? You can come by
and visit me anytime you want!
Get outta my face, Blondie!
"Blondie"?
Oh! One sec!
Here! I brought this is for you!
Cheesy fish sticks, oh yeah!
But why is there only one?
Well... that's a long story.
Oh, so there you are.
It's almost time
for afternoon training.
Yes, sir!
Hm?
Training? That's right!
I've got to find out if
this dojo is legit or not!
Okay, for this exercise all
you have to do is touch me
and you win the round.
Alright, let's go.
So Boobie-Girl's
his opponent, huh?
I sure hope he doesn't let her
feminine charms distract him!
Kenichi!
Hey! You better leave my
big brother alone, chesty!
Or I'll take you apart myself!
Oh! You're so cute!
It's go time! Right, Kenichi?
Ready when you are!
I know Apachai is a big sweetie,
so I bet he'll play nicer
than that blonde bimbo!
You think so?
Aaa...
paaaa!
Apachai went easy on him!
Honest I did! You've got
to believe me, Honoka!
I b'lieve you...
All right...
Huh?
I think it might be best if I
finish this round of sparring.
Get on your feet!
Let's move it!
Do you think your enemies will
stand around while you recover?
Stop it! Stop it already!
No more! Stop hurting him!
What kind of training
do you call this?!
You guys are just beating
up on my big brother!
You're all a bunch of bullies!
That's not true.
We're not beating up
on him, young lady.
What's wrong, Kenichi?
Are you ready to quit?
N-no. Not even close!
His eyes!
Leave her alone!
--Stop it!
--Big Brother!
Anybody who picks on my little
sister has to answer to me!
Oh, yeah? Guess what happens
to spineless little bookworms
who try to play hero?!
Take that, smart guy!
What are you gonna
do about it, huh? Huh?
--You're just a joke!
--Stop it, stop it!
Are you ready to quit?
Oh, are you still here?
No!
Huh?
I'm not done yet!
That... that kid must
be crazy or something!
Run!
That was the last time
I saw his eyes like that.
Just one more time!
How long ago was it?
I always thought I was
the only one who knew
about my brother's
fighting spirit.
But I guess the
people in this dojo
have seen it too.
One more time!
Be sure to thank mom
for the boxed lunch
and tell her it was delicious,
but please don't come
here to visit me too often.
What? Why?
To tell you the truth,
I really don't want my little
sister to see how pathetic I am
at martial arts.
You're not pathetic.
I promise, just
like you say, then.
I won't come here to visit you
anymore if that's what you want.
Well, I guess I'll
see you when I see you!
And you too, Big Boobs.
Be careful and
look out for cars!
That kid...
Are you really sure that
was the right thing to do?
Telling her not to
come around anymore?
Yeah...
I think it's what's
best for her.
Ahhh, apapa.
There! I win!
Do you wanna play again?
Apa! How did you do that?
Hold on...
Did you forget the little
talk we had yesterday?
What? I didn't come
here to visit you,
but I'm planning to come here
every day from now on to play
with Apachai and Shigure and
you can't stop me, so there!
Honoka!
One more time, please.
Let's play another round, okay?
Me too! Please!
Yeah, okay! How 'bout I play
you both at the same time,
to make it fair?
Just shoot me.
Siblings... huh?
Hey! Shigure!
That's the wrong move!
You can't put that there!
What are you talking about,
we just started!
Ryozanpaku is the funnest
place in the whole world!
What am I gonna do?
This is a problem!
Hey, hey, what's the matter?
My teachers are coming
for a home visit!
But Grandpa is on a trip and
Akisame is gone too!
If they show up now, it could
turn into a real mess!
This is awful!
Re-lax! Don't worry about it!
We'll take care
of it, no problem!
Miu...
you have nothing to
worry about, so calm down.
Gosh, thanks, you guys,
you're the greatest!
Wait a minute!
What are you doing with
that sword, Shigure?!
Put that awaaaaaay!