Not so mouthy anymore, are you?
Another gang who
bragged they could
take down Ragnarok gets
crushed into little pieces.
Sweep up the rest of this trash.
Pardon the interruption, but
after giving it much thought,
I think it's time for
Kenichi to start training
in the advanced techniques.
What about the
rest of you? Well?
It's harsh. Some of the most
severe training known to man.
But I agree it's time.
Dunno. Could be dangerous.
His body's not made of steel,
If we rush his training,
he might die.
Yes, but if we take our
time when we train him,
Apachai is sure
Kenichi can survive
anything life throws at him.
Plus, there's a reason why
he almost drops dead.
You guys, you push him too hard.
Like you're one to talk, pal!
Excuse me,
Masters, but,
Could-could you please not
talk about me like I'm not here?
Or at the very least, leave out
the part about me dropping dead?
My apologies. I was about
to ask your opinion, too.
I must forewarn you that
it's intensive training.
You ready for it?
It's really hard?
Of course.
Can it wait just
a little longer?
Well how much time do
you need? Till tomorrow?
Akisame's really anxious
to start his training.
Hope you survive it, kid.
Advanced techniques, huh?
Earth to Kenichi!
You looked a little
spaced out there!
Just lost in my thoughts
a little, Takeda.
Is your arm still
getting better?
Yeah. It's recovering
pretty quickly.
So much, in fact, that I joined
the school's Boxing Club.
Not to rain on your
parade or anything,
but has anyone from
Ragnarok come after you?
Not yet. Rumor has
it they've been
busy with some
organizational changes.
I guess they have other
things to worry about.
Well, that's good!
So I guess you're okay
for the time being then?
But if anything happens...
I-I've got your...
I've got your back, man!
Thanks, but I can
take care of myself!
Really. But It means a lot to
me that you offered, though.
Say hello to that strong-armed
hottie girlfriend
of yours for me!
See ya later!
Good luck.
That's cold.
Hey, quit trying to
scare me like that!
What were you doing
in there anyway?!
Hmph! Sometimes I have
to hide in strange places
if I wanna get
the inside scoop.
Go do it someplace else, okay!
Hmph! You're colder
than that water!
By the way, did ya hear?
Kisara Nanjo's getting promoted.
She's joining the
Seven Deadly Fists.
What? Who's this Kisara
you're talking about?
You don't know?!
Ah well, I think I've heard
the name a few times before.
But I can't recall
meeting her.
You're really hopeless,
you know that?
Here, let me enlighten you.
Kisara Nanjo. A female executive
member of Ragnarok
who's steadily risen
through its ranks. She's
also a sophomore here.
Hold on!
You mean she's a
student at this school?
Hate to break it to you,
but you really are
dumber than you look.
Of course that's what I meant.
She's the person who's been
sending all those
scary goons after you!
Some additional facts:
she's skilled in Tae Kwon Do
and within Ragnarok,
she's known as "Valkyrie."
"Valkyrie?" You mean like the
goddess of Norse mythology?
The one who guides the
souls of dead warriors?
Oh! So you do know something!
Too bad it's useless geek
trivia! But you're right.
Just like the myth, this
Valkyrie takes those who
have fallen and uses them
to bolster Rangnarok's ranks.
Oh, man! I knew Kisara was
ambitious, but I never thought
she'd make it into
the Seven Deadly Fists
as fast as she has!
The Seven Deadly Fists?
What's that?
Don't tell me you
haven't heard of them!
What, have you been
living inside a cave
for the past
couple of years?
They're an elite group
of fighters made up
of the seven most powerful
members of Ragnarok.
You know the only thing
that all the other members
of Ragnarok fear? Them!
The Seven Deadly Fists!
But I guess they'll be
the Eight Deadly Fists,
once Kisara joins.
Wow, they sound pretty scary--
They are! And it's your fault
they're getting scarier!
The only reason Kisara's
becoming a Fist
is because you haven't
defeated her yet!
But I've never even met her!
You probably will soon enough!
I just hope you haven't
derailed my plan too much.
What do you mean "your plan?"
Don't worry about it. You've
got more important things
to do, namely your rematch
and eventual defeat of Tsuji.
What?
Now's the perfect
time to strike!
He's been vying to become the
Eighth Deadly Fist for awhile,
but Kisara just snatched
that spot out from under him!
He's totally devastated!
Really? If that's the case,
then I actually feel
kind of sorry for him.
Idiot!
Let me share a little
tidbit with you!
Ragnarok's assigned
someone to punish Takeda!
Guess who it is? Tsuji!
Still feel sorry for him?
If you don't do this, your pal
Takeda could get banged up
and it's bye-bye
boxing career again.
You've gotta stop Tsuji
and I'm willing to help.
I can't let Takeda
get hurt again.
I have to help him
however I can.
Just don't lose, okay?
That would really
screw up my plan.
I'm gonna go collect some
more data on the Fists
and Tsuji that'll help
you out, buddy.
While I'm doing that, you
go work on your skills. Later!
Now I have a pretty good idea
what planet you're from,
Dr. Spock.
His name's Mister Spock.
You seem different.
Confident, tougher even.
Yeah, I guess it's
due to all the stuff
I went through
on Furinji Island.
Leave her alone!
Never in a million years did I
ever think I'd fight a shark!
That's a story you'll tell
your grandkids one day!
Yep!
I should thank that shark for
helping me work up my courage!
Now I feel like I can take
on anybody, even Tsuji!
Oh, then this must
be your lucky day,
because he's standing
right over there.
Huh?
So what's your plan? Issue a
challenge and then take him on?
No no! Not just yet!
The prudent thing to do
would be to watch him
and see what he's up to before
devising my plan of attack!
What a wise strategy!
You're becoming the
Eighth Deadly Fist?
Yeah, right. Don't
make me laugh.
In case you didn't know,
Ragnarok only makes Fists
out of its most powerful
members, sweet cheeks!
I guess that's why they
chose me instead of you.
No way!
I got an idea. Why don't
you and I fight it out
to see who's more
worthy of the position.
But I'm not gonna go easy on ya.
Who asked you to? Bring it on.
Um, Kenichi?
--Damn you!
--Stop it!
I'm talking to you, Tsuji!
Wow, I've gotta admit, Kenichi
knows how to make an entrance!
You're dead, man!
Get 'im!
Well, not bad. Not bad at all.
Nice work! He took out
Tsuji and his two henchmen
all at once with
barely any effort.
That was pretty impressive,
for a sneak attack.
Um, hey, are you okay, miss?
That was pretty good, kid,
Or should I say
Kenichi Shirahama.
I'm sorry, but, uh,
have I met you before?
Not personally, but you
have gotten to know
a lot of my friends.
Yeah? Who are they?
Members of Ragnarok.
My name's Kisara Nanjo.
Hold up! Y-you mean
you're the Kisara Nanjo?!
In the flesh.
And you're the guy who defeated
Takeda's three-man army.
I've been looking forward
to fighting you for a while.
The way her pants are cut
and those defined quadriceps
are dead giveaways. Her
specialty must be kicking.
And the way she holds her stance
to her advantage like that...
She's no amateur;
she's a skilled fighter!
She's a lot more powerful
than she looks.
Don't let your guard
down, understand?
What? Don't worry about it.
Nothing's going to happen.
She's a girl.
Yeah, do you have
a problem with that?
Well, sorta.
One of my rules in life is that
a guy should never hit a girl.
That makes it sound
like I'm not a girl
since you try to hit me
in our sparring sessions.
But, with you, I know you
won't let me get a punch in.
Oh? So you admit you've at
least been trying to hit me.
Um, no, not really, I'm
not trying to hit you,
just touch you!
Touch me where?
Um! On your shoulders?!
Refusing to fight
a girl is sexist!
It's stupid crap like
that, that pisses me off.
Don't think you're something
special because your
sneak attack knocked Tsuji out.
He wasn't even looking.
Huh? My sneak attack?
That was a cowardly move!
I didn't realize
he wasn't looking!
You're not to blame. He is.
All you were doing was
trying to protect a girl.
Hey c'mon! I'm not
done with you yet!
Get back up here!
Tsuji, I'm really sorry!
Please wake up!
This is just too weird.
I don't have time
for this today.
Hey, kid. Lucky for you there's
somewhere else I need to be.
So I guess you're
off the hook for now.
Huh?
But not for long. I'll be seeing
you and your buddy Takeda
soon enough and then we'll
settle things once and for all.
Why are you and your
gang hassling him?!
Why can't you just
leave him alone?!
Hm. Maybe I'll consider
it, if you defeat me.
What do I do? I don't
wanna fight a girl,
but now it seems like
I have no other choice.
Even if you agree to fight
her, she'll beat you.
There's no possible
way you can win.
What?
I mean at least in
your current state.
She's much more powerful.
And much more experienced too.
Oh, no, that means...
I'm not strong enough
to protect Takeda.
I'd say you'd need to be
at least strong enough
to score a point against me.
Otherwise, you won't be
able to lay a finger on her.
So, there's only one
way to get stronger.
More advanced
technique training.
Hey, you! Come outta there!
What the heck?
There's only one of you?
No.
There are eight of us.
They have numbered
insignias on their gloves!
Only the toughest Ragnarok
members wear those!
Those guys must be
the Eight Deadly Fists!
Do ya think this
is some kinda joke?!
I thought we were finally
going to settle the score!
I brought 50 guys and
you only brought eight?!
Mismatched odds
are fine with us!
It's your funeral!
Well, just to be fair,
we should even the odds,
so you'll only fight
three of us for now.
Say what?!
You'll be fighting
our newest member,
the Eighth Fist, Valkyrie,
the Sixth Fist, Hermit,
and the Fourth Fist, Loki.
I sincerely hope your
men can handle it.
Once we're done with them,
we'll take care of you!
Come on, let's destroy 'em!
Three against 50?!
Oh, man!
They took down 50 guys
without even breaking a sweat!
And that was only
three of the Eight!
Breakfast is ready, everybody!
Come and get it!
Apapapapapapa!
So? What do you
say about starting
the advanced training
this afternoon Kenichi?
Thanks for the food, Masters!
I don't want to be
late for school!
Miu, we've gotta go!
What? No, we don't.
We still have time.
Tch! Guess that's "no."
I thought Kenichi conquered
his fears on the island.
After all he's been
through, why is he scared
of a new type of training?
You know, we could
just force him to do it.
Remember what happened the
last time we tried that?
It would just make him fear
the training even more.
Let's just give him some time.
He's proven to be the type that
will come around eventually.
Yeah. It's recovering
pretty quickly.
So much, in fact, that I joined
the school's Boxing Club.
You know what's the only thing
that all the other members
of Ragnarok fear? Them!
The Seven Deadly Fists!
But I guess they'll be
the Eight Deadly Fists,
once Kisara joins.
But not for long. I'll be seeing
you and your buddy Takeda
soon enough and then we'll
settle things once and for all.
Even if you agree to fight
her, she'll beat you.
There's no possible
way you can win.
What's the matter?
You can tell me.
Something's bothering
you, isn't it?
Sure is. The training for
the advanced techniques--
I'm really worried about it.
You are? That's strange.
Usually people are happy
when they progress from
one level to the next.
The training's tough, but you
shouldn't be scared of it.
Honestly, it's not just
the actual training.
Something else scares
me even more than that.
What?
You know, I'm not
the best student.
Well, I guess.
Even though I've been
training like mad for weeks.
If the masters taught me
the advanced techniques
and I still didn't improve...
Well, I'd be letting
them down again
and they'd be incredibly
disappointed in me.
And I just don't think
I could live with myself
if that happened.
I don't think they'd be
disappointed in you at all!
You see, to be disappointed
in someone means
that you gave up on them,
and let me tell you, the phrase
"give up" does not exist in
the masters' vocabulary!
Yeah, I guess you're right!
They'll keep trying
even when the training
leaves you battered,
bruised, and bleeding.
What?! If that's the case,
I wish they'd just go ahead
and give up on me now!
Hey there, pal! What's up?
Would you stop jumping
out at me like that?!
I really wouldn't keep
going down this street
if I were you! I'd
turn right instead!
Well, if I were you, I'd
go back to whatever rock
you crawled out from under!
Now get out of our way!
And let my buddy head
in the direction
where Tsuji's waiting
for him? I don't think so.
You should turn back.
Wait, Tsuji's down there?
Yeah, and word on the street is
he's ticked off at a certain
someone for knocking him
out when he wasn't looking.
Hey, it's okay, you only
did it to protect a girl!
Everybody knows about his defeat
now thanks to the cover story
of this morning's paper!
Written by yours truly!
I even made up a couple
of quotes from you.
"What a pushover!" and "Tsuji's
as weak as a little girl!"
I heard that last
one is what really
pushed him over the edge!
How could you do this
to me? You gossip monger!
You yellow journalist! You
mud-slinging, libelous, lying--
You say that as if
that's a bad thing!
Now if you'll excuse me,
I've got to go straighten
some things out with
him, no thanks to you!
Your level of stupidity never
ceases to amaze me!
If you walk down there,
Tsuji's gonna kill you!
I've gotta go try to
square things with him!
What are you, nuts?! You've
seen him when he gets angry!
You're no match for him!
He's gonna kick your butt!
Don't throw away the win you
earned with that sneak attack!
If you go down
there, you're dead!
I don't care what you say!
I'm going! If I turn around
right now, all I'm doing
is running away from my
problems like a coward would!
At this rate, my plan's
gonna fall apart.
I can't let that happen!
Ha! You want to keep
going down this street?!
Fine, but you're gonna have
to go through me first!
You should've
seen that comin'.
Go ahead and get
killed! See if I care!
I'll write your obituary
for the school paper!
He sure is a funny
best friend, isn't he?
Look over there Tsuji!
The kid's back!
Huh? So the coward
shows his face!
You're gonna pay for what you
did to me the other day, punk!
I'm gonna get you
back for those lies
you told the school
paper about me!
Thanks to that story, my
whole gang abandoned me!
All of 'em except
these two guys!
You know, this is all
your fault, Shirahama!
Look, about the sneak
attack, I'm really sorry.
But I didn't have anything
to do with that story.
My friend Niij--
Can the lame excuses!
That's the last thing
I wanna hear from you, man!
But you know what
I do want to hear?
The sound of your puny
body hitting the pavement!
Let's settle this! Fight me!
Right here, right now!
If that's what you want.
Oh, I want it all right, kid!
Really, really bad!
Huh?
What are you trying to do
with those lame punches?!
Bring it on!
Tsuji!
You okay?!
I knocked him out?!
That explains why
they feel you're ready
for the advanced training! Wow!
What do you, mean?
That kung fu move you just did.
That proves you can take
what you learned from
training and put it to use.
And you thought you
hadn't improved at all.
But you obviously have.
That's why the masters suggested
you begin advanced training.
They could see you
were ready for it.
I didn't really even think
about that punch, I just did it.
I guess my training
is paying off.
Aw, damn!
Are you alright, man?!
Hey, are you okay, Tsuji?
What-what just happened?
Oh. You beat me.
Fair and square. Well, I
guess that settles it then.
You two get outta here
and join another gang!
You don't wanna ruin
your street cred
by being seen with me!
Nah! We can't leave!
We don't wanna join another
gang! We'll stick with you!
A gang with no members, whose
leader has been defeated twice?
We used to be feared and
respected, but now look at us.
We're nothing but one big joke!
As of this moment,
this gang is no more!
A man's worth is determined
by the number of men
under his command.
I used to have many,
but now I have nothing!
Tsuji wait!
Don't go!
You're wrong, you know.
What?
Tsuji, you have something far
greater than 100 henchmen.
It's a rare gift, do you
have any idea what it is?
Friends you can trust! That's
right! Two of 'em, in fact!
Hm?
Kenichi! Old buddy, old pal!
I always knew you'd beat this
loser! I was about to jump in
and help you out, but you
took him down so quickly!
Lucky? This is the kind
of friend I've got.
Come on, yo! We go
wherever you go, man!
Hell yeah! The three of us
can always start a new gang!
You guys...
Alright, we'll do it, but our
new gang's gonna be independent
and break all
ties with Ragnarok!
Yeah!
Sounds good to me! Let's do it!
Hey, Kenichi.
What is it?
That friend of yours,
the boxer guy?
I heard that Ragnarok's giving
him a farewell beatdown soon.
But when?!
I don't know the exact date,
but Kisara will be there
along with a witness from
the Eight Deadly Fists.
One of the
Eight Deadly Fists? Who?
The Sixth Fist. The guy
who's also known as Hermit!
I'd watch out for
him. He's bad news.
See ya around, kid.
Did he say "Hermit?"
Yeah. Do you know anything
about him, Niijima?
Uh-huh.
I saw him fight a whole gang;
it was pretty intense.
Only three of the
Eight Fists fought,
but they took down 50 men
in like 30 seconds!
What's the plan?
Hi, everybody! We're home!
Welcome back.
Was your day eventful?
Master Koetsuji!
I've decided! Starting
today, I want to begin
training for the
advanced techniques!
Hm. I don't know what happened,
but that look in your eyes
is completely different
from the one this morning.
So, shall we get started then?
Yes!
Takeda, I heard the members of
Ragnarok are planning something!
They've really got it out for
you, so please be careful!
Hm, is that so?
I'll keep an eye out.
Thanks for the heads-up.
Here's my cell phone number.
Promise me that you'll call
at the first sign
of trouble, okay?!
Geez! You sound like you
my mother or something!
Hey, look, I appreciate the
concern, but don't worry.
I told you before, I can
take care of myself.
I'll be fine.
Takeda's a really
good friend of mine.
I can't let him down!
No matter what happens,
I promise I'll be there
to protect him!