[Music]
Patience...
We'll wait for
our disciple...
That's our responsibility
as masters.
What do you all think
of Kenichi's progress?
He's been training with
us for a while now
but he still seems
pretty slow.
Well, it's not as though
he really had any
talent to begin with.
There's nothing more we
can do at this point.
We've taught him
everything we can.
Now it's all up
to Kenichi...
He will progress if
he can learn to use
what we've taught
him in battle.
I have to try it...!
Here we go!
Pay attention to what
happens with your other arm!
When you use a karate punch
it should feel
like your arms
are connected to a
pulley behind you.
You got it, kid?
In kenpo you wanna draw
out your strength
but you also want your arms to
be more extended and relaxed.
Don't hold yourself
back- let your arms fly!
A Judo chop uses
the same physics
as a downward sword slash.
You're basically
challenging the balance
of a four sided object.
You use your body to
chop your opponent.
Kenichi...!
Muay Thai is not
only a sport...
There have been many
soldiers back home
who have used it
on the battlefield
fighting for their lives...
Apachai's master told him
you must punch with
all your strength...!
Make your punch go
through your opponent!
I couldn't dodge it...!
He keeps punching!
How many beats are
in this one punch?!
I can't count the beats.
I can't find the rhythm...
No...
There is no rhythm!
That punch...
That was quite an
excellent punch.
The way you used the
force of gravity
to strengthen it like that...
I lost.
Impossible!
How could he have
defeated Siegfried?
Damn...!I can't wait to
get my hands on that punk.
He ruined the
perfect plan.
Oh...?I'm sorry, Loki...?
Things not going your way?
Did you underestimate
your enemy...?
So who is this formidable
opponent of yours?
Kenichi Shirahama.
Kenichi Shirahama...?
Kenichi...
Don't tell me it's him...
Ow... that hurt.
So you think that because
you beat Siegfried
you'll be able to beat me...?
I'm sorry Kenichi
but you should know
better than that by now.
What's wrong with me...?!
I can't beat you.
It seems like no matter
how hard I train
I can never catch
up with you...!
All that hard work
and for nothin'!
Don't hurt me.
Sorry Honoka.
I didn't mean to...
I was just in
sparring mode.
Well, don't
bully my brother.
It was practice...!
Honoka... stop it.
Go away, big boobs!
Um... Kenichi...?
Why don't we call it a day.
Don't worry, I got
her outta here...!
I'll do anything to
protect my big brother!
I asked you to leave me
alone while I'm training.
Right?
Apachai would ya please keep a
close eye on her from now on?
Quit treating me
like a little kid!
Oh I sorry...
Apachai was busy concentrating
on his next move.
And that is the
double palm.
It lets you break down
your opponent's defenses
while attacking at
the same time...
Now... I think it's about time
we taught you
this technique.
Hello...?Are
you listening?
Miu beat me again today.
She's so strong...
Ooh...
I guess I'm just
not cut out
for all this martial
arts business.
I'm no good at it.
I'm a big ole loser.
I'll never become a master...
Kenichi... What is it?
So you're worried
that since you don't have
the natural talent-
no matter how
hard you train
you'll never be
able to beat Miu.
I'm starting to think that
my win against the
Fifth Fist was a fluke...
I guess I got
lucky that day.
I'm just a regular guy.
No matter how hard I train
I can never catch up to someone
who trains just as hard
but also has a
natural talent.
Apa...
Aa-pa-pa...
My goodness...
I've never heard such a
heavy sigh from you, Apachai.
He's down 'cause he
hasn't been able
to beat Kenichi's
little sister...
She wins every game
that they play.
How 'bout this, Apa...
-why don't you and I play?
-Really?
You go first...
You might learn
a thing or two.
Hey wait... What about your
terribly depressed disciple?
I lost.
Sakaki that was easy...!
I'm sorry but... you suck...
Kensei... can you
come play with me?
Me...? But I'm busy trying
to cheer up Kenichi.
Oh well...
I guess one game.
Are you guys good at
anything besides fighting?
Apa?
Master Koetsuji,
you said you're a pro at
both Shogi and Go, right?
And I've never lost at
a game of Othello...
I'll play against you...
But don't be
upset when I win.
Damn Akisame...
That game was so close
I was startin' to
get a little worried.
Whoa...! Crazy...!
He beat Apachai but
only by a single point!
Yeah...
And I wasn't holding back.
What'd you say?
Seriously?
Aa-pa-pa-pa...
I realized something
during that game...
It's not that we are
becoming weak as players...
It's that Apachai's skills
are growing exponentially.
It makes sense.
He plays the
game everyday...
Even when Honoka's not here...
he keeps playing... alone.
I guess Honoka's
not coming today.
Oh well, Apachai will
play against himself.
He's played with that
Othello set so much
that the pieces have started
to wear away in the center.
They keep getting
thinner and thinner...
Why didn't you tell us...?
We'd get you a new one.
Master... I'm ready
to learn it...
the double palm...
do you mind showing
me one more time?
What...? You
wanna do it now?
You must remember,
Kenichi...
Miu is always training...
Even while you were
moping around here.
I'm gonna catch up...
I know I can do it if I
don't waste anymore time.
You're not the only
aspiring martial artist...
There are others who have
felt the same pressure
you feel now.
The opponents you
are about to face
or will face in the future...
They've been in
your position...
They're in the midst
of their own training
and they've had to work
just as hard as you have.
You're right...!
I'm gonna train so hard
that I break
through the floor!
And I won't give up...!
Not until that happens!
Hold on a second.
I don't get it.
If Apachai is such a
great Othello player
then how come he's constantly
losing to Honoka?
Don't tell me she's better
than Master Koetsuji!
Well, you don't
bully my brother.
It was practice...
Akisame, it's
time for dinner!
Right... I'll be there
in just a few minutes.
I have to practice.
That all ya got?
I've had a slight change
of heart, Valkyrie...
I'll go ahead and
lift your ban today.
Watching your
team's defeat
was punishment
enough on its own.
Yes... I greatly
appreciate it...
Thank you, Odin.
You know...
I never thought
one of the Eight Fists would
lose to a single person...
I'm sure Siegfried'll be
outta commission for a while.
Shinpaku Alliance...
I can't wait to
return the favor...
I'm dyin' to get my hands
on Kenichi Shirahama.
If the leader of the
Shinpaku Alliance
really is the same
Kenichi Shirahama...
then I can finally fulfill
the promise I made
when we exchanged emblems.
I win by a landslide!
Are ya gonna take me on as one
of the Eight Fists or what...?
Well...?
What do you think?
So... what number are
ya gonna give me...?
Why don't you guys just
make me a replacement
for that idiot, Hermit?
Listen punk...
You're way outta
your league here.
Oh yeah...?
Who do you think you are talkin'
to me like that?!
No way.
Quite an entrance...
Welcome back...
good to see you again...
Hermit.
None of you will touch
Kenichi Shirahama.
I will be the
one to kill him.
I'm a little sad you
didn't contact me...
Lemme guess, you were
off training again...
Right, Hermit?
Look, I understand
that you wanna have one final
showdown with the kid...
but I'm stuck in this now
and I wanna see how it'll end.
As punishment for leaving
Ragnarok without notice...
I think you should write
"I'm sorry" 100 times
on a sheet of paper for us.
I will be the one to take
down the Shinpaku Alliance...
and to kill Kenichi
Shirahama...
We don't need
your help anymore.
Shut up, Loki...
I don't have to
answer to you.
Wha?!
That's enough, you two.
I'll give you another
chance, Hermit...
But know that I do
not accept failure.
Damn it. Do you know
what this is gonna do
to Ragnarok's reputation?
This is bad news.
Hermit's always
been a loose cannon.
I might have a hard time
controlling him later.
I've never seen Hermit so
serious about an opponent.
You're pretty good,
Kenichi Shirahama.
But the next time you
face him he'll kill you...
You're a dead man.
Jeez...
I shouldn't be here I should
be training at the dojo.
Oh c'mon... it'll be fun.
Now quit whining-
you know taking your
little sister shopping
is one of your
brotherly duties.
But I don't wanna...
Now if it was
shopping with Miu...
Oh, Kenichi!
You mean you haven't
gotten over her yet...?
Are you saying that big boobied
bimbo is more important to you
than your adorable
little sister...?!
What's the matter with
you, ya big dummy!
They must be siblings-
isn't that cute.
I get it! I get it...!
Cut it out!
Man...
I'm so glad that I could
help you see things
from my point of view.
It's so pretty!
Yeah, yeah...
It's pretty.
I bet it's
really expensive.
Keep up, Honoka.
I'm leaving you behind.
I just wanna look a
little bit longer.
You wanna repeat that, punk?
C'mon. Tell us what you said.
Yeah... Speak up.
I... don't know...
I asked you guys
to calm down.
No, before that...!
Do you have the nerve
to say it again, loser?
Oh... that...
I, uh...
I guess...
I said you're dead
men walking...
And that I'll take all
3 of you bastards on
if we can just go somewhere
a little less crowded...
that what you heard?
Why don't we go into
that alley over there?
I don't wanna scare
anybody, you know?
What the hell is
up with this guy?
I gotcha!
You suck...!
You guys shouldn't be ganging
up on one person like that!
Fights are supposed
to be one-on-one.
Al least that's what the guy
with the mustache told me.
Oh... really...?
Well, thanks a lot for
buttin' in with that info...
I've never wanted to hit
a little girl before...
But now...
I've changed my mind!
My big brother is a
fighter for justice!
Alright big brother...!
Go get him!
Where'd he go?
Die you little brat!
-No way!
-Damn you!
Whoa! A fight!
Wow! It's just
like the movies!
Hey! Hold on a second,
pretty boy!
You're not gonna leave me all
alone out here, are you...?
Help me Mr. retty
Boy it's dangerous...
I'm adorable.
Could ya be a little
more delicate?
You're worse than Apachai!
So many people!
Hey Honoka!
Where are you?!
Where did she run off to?
It's gettin' late-
I should be on my way
back to the dojo by now.
Are we going to
see a doctor?
Doctors can't be trusted.
So I've brought you here.
Where's "here"?
My house.
Be more gentle, would ya?!
Alright, I'm done.
Now get out of here.
You can't just throw
me outta here...!
What if your
bandaging is lousy?!
Oh wow.
That's awesome...!
My knee doesn't
hurt at all!
You're not so
bad after all!
Get goin'.
Wow, I've never seen
such a big house!
Ooh! What a beautiful statue-
it looks expensive!
You must be really rich
to have such a big house
in the middle of the city...
So tell me... how much
are you really worth?
Millions or Billions?
Why is this covered?
What a waste.
Stop it.
A rich guy like you doesn't
bother to offer a girl tea?
-How rude.
-Just get outta here!
Oh well I'll go
make the tea
it's my way of saying
thanks for saving me.
I don't want tea- I
want you to leave!
I didn't know...
you live here by yourself!
Leave now!
You don't have anything
in your refrigerator!
Don't tell me you
eat fast food
and convenience
store food everyday.
Hey...
Looks like we're
not having tea...
I'm gonna take
what I can find
and try to make a home cooked
meal for you, sound good?
Please go!
Just... like her.
What is wrong with you?!
Have you ever cooked
a meal before?!
I suck at home ec.
What kinda girl am I?
Don't do it!
You don't have to force
yourself to eat it!
Hey big brother...
I made something very special
for you to eat today.
It's been a long time
since anybody cooked
a meal for me.
I'll go make some more!
No, that's okay-
I've had plenty.
Now... It's time
to start cleaning!
Would you please
just go home?
Someone's gotta take
care of this dust!
How long has it been since
you cleaned the place?!
What a nice picture.
Is that your dad and
your little sister?
Put that down right now!
Don't worry about me...
Just get outta here.
You know, when you get angry
your face changes back
to how it looked when
you were fighting.
Hey, you wanna see what
your face looks like
when you're in a fight?
Like this!
What?
You're laughing!
That's awesome...!
It must be a pretty
good impression!
Cut it out! Seriously!
Stop!
I'll see ya later,
Mr. retty Boy.
Until next time!
Please don't come back.
Man, she's a weird kid.
Hey Honoka,
where are you...?!
Time to go home...!
Come on out...!
We gotta go!
A-pa...
You're never gonna
beat me, Apachai!
Wow.
I gotta admit... Kenichi's
sister has got mad skills.
She might even be more
talented than Kenichi
at martial arts...
You think?
Could we play one more...?
Pretty please?
Sure thing...! I'll play
Othello with you anytime!
I bet you guys
had a great time
shopping together
this afternoon!
I'm jealous...
You're so lucky...!
It must be fun to
have a sibling!
You've gotta
be kidding me!
You have no idea how long
I wandered the streets
looking for her!
She told me she went to
some strangers house!
And that's not good-
she should know better...
You're a little kid...
be careful...
But he saved me from
those big jerks...!
He's not a bad guy-
I can tell...
He's nice...
He totally saved my life!
Listen...
Just cause the guy beat up
some delinquents to help you
doesn't mean
he's a good guy...
You can never tell just
by looking at someone!
I was really worried
about you, Honoka...
Are you even
listening to me?!
Now, now, calm
down Kenichi.
Although...
You are right.
You can't always judge
a book by its cover...
Someone who seems nice on the
outside could be evil inside...
I learned that
with Tanimoto.
The man who tried
to kill me...
The Sixth Fist of
Ragnarok, Hermit.
Shut up...!I've been
playing a role my whole life
so that I
could someday...
rule over both the
darkness and the light!
Then when I'm ready
the entire underworld
will bow down before me!
I wonder what
he's planning...
I know he's up
to something.
Hey Kenichi, don't worry
about that right now.
Right now... You need to
focus on the double palm.
Yes, sir...!
I can do it...!
I'll keep training...
Until I break
through the floor!
He must be good if he was
able to beat Siegfried.
Well, if he wasn't good
then he wouldn't
be worth fighting.
I will beat you
next time...
Kenichi Shirahama!
[Music]
What are you doing?!
I'm warning you- if
you touch me you die!
Sorry little girl but I'm
gonna be using you as bait
to lure out your
brother, Kenichi.
You can't do that!
If you hurt my big brother
I'll never forgive you!
And just so you know-
my brother is strong!
You baddies are
no match for him!
He's gonna show
you who's boss!
I guess I'll just have
to prove you wrong.
Next time you see Kenichi
he'll be crawling on the
ground begging for mercy.
He's not gettin' past me.