[Music]
Why did you drag my
sister into this...
That's dirty-
even for Ragnarok!
True... True?
Kenichi!
Fine- I'll do it.
Prepare to die, Shirahama!
You can hit me as
much as you want.
Hold... on...
You shouldn't even be able
to stand right now...
Your defenses are
better than I thought.
Go ahead and hit me
as much as you want...
as long as you
give Honoka back!
Well, now that's the spirit...
I'm fine with letting her go
if I get to beat
the crap outta you.
Now see what you
made me do...!
I told ya to stop
squirming around.....
This is your
fault, you know.
Help me big brother!
This is really
startin' to get old...
It's time we ended this,
don't you think??
Big brother!
I told you to stop!
Why...
Why'd you do that??
You shouldn't be
holding a weapon
if you're not gonna
use it properly.
This is it, kid!
Kenichi Shirahama!
It's okay.....! I'm safe
and sound now, guys!
Kill Loki!
Damn you... Hermit!
Fine... You're
just a traitor...
I'm sure everyone will
be happy to hear that...
Come down and fight
me like a man!
And you too Kenichi
Shirahama...
I'll take on
the both of you!
That's enough!
What's he doing here??
The First Fist!
Leave him alone, Loki.
The First Fist...
This can't be good news...
now I'm scared.
Why are you
afraid of him??
Cause he's the
leader of a gang...
and he doesn't mess around.
We're gonna be
in big trouble
if he brought all of
Ragnarok with him...
We'll be seriously
outnumbered.
Good to see you again,
Kenichi...
It's been a long time.
I guess you don't
remember me, huh??
That's okay.
I'm not worried about it.
I know the promise we made
will be fulfilled soon.
C'mon Let's go, Loki.
No way...!
You don't understand
how serious I am...
I'm not leavin' til I beat
the crap outta this punk.
I'll forgive you this once
for using the
Great Sage Fist's name
for your own
personal gain...
But I should warn you,
if you break the
rules again...
How'd he do that??!
I wanted to get rid of you
but for some reason
the great Sage Fists
wants to keep you onboard.
You're lucky we still
need your talent...
but if you don't follow
the rules it's over.
Whoa... Did he just
let him off the hook??!
Villains aren't
supposed to play fair
and they're not supposed
to give second chances.
What's the
matter with him??
You dumb ass...
How would you know what
it takes to be a villain-
you're nothin' but a pansy.
I have the makings
of villain-
I even have the ability
to make a demonic face!
Well... If villains are ugly
that explains why
Ukita, Hermit and I,
three of the top five
hottest guys in Ragnarok,
have changed our ways.
Was Loki one of the
top 5 hottest guys
because he's not
bad looking either.
Yeah... But he's only
slightly above average
so he's barely in.
'Slightly above average'
would be good looking, right??
Damn it.
Get the bike, Number 20!
Let's get outta here!
C'mon!
Wait!
What's the
matter, Kenichi?!
Are you feeling okay??!
Wait... I'll never forgive
you for what you've done...
I swear I'm gonna
take you down.
Now that's the
spirit, Kenichi.
Get angry and then work
your way up to my level.
Listen Hermit...
You need to remember
that our leader,
the Great Sage Fists,
deals with things a
little differently
than most people.
He never sends out
direct orders...
As an organization
we are simply there
to support him
and his beliefs.
I'm sorry Loki used
you like that...
It's not too late
to reconsider...
It's in your best interest
to stay with Ragnarok.
Forget it...!
I was using you because I needed
a place I felt I belonged...
But the Great Sage Fists
has taught us all to
walk our own paths.
That's unfortunate...
Then the next time we meet
we'll be mortal enemies, Hermit.
He... disappeared.
Yet another victory for
the Shinpaku Alliance...!
So that was Odin
the First Fist...
But why did he act like
I should know him??
Hang in there, Kenichi.
He'll be okay-
don't get too close...
your boobs'll
suffocate him.
Would you shut up??!
Yay.....!
We're okay!
OW!...
Careful Honoka,
I'm really sore.
Oh, whoops-I'm sorry ...
It's just I'm so
proud of you, brother!
Thanks... Glad you're okay.
That was so cute...
I really wish I
had a sibling.
Thanks... You saved my sister...
Guess I owe ya one...
I can't thank you enough.
I'm sorry but you
got the wrong idea...
The only reason I
saved her from Loki
is cause they were in the way-
I wanna end this
thing right now.
Are you kidding, me??!
You can't be serious.
Hermit, you still
wanna fight Kenichi??!
Of course I do...
I haven't changed my mind-
I still hate him.
What do you say.....?
Are you ready to take
me on now, Shirahama??
Yeah...
No prob...... Think
I can handle that...
You may be a big jerk
but I don't hate you.
But you're in no
condition to fight!
Sorry but I have
no choice...
I mean, I guess
I kinda owe him
one for saving my
sister's life.
If he wants a fight
then he'll get it.
I know you can do it...!
The Shinpaku Alliance
will win!
Piss off, ya alien freak.
They look lively.
I can't believe they have
the strength to fight anymore.
Well, They're youngsters...
In all honesty I think
it would be a shame
if they didn't fight...
after all we already bet
our desserts on them.
It looks like Kenichi's
taken on a lot of damage...
But I shouldn't be worried-
I bet it all on the
caped kid, right??
Just how much have
you had to drink?
I bet on the caped kid
and you bet on Kenichi.
You guys shouldn't
be fighting-
both of you are
really beat up!
Just Let them do
their thing... honey.
This is the end, Shirahama!
When two men have
a score to settle
there's no stopping them...
especially when
they're rivals.
Look at that- somethin's
up with capey there.
So you noticed it too...?
He's wasting all
of his energy...
No one has the endurance
to keep that up for long.
He's really hurt!
Well, Kenichi's injuries are
pushing his limits as well...
It seems this fight is about
to get very interesting.
Die!
No way!
Damn... If he
had taken that hit
he would've been
totally annihilated!
Whoa, that was
Ying Kung Fu!
Ying Kung Fu...
In that style
conditioning is used
to harden the
exterior of the body
which increases the
user's power...
It's considered much more
destructive than Kenpo.
Makes sense to me-
in karate we do
conditioning too-
we hit training poles
with our bare fists
to toughen them up...
All hand-to-hand
combat styles do it.
That's funny my palms
are as soft as can be.
This is the end...
Now... die!
Aw, hell yeah...!
He blocked it!
This is your chance, Kenichi!
Stop fighting.....!...
Please I'm begging you!
Kao Loi!
Big brother...
Look at them all.....!
Dontcha think chrysanthemums
are beautiful !
Oh, don't you worry...
I'm not gonna let some
stupid sickness beat me.
Big brother you can't
give in, okay.....?
Please promise me.
You can't give in!
No...! I will not give in!
Wait... He's unconscious.
Kenichi!
You did some damage!
This isn't good.
He's lost a lot of blood.
Will he be okay?!...
Hey pretty boy!
That was the best fight
I've seen in a while.
Our disciple's
come a long way.
And the winner is...
Kenichi!
Looks like your dessert
is mine tonight, Akisame.
Yes but dessert doesn't
happen until later.
Right now we need to get the
caped kid to my clinic...
before he dies
from loss of blood.
How long have the two of you
been watching all of this?!
Since the beginning!
I can't believe you guys!
Are you kidding me?!
Let me get this straight,
you were hiding in a tree
watching everything go down?!
I could've used your help!
Honoka was kidnapped!
But I'm not sure Master Sakaki
would've been any help-
I can smell the
alcohol from here.
Nice one.....! Got me.
Stop! This isn't
a laughing matter!
Guess I shouldn't
thank him
for winning me an
extra dessert just yet.
Big brother!
It's time to change
your bandages!
Wait a sec, didn't you
just change them?! Well??
It's my job to
change your bandages-
the mustache man
told me to...
He said every
hour on the hour.
Say what.....!..?
It takes too long
to do it every hour!
That's what you think.
Are you trying to
kill me, Honoka??
Ryozanpaku certainly
is a lot more exciting
whenever you're around.
Oh hey, Miu!
We're glad to have
you back, Kenichi.
Welcome home.
Oh...... wow...
Thank you!
This place was so quiet
when you left us...
It almost felt like there
was no one living here.
I am home!
Cut it out, Honoka!
I can't breathe!
I'm just doin' my job!
Hey... Kenichi...
Miu bought a new set-
you wanna play me??
Or you can throw
kunai with me...
Well.....?
What do you say??
I gotta admit it was pretty
lonely around here without you.
In fact, it was so lonely
that I decided to
spend my free time
taking pictures
around Ryozanpaku...
I don't suppose
you're interested??
The only reason
you were lonely
is you didn't have
anyone to swindle.
I get it.
You don't want them.
I never said that
I didn't want them.
I've done everything
I can, Kensei...
The rest is up to you.
Master...
Can you tell me how
Tanimoto's doing??
Well, he seems
to be stable...
But he lost a lot of blood
from that stab wound.
Wait a minute,
he was stabbed??
Yeah. It happened when he was
saving me from that girl...
I saw it.
He's suffered loss of blood
and the fighting you
did after he was stabbed
didn't help his situation...
It's a miracle that the boy
lasted as long as he did.
But don't you
worry about him...
Although we didn't do
a blood transfusion
he should recover quickly
with Kensei's acupuncture.
Alright... I'll go
check him out, then.
I'll go with you!
No... I wouldn't do that.
But why??
There's really
not much to be said
between winners and losers.
Kenichi.....!...
You play me now??
No come with me...
We can do some sparring...
Well??
Where... Where am I??
You've obviously
trained very hard-
your muscle definition
is impressive.
Who are you??!
I am your master
Sougetsu Ma's brother...
My name's Kensei Ma.
You're Master Sougetsu's
little brother?!
Who admitted me
to this place?
I don't trust
doctors.....!...
And who the hell gave you
permission to treat me?!
You were treated
by Akisame...
My specialty is a
little different...
Acupuncture.
Don't think of them as
needles and they won't hurt...
Now I have a question
that I'd like to ask you.
Pretend you're
a man, will you?
there's a good boy.
Tell me......
Was my brother
a good master??
He taught me to
kill people...
how to take
someone's life...
He was strict and seemed
to enjoy bullying me
during training.
He was cold-blooded
and ruthless...
And I think he was the
perfect martial artist.
Is that so??
However he did
have one flaw...
When he was drunk he
would talk to me about
how much he cared about
his little brother.
I've heard so much about
you and all of it good.
He said even though he could
never live a peaceful life
he hoped his brother
was able to......
in Japan...
So I guess...
he was talking about you.
What's the hurry, Honoka?
Where are you off to??
It's time to go change the
pretty boy's bandages now!
Hey! What are you doing
out of bed.....?..?...!
Didn't they tell you that you
needed to get some rest??!
Shut up.....!...
Listen midget...
I don't ever wanna see
you at my house again...
And that's an
order, got it??!
You don't have to
leave just yet...
I thought maybe
you and my brother
could hang out a little
and then- you'd be friends.
I'm sorry kiddo but I've got
more important things to do.
I'm a rebel- I'm so tough-
you can't tame me...
meeehhhhh
I'm so proud of
this pine tree.
I just gave it
a little TLC
and look how beautiful
it has become.
Take care of your wounds...
You'll regret
it if you don't.
I used to live
all alone as well
so I know what
it feels like...
So I thought maybe
you would benefit
from a little bit of advice
from one of your elders,
my young friend.
You've chosen
to walk a path
that while dignified
is very lonesome...
so I should warn you...
That path leads
to nothing...
not a single thing.
Your elders are
always right.
They've experienced it all.
I can't believe that Honoka was
hanging out with Tanimoto!
And why was she so
desperate for me and him
to be friends??
I don't know- it
almost feels like fate.
I know Tanimoto was only
looking out for her safety
when he told her not to
go to his house anymore
but still...
she seemed like she was
really depressed about it.
I mean, maybe we could
become friends someday......
You never know.
Hey everybody, look
who's back.....!...
Natsu Tanimoto's
come back to school!
You've been gone
for such a long time
we were starting to get
really worried about you!
I was in an accident so I had
to take some time to recover.
As leader of the
Shinpaku Alliance
I've got the
world at my feet.
It's good to see you, Miu......
So did you miss me??
Uh... sure.
Hey, I wanna apologize
to you Shirahama...
I know it's been
tough for you
with all those
rumors going around.
What.....?..?...! You mean
that story isn't true??!
So, wait, the accident
wasn't his fault??
No, are you kidding?
He would never do
a thing like that-
the poor guy was framed.
He's crazy!
All of this was his fault!
Well, don't worry I'll make sure
everyone knows the truth.
Hey and one more
thing before I forget.
I've decided to stay but only
until I can exact my revenge.
So I suggest you watch your
back from now on, got it??
Well, I guess I'll
see you guys later.
What's up Heri-...
Oops, I mean...
Tanimoto.....?...
Just wanted to let you know
we've got a pipin' hot spot
in the Shinpaku Alliance
reserved for you.
Wait up!
If you join there's
all kinds of perks!
I can even make you
one of our generals!
How's that sound?
Huh??
[Music]
Whoa, master! What the hell are
you doing hiding out here?
What's wrong with you?
Renka came all this
way to see you!
That's what you think.
Renka just wants to
take me back to China
and I'm not ready
to go back!
I wanna stay here!
Don't make me go!
Your life's been pretty easy
since you came to Japan, huh?
Maybe it's time
for you to go back.
You've had a nice
vacation, right??
I'd be careful what
you say, Kenichi.
Renka's set her sights on
taking you back with us!
What?! Me?!
What does she
want with me?!
Uh-huuuuuh.
I'm not going!