Nice to meet you.
My name is Tanimoto.
So you're the famous
Kenichi Shirahama.
I've heard a lot about you.
He's totally dreamy!
Like a pop star!
Oh, man, I haven't got a
prayer against this guy!
Tanimoto says the Drama
Club is short-handed
for their next play,
so he asked me
if I'd like to play Juliet
in "Romeo and Juliet."
I'm playing the part of Romeo.
It's true, the two of them
would be perfect together!
He's only a freshman,
but he's already the head
of the Drama Club and a born
leader. He gets good grades
and naturally the teachers
are wild about him.
But he never brags about
it, and what's more,
he tutors other students
in his spare time.
I think he's a little too
perfect, he just can't be real!
It's like Persian carpets,
no matter how squeaky clean
they seem to be, if you
pound them hard enough,
they're bound to show some dust!
Do you think so?
Hey, bro, when it comes
to dirt, I'm an expert.
This guy's suspicious. My sensor
is tingling like crazy.
And it's never wrong.
Aw c'mon, Kenichi!
Please cheer up.
You know that I believe in you!
Yeah. Thanks, Izumi.
No problem.
People can be so mean,
can't they, Shirahama?
Tanimoto!
Oh my gosh it's the
famous Prince Tanimoto!
What are you doing here?
Sometimes it just isn't
important how good
your intentions really are,
people are always going
to misinterpret your actions,
so it doesn't actually
matter what the truth is.
But I want you to
know I believe in you.
When I first heard the rumors
about the Martial Arts
Research Club being beaten up,
I was afraid you might've
been the one who did it.
But you're someone who
knows where to draw the line.
And what happened
yesterday was just sick
You know, everybody in
school has this crazy idea
that I'm some sort of
Mr. Perfect Student.
Consequently I don't
have many friends.
So I'd be really happy
if you'd consider me
as one from now on, Shirahama.
Sure. That sounds great.
What was it?
That look in his eyes.
A sort of sadness, shimmering
like a faint light.
Oh man he's so totally
hot! What am I doing?
I can't cheat on Kenichi!
Oh, Romeo!
Deny thy father and
refuse thy name,
or if thou wilt not,
be but sworn my love.
Whoa! She's so awesome!
That's wonderful, absolutely
wonderful! Way to go!
All the practice you've
put in has really paid off!
Congratulations Miu!
It's looking good!
Really?
But I think most of the credit
has to go to your coaching!
Damn it! She's right!
With him as her leading man,
her performance has
definitely improved!
There's no way I can deny it!
Those two are perfect together!
Don't be an idiot! If you
really can't stand the thought
of them together,
then take action.
Go ahead and kick his
butt from here to China!
According to my records
he only has a C minus
in physical ability,
it should be a snap.
Would you just shut up!
Oh come on! Don't you
know people are already
referring to them as
the perfect couple?
We should strip him naked,
paint him blue, and hang him
upside down from the tower
before things go too far!
I said shut up!
Tanimoto and I are friends,
you hear me, friends!
If you don't cut it out
I'm gonna get mad!
Ha! Fell for the old
"let's be friends" dodge, huh?
Man, you're such a sucker!
Look at him, Natsu Tanimoto...
No matter how you slice
it, there's something
wrong with that guy.
Man, all Kisara does
these days is train.
Meanwhile, I gotta look
for that big-boob girl.
Man, this is really
starting to get old.
You know what?
You look really pretty
without your glasses on Miu.
Huh? Oh no, I don't think so!
I've found her!
You really should get rid
of these geeky glasses
and switch over
to contact lenses.
No Contact lenses...
They just don't seem to
work well with my eyes.
Oh, I see.
That was just amazing!
Well, after all, I'm
in the Gymnastics Club.
Huh?
Oh man, they almost figured
out she wears fake glasses.
Ha, ha! I found her!
Who would have guessed she was
a student at my own school?!
Hey, Kisara! Looks
like you owe me one!
Did you find out where
that stupid cow is hiding?
Yeah, she turned out to be
a student at our school!
Damn! She was under
my nose all this time!
I've gotta be more
careful next time we meet.
I didn't think another
girl could be that good.
Anyway, this time I won't
hold back on that amateur!
All the extra training I've done
has made me way faster than
she could ever be with that big
rack of hers slowing her down!
Yeah! We're finally
gonna have some action!
Wait, Kisara.
We've received another
communication from Hermit.
Huh? Now what?
What's he want this time?
Uh, well, you see...
That "stupid cow",
Rather, Miu Furinji
is off limits.
You're not to touch her.
Who does that guy think he is?!
I'll do what I want with her!
Hold on, the way
things are right now--
You can tell Hermit from me
that if he gets in my way,
he's next, you got that?!
Don't you think we
should stop her?
After you.
What's wrong?
That was such a sad sigh.
What about you?
You sound down too.
Oh, no. It's just
everyone at school
seems to have the
wrong idea about me.
You know what I mean?
Oh, I wouldn't worry too
much, all that nonsense
is bound to blow over
sooner or later.
I sure hope so.
The truth is, I can't seem
to stop thinking about you.
So, what about you?
You must be pretty nervous
about tomorrow's
performance going well.
That's part of it,
I guess, but also...
Everybody else
in Drama Club,
well, they've got their families
coming to watch them perform
and cheer them on and stuff.
But me...
You know Grandpa's gone south
again on another trip, and I--
I just started thinking...
I'm gonna be all alone,
just like I was during parents'
day back in grade school.
Wait a minute, you have me!
Huh?
I'll come to the show tomorrow
and I'll cheer for you
as loud as three families could!
Really? That'd be great!
Thank you, Kenichi!
But, try not to cheer too loud
during the performance,
so people can hear.
Huh? Oh, yeah! I'll try!
You're sure? Miu said that?
It's really none of my
business, but I thought you'd
wanna know. I'm just passing
the information along.
So, there you are.
The Elder sure picks bad
times to go out of town.
There'll be cute
high school girls.
I-I mean, I should go,
for Miu's sake!
Very well. I think we
should all be in attendance.
Welcome to the show!
Come in and have a seat!
Really? You're
Ms. Furinji's father?
Huh?
Yes, thank you so much for all
your help with my daughter.
This is her brother,
and the lady's my wife.
You know,
you probably should've left
your sword at home Shigure.
Hey, at least it's
in a bag, all right?
Hi! My name is Apachai!
It's a good thing
we got here early.
These are good seats!
Everybody came!
They're all here for me!
I'm not gonna be alone today!
Hey, Miu, you ready?
It's almost time!
Ready!
Wait a sec.
Now that I think about it, I
didn't see Kenichi out there.
Hey! What are you doing
still moping around here?
Isn't the play supposed
to start any minute now?
To tell the truth, I'm not
sure I can bear to watch it.
It's just too much.
What?! Seriously, man,
you need to grow a pair!
You promised her
you'd be there, right?
So get going!
You know something?!
Turns out there's a big kissing
scene in Romeo and Juliet!
Reality check, loser,
it's just a play!
But I can't stand it!
I wish they'd just cancel
the stupid play and
get it over with!
Man, he's pathetic.
Stupid play!
Stupid kissing scene!
Listen, I'll let you guys
take care of the
Shinpaku Alliance wimps,
but the cow is mine, you got it?
Oh, man. That's Kisara Nanjo,
and it looks like they're
heading for the school.
But who's this cow
they're talking about?
Is she talking about Miu?
Moo! Got milk?
Uh, so what are you
gonna do, Kisara?
You know that girl is in
the middle of doing a play
right now, don'tcha?
How're you gonna get her?
So she's on stage, huh?
That kind of appeals to me.
I'll ruin her little acting
debut, and humiliate her
right there in front
of an audience!
What? That's terrible!
I've gotta try and
stop her somehow!
Not so fast!
Niijima! Where'd you come from?
Hey, sneaking up on people is
a major part of my skill set!
Aren't you worried?
This could spell big trouble
for your beloved
Shinpaku Alliance, you know!
You can relax.
I told the members to stand
down until things blow over.
I see. That's a relief.
This is no time to stand down,
Miu could be in danger!
Whoa, hold on. This
could be good for you.
if this attack goes forward,
Miu's kissing scene
won't come up and your
worries are over.
And your monster masters
are sitting in the audience,
so they'll be able to protect
her and take of Kisara!
First of all, I don't understand
why they cast that cow
in the role of Juliet when
there are so many other girls
who could play it! I mean,
where does it say in the script
"Juliet has to be a D-cup"?
Why is everyone so
obsessed with that?
It's not a talent!
Uh-oh, someone' jealous,
Shut up!
Why would I be jealous of her?!
I'm sorry!
Yeah, you're right.
If I just leave well enough
alone, the performance will
be ruined so the kissing
scene won't happen,
and the masters will mop
up Kisara and her thugs
so no one will get hurt.
All my problems will be solved!
Besides, there's no way I
could stop them all by myself!
I've got no choice
but to let them go.
Ha! Now you're making sense!
I was asked to play
the part of Juliet!
I think I'm losing my voice.
I can't do it!
Maybe I have no talent!
You're better than Apachai!
Wait, is this a real dagger?
Yes. It makes it more dramatic.
Don't get too caught up
in your character.
Remember technique is
as important as passion!
Right! That'd be great, Kenichi!
But try not to cheer too loud
during the performance,
so people can hear.
Let's go. I know a good spot.
We can watch the action
in air-conditioned comfort.
Not so fast, you guys!
If you clowns are planning on
disrupting Miu's performance,
you gotta get past me first!
If they do see thee,
they will murder thee.
Tell me, by whose direction
foundst thou out this place?
By love, that first did...
prompt me to inquire.
He lent me counsel
and I lent him eyes.
I am no pilot; yet, wert thou as
far as that vast shore wash'd...
Hey, this is better
than I expected!
Sh! This is a very
impressive performance!
This young man playing
Romeo is simply amazing!
He's not only completely
committed to the emotional core
of the role, but he's able to
adjust his performance based
on the audience's
subtle reactions.
He's young, but he's skilled!
Hey! Akisame! Hey!
Would you keep it down, please?
But that damn fool Kenichi
hasn't shown up yet.
I even saved a
special seat for him.
I understand. I know what
you're going through, Kenichi.
It's tough to be young.
By and by I come, Nurse!
Leave me now,
tomorrow I will send.
Adieu, my love!
That move...
That was the "stepping method"!
That can't be part of the play.
That boy's had some form of
intensive martial arts training!
Well, well. Looks like
the Shinpaku Alliance's
commander has
come out to play.
Get him!
Come here!
Stop right there! You're
never gonna get past me!
What?! Is he stupid?
He missed a perfect opportunity!
Damn it.
You'll pay for the other day!
Take this!
Punk!
Damn you!
Uppercut!
Yamazuki!
Hey!
Let them go.
Well, I don't know
what kind of training
you've been going through,
but you've definitely
gotten a lot better.
I've changed my mind.
I'll take him on first, then
I'll deal with that cow later.
You'll be perfect as a warm up.
So whadda you say, boy-o,
let's see what you've got.
Don't come any closer!
I've told myself I'd
never fight a woman!
I'm not gonna change my
principals 'cause of you!
What? What did you say?
So, you've resolved never
to fight with a woman?
Do you think that
makes you cool?
Have you forgotten
what I told you before?
That kind of macho
crap pisses me off!
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
Uh, the strap on my left shoe
snapped off all of a sudden!
Oh my goodness! Wait here.
I'll go grab another
pair from wardrobe.
Oh, okay. Thank you very much.
I thought these
shoes fit perfectly.
That's so weird.
These violent delights
have violent ends,
and in their triumph die,
like fire and powder,
which as they kiss consume!
The sweetest honey is loathsome
in his own deliciousness!
This isn't good.
I've never seen Kisara
this angry before.
That kid. He's as good as dead.
What's wrong?
Are you still too
cool to fight a girl?
Come on!
So, are you finally
ready to take me on?
I told you, no!
There's no way I'm
gonna fight you!
Damn you. Y'punk...
I'll kill you!
You won't fight me
'cause I'm a girl?!
How dare you say that!
Just look at her go!
She never lets up,
not even for a minute!
She'd beat me.
All right! That's
enough for today!
Yes, sir!
Kisara, it almost looks
like you've decided
to give the guys a
run for their money!
Yes, sir!
No matter what, I've resolved
never to be bested by any man!
When it comes to competing
at Tae Kwan Do,
I'll bet someday I'm even
gonna beat you master!
I see, then we'll have to
have a match someday, huh?
You bet!
You know, you're really amazing,
Kisara, I mean, even though
you're just a girl you not only
keep up with the boys' training
program but you manage
to pack in a ton
of extra practice as well!
Oh, come on, don't
say it like that!
I hate when people say things
like "you're just a girl"
or "you're good for a woman."
I wanna be as strong as
the boys, so I follow
their training program,
it's simple as that. Besides,
when it comes to Tae Kwan Do,
I try not to think of myself
as a man or a woman.
Oh, come on, get real!
You're way too pretty to
think like that, Kisara!
Aw, thank you.
And begin!
I can't lose!
This guy hasn't practiced
half as much as I have!
I won't back down just
'cause my opponent's a man!
Oh, no!
That's it! The winner
is, Kisara Nanjo!
C'mon man, you held back, right?
Please tell me you
let that girl beat you
and she didn't
really kick your ass.
What? You could tell?
Aw man, I tried to hide it.
What the hell was
I supposed to do?
I mean, she's good
but she's just a girl.
You can't take a match
against a chick seriously.
That'd just be sad.
You bastard!
It was a man...
A man like you...
...who destroyed all my
self respect and pride!
What a kick!
I blocked it but it still
made my head spin!
Heh. I have to say, you're a
whole lot tougher than you look.
Nobody else has ever
lasted this long before
I can't take much more of this.
Don't you just love
street fighting?
No protective equipment
like gloves or helmets
to get in the way, and
no rules to hide behind,
so you can't cop out and
say you lost on purpose!
Come on, smart guy, let's see
how long you can stay cool!
Take this!
It's over.
What the hell?!
I'm not quitting 'til you leave.
I understand you
have your pride,
but I have my principals!
Who is this kid?!
Man, he's dumb!
Why doesn't he just shoot
himself and save time?
Come on, kid. Get out
of my way already!
I know you're trying to save
the show for that stupid cow
of a girlfriend of
yours but get over it!
I'm not just doing this for Miu!
I'm doing this
for Tanimoto too!
I won't let you ruin
the play for them!
They've worked too hard for
you to go and spoil it!
Well, aren't you an old softie!
You know, that kind of attitude
might get you killed someday.
Oh yeah?
Well you're not getting through,
not over my dead body.