"Making friends
can be effortless
once you understand the power
of the casual approach"
C'mon, I've read
this ten times,
how come I
still don't get?
Maybe I'm taking
it too literally?
Eight minutes til'!
I better get a move on!
I'm gonna be late!
The sky?
Oh no! Oh my gosh!
I'm so sorry!
You came outta nowhere...
Ahh man, all my books.
Here, let me help you.
No, its fine, I'm good.
But thanks anyway.
I appreciate it.
Hold on!
You just go around
throwing people?!
You're lucky you didn't kill me!
I said "sorry..."
But that's what you do when
someone sneaks up on you.
It's one of the first
things I learned.
And where the heck
did she learn that?
Hit man school?
Oh great, look at the time...
I'm so gonna be late.
What are you talking about?
We've got four minutes.
What?
Heh. I know a short cut.
W-Wait! Where are you taking me?
Stop!
You aren't seriously thinking
of swimming across the river?
Of course not.
We're jumping across!
Oops, guess he
wasn't ready yet.
Kenichi!
Go stand in the hall.
Wow. First day of high school,
and I'm already a loser.
I'd like to introduce our new
transfer student, Miu Furinji,
to the class and I
expect all of you
to make her feel
comfortable here.
This is a bigger school
than Shochikurin was,
so it's going to be
a big change for me.
But I'm glad to be here and
can't wait to meet everyone.
"Miu Furinji", huh?
Huh? I don't get it?
Shochikurin ranks better
than any school in town.
Why would she want to come here?
Ms. Furinji, where're you going?
Your desk is right here.
Well we were both
late, so it's only fair
that I go stand in the hall
with him, don't ya think?
Uh, right.
Listen, it's your first day...
You shouldn't be standing out
here just because of me.
It's no big deal, besides
that's the first time
anyone's ever tried
to rescue me.
This is just my way
of saying thanks.
Rescue you? Seriously?
Uh huh. When I jumped
over the river.
Oh yeah, I guess I did--
But wait a second! All
I did was try to stop you!
You ended up pulling
me out of the water!
But that dosen't matter,
I mean, at least you tried.
Okay, I get it.
You're just makin'
fun of me now.
This may sound kind of forward,
but I'd like it if the
two of us could be friends.
Now that I see her up close...
She's so cute, it
almost hurts to look.
Wait! Forget it!
This is way too good to be true.
Wake up! Snap out of it!
Uh, are you alright?
Ms. Furinji, would you
mind taking this imbecile
to the nurse's office?
Ah, I'm late for Karate Club!
Those guys will eat me alive!
Easy there, killer.
Niijima?
I'd always assumed your
clumsy, pathetic nature
was something you'd grow out of
before you got to high school.
How silly of me,
I should have known your
defects were permanent.
Did weak-knees Kenichi stand
in the hall for being tardy?
Sorry to hear about that.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Just my luck...
Haruo Niijima...
He's a spineless bottom-feeder
that kisses up to the meatheads
so he can bully other students.
That reminds me, I heard
your class was chosen
to take the new
transfer student.
Tell me about him.
What's he look like?
She, wears glasses. Not
that it's any of your busi-
Given the current breakdown, the
overall power ratio of the class
should be relatively
unaffected by her presence.
So, next question, weak-knees.
Is she easy on the eyes?
You better stop calling me that,
you alien looking freakjob!
Uh oh?
What's that?
You better learn to watch
your mouth you loser!
Tell me weak-knees, have you
ever seen one of these before?
It's what's known as a P.D.A.
Over the past month I've been
gathering statistical data
on all this year's new arrivals.
I'll bet you're curious to see
what it has to say about you.
Why don't we have
a quick look-see,
shall we?
Grades--Sub-par...
Athletic ability--Negligible...
Looks--Common...
Fighting Skills--Negligible...
Courage--Negative, nil, nada.
That's pretty darn pathetic,
don't you think so?
But I guess that it
can't be helped...
You truly are a
weak-kneed coward.
You can't blame me for
calling a spade a spade.
You should just accept it.
You're a helpless loser!
Your overall score is F minus...
which means you're
completely worthless.
You're one to talk!
My grades are always
better than yours!
Huh?
You couldn't fight
to save your life.
Whah?
And you suck at sports too!
Shut your fat mouth!
You don't know what
you're talking about.
None of that matters.
Cuz' I've got influence.
And therefore my
strength by association
gives me the power to
bully whoever I want.
Ah, but I don't expect morons
like you to understand.
So, a little bird told me
you joined the Karate Club.
You trying to shed the
nickname "Weak-knees?"
Listen, if I were
you, I'd quit now,
and save yourself even further
pain and humiliation.
Take my word for it.
They're going to bully you just
like they did in junior high.
You're weak. That will
never change. Accept it.
You'll be a whole lot
happier that way.
Ha, ha, ha, heh, heh, ha!
Jerk. You'd better
stop laughing at me...
I'm getting stronger
just wait you'll--
Yeah! Good one, but what
about the footwork, Daimonji?!
No wait! I give up!
Daimonji kick!
Shut up, you can't quit now.
What would the rest of us do?
The only reason we even
let you in this club
is 'cause we needed
a new punching bag!
So no more fallin'
down on the job.
You're finished when I say
you're finished! Got it?!
I'm starving.
Let's go grab some grub.
Hey, don't forget your chores.
Get those floors squeaky clean.
Yeah, and scrub
those toilets too!
See ya.
They're not gonna
teach me anything here.
I'm just wasting my time.
I can't take it.
I'll gonna quit
the club tomorrow.
Heh! You're such a loser.
I better get cleaning.
That should do it...
I may be their punching bag
slash cleaning boy today,
but not forever.
Speaking of punching bags...
Should I? I've been
here for over a month
and they haven't even
let me touch it.
Hey Shirahama, what do you
think you're doin', huh?
I thought we told you
not to touch the bags.
Daimonji...
Don't you remember
the first day of class?
They said freshmen aren't
allowed to touch the equipment
without an okay
from the seniors.
But you're a freshman too
and nobody has a problem
with you using it--
Shut up!
Don't ever compare me, to you...
I don't have to ask.
I worked out every day in
junior-high for these muscles.
The seniors were begging
me to join this club
when I was still
in eighth grade.
You, on the other hand, had
to whine and beg your way in
like a freakin' lost puppy.
You don't belong
here, Shirahama.
I don't care what you think.
I go to this school,
just like you,
and the Karate Club is open
to anyone who wants to join.
What?!
Just seein' a guy like you
here makes me wanna puke.
Karate's for the strong and when
scrawny losers like you show up,
it really pisses me off!
Listen up 'cause this is the
only warning you're gonna get.
Quit the Karate Club today.
Leave now and don't come back.
Or else I'll bash
your tiny skull in.
That's my promise man to man,
I'll even let ya think about it.
Time's up!
Heh, heh, heh, heh.
Okay. On your feet.
Hey...
Do I need to explain it
to you one more time?
If I get strong enough,
I can master Karate.
I'm gonna do it, I'm
gonna get stronger!
Wake up, will ya?!
You're livin' in some
kinda fantasy world!
Here's a dose of reality
for you. You're a weakling.
You're never gonna be strong,
no matter how hard you try.
You're a loser!
You're always gonna be a loser!
And guys like me
are gonna step on you
for the rest of
your worthless life!
But y'know, I think I just
came up with a solution
that'll be perfect
for the both of us.
You and me get together for
a serious match next week,
whaddya say Shirahama?
Sounds like a plan to me.
Oh yeah...
and whoever loses, quits the
club forever without question.
Listen up.
You better borrow a stretcher
from the nurses' office,
'cause when I'm done,
you won't be able to
stand, walk, or crawl.
I'll keep training
hard every day.
You should do the same.
Man, that was close. I
thought I was dead for sure.
Wait, what am I saying?
Now I've got to fight that
overgrown jerk next week!
I only have one
week left to live!
I hate that guy.
I wish he was the
loser, just this once.
I'll train myself.
I'd be stronger already if those
idiots would just let me train.
I can do it. It's
completely up to me.
It's my destiny.
It's mine to master.
And then...
When I've finally
gotten stronger...
I'll be different.
I won't be a bully like
Daimonji and the others.
They're all losers.
I will protect the weak.
That's how your supposed to
use great strength, right?
I'll be the hero.
That's right,
Kenichi Shirahama, the hero.
I'll beat up the thugs
and defend the innocent.
What are you looking at?
You need to apologize
to him, right now.
Please, I'm just fine.
You'll only make
more trouble for us.
Okay I did not just see that.
There's nothing
happening over there.
I saw nothing.
Not a thing. Nada.
It's too soon.
I haven't had a
chance to train yet.
So, not only would
I be useless,
I'd probably just end up
making things worse.
And with thugs like that
it's really better to just
give 'em what they want.
I know!
I think there's a chapter
on this sort of thing
in my Urban Survival Handbook!
It's at home...
You fool!
You shouldn't be
searching through a book
at a time like this!
How can I be so stupid...!
That's my classmate over
there, she needs my help!
I saw it. You pushed him.
Where do you get off slamming an
old man to the ground like that?
Calm down four-eyes.
He was wandering down the
street in everybody's way,
so we shoved him aside.
Well that piece of
junk you call a car
is in everybody's way too.
Are you gonna do--
Oh no, arguing with them is
only going to make it worse.
We'll park our car
wherever we want.
And anybody that's got any
sense will stay out of our way.
Especially pretty little
blonde girls like yourself.
Yeah, nobody tells
us what to do.
Why don't you have
yourself a look?
Those people understand
what the score is.
You see all of them
pretending not to notice us.
Well I'm not one of them.
Apologize now.
You little brat...
They're going to bully you just
like they did in junior high.
You're weak.
That will never change.
Accept it.
You're never gonna be strong,
no matter how hard you try.
You're a loser! You're
always be a loser!
And guys like me are
gonna step on you
for the rest of your
worthless life!
I'm about to bloody that
pretty mouth of yours.
Aggh!
Let go of her now!
Aahh! Fists of fury!
Who's this dude?
Hurry get out of here Miu!
I can only hold them
back for so long--
Okay kid, now your dead.
You just made the biggest,
and last, mistake
of your life kid.
You know who we are?
Well, no, I don't
know who you are.
Sorry, I wasn't
thinking clearly.
I just acted on instinct.
It was a mistake.
Seriously, I didn't mean to...
Wait! You can't use that!
I'm unarmed! That's
against the rules!
We're playing by
different rule books kid.
And mine says you ain't
to live no longer.
Hold him down!
Nooooooooooo!
--Where'd she go?!
--She used me as a spring board.
Okay, now you've made me mad.
Whoa... I barely had
a chance to blink,
and she hit all
three of those guys!
Amazing. That was intense.
What is she? Some kind of killer
ballerina or something?
That was impressive. Thank you.
You've rescued me
twice in one day.
Oh.,yeah, sure thing,
it was my pleasure...
Wait, but that's
not what happened.
That took a lot of guts
back there, Kenichi.
You know I don't think I could
have found a better person
to be my first new friend.
Wait? So we're friends?
Of course!
The Karate Club huh?
I could tell you were a
martial artist from your collar.
Well, I don't know
if I'd go that far.
Kenichi... I just want you
to know that guy from the club
who told you martial arts
is only for the strong,
he doesn't know what
he's talking about.
What do you mean by that?
Um, well I've always
been interested
in martial arts myself, so
I know a little bit about it
Wait a minute, what're you
calling "a little bit."
My Sensai has always
explained it to me like this:
The Martial arts were
originally created
to help the weak fight
against the strong.
That means someone's size isn't
really all that important.
So the guy from the Karate
Club has it backwards.
I could try explaining that, but
I still doubt they'd teach me.
Not only that, but I've got
less than a week until--
Oh wait! My how-to books.
"Practice is the only answer."
Man, I'm dead.
Listen, If you're really serious
about getting stronger,
then I think I know of a place
where they can help you out,
if you're willing
to give it a try.
You think they teach
me to take out thugs
--like you just did?
--I can't answer that.
I can say is that if you
train in this place,
you'll get a lot stronger than
you are right now, guaranteed.
Tell me! Tell me!
One thing.
What is it?
When I say you'll get stronger,
that's assuming you
manage to stay alive...
Huh?
I'm pretty sure
this is the place.
I can't believe I
actually found it.
What was Miu thinking
when she made this map?
Sprinting? What does that
have to do with directions?
And what's with the crazy route?
Okay...
As long as you're
sure about this.
Of course I'm sure.
I don't have a choice.
One week from now,
I'm gonna be beaten
within inches of my life.
So, I've got nothing to lose.
I'm comin' in!
What's with this gate?
It feels like it's
made of lead.
Come on...
Open uuuuup!
Hello there.
What sort of business do you
have in this place young man?
Business! Uh, I
was just leaving!
Sorry...
What the--?!
Did you just...
...warp?!
How'd ya do that?
Judging by the
look on your face,
I'm not sure you could handle
the answer to that question.
Try to calm down a bit.
You wouldn't happen
to be some kind of
martial arts
master, would you?
I wouldn't consider
myself a master.
I'm just fortunate.
I have yet to lose
a single battle.
This is it!
This is the place
she told me about!
Uh, excuse me sir,
I'm Kenichi Shirahama.
I was sent here
by Miu Furinji.
It's both an honor and
a pleasure to meet you.
That was quite an impressive
introduction young man.
Your manners are excellent,
but there's no need to
be formal around here.
So then, Miu sent you, huh?
Yes.
Um, sir?
What exactly do you teach here?
I mean, you teach Karate, right?
Hm-mm. Among other things, yes.
That's awesome!
What is that monster and where
on Earth did it come from?
That's Apachai Hopachai,
from Thailand.
Only 28 years old,
believe it or not.
Wowwwww!
Amazing!
Apa! Apa!
Be careful you don't
speak too loud.
If he hears you, he
might start showing off.
ApaApaApaApaApaApaApaApa!
Alright!
That's enough Apachai!
Is he always like this?
We don't get many visitors.
He probably just got
a little over stimulated.
No visitors? What kind
of Dojo is this?
Miu's definitely cute,
but this girl is hot!
Maybe she'll give me
some private lessons.
Show yourself! What business
do you have with me?
Speak!
Ah, who me?!
Kensei! I know exactly
where you're hiding...
...and so does my sword!
Relax, I was just
passing through,
making sure everything's still
on the up and up, down below.
Looking good.
That doesn't explain the
camera you're holding.
What were you taking
pictures of down there?
Uh, what chu mean?!
I wouldn't recommend snooping
around here young man.
Now then,
I'm about to introduce you
to the Karate teacher
you've been looking for,
but I have to warn you,
he can be difficult.
Um, okay.
Hey, Shio! I need a favor!
Uh uh. No way.
I don't take disciples.
How many times do we
gotta go over this gramps?
Told ya.
He dosen't sound like a teacher.
It's a bad idea old man.
Let's suppose I did let
him become my pupil...
He would be dead
in three days time.
You don't say. Well
that's just too bad.
The man obviously doesn't want
to take on a disciple, ah well.
Thanks anyway,
I'll be going now.
This kid seems
kinda high strung.
He's certainly energetic.
W-Where am I?
What kind of crazy dojo is this?
Kenichi? Kenichi?
Miu!
You fainted,
you feeling alright?
We-We should get out of here!
This place is really dangerous!
This is...
my home...
You see Hayato is...
...her grandfather.
Uh?! Grandfather?!
Okay, right about now that
little voice in my head
is telling me to run for it.
Bad idea! Bad idea!
What the heck am I getting
myself into here?!
I'm dead meat.
Who are all of these
scary-looking people
and what are they
gonna do to me?
Each of them is a master
of a different martial art.
They live and practice
here at Ryozanpaku.
Kenichi, I promise if
you'll let them teach you
they'll help
you get stronger
But I'm not sure that I'm cut
out for this sort of thing!
You'll be fine, Kenichi.
I have complete faith
in you. Just go for broke.
No way! Are you kidding me?!
Getting "broke" is exactly
what I'm afraid of!
This is going to be a little
harder than I thought.