[Music]
Uh-oh...
Guess I was a little
too hard on you...
Gotta learn to
dodge, my boy...
Take a break...
You probably need
the time to recharge.
Can you let me down
gently next time??
You stay here and rest.
I'm going to go
get us some lunch.
I'm gonna die out here...
I never should've agreed
to do this special
training with him.
There's gotta be another
way to defeat Ryuto.
I wanna hear the voices of my
loved ones one more time...
Honoka...
Mother...
Father...
Miu...
Man this sucks...
I can't get any kind
of reception out here
in the middle of nowhere.
Oh my god...!
It's a miracle...!
The good Lord above has
recognized my dying wish
and has granted this lost
soul with a single bar!
Looks like I have to stay
like this or I lose it...
I better hurry
and call someone.
An email...?
But who's it from??
Niijima...?..?...!
He's the last person I
wanna hear from before I die.
This blows!
He's still lively.
His endurance must come from
the other master's training.
There's something weird
about this email...
I really wish I'd
had the opportunity
to tell you this before...
But you kept surprising me
so I didn't have
the chance to...
You see, I've always believed
that each person has a role
they play in the game of life...
Kenichi...
There are the wimps
who are bullied
and the bullies
that abuse them.
There are the people
who give orders
and the people
who follow them.
Each person's role has
been predetermined by God
and handed down to them
when they were born.
Or so I thought.
Your existence has shaken the
very foundation of my beliefs...
I've done plenty of
research on the human race
and as far as I'm concerned
your species is no better
than a mindless amoeba.
However, you rose
above the others
and became a
charismatic hero...
And it happened simply
because of your hard
work and conviction.
Watching you transform
into a champion
gave me a brilliant idea...
I knew that one day
I wanted to form a martial
arts group with you
as their leader, Kenichi...
I wanted to see just
how high losers-
like you used to
be- could climb
if they were given
the proper training...
I have no doubt you'll be
able to defeat Ryuto Asamiya-
I wish I could be
there to see it...
Your friend... Haruo Niijima.
Niijima...
Crap! Where'd you
come from...?..?...!
Quit sneaking up on me!
Well, that certainly is
a strange email, huh??
Yeah... it freaks me out...
I'm kinda worried
about him...
No matter what
was going down,
he'd never tell
anyone his plans.
Is that so...
It sounded like...
he's saying... goodbye.
Goodbye??
We're completely surrounded...!
If these goons attack all at
once we're gonna be dead meat.
Commander...
Have you gotten a
response from that email
you sent Captain Shirahama yet?
We could really use his
help at a time like this.
He's not coming...
Oh, I get it...
You didn't email him
after all, did you sir??
Matsui...
I understand...
There's no reason to
get him involved-
we can handle
this ourselves!
We'll bust through that wall
of dirty thugs and
head to freedom, sir!
Matsui...
uh...
Molotov cocktails??!
Burn the place down!
Damn it, they wanna
burn us to a crisp!
We don't have a
choice- open the door!
I'll make a grand escape
right under Loki's nose
just like
Yoshihiro Shimazu!
So who's this
Yoshihiro Shimazu guy??
During the battle
of Sekigahara,
General Shimazu was surrounded
by thousands of
Ieyasu Tokugawa's men
yet he valiantly escaped
by charging straight
through them!
Hey Commander...
I don't think we're gonna
get through these guys.
It's wall of Loki!
That's right and it's a wall
that you and your little buddy
are never gonna
break through...
Now boys.
Elder...
I have to get back home
immediately, I'm sorry.
What...? But we still
haven't finished
all of your
training yet, son.
My friend is in a
lot of trouble...!
I just know it...
Niijima's... not the kinda guy
who'd write an email
like that sincere
unless it was
something serious!
We've been in the same
classes since middle school.
He's been there next to
me through everything ...
Well, even though
he picked on me...
I probably know
Haruo Niijima better
than I know anyone else!
I guess he's learned enough
to face any delinquent
he may encounter.
Okay... I'll make an exception
and end your training early.
Thanks!
However, it's
going to take us
at least nine hours of
travel to get back home.
I knew it was too
good to be true!
Well... Now that
I think about it
there is a way that'll only
take us five hours instead.
Five? That's like
half the time...!
Cool...! Let's do it!
But... while it is much faster
I'm afraid there's a catch...
I can't guarantee that...
you'll live through it.
Say wha??
I'll just have to
take that chance...
I can't waste
another second!
Pack up your stuff.
Yes, sir!
As soon as he learned his
friend was in trouble
he perked up immediately.
Ryozanpaku couldn't have
asked for a better disciple.
I can't hold them back
much longer, Commander-
get out of here
while you still can!
Matsui!
I've never seen a commander
so worried about his
subordinates.
Number 20!
Hey let me go!
What the hell??!
I'm a real sumo...
My name is... Thor!
Damn it...
Not you.
Now listen up punks-
I'm here here to
protect the commander
at the request of my good
buddy, Siegfriedfried...
As of today I'm a member
of the Shinpaku Alliance.
And what do you think you're
gonna do on your own.....?...
You'll die in vain...
Just as ugly and
stupid as ever.
You're a dummy!
Okay, I may not be as smart...
as you...
But I'm not the only
one "stupid" enough
to confront you Loki.
I never thought
he'd actually come!
You never said anything about
running 100 miles an hour
on electrical wires.
I really am gonna die
before I ever make it home.
Don't worry- as long
as you keep holding on
everything'll be fine.
This is the fastest
way to get there
so just hang tight, okay??
This may be the fastest way
but it's dangerous.....!...
My hands are slipping!
Save me, Elder!
Uh-oh.
The former Sixth Fist, Hermit,
and the former
Seventh Fist, Thor...
I don't get it...
Why are they ditching us
to join up with that
alien freak's Alliance??!
So what happened to your
allegiance to Ragnarok-
are you just gonna trade it
out for the Shinpaku, Hermit??
This has nothing
to do with them...
The only reason I'm here
is to exact my revenge...
I'm gonna make you pay
for using the Great Saint of
Fist's name to try to trick me.
Hey... So Thor...
I heard through the grapevine
you swore to Shirahama
that you were never
gonna fight again.
That's true...
I did...
But... Who says
that I'm fighting-
can't a guy get in a
little sumo sparring
every once in a while.
Better watch out.....!...
Thor can be quite the
brute when he's sparring
so I suggest you
keep a safe distant
unless you wanna
get your ass kicked?
Number 3! Number 4!
Damn... At this rate
we're never gonna be able to
make it to the main event...
Now.....! All of
you surround Hermit!
Don't even try!
It'll be a tough fight if
I go head-to-head with him.
I'll have to think up a
way to wear him out first.
What are you waiting
for.....?..?...!
Go attack him... now!
Coming through!
Whoa... man this is
really messed up...
The only reason
I came out here is
cause I thought we could
totally roast 'em.....!...
But those guys
have got us beat...
I'm out!
Yeah!
Hey we were just
joking about leaving.
We'll go back to
our positions now.
Those two just had
to get in the way...
The First Fist, Odin...
And the Second Fist,
Berserker...
Whoa... That Berserker guy
and the number one dude
just showed up...
No.....!... I think
this is the end.
What the hell do you
think you're doing, Loki?
I thought I told
you to capture
the leader of the
Shinpaku Alliance?
Why have you gathered all
of their subordinates??
I wanted to make
sure I got the guy.
Quit coming up with these
ridiculous plans-
would you simply follow my
orders for once.....?...
You're completely
useless...
Now go...
I'm through with you.
It's a bit early but I
guess it can't be helped.
I think you're the useless
one around here, Odin.
What'd you say??
Let me out of here!
I'm... leaving!
Ow...! Let me go...! Now!
I thought that I told
you to lie down??
You're not going anywhere
while you're hurt.....!...
Kensei... the needle!
O-kay...
Go to sleep.
This kid's a lively
one, isn't he?
He broke three ribs and
he's still going strong.
That's impressive!
He seems to be really
worried about his comrades
for some reason.
Well, I'll let you
worry about this one...
I've got my hands full
trying to help the
girl Miu brought back.
I'm busya...
I've already treated her-
she doesn't need your help...
Leave the rest to Miu.
The last thing the girl needs
is someone gawking at her.
I hope that somehow this'll
keep you from having a scar.
Thanks but I don't care.
Not too bad.
Oh, sorry my hand slipped.
Very fast Kensei,
but you still didn't get me.
I have to go!
So where's the needle?
Let's try this again.
But... there's
nothing else I can do-
I've already
tried everything!
Somehow he's able to fight
the effects of my acupuncture.
Talk about conviction...
Let me leave.....!...
I must go....!
I have to help them.....!
Are you sure you
can't let him go??
She went and
put on a robe...
I mean, the Shinpaku Alliance
is having their final face-off
with Ragnarok right now.
She's right
and we should probably try
to get a hold of Kenichi
so he can be there... To help
Captain Shirahama...?..?...!
I'll call him.....!...
I'll ask him to come
home... right now...
We need him!
The last time we let you
use the phone to call someone
it caused some trouble...
You got so excited
making the call
you exhausted
yourself completely.
If I didn't call Thor
they'd be dead.....!...
Now give me the phone!
The telephone! Telephone!
Telephone! Telephone!
Jeez this is annoying-
knock him out!
Now calm down, Akisame.
He's too weak for
any more acupuncture.
Please let him
go, doctor...
He just wants to
help his friends.
As a fellow fighter I'm
compelled to let him go...
But as a doctor I know
that he's in no condition...
What're you gonna do when
you get there.....?...
Just to sitsitting up I took
almost all of your energy.
I may not be able to fight
with them... even so...
I can cheer for them.....!
Shinpa... ku.....!...
Still going...
And he should be
in a lot of pain.
Yeah.....!... Go-
Apa!
Apachai...
Opera boy can go
cheer on his buddies
as long as he follows
the doctor's orders
and stays in bed,
right.....?...
This is the perfect way
to make that happen.
Apachai will be very careful
not to hurt singing man
and will put him
somewhere safe.
I swear it's like
talking to children-
none of you has
any common sense.
Come on, doctor,
don't say that...
We all mean well-
Akisame... I understand...
If you really don't
want us to go...
then we'll stay
here, okay??
Nonsense!
Personally, I love going
against common sense
whenever I get
the opportunity.
What a hypocrite.
I said you're the useless
one around here, Odin.
After all, you're the one
who's allowed the Fists
to fall apart...
You're the leader so you
should take responsibility.
I'd be careful.
Now.....!...
Listen up, soldiers
of Ragnarok!
I have an announcement!
As some of you may know,
Freya of the Three of Cards
has been defeated...
How'd it happen?
Because of the negligence
of the First Fist.
He has proven he is an
ineffective leader...
Which means
this is the end.
Ragnarok is now... dead!
No way...
He can't call it
like that, can he??
You know, I was always
a little suspicious
of that bastard, Loki.
I see... we were the
distraction he was using
while he was forming
his own team, eh??
Whoa.....!...
Who are they.....?..?...!
That's a pretty
scary lookin' bunch!
I'd like to introduce you
to the fighters I've trained
to pick up where
Ragnarok left off...
The new Eight
Deadly Fists!
He's not serious, is he??!
So... they're the
Fists.....?..?...!
What the hell's going on??!
And their... new leader is...
Berserker, you're the one
who's right for the job.
I'm perfectly fine with
being second in command.
Everyone... I present to you
a fighting force to
be reckoned with...!
The reincarnation
of the Fists
and their new and
improved Ragnarok gang!
What.....?... He's seriously
created a whole new gang??!
Loki...
Listen up, men.
You have a
decision to make.
You're either going to side
with the new Ragnarok...
or with Odin and
his leftovers.
That bastard...
This must have been
his plan all along.
This is really
bad, Commander...
Now we've got a whole new set
of bad guys to worry about.
Yeah... However this moment of
disorganization and confusion
may be our only
chance of survival.
So... what should we do??
Why're you asking
me.....?..?...!
I don't know!
One more thing,...
If you guys decide
not to follow me...
Then you'll have to answer
to the new Eight Deadly Fists.
And don't forget that
Berserker has sided with me...
Freya has been defeated by
the Shinpaku Alliance...
Which means all that the old
Ragnarok has left is Odin...
The Three of
Cards are done.
Now... surround
Odin immediately!
It's not like we really
have a choice-
they'll kick our ass
if we don't join 'em.
Yeah... guess you're right.
Looks like Loki's
won by a landslide.
It'd work out better for
us if they'd split into two
and then just
beat each other up.
Maybe I can brainwash them
into doing exactly that.
Let's check it out.
Niijima eye!
I'm simply using
my alien ability
to assess each
fighter's power levels.
This'll also let me know
if their susceptible
to brainwashing.
Whoa, what's up
with Berserker?!
I've never seen anything
like this before!
You still refuse to
surrender, Odin.....?...
Hey... Why don't you
try to say something
that might convince
your old pal to give up?
Oh crap.....!...
What the hell's going on,
Commander.....?..?...!
Did the new gang
fall apart already??!
That's not it.
You bastard!
Berserker totally pulled
one over on Loki-
he never planned on joining
the new Ragnarok gang.
Damn it, Berserker...
I thought you were ready
to come to our side.
I would never... join... you.
I was simply positioning
myself closer to you
so that I would have
an opening to attack.
You had enough??
Damn... You You bbastard.
I've known about your plan
and I warned Berserker
not to get involved...
But... even if I hadn't,
there's no way he ever would
ever be controlled by you.
What the hell is wrong
with you....?..?...!
I was gonna make you the
new Ragnarok's number one.
I have no interest
in a ranking...
You're a loser...
I'will only serve someone
I can respect... not you.
What?
Loki... Are you okay??!
Damn it...! I was
supposed to be the one
to take him down
not you, Berserker!
I beat you to it...
Looks like you'll have
to take me on instead.
Fine then.
We're done playing games...
Surround the Shinpaku!
Berserker and Hermit
are going to face off
and I don't want
them interfering.
C'mon... We'd better do
whatever Odin says...
Let's go!
He's not playing
around, is he??
Be careful what you
say, Captain Thor.
We don't wanna
piss 'em off.
Odin's got complete
control over them-
a second ago they were
totally confused.
These guys are
out for blood.
You can see it
in their faces.
This is gonna mean
big trouble for us.
Hermit...
Do you really think you
can confront the two of us
and walk away
completely unscathed??
You know, I could say the
same thing to you, Odin.
Hermit and Thor
aren't gonna be enough
to get us out of this.
How about you
leave Hermit to me.
That's fine- I know you've
been looking forward to this
for some time now...
We'll take care
of these guys
once you've
finished Hermit off.
Our chances of survival are
getting slimmer by the second!
Niijima...
I'll create a path
for you to escape...
Just make sure you
stay behind me...
Outta my way!
It's over.
The Shintoukei??!
The Shintoukei is a
powerful attack
that causes internal
damage to an opponent.
This technique is not
easily mastered-
it requires a great
deal of training.
The Shintoukei...
I believe that's what it's
called in Kenpo, isn't it??
Hey!
Are you gonna
fight me or what??
Thor... No wonder
you were a Fist.
Your strength is really
quite impressive.
Now...! Go Niijima...!
I made a promise
to Siegfried
that I would protect
you at all costs!
No... Thor!
Are you sure.....?...
You've sustained
a lot of damage...
This blow just just
might be the end of you.
That's not gonna happen...
Not before I
smash you to bits!
Sorry, Thor.... Goodbye.
What now??!
Ow! Man, that hurt.....!...
Jeez, I wish the
Elder would figure out
how to let me
down more gently.
Hey you guys.....?...
You okay??
Its... Kenichi!
Captain Shirahama's here!
Kenichi Shirahama...
You haven't changed-
You're just as stubborn
as you were before.
[Music]
How dare you?!
How could you do
that to my friends?!
I'll never forgive
you for this!
Now I'm gonna take
you on Berserker!
Let's go!
No Kenichi!
This isn't your fight.
You've got more important
things to worry about.
Tanimoto! What the hell
are you doing here??!
That doesn't
matter right now.
You've been in the
mountains training
so that you could
beat Odin, right?!
Well, this is your chance-
just concentrate on him!
But what about Berserker??!
Don't worry.
I'll take care of him.
I've been dying to get
my hands on that bastard.
For a while now.