[Music]
Attack!
Not happenin'.
Kenichi, I appreciate the fact
that you're so dedicated to
your training these days...
but this is dumb.
I'm sure losing that
fight to the First Fist
was a bit of a letdown...
But that attitude isn't
helping your form.
I didn't lose exactly...
I just let him win.
Mustache Man- that
wasn't very nice.
Yes. I know.
Naked, naked,
naked, naked WOMEN!
Attack!
Not now.....!
I'm busy!
Hey you pervert!
Get back here and
apologize to my big brother!
Dude... This is sad...
I think you're at your
limit, little man,
you might wanna take a
breather for a while.
Master...!
Tell me, is it true
I have no talent at
all for martial arts??
Yes. That's true.
And you guys have taught
me everything you could
while I've been
at Ryouzanpaku,
so basically the only reason
I lost was because I suck.
Well, I can't argue
with any of that.
You're mean!
Sorry, I don't
believe in lying.
Ryuto...
He said...
He said the reason I
won't win is because...
My naïve personality
makes all my martial arts
training pointless.
So I wanted to learn to
put more killing intent
into my attacks.
No. That's where
you'd be wrong.
Yay!
Hi! I'm glad you're here.
My brother screwed up and
you need to fix it...
Okay, grandpa??
'Kay... You'll
leave it to me??
Yup... Make me proud!
How about it, Kenichi...?
What would you say to
some one-on-one training
with an old man like me??
You're kiddin'... This guy??
In all the years
I've known him,
he's never taken
on a disciple.
I think our young friend
could use a different style
of training for a while,
just to shake things up,
don't you agree??
And I even know of
a special training
place to take you, Kenichi...
So whaddaya say?
You gonna give me a shot?
If you think it'll give me a
chance to beat the First Fist,
I'm not afraid to face
any kind of training
you throw at me!
That right...?
Not afraid at all, are you...?
Is that the story you're
sticking with??
No... Sorry...
I'm scared.
Really. Really, really.
I'm just kidding...
No reason to
be scared, son.
Right... There is definitely
a reason to be scared.
Scared or not...
I just hope he comes
back in one piece.
Meanwhile...
the Shinpaku Alliance...
Singin'
Ragnarok, oh Ragnarok,
we're gonna stomp you
in the face... hey...!
Stomp you in the face...
stomp you in the face...
Break it down, Siegfried.
-Would ya shut up!
-No.
So alien...
you really believe you're
gonna be able to keep this chat
we're having with
Kisara peaceful...?
What makes you
think that...?
Good karma??
Duh... Isn't it obvious...?
I'll make her a
simple, fair trade.
Like I said...
We're just here to
have a cozy chat.
What do you think of
my photography...?
I think I'm pretty talented.
So what is it that
you want from me...?
Do you want money??
No! You misunderstand...!
We just have a tiny,
little request.
Yeah? What kinda request??
Well... If you don't want
those incriminating photos
spread all over
the city...
Then you're
going to join us!
What...?..?...!
That's blackmail!
Or I could just
kill you right now!
This is going
too far.....!...
What's in those
photos anyway.....?...
Show me!
Whoops.....!...
My hand slipped.
-Help me pick 'em up!
-Right!
Oh... So Kisara likes cats.
Yep! And as long as
I have these files,
I can print as much
proof of it as I want!
But if she pledges
her allegiance
to the Shinpaku Alliance...
I will lock her dirty
little secret in a vault
and throw away the key.
Shall I kill him now??
But it doesn't matter
if they kill me or not,
isn't that right,
Siegfried...?
Because only we know
where the master...
-Hey! Give me that thing!
-What are you doing, you idiot!
You weren't supposed
to bring that!
Forgive me,
my wise commander...
But I've also deleted the
backup files of her pictures
that you had on
your computer.
But... why, Siggy...?
You were my most
faithful lackey!
No, my friend!
You will not stoop
as-low-as-Ragnarok-doooeees,
they're-jeerks.
And you are great!
And blackmail
Is way beneath you
So I will not let you do it.
Though I would follow you
to the ends of the earth
should you happen
to ask it of me.
But I hope
That you wouldn't
Because...
You see...
I have a really, really really
really really good plan
It is quite a
grandiose plan
and I think you
will enjoy it...
My demon king.
That... was beautiful.
Grandiose...
I like that...
sounds kingly...
You may continue,
my subject.
Sir.
Listen Valkyrie...
From the moment you became
a member of Ragnarok
I could see that you were
diligently trying to suppress
your warm and
loving melody.
And now...
Without the organization
of Ragnarok...
your team is just a
cacophony of delinquents.
It will be dangerous
for all of you,
out there on your own
without protection...
Now is the time
to join us!
For your loyalty...
your friendship...
We offer... This
adorable kitten!
I know you're not
allowed to have pets...
but I'll make you
a glorious deal...
There's room
in my house...
I'll let you keep the kitten
there for now if you want...
I already have 20
other dogs and cats
so it won't make
much difference
and you can come play with
it whenever you so desire.
Sure! Fine! Whatever!
Just give me that kitty!
Ah.....!... an
exploitation of weakness.
Soooo cuuuuutee...
I also have a
fluffy one...
and a hairless one
if you'd rather.
What are you a
magician now, Siggy??
Whatever, it worked...!
Good job.
This is embarrassing
to watch even for me.
Hah! Like I even care
about a bunch of cats!
Too late for
that, sweetie.
Nice try.
Sure... I mean who could
think about kittens
at a time like this, right?
what with the
Second Fist coming.
So he is on the move!
The Second Fist...
He's known as Berserker.
The fiercest of the
Three of Cards...
And he's making his
move to wipe us out...
Doesn't look good...
A truce between us is
inevitable, Kisara...
For your own protection.
I normally only shake
the hands of people
who have defeated
me in a fight,
but I guess I have to make
an exception this time...
We have a truce.
Well then, we're off...
We should be back in
about a week I think...
But... I guess that's
up to Kenichi.
Be careful...
And you just try
your hardest, 'kay??
It's a rare opportunity
to train with someone of
the old man's caliber...
So you better not
waste it, you hear me??
Apachai wants to go to
the secret training place!
You can't go...!
You're in charge of watching
over the house with me!
Did you already forget??
Elder... Can you tell us
where you're taking Kenichi
for this training??
We're going to the
heart of Japan...
A place still untainted
by the ravages of
development and industry.
You don't mean...
The Dark Valley??
Why? Would that be so bad??
No... No...
He's taking quite a risk...
Bringing him to a place
where even the smallest misstep
can lead to disaster...
We'll just have to put
our trust in Kenichi now.
-So, we ready??
-Yep!
Kenichi...!
No matter what happens,
don't forget to
believe in yourself.
And trust your training
to see you through.
Thanks... I'll remember!
Good luck, bro...! Bye!!
Come back safely...
our number one disciple!
Jeez! Odin sure likes to
make his own moves, huh??
Of course, he did say he
wanted Shirahama left alone...
Yet he still wants us to get rid
of the Shinpaku Alliance...
If he'd just let me
finish the kid off...
we might not have lost four
of our strongest fighters
to a bunch of
high school kids,
you know what I'm sayin'?
I mean, it's a pity all
the decisions for Ragnarok
are up to him...
right, Berserker??
Got him!
So, hey... whaddaya think...?
You wanna make this hand a
little more interesting??
Sure...
What do you have in mind??
Let's play for the new
leadership position...
In the Raganrok we're gonna
form after Odin's gone.
Hah...! Oh I'm
just kidding...
don't worry.
I wasn't worried.
Well, that's good...
I'm glad we're both
on the same page...
I'll just take one.
Muscle-bound idiot...!
Loki's a pro at making
the game go his way.
Wouldja look at that...
It's four of a kind!
Hold on... where're
you going...?
Don't you want
another chance??
I'm going to look for
the Shinpaku Alliance...
like Odin said...
'less you happen to have
them up your sleeve, too.
Damn... That sly bastard...
Hard to tell what
he's thinking
when he just sits
there chewing his gum
and refusing to talk.
Oh well...
What did he have?
He got a royal flush!
Hey? What's wrong...?
What'd he do??
I stacked the deck and
he still got lucky
enough to beat me.
He's got a godly physique
and an ungodly talent...
add to that his ability to
stay cool in a crisis...
And there's no
doubt about it...
Berserker's
definitely the man
to lead the New Ragnarok
to greatness!
Ah!
Stop! Stop!
I'm falling!
Just keep quiet
and hang on!
Sorry Kenichi, but if
we went at your pace
I'd probably die of old age
before we got to
where we're going!
This is it...
we're here.
The place I trained
when I was a disciple.
This is the heart of Japan...!
The Dark Valley.
Three hours on
the train...
Two hours on a bus...
then four hours on
the Elder's back...
How can we still
be in Japan??!
We're surrounded by
mountains on each side...
This forest is far
from civilization...
which means it's removed
from the safety of urban life.
It's weird. The air feels really
different in this place.
Good. You noticed it...
The valley air is
thick with humidity.
If you train in
these conditions,
your wounds heal faster,
and your level of concentration
increases exponentially.
That's why the legendary martial
arts masters we learn about
did their early training in
the surrounding mountains.
Maybe that's true, but your
main reason for coming here
was to make sure you cut
off any escape route
I could use to get away
from you, wasn't it?
Such a smart boy!
What kind of
training is it
that you're so sure I'm
gonna want to run away?!
It'll be a bit hard for you in
your current state of mind.
If it'll help me beat the
First Fist in a fight,
I'll withstand anything!
Fine. Then I want
you to do nothing.
So for the rest
of this week...
You will not use
martial arts...
You will do no
training whatsoever.
What?! No way...!
Training is why I came to
this god-forsaken place!
It is...?
I thought you came
out here for me...
But I guess if that's how
you really feel about it-
You can just head back the way
we came on your own, okay...?
I'm pretty sure you won't be
able to find it yourself,
but oh well.
As long as you don't run
into any of the wild bears
that roam these mountains,
you'll probably last
at least three days.
Maybe two.
He's the devil.
I know what I'm
talking about.
Why don't you just
trust me, Kenichi??
Finding firewood,
douching water.
He didn't bring
me here to train,
he brought me here
for a camping trip.
How'm I supposed
to beat Ryuto
when I'm lounging around
here doing nothing...?
Maybe I should do some
training in secret!
What's that??
Did I just imagine it??
Hey! Kenichi!
What are you doing?
Where's my firewood??
Oh. Sure, that's convenient.
Something wrong, boy??
Oh, uh...
No.
How did you forget
food.....?..?...!
If you thought we were
gonna catch fish everyday,
why didn't you
bring a pole?!
It's too late now...
If we don't catch something
before it gets dark,
we'll be going
hungry til morning.
At least I don't have
to worry about a rematch
if I die of hunger first!
Ooh, that's right,
Elder...!...
Show the bears
how it's done!
Alright, heading
back to camp.
Yeah, I think
I will, too...
That should be enough for the
both of us, shouldn't it??
Huh? Oh no, this is just
enough for my dinner.
We each take care
of our own meals
when we're camping.
How the hell did he catch
those fish.....?..?...!
This is so stupid!
What, no luck Kenichi...?
Well, if you can't
catch any fish
you might look for something
to eat in the forest.
Okay.
A walnut...!
Yes!
There's more over here...!
And here...! More!
I'll just eat
them later...
First I have to
bury my stash
so the Elder doesn't
take them away from me!
My brother...
the squirrel.
What is that??!
Ever since I got here,
something's felt...
weird.
That's a Devil Walnut...
Not much meat, anyway.
I've officially burned
all the calories
this would've given me...
I hate this!
Well, I'm tuckered out...
Goodnight, Kenichi.
Yeah, right, whatever.
There, that should do it.
Damn him...
The Elder must be getting
softer in his old age...
I can't just give up on my
training right now...!
Not til I beat him!
Look, Kenichi's
bowl just broke...!
Great... that's not good.
You just leave
it to Apachai...!
I'll do my
super-duperdeluxe prayer!
That's not a prayer.
It's a curse.
Oh... His teacup's
broken, too.
You see...?
This is what happens
when you disobey me
and start training in
the middle of the night!
You end up exhausted
and starving...
You should pay more attention
to your master's instructions.
How does he know??
Now you listen to me...
Mountain training is a survival
test for a martial artist,
not something to be
treated lightly.
You may have to eat
bark or insects
to keep yourself alive...
You have no idea how the
mountain will choose
to test your character.
Do you understand
what I'm saying...?
Good. Then go
catch some fish.
I tried.
I've had nothing but
walnuts for three days.
Did you know that, buddy?
Walnuts sure
are nutritious.
You know how I know that?
Cause I'm still
alive, that's how.
You must really love
those walnuts, Kenichi...
You look more like a
squirrel every day!
No! I do not love
these walnuts...!
They're just the only things I
can find in this stupid forest!
That's just because you
haven't figured out
how to look for it, my boy...
The Dark Valley is endowed
with a number of tasty,
filling tidbits.
-See??
-Wha??!
So, Elder...
How 'bout you share some of that
plentiful harvest with me??
No! This is an important
part of training!
I miss Miu's cooking!
What is that?
What is it?!
I've been feeling it
ever since I got he...
Yes, attack!
You certainly have guts,
trying to steal my
hard earned food,
I'll give you that...
Might as well wrestle a
mama bear for her cub,
you silly boy.
Are you...
gonna eat the bones??
Calcium, yum!
Food!
It feels like you're
a wild animal
and I'm a trainer
in the circus!
Come back here!
Oooh! Bet you
can't catch me!
Stop! If I can't catch you
then I'll have to stop
you like this!
Not bad, Kenichi!
Good arm!
Get back here, you jerk!
Totally lost him.
Speaking of lost...
where am I??
My brother...
in trouble.
I'm so hungry I feel like
I'm gonna pass out...
I don't see how this can even
be considered training...
I mean the other Masters
were pretty tough...
but at least with
them I usually knew
what they were
trying to teach me.
I better keep
looking for camp.
I wish I'd thought to bring
Diagakukan's survival
guide with me.
It's late...
Wait...!
Didn't the Elder say
this forest is full of
tasty filling treats
if you know where to look??
Not... so tasty.
Come back! Come back
here so I can eat you!
Master...? C'm out here!
Is this where
I'm gonna die??
Kenichi's other
bowl is broken...
It broke right
into halvies.
Uh oh...
His chopsticks are
broken now... look.
Ominous...
Okay. That's it.
This is just getting
freaky you guys.
Akisame... what do you
know about this place??
Oh, I don't
know anything...
Nothing at all.
Maybe not...
but when you touch your
stache like that...
it usually means you're
lyin' about somethin'.
Akisame if you
have any inkling
of what my grandpa is up to
you better tell me right now!
I... don't??
Apachai wants
to know, too!
If you don't tell, I won't
play Othello with you no more!
Calm down, both of you.
We all know how stubborn
Akisame can be when he wants to.
He's not going to
tell us any secrets,
no matter how
much we grill him.
But... Even the
most stubborn person
must have a
weakness, right...?
Akisame...
if you really insist on
keeping all of us worried
and in the dark...
Miu and I will
have no choice
but to serve you green bell
peppers at every meal...!
And I'm talking main course!
How did he figure out I
don't eat green bell peppers??
Yes, that's it...!
I'll serve them until
you have peppers
coming out your ears!
Peppers! Peppers! Peppers!
Peppers with rice!
Peppers in soup!
Little green
pickled peppers!
Peppers! Peppers!
That's enough.
I have thought
long and hard about
whether or not to let you
all in on my suspicions...
I've decided it's
best if I don't...
As it would serve no
purpose at this time.
This is a huge gamble...
If Kenichi can make it back
out of the Dark Valley whole...
then he will continue to
grow in strength and technique
as a martial artist...
However... if he ends
up getting lost...
the Kenichi we know
will disappear...
forever.
[Music]
Wait a minute...
The Kenichi we know
will disappear...?
What're you talking about??
There are two types
of martial artist...
The type that remains calm
and relies on talent
and training...
And the type that
forgets everything
they know in a fight...
loses it to rage...
-We know. We know.
-So what?
Kenichi is at a crossroads now,
as to which type of
fighter he will become...
and if he loses
himself out there
and chooses the wrong path...
Yeah...? If he chooses
the wrong path, what??
He will be consumed
by the fire and anger
of the Asura realm.