[Music]
Alright...
If any attack of
mine that I try...
is pointless...
That leaves one option...
Let's see how you handle
attacks from somebody else!
Apa!
A-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-PA!
No way!
And the hundred degrees
street fighter...
Let me introduce you
to the master of all Chinese
martial arts, Kensei Ma!
No! Not again!
Now face the maiden of weapons,
Shigure Kosaka.
The philosophical judo master...
Akisame Koetsuji!
Sheer ignorance...
All fighters know that
to study martial arts...
The art of imitation
is the most important
skill required to master.
What's wrong with him?
Unbelievably reckless...
He's combining his Sei and
his Dou powers together.
Kenichi, whether you
remember it or not,
a long time ago
you did something
for which I can
never forgive you!
What...?
What did I do?
What an amazing kick!
Damn...! Where'd he go?
Behind me!
He activated his Seikkuken
in midair just then.
Is that even possible?
By using both the
outward powers of Dou
and the inner powers
of Sei, it is...
but it is very,
very dangerous...
And not a choice that
most fighters would make,
regardless of
the situation.
Oh no!
Kenichi!
Ogata...
Are you proud of what
you've led your disciple to?
I can't believe it.
I don't think I've ever
seen Akisame mad before...
Not like this.
A-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa!
A-pa!!
I've... never seen
that kind of strength.
I know it's amazing, huh?
Now die!
How's he doing this...?
Does he have a
Berserker mode, too?
Not quite...
From what I'm seeing he's much
fiercer than Berserker...
This is another
level entirely.
We just have to hope
Kenichi survives it.
It's happening already.
-Look.
-Yes, I see.
What...? What's happening?
It's the Dou and Sei...
The two opposite
forces are competing
for ultimate control
over his body.
Releasing them
at the same time
is like releasing
simultaneous explosions
in a sealed bottle...
The payoff is that you
get almost limitless power
while the explosions
remain contained...
but the consequence...
is that the bottle...
inevitably...
must break.
Yeah right...!
Like that's the
worst of it!
What happens to your
body is just a part...
It's what happens
to your mind...
it's what happens
to your soul
we should be worrying
about right now.
And that is
Ogata's plan...
To wait and find
out exactly
what does happen to the boy.
Yes, of course...
He's using his disciple
as a test subject.
Yes, that's right, you're doing
everything perfectly...!
Don't hold back, Ryuto.
Show me how magnificent
we both can be.
So.
You telling me this doesn't jog
your memory a little bit?
About what
happened that day?
Think back...
After that mysterious
girl saved the day...
-Are you okay, ma'am?
-I am.
Thanks to you.
Do you mind if I ask
if this happens a lot?
Oh, dear me, yes.
Then I should probably tell
my grandfather about it.
That brat!
Gimme that!
K- Kenichi?
Grandpaaaaa!
Yes? What's wrong, Miu?
I found some bad
guys, Grandpa!
Ohhhh? And where are
they, little one?
Hang in there! Everything's
okay, Kenichi! I promise!
We don't want any trouble.
We were just, you know,
minding our own business.
Was it you who blew
that whistle back there?
Uh... I...
I just...
Thank you so much!
It really helped!
Uh... Sure.
She was incredible, huh?!
Yeah.
You know what, I think
I do want that badge.
Why?!
I'm the one who traded
that girl for it!
It's mine!
Yeah, but the cat badge
was mine in the first place!
You said you
didn't want it!
You said it was dumb!
Who cares!
Now I want that one!
No!
That's why we fought.
Over that badge!
It was the very first time
I had ever raised my
fists to anyone...
I fought so hard!
Yeah...
And if I remember right
I won that battle.
It was a fluke that your
punch got me in the end!
Damn it...
My ribs...
The thing I could
never forgive...
The reason we're on
this roof right now...
like this...
Is because I lost...
I lost...
But you gave me
the victory anyway!
It's sad...
Really...
That someone of your caliber
must be cut down like this...
Kenichi Shirahama.
In fact, who knows...?
Perhaps I'll decide to bring
both of them back with me.
Who's there?
A master never...
interrupts his
pupil's fight.
Ah, yes, no surprise...
It would be the
philosophical judo master.
And he's not alone.
We won't let you
interrupt this fight.
When Sakaki is serious...
Apachai is serious...
And you should be
big time scared, yes?
Surely not even you
are stupid enough...
to try and fight
all six of us.
Nobody kills Kenichi...
At least not until...
I do... first.
Shigure, that's not
really the message here!
Might as well sit back
with the rest of us
and watch how this little
experiment of yours plays out...
Ogata.
Where did they go?
And do you know
the worst part...?
After you beat me...
After I lost...
You know what
you said to me...?
-"Let's just pretend you won."
-Damn it!
And you tried to
give me that badge!
So is that all there
is to it, Ryuto?
All there is...
All there is to it?
How can you not realize
how much pain your naivety
inflicts on others?
I went back that night...
Back to the general
store by myself...
It took me all night,
but I finally got
a yin-yang badge.
But it was pointless...
empty...
I realized it wasn't
the badge I needed,
it was what the badge
represented to me...
I needed the victory
that went with it!
It was because of that day
that I started training
to be a martial artist
from such an early age...
I suppose I do have
you to thank for that.
I kept on fighting.
Searching for that
complete victory...
Then I met the
Great Sage Fists.
And I learned...
The reason people live...
Is to rid themselves
of weakness.
And it's time I said
goodbye to my weakness...
Bye bye...
Kenichi.
And it's time I said
goodbye to my weakness...
Bye bye...
Kenichi.
Shut up...!
Idiot!!
What?!
Damn, I got careless...
I didn't know you had that
much power left in you.
Where is he?
All this power...
You wanted it all just
so that you could win?
Well that...
is called the path
of Asura... Ryuto!
Impossible...!
That swing was a
limitless... attack...
and he blocked it!
Bastard!
If I don't put a
stop to you today...
Someday you really
will use your powers
to kill somebody.
You can't stop me!
Once more...
Ryuto...
For your sake...
I will...
Defeat you!
No!
I won't let you win again!
The only reason you
beat me back then
was because you were bigger!
That's the only reason!
Wow... They're so powerful.
With every moment
that passes...
Both of them
gain strength.
Yes... But unfortunately
for one of them, time is up.
Ohhh... it looks very painful.
Why...?
Why do you always
find some strange power
that carries you through
to the final moment?
That infuriates me more
than anything else!
What am I doing...?
I have to put up
my Seikkuken...
but... my body
won't listen to me.
That's what happens when
you combine Dou and Sei...
There are tragic
consequences...
His muscles and joints are
responding to the damage
that he's done to them.
Just a little more...
Let me move!!
Please...! I've come
too close to lose now!
Our disciple saw...
without help...
that there was something
wrong with that power...
and that's why...
he's determined to
stop his old friend.
Ryuto... What the...
The gasoline tanks in the
building are exploding-
somebody get
them out of there!
Right! You guys!
We gotta do something!
Yeah, we gotta
help them somehow!
Oh great...! I'm
surrounded by imbeciles...
Just my luck.
Ryuto!
Tell me...
How do you do it, Kenichi?
You owe me that
much, at least...
You're just an average guy,
no different than any other
guy I run into on the street.
While I have an
unparalleled talent...
and the training of
an excellent master...
I've been working
toward this since
I was old enough
to make a fist.
And yet still...
It feels like every
time I look behind me,
there you are, waiting!
Isn't the answer obvious...?
It's because...
No matter what happens
I'm still your friend!
No matter how much
you've changed...
That will always
stay the same.
It looks like that stupid
badge still belongs to you...
Maybe you don't remember
the promise we made back then
but I do.
We swore...
that when we met again
we'd fight for the
honor of wearing it...
Well you won...
It's yours.
Ryuto.
Oh...
and, tell that
girl for me...
That whistle...
I wasn't the one who used
it to save her that day.
Ryuto!!
Hey, I made it in time!
Elder!
Your training methods
are too soft, old man,
you'll never make a champion
out of your disciple
that way, you know.
You pamper him like
a bonsai tree.
Ha! A bonsai...?
That's a good way
of putting it!
What?
But understand,
the bonsai tree
we're cultivating
at RyouzanPAku...
Will be the strongest
in history!
Excuse me, but what do I have
to do with a bonsai tree?
There's something you should
understand as well, old man.
Well, for old time's sake
I'll allow you one sentence
in which to prove your
point, Ogata Ishiinsai.
Then here it is...
Don't disappoint yourself
by believing Ryouzanpaku will
remain history's strongest...
Prepare... for the darkness.
That... Was two sentences.
They ventilated the
entire warehouse
with their bare hands.
The fire has been diverted!
Heh... Can't top that.
How anticlimactic...
Sometimes it's hard
to hold myself back
and do only
what's necessary.
You call that holding
yourself back?
Did you see that?
They're my friends.
Those guys're my friends...
I know, right?
They're pretty amazing.
Heh heh heh.
I think I took us
a bit too high.
Elder. Hey.
Hello, son, you're
awake again are you?
Very well done, Kenichi.
Very well done.
Yeah...
Thanks.
What's wrong...?
You seem a little quiet.
It's just that...
I kinda wanted
my friend back.
Ah, yes...
and that's got you down...
I certainly understand
where you're coming from.
Losing a friend
is no joke,
even a bugger
like that one.
Take a look down there.
That is your
greatest power.
Your most precious treasure.
Everyone...
All my friends...
They're waiting for me.
[Music]
Kenichi you're alive!
I'm so glad you're okay!
Oh, Miu.
I'm back, guys...
Your number one disciple.