[Music]
Hey...
It's been a long time...
Kenichi.
Hey...! I recognize the way
you opened that snack!
Don't tell me you're...
Ryuto Asamiya?!
There's no such thing
as a meaningless fight
in martial arts
every fight has meaning!
Whenever you beat
a new opponent...
you get one step closer
to the ultimate power
that every fighter dreams of!
You've dreamt of it-
you made the same
promise I did!
Stop your meaningless fights
with the Shinpaku Alliance.
You don't get it,
do you Kenichi?
I told you there's no such
thing as a meaningless fight.
We'll continue to fight...
And I will carry out the real
promise we made that day
which you seem to
have forgotten.
What's this "real promise"
you're talking about?
I don't remember
making it.
Did we promise to fight
or something...?
Why won't you just
tell me, Ryuto...?
Or should I call
you the First Fist?
Very good guess...
We did promise
to fight again...
And if you lose I get
that badge of yours!
No way...! My badge?
Why do you want a badge that I
got out of a toy machine...?
I don't get it.
Must be a badge collector.
Enough with the talking...
Time to show me what
you're made of, Kenichi!
I don't really understand
what this is about...
but I'll fight
you if I have to.
What? What's the matter, Miu?
It's just that you're so
quick to rush into a fight.
Shouldn't you guys
try to talk this out?
You heard him- he doesn't
wanna talk he wants to fight.
He may be an old
friend of mine
but that doesn't matter cause
he's with Ragnarok now...
Besides, I would try to
talk him out of this
if I thought it
would do any good.
But it won't...
He's the First Fist,
the leader of Ragnarok
and he's made it
perfectly clear
there's nothing I can
do to change his mind!
It's been ten years
and yet you seem just as
immature and idealistic as ever.
Who do you think is going to
come out on top this time?
I don't think I've ever
seen him this mad before!
Ryuto...
Growing up you were
always shorter than me...
you were weaker than me...
and you were
nicer than me...
What the hell
happened to you?
Damn it, Ryuto!
That was a little
close for comfort...
You're the first person
who's been able to penetrate
my Seikuuken that far.
I'm impressed
you must have been through
some serious training.
But I'm afraid that you've lost
your only chance of winning now.
When you attacked you should've
had enough power to strike me
but for some
reason you let up.
What happened, Kenichi?
I could tell that
your punch lost power
as it got closer to me-
it's almost as if you
were holding back.
What's the matter...?
Don't have it in you to
hit an old friend...?
How pathetic.
Damn it! This time I'm
going in full force!
You okay...?!
How'd he do that?!
I wish I knew the
answer to that!
There must be a
full moon tonight
cause this is just crazy...!
I never thought that Scarface
would treat us to dinner!
The world must be
coming to an end.
No need to be so
dramatic midget.
I can be nice I just don't
wanna make a habit of it.
No worry Honoka-
Apachai can pay the bill
with the money he won
at the track yesterday.
If they knew you could
talk to animals
they would've kicked you
outta there so fast...
A... pa... A... pa.
Even so Apachai's
horse barely won race
so it must have
been beggar's luck.
Beggars don't
have good luck.
-He meant "beginner's".
-That not what I say?
So... Guess I should
thank Scarface
for taking you to
the track with him.
You can thank
me all ya want
but would ya quit
callin' me that?
What the hell...?!
You tryin' to pick a fight
with me, dumbass...?
Watch what you're doin'-
you got eyes dontcha?!
Eyes...?
What? You mean these
two right here?!
Whoa...! You knocked
that jerk out
and you didn't even
have to touch him...!
Hey how'd you do that?!
It's a ki attack.
The kind that open doors?
Naw, have you ever watched
a cat hunt a mouse?
Sometimes you can sense
it's urge to kill .
That's called ki.
It's usually
dormant in humans
but if you work hard enough
you can learn to control it.
When two well trained
fighters throw down,
the ki attack is
very important.
It can be used as a feint
or to pressure your opponent.
If you're a high level
fighter who's trained hard
you can learn to
control your ki
and attack your
opponent with it-
like I just did.
What's the matter...?
Hit me.
What the hell is
that crazy feeling
I get whenever
I'm near him?
I can't even get close!
The First Fist's
ki is strong.
He must really have
the intention to kill.
What's wrong, Kenichi...?
You aren't afraid
of me, are you?
No.
You were always
the nice guy-
even when we were younger.
And you know what
they say about them...
They finish last...
Because they're nothing
more than cowards!
Oh no!
My finishing move...
the shutdown cross.
I never go easy
on anyone...
be they friend or foe.
Kenichi!
So that's all you've got...?
How disappointing.
Furinji.
That weakling isn't on
your level you know...
You could do
so much better.
I wouldn't speak so soon
you haven't seen his
true ability yet.
What was that feeling
all of a sudden?!
I felt a subtle
but strong ki...
Is it coming from him?!
So it must have
been your ki
that was affecting
my attacks.
I won't let you beat
me my fighting spirit
will prevail, Ryuto!
I acted too hastily...
Bad judgment on my part.
Here, I'll help you.
No don't touch me, Miu...
I've gotta do
this on my own.
Wow...!
You got up so fast!
I'm not touching!
Guess you took on more
damage than you thought.
I'll be fine!
I knew you could do it.
This one's gonna be tough.
His palm stopped me
dead in my tracks.
It absorbed the
force of my attack
and bounced it back at me...
And he was able
to stop my punch
just by turning his body-
nobody's done that before.
What're you waiting for...?
I thought that you said
you weren't hurt...?
Let's go.
He has amazing ki and he's
using it to pressure Kenichi!
Damn you!
Not again...!
There's no way
his limitless ki
could have been achieved
through regular training.
Kenichi! Turn around!
I'm impressed...
He was on his way down
but he was still able to
turn at the last minute...
I've never seen that .
The poor guy's used to
being tossed around a lot...
I guess you could say he's like
an Olympic level punching bag.
He's a genius...
when it comes to
getting beaten up.
You're not really helping
me out here, Miu...!
Bastard!
His ki's not
strong enough...
Go ahead!
What an awesome fighter!
Any attack that penetrates his
ki gets deflected immediately!
What's the matter...?
Haven't you had enough...?
I can tell that
you've been trained
by some really amazing
martial arts masters...
but your ridiculous naivety...
makes it basically worthless.
What the hell did you say?!
You have to find
your urge to kill...
Otherwise you'll never be able
to break through my Seikuuken.
Seikuuken?
I knew it...
You're just a beginning martial
arts student, aren't you?
It's the art of keeping
your range open,
yet staying closed
to attacks...
Therefore the Seikuuken
is the impenetrable
circumference
of defense around your body.
Say what?
I'll give you an example
an idiot can understand.
Gee thanks!
You keep yourself open...
yet protected
at all times.
When I move like this
you can see that I'm controlling
everything within my arm's
reach all the way around.
That is the circumference
of my sphere of control.
This is the basis
of my martial art.
I don't really
understand it
but now I see why my
attacks were struck down...
I'll just have to attack
him with my death blow
and hope I can get close
enough to make impact.
Yamazuki...!
Kao Loi...!
Headbutt...!
Falling tree!
Let's see how you handle
my strongest combo!
Yamazuki!
Kao Loi!
No way!
How was he able to block
my death blow so easily?!
That first move was
pretty dangerous...
I'm sure it would've
worked on any other opponent
but with my Seikuuken
I'm completely guarded
so unfortunately for you
it didn't even phase me.
You should give
it a try sometime.
No! Kenichi!
I knew you couldn't
handle it...
You're so wrapped up in
visualizing your target
you didn't catch my attack.
What happened?!
I felt like I was being
pulled into that punch!
We made a deal so
this is mine now.
You're good but you've
still got a lot to learn...
friend.
But why...?
Why do you want that
silly badge so badly?
Don't be stupid this has
nothing to do with the badge...
Ten years ago Kenichi
did something to me
that was unforgivable...
I simply wanted to
return the favor.
Something unforgivable?
Oh yeah, I almost forgot...
It's not really a
fair trade but...
I thought you
might want this.
You see, this badge...
is the medal of a loser.
What was the name of
your little club again?
The Shinpaku Alliance, right?
It's unfortunate because
I was excited to see
what they had to offer...
Not much to look
forward to now.
Least I know they'll
be easy to get rid of.
Kenichi, just hang
in there, alright?
Hey Tanimoto...!
The Shinpaku Alliance is...
How many times do
I have to tell you?
I'm not interested in
joining your stupid club.
Talk to me about it
again and I'll kill you.
Commander!
Are you okay?!
Listen sir, I think you
should leave him alone.
He's not the kinda guy
you can reason with.
I won't give up
that easily...
We've taken out four of
Ragnarok's Deadly Fists
so it's only a matter of
time before they strike back.
We have to make
sure we're prepared.
We're gonna to need
Tanimoto on our side
when it all starts
going down...
So I'm gonna keep pestering
him until he breaks.
Commander...
I'm not gonna give up
our lives depend on it.
Besides...
My little encounter with
him wasn't totally fruitless.
I'm gonna need some help
persuading Tanimoto to join us
so I'm bringing
out the big guns!
Whoa... no way...
Oh wow...
You got him to join the
Shinpaku Alliance...?!
No wonder you're
our general!
Just you wait, Tanimoto...
Soon you'll be eating out
of the palm of my hand.
You got some nerve, kid.
Did you really think you'd just
waltz up here and ambush us...?
There's only four of ya-
that's not even a fair fight!
Surely you didn't think
you could pull one over
on Loki himself, did ya?
Shut your mouth
you big fake fatty.
We've got a secret weapon on our
side that makes us invincible.
Feast your eyes on this...!
We've got one of
your team mates-
The Sixth Deadly Fist, Hermit,
is now a member of
the Shinpaku Alliance!
What...?! No way...!
You've got Master Hermit...?!
Uh, I mean...
That idiot joined you?!
That's right, fatty...!
Hermit has had enough
of Ragnarok's crap
so he decided to
ditch you guys
and become a general of
the Shinpaku Alliance!
Impossible...!
He would never
leave Ragnarok...!
You guys are lying!
Even if he left Ragnarok
he'd never join you
Shinpaku losers!
Guy's a fake...!
He's built completely
different from Hermit-
you're not foolin' me...!
Whoever he is he's gonna
get his ass kicked...!
Get him men!
It's him!
He's so strong he's
gotta be the real deal!
What's the matter, you guys
can't take a little
rough housing...?
Be sure to tell
all your friends
that Hermit's with the
Shinpaku Alliance now!
My plan to spread the word
that Hermit has joined our
alliance is working perfectly.
Good work, pal.
Now Tanimoto will have
no choice but to join us.
So that's the plan, huh?
Well you can forget it.
Sorry I can't let
you do that, Hermit.
You're stronger than
I was expecting...
who the hell are you?!
Go ahead and reveal yourself,
our newest recruit.
Siegfried!
The most amazing melody
just popped into my head...!
Oh, Hermit...!
It's all because of you...!
The excitement of reuniting
with my old friend
has inspired me musically!
Give me a second
to write it down.
Sieg... Why don't
you just say hello?
But how... How did
you get Siegfried
to join your
stupid alliance?
I'd explain but
it's a long story.
It's okay Niijima allow
me to do the explaining...
With song!
After my defeat
I lost my confidence...
I've been sulking by
the sea ever since...
Then one day...
a brilliant melody
came my way...
Though it was off key...
I could tell what
Nee-jee-mah wanted it to be.
His melody shone with such a
revolutionary brilliance...
That I had no choice but to
join the Shinpaku Alliance...
la la la
That didn't make
any sense at all.
Say what you want but now
that Sieg's on my team
I know you're
not far behind.
Last time you turned me down
you left your locker key behind
so I had no problem
stealing your Hermit gear...
What now, Tanimoto...?
Everyone in Ragnarok
already thinks
you're a part of the
Shinpaku Alliance-
so what's stopping
you from joining?
I gotta tell ya, if
I were in your shoes
I'd want somebody on
my side about now...
I mean, now that Ragnarok
thinks you've betrayed them
and joined the
Shinpaku Alliance...
they're sure to come looking
for you, aren't they?
In fact, they're probably
planning their attack right now.
Do you really think you can
take on all of Ragnarok
all by yourself?
Cause I sure
don't think so!
Here's the deal,
Tanimoto...
Join now or die alone...
Well?
I told you that if you
asked me one more time...
I was gonna kill ya.
Now wait just a
minute, Hermit.
It's no secret that I am able to
hear other people's melodies...
they're almost like
an audible aura
that surrounds you.
And your melody is one full
of sadness and despair...
the only way it'll
ever be changed...
is if you become one of us and
join the Shinpaku Alliance.
You see, it's your fate
to become a member
of this alliance, my friend.
Yeah...
Sorry Sieg but I don't
buy a word of it...
See ya.
I can see what lies in
your future, Hermit...
And I know you will be
back to join us very soon!
Would you guys give me back
my locker key, damn it?!
I told you so...
I can't believe I
let him beat me...
damn.
Are you sure you're
gonna be okay, Kenichi?
Yeah... I'll be fine...
Thanks for your concern...
I'll get over it.
That's the spirit...
Good...
Cause we've got a lot more
shopping to do today.
You mean I'm not gonna get even
a little sympathy from you?
No, of course not.
There's no reason for
you to be upset...
You're still alive.
A true martial
artist knows that
you never really lose a
fight until you die...
As long as you're still alive
you can always train harder
and come back victorious.
You'll be just fine...
I was worried for a while there,
but you held your own.
She's right.
As long as I'm alive
I'll have another
chance to defeat him...
I gotta keep training.
Let's see,
what do you think I should
make for dinner tonight, huh?
Grocery shopping
after a fight?
I'm surprised you
haven't asked me
to buy your favorite
fish sticks yet.
She's trying to make
me feel better...
I lost today and
that's okay...
because I won't
become a loser!
So you're a loser... huh?
Yeah, I can tell just by
lookin' at you, kid...
Don't go showin'
everyone your loser face.
Quit picking on me!
Kenichi is it true
you lost a fight?!
You're killing me!
That look could win
Martial Arts Weekly's
"Loser of the Week"
photo contest.
Be more considerate,
would ya?!
Stop talking about
what a loser I am!
You win some you
lose some, right?!
If the loser's gonna
cry like a baby
then I have to get
a recording of it.
How do you even
know that I lost?!
What if I let him win?!
It's been like 10 years since
I've even seen the bas...
Hold on... Your old
friend is a Bass?
They can be mean!
You're just comin'
up with excuses.
And It's pretty obvious
to us that you lost... Yeah.
Damn it, First Fist!
I swear next time I see
you I'm takin' you down!
There you go!
That's the spirit.
Kenichi...
Elder wants to see you...
There's something
he'd like to ask.
You must try to
remain humble...
you won't reach master
status with an ego.
When it comes to a
martial arts fight-
the loser usually walks away
with more knowledge
than the winner.
So how was it, Kenichi...?
Did you come away
from your loss today
with any new martial
arts knowledge?
The Seikuuken.
You're so wrapped up in
visualizing your target
you didn't
catch my attack.
The most prolific
martial arts masters
will thank any opponent
that can beat them
for they've learned
something new.
You'll get over your
loss in no time...
and you'll become a
better fighter for it.
Right!
He's right.
Today I was able to
see how far I've come.
To become a master I have
to thank any opponent
who beats me.
Thanks for talking to me...
Please teach me
everything you know!
Then again... I can't
remember an instance
when I've ever lost a fight.
You gotta be kidding!
[Music]
I have an idea, Kenichi!
How would you feel about
my taking on your
training responsibilities
for a little while?
You mean, I'd get personal
training sessions with you?!
It's about time we shook
up your training a bit.
I think you're
doing a fine job
but we have to keep
you on your toes.
What do you say?
If you can help me beat
Odin then I'm up for anything!
I'll take whatever
you dish out!
Please share your
wisdom with me, elder!
This is going to
get interesting.
So you'll take whatever
I dish out, huh?
Don't forget you said that-
I may make you
eat those words.