[Music]
Get back here!
Come and get me, big boys!
Ahh, yes!
The great Shinpaku
Alliance...
They may seem
impressive...
but one only has to
observe them for a while
to find their weakness.
Niijima's your
secret admirer...?
Well... That explains a lot,
too bad he's not your type!
Yeah, yeah, just get
it outta your system...
And when you do, I don't ever
want to talk about it again.
Yeah, that's right...!
You stupid cow!
Quit teasing my brother.
Honoka, I don't mean
any harm. Really.
Why are you talking?
The purpose of hand pushes
is to develop the ability to
anticipate your opponent.
Yes, sir!
Even I knew that.
Apa?
Apa!
One...
two...
three...
Apachai... Don't cry... Please.
Big news, Kenichi!
Big news!
My inside source just gave me
the inside scoop on Ragnarok.
It's about one of
the Eight Fists.
Interested?
Comfortable...?
You must be getting
used to this by now.
I made it tighter...
you like it... huh?
The Fifth Fist.
Aka Siegfried...
Not a very nice guy.
Uh... What's a Siegfried...?
Apa?
I think he's that
scary circus guy
who got mauled by a
tiger a while ago.
No that was Roy.
And that's not the Siegfried
I'm talking about.
Now, I've gathered
together some statements
from people he's
fought in the past.
Starting with the leader
of the Dead Society...
Sure I remember the Zombie-
went down at the first punch
like he was dead on his feet...
before I knew what
was happening,
he was risin' from the dead and
I was the one eatin' asphalt.
Oh great.
Next up, Toramachi from
Johnny Knife's crew.
He's a freakin' night of the
living dead Zombie bastard...
You don't even know, man,
I kept punchin'
and he'd go down...
but he just wouldn't die...!
You hear me...!
He will eat your
brains for dinner!
I know I have more
here somewhere.
No! That's enough!
Haven't I been telling
you over and over
that I want nothing
to do with your
stupid Shinpaku Alliance
now or ever?
And yet you keep
bringing me
this half-assed
Ragnarok information!
Did you say half assed...?
You think the intricate
network of spies
and informants I worked
so hard on is half assed?
Yeah, that's right...
I think all of your spreadsheets
and diagrams and interviews
only prove one thing.
You don't know what
you're dealing with
and you're in way
over your head!
Admit it.
Fine... If you
choose to believe
that the information
I've put together
for you so lovingly 'til now
is nothing more than a foolish
hobby I'm indulging in,
so be it...
I'll have to
prove you wrong...
I'll bring you a report
on Siegfried so juicy
you can drink it
with your breakfast!
I told you, I don't want
anything to do with this stuff!
I'll be back.
What the...
He's insane.
Well, your buddy there
is certainly ambitious,
isn't he, Kenichi?
My buddy...? Are you
talking about Niijima?
At least this opponent
he has lined up for you
sounds interesting...
An enemy who gets back up
no matter how many times
you knock him down
to the ground, huh?
I've never fought
a zombie before
could be just the
challenge I need.
I have.
So who is this tiger wrestling
guy he was talking about?
The name he used
was Sigfreed.
A name to respect...
In Norse mythology,
Sigfreed was a warrior
who was raised by a king...
After slaying the
vicious dragon Fafnir,
he accidentally tasted
the beast's blood
and therefore became
an immortal.
I know... But then kids these
days love fanciful names...
There might be
no connection...
Oh, and Sakaki,
Roy was mauled.
Whatever... I know.
Look, I don't care...
tiger wrestler or
a dragon slayer...
It has nothing whatsoever
to do with my life...
I'm refusing to be a puppet
in Niijima's master
plan anymore.
That man is bad news...
his path is dark...
he will suffer greatly.
The smell of death
is around him...
it poisons his future...
haunts him.
What?
How do you know
that, Shigure?
Humph.
Ignore'er...
She only sounds like
she knows what's
going on...
It's because of
that low voice
and the flat
delivery she uses.
I don't know.
Sometimes she's kinda right.
She says it so spooky it
almost makes me believe it.
Heh... You worried?
Uh-uh!
You sure, Kenichi...?
It's okay to be
a little worried
about your friend's
safety, you know.
He's not my friend!
A bad friend is still
a friend, young man.
And you should
always be concerned
about the well being of
someone you care about.
I don't care.
He'll be fine! Niijima
would never do anything
to put his own
life in jeopardy.
He's a pansy!
Right?
May I help you with
something, Loki?
Sorry to bother you...
just wondering how your latest
symphony or whatever is coming.
My recent battles have
been uninspiring...
I don't know when
I'll be able to finish
this particular piece,
unfortunately.
I need swinging arms
to give it tempo...
I need cries of pain
to give it a voice...
and I need a face
discovering true terror
to show me the journey
of my melody...
without any of that,
I am lost...
Raw combat is
my only muse.
Too bad the Great Saint
Fists forbids it...
I would like to have a
rousing battle now, Loki...
Would you?
Tell me, how goes
your search
for the ever-elusive weakness of
the great Shinpaku Alliance.
Though I fail
to see a need
for such cautiousness, myself.
I like coming up with the
right plan for each enemy
and watching it
put into action...
That's half the fun,
isn't it?
By the way,
have you noticed anything
suspicious lately, Maestro?
Any prying eyes?
I have been curiously
popular the past few days...
I suppose I shouldn't
be flattered?
Your call...
His name is Haruo Niijima,
and he's with the Shipaku...
Actually, he's the one
who holds them together...
In other words if
somebody got rid of him...
they'd take care of
the whole problem.
This peeping tom
is the Shinpaku Alliance's
greatest weakness...
Whaddaya think, Sieg?
Ready to hear the music?
Weird. My neck
feels all tingly.
Ooh, lookey...!
It's a worm!...
I caught myself a big,
juicy one...!
Loki's gonna be happy!
Is that a woman?
Gimmee, gimmee,
gimme, gimmee!
A pervert...!
The guy's a pervert...!
He touched me!
So that didn't
go so bad...
Got a little careless,
but my special
boob-entrapping maneuver
worked like a charm.
He's after me!
Tear gas!
The Enforcer!
And that was the
Niijima combo.
Don't see why
everyone's all afraid
of this Immortal Composer guy!
That was a piece of cake!
So the Fifth Fist is nothing but
a musically inclined dupe...
Let's see how interested
you are in this, Kenichi.
I find you intriguing.
You have strength of will,
though you are weak.
No, that's impossible!
I saw you go down!
I like you...
Niijima.
I took him down!
I know I did!
Oh well, no time to
think about that now.
Just concentrate
on running.
There's no way
he'll catch me!
How is he not even hurt?!
I'll chase you forever...!
If you run to France...
We shall battle
at the Bastille!
We'll what?!
Niijima U-turn!
Such a beautiful rhythm!
Ahhh!
Niijima trash can toss!
Yes, Niijima!
What a perfect melody
you're creating!
This guy has some
serious issues!
I'm sorry, my
beautiful instrument...
I wanted to wring
so many more notes
from our worthy encounter...
but I'm afraid
our time is up...
the music is calling...
Can you hear it...?
There! The grand finale!
What is he talking about?!
There!
Finally, I can see
my path to victory!
Within that sewer
lies my oasis!
Onward, to freedom!
Niijima excrement...
DEFENSE!
The fates want us to take
this plunge together!
What?!
No...! Let me go!!
Your solo ends here
and we begin our duet!
I lost...
I never lose...
Save me, Kenichi!
Commander, the Captain!
He's gone!
How many times have I asked
you not to call me that...?
My name's Kenichi and I
am not your commander.
Captain Niijima hasn't been
at headquarters all day, sir!
Well, maybe he finally got
tired of playing dictator.
But he sent me a text
message yesterday...
It said 'Tell Kenichi
to save me.'
And I haven't heard
from him since.
It's always possible
he's been kidnapped.
Yeah, by NASA...
Only they'd want him...
Hey, what do you think,
have they got around to
dissecting him yet?
Now go find someone else
to play his little game.
I'm done with him.
But sir! We can't...!
We already tried asking
the other Generals
if they'd help him.
Tell Niijima he's
full of crap.
And they think he's lying!
Well, I can't blame them...
He probably is!
Um, okay, look...
This morning underneath
the bridge I- found- this...
It's the Captain's PDA!
It must've floated
to the surface
because of the water
resistance feature.
Uh-oh.
He never goes anywhere
without this stupid
thing attached to him.
He must really be in
trouble this time.
You're sure?
Yeah, there's no way he would've
just left it somewhere...
I don't care if it was at
the bottom of a lake...
he would've
dived for it.
Then somebody
must've taken him.
It was Ragnarok!
It's gotta be them,
who else would it be?
Okay, don't panic...
I mean Niijima can take
care of himself, right?
Miu! We should
start heading home!
But, sir!
So you're really not
worried about him?
Oh, I'm sure
he'll be fine...
And anyway...
I've got my training to
worry about today, right?
Y' seem anxious
to get to it...
that's a new one.
Yeah.
I almost forgot.
Forgot what?
Today's the release date
for the new issue of
Daigakukan's Martial
Arts of Fury!
I'm gonna stop by the
bookstore first. Okay...?
I'll see you at home!
Kenichi!
You're not fooling
anyone, ya big softy.
Wouldn't this have
been the time
to use your "escape skills",
alien freak?
You know, so you
don't get captured?!
Okay, if they found his
PDA under this bridge...
Then there should be a
clue here somewhere...
I'll just have to keep
looking further downstream
I guess.
Did you find anything yet?
Not yet, but
Niijima's too sneaky
not to have left me
a clue here somewhe...
Miu...!
You followed me? !
I saw something
over there.
Do you think
that shoe is his?
Yeah... That's his...
He must've dropped
it in a struggle.
Look, there's
another over there!
He left us a trail.
Niijima!
I take it you're
coming with me?
Right...
Keep your eyes peeled.
Got it!
Niijima, hang on...!
You did good.
I won't waste the
clues you left me...!
I will find you!
Kenichi? He'll be alright...
Won't he?
I don't think we're gonna
find any more clues.
He tried so
hard to help...
but he had nothing left...!
At least I hope he didn't leave
us anything else after this,
cause: Ew.
Well, we know the
general direction
they were taking him in,
that's good, right?
Yeah...
but the area's
still too big.
Why is he naked, Sieg?
He lost all sense of modesty
after hearing my beautiful song
and gave himself over
to the elements.
Uh huh. Or... he left all his
clothes behind in a trail
so his friends
could find him.
Niijima, I'm sad...
Don't you want to create
transcendent music with me?
Look at what we
accomplished last night...
We wrote a wonderful
rondo of despair.
I couldn't have done it without
your screams of terror.
So what are you jerks
planning on doing with me?
Quit trying to act like
you're all tough, you pervert!.
Loki, his bony legs
are freaking me out,
can't we just kill him now?
What?!
Oh, don't worry...
20's just having
a little fun...
Ragnarok isn't
a death squad,
we are a team of
martial artists...
We don't kill the
people who offend us...
we do, however,
administer punishment
accordingly, of course.
Punishment?
Yeah... For instance, you're
gonna take a one way trip
on this cargo ship here......
In a box.
It'll be a little vacation.
Only you won't
be seeing much.
Or moving.
We don't know how many
months it'll take,
or where you'll end up.
But I'm sure
you'll love it.
Who knows? Maybe if
you're really lucky
you won't get your head
cut off by pirates.
Boys... load him on up!
Yessir!
No! Let me go!
Let go!
You guys are making a big
fat mistake, you hear me?
When the great Shinpaku
generals hear about this...
They're not going
to be too happy!
You think...?
I doubt they'll care.
I saw how they
felt about you...
when they came to
the restaurant...
That day you tricked
them into helping you...
They never wanted to be
part of your Alliance.
They don't care
about any of it.
And I'm betting they don't
care about you, either.
But... can't be sure
until we test it.
So bon voyage.
We looked all around
the neighborhood,
but we didn't find anything.
We're not sure
what else to try.
I see, well that is
a dilemma, isn't it?
But, I mean, it's not like
I care about that freak...
Not really anyway...
No, no, of course
you don't, my boy.
I can find him...
That won't be a problem.
What?!
Me too! Apachai can
find the alien!
Yeah you can, Apachai!
I need only one
thing from you...
His birthday.
Star charts?!
He has long ears like this,
and his eyes are sneaky.
And birds?!
I know where they took
your friend, Kenichi!
How could you possibly
know the answer from that?!
If my calculations
are correct...
Your friend is being...
We tried everything else,
we might as well give
them a shot, right?
Here!
Ahhh! How'd they do that?
Come on, Kenichi, let's go!
You ready to save
Niijima or what?
You bet I'm ready!
I think I might
tag along with ya.
Oh yes, me too!
Can Apachai come with?
We do not interfere in
our disciple's battles.
-Alright, it's just us.
-Right.
You're no fun, you
know that, Akisame?
Wish I could come
with you, big brother!
Me too.
We're coming to
save you, Niijima!
It's done sir...
The crate's been loaded
and we didn't have
any problems at all.
Now that that's done...
Nice. I might actually
like this new song...
Let's help our friend Sieg
come up with a good
ending, huh boys?
Found them!
They're over here!
It's you!
Hello, Loki...
I'm here to take
Niijima back home.
That's right!
I don't understand
why you're here...!
It doesn't make any sense
for you to be here.
I researched you...
I know that Haruo Niijima
bullied you in school
and that he teased you...!
Well? Am I wrong?
Am I missing
something here...?
Why do you care?!
I won't say the
guy's perfect...
He's not...
All that matters is that he
wants to be my friend...!
So he is!
Ugh... This is such a
big disappointment...
All my plans,
blown to crap
because of some
ridiculous principal
you got stuck in your head,
like a tumor.
You screwed things up.
And I don't forgive something
like that real easy...
Too bad for you.
What's going on...?!
All the shouting out here made
me lose my beautiful melody!
And somebody's
going to pay.
Hey...! I won't
ask you again.
Where's Niijima?!
Unfortunately I seem
to have misplaced him,
but please, feel free
to try again later...
When I'm in a
better mood, maybe?
Think you're in a
bad mood now...?
You just wait!
I won't allow you
to fight him yet...
Not until you return my
melody with your blood!
I am the Fifth Fist,
Siegfried...
And you will
be battling me.
So this is Siegfried.
Tell me where you've
hidden Niijima...
And I'll give you the
fight you're asking for.
Yeah, like any of us
would be stupid enough
to answer that, kid...
He's on the ship in a box.
Okay. Fine, which ship?
I think it's that
one over there.
Alright, that's
enough, Sieg.
Number 25 and Number 30...
-Take him down!
-Sir!
I told you, tonight this
one shall fight none but me!
Number 20! Number 43...!
There's nothing
we can do here
when he's like this...
we're leaving.
'Kay!
Hold on! You have
to come back here
and tell me if he
has the right ship!
I need to know if he was
pointing at the right one!
Now we will fight!
And I swear to you
if the melody we create
together is satisfactory,
I will help you
locate your friend.
I think you should
stay and fight him...
I'll follow Loki
and the rest!
'Kay.
I'll stay here and
fight you, I swear,
but first you have
to tell me...
Where is he?!
No... The time for
bargaining is through.
Guess I don't
have any choice...
FINE!
What's different
about this guy...?
It's weird...
He has this energy...
My passion for music
fills my essence
and lends power
to my every move.
Oh my god...
I'm a dead man!
Or not.
So what do you think of my
custom made air gun, blondie?
It might not kill you,
but it'll hurt like
hell if you get hit!
Oh...
Like to play, huh?
Oh my gosh, you
could've died!
You know, Loki
keeps telling me.
People with principals
are really, really...
DUMB!
Darn it! I got careless.
It's... over...?
Wow... This guy's
a lot weaker
than I thought he
was gonna be...
Umm, hey...
Can you wake up and tell me
where the ship is, please, sir?
And the prelude comes
gracefully to an end...
-Feroce!
-Oh, crap!
Accelerando!
That's weird.
His energy is back!
You were playing dead!
I don't play at death...
I rise from the earth!
No... Pretty sure you
were playing dead...
Whatever... I won't
go easy on you now.
Yes, that's right...
Give me your anger,
your fury,
and I will turn it
to luminous sound...
Yamazuki!
I didn't pull that punch.
Now give me my answer...
I wanna know which
ship Niijima...
Fortissimo!
Animato!
Damn... No matter what
I try my attacks
won't phase him.
Your attacks are
slow and obvious,
with no emotion
behind them...
I had hoped that you would gift
me with your full attention.
But I can see that my
expectations for you
were too high...
You do not fight
for your life,
and the melody falters.
Hah...
Perhaps your
lovely companion
would have been a
better opponent for me.
I think I'll seek
her out and see...
Women in pain make lovely
muses for any artist.
Leave her alone!
Excellent, you begin
to show potential.
It's coming!
Listen!
You want my attention...?
You got it! Kao Loi!
Annnnd...
a throw!
Alright...
You through playing
music with me yet?
Verrrry good.
How...? No way!
Despair...!
That is the symphony
that fills the body!
Now the time for our
tempestoso has arrived.
He isn't even in pain...!
It's like he didn't
feel my attacks!
Is he really... immortal?
[Music]
How about now?
You can't tell me you didn't
feel that attack this time!
Such a shame.
No rhythm at all.
If you stop to rest every
time you attack me
this melody will
have no beat.
Jeez...! This guy
really is a zombie!
Come now.
Surely you have
more left in you.
Your friend, Niijima's very
life hangs in the balance...
don't you remember?
Damn it! Fine!
You want a fight?
I'll use every trick I've
learned to defeat you!
Bring it on, Siegfried!