Now it all makes sense,
that way my defensive move
becomes an offensive move!
Please, I just--
I don't want to quit the club!
Please don't make me
quit! Karate's my life!!
As a reward for your
victory, I've got some info.
The guy who refereed your
little fight session
is pretty fired up, I
think it's only right
to give you fair warning
and let you know
that he's gunning for you.
He what?!
Are you kidding me?
No... What am I going to do?
Hey man, can I ask you something
without you makin' fun of me?
Yeah, sure.
You know that new girl in class?
What was her name again? Miu?
Do you think she'd go
on a date with me?
In my opinion, you don't
have a chance in hell...
because I was gonna ask
her to go out with me!
How stupid are you, you've
never even talked to her!
Of course, I haven't
talked to her either.
I don't know how
to approach her.
She's weird, in a 'hot'
way, kinda spacey.
I haven't seen her talk to
anyone, she can speak, right?
Shut up, she's about
to talk to somebody.
It's not a guy, is it?
Hello, anybody home?
No way that's
weak-knees Kenichi!
I've decided I'm
going to sign up
for the Rhythmic
Gymnastics Club.
Have you thought about which
activity you're going to take up
now that you've left
the Karate Club?
Maybe Judo?
And the Kendo Club's
not so bad either.
The... the...
The Gardening Club.
Uh, Like as in
plants and flowers?
You sure you don't want to join
another Martial Arts Club?
Is anybody there?
Hellooo?
And from that day on, Kenichi
devoted his life to watering
innocent flowers who never
cornered him in alleys or tried
to kick his face
down his throat.
They lived happily ever after.
That look in his eyes...
He's cracking
under the pressure.
I have to go, the
flowers are calling me.
Snap out of it, Kenichi, it's
almost time for class to start!
What in the world
has gotten into you?
Allow me to answer that.
Okay...
Pardon my nosey intrusion,
but that's that's what I do.
My name is Haruo Niijima,
and I am Kenichi's closest
of close friends.
Oh, you're one of
Kenichi's friends?
That's right, I am
his closest friend.
And a friend of my close friend
is a friend I'd like
to get close to.
Oh, well nice to
meet you, I'm Miu.
You've gotta be kidding me!
Aw, c'mon, anybody but that guy!
School always seems to interfere
at the worst moment...
I really hate to cut this short,
but I hate expulsion even more,
so how about we finish this
conversation during gym class?
Farewell.
Okay see you later!
Uh...
So the number of electrons
within the atom...
uh...
Um, Tsukuba,
Could you please put
those walnuts away?
I know you're not trying to be,
but they are
somewhat distracting.
Tsukuba...
Uh, Just pretend I didn't
say anything, do as you like.
Uhh. The atom, yes. Where was I?
Something about the atom...
I, uh...
Kenichi Shirahama...
What a scrawny little brat.
The kid's got no
natural talent at all.
But somehow after a week, he
suddenly knows how to fight?
It must have been a fluke.
Either that...
...or he's just been
pretending to be a weakling.
In any case, I'll find
out soon enough.
So he's in the Karate Club too?
Yes, he refereed Kenichi's last
fight and I'm afraid he's taken
quite an interest in his
abilities as a sportsman.
I've heard that he's
become rather keen
on the idea of
testing his skills.
I don't understand?
It's a nice way of saying
that he wants to beat
the snot out of him.
Oh, he just wants to fight?
You had me worried,
I thought Kenichi was
in real trouble.
Well, I admire your optimism,
Miu, but it's not gonna be that
easy for Kenichi, this Tsukuba
guy is pretty serious--
Tsukuba?!
He's never lost a match, I've
seen him spar and he's always
up against at least
two guys if not more.
That guy is so strong,
he could breaks rocks with his
bare hands like it's nothing!
And I've seen him
snap a baseball bat...
...with a single kick!
That's no biggie.
This is bad. This guy
must be a black belt.
Maybe he is in real trouble.
But enough about Kenichi.
Tell me about you, your
family, your measurements,
do you like pointy ears?
You know what they say
about big ears, right?
Oh no!
Didn't anybody ever tell you
not to sneak up behind a girl?!
Hey, are you okay?
I didn't hurt you, did I?
How long before
he hunts me down?
Today? Tomorrow?
The day after?
How long do I have to live?!
You know what you look like?
A loser.
Wait, what's that
supposed to mean?
She's saying you have a
look of defeat about you,
now that you've realized your
"great victory" the other day
has only led to even
greater problems.
Wait, can this guy
actually read my mind?
Moping won't do you any good.
No, the best fix this problem
is more rigorous training!
Akisame sensei!
Yes?
Isn't... there...
a... faster...
way...?
Of course.
There is? 'Cause Tsukuba's
gonna find me any time now.
Is it like some kinda secret
ancient technique or something?
No, faster training
requires faster running.
Do I look like a horse to you?!
No, a horse would run faster!
Now shut your mouth
and move your legs!
This training is gonna kill me
before Tsukuba ever
gets the chance!
Now, nice and slow
in medium stance.
Good, yes, just like that.
And now you've got it.
Martial arts are
rooted in the legs.
Those with weak legs
have no foundation
for their skills to grow on.
Sure, that makes sense, but how
many of these do I have to do?
Just another 9,566,to go.
What?
It's Apachai's
teaching time now!
Apaaa!
Apaapapapapapapapapapa!
Okay, Apachai's fists are done
being warmed up, Kenichi!
Am now ready to fight to death!
We should spar now, yes?
Apa?
Thanks, anyway but
I just remembered
I gotta take care of something!
Poor Kenichi.
Miu.
You went and taught
him a technique
behind our backs, didn't you?
What, but who told you,
how did you find out?!
Come on, everybody knows.
We're not as dumb as we look.
I'm guessing he took down
some Karate Club punk
at his school, right?
--Yeah, pretty much.
--Apa! Apa! Apa!
I'm sure you just wanted to help
him defeat this bully, but you
didn't think about what the
outcome was gonna be, did you?
About all the other bullies
that are just waitin' in line
to take his place? He's
already caught the eye
of some bigger,
stronger guy, hasn't he?
Well that's a yes if
I've ever seen one.
Too bad I don't
take on disciples
or I might actually give a damn.
Everybody else knew this kind
of thing was gonna happen
so they made a point not to
teach him any techniques.
The kid doesn't even have
an ounce of muscle on him,
yet he's already got
fight-hungry thugs
looking to eat him for dinner.
He doesn't have
a chance in hell.
Tell my family I love them!
Come back, Kenichi!
Kenichi?
Kenichi!
Kenichi...
What's wrong?
That you, Honoka?
Wait a minute, what's going on?
Don't tell me you died too?
It's so sad, we're both dead.
But at least I'll have my sister
to keep me company in heaven.
And we'll always be happy.
Always...
Snap out of it, you're not
in heaven, you're at home!
I'm home?
Wait, then that means...
Apachai didn't kill me?!
I'm still alive!
Mom!
Kenichi thought he was dead
and he's freaking me out!
Look at you, bruised and covered
in band-aids; battered...
You do know there
are better things
to spend your
allowance on, right?
Am I supposed to watch you
come home like this every day?
What kind of legitimate
business does this
to its paying students?
The effective kind.
You--
you wouldn't understand, Dad.
This is the only way I'll ever
learn to protect myself!
Hey!
Kenichi, wait up!
Those guys at that dojo
that are the real bullies.
Kenichi! Come back!
What are we gonna do?
No matter how many
times I tell them,
they keep running on the stairs.
Saori...
Yes, dear, what is it?
Our poor little baby
boy is in trouble!
We can't just stand back while
he's getting hurt like this,
we have to do something
to protect him, we have to!
Listen, dear, he wouldn't
have chosen this dojo
if it wasn't safe.
We have to trust
him on this one.
Are you sure, Saori?
But he's just a child! He's too
young and innocent to realize
this dojo has evil intentions!
Our son's life is in danger,
and there's nothing
we can do to help him!
Wait.
Awaken, Sebastian!
We'll have to deal with
this ourselves, old friend.
Just like we delt with those
pesky squirrels in the backyard.
Are you ready for some action?
Sebastian...
Um, dear?
Kenichi has always
run to us for help
or hid whenever there
was any trouble.
He's always been afraid
to live life to the fullest.
Now he's chosen to
stand up for himself.
So I think we should let him
try and fight his own battles.
Sleep now, Sebastian!
Once again,
my love, you're right.
There's no need
to worry about him.
With our DNA, he's destined
to become a strong man!
I'm a little worried
about your DNA, though.
They're waiting by the
back gate for you, too.
They're from the Karate Club.
Tsukuba must have ordered
them to look for me.
There's only one
thing to do.
Strategic withdrawl!
This isn't considered running
away, it's my plan of action.
This way I'll live
to fight another day!
Whatever you say, Kenichi.
He maybe running
from the thugs now,
but I can tell he's
getting stronger everyday.
Wow...
So beautiful!
How does she do that?
That's right, I'm the
best in the class.
The lack of competition
around here is just sad.
Look at that!
Incredible! Whoa!
Oh my golly,
she's so flexible!
How do you even do that?
Wow!
You're so nimble!
Totally effortless!
You must be Miu Furinji.
Transfer student, right?
What are you doing over here
over here in the corner?
Word is you've been training
at an expert level
since junior high.
A talented girl like you
shouldn't be sitting on the
sidelines. That's just stupid.
You should be the
center of attention,
show all of us amateurs
what you can do. Come on.
Why don't you teach
us a thing or two?
Well, what are you
waiting for, show us.
Oh, please, Miu!
Yeah, we'd love to
see what you can do!
Okay? I'll hold your
glasses for you.
Huh?
Don't be shy!
Oh no, this is exactly what
I didn't want to happen.
I was trying so hard
not to stand out.
Alright then. Well
here goes nothing.
This should be
good for a laugh.
Let's see what you're made
of, little miss perfect.
No way...
I've never seen anyone
move so gracefully!
She's amazing...
But it's not just grace.
I can't put my finger
on it. The control...
The precision...
like she's cutting the air...
That's it!
It's like she has the
elegance of a sword.
Here's a towel for you.
Oh, thank you very much.
With you on the team,
we'll definitely take
the championship!
Isn't she great, Takashima?
Huh?
Yeah, great.
Will you teach me
some moves, Miu?
Oh, me too!
And me, and me!
Yeah, me too!
I think I'm really qualified
to teach anything.
Nicely done, Miu.
But don't let this go
to your head, okay girly.
Alright, girls, time
to hit the showers.
Okay!
But what did I do wrong?
I was only doing what
she asked me to.
I don't get it...
Now that class is out,
those Karate Club jerks
are gonna be scouring
the halls looking for me.
Okay, got my shoes.
Now, all I gotta
do is find Miu
and escape out the
first floor window.
All clear on the right...
...and all clear on the left.
And behind me...
I'm clearly in trouble.
Can't we...
Can't we, talk this out Tsukuba?
C'mon, Kenichi...
What's taking you so long?
Come on, you don't
have to do this!
Please just let me go!
You already know you can beat me
so what's the point of fighting?
The point?
I never said I was
making a point.
I just wanna fight
you, Shirahama!
No.
I won't fight you
without a reason.
Running away?
Everyone was right about you...
You really are nothing
but a coward.
No...
Shut up!
Take it Back! Who are
you calling a coward?
Looks like you're
gonna have to make me,
but I don't think you can.
So fast!
Come on, quit wasting my time!
Why aren't you fighting back?
Don't try to act like
you don't have skills,
I've seen you in action. Now
quit playing dead and get up,
Kenichi or I'm gonna have
to beat you while your down.
You think this is funny?
You really are just a
worthless amateur, aren't you?
It was just a fluke
that you beat Daimonji!
Take it back!
That's enough. Let go.
Let go of me now!
I'm warning you kid, you've
already lost, so just give up.
Kid!
Let go!
Impossible!
He bruised my ankle.
How can an amateur be so strong?
No way, unless he really
is faking his weakness.
Hey!
Get up, you worthless loser!
Doesn't make any sense.
Does anyone know if Kenichi
is home from school yet?
Hey, I've been looking for you.
What happened today?
I waited forever.
I was actually starting
to get worried about you.
It's not very nice to
keep a girl waiting--
You're covered in bruises!
So that's where you were,
Tsukuba found you, didn't he?
If I was there I
would have helped you.
I'm fine, Miu.
Nothing happened, I just
fell down the stairs.
Your bruises didn't
come from a fall!
Come on!
Tell me the truth Kenichi!
I'm not lying, I fell
down the stairs.
That's it...
...honestly.
Anyway, I need to
get started training.
Wait, Kenichi, come talk to me!
Just leave him alone.
But Sakaki...
Why?
Listen, Miu.
He doesn't want to see you now.
Sometimes it's too painful
for a man to show his face.
Especially to a woman.
Oh, I see.
Poor Kenichi.
Hm...
It doesn't seem like any of your
bones are broken or fractured.
Nothing seems to
be dislocated either.
That doesn't mean it
doesn't hurt like crazy.
The important thing is that
you made it back safely.
Safely?
Quit laughing, this isn't funny.
I worked so hard to train
and it didn't even matter.
It didn't help. Tsubaka beat me
without even breaking a sweat.
I'm sorry, it's not funny,
I shouldn't have laughed.
What do you plan
on doing about it?
Would you do the same thing
to him, that he's done to you,
if you were given the chance?
All I wanted to do
was prove to him
that he was wrong about me,
but all I could do was tell him.
And that wasn't going
to change anything.
I had to show him!
But when it came down to
it, I had nothing to show.
No matter how hard I tried,
I just couldn't do it.
I'm not strong enough.
I need strength
and I need courage.
But I don't think
I'll ever have either.
Alright!
Tomorrow you will begin
technique training!
His sense of justice
is remarkable.
I never dreamed I would
hear the same words
I spoke to my master
repeated back at me like that.
Kenichi!
Apachai is ready for
your ultimate training!
Apachai, as much as I
appreciate your enthusiasm,
I'm not sure you're capable
of the proper limitations.
Apa?
Apachai no has limits!
I is teaching no limit fighting!
That's not what
he meant, Apachai,
that's not what he
meant! Save me!!
Don't worry, Kenichi!
Only limit is limit of
fear, so do not be afraid!
I show you to
get past fear
and become great
fighter some day!
Okay sure!
Apapa!
I guess he was so excited,
he didn't hear you
say 'starting tomorrow'.
Well, I'm glad that he's happy.
He's just excited to
have his first disciple.
♪ Oh, Apachai teach
you how not to fear! ♪
♪ Apachai kick you
right in the rear! ♪
Wow, he's so happy to
teach me that he's singing.
Apa, Apa, Apa,
Apa, Apa, Apa, Apa!
Oh, wow! He's so fast I
can't even see his punches.
Apa, Apa, Apa, Apa, Apa!
Look at that, he's punching
right through that-- that wall!
Well, Apachai sure is
getting into this, isn't he?
It almost... looks fun.
Will somebody please explain to
Apachai what limitations mean?!
Limits are good!
We need limits!
C'mon, Kenichi, you're not
really giving up, are you?
You're never going to win
with that kind of attitude.
I had no idea that it would
be so hard to learn!
Didn't you just tell me how much
you wanted to learn
these techniques?
You might be in agony now,
but that's how you
know you're learning.
What a horrible way to learn!
Nothing's easy, Kenichi,
but if that's what you want
then I guess you're not
ready to become stronger.
No, I will get stronger!
Forget what I said, Sensei,
I don't want the easy way out!
Once more, please!
Okay, now that's the spirit.