[Music]
You can't even
handle a feint...
High level fighters
can always tell
when their opponent's faking.
How can you be so naïve?!
I'm wasting my time.
You're not on my level!
You... You say you stand
for justice and truth
but don't you see that's
not gonna get you anywhere
as a fighter?!
A martial arts master
has to have the ability
to trick his opponent
and use their powers
against them.
Someone like you would never
be able to pull that off.
Our little chat is over...
You probably don't even have the
strength to stand right now.
Die!
What the...
I've heard enough...
I won't let you trick
me into pitying you
so you can pummel
me into the ground.
I'm ready to fight!
Impossible!
You may have
amazing masters
but you're naivety is
gonna get the best of you.
It seems that the
winner has been decided.
Power and deceit...
Those two things are all you
need to get by in this world.
You're...
You're wrong.
If you live a life
full of deceit-
constantly struggling
for power...
you'll end up with
nothing but sadness.
My karate master
once told me...
talking with your fists makes
your words hit... harder.
No matter how much someone
tries to put on a façade...
you'll have them
completely figured out
once you fight them.
I know you aren't the
one who kidnapped Honoka.
After what you've
been through
you'd never kidnap
someone's sister...
I know that you
didn't do it...
but you know that
as her brother
it's my duty to protect her.
But that's impossible...!
He shouldn't even be
able to stand right now-
not after I've attacked
him repeatedly!
What you truly need to
get by in this world
is not power or deceit...
You need a heart that is
capable of trusting others
and deep down
you know that.
Trust your masters.
Trust your friends...
and most importantly
trust yourself...
because that
is true power.
'A heart that is capable
of trusting others'...
I don't think you
get it, Shirahama...
That way of thinking is
what killed my sister!
Well, my sister is
counting on me to save her
and I'm not gonna
let her down!
You're so naïve-
do you really think you'll
be able to protect her?
Double palm!
That's quite impressive...
The Double Palm...
I never thought
you would know
one of the eight... punches...
But if you don't attack
with all of your might
it's very easy
to block it.
That punch was
so powerful...
It's much stronger
than anything
I've ever been capable of.
That's right...!
You don't have to be
deceitful to gain power
all you need
is determination
and some good old
fashioned training!
I don't understand- how do you
know all these martial arts?
At first I thought
it was just karate
but you also use Jujitsu,
Kenpo, even Muay Thai...!
Just who the hell do
you think you are, kid?
I'm Kenichi Shirahama...
and I'm history's
strongest disciple.
I don't know what
you're talking about
but it's about time
we end this...
Let's go!
That's enough you two.
That was awesome...
Definitely a great fight.
But you've been rained out
so I think you should
call it a day.
The final victory
always goes to Ragnarok.
Don't forget that, kid.
Big brother!
Honoka!
Why'd you drag my
sister into this...?!
That's dirty-
even for Ragnarok!
True... True.
Kenichi!
-So what should we do now?
-Nothing...
We will wait here...
We've got to let
him handle this...
We'll jump in if
he needs help
but otherwise we stay put.
Yeah, you're right...
Ya never know what life
is gonna throw your way
so he needs to be able to
handle it on his own...
Still wouldn't mind takin'
a swing at him, though.
I feel the same...
but he has to fight
his own battles...
we need to stay
out of this one.
Alright then, Hermit...
This is your chance to take
down Shirahama for good...
You think you
can handle it?
I'm not taking any
orders from you... Loki!
From me...?
What did I say...?
These aren't my orders
they're direct orders from
the Great Sage Fists himself.
If I were you I'd
shut my mouth
and do whatever he
asks, Hermit.
After all, you owe
him one- remember?
Hey, what do ya mean...?
Does this guy seriously
have some kinda connection
to the Great Sage Fists?
Yeah, want me to
tell you about it?
Bastard...
It's a great story...
you see, back when
our friend here
was known as Natsu Tanimoto
there was an accident
involving his father...
Evidently Hermit's stepmother
poisoned the poor man
leading to his death.
Little Natsu inherited
his father's corporation
which left him with
huge responsibilities
for one so young....
He wasn't able to manage
everything on his own
and the company employees
quickly bullied him
into signing over the
corporation's assets to them.
They practically
cleaned the place out.
Poor little Natsu didn't
even have time to cry...
His sister Kaede
was very ill
and he needed money to
pay for her treatment...
As a result of
losing the company
and expensive medical costs,
the family fortune
was dwindling away.
Is something wrong?
Don't you worry- everything'll
be fine... Kaede.
I'm not gonna
lose to them...
I promise I'll do whatever
it takes to protect you.
Eventually he was
able to find a lawyer
who was willing to
listen to a child...
but only after most of
the company's assets
had already been stolen.
You must be exhausted.
I would be too...
I'm surprised you've been
able to handle all this
by yourself thus far.
It wasn't easy.
I'm sure...
Now I need you to
sign this document...
These papers will ensure
that no one steals
from you again.
Thanks... You're the
greatest, Kondou!
You're a lifesaver.
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
Don't worry about it,
Mr. Tah-nee-moto...
I've always got your
best interests at heart.
Hey...! What the...
Get out.
Sir... I think...
We should go ahead
and do what they say.
Let... go!
You're hurting me!
Quit struggling, kid...
There's no sense in making
this any harder than it is.
Do what you're told
and you won't get hurt.
Go ahead and kill
me if you want
but you're never
gonna get my money!
I've got some bad
news for ya...
We've got your signature-
we're entitled to
everything you own.
You can see for yourself...
The document's right here.
No... Kondou how could you?!
At some point the powerless
have to take matters
into their own hands...
That time is now.
This document
changes everything...
Now the employees control
the company and its assets.
Not some orphan who hasn't
had to work a day in his life.
That means... we don't
take orders from you.
Do it. Throw
him over the side.
No one will look
for him down there.
Stop... it...
let... me... go...!
Almost as easy as taking
candy from a baby, isn't it?
Who's there...?!
Show yourself!
It's such a beautiful night,
don't you agree?
Let's not ruin it
with talk of murder.
Look...! He's up there!
Whoa... No way.
Now... I suggest that
you leave the boy alone.
Hey... Butt out...
What do you think you're
doing here anyway?
Taking a walk...
Is that okay?
Who is this guy?
Uh... I don't know.
Let the boy go...
Just leave him be and
shoot me in his place.
This is your chance.
Go ahead.
You heard the man...
He saw our faces we
have to kill him...
Shoot him!
I didn't think you'd
actually do it.
Where'd his feet go?!
Now I'm angry.
Are you okay, young man?
Yeah... I remember it all Loki
so there's no need
for you to remind me.
The Great Sage Fists
saved my life that night
and he shared his
wisdom with me.
He said, "If you want
people to follow you
then you must first learn to
become a righteous leader."
"You must be physically
and mentally strong...
and you must
have the ability
to move freely
from head to toe."
That was when...
he told me...
I should learn
martial arts.
I'm handing down orders
from your savior,
The Great Sage
Fists, himself...
If you know what's good for
ya you'll kill Shirahama
Ha...! I knew it...
You can't...
Fine- I'll do it.
Prepare to die, Shirahama!
You can hit me as
much as you want.
Hold on... You shouldn't even
be able to stand right now...
Your defenses are
better than I thought.
You want to turn it
down a notch...?
you're scaring
the crows away.
Go ahead and hit me
as much as you want...
as long as you
give Honoka back!
Go ahead and hit me
as much as you want...
as long as you
give Honoka back!
Now that's the spirit...
I'm fine with
letting her go
if I get to beat
the crap outta you.
Don't worry about me-
kick his butt, Kenichi!
Hey... you better shut
it ya little twerp...
I'd hate to
have to hurt ya.
Let... me... go...
you... big... bully...
-Shut up!
-mmmm
I love how anytime I mention
the Great Sage Fists
you do what
I say, Hermit.
Now let me show you
how this is done...
I'll take this kid
out with one attack!
Damn it...
What's the, deal...?
Punching you feels like I'm
punching a tree or somethin'...
I honestly didn't expect
you to last this long.
But I'm not too worried,
cause I can keep on
going all night,
and besides it's not like
Hermit could do any better.
Damn you!
That's karate's
three point stance...
He's doing exactly
what I taught him-
keeping his legs in
tight and his arms up
so his opponent
can't hurt him.
Gotta say I'm impressed...
he's done... so well...
He's keeping his muscles
tight and his joints loose...
That's one of the best 3
point stances I've ever seen.
I like a challenge...
Makes things interesting.
Then give it
all you got...
I can tell you're
a strong guy...
but you're obviously not
strong enough to knock me out.
Bite me again and
I'll bite back!
Why'd you have to go and get my
sister involved in this...?
If you wanted to fight all
you had to do was ask
and I would've
gladly accepted.
You don't get
it, do you kid?
Bad guys don't
play by the rules.
That's what you were gonna
say next, wasn't it...?
I got you figured out.
Sorry we're late...
We got here as
fast as we could.
Awesome...
Looks like I'll finally
get to fight the real Loki.
Damn... I swear those idiots
are good for nothin'...
I mean jeez, couldn't they
have at least stalled
for 10 more minutes?
Hey... you guys.
If you punks lay
a hand on Loki
I'm gonna slice this
midget's throat, got it?!
Don't worry 'bout me-
I'll be alright...!
Save my brother,
okay Big Boobs?!
You can count
on me, Honoka...
But my boobs
aren't that big.
Shut up, ya dumb ass.
You ready for this...?
Now that we've
got an audience
ya might wanna try not to
embarrass yourself, kid.
A palm?!
No.
No...! That punch he's
using is dangerous!
The instant his hand makes
contact with his opponent
he makes a fist.
This creates a
thrust of energy
which makes his punch
twice as powerful...
It's a very complex move.
One that relies on the
joints of the wrist.
Oh... I get it...
It's like flicking
someone's forehead.
If you build up some
energy beforehand
it makes the force of the
flick that much stronger.
The good thing is he
didn't anticipate Loki
using that punch so
he didn't tense up-
he stayed flexible so he
could absorb that energy.
The 3 point stance
isn't just for defense.
The energy he's
used is powerful...
It can deal a death
blow at close range.
I bet Kenichi's waiting for the
perfect chance to retaliate.
Go Kenichi!
Let go!
Would you cut it out?!
Brother!
Let go... now!
Now see what you
made me do...!
I told ya to stop
squirming around...
This is all your
fault, you know.
Help me...!
Big brother...!
Kaede... Kaede...
Hang in there.
Please... Everything's
gonna be okay...
You'll get better
in no time.
Brother... don't... lie...
I know better...
Kaede...
I'm sorry...
Natsu...
I'm...
Sorry...
Why are you
apologizing to me...?
Kaede...
Please don't...
You didn't do
anything wrong, kay?
Brother I...
I can't...
I can't hang on...
not anymore.
I love you big brother...
please... don't give in...
please.
Kaede...
Hey...?
No...! Kaede!
Please...
Don't leave me...
Kaede... Kaede!
This is really
startin' to get old...
It's time we ended
this don't you think?
Big brother!
I told you to stop!
Why...
Why'd you do that?
You shouldn't be
holding a weapon
if you're not gonna
use it properly.
This is it, kid!
Kenichi Shirahama!
It's okay...! I'm safe
and sound now, guys!
Kill Loki!
Damn you...
Hermit!
Yeah!
He did it!
Wow!
Hold up! What'd I miss?!
Loki...! I should kill
you for what you did...!
You bastard!
Damn it...
And everything was
going according to plan.
I can't even
think straight...
That punch
really got to me.
That's... blood!
I'm not gonna let you
get away with this...
How dare you
draw blood...!
And you, Hermit...!
How dare you go
against orders sent
from the Great Sage
Fists himself?!
Your days as a member of
Ragnarok are numbered!
I couldn't care less...
I don't wanna be a part
of your stupid club, Loki.
Fine... You're
just a traitor...
I'm sure everyone will
be happy to hear that...
Come down and fight
me like a man!
You too Kenichi
Shirahama...
I'll take on
the both of you!
That's enough!
What's he doing here?
The First Fist!
[Music]
I don't understand. You still
wanna fight me, Hermit?!
Of course I do! What
better time than now?
All of our
distractions are gone-
it's the perfect opportunity
for us to end this!
But there's no reason
for us do this anymore!
You need a
reason to fight?
Okay, how about this...
I don't like you.
Is that enough for ya?
Now let's get
this over with.
Are you ready Shirahama?
This is your
chance to opt out
if you're not man enough.
I'm ready.
If you really want a fight
then I'll give you a fight.
I've had enough.
Let's do this!