Man this sucks.
How much longer I'm gonna
have to sneak around like this?
You just need a
little more training.
Once you are able to show
those bullies who's boss,
you'll be able to relax.
Hold on, so you saying,
I can't relax 'til I've fought
every bully in school?
Yup, that about sums it up.
They haven't been able
to find us up here yet,
so you can relax a little.
You can run, but you
can't hide, Kenichi.
But the worst of your worries
is another senior, Takeda Ikki.
Not only is he ruthless, but
he's a former lightweight boxer.
He's a boxer?
Yep, he's a professional
fighter. Word is that he was
the premiere rookie until he
dropped out of the league.
What's a guy like that doing
fighting for Ragnarok?!
But I'm still an executive
member, and you're just a grunt.
Say hello punk.
I said hello to the
one who matters.
Oh yeah? You really think you're
pretty slick, don't you?
You sure are jumpy, I was
just stretching my arm.
Oh, by the way,
do you need this?
It's the button
from your sleeve.
No thanks, I go plenty.
A-pa pa pa pa!
Whoa-ho, you scared me
there, that was a fast one!
I thought I was a goner!.
That was so fast I
didn't even see it!
In that case, watch
your opponent's shoulder
and guess the speed.
Okay!
Oh wow! He learned how to
hold back, that's so great!
Okay, now it time
you have to dodge!
Okay!
Apapapapapapapapa!
Hey, check out that hawk.
It's so peaceful
and quiet up here.
Kind'a nice for a change, huh?
C'mon, will you
take this seriously?
This is where the kid's been
hiding during lunch, right?
So why hasn't he shown up?
We've been here an hour!
Someone must've tipped him off.
Don't fall asleep on me!
Jeez, will you take
it easy, man?
No, I won't take it easy!
It's already been a month since
Kisara told us to find this punk
and so far we've got squat!
It's ridiculous! And our rank
in Ragnarok is on the line here!
Why can't we find him?! I mean,
we go to the same school!
Does he even exist?!
It's insane!
Yeah, sure, the
school is huge,
but it's not huge enough
to hide in for a month!
This kid's gotta be
made of camouflage!
Quit freaking out.
I've got an idea
that might work.
You're acting like
it's no big-- what?
I've got a plan to lure
him out of the shadows.
There's one thing we've
been doing wrong.
You see, we just haven't
been using the right bait.
Well, it's about time
you came up with an idea
instead of just
laying around.
So what are you waiting for?
Just attack me, you
can't hesitate in a fight.
Yeah...
I know, it's just that...
...it goes against
my principals.
My mother always told
me not to hit girls.
Well, that's chivalrous of you,
but we're supposed to be
sparring so c'mon attack me.
Hey! You still spouting
off that chivalry crap?
Miu can handle it,
you've got gloves.
Even if you didn't,
I doubt your punches would
have any effect on her.
Oh, come on! You don't
have to insult me!
Just fight!
He's right!
You've got to punch!
You have to have sparring
practice with a person
before you can fight the boxer!
Apachai would do it,
but I would kill you, and it
would not be a good practice.
We're all too advanced,
so it's pointless for
you to spar with us.
So, whether you like it or
not, Miu is your only option.
Now fight!
Alright!
But I can't bring myself to
hit a girl, it's just not right!
I've never met anyone
with such a strong sense
of what's right and wrong.
He honestly believes
that kindness is more
important than anything else.
But fighting can be ruthless and
his enemies won't feel that way.
Whoa, you almost hit me!
Hit him, Miu!
Apa!
Listen closely, Kenichi!
Your concern is admirable.
But refusing to acknowledge
your sparring partner
isn't a sign of respect.
You should never take a
deferential attitude towards
a rival who is attempting to
help you improve your skills.
That is not an expression
of kindness, but rudeness.
I'm sorry if I was rude.
Okay, I'm gonna attack
you from the side.
Go for it.
I couldn't even get close
enough to touch her.
And Miu was moving much more
slowly than she usually does!
Thanks for hiding out with me.
No problem. So how're you
feeling? You still sore?
Nah, I'm fine.
I think I'm gradually
building a tolerance to it.
This place is nice and quiet,
even if it is a little musty.
I thought it was kinda
depressing at first,
but now that I'm used to it,
it's actually kinda cozy.
It is cozy, the
two of us here...
no interruptions,
just us, alone.
Why am I just now realizing
how awesome this is
and why am I totally frozen?
Hey, you're red, you okay?
Come here.
So close!
Oh, good. I was worried
you had a fever.
I can't go one on one
with someone who's sickly.
Um, I was talking
about training.
This is my chance.
Don't blow it, Kenichi!
Miu, you look kinda tense,
why don't you sit
down and relax a bit?
Thanks...
I've been sitting here
for a while, you know.
Uh-huh! And dontcha
think it's nice?
Just the two of us, alone.
You're so generous.
What is it with you?!
Is there no such thing
as privacy on
your home planet?!
Is this lunch? Thanks.
Go ahead, help yourself.
Where did you come from anyway?!
He's been standing
in that corner
the whole time
we've been here.
I'm surprised you
didn't notice him.
Why the long face?
I thought you'd be
happy to see me,
especially with the dirt
I've dug up for you.
You've got new information
about the boxer?
Yep.
His name's Takeda Ikki.
If he hadn't shown up I'd be
making out with Miu by now!
He ruins everything!
I hate him.
Supposedly this Takeda
fellow was making
quite the name for
himself as a boxer.
He won the pro rookie
tournament using an attack
called the Lethal Left.
Heard of it?
The Lethal Left?
Yeah, evidently his
left arm is the one
you need to watch out for.
From what I've heard,
it's unlikely you'd
even see it coming.
People have apparently tried
to replay the video footage
of his fight
in slow motion,
but they still couldn't
see his left punch.
I'm going to die soon, aren't I?
Sure are.
One thing I couldn't figure out
is why he dropped boxing in
exchange for a life of crime.
Lousy trade to me.
I can't believe you
still haven't asked Miu
to go to the movie with us.
Give me a break, it's
harder than you think.
You could try to ask
her too, y'know.
I would but I'm tryin' to help
you step up and be a man.
You better ask her before
the movie stops showing.
I've got it!
Why don't we try to be friends
with weak-knees Kenichi?
That's not a bad idea.
We'll pretend to be his
friends to get to Miu.
It's like that old saying,
"if you wanna shoot the general,
shoot his horse first."
Let's make a pact! From now on,
no matter how annoying he is,
we're Kenichi's friends!
No matter what.
We're his best friends!
Huh?
So you're his best friends? Well
then, come with me for a sec.
Good afternoon, class.
We've got a test review today.
But let's take
attendance first...
I finally get to read my book.
Seems like I never get
the chance to read anymore.
What?
We're holding your friends
hostage on the roof.
If you wanna see 'em alive
again, ya better get here fast.
My friends...?
Do I even have any
other friends than Miu?
Wait, two?
Oh, It looks like both Shimayama
and Tanaka are absent today.
Must've gone home early.
Shimayama? Tanaka?
Hey, weak-knees!
Is it true that everyone called
you weak-knees in junior high
because you're
such a coward?
They can't be serious.
How could anybody think those
two guys were my friends?
This has gotta be
some kind of mistake.
It'd be a different story
if they'd kidnapped Miu,
but those two jerks?
The friendliest thing
they've ever done
is pretend to help me up so
they could push me down again.
What'll I do?
If I go up there I'm
gonna get slaughtered.
Are they even worth it?
Takeda, you can't
seriously think
a trick like this
is gonna work.
Trust me, if the kid cares
at all about his friends,
he'll show up
to save them.
It's a foolproof
plan, my friend.
Dunno. A normal person
would get scared and run.
He's gonna show.
What the hell is
wrong with him?
He can't be serious.
it'll never work.
Nobody would walk
into a trap like this.
I know I wouldn't do it.
Any minute now.
Excuse me, I'm sorry
to interrupt, but um...
See, The thing is, we're not
really Shirahama's friends.
What? Don't you lie to me!
I heard you say that you
were his best friends!
We were just using him to
get close to his hot friend.
We always pick on
him because he's weak.
And I'm pretty sure
he hates our guts
for bullying him all the time.
So you're saying that even
though we kidnapped you--
He's not gonna
come to rescue us!
I bet he's laughing at the
idea of us getting killed!
We did this for nothing?!
Would ya quit
throwin' 'em around?
I don't really feel
like burying them.
Shut up! Your stupid plan
didn't work did it, Takeda?
From now on we're doing
things my way, you got that?
I'm gonna do whatever I wanna
do! Just try and stop me.
Please, I'm sorry
just let me go!
Fine, blow off some
steam if you have to.
Let him go!
I'm the one you want,
now let them go!
Hey, there he is,
what did I tell ya?
He's definitely an idiot
Aren't you Mr. Nice guy?
Coming up here to save your
pathetic little friends.
Maybe you should've
thought twice.
'Cause your nice-guy act,
just landed you in a
whole lot of trouble.
That look...
It's so cold.
This artist was particularly
popular during the early...
I wonder why Kenichi hasn't come
back from the bathroom yet.
What's taking him so long?
I hope he's okay.
It's about time
we met, Shirahama.
Hey wait up!
About a month ago our
boss asked us to find you.
We've been searchin'
for you since.
We're taking you to Kisara.
But considering the chase
you've led us on,
we can't ask you to come along
with us peacefully, now can we?
You blew it.
Please, just let me go.
There's no reason for us
to resort to violence.
I can think of 100 reasons,
here's a few for ya:
you've wasted our time
and I think it'll be fun.
Well? What's the deal, Ukita?
C'mon, are you gonna
throw the kid or not?
Let go, dammit!
What? No way! I don't wanna
get thrown off the roof!
Hang on, Shirahama!
So what do you
call that technique?
Soon as you let go, you're dead!
Thanks for the warning,
I'm never gonna let go now!
Alright then, hold on!
You worthless, little brat.
You signed your own death
certificate with that stunt.
Whoa, hey, man!
Why don't we just
try to talk this out--
As soon as you
get close enough,
You grab them by the
head and finish it!
Did I really just do that?!
My body moved on its own.
Oh, no! Please, please,
please be okay!
I'm sorry, I really didn't
want to hurt you!
It's just like I've been
brainwashed or something!
Everyday they charge at
me and yell 'finish it'!
C'mon, hello? Can you hear me?
Looks like he's out.
It's just you and
me now, Shirahama.
And I hope you're ready 'cause
I'm gonna have to hurt you
for what you did
to my buddy Ukita.
Is he pulling a knife?
Is that a watch?
And chalk?
Okay...
Alright! You ready?
Is that supposed
to be a boxing ring?!
He can't be serious...
Are you kidding me?!
He obliterated that
chalk with one punch!
You do realize I was a
professional boxer, right?
But I'll go easy on ya.
I'm gonna take you on
using only my right arm.
You ready to take
it to the ring?
This jerk took hostages
just to get me up here.
I think it's safe to say I can't
talk my way out of this one.
By the way, you know your pals
you were tryin' to protect?
Looks like they've
ditched you.
Bet you regret comin'
to save them, huh?
This is some situation
you've got yourself into.
You're not too bright, are ya?
If I had to describe you
in one word it's be...
...dumbass.
You think so?
Well, I may be a dumbass,
but at least I'm not a thug!
Oh really? Aren't
you a tough guy?
Let's see just how dumb you are.
I think you might
change your mind.
You can attack me with
any style you've got.
Anything goes, alright?
Ten counts for a knockout,
three knockouts and it's over.
So basically if you go
down 3 times in one round,
then you lose by K.O., got it?
He's laughing. He thinks
this is a joke.
The only way I'll make
it out alive is if I win.
I really hope all that
Muay Thai training pays off!
And he's down!
So are you gonna get up
or should I start counting?
One...
What just happened?
How the hell did he do that?
He managed to hit
me 3 times, but how?
They were so fast!
Three...
Four...
And he's only using one hand!
Hey...
There ya go, that's the spirit.
The tension in the air...
the taste of blood
in your mouth...
Don't you just love boxing?
His punches are so fast!
Not as fast as
Apachai's but close.
I can't even see them!
What am I gonna do?
I've gotta land
a punch somehow.
Otherwise I'm a dead man!
Heh. Looks like someone's
taken a couple karate lessons.
Bring it, kid.
You got it!
You've got enthusiasm but
you don't have the grace
or speed to pull the moves off.
He's not quite
as skilled as Miu.
But I still can't get close
enough to touch him!
Not only are his punches fast
but his defense is flawless!
I've gotta slow him down!
There's no way!
I can't! There's no
way I can beat him.
And that makes number two.
One more and it's over for you.
You come to
your senses yet?
All this trouble 'cause
of your stupid friends.
Tell me.
Was it worth all
this to save them?
I feel like I'm
about to pass out.
What did Apachai say?
I can't remember...
Don't worry, you
tried your best.
You just weren't quite ready.
What was it?
To fight a boxer.
Boxer...
You really believe
that Kenichi could win
against a boxer with the
shape he's in right now?
'Cuz I'm not so sure about it.
You wrong Sakaki. He will win!
Apachai. Did you give
him extensive training
in the technique I
asked you to show him?
And what technique is this?
I taught him good!
Apachai made him practice
'til he threw up.
Hey, did you not hear me?
What technique is this?
Is it some special
Muay Thai boxer repellant?
Something like that...
It's been said that if one
is capable of mastering
this technique, then he's
capable of mastering the world.
It's known as the "ti lan".
That's it! I remember now!
A boxer's greatest weakness!
You can still stand up
straight. I'm impressed.
This is my only
chance to stop him.
Ti lan!
A low kick? What the hell?
He faked me out
and I fell for it.
I didn't think he was
gonna attack my knee.
Was he just pretending
to be an amateur?
His lower body
strength is incredible!
He obviously knows
more than just karate.
But how much does he know?
And where the hell
did he learn it?
A boxer's weakness
is his lower body!
It worked! Apachai!
The ti-lan! It worked!
Not bad.
He didn't have time to react!
He seems so slow
all of a sudden!
This is...
...it!
What's wrong with you?
Why'd you stop like that?
The bell rang. That's a
three-minute break, right?
Say what?
You know, you really
are a dumbass, kid.
What?
The break's one minute.
You only wish you
had more time to rest.
Yeah, whatever.
It's probably a good
idea for you to sit down.
You can't recover
while you're standing.
What makes you think I need
to recover from anything?
Try not to flatter
yourself, amateur.
Save your breath for fighting.
Damn...
Who am I kidding?
If I sat down now, I'd never
be able to get back up again.
What now?
There's no way I can withstand
another one of his low kicks.
Kenichi Shirahama...
There's a lot more to you
than I thought there was.
Niijima was right about him.
He's an incredible fighter.
But I don't get it...
Why would such a talented guy
give it all up... for nothing?
I have to say, I'm surprised--
I didn't think you'd
last this long.
There's something I've
been meaning to ask you.
Why'd you give up your boxing
career to become a thug?
Why do you care?
Every time you open your mouth
you prove that you're
just a sucker.
Look Mr. Nice Guy, caring
about other people
is the stupidest
thing you can do.
Trust me, I know, that's
what ruined my career.
There's the bell.
Better watch out 'cause I'm not
holding back this round!
Fine with me!
I wasn't planning on
holding back either!