[Music]
Nice. I think I might actually
like this new song...
Let's help our
friend Sieg come up
with a good
ending, huh boys?
Found them!
They're over here!
It's you!
Hello, Loki...
I'm here to take
Niijima back home.
That's right!
What's going on...?!
All the shouting out
here made me lose
my beautiful melody!
And somebody's
going to pay.
Hey...! I won't
ask you again.
Where's Niijima? !
Unfortunately I seem
to have misplaced him,
but please, feel free
to try again later...
When I'm in a
better mood, maybe.
Think you're in
a bad mood now...
you just wait!
I won't allow you
to fight him yet...
Not until you return my
melody with your blood!
I am the Fifth
Fist, Siegfried...
And you will
be battling me.
It's... over...? Wow...
This guy's a lot
weaker than I thought
he was gonna be...
Umm, hey...
Can you wake up and tell
me where the ship is,
please, sir?
And the prelude comes
gracefully to an end...
-Feroce!
-Oh, crap!
Accelerando!
That's weird.
His energy is back!
You were playing dead!
I don't play at death...
I rise from the earth!
No... Pretty sure you
were playing dead...
Whatever... I won't
go easy on you now.
Yes, that's right...
Give me your
anger, your fury,
and I will turn it
to luminous sound...
Yamazuki!
I didn't pull that punch.
Now give me my answer...
I wanna know which
ship Niijima--
Fortissimo!
Animato!
Damn... No matter what I try my
attacks won't phasing him.
Your attacks are
slow and obvious,
with no emotion behind them...
I had hoped that
you would gift me
with your full attention.
Much like a raging
thunderstorm...
I will attack with
uncanzone tempestoso...!
La-La-La-La-La-La-La-La-LA -La.
Be afraid...! I want to feel
your fear and anger...!
Your emotions will become
the body of my symphony!
It seems like my
attacks aren't having
any kind of affect on
this guy at all...
So that's the power of
Ragnarok's fifth fist,
Siegfried ...
Is it possible
that he's immortal?
Let me outta here...!
Somebody please
let me out...
This isn't funny
anymore...!
If you know what's good for ya
you'll let me out of here
before I start to get
REALLY angry!
Got him.
Fortissimo!
That's crazy!
My hit made
contact with him...
how'd he hit me
back so quickly?
I'll have to write
that one down.
I gotta figure out
how he's doing that.
So, whatcha think about my
custom stun rod, Blondie?
Well I think it's
pretty cool-
I wouldn't try to
get up or anything
cause it takes even
the biggest guys
at least an hour to
get over my attacks.
This rod comes in handy
when chicks try to get
too close to Loki...
Forget it ladies!
Whoa how'd you do that?
! It's impossible...!
No way...
You shouldn't
be able to move!
It'll take a lot more
than that to keep me down.
That brat got
me pretty good-
I shouldn't have
been so careless...
My outfit is
totally ruined.
If Grandpa finds out about
this he'll kill me...
I'll just have to
keep it a secret.
Now I've gotta find that
four-eyed turtle lookin' guy-
he's the only one who
knows where Niijima is.
And I've gotta
make dinner...
before anyone at home
notices I'm gone.
What the hell's going on? !
Hey, where's the
four-eyed turtle man...?
I mean, uh...
I know Loki was in there
with you- where'd he go? !
What...? Dumbass...!
Dontcha get it girl?
We were just the bait...
I'm sure Loki's safe and sound
back at headquarters by now.
You wanna tell
me which ship
I can find my
friend Niijima on?
I have no idea.
Tell meeeeeee...
I'm serious! I don't
know anything about your friend!
I'm tellin' ya the truth!
I swear!
You dummy! You're good
for nothing! I hate you!
Looks like the four eyed
turtle man is the only one
who knows where
Niijima is.
Now that Kenichi's
up against Sig
the Shinpaku Alliance
doesn't stand a chance.
Why aren't my attacks
doing anything?
I'll try again.
You bastard!
I feel your passion!
What the hell?
Damn it. He did it again...
I had him but he
turned it on me.
Let loose your anger.
La-la-
How unfortunate...
It would appear
that Niijima's ship
is about to leave port.
It's leaving?
I gotta hurry
and go save him!
Well, well...
You've got quite
a dilemma-
you'd better defeat me soon
or it'll be too late
for your friend.
Now get in touch with your
anger, your frustration.
And attack me
with all of it!
Don't get angry.
Listen up...
the person who's feelin'
the most pressure
is always the one that's
gonna lose the fight.
If you start gettin'
too wound up
then your opponent can see
every move you've got.
I know what you're
saying but I don't think
I could help but get wound up
in the excitement of a fight.
Well then if ya
can't calm down...
try changin' your pace.
In the middle of a fight?
One sake please!
Hellooo...?
So... as I was sayin'...
you just gotta
stay calm...
you can always throw in
some training exercises
or whatever'll help
keep you grounded.
You wanna change the
flow of the fight
so you can catch your
opponent off guard.
Then you can swallow him
whole, in one giant gulp!
Guess it's worth a shot.
Couldn't have asked for
better weather today!
One, two, three, four...
What should I have for
breakfast this morning?
Morning?
Alright, I'm
spoilin' for a fight!
I hope you're ready
for me, Siegfried!
Yes! So, what kind of attack
should I start out with?
Got him.
Hold on- I totally forgot
to finish warming up first!
Hey...! I didn't even
touch you that time
and you went flying...!
I knew there was
something up with you!
As a musician I can pick
up my opponent's rhythm.
I can see through their
attacks and dodge them-
pretending to be hit.
I combine the propulsion
of their attack
with my own to make
it more powerful.
I call it the
Round Attack!
The Round Attack...?
Don't you think that name's
a little unoriginal
and... weird?
Even though you know the
secret of the Round Attack
I'm afraid your moves will
still be useless against me.
So go ahead, come at me...
just remember...
the harder you hit me
the harder you'll fall.
I'm screwed.
He's gonna use my
power against me!
What'll I do now?
Dontcha think those two
shoulda been home by now...?
It's gettin'
kinda late...
What should we
do, Akisame?
You want Apachai to
go find the baddies
and kill them so that we
can have dinner now?
How bout no... thank you.
Patience...
We'll wait for
our disciple...
That's our responsibility
as masters.
What do you all think
of Kenichi's progress?
He's been training with
us for a while now
but he still seems
pretty slow.
Well, it's not as though
he had any real talent
to begin with.
There's nothing more we
can do at this point.
We've taught him
everything we can.
Now it's all up
to Kenichi...
He will progress if
he can learn to use
what we've taught
him in battle.
If I attack recklessly he'll
just counter me again...
He'll use the power of
my moves against me.
I've gotta try to keep him from
seeing through my attacks.
Here goes nothin'...
At attention!
What are you up to now?
Kenichi Shirahama,
permission to step forward...
Granted...!
One, two... One, two...
What's he doing?
One, two...
Now all men at attention!
Okay men, face forward...!
Prepare to attack!
First warm-up exercises
and now a military drill...?
I don't know what
you've got planned
but I can assure you that your
silly tricks won't work on me.
I know that he's gonna
dodge the brunt of my attack...
so if I'm gonna take
this guy down...
I'm gonna have to
try that punch!
I'm gonna have to use my
most powerful punch
even though I can't
always pull it off.
Good work.
Give me ten more reps and
I'll let you move on
to kenpo training
with Kensei.
I've got a
question, Akisame...
It's been bugging
me for a while .
What's on your mind?
I'm learning karate, Muay
Thai, kenpo, jujitsu...
That's a lot of different
martial arts at once-
wouldn't it be easier if I
concentrated on one at a time?
-You can handle it.
-Wha...?!
Is that all you're
gonna say...?!
If I could train in each
martial art separately
it'd be a lot easier.
When you came to
Ryozanpaku you said
you wanted to become a
master of martial arts...
You know that's not
going to be easy.
You must fall off the
cliff of training
into the world of masters.
GO!
No...! I don't wanna!
Fall...? But that's
so negative...
shouldn't I be climbing?
No because when you're
climbing you have the option
of giving up when
things get difficult...
You, on the other hand,
don't have that option.
We take this
very seriously...
we refuse to let
you just give up.
We'll do whatever it
takes to mold you
into a martial arts master-
even if it kills you!
Now listen
closely Kenichi.
We Chinese like
to mix things up.
That's how we're able
to come up with
new fighting styles
and techniques.
We then add those new
techniques to our repertoire-
to keep our enemies
on their toes.
That reminds me of
the wounded master
who set out to find
a healing salve
using seven different leaves
he would press
onto the injury.
Individually the leaves
had different benefits
but nothing quite
healed him completely.
Not until he combined
the seven leaves
and he created a healing
salve unlike any other!
At least that's
how the story goes.
I see...
We're not finished
training yet!
Hold on...! If I combine
all of the training
that I've received so
far what will I create?
A more powerful
punch? I wonder...
I'm not finished!
I'm gonna try it.
What's the matter?
Go ahead. Do your worst.
Let me guess,
you don't think
I can dodge your
punch at close range.
That may be true of another
fighter but not with me...
I'll use con Bravura.
In other words, I'll use my
brilliant technique and
pure, natural skill to evade
your gauche attacks with grace.
Kenichi!
I have to try it...!
Here we go!
Pay attention to what
happens with your other arm!
When you use a karate
punch it should feel like
your arms are connected
to a pulley behind you.
You got it, kid?
In kenpo you wanna
draw out your strength
but you also want your arms to
be more extended and relaxed.
Don't hold yourself
back- let your arms fly!
A Judo chop uses
the same physics
as a downward sword slash.
You're basically
challenging the balance
of a four sided object.
You use your body weight
to chop your opponent.
Kenichi...!
Muay Thai is not
only a fun sport...
There are many
soldiers back home
who have used it
on the battlefield
fighting for their lives...
Apachai's master told
him you must do punch
with all of your strength...!
Make your punch go
through your opponent!
I couldn't dodge it...!
He keeps punching!
How many beats are
in this one punch? !
I can't count the beats.
I can't find the rhythm...
No...
There is no rhythm!
That punch...
So you think he'll make
headway if he can use
what we've taught him
in battle, huh?
I guess that
does make sense-
he did have a great
punch that one time...
Look what I did...!
I broke the post...!
Did you see that master? !
That post is old and I
wouldn't be surprised
if it had a bad
case of dry rot.
Is that true, Sakaki?
It's time for his
kenpo training!
The poor kid thought
he was in trouble
for breaking
the equipment.
It sounds like he was
excited because
he was able to break
the post, Sakaki.
I didn't think
about it that way-
I shoulda
congratulated him.
Don't worry- it's not
like Kenichi's dead-
I'm sure he'll make it
through this fight-
so you can congratulate
him when he gets back.
That's enough...
Let's just wait a
little while longer...
How unprofessional.
Oh no Akisame- That last
bit of kanji is wrong!
What? ! It's wrong? !
What do you mean? !
-Where? !
-Just kidding.
You got me, Kensei.
Impossible.
No way!
That was quite an
excellent punch.
The way that you used
your center of gravity
to strengthen it like that...
I lost.
I can hear the music...
A beautiful melody!
Kenichi, that punch
was too powerful!
Why'd you do that? !
B-But you saw him, right?
That guy was totally
unphasaeble five seconds ago!
Thank goodness he's still
alive but that was close...
You could have
killed him, you know.
Seriously?
Never mind that-
leave him to me-
you've gotta get out here
and find Niijima
before the ship leaves!
You forgot to ask this
guy which one he's on
before you knocked him out
so I guess you'll just
have to search them all.
I totally forgot...!
And that's the reason
I fought Siegfried
in the first place!
I'm sorry! I'll go
look for him now!
Let the crew know
about the situation
so they can delay
their departure!
Niijima...
even though I think you're
a jerk and a bad friend...
hang in there...
I'm coming!
No... not a single ship...
Ha!
Nothing I can do now.
Goodbye Haruo Niijima!
Well, there's no way to
stop it once it's left port...
It's not like I have
anything to worry about-
I mean, the ship has plenty
to eat, plenty to drink-
I even found a
change of clothes!
Guess I got no choice
but to sit back
and enjoy the good life until
we make it back to shore again.
What's up, furry friend...?
Thanks for chewing through those
ropes and setting me free.
Go on, eat up!
Alrighty then...
Let's see what's
inside this box.
Ooh!
I found something I like!
This is awesome!
What's the matter, Johnny?
Quiet...!
I can hear something weird
movin' around in there-
come take a listen Andy.
What...? Shut up...
Man, that's the dumbest
thing I've heard...
There's nobody in there-
I think you're just
hearin' things.
Yeah...? Then why don't you
go in there and check it out?
Okay... I'll do it...
I can't believe you, man.
Holy crap!
Damn it! It's an alien!
I bet he's here to
kidnap the entire crew!
Loki...!
Terrible news!
Impossible!
How could he have
defeated Siegfried?
And that's not all...
Big boobed girl
kicked my butt.
Damn...! I can't wait to
get my hands on that punk.
He ruined the
perfect plan.
Oh...? I'm sorry, Loki...
Things not going your way?
Did you underestimate
your enemy...?
So who is this formidable
opponent of yours?
Kenichi Shirahama.
Huh? !
Kenichi Shirahama...?
Kenichi...
Don't tell me
it's him...
Oh, Apachai is sweepening...
Apa?
Ah-pa-pa!
I don't see anything
about a kidnapping.
Damn it... See...?
If we had gone with
them in the first place
this wouldn't
have happened!
Look at this...
It says an alien
hijacked a cargo ship
and terrorized it's crew...
It turned around
3 hours later...
I just love reading
about alien sightings!
I'm glad that you were able
to defeat your opponent
but it's unfortunate
that you were unable
to save your friend.
Hey...
I think we should
probably go ahead
and contact the police.
Jonathan told Apachai he
seed someone that looks like
Niijima on the
horizon this morning!
What?
Okay go ahead, Apachai...
ask your friend to show
us where Niijima is.
Okay Jonathan,
where is he?
The place you saw him
isn't anywhere on that map? !
Aa-pa!
But then that means...
Oh no...
I couldn't possibly
eat anymore...
thank you princess...
My head really hurts...!
I had a dream that I was
taking over a castle.
Wait...
Hold on...
Where am I?
Kenichi!
[Music]
Wait a second, pretty boy!
What do you want?
I hurt my leg so you have
to take me to the hospital.
Like, now! Got it?
I don't even know you.
Why would I do that?
You're just gonna leave
a pretty girl like me
out here on the street? !
That's so mean!
Don't you have a heart?!
I'm injured!
I could die out here!
Alright then, come on.
I knew you'd
change your mind.
Hey, wait a minute-
this isn't the hospital!
Where are you taking me?!
Put me down, ya big jerk!
Somebody help me!