[Music]
Seriously, does
anyone know
what the boss
was thinking?
If he hadn't stepped
in like that
I could've finished off
Kenichi Shirihama and Hermit
on the same freaking day!
I don't understand
the problem.
Oh have you heard...?
There's a rumor about
our favorite boss...
Looks like he's been doing
some martial arts training
with the Great Sage
Fists for some time.
And here we peons can't
even get ourselves
an audience with
the man on top.
Loki's correct...
The reason I joined Ragnarok
was for the opportunity
to train with the
Great Sage Fists...
And I've never so
much as seen his face.
Wouldja take it
down a notch, Thor?!
Who cares...? Heh...
The only reason I
joined this gang was
so I could figure out how to
use my sumo in real life...
Now I'm a better fighter
than I've ever been
and I figured it out
without anyone's help...!
I say who needs a teacher!
Hah... Oh sure,
if you're satisfied
beating on high school kids
and street trash then
you're doin' just fine.
You wanna fight me, Freya?
My pleasure...
Think you can take it?
Ah...! We're not supposed
to fight each other;
you know that.
Truth is, Berserker...
Sometimes I think that you're
better suited to be our leader.
Won't be much longer now.
The seeds have
been planted.
My deathblow, huh?
Hey Kenichi, I just
thought you should know
that you already
have a death blow...
but it seems like you haven't
figured that out, ya know?
Lately when I'm
in a fight,
I get so involved in it
I'm not thinking about
what moves I'm using-
so I don't even know what
she's talking about.
Shinpaku!
Oh no.
Sharpen up those salutes, men!
Straight arms...! And you!
Why aren't your feet
shoulder-width apart? !
Niijima! Why are you
making them do that?
Shinpaku!
You're drifting
up too high again.
You wanna keep
your arm down.
No! How'd they suck
you guys into this?
Shin...
Oh, hey, Kenichi...!
Check us out...!
We're lookin'
pretty sharp, huh?
Shinpaku!
Damn! I'm too late.
They've been infected.
Huh. Your deathblow. Sure...!
You used it that one
time, don't you remember?
I did? When?
You talking about
your Killer Combo?
Huh...? My what combo?
I've got in my
log right here. See...?
It's what I'm naming
the combination of moves
you used to school Loki at
the Matsue Lark that time.
A karate move
called Yamazuki...
followed by a Muay
Thai Kao Loi...
and then a Chinese
martial arts head butt...
You finished him off
with a judo move
called the Falling Tree.
I'm calling it
your Killer Combo.
Yeah, that's the one,
pretty impressive stuff...
a move that combines all
the different kinds
of martial arts training
you've learned...
I'd say it's a fitting
death blow for you, Kenichi.
A combination using
all the different
fighting techniques
I'm learning.
Oh! I almost forgot.
I have some information
that might be interesting
to you do-gooders.
There's a new hotspot
in town offering
underage gambling over
one-on-one combat.
They're betting on fights?
Apparently one of
the eight fists
and his followers
started it all.
The seventh fist, Thor...
He uses Sumo wrestling
moves in street fights.
It's rare for me to
get my hands on
such detailed information
about any of the Fists
whereabouts, Kenichi...
Very rare...
If I were you I
wouldn't waste it.
What, so you want me to
just attack them head-on?
Yes, exactly.
I'd watch my step if
I were you, buddy...
He's probably just using
you for his own gain again.
Well...? Is he right,
Niijima, are you using me?
-Yes.
-Of course.
You stupid alien parasite!
What...? This doesn't
change anything!
You wanna hit Ragnarok
where it hurts,
you're gonna have to face
one of the Fists sometime
and you know it!
You have to defeat the
ones the riff raff
are afraid of or
what's the point?
He's right...
I hate to fall in with
one of Niijima's
ridiculous plans again...
but Ragnarok's dangerous.
They have to be stopped!
No kidding.
You're finally taking
the fight to them, huh?
Good for you, kid.
It's about time.
Well... I haven't really
decided anything for sure...
I guess I just I don't
know how I feel about
instigating violence;
you know what I mean?
It's true that the art
of karate teaches us
not to instigate violence
without provocation...
but those jackasses
kidnapped your sister-
I say we call this
one a counterattack.
Yeah... it's just martial arts
are meant for self defense...
I'm not sure when using
my training on my enemies
first is justified.
I'm trying to have a
serious conversation here!
What's wrong with you? !
(ahh)... I'm sorry...
That's just a bit
nostalgic for us.
What do you mean?
Well...
this is a line all martial
artists must learn to negotiate.
I remember tiptoeing
around it myself
when I was about
this little.
Apachai also worry this way
from the moment he was born.
Don't worry about it...
It's just another
part of your training.
It's okay if you haven't
found the answer...
You just keep thinking about
it like you're doing now...
and one day, when the
answer comes to you,
it'll be your own.
They didn't really
answer my question--
they just shrugged me off.
I see what they
mean, though,
it's kind of a
personal question.
-It is?
-But...
just this once...
I think... you should
fight... 'Kay?
I should fight...?
Just like that.
You'll try your best not
to hurt anyone too badly,
of course, and to resolve
this all quickly...
But I'm sure you'll
be very honorable
about the whole thing.
I should fight...
but still be honorable...
Right.
Well look at that...
I don't know
what happened...
but I think you're ready.
Alright then...
let's go crash us a party.
Yeah!
Kick his ass!
That's where Thor
and his lackeys
gather their little
gentleman's club.
Other than a few
bloodthirsty bystanders,
almost everyone here is
a member of Ragnarok...
If we attack them head-on we'll
be lucky to come out alive.
Maybe not.
As part of my training,
my karate master taught me
how to win a fight when
you're heavily outnumbered.
Now sometimes the numbers
aren't gonna be in your favor...
When that happens, the
worst thing you can do is
lose your energy right
before you fight the boss.
So you fight the strongest
guy you can find,
right off the bat.
I can't even warm up,
I have to start with the
strongest guy? That's stupid.
I see...
So you wanna go mano a
mano with the boss, huh?
Yeah, but only if you
can come up with
a way to make it happen.
Come on, Niijima...
It's our only chance.
I guess I can
think of something.
Alright, listen up, boys...!
I want you to blend in
with the audience for now.
Not you two...! You'll
have to stay here
or someone'll recognize you.
I told you to stop
ordering me around!
Calm down...
Don't you know the real
heroes of the story
always show up at the last
minute to save the day?
Hold it! Who told you
about this place?
Actually, it was
Taichi Koga,
so I suggest you get
out of our way.
Koga the Kicker?
Man, I didn't know...!
Go on in, sorry!
Thank you! (Come on)
I almost forgot what
a good liar he is.
It's almost scary!
Hey Look! It's the
Shinpaku Alliance!
Uh oh...!
-That's bad.
-Great, Niijima!
How'd they know?
Matsui! You idiot!
What are you doing? !
Put it away!
Doesn't matter if
we're recognized now.
Dude...! You gotta
put the flag down now!
No! Never...!
I can't let this symbol of
justice touch the ground!
Where is the
Shinpaku Alliance?
He's here...! It's
him, Kenichi,
the Seventh Fist
of Ragnarok, Thor!
-That guy is huge.
-Watch out, Kenichi!
Just stop this pointless
violence, you delinquents!
Oh what manners...!
I'd have thought
Ragnarok members
would be much better
trained, such a pity...
The Shinpaku Alliance
comes all the way out here
to extend a direct
challenge to the Seventh Fist
and look
what happens...
His idiot gang ambushes
an innocent audience!
He's doing it!
He's manipulating them
just like we planned.
No they did not...!
If anything, you're the ones
who ambushed us...!
I was just inside mindin'
my own business.
Of course! And we're not
judging you for hiding!
It's completely
understandable.
Start laughing.
Oh look, the great big Sumo
wrestler's growling at us...!
Too bad... I guess that's
all he's gonna do.
Hey...! You
wanna fight me? !
Uh oh...! Now he's mad!
I'll take on any challenger
who's stupid enough
to get in my
way on purpose!
I held up my end
of the bargain...
Now he's all yours.
Yeah... Thanks, I think...
But I wish you'd warned
me your end of the bargain
was gonna make
him so angry.
Are you ready...? Come out
and face me, challenger!
I came here to make
a bet with you, Thor,
not just
looking for a fight!
Make a bet...?!
You're already gambling
with your life, loser!
Now listen up,
here's the deal...!
I don't care what
you want from me
if you manage to
win this fight...
But if I win there's only
one thing I want from you!
I want you to leave
the Ragnarok gang...
And stop fighting.
Laughter.
What's wrong, Thor,
are you scared of him?
-Shut up!
-And stop.
Alright, fine...
I accept your
ridiculous terms.
But I've got some
terms of my own!
Terms of his own?
That's not good.
We're losing momentum!
Hah...! So
let's hear them!
I accept!
You what? ! That's
terrible negotiation!
He just wrote this
guy a blank check!
Good... We'll
fight in the pit.
Don't you ruin my carefully
laid plans, big shot!
Thank you for everything
you've done, Niijima...
I couldn't have gotten this
far tonight without your help.
You couldn't have?
Listen, if his request
is that you give up
the Shinpaku Alliance
you're just gonna have
to find some way to
talk him out of it.
Wha...? Okay...
If that's the bet,
I'll lose on purpose.
Hey! Kenichi Shirihama...!
You coming?
Yeah... but how did
you know my name?
My friend Siegfried told
me to look out for a kid
in the Shinpaku
Alliance...
He said the kid's called
Kenichi Shirihama
and he's a small
guy with good eyes.
Thor, I'm going on a
journey of self discovery.
Siegfried?
He thought you were
worthy of fighting...
and Siegfried has
good eyes, too.
Shinpaku!
We fight in this four
sided metal arena...
and we don't stop
until one of us admits
his defeat or until one
of us cannot stand.
Prepare yourself...
Shirihama!
I--Wait!
Here I come!
Hey! Who said I was ready? !
Not many men can dodge a
blow from me like that.
Aren't you supposed to
explain your terms
to me before we fight?
Sure... If that's
what you want...
I only have one
demand here.
After I pound you
into the ground...
You're going to dedicate
yourself to remaking
the face of the Sumo
wrestling world!
I whaaa?
Siggy's one of the strongest
fighters I know...
If you could beat someone
as fierce as him...
I must have
you on my side!
Um... You want me to
practice Sumo?
No, I want you to
be one of the best!
Thanks for the meal!
But Kenichi... Why are you
leaving Ryouzanpaku? !
No...! Can't
let that happen!
Now! Let's do this thing!
You have no idea...
just how strong a Sumo
wrestler's body is
and how powerful
he can be!
Your puny fists have no
effect on me, little boy!
Bastard!
Underneath all the fat on my
body is a layer of muscle
like a suit of armor!
A Sumo fighter's hit
isn't like a punch-
-its force is spread out...
so we don't wear gloves
for protection...
Not like those scrawny
boxers who wrap their
fists up so no
one gets hurt!
Hey! Who're you
callin' scrawny? !
Easy there.
How do you like that?
This guy's a monster!
How about this? !
The strength of my leg muscles
is my ultimate weapon...
I've altered sumo moves
to account for them
and developed a new
fighting technique...
I call it Fighting Sumo...!
You like it?
No. Impossible!
I have to admit,
that really hurt!
No way...!
How can he still be able
to stand after that?
So let me just make
sure we're clear...
you meant what
you said...?
You swear you'll leave Ragnarok
if I beat you in this match,
fair and square?
I wouldn't hold your breath on
winning here tonight, kid...
But I will tell you
that a Sumo man
always keeps his promise.
Think about it.
Haven't you ever heard
of a Judge's Seppuku?
Yeah... I think so...
it's when... a judge...
makes a mistake.
You idiot!
Why do you think the judge
of the highest ranked
Sumo wrestling match has a
knife with him in the ring...?!
It's because he's sworn to
use it to commit seppuku
if he makes any error in
judgment during the fight!
Man that's an
extreme sport.
Sumo was never
meant to be a sport
you ignorant
little pipsqueak!
It's a martial art that
great men have dedicated
their lives to
just like... me!!
And someday... when I've
finished my training...
I'll show the world!!
My Fighting Sumo
technique will be taught
in every athletics class,
in every school...
There will be Sumo rings
in all the parks
for children to learn...
and they'll all hope
someday to master my craft!
The men considered
most handsome
will have Sumo
fighter's bodies!
Y'want my hot body?
My fighting technique
will rise above all other
martial arts as the most
sought after discipline
in the world!
This guy's ambitions are
even bigger than his body.
No joke, but I like what he
said about handsome big guys.
That's disgusting.
And that's why I
can't let you win.
I have a dream, too...
It's to put a
stop to Ragnarok!
You really don't get what
I've been saying at all,
do you Shirihama...?
That- won't- work!
You have to retreat...!
Don't let him catch you!
I see...! That's why
they're in the ring!
It doesn't matter how much
faster some one is-
-they can't get too far
away--all that counts is
how powerful
your attacks are!
Do you get it now?
รกThis is pointless...
There's no way you
can win against me
while we're playing
by my rules,
so why don't you
give up now?
Just accept your new place
training by my sideรก
And together we will usher
in the age of Sumo!
What should he do? He can't
attack and he can't evade.
I don't know.
With that metal ring he
can't foul himself out either,
how's he s'posed to get
outta this one alive?
You two really don't know
Kenichi at all, do you...?
Look closer.
I've seen Kenichi in a lot
of tough spots in his life,
and if he really wanted
to run away I'd know.
So this ring...
It's just like any other
Sumo ring, is that right?
Yeah, that's right...
so what's your point, kid?
Oooh. So you're gonna
fight me head on, are ya?
Should be interesting!
You know your punches
won't affect me--
I'm curious to see what
you have in mind.
Yamazuki...!
Kao Loi...!
Headbutt!
Yeeees...
He's doing it...! Hah!
Yeah, but something
isn't right, look!
And the Falling Treeee...
The Falling Tree is
a good maneuver
if your opponent is
about your size.
Or smaller...
But with such a big
difference between them...
That knee thing actually
hurt a little bit...
But just a little.
Now let go!
There.
Where did he find all
the power for that?
Why do you think I made him
the leader of the Shinpaku?
No way...!
That's impossible!
The Falling Tree!
Whoa!
Quick! Finish
these losers off
while they're still in the
shock of humiliation!
Don't do that!
Oh...
no... you won't!
Stop, all of you!
This is his victory...
He played by the rules...
And he beat me
fair and square.
But... you're just gonna
let him walk away?
A true Sumo fighter would
not dishonor his craft
by ignoring the
terms he agreed to
at the beginning
of the match.
No matter what the
outcome may be!
After all that talk
about Sumo honor
he can't very well
ignore his own rules,
now can he...?
That's his weakness.
Of course... Not everyone here
considers honor a weakness
like you, you
freak of nature.
I can't believe my Fighting
Sumo technique is dead...
That was my dream-
what do I do now?
What are you
talking about?
All I wanted from you if
you lost was a promise
that you'd quit
Ragnarok...
I don't remember asking
you to give up any dream.
I hope you keep developing
your new Sumo technique,
just like you planned...
I think it's a
amazing idea...
I wish you luck.
Well I'll be damned...
You are a pretty interesting
guy, aren't you?
I think we'll fight again
sometime without the ring!
Uh, yeah, I tell you what,
I'll think about it
when my internal
injuries finish healing!
You did it!
We knew you could
beat him, General!
Whoa, hold on.
Guys, I'm still
in a lot of pain!
ah...! Lemme
down, seriously!
ahh! I really don't
mind walking!!
Well, Shinpaku leader...
You have some pretty well
trained followers
for one of them to
fight like that.
Followers...?
tsk tsk...
Kenichi Shirihama's
no follower.
Just a bad friend.
A friend...
So that's it...
I knew there was something
different about this
Alliance of theirs, I
couldn't put my finger on...
The difference is,
they actually seem to like
the guy they're following.
Men! Take us
onward and upward,
to infinityyyyyy and beyond!
Owowowowowow!
Niijima! Get off!
I'm one big
bruise already!
[Music]
Hey! Kenichi, isn't that
Kisara from Ragnarok
over there by that alley?
Huh.
Yeah, I think it is...!
But what's she doing...?
She's kicking boxes...
there's a cat in that box!
And she's kicking it!
We have to go kill her.
Whaaaaat? Miu! Calm down.
Eaaasy!
Don't worry. I'm kidding.
I'll only rip out the
unnecessary organs.
I've never seen
you like this, Miu.
You're actually
kind of... scary!