(upbeat music)
(thunder roaring)
(men shouting)
(fighter panting)
(both grunting)
(thunder roars)
(thunder booms)
(fighters grunting)
(Ryu panting)
(thunder booms)
(both grunting)
(Sagat chuckles)
(Sagat yells)
(both grunting)
(Sagat pants)
(Ryu pants)
(thunder crackles)
(Sagat grunts)
(Sagat pants)
(thunder booms)
(Ryu pants)
(Sagat yells)
(Ryu yells)
(rock music)
(upbeat music)
(people chattering)
- [Reporter] Sir, what is your position on the homeless?
- Oh my goodness, what a crowd.
- Well, let's tackle one problem at a time.
- [Journalist] Minister, do you care to make a statement
on anti-corruption?
- No, sorry.
Thanks.
- [Reporter] Mr. Sellers, could we have a statement?
(crowd shouting)
- [Sellers] Huh?
(Cammy yells)
- [Guard] Get back, sir.
- [Cammy] Going somewhere, Mr. Sellers?
- [Sellers] What do you want?
(bones crunching)
- After her, come on. - Get her back.
- Give me some back-up. (Cammy yelling)
- Get the hell off me you...
- What the hell's going on? - Over here.
(Cammy yells)
- This timid little flower is Cammy White.
What we know is that she's a special agent attached to MI-6.
She's being interrogated at Base B.
However, she claims to have no memory
of the past three years.
- Which means?
- Which means, sir, she's being controlled somehow.
According to our data,
Shadowlaw is creating its own terrorists
by manipulating the victim's subconscious.
We're trying to figure out how that's being done.
- We do know that Shadowlaw
isn't selecting killing machines at random.
It's gathering information
on street fighters around the world.
We've had several reports on this.
- Street fighters turning terrorist?
- This walking mountain of muscle is called Sagat.
He's a champion Muay Thai fighter
and is considered a national hero in Thailand.
Contestant number two is Balrog,
whose penchant for violent behavior
got him permanently banned from boxing.
From Spain, we have Vega.
He's savage, ruthless, and a card-carrying psychopath.
- Bison has recruited these three mercenaries
to be special soldiers for Shadowlaw.
They're all extremely dangerous.
- [Officer] Hm.
- Each year, the crimes they commit grow bigger
and more brazen.
Shadowlaw must be crushed once and for all.
- We are going to plan a joint investigation
with the American military forces.
(jets roaring)
(engines whirring)
- Captain Guile.
Someone from Interpol is here to see you.
- For me, here?
Hm.
- I'm Chun-Li.
- Yeah, and?
- Oh.
Well, captain, we're here to discuss the joint Shadowlaw
investigation with you.
- Bison's ass is mine.
- Huh?
What do you mean, captain?
- [Guile] I don't need Interpol's
or anyone else's help to take him out.
- Hey, brush-head, this is not a request.
- You want Bison destroyed, don't ya?
So what's the problem?
- Uh.
(growls)
(plane whooshing)
(mystical music)
(engines whirring)
(ominous music)
- [Scientist] Of course, if you're...
Oh.
- I've been expecting you, sir.
- Is it ready?
- Yes.
A masterpiece of computer technology.
It's splendid.
We've created the ultimate high-performance monitor cyborg.
It's state of the art.
The images it receives are immediately beamed
via satellite to the supercomputer at headquarters.
They've been so successful,
we've already replaced our older,
obsolete surveillance robots with these superior models.
- Good.
(gears whirring)
And the man I'm looking for,
has there been any report of him?
- No, my lord, not yet.
- Any man strong enough to beat the crap out of Sagat
is a man I want found.
- I assure you, we're scouring the world for him
and other fighters as well.
But, sir, do you really think that this man Ryu
is as powerful as the computer analysis rates him?
(chuckles)
Even the highest-ranking martial arts specialists
average only 2,000.
It seems incomprehensible that he could rank over 3,000.
- I don't recall asking
for your inept opinion regarding this.
I expect you to employ every means necessary to find him.
Search everywhere, even if you have to fly a cyborg
into the depths of the Himalayas.
(pleasant music)
- Shoryuken.
- [Sensei] Ryu, what do you see in front of your fist?
(both grunting)
(Ken yells)
- Oh?
- [Sensei] Good.
That's enough for now.
You both deserve a rest.
Ryu, Ken, you boys go fetch some water from the valley
before breakfast, eh?
- [Both] Yes, sensei.
(Ryu sighs)
- Hey, girlfriend, why don't you throw more punches?
Might break a nail?
Wooga, wooga, wooga.
- Get off me.
What are you accusing me of, sluffing off?
- Just kidding.
Gosh, you're so sensitive.
(Ryu yells)
Hey, not bad if you're planning to fight old ladies.
We won't be training forever, you know?
The time will come when our lives will depend on this.
(wind howling)
(rock music)
- Oh.
- Sorry I'm late, honey.
- I was beginning to think that you'd forgot all about me.
- I was delayed by underestimating my opponent.
He was much better than I actually thought.
- And?
How did you do?
- I won.
- Oh.
I guess you can put another notch on your gun, cowboy.
- Uh-huh.
- Time is money.
Does he care?
Obviously not.
It's a little difficult to make the movie without the star.
- He knew when his call time was
but nobody's seen him since lunch.
- [Director] It's always something with that Fei Long.
He's an asshole.
- That idiot doesn't stand a chance.
Come on, kick his ass.
- Hey, Fei Long.
- Oh man, what's this?
- [Friend] Nothing, a little extra fun, that's all.
- Fun?
- Yeah, they're dragging some poor schmuck into the ring
who's dumb enough to shoot off his big mouth, you know?
- Hey, I didn't say anything.
- The fighters don't take smart-ass remarks
lightly around here, chicken.
- You can back up your words, can't ya?
- Eh, looks interesting.
- Maybe showbiz turned you into a big star
but this stuff brings you back, doesn't it, huh?
- Keep your eye on the new guy, he looks good.
- Huh?
(bones popping)
(both grunting)
- Not bad, or was it just luck?
Let's see how well you do against a fighter like me.
(upbeat music)
- Come on, double or nothing on Fei Long.
- There's been a shortage of new blood around here lately.
So, what's your name?
- I'm just passing through here.
Just a Japanese guy taking in a fight.
And Ryu is my name.
(Fei chuckles)
- [Crowd] Fei Long, Fei Long, Fei Long, Fei Long, Fei Long.
(Fei shouts)
(Ryu grunts)
(Fei howls)
- [Onlooker] That's great, kick-ass.
(both grunting)
(Fei yells)
(crowd shouts)
(both grunting)
- Send him home. - Finish him.
- No, we're not done yet.
You haven't seen anything.
Get ready.
Hm.
(grunts)
Shien Kick.
(howls)
- [Ryu] Tatsumaki Senpuu Kick.
(friend whimpers)
(pleasant music)
- That's it, now I remember who you are.
You're the guy who beat Sagat, the Muay Thai champ,
a few years ago.
I feel better about losing now.
But you disappeared.
Now, don't try to tell me it's a coincidence
and there's another Japanese fighter
roaming around named Ryu.
You know, I heard Sagat was hired as an attack dog
by the Shadowlaw organization.
- What's the Shadowlaw?
- You don't know?
- Nope.
- [Fei] It's a major organized crime syndicate
that trades in weapons and drugs worldwide.
They're involved in just about anything that's illegal.
- [Ryu] So, that's the path Sagat took.
(pleasant music)
- So long, see you again, my friend.
(wood creaking)
(electronic beeping)
- [Challenger] Dammit, Masters,
I came here to challenge you.
Fight me.
- You don't hear very well.
I won't take part in a street fight, I said, got it?
- [Challenger] It does not matter where a battle is waged.
- Oh, please.
(both grunting)
- So, just what are you trying
to prove here, Chief Running Mouth?
- You are known as a skilled fighter
and have won many titles in your time.
I seek glory and honor
by defeating a warrior such as yourself.
(yells)
- Well, that reason's completely lame.
And so are you for thinking you can beat me.
Nobody alive has been good enough to beat me yet.
Except Ryu.
- Ryu?
The vagabond who dropped off the earth.
You compare him to me?
(yells)
(both grunting)
- Watch out.
When you ask for something, you might get it.
(yells)
Shoryuken.
- Finish it.
You can't leave it like this.
(Ken sighs)
Huh?
- [Ken Voiceover] Ryu, where the hell are you?
We've got unfinished business.
(tires screeching)
(electronic music)
(baby crying)
(girl panting)
- Oh.
Are you okay?
Sorry, kiddo.
Huh.
I see, that milk was for your mother, wasn't it?
It's my fault.
Take this and buy your mom some more milk, okay?
Go ahead.
(girl giggles)
(Ryu chuckles)
(crowd yelling) (upbeat music)
(fighters grunting)
(bones popping)
- [Crowd] Yo, yo, yo, yo.
(fighters yelling)
- Rush him.
(rock music)
(Honda yells)
- Fight fair, Dhalsim.
(heart pounding)
- Kill, kill. - Hurry up and finish it off.
- Huh?
A power, but where?
Emanating from a man.
(electronic beeping)
(Honda yells)
You win.
- [Honda] Huh?
- I throw in the towel to you.
- What?
Don't you wanna lose with honor, you witch doctor?
- I can't fight.
I feel another power among us.
- Power?
What are you babbling about?
Are you trying to throw the fight?
- I don't care if you win.
The fight is over.
- [Crowd] Choke him, choke him, choke him.
- Bonehead.
I'll take my winnings now.
- Okay.
Have you ever felt the fighting spirit of another?
(upbeat music)
- [Girl] Hey, mister.
- Hey.
(girl giggling)
(man grunting) (crowd gasping)
Huh?
(guns firing)
(tires screeching)
(glass shatters)
(men grunting)
(tires squealing)
This poor little kid.
(sirens wailing)
Who the hell were those guys?
- They're Shadowlaw terrorists.
- Shadowlaw?
- There was change for you.
- [Ryu] Don't worry about it.
Everything will be okay.
(sirens wailing)
Huh?
(Honda chuckles)
- Hey, man, half this money is yours.
- Money?
- Cash, my man.
I might have lost the fight if you hadn't been around.
(chuckles)
Here, keep it.
Japanese fighters stick together, 'cause we're brothers.
(laughing)
(plane whooshes)
- [Bison] Are you certain Jahan was eliminated?
- Yes, it was confirmed by the monitor cyborg
who was on-hand to verify it.
He also sensed an unidentified fighter
and we're looking into that now.
- That's all?
- One more item.
Our cyborg in Seattle sent back an interesting video.
I think you might find it very enlightening.
- Ha, on my way.
(plane whooshes)
This call has interrupted me and I hope,
for your sake, that the information is worth it.
Speak.
- Sir, I assure you this will prove most valuable.
This man appears to be quite a remarkable fighter,
but we discovered something extraordinary
when we overlaid his picture on top of Ryu,
the one we're looking for.
- And who is he?
- Ken Masters.
We've compiled a computer dossier on him and his fights.
But nothing was mentioned of his relationship with Ryu.
- Is there a connection?
- We learned that both men, in Japan,
studied at the same dojo together for over 10 years.
Their fighting skills are considered equal.
- [Bison] Equal, eh?
But that doesn't mean
their fighting potentials are the same.
- We do not have enough current data
to substantiate Ryu's implied capabilities.
Either our sources have failed to obtain this data
or it's possible that he's withholding his full potential.
- I see.
From the same school now, is he?
Gentlemen, I believe we have found our new secret
P Project weapon in the form of Mr. Ken Masters.
- Fine choice.
As you know, our master, Ed Pressman,
may win the next presidential election.
His Brady Bill support exposes him
to the threat of assassination.
His security must be ensured.
And, of course, if we fail, Shadowlaw will have
to oppose the American government.
- Failure is not an option
once Masters submits to my Psycho Power.
- But, sir, I should remind you of Cammy.
(Bison grunts)
- [Bison] She carried out her mission, didn't she?
- She's at Interpol.
They have her for questioning.
- I don't give a shit.
If her job's finished, she's finished.
- On the subject, we've monitored portions
of Cammy's interrogation from Interpol's offices.
- Show me.
- [Chun-Li] Are you aware that you're a special agent
of Britain's MI-6 division?
- [Cammy] I don't remember.
- [Chun-Li] How can a trained agent
like yourself follow orders
from Shadowlaw to assassinate the Minister of Justice?
Did you know what you were doing?
- [Cammy] I don't remember.
- Cammy, your mind is being controlled.
I don't know how it's being done,
but we're trying to learn how.
You've got to help us out here.
Can you give me anything to work with?
Think, any kind of clue at all.
- [Cammy] I, I don't remember.
- Don't be concerned.
They won't be able to break my hold
on these mindless puppets.
- But, sir, there's so much at risk to allow her to live.
- All in due time.
But right now, I want you to continue searching for Ryu.
I don't care what it takes
and I don't want excuses, just find him.
- Yes, sir.
Do you want me to issue an order to our Northern U.S. agents
to apprehend Ken Masters?
- Hm.
Don't bother.
I haven't been hunting in a long time.
I'm getting out of practice.
- Huh?
(pleasant music)
Hey, get out of the way.
- You can't conduct an investigation by yourself.
- Hm.
Yeah, I've heard that before.
Now move your cute little butt before I run it over.
- Hm.
Go ahead.
(Guile grunts)
(tires screeching)
(Guile growls)
Guile, you're putting personal revenge
in front of common sense and duty to your country.
- I see when you're not being a royal pain in the ass
you're snooping around in other peoples' personal affairs.
- I don't mean to invade your privacy,
captain, but I have to read the files of everyone
who'll be involved in this assignment.
I'm truly sorry about your best friend,
but we have to put this situation beyond vengeance.
- And all your chatter won't bring Bison down either.
- Well then, are you man enough
to check out my other abilities?
- I don't have time for this.
Huh?
(Chun-Li grunts)
- I'd like Bison myself because he killed my father.
But first and foremost, I do my job here, Guile.
My duty as an agent comes before personal feelings.
Please, captain, we can't do this by ourselves.
We have to try and help each other.
- I can't stand women who jabber like parrots.
Well, are you getting in or not?
(Chun-Li chuckles)
- Dare I refuse that invitation?
(both grunting)
Why are we going to a disco?
Are we looking for a monitor cyborg?
- Nah, just a guy I heard of,
a pretty good fighter named Dee Jay.
(glass shattering)
(thugs yelling)
(Dee Jay laughing)
- If you boys can't appreciate my music
then you better haul your sorry asses outta here.
- Get up, come on.
(both grunting)
♪ Here we go
Yo.
Hey, man, no trouble, it's cool, okay?
♪ One, two
- Nice kick.
I'm Captain Guile, Air Force.
- You flying kinda low tonight.
If you want the USO, you in the wrong place.
Or are you looking for Dee Jay?
- I came with a warning.
Shadowlaw's after you.
- Yahoo.
They are some badass motherfuckers.
I am honored.
- I'm not joking.
You have no choice when they find you.
You either die or join them.
- Hey, ease up, man.
It's just my sense of humor.
Besides, what does Shadowlaw want with me?
- [Guile] They're searching the world collecting statistics
on fighters who can serve their purposes.
- [Dee Jay] Shit, they don't want me,
so this ain't my problem.
- Oh, yes it is.
This thing's transmitting information right under your nose.
(yells)
(electricity crackling)
- [Dee Jay] I'll be a son of a bitch, what the hell is that,
the Tin Man on steroids?
- It's a monitor cyborg.
It's one of the computer-controlled surveillance devices
that Shadowlaw's been using.
Dee Jay, you can help us
by putting the word out on the street.
These things are everywhere, so keep an eye out.
(ominous music)
- Well, well, Guile.
So, the boy scout is joining the game
by teaming up with Interpol.
This is getting more interesting by the minute.
Mm-hmm, speaking of interesting,
what do you think of this little number, Vega?
Why don't you go have some fun with Ms. Li?
I'm sure you can conjure something
from that dark imagination of yours.
(chuckles)
Lovely, isn't she?
(man screaming)
Ah, I can remember her father's unfortunate accident.
It's so sad, don't you think so, Vega?
Enough.
Get me Las Vegas, now.
- [Waitress] Your drink, sir.
(party-goers laughing)
- [Server] Enjoy.
- This is my partner, Mr. Biers.
(all laughing)
- [Balrog] It's a regular corruption convention.
Every crime boss from around the globe is here.
Hm?
No.
Don't worry.
I'll contact headquarters.
Yes, sir.
(throat clears)
- Do I need to tell you I've been getting
kind of a funny feeling lately?
Are you sure this deal's gonna go off without a hitch?
- You can just chill.
I made the preparations myself.
Did Coco 5000 get to London?
- It's all taken care of.
Oh, and would you tell the master
I'd like to speak with him later?
- Yes, of course.
- [Announcer] Ladies and gentlemen, your attention please.
Thank you for waiting.
Our evening's entertainment is about to begin
in the main loft.
Please take your seats and enjoy the show.
- Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the main event.
You're in store for some exceptional excitement tonight.
It's my pleasure to introduce the contenders.
The Iron Cossack of Steps, the Russian Czar of Wrestling,
Zangief.
(crowd applauds)
And his opponent this evening is a feral fiend
from the jungles of Brazil who hones his skills
by fighting man-eating predators, Blanka.
(Blanka roars)
(woman gasps)
(Blanka growls)
(rock music)
(both grunting)
(Blanka screams)
- Don't let that monster take you.
(Blanka yells)
- There you go, huh, what are you doing?
(Zangief growls)
(Balrog growls)
- What the hell are you waiting for?
Scalp him.
- Dump his freaking head in.
(both grunting)
(Zangief yells)
(ominous music)
(phone ringing)
- That's weird.
I thought she said she was going back to her apartment.
(phone ringing)
(door creaking)
(pleasant music)
(singing in foreign language)
Huh?
Shit.
This is just great.
(singing in foreign language)
(lampshade rattles)
(Chun-Li gasps)
(Chun-Li yells)
- Oh god, Vega.
- Come on.
Pick up the telephone.
What's she doing?
(phone ringing)
(Chun-Li grunting)
(singing in foreign language)
(Chun-Li yells)
♪ And you cry
♪ Tonight
♪ Don't you cry
♪ Good night
(Chun-Li screams)
- Huh?
Chun-Li, hang on.
(tires squealing)
(Vega chuckles)
- My hobby is to slowly peel the skin off the rabbits
I catch, especially cute little bunnies like you.
And my friend here is thirsty for blood.
Sweet.
(gasps)
(grunts)
- [Chun-Li] Spinning Bird Kick.
(both grunting)
(Vega whimpers)
- My beautiful face is ruined.
You bitch, I'll make you suffer.
(tires squealing)
(both grunting)
(Chun-Li grunting)
(Chun-Li gasps)
Huh?
(Chun-Li gasps) (Vega chuckles)
(Vega gasps)
(Chun-Li panting)
(Chun-Li growls)
(Vega screams)
(Guile grunts)
- [Guile] Chun-Li.
(pleasant music)
I'm here, kid.
Open your eyes.
Come on.
(sighs)
- It was Vega.
- What?
(gasps)
Chun-Li.
Hang in there.
Don't cash out on me now.
- And what's Ms. Li's condition?
That's unfortunate, she's one of our best investigators.
So, we'll have to rely heavily right now
on our own surveillance methods.
We've confirmed that a monitor cyborg
is near Ken Masters in Seattle.
Thank you.
Yes, he's very good, not just another street fighter,
he's the All-American Martial Arts Tournament champion
no less.
I have no doubts that Bison will try to approach him.
We've also discovered there was another fighter named Ryu
who studied with Masters at the same dojo.
We're investigating that now,
but our sources indicate that he traveled to Thailand
after leaving India.
- Keep on it.
I wanna know everything about this Ryu character.
The doctors said they're gonna work on Chun-Li right now.
If you need to reach me, I'll be here.
As soon as I know things are stable,
I'll catch the next flight to Seattle.
Also, have a dossier on Ken Masters ready for me.
(car engine thrumming)
- Eliza, let's get married.
- Huh?
What do you mean, right this minute?
- [Ken] Sure, why not?
- Well, this is out of the blue.
You know, I don't even think I've heard you
mention the word marriage before.
- [Ken] So then, let's do it.
- [Eliza] But...
- But what?
- Something doesn't feel right.
- [Ken] Whatever.
- Hey, don't be angry.
- I'm not.
(rock music)
(singing in foreign language)
(Ken panting)
(Ryu panting)
(Ryu grunts)
(Ken shouts)
- [Ken] Ryu.
(both chuckling)
- Ken.
(horn honking)
(tires screeching)
Well, maybe I should have said yes.
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Hey, we made it.
And your offer?
I'll consider it.
- Eliza.
- I love you.
Uh, call me later, okay?
- [Ken] Sure.
When I get back.
Ryu, I'm getting tired of waiting.
- [Pilot] Master, I've located the target.
- [Bison] Excellent, move in closer.
(plane roaring)
- Hm?
(tense music)
(tires screeching)
Are you crazy?
What is going on?
(ominous music)
- Greetings, Mr. Masters, I have come for you.
- [Ken] Excuse me, but who the hell are you?
- I am Bison, Shadowlaw's master.
- [Ken] Should I be impressed?
I never heard of ya.
What do you want?
- [Bison] I will turn you into the strongest fighter alive.
- Huh, Buffalo or whatever
you're called, you're full of crap.
- Don't you realize the potential
of becoming an even better fighter than Ryu?
- Huh, Ryu?
Just how do you know about him?
- Well now, it would appear I've touched a sensitive spot.
- Shut up.
I have had enough of this.
Hey.
Whoa.
I guess I'm in no position to bargain.
(yells)
Hey, what kind of a punch do you call that?
- [Bison] Your pathetic efforts are futile
against my Psycho Power.
- Psycho Power?
- Ken, you will follow my command.
There is no point in resisting.
- No way.
(grunting)
(shouting)
- [Bison] You have no choice.
You will obey me.
- On a cold day in hell.
- You foolish young man.
- [Ken] Hadouken.
(Bison chuckles)
- You disappoint me, Masters.
I'll fashion you into a real fighter.
- If you don't mind me asking, sir, what's so urgent
to bring you all the way out here to see Ken Masters?
- It's likely Bison is targeting him.
Is that his car?
- Yes, sir, no mistaking it.
- Dammit, we're too late.
- Shadowlaw has stationed monitor cyborgs
in every corner of the earth.
And other than warehouses they use for storing weapons
and narcotics, we haven't been able to find anything
that resembles their primary headquarters.
- It seems logical to me that Bison would take Masters
back to the same training facility
where he took the other fighters.
The big question is where is it?
- It seems their main bases of operation
are concentrated in Southeast Asia.
So, I suggest we focus our search in that area.
- Captain Guile, sir, talking about Southeast Asia,
we've located the fighter you're looking for, Ryu.
He's the one who trained with Ken Masters.
- So this is the guy who was in India.
Where is he?
- He was last seen at the Thailand-Laos border
and was reportedly heading into the hills there.
- Do you know if any monitor cyborgs
have been reported in his proximity?
- Yes, sir, we've detected several,
but I don't think they've found him yet.
Ryu doesn't sit still, he's constantly moving
through India, Thailand, and China.
His travel seems random and we don't know why he moves
around, so it doesn't seem likely a cyborg is tailing him.
- I'm sure the fact that Ryu is as good a fighter as Ken
hasn't escaped Bison's notice,
but so far, we have the advantage.
We've got to reach Ryu before Shadowlaw does
so we can plan a welcoming committee for Bison.
Also, what plans have been formulated by Interpol
and the American military for destroying Shadowlaw?
- Since we've already determined the locations
of their main bases, our tactical force teams have been
assembled and are secretly waiting the signal to raid.
The first attack will be the hardest,
focusing on the Shadowlaw headquarters
near the Cambodian border.
Interpol and the American forces have decided
that this is the best choice we have.
- I've got some good news.
I came to tell you that we found Bison's hideout.
I guess you'll chew me out for this,
but I'll get revenge for what he did to both of us.
I hate to see you like this.
I know it means as much to you as it does to me
to pull Bison's plug, kiddo.
Let me take care of it this time while you rest up.
I gotta go.
(mystical music)
(thunder crackles)
(Ryu grunting)
(electronic beeping)
(Ken grunting)
- [Bison Voiceover] Your passion to fight stems
from your competitiveness with Ryu.
(chuckles)
Just the quality I'm looking for.
With my Psycho Power, I will increase
and destroy that emotion many times over.
(Ken grunting)
(Ken yelling)
(Ryu grunting)
(pleasant music)
(both grunting)
- Hey, buddy, you all right?
- Oh yeah, I'm okay.
(Ken gasps)
- [Ken] There.
- Thank you, Ken.
So then, shall we?
En garde.
(Ken chuckles)
(Ryu grunting)
(helicopter whirring)
- [Pilot] Captain Guile, we'll be in the mountains
at the Laos border in a few minutes.
- Roger.
(rock music)
- Master Bison, we just received word
that Guile is aboard a military helicopter
now heading for the Thai-Laos border.
We believe he's discovered Ryu's location.
- How nice, he did the work for us.
(chuckles)
It seems the captain's trying to get there
before we reach him first.
We'll be there.
We'll take Ken and give him a nice, warm welcome.
- But, sir, Ken isn't quite ready yet.
- No choice.
I'll let Ryu and Ken fulfill their destinies
by staging the fight they've been longing for.
Make preparations to bring Ryu back with us.
- Yes, sir.
- Please, master, give me the chance
to prove myself against Ryu.
- Remember, you are a Shadowlaw warrior now, Sagat.
Put these commonplace thoughts aside.
- But, sir, we're talking
about fighter's pride and my reputation here.
- Fighter's pride, how dull.
The world is now your arena, not the street.
- My lord, please.
- Sagat, I'm losing patience.
My authority is absolute and I won't tolerate questioning.
I hope that's clear.
Besides, you have other orders to carry out.
You'll leave for New York at once to take care
of Cammy and Vega, if he's not dead already.
You'll soon learn that Shadowlaw does not forgive mistakes.
(wind howling)
(Ryu panting)
(Ryu grunting)
- Hey, I'm getting tired just watching ya.
Take a break and have a drink with me.
- Yeah.
(thunder roars)
- Uh-oh, looks like a storm's brewing.
Who's that?
(helicopter whirring)
We finally have visitors drop in
and look at me, I'm just a mess.
(Guile grunts)
- [Guile] Are you Ken Masters' friend, Ryu?
- That depends.
Who wants to know?
- Captain Guile, operative with United States Air Force.
- I'm Ryu, but what's this about Ken?
- Your friend's been abducted
by a crime organization called Shadowlaw.
- What do you mean abducted?
- And their ultimate plan is to turn him into a terrorist.
- That's ridiculous,
there's no way he could ever become a criminal.
- They're subjecting him to a form of mind control.
- Ken is not a terrorist.
(plane roars) (ominous music)
- Shit, Bison had me tailed.
- What the?
- Boy, a lot of visitors today.
(coughs)
He likes to make an entrance.
- Ken.
- Well, look what crawled out of the woodwork.
- Why, Captain Guile, it's been such a long time.
Finally, the stars of the show are all assembled onstage.
Take a bow.
- Stinking bastard, what have you done to Ken, huh?
- Well, well, well, Ryu.
I was looking for you.
But you're a difficult man to find,
so we recruited Ken in your absence.
(cackles)
- Let him go, now.
(gasps)
- Ryu.
- What have they done to you?
Ken.
- Nice job, huh?
Your friend is now the perfect exterminator
thanks to my subtle influence.
Beating him isn't going to be easy.
- No, don't.
Ken, resist it.
(Bison laughs)
- Save your energy, boy, you're going
to need all you can muster on the battlefield.
And your utter annihilation is the sole mission in his life.
- No way, he's my friend.
- Bison, I'll rip your fucking heart out,
you filthy bastard.
(Bison cackles)
- Afraid I don't have one.
You know, Guile, evil is a good career choice.
It has a lot to offer.
- Huh? - Hm?
- Here is a sample of my power.
- Oh god, I can't take it.
I gotta kill this nut before I kill myself.
(shouts)
(grunting)
Hi there, and you are?
- I'm the welcome wagon.
It's nice to meet you, friend.
- [Bison] Hello, captain, are you still planning
to give me the heart transplant you mentioned?
- Ready and waiting.
- Ken, don't you recognize me?
Ken.
(Ken grunts)
(Ryu grunts)
Stop it, it's me.
I'm your friend, dammit.
(both grunting)
- What's wrong, Guile?
Thinking about your friend I killed?
Try harder.
(Guile grunting)
- Sonic Boom!
Huh?
- You're mine.
(Guile screams)
(Balrog yells)
(Honda yells)
(both grunting)
- Huh? - Oh shit!
(thunder crackles)
(Guile groans)
(Bison chuckles)
- [Guile] Coward.
Don't walk away from me.
We're not finished.
(Ken yells)
(thunder roars)
- This is crazy.
Don't you realize someone else is making you fight me?
Don't you get it?
For God's sakes snap out of it.
(Ken yells)
(Ryu gasps)
(thunder roars)
(both grunting)
(Ken yells)
Ken.
(thunder rumbles)
- Huh?
Huh?
(yells)
(rock music)
(thunder rumbles)
Huh?
(Ryu panting)
(Ken screams)
(thunder rumbles)
- Ken.
(thunder roars)
Take a good, long look at me, dammit.
Come on, this is a real fight.
Tell me who I am.
- [Ken] Ryu.
- Yes.
(gasps)
- You worthless pile of excrement.
- Stop it!
(Ken screaming)
(Ken yells)
Ken!
You get the hell out of my way.
- Well now, aren't you the big He-Man?
Now is the opportunity to see just how good
your legendary fighting skills really are.
- Move or I'll go through ya.
- All I get is talk and no action.
You must not be too concerned about your friend
who's probably dead by now.
- I'll show you action.
Well, I'm leaving.
- Time sure flew by.
I'm heading outta here myself in a couple of days.
- Take care, hotshot.
- Next time, muscle man.
- I'll see ya when fate brings us together again.
(grunting)
(rock music)
Huh?
(Bison laughs)
- Here's my offer.
Give up this life of luxury
and join me as a Shadowlaw soldier.
Otherwise, I'll destroy you.
- There's no chance.
I'd gladly take death over slavery any day.
- Ha, very good, there's still plenty of fight left in you.
That's stamina.
- Get outta my way.
- You stupid fool.
- [Sensei] Are you going?
- Yes.
I hate to go now, but I must leave.
- [Sensei] Your training here has been but a step
in your preparation.
A time will come in your life when you will face an opponent
and to defeat him, you must go beyond victory.
- Beyond what?
Sensei, I don't understand what you mean.
Please explain it to me.
Sensei.
- [Bison] I'll explain it to you, boy.
(laughs)
(Ken screams)
- What the?
What the hell happened?
I can't remember.
(groans)
My legs, they won't move.
(Ryu grunts)
(Ryu grunting)
(Ken panting)
A plane.
(thunder roars)
That's it.
It's coming back to me.
I remember now.
It was Bison, he brought me here.
(Ryu screams) Huh?
Ryu.
I'll have your head.
(thunder roars)
Bison!
(grunting)
Ryu!
(Ryu yelling)
(Ken grunts)
Dammit.
(thunder roars)
Breathing.
Spirit.
Discipline.
(groans)
- [Ken Voiceover] Focus the mind.
Cleanse the soul.
Keep sight of my target.
Concentrate.
Focus.
Don't lose it now.
- [Ken And Sensei] Be prepared for the unexpected.
Concentrate.
Mind and body as one.
Achieve tranquility through movement.
Integrate spirit and flesh.
Channel the powers.
Focus the mind.
Cleanse the soul.
Release that which is negative.
- Separate darkness and light. - Mind and body as one.
- Give birth to yourself. - Oneness through knowledge.
- Define your existence. - Oneness through emotions.
- Create your divination. - Oneness with the heavens.
- [Both] From strength, learn gentleness.
Through gentleness, strength will prevail.
- [Sensei] Ken, what do you see beyond your fist?
Ken, awaken.
- Huh?
(wind howls)
(thunder roars)
My fate.
(Ryu grunting)
(thunder roars)
- What's wrong?
Getting tired?
Ha, shall I end it now?
(Ryu yelling)
(Bison cackling)
(triumphant music) Huh?
(Ken yells)
- Ken, you're all right.
- Hey, buddy, how ya been?
We'll catch up on the reunion stuff later.
We got something to do first.
Like taking out the trash.
- Yeah.
- You both seem bound and determined
to meet destruction at my hands.
So be it.
I'll fight you on your own level.
Come on.
(rock music) (Ken yelling)
(all grunting)
(singing in foreign language)
- Huh? - Huh?
(Bison cackles)
- Even though you two amuse me, I must conclude this game.
I have engagements to keep and I can't be late.
(Ken yelling)
(both grunting)
(Bison cackles)
(thunder roars)
(Ken yells)
One.
Two.
Three strikes, you're out.
(both grunting)
(thunder roars)
Little maggot.
No one has ever toppled me before.
I clearly underestimated this man.
- Bison.
(both grunting)
- Ken, do it now.
Shoryuken.
- [Ken] Let's finish this.
- [Ryu] Now.
- [Both] Hadouken.
(Bison screams)
(Ken gasps)
(explosions booming)
- Whoa.
All right, guys.
(helicopters whirring)
(explosions booming)
(phone ringing)
- [Guile] Hello?
- Captain Guile? - Yeah.
- [Caller] This is New York Central Hospital.
Would you please come in right away?
It's urgent.
- Chun-Li.
(tires squealing)
(horns honking)
(ominous music)
- [Driver] You asshole.
(tires squealing)
(Guile panting)
- Oh god, I'm too late.
Chun-Li.
You can rest in peace now, kiddo.
Bison is history, so we got our revenge
like I promised ya we would.
- Yeah, I know.
- Huh, huh?
- Joint Interpol American military mission
to destroy Shadowlaw victorious.
You did it. - Why, you little brat.
What a dirty trick. - Sorry.
- So you wanna play dead? (Chun-Li laughing)
I can arrange that.
- Ryu, next time around, we've got an old score to settle.
- Right.
(car horn honking)
- Hi.
- Do you want a ride?
- Rather walk.
- So, where are you going from here, Ryu?
- Don't know.
- You've gotten stronger, you know that?
- So have you.
- Ha, see ya.
(pleasant music)
- [Ryu] Huh?
(dramatic music)
(Bison laughs)
(Ryu yells)
(triumphant music)
♪ La la la
♪ La la la la la la la la
♪ La la la la la
♪ Hooray, hooray for the street fighter ♪
(singing in foreign language)