I beseech you, please
forgive my indiscretions!
Looks like someone
hasn't had enough!
Now get back to work!
[yells]
[GAKUTO yelps]
[screams]
Dumb ass!
How dare you pull a stunt
like that with the President?!
--[GAKUTO groans]
--[MEIKO growls]
[MEIKO]
Have some shame!
[MARI] Yes, well then. Madam
Vice President, I'm leaving.
Do you have the slightest idea
how much trouble you're
in right now, Freak?
You'd better say your prayers.
Ptui.
Madam President, please wait!
[ANDRE]
Are you okay?
[SHINGO]
Shit, how're you alive?
Damn, dude.
What were you thinking, going
thermo-nuclear like that?
It was a necessary evil.
This part is critical to
the new breakout plan.
[KIYOSHI gasps]
[SHINGO] So apparently, Gakuto
went to the Vice President
to make a formal apology.
I wonder...
What kind of working over does
she have in store for him?
[SHINGO] Sounds like
you wanna trade places.
That's what he likes. Kinky.
[MEIKO]
Ready for your punishment?
[GAKUTO]
Yes, ma'am.
I am fully prepared to
take what's coming to me.
--[electronic buzzing]
--[GAKUTO gasps]
[gasping continues]
[SHINGO ] Chugga-chugga,
chugga-chugga, choo-choo!
Chugga-chugga, chugga-chugga...
[KIYOSHI]
Gakuto's been gone a long time.
[BOYS gasp]
[KIYOSHI gasps]
Oh shit, bro! What
happened to you?
Well, yours truly felt bad
about his wild behavior.
So I asked the Vice President
to tonsure my scalp
with her clippers of justice.
[ANDRE]
Oh, so she didn't work you over?
[GAKUTO]
With this act of penance,
she's forgiven me
for today's misdeeds.
Wait, was shaving your head the
final clincher for our plan?
Yes, although indirectly.
Here, this bag holds
the key to your escape.
What, your hair?! Gross!
Ignorant swamp ape!
You will use it like this!
Stop! That's gross!
A wig? Gotcha...
Your disguise as a girl
would be dubious at best
if all you did was attire
yourself in the vestments.
That craziness today... You
wanted to provoke a reaction.
A shaved head is a
mere pittance to pay
for my Three Kingdoms figurines.
Assuming they're
limited edition.
[KIYOSHI sobs]
Thank you... Gakuto...
[GAKUTO] It is yet too
soon to weep, Sir Kiyoshi.
Save those tears to
rejoice in the afterglow
of a successful breakout.
Yeah. You're right.
We'll make it.
I swear.
[STUDENT 4K]
So how'd it smell?
[STUDENT 4A]
I need this dry cleaned, please.
Sure! Please write your
grade and name down here.
[GAKUTO]
Before the breakout,
we must procure a
girl's uniform for you.
Which necessitates you gaining
access to the laundry room.
I use the drainage channel
to get closer to the girls'
dorm and snag a uniform,
but the service door to
the laundry room is locked.
Meaning...
I'll have to sneak inside
while the guy from the
cleaning service is working.
[GAKUTO] This mission is
of the utmost importance.
May the fates smile
upon us this day!
Here we go.
[KIYOSHI] He's coming and
going non-freaking-stop.
I don't have enough time to
get into the laundry room.
[GAKUTO] Sir Kiyoshi, you
must act with great haste,
before he loads all of
the baskets into the van!
Unless, of course,
he has no plan
to actually get
inside the facility.
Oh no!
[GAKUTO]
Hey, you!
Yeah, you!
What the hell are you
looking at, Pops?
The hell?
Did you just call
me "Pops," weirdo?
[GAKUTO] You see anyone
else standing there?
You were staring at yours
truly's recently shorn head
--and laughing, weren't you?
--[CLEANER] What?
Why would I?
[GAKUTO]
Art thou calling me a liar?
Enough already, boy.
[GAKUTO] Come hither and say
it to my face, you big coward!
[CLEANER] I was already
coming over there, idiot!
[GAKUTO]
That's right! Come get some!
Continue walking
towards me, Chrome-Dome!
[CLEANER] How do you not
see me walking towards you?
♪ Yo! Time for you to learn that
your position's untenable. ♪
♪ Suckahs step to me, and
the battle's unwinnable. ♪
♪ Throwin' down against
Nerima's craftiest general. ♪
♪ Yo! Yo! Yo! Yo! Yeah! Yo! ♪
--♪ Word to your matriarch! ♪
--Hey, Eight-Mile!
I'm gettin' real
sick of your mouth,
you want me to shut it for you?
[GAKUTO]
♪ I'm the anachronistic MC. ♪
♪ Take another step and
I'll unleash the pee-pee! ♪
[KIYOSHI]
What do we have here?
These are the Vice
President's panties!
I'd recognize them anywhere!
[GAKUTO]
What's taking so long, Kiyoshi?
[KIYOSHI]
Any panties with this much...
[GAKUTO]
♪ Yo! Yo! To the Yo! ♪
♪ You a fake-ass MC!
Don't front on me! ♪
--♪ Word up! ♪
--[CLEANER growls]
--[GAKUTO rapping]
--Gakuto! What are you doing?!
--Unhand me, sir!
--Sorry, mister!
My friend's not
right in the head!
[CLEANER] Yeah, I'd clued
in on that already, Slick.
[SHINGO] What the hell's
gotten into you, bro?
You just got your
head shaved last night
for this kind of shit!
Piss off, Four-Eyes.
I still got work to do.
[SHINGO]
Stop freaking out!
What if the Vice
President sees you?
[CLEANER]
Unbelievable.
There's something wrong
with kids these days.
[GAKUTO]
Sir Kiyoshi, please hurry!
Yours truly can no longer
provide further mission support!
Now I can finally
get out of here.
[lock clicks]
[KIYOSHI]
Oh, no!
Hey, where'd Kiyoshi go?
[GAKUTO] You have to get
out of the truck, quickly!
[GAKUTO] If they catch you
outside school grounds,
then our breakout plan
will be a total bust!
Additionally
worth mentioning,
all of us will have our
sentences extended by a month,
with naught to show for it!
No! We're done for!
--[crash]
--[ALL gasp]
[CLEANER]
The hell was that?
Did I run over something?
[CLEANER]
Well that's just great.
I must've forgotten about it
when that kid
started yelling at me.
A laundry basket?
Sir Kiyoshi must have
set that up ahead of time!
[KIYOSHI chuckles]
You gave yours truly
quite the scare.
Yeah, that was too close.
No offense intended, but
your usage of the basket ploy
was cleverer than I expected.
None taken.
But I've gotta thank you.
Distracting the
cleaning guy really--
[KIYOSHI]
...really saved the day.
[GAKUTO] T'was mere
child's play, I assure you.
[BOTH laugh]
[MARI] If the events of
yesterday are any evidence...
It seems obvious
that the prisoners
have begun to rebel
against our authority.
Have you not been providing
sufficient supervision?
It seems the boys
have grown accustomed
to the harsh environment
of the prison.
Their will to live rivals
that of a cockroach.
[MARI] You're not here
to give me excuses.
--[CROW caws]
--[MEIKO gasps]
Yes! Y-You're right, ma'am.
Starting tomorrow, I would like
to reinforce the methods of
discipline I employ while
overseeing the prisoners.
I-Is that acceptable?
[MARI]
Yes, see that you do.
[CROW caws]
[MARI] If those degenerates
commit another scandalous act.
[MEIKO whimpers]
[screams]
Do I really need to
spell out what will happen
if you disappoint me again?
No, ma'am.
[ANDRE]
I'm really looking forward to
helping out with the
track meet tomorrow.
Might even be kind of fun!
[JOE coughs]
And chicks.
[GAKUTO]
The day has come.
By this time on the morrow,
the quadrennial limited edition
Guan Yu and Red Hare figurines
will be all mine!
I don't need any girl.
Not as long as I have
my collectables!
[CHIYO] Can't wait for
the match tomorrow.
I'm keeping my eye
on Big Bad Tanaka.
He's a real powerhouse!
[MAYUMI sighs]
Once he gets his left arm in,
he's pretty much unbeatable.
[MAYUMI sighs]
Are you even listening
to me, Mayumi?
Yeah...
--Unfortunately.
--[CHIYO whines]
[KIYOSHI]
Tomorrow's the big day.
When I face the greatest
challenge of my life.
I swear, I will
break out of here,
and then I'll have my
sumo date with Chiyo!
[bell rings]
[MEIKO]
On the gate!
[MEIKO] The track and field
regional meet takes place today.
Kiyoshi and Brown Thunder
will guard the bags,
while the rest of
you pull odd jobs.
[BOYS]
Yes, ma'am.
[SHINGO]
Check it out!
Here comes the buffet of fresh
talent from the other schools!
[ANDRE]
Imagine how great it would be
if you were the starting block
they were crouching over.
[JOE]
Bitches better hurry and change.
I just can't get enough
of the taut-bodied babeage!
[MEIKO] Who gave you
permission to speak?!
[GAKUTO]
While we have down time,
let's go over today's plan.
When the school bell
chimes at noon,
you'll grab the errand bag,
and yours truly's
specially made wig.
Then make for the toilet.
--Yeah...
--[STUDENT 4B] Excuse me!
Would you keep an eye
on my bag for me?
I acknowledge receipt of
your possessions, miss.
Everyone feel free to use
the complimentary bag check.
Okay. Here's mine, too. Thanks.
[STUDENT 4B] I wonder why
they were dressed like that?
[STUDENT 4C] I think the
guy who was talking funny
totally had a boner.
Okay. Time to continue
going through our checklist.
I have the portable
speaker right here.
[KIYOSHI]
Gross, dude. It's still warm.
You'll enter the lavatory,
set up the speaker unit,
clamber up and out
of the rear window,
travel through the drainage
channel to the refuse area.
Here, you'll don your disguise.
First, pop the wig on.
Next, it's time to change
into the girl's uniform
we stashed there.
And walk boldly
out the front gate.
Then you watch your sumo
matches and buy my figurines.
Afterward, you return on
the two o'clock train,
and all is well.
[KIYOSHI]
It's almost that time.
[MAYUMI]
Making a picnic lunch?
Well... lunch at least.
I thought it would be nice
to have something to eat while
we watched the sumo matches.
[MAYUMI]
Feeding an army?
He... is a boy. They like
to eat a lot, right?
A boy?
You mean you're
going with Kiyoshi?
Of course, lame brain.
I told you all of this.
Well, yeah, but that was before
the boys got caught
trying to peep.
He says they gave him
permission to leave.
Yeah, but it's still
a date with a boy.
Calm down. It's not as
big of a deal as all that.
Eating boxed
lunches in the shade
while looking at shapely
asses is the best.
Yeah.
[GAKUTO]
These last three weeks...
They seemed so long
and yet so short.
Right? Three weeks ago,
I never thought we'd
be such good friends,
but we make a good team.
Ultimately, I did it
all for my figurines.
[KIYOSHI]
Yeah, man. I know.
[bell chimes]
[KIYOSHI]
That's my cue.
It's all in your
hands now, Brother.
Sally forth to victory!
Here I go.
[BOYS groaning]
[KIYOSHI grunts]
[MEIKO]
What are you slacking off for,
--you rotten dingleberries?!
--[BOYS scream, groan]
[screaming continues]
--[BOYS crying]
--[MEIKO grunting]
[gasps] Hm...
[MEIKO]
Long, black hair?
Something about these
strands seems familiar.
[gasps] Filthy Four-eyes!
[KIYOSHI]
Damn, this is really hard
with the buttons
on the other side.
[gasps]
[KIYOSHI] Crapburgers!
There's nowhere for me to hide!
I'll just have to
finish getting dressed
and make for the front gate!
[grunts]
It's too small!
[KIYOSHI]
Come on!
Stupid jacket.
[gasps]
[KIYOSHI]
Now if I run down the other way
she'll see the rip in my jacket,
and will call out
to me for sure!
[whimpers]
Wonder what she's
doing back here?
Hm.
[KIYOSHI]
Okay... That was close!
[CHIYO] I'm starting to
feel a little bit nervous.
That's natural;
this is my first one.
[CHIYO]
Student sumo matches...
I'd have cold feet
if I had to go alone,
so I'm really glad Kiyoshi
said he'd come with me!
This will also be the
first time I've gone out
where it's just a boy and me.
That sounds like a date to me.
[CHIYO]
But it isn't a date!
We're just sumo spectators.
Thanks for making
me anxious, Mayumi!
I wonder if they've let
Kiyoshi out of prison yet.
Here goes.
So close.
I'll see you soon, Chiyo!
So should I just cut
through right here?
If anyone sees...
[STUDENT 4D]
A boy!
[KIYOSHI]
I'll zoom past Gakuto
as pervy freak
numero uno in school!
No, don't lose your nerve!
I can do this!
I am a girl!
The finest girl at
Hachimitsu Academy,
walking home...
Just a little further.
And then sweet freedom is mine!
Hold it, stop where you are.
Out with it.
Why do you think it's
okay to dress like that?
You shouldn't wear
this bag on your back.
It's most unbecoming.
[KIYOSHI]
The bag?
So then, she doesn't
realize who I am?
[MARI gasps]
[MARI]
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
You were trying to hide the fact
that the back of
your jacket was torn.
If I embarrassed you,
please accept my apologies.
Go ahead.
[KIYOSHI]
I did it...
I freakin' did it!
[KIYOSHI]
Flawless Victory!
Just sit right back,
Chiyo, baby.
I'll be there soon!
[MEIKO]
Hey, Fudge-Bomb.
Are you keeping an eye on
the ladies' belongings?
Yes! As a gentleman should--
[groans]
Kiyoshi should be with you.
Where is he?
Sir Kiyoshi is indisposed
in the lavatory.
It seems his piles
are flaring up again.
Goodness, what are we
to do with the lad?
[laughs nervously]
Bitch, please.
[GAKUTO]
Yes, ma'am?
[MEIKO] What is the
meaning of this exposure?
[GAKUTO gasps]
I'm heartily sorry! Such a
lapse for a true gentleman!
--[MEIKO grunts]
--[GAKUTO yelps]
So it's not just your
bunghole that's loose,
now your fly won't even stay up?
The guy who talks funny had
a boner when he took my bag!
Did he seriously poop his pants?
That's gross!
[panting]
Eh?
[CHIYO]
Hey, there!
[KIYOSHI]
Chiyo! Hi!
You look nice.
Sorry I'm a bit late.
I just got here, too.
You're sweaty. Do you feel okay?
[KIYOSHI] Oh. I ran here
from the train station.
Here you go.
[KIYOSHI]
Seriously?
For sure.
I brought it just
for you, after all.
That's really rad of you!
[KIYOSHI sighs]
It smells so good!
[CHIYO]
Let's hurry inside!
They've started!
[KIYOSHI]
Yeah, let's go!
Sumo dates rule!
There might be a future
championship contender
among the wrestlers here.
Talk about excitement!
You're right. It's incredible!
[KIYOSHI] Honestly,
I'm not even interested.
On the other hand,
watching Chiyo's face light
up is cooler than cool!
Oh, yeah! Have you
eaten yet, Kiyoshi?
Huh? Eaten?
[KIYOSHI]
Yeah, right before busting out.
Well... I made us some
lunch if you're hungry.
I haven't eaten.
I'd love some lunch.
[CHIYO giggles]
That makes me glad!
Don't be shy, help yourself!
[KIYOSHI]
Just onigiri?
Nice! Looks tasty!
I have tea, as well.
[KIYOSHI] Hey, they're onigiri
that Chiyo made for us.
That's why I could
eat a ton of 'em.
Whether they're plum
or salmon or whatever!
Thanks for the food!
Delicious, even with
just a... little... salt!
[CHIYO]
Oh, good!
I made all of them
lightly salted!
[KIYOSHI]
Nothing but carbohydrates?
[MEIKO]
Is Kiyoshi still in the john?
Indeed, he is, ma'am--
Hemorrhoids or not, he's been
gone from his post for too long.
[GAKUTO]
You're right.
I, myself, warned him of
the same, just moments ago.
I shall go convey to him
Madam's displeasure.
[MEIKO] No need.
I'll go warn him myself.
Uh...
[MEIKO]
Kiyoshi!
Keep your bathroom breaks
to a bare minimum!
[MEIKO]
Answer me!
When I ask you a question,
you'd better respond, Worm.
[wet farts]
How dare he answer
me by crapping?!
[GAKUTO] Sir Kiyoshi
requires considerable time
to move his infirm bowels.
Shut up! You're not
to leave your post!
[sobbing]
[chuckles]
I can't believe we actually
managed to make it work!
My incontinence issue...
There was purpose to my
pants pooping after all!
[STUDENT 4H] The kid who
talks funny got smacked,
and now he's laughing.
[STUDENT 4I]
That nerd is such a creep.
They all look so big and strong.
Huh?
Ah!
Kiyoshi, hold that pose!
--Let me take a picture of you!
--[camera clicks]
There's rice stuck to your
cheek and on your nose!
It's perfectly adorable!
Oh, I've got to get in on this.
[KIYOSHI whimpers]
She's close.
She's right next to me,
and she smells wonderful!
Aah, it's like we're
boyfriend and girlfriend!
Watch out Jay-Oncé.
--Here's Chiyoshi!
--[camera clicks]
[stomach rumbles]
Excuse me, Chiyo.
I need the restroom.
Mm! Sure, go ahead.
[CHIYO sighs]
Oh, no! If his phone or
something is in there,
I may have just ruined it!
[gasps]
This is going well.
I hope she sends me that
picture of us together.
Her face was like
right next to mine.
Maybe we could even
start holding hands
when I get back to her!
But why would...
[KIYOSHI]
Wow!
There was a student sumo
wrestler in the bathroom also!
Seeing him up close,
that dude is huge!
Hm?
I can't...
Uh?
You disgust me.
[KIYOSHI gasps]
I disgust you?
What, for going to the toilet?
[squelch]
[gasps]
[KIYOSHI gasping]
[CHIYO] You disgust me!
You disgust me! You disgust me!
You disgust me!
One hour left...
I wonder if Sir Kiyoshi
has already procured
my limited edition figurines.
[SHINGO]
Being a baggage clerk
looks like a total
cakewalk, bro.
[GAKUTO]
Shingo, if you'll recall,
it was you who opted for
miscellaneous duties.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Say, where's Kiyoshi at?
I haven't seen him in a while.
Sir Kiyoshi is indisposed
in the lavatory.
His piles seem to worsen
--with each passing day.
--Nah...
Bet he's just takin' it easy.
I'll go have a chat.
[gasps] Speaking to someone
using the facilities
is the epitome of
impolite behavior--
[MEIKO yells]
What are you fart-huffers doing?
I think Kiyoshi's slacking off
on the clock, ma'am!
As I've told you before,
he's voiding his bowels!
Hey! Kiyoshi!
Come out immediately!
I haven't seen you at your
post since before noon!
If you're refusing to come out,
then I'll have to go in.
[CHAIRMAN] The boys' release
date is coming up soon.
Next week, in fact.
Right?
That's up to them.
But those five degenerates
are perverted fools.
Once they're freed from prison,
they'll surely do something
to be put back in.
[CHAIRMAN]
Don't say that.
They've endured the
Underground Student Council's
strict mentoring regimen.
Even animals can learn
from their mistakes.
Agreed?
[phones ring, vibrate]
[BOTH]
Pardon me, I have a text.
[MEIKO]
I won't ask you again, Kiyoshi.
Step out of that
stall immediately.
[GAKUTO gulps]
This is no time for pocket
pool, Filthy Four Eyes!
[GAKUTO]
I have an itch!
[MEIKO]
So both your ass and your
--toolbox are filthy?!
--[GAKUTO] What this?!
When needed most, my defecation
sound refuses to play?
[MEIKO]
Still nothing, huh?
Well... in that case...
I'll just do... this!
[KIYOSHI]
Next time on Prison School:
"The School's Number One
Most Treacherous Man"