So what am I gonna do?
I didn't have enough
heads-up to make any plans.
I know.
I'll take care of that
errand for the VP first.
Buy me some root beer
and kaki peanuts
from the store in front
of the train station.
[SHINGO]
After that, guess I can
kill some time at the arcade.
[GAKUTO]
General Guan Yu,
your commanding presence
counters my inner weakness.
For I have reaped the
rewards of what I'd sown,
yet abandoned my brother-in-arms
to shoulder the blame
for the breakout alone!
The shame!
Such ignoble cowardice!
No, worse than cowardice.
More like treason!
I don't want to be a traitor!
Lord Guan Yu, how can
yours truly put things right?
What do I do?
[game characters grunt]
[SHINGO]
Shit-snacks!
[ANNOUNCER]
KO!
[SHINGO sighs]
[SHINGO]
Guess I'll go back.
Though there's still time...
--[ANZU] Giving up already?
--[SHINGO gasps]
Pretty sad performance.
I've been way too busy to play
the last couple weeks, so
I kinda got a little rusty.
Uh-huh. Is that one of
our school's uniforms?
Wait, you go to Hachimitsu High?
[SHINGO]
She seems a helluva lot cooler
than the rest of
those stuck-up chicks.
So what exactly are you
doing here at the arcade?
I thought all of the boys
were supposed to be stuck
in the school's prison.
[SHINGO] I was asked to
run a couple errands,
not that it's any
of your business.
[ANZU] Whoa! Pump the
brakes, Arthur Fonzarelli!
Have you got a
stick up your ass?
Or is that your pathetic attempt
at talking to an older girl?
[SHINGO gasps]
You're uh...
What?
[ANZU] You all right?
Your face is turning red.
[SHINGO]
No, it's not!
Take it easy there, Tiger.
It's natural to get a little
excited by cleavage.
Nah! I wasn't lookin'!
Anzu! It's photo booth time!
[ANZU]
Just a sec!
I'll take you on
any day of the week.
Guess whose name
is number one?
--[SHINGO grunts]
--[ANZU] See you around, Slick.
[SHINGO] I haven't talked
to a girl that much without
getting smacked
since I enrolled.
Or ever, really.
I wonder if she's
always at the arcade.
[door creaks]
[MEIKO] So, did you
enjoy your time outside?
[SHINGO]
Very much, thank you, ma'am.
But the time seemed
to really fly by.
[MEIKO] Did you purchase
what I requested?
[SHINGO]
Yes. It's in the fridge.
[MEIKO]
Huh...
[SHINGO]
So, uh...
Is there a chance, maybe I
could be allowed out again?
[MEIKO] That depends entirely
on your performance.
[MEIKO gasps, coughs]
Damn it!
--Ass hat!
--Sorry! I was running
to get back in time!
For the record,
root beer's carbonated!
Stop gawking!
--And get back to work!
--[SHINGO] Yes, ma'am!
[SHINGO] Getting out of here
depends on my performance?
But nothing's really
been happening
that's worth reporting.
[SHINGO]
Hm?What's that?
Where did you come from?
[crackling]
Stop.
That should be sufficient.
[SHINGO] So why did you want
me to crush these kaki peanuts?
Watch and learn, Einstein.
[SHINGO]
Chicken breasts?
You mean--
No way!
[MEIKO]
Agh!
Fryer grease is dangerous!
You should put an apron on!
[MEIKO] The kaki-peanut
breading acts like a barrier,
sealing in the
marinade's flavor,
and prevents the chicken
from getting dry.
It also provides for
a succulent crunch.
Looks like it tastes good.
It does.
--[yelps]
--[SHINGO] It's too hot
straight out of the fryer! You
gotta let it cool down first!
[blows]
Now then...
Have you found any tasty tidbits
that I might like to hear?
Oh, right.
--Well, uh... Not much.
--Too bad.
Looks like you won't
get to try any.
[SHINGO]
Aw, man.
Come on, brain. I need ya.
[gasps]
Oh yeah!
What the hell is this?
[SHINGO]
That?
It's, uh...
I honestly don't know.
I found it on the floor of
the restroom by the field.
[MEIKO grunts]
Don't make me touch something
that was on the floor of
a restroom, Jackwad!
[SHINGO]
I'm sorry, ma'am!
[MEIKO]
Now you're sure as hell
not going to get to
try some of my chicken!
[GAKUTO]
Damnation! It's gone!
Whither is the mighty tip of
the Green Dragon Crescent Blade?
The majestically
symbolic embodiment
of Guan Yu's unmatched
warrior spirit!
Where are you?
I should have been more careful
when gazing upon it earlier.
That's not how you use
a toilet, Pants-Crapper.
[GAKUTO]
Oh! Uh...
I was just picking
up my glasses.
You see, I dropped them, and--
I don't give a flying
fuck, Shit-Nuts.
Now back to work before
I rock your face.
Help yourselves.
I hope you like my popcorn tea.
And to complement
the popcorn tea,
I've provided kaki
peanuts as today's snack.
This flavor...
Crispy rice crackers
in a spicy soy glaze...
Tsuruta brand, correct?
Madam President, your
discerning palate humbles me.
All it takes is
time and dedication.
Though money is helpful as well.
Oh! I forgot to mention it, but
I caught that "yours truly" guy
crawling around the restroom.
[MEIKO] Ugh! He was probably
just crapping his pants again.
If you don't mind,
I'd prefer you not use such
crass language during teatime.
[MEIKO gasps]
Forgive me, Madam President.
[cracking]
[MARI gasps]
This isn't a rice cracker.
[gasps]
[MARI]
Do you know what it is?
[MEIKO]
No...
[MEIKO] That's the toy
Shingo said he found
on the floor of the restroom!
But I can't let her
ever know about that!
It looks like a falchion blade.
[HANA]
A falchion blade?
A curved sword.
This one is a Chinese design.
--It appears to be a miniature.
--[HANA] Huh?
Why was it mixed in with
a bag of kaki peanuts?
You should file a claim!
[MEIKO]
A Chinese sword miniature?
A Chinese sword.
Falchion blade.
Miniature.
Brown Thunder, crawling
around the restroom floor,
--looking for something.
--[rustling]
[chuckles]
I can go out again?
That's right. You even
get an extra hour.
[SHINGO]
I appreciate that a lot,
but... did I even do anything?
You've done a better job than
anyone would have guessed.
[chuckles]
[ANDRE, JOE laughing]
Where's Gakuto?
He said he didn't feel
like coming outside.
[JOE] He's seemed
really depressed lately,
don't you think?
Did something happen?
[ANDRE]
He won't even answer back
if you ask him something.
[GAKUTO]
Whither hast thou gone,
Green Dragon Crescent Blade?
[MARI] Hard to believe.
The toy sword I put in my mouth,
thinking it was simply
a rice cracker...
...ends up being the rope
that they'll hang from.
I'll let you take
it from here, Meiko.
At your service, Madam.
One thing.
Where on campus did you find it?
It was in the rest-- [gasps]
The rest?
[MEIKO] I-I mean--
It was in with the rest of
the prisoner's
miscellaneous items.
I must've dropped
it into the bowl
when looking over what
Shingo had brought me.
[MARI]
Ah, well. Accidents happen.
Quite the useful spy
you have there.
[MEIKO]
Right as always, Madam.
[MEIKO] I have to carry this
secret to the grave with me!
[game characters grunting]
[SHINGO]
Guess she's not here today.
[game character yells]
[ANZU]
Stop spacing out, Nimrod!
She's beating the
crap out of you.
Come on. Keep your
head in the game!
--[game character yells]
--[ANNOUNCER] KO!
Well, damn...
You really suck
at this, don't you?
[SHINGO]
She's so close!
And her boobs are totally
pressing into me!
[ANZU]
So...
Did you get to come out
today for another errand run?
[SHINGO]
Yeah.
I've gotta buy some
root beer after this.
Well, don't go to
the arcade first!
Moron!
[SHINGO]
Oh, shut up!
It doesn't matter either way.
Well then, let's go!
Huh?
I've got some time.
I'll run your errand with you!
[ANZU]
Here you go.
My treat, 'kay?
Uh, thanks.
It seems to me that the
Underground Student Council
must really trust you if they
let you roam around like this.
I am a model prisoner.
[ANZU] That's funny. You don't
look like a model prisoner.
If you ask me, you look
more like a hipster.
Yeah, well.
You know what?
The same can be said about you.
[giggles] I get that a lot.
[gasps]
Hey, dude, let
me have a bite.
Here you go. You can have some
of mine, if you want a taste.
Do you like lemon?
Oh, wow!
That chocolate is
really freakin' rich!
[SHINGO] Man, she's going to
town on that thing!
It's not going to get weird
if I lick the ice cream
she was licking, right?
[SHINGO] She's not gonna be
like, "Eww!" or anything--
[ANZU] I almost forgot!
I have a couple of
free movie tickets.
[SHINGO]
Wait, "The Grapes of Wrath"?
Sounds kinda freaky.
What, do giant mutant
grapes go on a rampage
in a small Midwest town?
[ANZU]
Ah, like a B-grade horror flick?
That sounds cool.
I got 'em for free; I don't
really know what it's about.
So... Wanna go watch it now?
I'd really like to,
but I can't today.
[ANZU] Man... You're
making things difficult.
Sorry.
I wish I could though, for real.
[ANZU growls]
[ANZU]
Here, hold this for a second.
Oh, sure.
[ANZU]
You're a model prisoner, right?
Then you should get out again.
These movie tickets are
good through next week.
Yeah, but I don't know
when I'll get out again.
[ANZU] When the time comes
and you know you'll be let out,
put this hairband on the prison
fence during your lunch break.
Then we'll meet up at the
arcade.
Don't lose it,
Mister Model Prisoner.
All right.
You'll now take a
five minute break!
But first, line up!
Since you've all been doing
such good work recently,
the President has
a reward for you.
Be grateful.
Next! Hold out your hand.
[gasps] Just one piece?
You got a problem with that?
[KIYOSHI]
No! Thank you very much.
[MEIKO]
You get one too, Scat-Stain.
Much obliged, milady.
[gasps]
Oh, my mistake.
It's supposed to go with this!
Isn't that right,
Chocolate Trousers?
[GAKUTO] I've never seen
that before in my life.
[MEIKO] You mean you
don't recognize him?
I thought you were a
big fan of Guan Yu,
hero of the Three Kingdoms.
Ha, ha! Indeed, yours
truly is a fan of Guan Yu,
but I think figurines are dumb.
[MEIKO]
You don't say.
Kiyoshi, does this
belong to you?
[KIYOSHI]
No, ma'am. It doesn't.
I see, So neither of you
know where this came from?
Seems to be the logical answer.
[MEIKO]
I refuse to believe that!
I did the research,
Knuckle-Knob,
and this figurine is
a limited edition,
which could only
have been acquired
in Akiba on Saturday,
May the 7th,
the day Kiyoshi broke out!
Which means you had Kiyoshi
get this figurine for you
in exchange for
providing assistance
--with his escape, right?
--[ANDRE] If Gakuto helped
Kiyoshi escape, that's
bad for all of us.
[MEIKO]
You helped him out because
you needed to add Guan
Yu to your collection.
I'll make a deal with you.
just admit that you were
hiding this figurine
in the field restroom,
and you can have it back.
[GAKUTO gasps]
[KIYOSHI]
Hang in there, Gakuto!
If you admit that it belongs to
you, then you're also admitting
that you helped me out
with the prison break!
If that happens,
everybody's sentences
will be extended again!
Come to think of it,
Guan Yu also came with
a lovely horse figurine.
Let's see.
I loved horses growing up.
Think I'll go for a little ride.
[BOTH gasp]
[MEIKO]
My, what a comfortable saddle.
Giddy-up. Giddy-up.
[KIYOSHI]
Damn you!
Don't you know what
Gakuto had to go through
--to get that?
--[MEIKO] Giddy-up. Giddy-up!
[KIYOSHI] He sacrificed
his adolescence.
It's a quadrennial
limited edition!
Add in another three years
of high school bullying,
that's seven years of his
life tied up in that model!
--And now...
--[MEIKO] What's wrong?
You're sweating like
a whore in church.
I know! I'll ride
double with Guan Yu!
[ALL]
Double?!
[MEIKO sighs]
--[MEIKO] Whoa! Whoa!
--[KIYOSHI] If she keeps
doing that, his Guan
Yu's gonna break!
[GAKUTO gasps]
[GROUP laughs]
Now, my friend! We drink!
Indeed!
[LIU BEI] Let us as
brothers swear to aid those
who are in distress!
[ZHANG FEI] While we may not
have been born on the same day,
[ALL]
we shall die on the same day!
[laughs]
[GAKUTO]
All for one, and one for all!
[MEIKO]
Hyah! Hyah! Giddy-up!
--Thatta boy. Giddy-up!
--[KIYOSHI] Gakuto! Do it!
Confess that he's your figurine!
Hyah, hyah!
[KIYOSHI]
If you don't do it, I will!
[GAKUTO yells]
[KIYOSHI]
Don't worry, Gakuto.
I understand.
Is he guilty? I'm confused.
[coughs]
[MEIKO]
Madam President.
As you can see, his
desire to save the figure
is proof of his complicity.
So it would seem.
[MEIKO]
Which as you know,
only serves to compound
their prior crime--
[gasps]
What do you think you're doing?!
[inhales]
As you were told before...
Yours truly has no interest
at all in such silly toys.
Our break time has
now come to an end.
If you'll excuse me, I'd
like to head back to work.
I'll take a cracker,
as I was promised.
[KIYOSHI]
You didn't have to.
[GAKUTO]
It was for the best, my friend.
[KIYOSHI]
How? You blew any chance of
getting laid before
college on that figure!
[GAKUTO]
I had two choices:
sell out my friends,
or lose a hunk of plastic.
Either way, I'd never be
able to face Lord Guan Yu.
I should have acted sooner.
Seven years is but a pittance
compared to an entire
life cast into the sewer.
That's heavy, man.
Oh, Sir Kiyoshi. I'm sorry
for everything I've done,
and for what I didn't do
when you alone had to
endure their bullying.
I shall never again conduct
myself in such a base manner,
on my honor!
[GAKUTO sobs]
[KIYOSHI sniffles]
Dumb ass, you don't have
anything to apologize for.
We're homeboys, man.
[GAKUTO]
Thank you, Milord.
[sighs]
Looks like your plan
to connect Four-Eyes to
the crime has backfired.
This is becoming frustrating.
I am so mortified, ma'am.
I never expected him
to take things that far.
[SHINGO panting]
Sorry, I'm late. Just got back.
And I dropped your root
beer off in the fridge, too.
[gasps]
Hey, this looks like
the little toy sword
that I found in the restroom.
[MARI, MEIKO gasp]
Rewind.
Where did you find it?
This?
I grabbed it from the
floor by the toilet,
and handed it off to
Madam Vice President.
--Didn't I, ma'am?
--[MARI gasping]
[MEIKO] Madam President!
I didn't know how to tell you!
[MEIKO]
Madam President!
Madam, are you all right?!
[SHINGO]
Huh?
[MEIKO]
I apologize with all my being
for this indiscretion, Madam!
I'm prepared to accept any
form of punishment you wish!
It's fine, Meiko.
You can get off the ground now.
[MEIKO]
I couldn't!
Please punish me in
any manner you see fit!
I deserve it!
[water splashes]
[MARI] I'm the one at
fault for relegating
this assignment to you.
[MEIKO gasps]
What? Filthy Four-Eyes just
smashed the doll to pieces?
Yes. And we'd come
so close, too.
Aw...
I don't know, maybe
we missed something.
--[MEIKO] I alone am to blame!
--[HANA gasps]
Please, Madam!
Some form of punitive
measure must be taken!
Here, use this leather crop and
spank me, please! I beg you!
Hana, this tea blend is divine.
[gasps] How kind of you to say.
[MARI]
What did you use to make it?
Well, um... A little lemongrass
and some hibiscus buds.
I think I'll have
another cup, please.
[HANA]
Okay.
So, uh...
Tell me, does DTO have a Plan B?
--[MEIKO whimpering]
--[MARI] Yes.
From here on, I will
personally assume command.
My friends!
I apologize earnestly for
the trouble I've caused.
Madam Vice President
was correct.
I aided Kiyoshi's escape for the
sake of that Guan Yu figurine.
Nay, in truth, it is fair to say
I was ringleader
of the operation!
I am eternally sorry for having
held my tongue for so long!
Knew it all along.
No way in hell Kiyoshi could've
pulled it off on his own.
So, what do we do about
our double-crossing geek
with a loose turd-cutter?
[JOE] I'm not gonna
do much of anything.
Sure, Gakuto may have
assisted with the breakout,
but the Underground Student
Council doesn't know.
[SHINGO] You're missing
the point, Lame-Brain!
Gakuto betrayed all of us!
I went crazy during
the anting incident.
If Kiyoshi hadn't jumped
in at the last second,
I would have made things
a lot worse for everybody.
I'm the last person to
start the blame game.
Joe...! [sobs]
[SHINGO growls]
Andre, what about you?
Aren't you pissed off, bro?
I choose to forgive
Gakuto as well.
Are you shitting me?!
What's wrong with you?!
Not a thing.
Gakuto went so far as to
destroy his precious figurine,
and he did it to keep the rest
of us out of more trouble.
I say, he's suffered enough.
Thanks, Andre.
Would you stupid dickheads
stop being so freakin'
mellow about everything?
Gakuto's just as
guilty as Kiyoshi is.
While we were out there
busting our asses.
He was staring at his
dolly in the john,
not giving a shit
who he betrays.
The john? So he hid the
figurine in the crapper?
[SHINGO gasps]
Yeah, he did.
But how'd you know that, Shingo?
[SHINGO grunts]
The Underground Student
Council chicks said so!
Anyhow, I say Gakuto
has to pay, you feel me?
Did they say that?
Shingo and the Vice
President have been
spending a lot of time
together the last few days.
Maybe he heard where
it was from her.
Alone with Madam
Vice President...
Color me jealous.
[MEIKO whimpers]
To not even be allowed to
receive punishment is too much.
Was I naïve in thinking that
if the President punished me,
I would be deserving
of forgiveness?
What if her punishment for me
is to not punish me at all?
[MEIKO gasps]
I'm ready!
[HANA gasps]
[MEIKO]
Hi, Hana...
Let's see... The President
said this is for you.
She said so?
[MEIKO]
Is that...?
Which one of you dirt-grubs
left this shovel
sticking out of the ground?
Ah! I'm so sorry, Mistress!
It was me, all my fault!
How shocking.
Sir Andre is actually running
to receive his due punishment.
Yeah, without a doubt--
[coughs]
No... Madam... Why?
What the hell?
Where are those glorious tatas?
Neither breasts nor
panties are on display!
So you're the one who
left this shovel here?
It was me, Madam!
Let me apologize by
licking your boots!
Moron! He's bound to get a
whipping, going in like that!
Perhaps that is Sir
Andre's true intention?
[ANDRE panting]
Huh?
[MEIKO]
Move your ass and stow it away.
[ANDRE]
Mother fucker!
[MEIKO] Your glasses are
on crooked, Dog-Nuts!
Why doesn't she use
her riding crop on me?
Let's go, Andre. No giving up!
Hiya, Toots!
I put the shovel away,
so why don't you whip
your knockers out?
Did he just play the
"full-on perv" card?!
I know Andre's a
raging masochist,
but pulling that kind of
maneuver on the Vice President
is totally friggin' suicidal!
What hell has he unleashed?!
--Very good.
--[ANDRE] I don't get anything?!
[ANDRE]
"My Slave Diary.
Even my construction
worker level harassment
completely fell through." [sobs]
[MEIKO pants]
[sighs]
The President said I have
to wear this uniform,
even though it's
a size too small.
[grunting]
[sighs]
But this might as well be a
straight-jacket for my body.
However, this is the punishment
that she chose for
my foolishness.
Therefore, I must bear it.
Which one of you halitosis-farms
left this hoe in the ground?!
It was Andre! [coughs]
I planted it there for you.
Now go get your whooping.
Yes, it was me!
Between the shovel and hoe,
I should be whipped for
not taking proper care
of school equipment!
--[MEIKO] Put it away at once.
--[ANDRE gasps]
[ANDRE]
"My Slave Diary.
I didn't get a
whooping today either.
Joe even tried to set me up, but
I was unable to seal the deal."
[CHIYO gasps]
[MEIKO whimpers]
[CHIYO]
What's the matter, Meiko?
You don't look well!
Chiyo, thank you.
[CHIYO] Here, I brought
you a glass of water.
Don't you think that uniform's
a bit too small for your figure?
[MEIKO]
No! This one is perfectly fine.
I feel much better
now, thank you.
Come on.
You should probably lie
down a little longer.
Huh?
What is DTO?
[MEIKO]
I think I will have some water.
[CHIYO]
"Danshi Tai-gaku"?
"Destroy Testicles"?
--[gasps]
--Oh, Chiyo.
[MARI]
Why are you here?
Can I help you?
Meiko looked like she
wasn't feeling well,
so I brought her here.
I'll uh... See ya later!
[ANDRE]
"My Slave Diary.
Hope is an illusion.
More cruel than any whip.
I can't take it.
Please spit on me, Mistress.
Anoint me in my own shame.
I long to be the ground
beneath your sharp heel.
Everyone else gets
punished; why don't I?"
I see.
Thank you for the
illuminating read.
[MEIKO]
Did you find it informative?
[MARI]
Yes.
He's getting close to the
breaking point, mentally.
It seems that
the time has come.
At last, tomorrow, we set in
motion the final phase of
the Destroy Testicles Operation.
[CHIYO]
What are you planning, Sis?
[KIYOSHI]
Next time on Prison School:
"The Diary of Andre"