[ANDRE whimpering]
[GAKUTO] Have we
no course of action?
[JOE]
I tried talking to him,
but he didn't seem to
notice me at all. [coughs]
It's hard to fathom
how the human mind
could devolve to such a state,
and much less for one
pining for punishment!
[ANDRE]
Punish me, Madam.
Please, punish me.
Why won't you punish me?
[MEIKO] Make sure to be back
here by suppertime, at 6:30.
If you're a minute late,
we'll chalk it up as a breakout.
Thank you, Madam.
But... I haven't really done
anything to earn this favor.
What's the matter with you?
You want the time
outside or not?
[SHINGO]
No, ma'am!
I mean, yes, ma'am!
I'd like to go out please!
[ANDRE grunting]
Please, punish me.
[KIYOSHI]
Andre's looking terrible.
Why is he the only one not
getting smacked around
by the Vice President?
Now that I think of it,
there's been a lot of
weird crap going on.
--[KIYOSHI] Shingo!
--[SHINGO gasps]
The hell, man?!
Don't shout at me like that!
Uh... My bad.
It's just that...
The Vice President's been
taking you off alone a bunch.
Are you okay?
Uh, I don't know what you mean.
Cool, man.
As long as she's not
torturing you or something.
I dunno. The Underground
Student Council's been
acting strange lately.
Anyway, if the situation
goes south, just let me know.
I'd like to help you if I can.
[MEIKO]
Shingo!
Come to the office!
Yes, ma'am.
[SHINGO] I should be back
by 6:30, with time to spare!
--[ANZU] Here.
--[SHINGO gasps]
[ANZU]
Whatcha spacin' about?
--[SHINGO] Oh, nothing.
--Actually...
Could you hold mine for a sec?
And let me just scooch over...
[SHINGO]
Oh, ho, ho! Jackpot!
[ANZU] I can't wait to see
these "Grapes of Wrath."
Ditto. I really wanna
scope what kinda rampage
these monster
grapes'll bust out.
Yeah, right.
I bet you're acting tough
'cause you're scared!
[SHINGO]
I'm not scared!
It's a movie!
[ANZU]
Ssh! It's starting.
New job today!
You snatch-rags are going to
service the barricade entrance.
What's this?
Decided to bring your club
activities outside, huh?
Yeah!
It's a lovely day, I thought
we'd get some fresh air.
Sounds like a delightful
way to spend your time!
--Have fun!
--[CHIYO] Aye-aye!
[gasps]
[JOE]
What're we doing?
The gate's working fine.
[GAKUTO] Is Sir Andre foregoing
his ablutions yet again today?
[JOE] Yeah...
I tried to get him to shower,
but he's gone back to sitting
in the corner of his cell.
[MAYUMI]
I was so nervous
the Vice President would figure
out what we were doing.
Thanks for your help, Mayumi.
You did great!
I really hope Kiyoshi was
able to see our message.
I think he did.
As he was walking past us,
I looked in his eyes, and it
seemed like he understood.
[KIYOSHI]
"Yadot dellepxe syob."
What the fuck does that mean?!
[ANDRE]
Spit in my face.
Spank me.
--Punish me, Mistress.
--[MEIKO] Andre...
[gasps]
[MEIKO]
It's punishment time...
Andre...
Come take your whipping...
[SHINGO groans]
Hey, this movie kinda
blows, doesn't it?
[SHINGO]
Oh! Uh, yeah... It's slow.
[ANZU]
I totally think we should bail.
So, you've still got some
free-range time, right?
Uh-huh.
A little more than an hour.
Where should we go?
Well! Pick a store. My treat!
Chill. You don't have
to overdo it with me.
There's a pretty nice
park over there.
Let's check it out!
[MEIKO]
Andre...
You've been a very naughty boy.
Prepare to take your punishment.
Madam Vice President!
Put me in my place!
Whip me mercilessly!
It isn't her...
[sobs]
[ANDRE]
How did my diary end up in here?
"I sat in the corner of the room
feeling sorry for
myself, as usual.
When I heard a voice from
out of nowhere saying,
"Punishment time."
After following the voice,
all I found was a stand-up
cutout of the Vice President,
and I was so disappointed."
It can't be.
How's cartoon me
know what happened?
[ANDRE] "The door to
the Corrections Office
was left open, and
just beyond the door...
...was the Vice President!
I was finally able to get all
the punishment I deserved!"
[ANDRE gasps]
[ANDRE]
Right through that door...
She's waiting for me.
[GAKUTO]
Sir Kiyoshi.
[KIYOSHI]
Uh...
You seem preoccupied.
Is something amiss?
Sort of.
Does the phrase, "Yodat
dellepxe syob," ring a bell?
Wait, did you mean,
"Klaatu barada nikto,"
works on alien robots
and the Necronomicon?
[KIYOSHI]
No... It's a message from Chiyo.
[glass squeaks]
[GAKUTO gasps]
What foul augury is this?
You got it backwards, Dolt!
[KIYOSHI]
"Boys expelled today."
It was a warning!
Hang on, whaddaya
mean, "Boys expelled"?
[GAKUTO]
Yours truly is no ladies' man,
but that doesn't seem
to be a love note!
[KIYOSHI]
It might have something to do
with all the weird shit
that's been going on.
What if they were all set-ups
to give 'em a reason to
kick us out of school?
[JOE]
Who's settin' us up?
The Underground
Student Council, Genius!
[gasps]
Andre!
Madam Vice President,
I'm ready for my punishment!
Andre!
--[GAKUTO] Sir Kiyoshi!
--[KIYOSHI gasps]
Come hither, quick!
[ANDRE moaning]
[MEIKO]
You've been such a naughty boy.
I'll have to whip you
harder than ever!
[yells]
[ANDRE gasping]
[MEIKO]
And now... I hope you're ready.
You've earned a harsh
lesson in discipline.
[panting]
Oh, Mommy!
--Baby needs his spanking!
--Fat fuck!
Did you really
just call me mommy?!
Too bad. You're
just out of reach.
I can't punish you from
all the way back here.
Guess it'll have to wait.
Andre!
--No! You mustn't!
--Stop!
--[wires snap]
--[ANDRE yells]
Oinker.
Take this!
[ANDRE]
Oh! It hurts so good!
[MEIKO]
Prison break!
What? But I was
submitting myself--
--[screams]
--Hold still, Butterbean!
He shouldn't have
gotten through.
Sir Kiyoshi... Take a look.
These wires appear to have
been partially cut through.
They screwed us.
This was all just
part of their plans!
That went well, don't you think?
Yes. All thanks to
our secret weapon.
I never imagined such utility
from a too-tight uniform.
He was at his breaking point.
My wardrobe malfunction
just lit the fuse.
Just as you planned,
Madam President.
You put up with the constraints
of that tight uniform
like a champion.
[MEIKO]
You flatter me.
Thank you.
Now we wait for your
canary to return to his cage.
Y'know, "The Grapes of Wrath"
is a really misleading title.
I'll take your word for it.
I was fast asleep before
the thirty-minute mark.
[ANZU] That's way too soon!
It might have been boring,
but at least I stayed awake!
Hey, I'm sorry.
[ANZU growls]
--[BOTH laugh]
--[ANZU] Gotcha!
C'mon! Stop!
[SHINGO]
I'm so happy!
Things are finally
working out for Shingo!
And now, with the way
that things've been going,
it might get even more perfect.
Like...
She might even
let me kiss her!
[ANZU gasps]
--[SHINGO gasps]
--Dude, don't get angry.
Your face goes all
monster-creepy.
I ain't mad at all!
Actually, to tell the
truth, I'm really happy.
Yeah? You're happy?
Yeah, I think.
If you're so happy, why'd
you pull a psycho-face?
When you're squishing
cheek muscles,
the face is gonna respond.
Seriously?
Fine, you pinch my
cheeks and let's see.
Well? Do I look all creepy?
[ANZU]
What is it? Say something.
[KID 8A laughs]
[SHINGO growls]
I can't watch anymore!
What are you throwing sand
at that little dude for?
It could get in
his eyes, you know!
I don't care!
Besides, it's his
own fault anyway!
He ditched us to go get cooties
--from playing with a girl!
--[SHINGO] If the kid
wants to play with a girl,
let him play with a girl!
--[KID 8A] I don't wanna
get infected! We made a rule!
No playing with girls!
[KID 8B]
He's a dirty double-crosser!
I told you to
stop throwing sand!
[KIDS gasp, cry]
Ah! Hey, I'm sorry, kid.
But it's not very cool to
pick on someone like that.
Because... if he's your friend,
you should forgive him.
--[KID 8C grunts]
--[SHINGO groans]
Hey, what was that for?!
Stop being a bully!
[SHINGO gasps]
[KID 8C]
Let's go, you guys!
[KIDS]
Yeah!
[KID 8B]
Twat!
Kids can be so dumb sometimes.
You didn't get sand in your
eyes, so that went well.
It looks like they made
up with their friend, too.
Way to handle it, Shingo.
You should be proud of yourself.
That was pretty cool.
[SHINGO]
If he's your friend.
[ANZU gasps]
[SHINGO]
You should forgive him.
[sighs]
How can I say that after the
way I've treated Kiyoshi?
Hey, come on.
Are you okay?
[SHINGO]
I wanted to think so.
I've been giving
info about the guys
to the Vice Prez... in return
for special treatment.
They're all stuck
doing prison labor.
I'm fooling around
at the arcade,
and of course,
hanging out with you.
I'm a low-life asshole.
[MARI] I'm afraid this counts
as another breakout attempt.
[KIYOSHI] You wanted to
lure him out, didn't you?!
You're entitled to your
opinion, of course.
But it won't change the fact
that he broke through the fence.
[ANDRE] I'm sorry, guys.
I couldn't stop.
[MARI]
Today's sad little incident
counts against you
as a second breakout.
In accordance to the Underground
Student Council bylaws,
your sentences will be
extended by three months.
[SHINGO] Sorry to bore
you with my sob story.
It's a bit early, but
I'm going to head back.
I've gotta make some apologies.
Hopefully, I won't embarrass
myself anymore than I have.
[gasps]
[ANZU sobs]
Shingo...
I'm sorry.
[ANZU]
I'm so sorry.
I've done something
I'm really not proud of.
[SHINGO]
Huh?
[JOE coughs]
Hey, where's Shingo at?
[MEIKO]
I told him to return by 6:30,
but he certainly seems to be
taking his time coming back.
I also let him know that if
he's even one second late,
it'll count as a breakout.
So that's the final
step of your plan!
[MEIKO laughs]
Not much longer.
He sure is cutting it close.
[MARI] Have you enjoyed your
time in our organization?
[ANZU] Yes, ma'am. It's been
my privilege to support the
Underground Student Council
as Captain of the Guard.
I didn't do something
wrong, did I?
So tell me, Anzu, would a
position in the executive branch
be of interest to you?
You flatter me, Madam President.
[MARI]
Listen close.
I have a certain task
I'd like you to attend to.
You have what it
takes to succeed.
You'll have my
recommendation on your résumé.
So, yeah. My mission was
to get friendly with you
during your time
away from school.
You're a plant? No way...
[ANZU]
Everything led up to this day.
I was supposed to take you out.
And to make sure that you didn't
get back to the school in time.
Which would then count
against you as a third breakout,
meaning all of the
boys get expelled!
[SHINGO]
Expelled?!
The Underground Student
Council set you up!
You're running out of time!
Look, I'm still kinda
confused, but all right!
There's plenty of time if I run.
But there's not! Your watch
is thirty minutes slow!
I set it back while
we were at the movie.
[SHINGO gasps]
It's 6:25?!
Five minutes until
Shingo's late.
That's not enough time,
less than 300 seconds now!
--[cries] We're done for.
--Totally, royally screwed.
[KIYOSHI]
He'll be here.
I have faith that Shingo will
make it back here in time.
Based on what?!
Hope is all we have left!
So shut it!
And hope that
Shingo's hauling ass!
[MEIKO]
Just four more minutes now.
And then we'll be forever
rid of your foul presence.
It's a real shame, too.
Over the summer, we have
school by the seaside.
We have campfires.
Then there's barbecue.
And then, the wet t-shirt
contest is a favorite.
[BOYS]
Wet... t-shirt... contest?!
[MEIKO]
As well as a heaving helping
of other titillating events.
No... I know Shingo's gonna
make it back here in time!
All we have to do
is believe in him!
--Boob aquarium.
--[KIYOSHI] That's right!
Focus on Shingo and
send him all our hopes!
[BOYS yelling]
Shingo! Come back!
Shingo! Run! Dude! Run!
[SHINGO gasps]
[BOYS yelling]
Shingo! Shingo! Hurry up!
--Wet t-shirts, man!
--Stop making such a racket!
[GAKUTO]
Sir Shingo! Come home at once!
What did I just say?!
[MARI]
It's fine, Meiko.
Let them yell their heads off.
As long as Anzu does her duty,
our little snitch will
never make it back by 6:30.
[CLEANER]
Kid, are you okay?
[groans] Yeah, I'm all right.
I just fell down.
You didn't even hit me.
But never mind that,
do you know what time it is?
[BOTH gasp]
[MEIKO]
Hah! Take this! And this!
[BOYS screaming]
One more minute left.
And then we'll finally
be able to return
to our peaceful way of life.
[gasps]
[BOYS gasp, cheer]
Thanks a lot!
--It's Shingo!
--Yeah! Go, man!
I knew he wouldn't let us down.
That's the old fellow
from the cleaning service!
But how?
[BOYS yelling]
Come on! Hurry! Shingo!
We're running out of time!
--What's the time?
--[MEIKO] Thirty seconds!
Looks like he made it!
[BOYS cheering]
Yeah, man! Sir Shingo! Shingo!
Hey there, guys!
[MEIKO]
You've got ten seconds!
[KIYOSHI]
Stop jerking around and open it!
--[MEIKO] 5... 4...
--[SHINGO] I'm trying, bro!
--...3...
--It won't budge!
--...2...
--Don't you give up!
--...1...
--Get in here now!
[MEIKO]
Zero.
He is officially late.
That's bullshit!
It doesn't count! It was locked!
[MEIKO]
What are you talking about?
You simply weren't
operating it properly.
What in the hell?
But wait! When did it...?
The original gate had
a couple of flaws,
which is why today's
work detail hinged on it.
Damn! Everything's
coming together now.
[SHINGO grunts]
[MARI] Your tardiness counts
as your third breakout.
And according to the rulebook,
a third strike means
forced expulsion.
[STUDENT 8A]
Did you hear?
The stupid boys got caught
breaking out twice yesterday.
[STUDENT 8B] Sounds like those
creeps are getting expelled!
[STUDENT 8C]
That's a relief.
Maybe the school won't
smell like feet anymore.
[ANZU]
Shingo...
Sorry...
We're all getting expelled
because you were out there
hanging with a girl?
And after you've been
non-stop raggin' on Kiyoshi
for doing the exact same thing?
Not to mention, it was
all to victimize you
through the use of the old
'honey-pot' espionage trick.
Guys, I'm really, really sorry.
I was a total jerk,
and I'm prepared to take
what's coming to me.
Go ahead!
Stand up, Shingo.
[KIYOSHI] When they
discovered my breakout,
you punched me.
You remember that, don't you?
[GAKUTO]
Sir Kiyoshi!
Yeah. Hit me as
hard as you wanna.
[KIYOSHI]
Okay...
Think I will!
[BOYS gasp]
I'd say that we're even, now.
Kiyoshi...
I can't be mad.
We're all guilty somehow, man.
So just relax. No one in here
has any right to bash you.
His word is true.
You were victim to the
Underground Student
Council's scheme,
and they took advantage
of your manly desires.
If anything, we
feel sorry for you.
You gave us all a
heart-felt apology.
And that is good enough for me.
Well, after my rampage,
I can't judge.
Thanks, guys.
[sobs]
I did a lot of
selfish things and--
and I betrayed your friendship.
Thank you for being so cool!
You know, watching you dash
for the gate at full throttle
was all rather inspiring.
[SHINGO]
When Anzu held my hand,
--she changed my watch
--[BOYS gasp]
to make me late,
but later told me.
[GAKUTO]
Oh...? Is that right?
You were holding
hands, were you?
Totally, bro!
I held her hand, and we
even sat in the park,
pinching each other's cheeks.
[coughs]
Lucky jerk.
Yeah, but it was all part
of her elaborate trap,
so it couldn't be
helped, I guess.
Yeah, could be.
--Guess the cleavage,
--[BOYS gasp]
and the mini nip-slip were
--all part of her game as well.
--[BOYS gasp]
But in the end, she decided to
clue me in on her little scheme.
She must like me.
Why else would she come
clean to me about it?
Hm?
--[KIYOSHI grunts]
--[SHINGO groans]
[BOYS yelling]
[SHINGO groaning, coughing]
I thought you guys said
you didn't have the
right to bash me.
That was before.
--Now, we know you saw nippage.
--Though seeing nipples
might have been the Underground
Student Council's design
from the very beginning,
it doesn't stop yours truly
--from being jealous.
--If you caught a nip-slip,
a simple apology isn't
going to cut it, homie.
Tell us dude, pink or brown?
Okay, so now the
score's back to even.
[CHAIRMAN]
Welcome to my office.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Hi!
[BOYS]
The pleasure's all ours, sir.
[CHAIRMAN] I had hoped we
wouldn't have to meet
in this fashion.
You boys are all aware of why
you've been called before me...
--...right?
--Mari and the rest set them up!
[CHAIRMAN]
Chiyo...
I'll listen to what
you have to say--
I saw it in the Underground
Student Council's office!
A document with "DTO:
Destroy Testicle Operation"
written on it!
Mari, is what your
sister saying true? Well?
She must be mistaken.
I have neither seen nor heard
of anything like that, sir.
[MARI]
Without any proof,
there's nothing
for me to explain.
[CHIYO gasps]
[MARI]
Unless there's something else,
why don't you run along, Chiyo?
[CHIYO] I'm so sorry,
Kiyoshi. I tried to help.
[KIYOSHI]
Thanks, Chiyo.
In accordance with
student regulations.
the five of you are
to be expelled.
Isn't that right, Chairman?
According to the student
handbook... Yes!
We can discuss
this matter further
at next week's
committee meeting,
which will end with the
Chairman putting his seal
on the expulsion papers,
making the decision final.
Does that timeline work
for your schedule, sir?
[CHAIRMAN sighs]
[MARI] Mister Chairman!
The rules are very clear!
How long will justice wait?
The week after next,
at the very latest... Aah!
Well, I'd say that DTO
was a rousing success!
And masterfully
executed, ladies!
Here, let's raise a glass
to a boy-free Hachimitsu!
[ALL]
Cheers!
[MEIKO] And now, to celebrate
the favorable conclusion of DTO,
might I be so bold as to
give a little performance?
Marvel as I do 50 pull-ups,
utilizing only the
strength of my fingers!
One... Two...
[HANA]
One thing still bugs me.
--[MEIKO] Three...
--How did Shingo make it back
in time for curfew, anyway?
--[MEIKO] Four...
--[MARI] I'll have Anzu
come join us, and ask
her for a few answers.
[MEIKO]
Forty-seven...
--[MEIKO] Forty-eight.
--Only two more left, now.
Hang in there, Meiko!
[MARI]
You're getting close!
[MEIKO grunting]
Forty-nine...
Fifty...!
--[grunt]
--[ANZU] You sent for me?
[GAKUTO]
So it's come to this.
In less than two weeks,
we'll be gone.
[ANDRE sighs]
Goodbye, wet t-shirt contest.
Huh? Wet t-shirt contest?
Where they blast
girls with water
till their shirts
are see-through?
Yeah.
They have summer school
by the sea, apparently.
[SHINGO sighs]
I...
Somehow I already knew about it.
The image of a wet
t-shirt contest
flashed through my mind
as I ran back to school.
I saw it, and I thought
to myself, "What was that?"
I turned, and there
was this van.
If it hadn't been
for that vision...
Well, he would have
squashed me flat.
In sooth?
Then our hopeful thoughts
managed to reach out to you!
It's a miracle!
Seriously? Bad ass.
[ANDRE]
I guess miracles do happen, huh?
So then you became
enamored with this Shingo,
and divulged our plan to him?
You're the Captain
of the Guard, Anzu.
This won't reflect well on you.
I'm terribly sorry.
That's all in the past.
[gasps]
[MARI] DTO was still
a complete success.
I won't pursue the
matter any further.
[ANZU]
But Madam President--
I said it was all right.
Now go.
[ANZU]
Yes, ma'am.
Don't worry about the
door on your way out.
Okay. Are you certain
you don't need a hand?
[MEIKO]
It's okay. Go on.
Was that wise,
Madam President?
I'm afraid she knows too
much about our operation.
Until the boys
have been expelled,
keep her under
constant observation.
Clever indeed! Keeping tabs
on her comings and goings
is a wise course of action.
Hey, Meiko? Are you sure
you don't need a hand?
[MEIKO]
I'm fine, thank you.
I can get out of this by myself.
[HANA]
Hang in there, Meiko!
[MARI] You're getting close,
Madam Vice President!
[MEIKO panting]
My fingertips have
lost their strength.
But I refuse to quit--!
[HANA gasps]
[MEIKO grunts]
Miracles wait for no man.
We have to make
them happen, dudes!
[BOYS gasp]
[KIYOSHI] Like saving Shingo
from getting hit by that van!
He's right!
The tale of Sir Shingo's
deliverance is miraculous!
So what's the plan, you guys?!
Think of the wet t-shirts!
There's no way in hell
we can just give up!
You're right.
--But what can we do?
--[KIYOSHI] Well, Chiyo said
that she'd seen a project
plan for DTO, didn't she?
If we can just get
our hands on that...
Right, but I'm sure they've
already trashed any evidence.
[KIYOSHI sighs]
Probably.
[SHINGO]
Wait...
I know I saw the initials
"DTO" somewhere before...
[KIYOSHI]
Next time on Prison School:
"Full of Bodily Fluids"