[trickling]
[KIYOSHI screams]
[gasps]
[HANA gasps]
--[HANA screams]
--[BOYS] Huh?
[HANA sobs]
Hana! What's wrong?
[gasps]
What the hell did you do to her?
[KIYOSHI]
Nothing, I just fell--
No! Don't say anything!
Someone doesn't seem to learn.
[KIYOSHI]
No! It's not like that!
--You gotta--
--[MEIKO] Enough!
That's all the work for today.
Get your asses back inside!
[GAKUTO]
Huzzah, and well-met, good sir!
You brought that frigid
monster Hana to tears!
Nah... This crow whooshed--
Yeah, boy!
When you strike, you really
rock no-holds-barred, huh?
[KIYOSHI] I'm still
amazed I got through it
without being skinned alive!
All right, let's hoist him!
[KIYOSHI]
Stop!
[KIYOSHI] I told Chiyo
we'd watch sumo together,
but Hana may murder
me before then.
What do I do?!
[BOYS]
Heave-ho!
[CHAIRMAN]
I've been informed that all five
of the boys are in that prison.
Come.
Admit it.
Isn't that treatment the
slightest bit... harsh?
They were guilty.
Under normal circumstances,
they would face expulsion.
Open and shut.
And besides...
I was against going
co-ed from the start.
As were the majority
of the student body,
the alumni, and
the entire faculty.
[CHAIRMAN] Look, I realize
the desire you all have
to hold on to tradition,
but the natural order needs
a good shake up
from time to time.
Understand?
[MARI] Mister Chairman, you
ignored all our objections.
And on the first day, those boys
exhibited problematic behavior.
This chaos is the result
of the changes you made.
Young bucks, that's the
kind of hare-brained scheme
that boys their age come
up with every single day.
Hormones.
[MARI]
They're criminals.
[CHAIRMAN]
I know that, Mari.
And I'm not trying to justify
their actions in the slightest.
But I want you to at least
let them have their Saturdays
and Sundays off.
Prison rules were set with
those contingencies in mind.
Weren't they?
That is accurate.
Goodbye, Father.
--[whip cracks]
--[doors rattle]
New after schoolwork detail!
You cretins are to clear
this wooded area.
[GAKUTO]
Huh?
I didn't say anything!
Why did you strike me thusly?
You failed to ask me why you're
clearing this plot of land.
I just can't win.
[MEIKO]
Now that you know the question,
the answer is:
you're clearing this land
for the campus vegetable garden.
Um... May I ask a
question, please?
Go ahead.
[KIYOSHI]
About the weekend...
Do we get Saturdays
and Sundays off?
[MEIKO]
We need that garden.
And since there are no
classes during the weekend,
you have more time for work.
[BOYS groan]
--[MARI] However...
--[BOYS] Huh?
[MARI] ...prisoners
exhibiting good behavior
will earn three hours
of weekend free time;
which would include furloughs.
--[BOYS cheer]
--Madam President!
[KIYOSHI]
No shit?
This could work!
My sumo date with
Chiyo is on Saturday!
Three hours is perfect!
Yeah!
C'mon, guys!
Let's do it!
We shall be convicts
of the highest standing!
[KIYOSHI] We are getting this
weekend pass, no matter what!
[STUDENTS squeal]
[STUDENT 2A]
Taking care of business!
[STUDENT 2B] The Underground
Student Council is so cool!
[HANA]
Guess what, guys!
[MEIKO]
Mm?
[HANA] This year's Official
Underground Student Council
Guide Book just arrived from
the Official Underground
Student Publishing Company
for your inspection!
Looks like the Underground
Student Council's
pretty popular.
But a guidebook seems
counter-intuitive.
--[groans]
--[GAKUTO, SHINGO gasp]
Okay...
What's the big idea, Hoodrat?!
Sorry... [coughs] But you
almost stepped on some ants.
My bad...
[chuckles]
Don't mind him.
He's really into ants.
[MEIKO] Hey, Pig Dicks!
No slacking off!
[BOYS]
Sorry!
[knocking]
[door creaks]
[MARI] Chairman, your copy
of this year's guide book--
[computer buzzes]
[gasps]
And yet, people wonder
why I think men are scum.
Break time!
[BOYS sigh]
Guess break time means she's
gonna make us keep working.
[KIYOSHI]
This work is brutal,
but I have to push through,
and be a model prisoner.
Then I get my date with Chiyo!
[MARI] Why are these
slouch-packs on break?
They don't seem to
have made any progress.
As it stands...
They'll need to put in some
work over the weekend, as well.
[BOYS scream]
[KIYOSHI]
Madam President!
--That isn't fair!
--Get back, Clown!
[KIYOSHI] I won't be
able to go on my date!
What can I do?
Sick family member?
No, they'd see through that.
Say my stomach hurts?
They won't give a shit.
What do I do?
I promised her...
[sobs]
[KIYOSHI gasps]
[KIYOSHI]
Digging...
I can break out!
[bell rings]
[MEIKO]
On the gate!
Roll call!
[KIYOSHI]
One!
Two!
[ANDRE]
Three!
Four!
Five!
[KIYOSHI]
Pardon me!
This trash has really built up.
May I go dispose of it, Madam?
[MEIKO]
Permission granted.
[KIYOSHI grunts]
[KIYOSHI grunting]
[KIYOSHI] At this rate,
it should be big enough
for me to get through
when the time comes.
--[whip cracks]
--[BOYS yelp]
[KIYOSHI] And I've got three
minutes for each trip here.
[sighs]
[groans]
Eh?
[KIYOSHI]
It's Chiyo!
Uh.
[KIYOSHI]
What is she trying to do?
[CHIYO]
"Dear Kiyoshi.
The doors open at 1:00 PM
at the Civic Gymnasium for
the student sumo tournament.
You can get sprung on
Saturday, can't you?"
Su-more of you soon.
[KIYOSHI]
The sad truth is,
we won't get any furlough time.
So the only choice I
have is to break out.
But seeing Chiyo gave me hope!
--[whip cracks]
--[gasps]
Why didn't you load all
the refuse onto the cart?
You piece of crap.
I'm sincerely sorry.
[KIYOSHI] Oh shit!
I must've missed some!
Now Gakuto's taking the
heat for my mistake.
[KIYOSHI]
I'm sorry!
I'll take care of it right now!
[GAKUTO]
Kiyoshi... Thank you!
[MEIKO]
No, he'll do it!
Hey, Gakuto...
I'm sorry, man.
She flipped out on you,
and it's all my fault.
...Gakuto?
Are you okay?
Yes. Just fine.
I've become inured to it.
Thus, all is well.
It was my bad, so have
one of my nuggets.
My, how very generous.
[GAKUTO] Sir Kiyoshi,
would you fancy some more tea?
[KIYOSHI]
Sure, thanks.
[GAKUTO]
I thought you should know.
I recovered
something of interest
lying near the refuse site.
[KIYOSHI gasps]
[KIYOSHI]
He knows.
There's no doubt about it.
But what's he planning?
How is he going to use
this to his advantage?
Would you like for me to
wash your back for you?
[gasps]
[GAKUTO]
You know, Kiyoshi...
It's my understanding that
the top sumo wrestlers
have devoted assistants.
Men who'll wash
their backs for them,
as well as their
bulbous posteriors.
[KIYOSHI gasps]
Well... Uh... I'm not a
sumo wrestler, so I'll pass.
For today's work shift, Hana
has returned as overseer.
Hi, fellas!
[BOYS groan]
This sucks balls.
[HANA]
I'll give you crap-burgers
something to whisper about!
[MEIKO]
Now get to work, maggots!
[BOYS]
Yes, ma'am!
[KIYOSHI]
One things for sure.
Gakuto knows better
than to rat me out
to the Underground
Student Council.
If they so much as catch
a whiff of a breakout,
then everybody's
sentence gets extended
--by another friggin' month.
--[GAKUTO] Kiyoshi!
Let's put all our
weight behind it today!
[KIYOSHI whimpers]
[HANA]
No unauthorized sumo displays!
[KIYOSHI]
What the hell was that about?
Making a show of sumo customs.
Is he trying to play some
kind of mind game with me?
He crosses me,
--he gets fork stabbed!
--[HANA] Hey, Pervert.
Where did you run off to?
[KIYOSHI]
Sorry about that,
I was sorting the
trash into piles.
[HANA grunts]
What is it?
You told the other
convicts, didn't you?
[KIYOSHI]
Uh--
[HANA]
About what happened.
[KIYOSHI]
About what happened?
[HANA]
Me peeing.
--[KIYOSHI] Uh...
--[HANA hisses]
Ugh, what you saw!
You told everyone and
made me a laughing stock!
No, I haven't told a soul.
[HANA]
You liar! I don't believe it!
Too bad. It's true.
[HANA] Fine, but you
have to do it, as well.
Huh?
Do what now?
I want you to pee
for me right now!
I'll watch, so whip it out!
Do that and I'll believe you.
No, I couldn't "do that"!
It's way weird!
You saw me "do that," so I've
gotta watch you "do that"!
Otherwise, we can't
make things even!
Now, bust it out,
and take a whiz.
Or refuse, then I'll kill
you and off myself.
[KIYOSHI]
All right! Fine!
Are you sure...
you wanna see this?
[HANA]
Of course I do.
[KIYOSHI grunts]
[HANA]
What are you doing?
[KIYOSHI]
Uh...
You saw me up front,
so turn around.
[gasps]
Whoa! Isn't that kinda close?
[HANA] You were even
closer when I was going.
Now hurry up and get started.
'Kay...
--[GAKUTO] Sir Kiyoshi!
--[BOTH gasp]
Where art thou?
[KIYOSHI]
Gakuto, what's up?
You forgot to dispose of some
piles of debris yet again.
Tch.
Oh, sorry.
Once that's been dealt with,
you're to return
to work immediately.
Right!
You saved my ass, Gakuto.
Much appreciated.
[KIYOSHI] The question is,
did he mean to save me just now?
I dunno what angle he's working.
Maybe he'll try to get special
treatment for squealing on me.
Oh shit! He's heading straight
for the hole I'm digging.
This is bad! Damn! If he finds
it, he'll have definitive proof!
I've come too far...
Only one thing left to do.
Stay your hand.
Very smart.
Coming here where
you're unaccompanied
to dig your way out.
[KIYOSHI gulps]
[GAKUTO]
I want you to break out.
[KIYOSHI]
Hm?
And yours truly shall
provide assistance
in your daring escape.
[KIYOSHI] Hold on now.
You want to help me break out?
That's right.
[KIYOSHI] So what's the deal
with all the creepy sumo threats
you've been dishing out?
Clever signals that I would help
you abscond from this hellhole.
How was I supposed
to know that?!
And why do you want
to help me anyway?!
The upcoming student
sumo tournament--
That day is also a momentous
one for yours truly.
Specifics forthcoming.
[MEIKO]
Madam President...
May I wash your back for you?
Thank you.
You may proceed,
Madam Vice President.
[MEIKO]
Incidentally,
I've heard that the
top-ranked sumo wrestlers
have assistants who help
them wash their backs...
...as well as their derrieres.
What're you saying?!
You look at me and think about
sumo wrestlers? Am I fat?
No! It was just an
interesting factoid.
I meant nothing by it!
[MARI] I apologize for you
having to spend your weekend
overseeing the boys.
No, I don't mind that at all.
It's just... Are you
sure it's a good idea
to disobey the
Chairman's orders?
We're not supposed to
make the prisoners work
on their days off.
The Chairman's rule
granting free time
on the weekends applies
to model prisoners only.
And since their work
is behind schedule,
then they are not
model prisoners.
[MEIKO]
You couldn't be more right.
This is our duty.
When I think of how
those peeping toms are
going to be released
in half a month,
I can't sit by and do nothing.
It looks like Mari was here,
and she saw what
was on my screen.
Maybe that's why she took
the boys' free time away.
To pay me back.
Oh yes, Cruelty, thy name is...
...Woman!
But just in case,
I'd better take this home
before she finds it... too!
[JOE, ANDRE singing]
[GAKUTO] Yours truly has
a motive less fleeting
than a sumo date with
the fairer sex, my friend.
Art thou at all familiar with
"The Romance of the
Three Kingdoms"?
Well, I've heard the name
before, at the very least.
We look back to the
later Han Dynasty,
the end of the second
century, Common Era.
The emperor dies,
and the eunuchs
--known as the Ten Attendants--
--Just get to the point!
[GAKUTO]
Very well.
To make a long story short:
Quadrennially, the Three
Kingdoms figurine expo
is held in Akihabara the
same day as your sumo match!
It's quite simple, really.
Yours truly needs the
limited edition Guan Yu
and Red Hare figurines
to complete my collection!
And you had the nerve to
call my motive fleeting?
[GAKUTO]
Not even the same ballpark!
We're talking once-every-
four-years limited edition!
[KIYOSHI]
All right, I get it.
That's why you want
to break out with me.
Sir Kiyoshi, you really are
a buffoon, you know that?
We'd both be caught--
Yo! What're you guys up to?
Playing a little gomoku.
You want next?
Man, that's boring.
Count me out, bro.
Kiyoshi, it's a one-hour trip
one-way from the prison
to the gymnasium where your
sumo date will take place.
If we assume that watching
the matches takes one hour,
then we're talking a grand total
of three hours with you missing.
But if you go missing for three
hours during work detail,
the overseers will
definitely find out.
You got a point.
[GAKUTO] Simply put, it is
categorically impossible
for you to successfully
break out on your own,
and that's why I said
I'd aid your attempt.
Saturday afternoon,
during the three hours
when you'll escape to
go on your sumo date
as well as buy both Three
Kingdoms figures I want.
Yours truly will distract
the gaze of the overseers.
But how the hell are you gonna
distract them for that long?
[GAKUTO chuckles]
I have a stratagem.
Now pay attention.
[KIYOSHI]
No way!
A map of the school disguised
as a gomoku game! Badass!
Patrolling the campus
by night, are we?
Were you heading home?
Be careful--
--[thud]
--[gasps]
[MARI]
Starting tomorrow...
Those boys will learn the true
meaning of cruel and unusual.
Despite their crimes,
I want to ensure that
they don't end up becoming
the deplorable kind
of pervert that you are.
[CHAIRMAN]
Good luck with that.
Hmph.
The hole you're digging is
in the back of the
refuse shack, here.
Through which, if you
can extricate yourself,
you'll make your escape
without anyone the wiser.
The question is, how do I
keep our guards distracted
from your absence
for three hours?
The Underground Student Council
is rather observant, after all.
I appreciate the help, dude.
But from everything
you're saying,
it doesn't sound like breaking
out is even a possibility.
[GAKUTO chuckles]
Never fear, Brave Knight!
I, myself, have been called
the most resourceful
general in Nerima.
Yours truly has a
beauty of a plan
that will make the
impossible possible.
The cart's full. I'll dump it.
[MEIKO]
Permission granted.
[GAKUTO]
Dammit, Kiyoshi!
What is up?
Once again, your
dereliction of duty
has lead to me being
horrifically savaged!
Aw damn, that sucks.
My bad, dude.
[GAKUTO] After everything
I've been through, that's it?
Get on your knees, and plead
for my forgiveness, right now!
You need to calm down.
None of it matters.
It matters to me, you oaf!
Now stand ready to accept
a pummeling long overdue!
What's the big idea?
[GAKUTO]
Apologize!
[HANA] What do you jerks
think you're doing?
[BOTH gasp]
[HANA grunts]
Hya!
[MEIKO]
Care to explain?
[GAKUTO, KIYOSHI gasp]
It wasn't us!
Hana knocked the shack down!
The two of them were fighting
and crashed into the shed.
[BOTH]
Hey, she's lying!
Heads or tails, boys.
Choose one now.
--[BOTH] Uh...
--[MEIKO] I said choose one!
I choose heads.
Fine, tails.
--[GAKUTO yelps]
--[KIYOSHI screams]
[BOTH groaning]
[MEIKO] The president
suggested we increase
the intensity of your
discipline regimen.
So I brought along
this riding crop.
[GAKUTO gasps]
[muffled screaming]
[GAKUTO]
I can't breathe!
[KIYOSHI screams]
Don't squirm!
Don't make a sound!
[MEIKO grunts]
--[whipping continues]
--[KIYOSHI screaming]
They're getting it really bad.
[JOE]
Must suck. [coughs]
Yeah...
Remind me not to pick tails.
But given the options,
heads looks all right.
You two are hereby ordered to
rebuild the shed you destroyed.
[BOTH]
No way!
--[GAKUTO] Nigh unthinkable!
--[KIYOSHI] Just the two of us?!
[BOTH sob]
[BOTH chuckle]
[GAKUTO]
Well played, sir.
Back atcha!
Stage One of the plan complete.
And it couldn't
have gone better!
Cut some notches in the
support posts with the saw,
pretend to start a fight, and
bring the shed crashing down.
The perfect reason to
leave us by the escape hole
for the rest of the day.
Flawless victory.
[HANA]
What are you doing?
[BOTH gasp]
Don't give me that.
Now get your asses
in gear, Dickbags.
[KIYOSHI] So, uh... Hana,
are you planning to stay here?
Of course I'm staying.
I have to guard you two idiots.
All right, Brainiac.
Now Hana's gonna be guarding us.
You got a Plan B or something?
[chuckles]
Remember, Brave Knight,
you're with the most
resourceful general in Nerima.
[KIYOSHI] So you have something
up your sleeve for this?
[GAKUTO chokes]
I'm afraid to say,
even my strategic mind couldn't
foresee this development.
No shit?
Verily, we are screwed.
[HANA]
Standing around whispering
isn't going to repair the shed.
Hey, Kiyoshi,
come here a minute.
Why the hell am I
being singled out?
[GAKUTO] It was an honor
serving with you.
What's with the whispering?
Were you telling Four-Eyes
over there about our incident?
[KIYOSHI]
Incident?
Oh, the piss!
Shut it! Not so loud.
Yeah, my bad.
I mean it.
You tell anyone
about what happened,
I'm gonna kill you,
then off myself, capiche?
Will you stop saying that?
I told you, my lips are sealed.
[HANA] Good. Now we can
pick up where we left off.
[KIYOSHI] I don't really
need to go right now.
That's fine. You'll drink this
until you're ready to burst.
So, what the hell is it?
[HANA]
It's just a cup of tea.
Now knock it back!
[KIYOSHI sighs]
[GAKUTO]
She hasn't killed you yet?
Plan B, you got anything yet?
[GAKUTO] If you think coming
up with ideas is so easy--
Then you'd be on target,
for yours truly has the sharpest
wit in all of Nerima, Comrade.
Hell yeah! So what's up?
We are no match for Hana
in the realm of strength.
Thus, we'll have to
attack from the inside.
Good call. But how?
Isn't it obvious?
I'll take the Lady
Hana as my bride.
Huh...?
The surest way is to win
over the lady's heart
utilizing my noble
demeanor and rakish charm.
[KIYOSHI]
Wait... I'm confused.
Is this your Plan B?
[GAKUTO]
Indubitably!
According to my
proficient profiling,
a young maiden who likes clover,
puts jorts on under her skirt,
and wears her hair
in straight bangs...
...is without a doubt,
a history fangirl.
Hence, I shall use
our shared passion
as a foolproof way to
curry favor with her.
[KIYOSHI]
Okay. So what's Plan C?
We haven't the time.
I must away.
Now wish me luck.
Don't go!
You're gonna get killed!
--[GAKUTO] Lady Hana.
--[HANA grunts]
In times of strife and trouble,
comes a tale from China at the
dawning of the third century.
Zhao Yun, carrying the
son of lord Liu Bei,
outstripped a force of
a hundred thousand--
--[smack]
--[GAKUTO groans]
[HANA] Don't go spitting that
static at me, Nerdlinger!
[GAKUTO] I am stunned by
this most unexpected turn.
I'm pretty sure you're the
only one who didn't expect
--that to happen.
--[GAKUTO wheezes]
[retches]
All doors are now closed to us!
My dream is dead,
rotting in the sun!
[KIYOSHI] Damn it, I refuse
to give up so easily!
Uh-- Kiyoshi, have you a plan
involving that
little dance step?
Dance step?
No, nothing like that.
Then that can only mean...
How timely!
Allow me to handle this!
[KIYOSHI]
Uh--
[GAKUTO] My friend, Kiyoshi says
he need to use the lavatory!
Requesting permission!
[KIYOSHI]
What the hell, man? Shut up!
Sir Kiyoshi, don't act
like such a child!
There is naught to be
ashamed of, Friend.
Nope, I'm just fine!
Ol' Gakuto must've
gotten his wires crossed.
Go ahead.
--[KIYOSHI whimpers]
--Holding it in
is not conducive
to your well-being.
You're only making
things worse, dumb ass!
Stop stalling,
and get ready to pee!
[gasps] Damn...
[KIYOSHI] Of course, she's
following me like a shadow.
[HANA gasps]
[pants]
--[HANA grunts]
--[KIYOSHI yelps]
Now, good to go.
[KIYOSHI]
What're you talking about?!
You shouldn't be in here!
I'll leave after
we're fair and square
--on watching each other pee!
--[KIYOSHI] I mean it.
--You don't know
--This is really awkward!
--when to quit, do you?
--Stop!
--Let's go already!
--I'm about to burst!
[HANA] What did I tell you?
--Fair is fair!
--Come on! Stop pressing there!
--[HANA growls]
--[KIYOSHI hisses]
[BOTH grunt]
--I'll get it.
--[KIYOSHI whimpers]
Keep still!
[pants]
[KIYOSHI yelps]
No!
Stop that!
--Let me go!
--[HANA] Quit squirming!
[HANA yelps]
[gasps]
[HANA grunts]
[KIYOSHI moans]
[HANA screams]
[MEIKO gasps]
[MEIKO]
Hana! What happened?!
Madam Vice President...
Is that...?!
I'm so sorry.
I had a little accident.
[giggles]
[MEIKO]
Hana! Pull it together!
[KIYOSHI panting]
Hana isn't feeling well,
so she'll be taking the
rest of the day off.
Good work, Kiyoshi.
What manner of sneak attack
did you unleash on her?
Uh... I didn't do anything.
Mum's the word,
I understand.
But whatever you did, our plan
can now proceed uninhibited!
Hey, Four-Eyes! No one gave
you permission to speak!
--[whip cracks]
--[GAKUTO groans]
[KIYOSHI]
Next time on Prison School:
"A Mighty Spurt"