A world reliant on
Trapars for survival.
Doomed from the start.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
Are you happy, Nakamura?
Let me go.
Why are you guys here?
Are you happy?!
Answer the question!
This what you hoped for?
I wasn't a fan of how reliant
on the Trapar business
Okinawa became,
but I never wanted
something like this to happen.
What did independence
mean to them?
Simply not becoming Japanese?
And don't tell me they were
hoping to ally with the Secrets,
or go on some kind of
crusade to protect the Scubs.
It was a toy to them.
Independence was
something they could gain
if only they threw
enough tantrums.
Uh, Gazelle.
You know.
That sounds a lot like you.
Shut up!
It isn't the same thing.
Look, I don't know
how the military works.
But in the business world,
we don't lay down arms just
because a common enemy appears.
That would be ridiculous.
We can sway public opinion
with a PR campaign
that depicts Truth as
the Secrets' accomplice.
A truce is ridiculous, huh?
You may not know this about us,
but soldiers are the
biggest romantics there are.
We fight when we must
but nobody wants peace in
this world more than we do.
The experiment with the Coral
Carriers ran into some problems,
I know, but is that
a good enough reason
to surrender to the Secrets?
You don't get it, Stanley.
You really don't.
Why are you so surprised?
Is it really so strange
that negotiations
with the US government
went smoothly?
Secret, I don't understand.
We thought you were
destroyed in the battle.
I cannot be so easily killed.
My being has already
assimilated as Georg.
There are countless
iterations of me.
No ammo?!
Ao!
Damn.
Fleur?!
What are you doing, Ao?
Return fire, already!
Is firing this thing
my only choice?
Was that--?
You take care of Truth.
I'm going to find out
who the new arrival is.
What the hell are
you doing here?
And what do you want with Ao?!
Elena!
Oh, no!
Noooo!
At least tell me why, Naru!
Why are you taking his side?!
Because you have no
chance of defeating Truth.
For the same reason you
are no match for my Nirvash.
You have no Archetype.
So what?
What the hell is
this Archetype thing?
Whoa, those are Trapars.
This Nirvash is a living being.
Inside him there
is an Archetype.
Archetypes are
actually Coralians.
Yours is a machine.
Nothing more.
Naru!
A new era is coming, Ao.
One heralded by Scub Corals.
In this new world,
nobody will ever suffer.
You see?
That's the future we
should be fighting for.
It's the Scub Corals
versus the Secrets.
Does it have to
be one or the other?
Fleur! Behind us!
What is it?
Wait, is that?
No way.
I thought Harlequin had switched
their allegiance to
the Allied Forces!
The Allied Forces
have entered into peace
negotiations with Japan.
Coral Carriers are
being hospitalized
with hyper-acute symptoms.
A number of countries are
responding to this threat
by making the area around
Coral plants off-limits.
Coral Carriers?
Like Naru?!
What's going to happen to her?
We think she may
be in danger, as well.
You, too, Ao.
No!
Wait, Ao!
Danger or not,
we have no choice.
The world is depending on you.
If Ao comes out
of this the winner.
If Nirvash defeats Truth,
the world will have
to acknowledge that
we were in the right,
and our exile would be over.
It may be no more
than a fleeting peace.
But even that is
better than war.
The year 1096.
The First Crusade is launched.
The year 1206.
I understand how this must feel.
To be rejected by everyone,
even the Secrets.
Only I know the truth about you.
Only I know who you really are.
I know because
you're the same as me.
Your life is preserved
by the Scub Corals.
You began as a Secret, but
the Scubs got into your body.
They became an
inseparable part of your being.
Hey, do you remember?
All the way back to
when we first met?
Each of us was able
to breathe more easily
because of the Trapars
the other exhaled.
Since that discovery,
we've dedicated ourselves
to fighting for the Scubs.
Truth.
The powers you have
as a Secret will help us.
You don't need to deny them.
The year 1911.
The Xinhai Rebellion
erupts in China.
The year 1945.
The Manhattan Project.
Hiroshima.
Nagasaki.
That is the correct
version of history.
That is the world
that should be.
And there!
No!
No! No! No!
You're wrong, Naru!
Ao?
Hey!
Everything's fine now!
Truth is on the
side of the Scubs.
You have to get away from there!
Hurry!
Truth.
Why are you doing this?
The world is wrong.
Mankind harnesses nuclear
power in the name of progress.
The Soviet Union becomes Russia;
the US uses its military
might to become a superpower,
and Okinawa never declares
independence from Japan.
That is the correct world.
It is a world in which
there are no Scub Corals.
Nor are there Secrets.
As for me, I am
neither of those things.
This power that I wield.
It is the power of the world as
it was meant to be!
Naru!
Naru!!
Naru.
Damn you!
Come.
Ao Fukai!
The Trapar concentration is
rising rapidly.
Rajkumar.
Take Naru and get out of here.
As far as you can go!
Is Ao going to be okay?
You said it affects Coral
Carriers.
You did it for yourself.
If you can't change something,
then you should accept it.
Are you going to answer her?
You are the all-knowing Mom
Hannah, aren't you?
No, don't do this.
Liu.
Lerato.
Do it, Ao!
Fire the gun!
It's okay.
We were prepared for this.
We've been waiting.
I can't shoot!
If I fire, you'll both be blown
to bits along with him!
Truth destroyed the
Poseidon and its crew.
He won't get away with it.
And don't forget.
He almost killed someone
you care about, too.
I know.
But I can't sacrifice
you so easily.
How can I open
fire on my friends?!
You really are a weakling.
Liu!
Lerato!
What's wrong, are you scared?
Are you afraid of
learning the truth?
You are so pathetic.
I can't let someone as weak as
you wield so much power!
First I thought the
Secrets were our enemy.
But it turns out they weren't.
After that, the Scubs
were the bad guys.
And now Truth.
He's the evil that
must be fought.
Is all of this just me?
Is that what's going on?
All this time.
Have I just been
looking for an enemy?!
You're not a Secret, and
you're not a Scub, either.
So you're not allowed
to exist in this world.
Seriously?!
Come on.
Who made that rule?
I get that you don't
feel like you belong here.
But that doesn't
make the world wrong,
and it doesn't give you
the right to destroy it!
Do you hear me?
What does this even change?
Nothing.
Nothing!
Like I said before,
you're too weak.
I hate repeating myself.
You're still--?
However it happened,
I learned of the correct world.
I can't undo that.
I cannot erase the
knowledge from my mind.
So that's what he wants.
To vanish.
Leave the world where
he can't truly exist.
The world where
he doesn't belong.
The correct world.
The one and only truth.
What does that even mean?
How much are you going
to sacrifice on this
impossible quest?!
Will you die?
Or will it happen again?
Will I lose more friends when
history rewrites itself?!
What's going on here?
Great, Ao!
You did it!
Did what?
You used the Quartz Gun
to take that guy out!
That guy?
You mean.
I got Truth?
Truth?
What are you talking about?
The Coral Relic IFO
that the Allied Forces
had stolen has been
confirmed destroyed.
Remainder gauge
is at twenty-three.
I did it, then.
This is a new
version of the world.
Because I fired the
gun a second time.
It's finally over.
We've won.
Mankind won't have
to fight anymore, now.
Divided between
Scubs and Secrets.
We have word on Naru Arata.
Her Nirvash has
been incapacitated.
Naru!
Is that you?
After all this,
that' s what you say?
I'm sorry.
About everything with Truth.
Truth?!
Is that your new girlfriend?
Weird name.
Come on.
Go ahead and
finish me off, already.
It'll be your final shot, right?
What are you talking about?
The Quartz Gun works
by releasing the energy
in the Quartz themselves.
It'll be used up
before much longer.
If you won't.
I will.
What happened?
I shot her.
Naru!
Where's Naru?
What have you done
with my daughter?!
She's in the
hospital on this base.
Some military personnel attacked
the Generation Bleu headquarters
and stole an IFO prototype.
Eco-terrorists
were also involved
in trying to protect the Scubs.
Both groups will be
placed under investigation.
Why?
That's not fair!
The US put them up
to it in the first place!
And now.
The entire world
finally understands
that Scub Corals are dangerous.
However, we're getting a reading
from inside Naru that's
the same as it is for Quartz.
Hey, shouldn't you
be back on duty?
No, man.
I'm still not healed up.
When I fired it the first
time, it rewrote history so that
the Coral plant in Norway
never existed to begin with,
and Team Goldilocks disappeared.
The second time I fired it,
it made it so that Truth
never existed to begin with.
The Allies stole the Canon
and tried to fight against the
Secrets alongside Naru's people.
That's how things have
been rewritten this time.
They'll be reconsidering
the Trapar business now.
What will happen to the Quartz?
If there are Quartz inside
Naru and people like her, then--
What was that?!
Keep an eye on Naru for me!
Why, what's happening?
Oh, it's nothing.
We won't have to make
someone the enemy anymore!
Come on.
What's with the long face?
The world's the way you
always wanted it, right?
Yeah, I guess.
But in the end, Japan
is still just a minor power.
Hey, look.
He's sure running fast.
I wonder if something's up.
The Okinawa Coral plant?
Is something happening there?
Its Quartz is scheduled
to be removed tomorrow.
What's going on?
Could it be a Secret?
It's him.
Yes.
He has come.
Who is this guy?
Hey, Soga!
No Secrets should be
appearing anymore, right?
That's the deal.
But this craft isn't
from any country I know.
Sure enough, a Scub Coral.
As I thought, they're here, too.
Ao!
What happened out there?
Are you okay?
We should head out, too, Chief.
It's Eureka!
This is her?
He's here.
The remainder gauge
is at forty-eight.
The Quartz went
and did it again.
Damn it!
At close range like this.
A man.
Who is that?
Whoa, what?!
No way.
How's he know about that?
Did you tamper
with the Nirvash Neo?
What have you done
with the real pilot?
Well?!
This Nirvash Neo was originally
piloted by a woman named Eureka.
Those eyes!
Who are you?
Ao! Do you copy me?
Eureka has appeared
onboard the Triton.
My mom?!
I see.
So you're.
Roger that.
I'll work something
out here and be right--
It's time to go, Ao.
I have to see Eureka.
I want you to take me to her.
You disappeared from Okinawa,
along with the giant Quartz.
And you've just been
wandering randomly
through time ever since then.
Isn't that right?
I can't seem to remain in the
same time or place for long.
It's jumbled.
I come back after a few days
and find years have passed.
Hey!
Wait.
I'm sorry.
This guy undid the
lock on his own, and I--
Eureka.
It's you!
Don't!
Stay there.
You can't touch me, anyway.
Eureka.
Did you have no other choice?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm the one who
should apologize.
So, you met Ao.
He's a good boy.
Very energetic.
And more honest than you!
What you've been
looking for is here.
Ao has it.
It was the same thing
that summoned you here.
Wait, Mom!
As for you, are you
who I think you are?
You can't be.
That's right.
My name is Renton Thurston.
And I am Eureka's husband.
To be continued.
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
The blue planet the
parents strive to protect.
The blue skies
the child strives to fly.
With eyes wide open,
Ao has chosen his final path.
But what waits for him beyond
the brilliant pillar of light?
Eureka Seven AO, Final episode:
"The Door into Summer."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.