What are you talking about, man?
She's totally into you!
I don't know if your tenacity
is a credit to you, Nakamura.
Your bid to get us the
Mark I four months ago
ended in abject failure.
The entire IFO Defense Project
is set to be scrapped.
We've been marginalized on the
world stage for long enough.
And our dealings
with the Allied Nations
could go sour at any time.
If we can get our hands
on something this powerful.
Japan could emerge from the
doldrums as a modern juggernaut!
Maybe so but on the other hand.
Japan has only made it this far
because we've avoided your
brand of military posturing.
Stirring things up like that
just makes the people nervous.
Not to mention that
it's a PR nightmare.
You need to keep in mind that
anything Scub-related is going
to be an extremely hard sell
to your fellow Japanese.
I'm trying to fix our nation,
and the Ministry of Finance
can't be bothered to help?
Sir, it will work.
Please, get out of the car.
So they didn't go for it.
If they have their way,
nothing around here
will ever change.
I'm thinking of our future.
Why the hell can't
they see that?
So be it!
The cowards can rubber-stamp it
after we've succeeded
in our goal.
I'm forwarding you the data
that the Firecracker
people sent me.
Here it comes.
Are you positive we can
trust this information?
I mean, they're
cyber-terrorists, aren't they?
Getting into bed
with people like this.
It just seems risky that's all.
They probably just
feel sorry for Japan.
We were put under a
global intelligence blockade.
You should be glad
they're giving us a leg up.
This is intel the U.S.
military has been
stonewalling us on forever.
How'd they get it?
I don't know.
And honestly, I don't care.
We need to make the
most of this moment,
for the sake of Japan.
This may be the only
chance our generation gets.
Come on.
It's time to get training.
You've been slacking
off for long enough.
This is more fun
than running maneuvers.
Come on in, the water's fine.
Laps in the pool aren't
going to help me fly better.
Oh, right, a thousand pardons.
I forgot someone's in a hurry
to rescue his girlfriend.
Naru is not my girlfriend, okay?
Of course.
My mistake.
What've you got
against pools, Ao?
Did you eat a weird
fruit and now you sink?
What're you talking about?
Scandalous!
So you don't know how to swim?
Well!
If I ever catch you drowning,
you're on your own!
Get real.
I've been swimming
since I was a kid.
We just got a heads-up
from someone in Japan's
Ministry of Self-Defense.
You have folks in the
Japanese government?
Got to admit, I'm impressed.
There's no way of knowing
if it'll actually work
but it seems they intend
to run an experiment
to artificially
create a Scub Burst.
We can't allow Japan
to have a Coral plant.
Maintaining global
equilibrium dictates
that we prevent that
by any means possible.
Enter Team Pied Piper.
Our company's wunderkind when it
comes to getting the job done.
I assume that means
you're ordering us
to go in there and take
out the Quartz on the sly?
Please, Ivica.
Why would you put words
in my mouth like that?
What?
Hurry it up, kids.
Well that's the long and
the short of it, at least.
I'll instruct the
more-than-capable
on-site staff to pass
along all the details.
I understand.
I figured I'd see
the sites, you know?
Yeah, so my mom got
remarried to some Swiss guy.
And being around all that,
Swiss gave me this weird kind
of Okinawan accent, see.
So, this is Japan, huh?
To think than an Okinawan
like me would have
to come by way of Switzerland
just to get in here.
The customs
agents are dinosaurs.
It felt like I was in a museum.
What do we do now?
Now we get our asses on a train.
Time to get our Shinkansen on.
I guess Tokyo used to
be on the other side
of that thing, back in the day.
Yup, that Scub Burst 70 years
ago was the knockout punch
to post-war Japan's
rebuilding and recovery efforts.
Like things weren't bad before.
Light emission confirmed.
Water temperature
has begun to rise.
The broken Quartz seems
to be beginning to fuse.
Good!
The reactivation
has been a success!
This is a momentous day.
Japan will finally
have a Coral plant.
With all due respect, sir,
this is just the first
part of the operation.
I believe he's trying to tell
you that the fun's not over.
They're all saying the
test was a big success.
Light emission confirmed.
It matches the spectral
signature of Quartz.
Has the Scub manifested yet?
Patch me through to
Team Pied Piper, now.
Round and round you go, Noa!
Hey Rebecka, how long do we have
to sit out here doing nothing?
You'll sit until we
give you the green light.
You'll approach by sea
when the time comes,
so waiting there makes sense.
Rebecka failed to
mention that we are on
the very edge of Japan's
territorial waters.
This is as close as we can be
without its armed
forces engaging us.
The submarines
patrolling their waters
are likely armed with...
Anyway.
Looks like their eggheads
pulled off the test.
They just made a
Scub Burst, so get ready.
Secret incoming, Chief.
What the hell was that?
That's a Secret manifesting!
Down in the water,
near the test site!
Remain calm!
We will now commence
with capturing the Secret!
Check all of the
equipment at the test site!
What?
Are you mad?
Why should our needs
be filled by IFOs
when the weapons carried
by the Secrets themselves
pack so much of a punch?
Not to worry.
It'll head straight to the
Coral just like always.
We'll be perfectly safe
here in the command center.
The Kazusa has taken
extensive damage to her hull!
Your Secret just
tore the hell out of it!
Huh?
So uh fellas, I think that
thing's ignoring the bait.
Your theater for this mission
will be the southern
section of Tokyo Bay,
near the submarine canyon that
connects to the Sagami Trough.
The waters of
Tokyo Bay are generally
no deeper than 20 meters,
but this mission will take you
to depths far exceeding that.
At times, you'll be maneuvering
500 meters below the surface.
The water pressure
at such depths
could possibly damage
portions of your IFO,
beginning with the
outer extremities
and working inward to the frame.
Your IFOs should be kept
in their flight configurations
until such time as
environmental conditions
no longer prove injurious.
Then you may switch
to their humanoid
configurations forthwith.
In other words,
don't transform too soon
or your craft will implode.
You have got to be kidding me!
I hope the Secret's
polite enough to sit back
and let us get ready to fight.
I don't get it, Chief.
If underwater is so dangerous,
why don't we just surface and
fight the Secret up there?
Eliminating the Secret is not
the objective of this operation.
You'll be dealing
directly with the Scub.
Huh?
Getting the Quartz outta the
Scub is priority number one.
The Secret is raising hell
towards the JAF base right now,
which helps us out.
You'll slip in, right to
the Scub Coral's point
of occurrence,
and eighty-six it.
Then it's simply a matter
of grabbing the Quartz
and returning to headquarters.
Roger that Chief.
So, what is this
"Quartz" thing, anyway?
A crystal found in every Scub.
They're the reason the Secrets
make a beeline for the Coral.
Is that the stuff
we were transporting
when everything went to hell?
Yeah.
The Secret goes for the Quartz
like a bloodhound at least
that's what the Generation Bleu
guys think, anyway.
And all that Quartz they take?
It's sitting pretty inside some
closet back at headquarters.
But, why would they keep it?
Damned if I know.
Wait, are you telling me
that collecting the Quartz
has been Generation
Bleu's top priority
on all of the missions
it's been running?
It's our top priority now.
Look, Japan's playing with
fire with these experiments.
We got to deprive them of
that Scub for the greater good.
What about saving people?
Once the three of you
have retrieved the Quartz,
the Scub Burst will stabilize.
The faster you do that,
the fewer casualties.
Oh, how caring of you.
Ao, don't waste your breath.
They've all forgotten these
are real people we're
talking about here.
Yup-yup, war is a
hard business, guys.
Look, we can't let the
Japanese get their hands
on a homegrown source of Trapar.
As a native Okinawan,
I would think you'd understand
that fact better than anyone.
People are dying, dammit!
I don't care if they're
Japanese or Okinawan or what!
I'm not going to
sit back and watch!
Ao!
Back in formation!
Alleluia and Kyrie you're
both still on Quartz retrieval.
Roger that, Chief.
We're on it.
Forget eavesdropping
on them from far away!
Let's just barge onto their base
while everybody
there's all distracted!
That's a great
idea, really, man!
But don't kill us on the way!
Land-based cars are for geezers!
How does anybody drive them?
An explosion at the port.
Of course!
The Secret must be down
in the water over there!
Son of a!
That was the
Mark I that flew by!
What's going on?
Why did you stop?
Not to split hairs,
but that was my Nirvash.
Who, are you?
You employed my
intel to good effect.
I'm very grateful.
So you're my
contact in Firecracker?
Call me Truth.
I insist.
Stupid ground cars!
My head's killing me!
You're the guy who
blew up the john.
This crazy crap going on.
You did all this, huh?
Hey, Chief!
This isn't Scub Coral!
It's Damaged Quartz.
How'd they get their
hands on so much of it?
And what's that
light it's giving off?
The fragments have
been reactivated.
Damaged Quartz comprises the
empty shell of a Scub Burst.
Given the amount
we're seeing here,
and the fact it's in Japan,
one can assume this is--
This is what remains
of the post-war burst
from 70 years ago.
If you gather enough
Damaged Quartz
in one place the
results are explosive.
I hoped that a
Secret would manifest,
to kick off the festivities.
Mission accomplished.
So your game is fake quartz?
Then all along, it was you!
Where'd it go?
Let me go, dammit!
This is bad!
The water pressure's going to
crush Nirvash like a tin can!
I lost it!
Show yourself,
you sneaky bastard!
Next time, just ask me for help!
Fair enough!
Fleur!
Okay!
How do you track this thing?
That's it?
Now I get it!
What are you doing?
Do I look like a Secret?
Bring it!
But I won!
I'm still going to die?
Not like this!
What?
So much for that
tough talk at the pool
about letting him drown.
I forgot.
Answer me.
Were you the person who hired
us to transport that stuff?
You demand the truth of me,
but you can't even see it.
The hell I can't!
The truth reveals
itself only to those
who are courageous
enough to embrace it.
Hey, how'd you know the Secret
was drawn to the
Trapars in our IFOs?
I just saw it.
What was it like
when you saw it?
Did it feel like a
super-power or what?
That is so cool!
It's like your eyes are magical!
I tried to see an
answer, and then I did.
I can't really
put it into words.
I trust you've
learned your lesson?
Japan has no need for your
brand of military recklessness.
We may be poor, but at
least we're still in one piece.
You again!
Whose side are you on?
Are you for me or against me?
Why content yourself
with changing this country?
Why aim so small?
When the truth of the matter
is there's a whole
planet out there?
To be continued!
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Mankind makes a choice
amid the canyons of America
one that prompts a dire
evolution in the Secret
and leads to much
shedding of innocent blood.
With their backs
against the wall,
will Ao and the others be
able to rise to the occasion?
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 10:
"the pied piper of Hamelin."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.