Ooh!
That's totally awesome!
Sorry, you are?
Elena Peoples.
The color of your
hair is really pretty.
Kind of like blue quartz.
Sign a contract with us,
so you can become a
member of Pied Piper, too!
Huh?
Don't mind her.
She's always like this.
You get used to it.
I'll be with you as soon
as I finish this video.
Oh, wow!
That's Generation Bleu
Headquarters?
Incredible!
But why's it shaped like that?
Nifty, isn't it?
It's made from
all kinds of things
that were found in Scub Coral.
This is control.
Locking onto aircraft.
This is Triton.
Aircraft locked in.
Guiding aircraft.
Transfer to Deck Three.
Roger that.
Connecting all systems.
Systems connected.
Starting check on all systems.
Confirmed: systems
check started.
Triton systems check complete.
Triton shutting down engines.
Shutting down now.
Transfer to Deck Three complete.
All engineers,
begin maintenance work.
Again, transfer of Triton
to Deck Three is complete.
All engineers,
begin maintenance work.
So, are you the
pilot of the Mark I?
I'm Alexander Boyle, the
technical director at HQ.
I'd like a word with you.
I'm so sorry
I wrecked the left arm!
That's fine.
I should be able to have
the replacement parts
tuned up in just
under four hours...
From what I can see, it has
a tendency to over-steer, yes?
Huh? Oh, uh...
I'll handle it on my end.
Can I get all department
chiefs here, please?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ao.
This way!
But what about Noa?
I've left Rebecka
to handle things.
It'll be fine.
Raising the Triton!
So soft and warm!
You saved us!
Stowaways.
Holds on, are you
guys from Okinawa?
I would like to speak
to whoever's in
charge here, please!
Pardon?
I would like to talk to
your boss immediately!
All right then.
This matches up with the data
Fleur brought back, as well.
It's similar,
but there is one spot
on his genome map that
differs greatly from ours.
Which is?
The retina.
The part of the eye most
responsible for vision.
His has an abnormality?
The range of visible
light may be larger for him.
Our eyes cannot
perceive infrared
and ultraviolet light, but
electromagnetic radiation
of that sort may
be visible to him.
If so, what does the
world look like to him?
Is it different from
how we see it?
I wish I could hear
what they're saying.
Nothing irregular.
You're the very picture of an
ordinary twelve-year-old boy.
I'm all normal?
But what about this crazy hair?
It's nothing.
Simply an idiosyncrasy,
just like your mother's.
Right!
So, want to tell
me about this place?
Excuse me?
You should be more respectful.
Of course, ma'am.
Much better.
This is our Swiss Headquarters.
We have several thousand
employees working here.
Right now, we're at the
very top of the tower,
where the IFO teams are based.
The structure continues
to sprawl underground, too.
All in all, HQ is
about as big as a city.
Now, just past here
are the living quarters.
We've got a brand
new arrival with us.
All right then has
he been issued an ID?
Oh!
I completely forgot
to ask the chief.
You can let it slide,
though, right?
Sorry.
Rules are rules.
Oh, come on!
Our next item.
A strange intruder.
This odd trespasser was
sighted on company grounds.
Thought to be a
three-toed sloth,
the creature caused
a brief disturbance
and then disappeared after
this photo was taken.
I can't let anything
happen to her!
Naru would never forgive me.
Hmm.
You care about her a lot.
So, what is she?
Your girlfriend?
It's nothing like that.
We're friends, that's all.
I need to find Noa!
Come back!
You've come a long way.
Welcome.
My name is Christophe Blanc.
I'm the company president.
I'm told you have interesting
information for me.
Han.
We were filming when one
of your IFOs extracted
something from the Scub.
The Scub instantly
turned gray and receded.
It makes you wonder:
what is this world
famous rescue group up to?
I bet it isn't common knowledge.
Our tasks also
include carrying out
scholarly research
on Scub Coral.
Nothing mysterious
about that, is there?
That's not the interesting part.
That glowing stuff
you guys extracted--
I've seen something
like it before.
See, a similar substance
showed up packed inside my FP.
It seemed like the Scub
was making a move for it.
And then, right after,
the Burst began.
So, I have to ask.
Is Generation Bleu really
the charitable organization
the world thinks you are?
I see.
Very well.
You have my full attention.
No luck!
Hey Elena?
Where did?
So sorry I got distracted.
I will look high and
low for your creature.
Very believable.
Ooh!
Is that a sloth?
Where'd you come
from little one?
Here, have a snack!
Look at that!
I think she likes it!
Hold still.
All that fur!
Aww!
Huh?
Is something wrong?
What are you doing, Maev?
It's just a little fur!
Hush, Chloe.
Hold real still, Maggie!
Goldilocks.
They're another
IFO team, just like us.
They've got a different
vibe going, though.
Hey, where's the Okinawan
kid who was with you?
Look! She's Pied Piper!
Rebecka, who are these guys?
They're uh, stowaways.
What?
Did you have to
put it like that?
Well, see you later, Fleur.
Bye!
Stowaways... Huh?
So, Rebecka, last name?
Why should I tell you that?
Well we're gonna be
colleagues, aren't we?
The president's gone
too far this time.
What's wrong?
A Scub Burst, most likely.
Oh yeah, I heard about you!
Ao Fukai.
Is it true, then?
You beat a Secret
inside the ZOA?
No way!
Didn't you know, Sis?
They say he got
the Mark I working.
Seriously?
Wow, I thought that thing
was out of commission.
None for you.
All of it is for Chloe.
You can eat all of that?
But, you?
She was about to pout and say,
"Don't tell me I'm too little."
Was not!
You may be the ace team,
but that doesn't change the
fact that we have seniority!
Hold still!
You got some on your nose.
Anyway, it's nice to meet you.
I'm sure you'll have
questions about company life.
Feel free to ask anything.
I'll do that, thanks.
Your sloth is sweet.
But we've got somebody
even sweeter here!
Jolly old Bruno!
Yah!
Hey!
No hugs for Pied Piper!
It's not like I asked for this.
Welcome to the Generation
Bleu headquarters!
Now, son.
Turn around and go back
home as soon as you can.
If you stay here you're
sure to bring sorrow
to the people you care
most about in this world.
Well, then!
Shall we go?
What's going on?
Is their team being mobilized?
What do we do?
For now we don't do anything.
Why?
Because the orders were
only for Goldilocks, that's why.
Not for Pied Piper.
It's huge.
Any sign of a G-Monster?
They're called "Secrets."
And no, none so far.
However, there is a
medium-sized hurricane
closing in on the location.
A typhoon, huh?
It's you boys!
Have you not met?
These gentlemen are going to be
joining us here at
Generation Bleu.
I'm Gazelle.
These two here
are Pippo and Han.
It's our duty as
leaders in society, right?
Providing opportunity
for the young.
I don not condone
indiscriminately
involving civilians like this.
The Medon has now entered
a suborbital flight path.
Okay, we're here.
Wouldn't this have been easier
if I'd gotten my ID first?
Oh, quit worrying!
It's fine!
It's time for a nice,
relaxing shower!
You got to love fan service!
Noa, he said I was
going to hurt people.
People I love.
Why?
Why are you here?
Jeez, this is a women's dorm.
Oh, I, uh!
Elena!
Really!
I thought I told you
to be more respectful!
Tell me Ao, what is
it you came here to do?
I'm sorry, but it...
it's just, well...
And the Secret?
Negative.
We have yet to receive
word of its appearance.
Cases like this
are exceedingly rare.
According to the records--
Let's see, there's Tashkent
in nineteen fifty-two.
Then Quebec in sixty-seven.
And the Strait of Malacca
in nineteen ninety-five.
There are plenty of instances
where it took some time
for the Secret to appear.
So don't let your guards down!
If that's the case, why don't
we just collect the Quartz now?
Chloe, girls!
I don't want you
getting too far ahead!
Don't worry.
We know how to handle it.
We'll make sure
she stays close by.
That's right.
Maev and I have a
close eye on Chloe.
Seriously Bruno you can relax.
Chloe isn't a child!
She may look a little
small for an eleven-year-old.
But Chloe's a big girl now!
What's that?
An Eisenhower?
What are the Allied
Forces doing here?
That's a violation of airspace!
Maggie!
It can't be!
A Secret?
The Credo?
We have her location!
No response!
Request reinforcements!
And do it now!
The Secret disguised
itself as a hurricane?
It was spinning quickly
thus kicking up water
from the ocean,
interfering with our visual.
It's traveling within one
hundred kilometers of the Scub.
Off the shore of Point Gallinas.
Stanley.
To be safe, team Pied Piper
will prepare to mobilize.
You can't be serious!
Our kids just got back!
If it was us out there,
we'd have Kyrie standing by
above the clouds,
don't you think?
So, uh, what should I be doing?
Don't know.
Are you going to
start flying with us Ao?
I thought so.
They probably just
wanted the Mark I.
It is something our
president would do.
Those're fighting words!
Come on, we both know
that's how he operates.
But, then...
what was the point in
coming all this way?
Hold on!
Where are you going?
I'll ask you again.
Just once, what is it
you came here to do?
Requiem, Gloria, Credo!
Why are none of
them are responding?
Medon come in!
We're going to rescue our IFOs!
Requesting urgent
reinforcements!
Right!
Pied Piper,
move out immediately!
Sorry!
And where do you
think you're going?
This is your uniform.
Go on and get changed.
Hold on a sec.
Hurry.
Right.
Take this.
What is it?
It's the key to the Nirvash.
Excuse me!
The Nirvash is tuned up
and ready to go,
including the left arm.
Sorry, but don't people
call it the Mark I?
Those are the
president's orders.
That's how it's been registered
with the company:
As the "Nirvash."
You sure there
isn't anything else
you should say to the new kid?
You mean Ao?
He came on board of
his own free will.
There's no need to.
Triton.
Stand by on hangar deck.
Opening catapult gate.
Transferring Triton
to catapult deck.
Catapult deck, all clear.
Triton set on catapult.
Ready to take off.
Course is all clear.
Control's given
permission for takeoff.
Engine output at max.
We're ready to take off.
Let's launch the Triton!
To be continued!
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Still unsure of
where he truly belongs,
Ao takes to the
air with Nirvash.
On the other side of tragedy,
there may yet be triumph.
And beyond the
light's long reach,
is the shadow of one
who seeks the truth.
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 6:
"noblesse oblige."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.