Hey, look!
There!
It's a little kid!
Right in the middle of the road!
Bang!
What the hell?
Who are you?
Who is that?
Contact HQ!
A terrorist?
Who am I, you ask?
A very good question.
Let me see.
From this moment on...
my name is Truth.
Where's the target?
Sir, he's one floor below us!
He'll be here any second!
An intruder?
Whoever he is,
I'm sure our security teams
are up to the challenge.
But just to be safe,
the two of you sit tight.
What?
I got to stay here with him?
I sent someone
to escort you back.
If being here's so terrible,
why'd you come barging in?
Oh yeah?
Well if I hadn't
been here to help,
you wouldn't have been
able to take this call!
Yeah, I could of!
I'm assuming Elena
isn't with you?
Huh?
No why?
I've been trying to reach her
on the emergency frequency,
but nothing so far.
Into my civilian duds!
This is pretty comfy and
I am covered up, technically.
Wonder if I could go out
and about like this?
I Better not.
Think of the nosebleeds.
You're telling me we were
totally blindsided by this?
As we're seeing out there,
the element of surprise makes
for a powerful advantage.
According to witnesses,
this damage is being
caused by a single man.
How is this possible?
There have been casualties
among the security guards.
This is nothing we
were prepared for.
I wonder if Langley
has a hand in this.
What've you heard?
Nothing.
And the US military isn't
involved, as near as I can tell.
Well, take care of the data,
move the IFOs, and see that
the pilots are all secured.
Worst-case scenario, we destroy
it and scuttle the base.
What about him?
I wouldn't worry
Blanc with the details.
I suggest you hurry.
Attention, employees!
An intruder is on the
loose within the facility.
If you see him, do not engage!
I repeat, do not engage!
He is armed and dangerous!
Multiple fatalities
have been reported.
You're hard to find, Miller.
You know that?
They just told us the
gig tonight's a no-go.
Come on, we should
get to the shelter ASAP.
Totally!
You guys go on ahead, I'll be
right behind you in a second.
Hurry it up!
Oh man.
He's right around
the corner from here.
Don't move!
We've got you outnumbered!
Identify yourself!
Excuse me,
but are you Miss Miller?
Huh?
I'm a real big fan of your work.
Thanks.
Last chance!
If you want to live,
you're going to tell
us who the hell you are!
You want a name?
You may refer to me as Truth.
It's your lucky day.
My concert is about to begin.
What're you waiting for?
Shoot!
Shoot him!
And who are you, pray tell?
People call me, Miller.
Hmm, "Miller"?
What do you do in
this cozy little cage?
I'm a singer in a band.
So I see.
And you appear
to sing, the truth.
The intruder's
objective is the--
I repeat his objective
is the Coral Relic.
He'll be headed for the basement
to try and make off with it!
Sorry, guys.
He wants something, all right.
And that ain't it.
Service on all
Central Shaft Cable Lines
has been suspended
until further notice.
Service on all
Central Shaft Cable Lines
has been suspended
until further notice.
What day is it?
They were saying something
about an emergency.
I think it's down below, but.
This is HQ for
Generation Bleu, man.
We're safe as can be.
I'm going to hurl!
Meets a pretty girl
and goes on a bender.
Nice!
I thought it was
because we got hired on.
Glad Ao wasn't the only one
who got some love from them.
Shut up!
Ah, what the hell?
Hold on!
You busted straight
through that wall!
I'm looking for the truth.
No wall can withstand me!
What kind of "truth"?
He's over here!
Hey!
Watch it!
Wait!
So he's heading
to higher ground?
Are you absolutely sure?
Sir, he was last sighted at
the Central Plaza Station.
Given his path thus far,
it stands to reason that he'll--
He's bluffing!
Send men to canvas
the central shaft
that leads to the lower levels!
Scramble Team
Pied Piper, on the double.
What?
It's nothing to
be surprised about.
All signs point to the
intruder heading higher.
Might as well get
the team airborne.
You're telling me the IFOs
are his ultimate target?
It could be the pilots he's
after, we just don't know.
Either way, if you're correct
about him heading to the
lower levels, wouldn't
mobilizing all the IFOs be an
especially good idea, in terms
of getting them into the game?
"Scramble"?
Don't be ridiculous.
Nirvash isn't even
on the Triton yet!
The Nirvash is the
one we need to evacuate!
Don't tell me the US is
trying to take it back?
Ao!
Hurry it up!
If we can't load you in the next
minute or two, you launch as-is!
Uh!
Okay!
Whoa! What?
I thought I saw you up there.
I have long wanted to meet you.
Excuse me, but!
You mind not standing
on top of the Nirvash?
Oh my god!
"Nirvash"?
Interesting, and now
I know your name.
Well, what's a boy
like you doing here?
Sitting in that woman's machine?
"Woman"?
Hey, that's my mother!
Hands in the air!
Now!
If you're not off of
there by the count of three!
I open fire!
Rebecka, are you all right?
Don't worry about me!
Just take off!
Where do I go?
Anywhere is safer than here!
Just fly!
But what if--?
The Nirvash is taking off!
He's heading down Corridor 57!
Open Gate A-Three-Oh-Three
immediately!
Huh?
Ah, so controlling
the woman's craft seems
to be a family affair.
In that case--
You wanted to see us, sir?
Forgive me, girls.
More time recuperating
would've done you good.
That said we appreciate
your diligence.
For the time being,
at the very least,
I'll be heading up
Team Goldilocks.
Oh, okay.
So uh, what about
that newbie, Ao?
You mean the Fukai boy?
At the moment--
Stanley.
He's gone at the moment.
Hey, Gram?
I can't find Big Sis!
Flown the coop again?
I told that girl to stay in bed!
And I bet you I know
where she went.
No doubt about it.
The island changed
after you boys moved on.
Don't go pinning this on me!
Things have been different
around here for years now.
We railed so hard
against Japanese rule,
but now that we're in
bed with the Allied Forces,
it's the same damn thing.
I still talk about independence,
but nobody listens...
It's because the coral, huh?
Used to be only the
main island had Scub,
but now Iwato does, too!
The trapar harvesters swooped
in like a swarm of locusts.
Brought a bunch of jobs, though.
We're a real
boomtown these days.
No one's going to rock the boat
when they have full pockets.
Jiro, won't you consider
coming back home?
You could take over the
family business and I'll just--
You got to be kidding me!
After all those
times you called me
a good-for-nothing
waste of space?
I don't think so.
I'm at the end of my rope son.
Just like the rest of them.
You wouldn't know what
the truth was if it bit you.
And you do, is that it?
Not yet, but I'm gonna.
The guys at the
top of the food-chain
don't want the
truth getting out.
They act like they
got something to hide.
It's on.
I'm going to track down the
truth that you weren't able to.
Seems like things
are really picking up.
Yeah.
Hey, isn't that?
You're supposed to
be home in bed, Naru!
I know, Dad,
and I'm sorry, but..,!
I don't want to hear it!
What if you get
sicker because of this?
Please, just go home
and get some rest!
Can you do that for me?
Yeah.
Ao?
You know they're
going to catch us,
and my cough will get worse.
If you want to see the coral,
let's make it happen.
Yeah, but the Scub
on the main island's
what made me sick
in the first place.
Hey, an alley!
I think we can sneak
in through here.
It's kind of creepy.
I believe in you.
You know, you've
changed a bit, Ao.
You think so?
I don't feel any different.
Why'd you come back home?
And what's Generation Bleu like?
They're nothing special.
And I came back.
So that I could see you.
You really mean it?
I have to know, the truth.
But I--!
You don't need this.
I want you to
take a deep breath.
Huh?
That's crazy, it doesn't hurt.
Yeah, I know.
What?
Just being here with you.
It feels good being
together again.
Naru!
What is the meaning of this?
Naru?
Ao?
Well, the son of
the Nirvash pilot.
Why'd you go to Naru pretending
that you were me, huh?
Naru is a lovely
name you know that?
You leave her alone!
Are you okay?
Wait up!
Look alive!
We're going after them!
So, when did they
build this crap?
Give me a lift!
Hey, let me go!
Did you fall on your
head or something?
What's wrong with you?
That's, the Sea Colossus!
What are you doing in
my hometown, you faker?
I think you're
a being who exists
in close proximity to
the truth of this world.
And as such, you intrigue me.
That said, Naru
intrigues me even more!
Shut up!
She's got nothing
to do with this!
You just keep telling
yourself that, all right?
Leave her alone!
Whoa! Change of plans!
That thing is nightmare fuel!
It was you.
The Sea Colossus.
Thanks for the ride!
Huh?
Wait!
Naru!
You can fly.
Trust me!
Quick, Naru, give me your hand!
That guy is dangerous!
Sorry, but no!
You've got to snap
out of it, Naru!
He's not the real me!
I knew that from the beginning,
because the real you
would've brought Noa.
Then why?
Because he's him.
He was my Sea Colossus,
all those years ago.
Naru?
With him, I'm not sick.
And I can fly.
Please, take me with you!
What're you doing?
Ao, this world is
wrong, you know that.
Oh no!
Naru!
Where am I?
The hospital, you've been
asleep for three whole days now.
Hospital?
Yeah, how could you forget it?
You flew away with that guy
stuck to the top of the Mark I.
Crashed pretty hard.
We rushed out to provide backup,
but there was no
sign of the assailant.
Just you and your downed craft,
both of who were
pretty banged up.
The recovery team pulled you
from the Mark I and
brought you here.
Meanwhile, it sounds like
the Public Safety Department
is looking for our mystery man.
Thank goodness.
It was just a nightmare.
There's more.
Yeah?
Rebecka said not to tell you,
but it doesn't seem fair
keeping you in the dark.
There's a story that's
been going around the news.
There was a kidnapping at
the coral plant near your home.
That's your friend, right?
Do you have any idea
how much of our budget
we threw away trying
to acquire the Mark I?
There are no sure
things in life, gentlemen.
If I may be frank,
our country shouldn't
be using IFOs as a
crutch in the first place.
You bastard!
That said, we can't sit idly by
and let Generation Bleu do
whatever they want with it.
We spent the people's
tax money on this.
We'll make them rue
the day they took it.
Right!
Straight from our
mole in their HQ.
Yeah, it's all in the report.
Goes by the name of
Truth, apparently.
But I'm thinking he's our guy.
Also, Generation Bleu's
still keeping you-know-what
under wraps down
in the basement.
To be continued!
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Having lost Naru to
his mysterious rival,
Ao's feelings gnaw away at him.
Fleur's resentment
towards her father
finds an outlet in combat.
What will the two gain in the
wasteland at which they arrive?
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 8:
"blue thunder."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.