What's happening?
Hold on--where is Blanc?
Hey JJ.
That you?
I'm sorry.
The Kyrie and Alleluia
are in no shape to fly.
What're those?
Oh.
They're prototypes.
The Requiem,
the Gloria, and the Credo.
The Credo.
Dad, hey!
Hello?!
Come on, Dad!
Please, answer me!
I'm sorry.
There're Trapars in there.
The result of a fusion blast.
Georg?
No wait, you're the
Secret, aren't you?
What do you mean,
a fusion blast?
Christophe Blanc
must have hit Truth
with all the Quartz he had left
after the forming of the Gun.
Because Truth was also a Secret.
And my dad?
Tell me what's happened to him!
Quartz are invaders.
They do not belong
in this dimension.
In order to destroy them,
Secrets annihilate
not just the Quartz,
but the very space
around them, as well.
I don't believe you!
Remember what they told us?
Georg's messed up thanks to
his contact with the Secret!
It's his fault.
He did this!
Hold on, Fleur.
Remember what
your dad said, too.
That maybe the Secrets
aren't the enemy, after all.
We can't be sure now.
There's just too
much we don't know.
Hurry.
We don't know how long
the power will last.
Commander, are we not
launching a direct attack?
I'm hoping to avoid
the use of brute force.
It'll be easier for everyone
if they just come out
with their hands up.
They profit from our desire
to do no more
harm than necessary.
We haven't been able to get a
read on Blanc's ID badge yet.
I'm sorry.
Give up the search.
He was the president
to the very end.
Even if we tried to recover
him, the way things are--
The Allied Forces' attack
shouldn't last for much longer.
We know the Quartz Gun
is what they're after.
If we surrender it to them--
The Quartz Gun is safe.
It's still in a secure
location on the deepest level.
Is that your plan?
You want us to
just hand it over?
There's no need to
discuss this any furthe--
We shouldn't do it.
I know this might
sound unconvincing,
since I did consider joining
the Allied Forces at one point.
But Blanc told us something,
he said that we
needed to figure out
what the right thing to do was.
What else could be
right in this situation
but doing what
we can to survive?
I don't know for sure yet
what the right path is,
but I don't believe
it's giving in.
If we don't step up
to the plate now,
when the threat to our survival
is greatest, when will we?!
That sounds like the
logic terrorists use.
You're one to talk,
blindly following the higher-ups
and erasing Georg!
What other choice did I have?
I did it to protect everyone!
Fighting the Allies has never
been a viable option, Ao.
Don't you see that?
Here, look.
You know what this is, right?
Impossible!
All the main systems were
wiped clean simultaneously!
The pilot terminals have sectors
with high security levels.
These were not
affected by the purge.
We can make a copy off that.
The Triton will be able to fly!
Ivica?!
If you take the center shaft,
you can get to
the deepest level.
I'm going.
We can't leave the
Quartz Gun behind.
Ao.
Don't worry. It'll work.
Even without Georg,
Nirvash can st--
I'm gonna need you
to fire the gun, Ao.
Sorry, but I can't.
As soon as Georg is successfully
reinstalled on the Triton, link
them up to the electromagnetic
catapult controls.
Prepare for launch and
equip IFOs at the same time!
Hurry, but don't rush!
We're going to
need some volunteers
from among the mechanics.
You realize if you
ask for volunteers,
you'll wind up taking them all.
Hey, Alex, can
you open this gate?
Once you get past Gate Twenty,
everything's restricted.
I can't open any
of them remotely.
You don't mind if I destroy
them, then, do you?
How long is it gonna
take them to surrender?
Take a look at this.
They're finally giving in?
No, it's just the
residential zones
and the general population
that have been released so far.
This is the part of
the job I really hate.
It makes it feel like we're
the bad guys instead of them.
Are you going to go back
to your pals at
Big Blue World now?
They were the ones who sent me
to work at Generation
Bleu in the first place.
So they could have
someone on the inside
controlling what went on here.
Big Blue World is the most
influential PR company
in the world, you know.
If they say that the Secrets
are evil, that's what
the rest of the world is
going to believe, as well.
Like they did with Trapars.
Convincing everyone
they were necessary for--
Please, Rebecka.
Listen to me.
You know perfectly well
the kind of burden I bear.
It's not something I can
just walk away from.
This is all we need, isn't it?
Ao's cell.
We're going to use it to
restore the Triton's system
and get it up and running again.
How long do you
think it will take you?
You're doing it?
Chief, are you sure?
The children have
chosen the field of battle.
I will protect them
as long as I can.
Don't you want
to help me do that?
Their safety is
our responsibility.
Are you saying that you need me?
Give me about seven minutes.
Nicely done, Chief.
What about you?
What will the
Gazelle Agency do now?
I'm not sure yet.
For the moment, I guess
we're on official sloth duty.
Any response from
Christophe Blanc?
None so far.
The evacuation of civilians
and what personnel that
surrendered seems complete.
There can't have been
many who opted to surrender
if they were able to get out
of there in such a short time.
Pilots open fire!
Opening fire, sir!
What's our status, Alex?
Do we have the Gun in hand yet?
Of course not!
Are you kidding?
We've got to break through
fifteen gates just to get to it!
What about the defensive grid?
Is it holding?
It's operational,
but it can't keep up
with the speed of the
Allied Forces' IFOs.
That kind of maneuvering,
and he's not a child.
You can't do that sort of thing
unless you can see the Trapars.
But how can that be possible?
Yes!
I can see the Trapar
waves everywhere!
The power to the catapult
is becoming unstable.
Chief, authorize the launch!
We need to hurry.
We won't last.
Not yet!
We wait for Ao to return.
But, sir--
This is the Nirvash.
Please go ahead
and launch the Triton.
Why should we do that, Ao?
It'll be faster for
the Nirvash to escape
from the deepest level
than for the catapult
to launch the Triton from there.
Please, hurry!
Fine. Launch the Triton.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Launching the Triton.
Good luck.
We don't have a confirmed
location for the Mark I?
No, sir.
Not anymore.
We lost the signal
from its transmitter
a couple minutes ago.
They caught on to us,
then, and removed it.
Energy reading detected
from beneath Generation
Bleu Headquarters.
What is it?
Energy readings increasing and
expanding toward the surface!
This is it.
Thank you, Mr. Blanc.
The gauge for the Third Engine.
But why would it be
glowing like that now?
What do these indicators mean?
What's going on, Nirvash?
Are you doing any of this?
The Quartz Gun!
They've done it, sir.
Headquarters is
self-destructing!
Wait, look.
What's that at the center?
Is that Quartz?!
Launching the Triton, now!
You are powerful.
But no matter how terrible a
thing you areI won't fear you!
Not anymore!
What was that bright glow?
Could, Could it be--?
Have we just seen one of
the powers of the Quartz Gun?
What's happening?
Hey!
Elena do you know
what's going on?
Ao, think carefully
before you shoot.
What will the world become?
What now?
What will it take to
rectify their mistake?
Ao! Try to remain calm.
What do I do?
Which is the right path?!
Reinforcements?
But who?
Everything will
be all right, Ao.
That was Mom Hannah!
Fortunately, we escaped just
before the explosion,
aboard the Great Proteus.
But more than two hundred
of the crew weren't
able to get away in time.
I'm sorry.
The rest of you will come
join up with us, of course.
Ivica, we've already discussed
our next move
with Big Blue World.
We won't be fighting
beside Pied Piper.
Team Harlequin's
joining the Allies.
Are you serious?!
What are you saying?
Even down here, Harlequin's IFOs
are capable of performing
to their full potential!
With you on our side--
Blanc is no longer with us.
What can we do with
what we have now?
Don't you see, Ivica?
I understand.
That's what this is about.
What does this mean?
Team Harlequin is the enemy now?
That's it, Ao.
We're retreating.
I'm sorry, Chief.
We're shifting into
ballistic flight immediately.
Come back.
Roger that.
If we're lucky,
that will have bought
us a little time at least.
Hey, Rajkumar.
Is that signal still
being transmitted?
Yeah.
It's still going strong.
Honestly.
They require so
much looking after.
Fleur.
Come on.
Something's wrong with Elena.
She won't come out of the Kyrie.
I wonder why.
Elena!
Please just tell
us what's wrong!
Opening!
Hey, Elena!
Where is she?
I believe you are Elena Peoples.
Is that correct?
Yeah.
That was the name
on the ID I picked up
when I came to
this world, anyway.
I know all about that.
It seems you took part
in US intelligence
operations, as well.
Why're you here?
Did they leave you behind?
Well, do you want me?
I do, indeed.
Then here I am.
Tell me, though.
Why bother hiding your face now?
Some kind of symbolic expression
of her status as
a traitor, I guess?
A dramatic gesture.
Think we should get masks
for ourselves then, too?
Hold on a second!
I'm picking up something, here.
Not the signal we're tracking.
What are we detecting?
Any ideas?
No, I'm not sure.
But it's coming from
the ruins of Headquarters.
Something's rising
out of the rubble!
What the hell?
What in the world is that?!
I knew it!
In a place like this,
there's always something
in the basement.
Impossible!
Is that the IFO Zero?
So Blanc was
hiding it, all along.
Damn him!
Pull back now.
All three of you!
What's going on, Mom?
What is that thing?
Well its code name is Canon.
Canon?
It was excavated
following a Scub Burst
in the Soviet Union.
As you can see,
it resembles an IFO.
But nobody was
able to control it.
A great swath of land
from Siberia all the way
to northern China was
annihilated in an instant.
I thought that was from
a series of Scub Bursts.
No.
Luckily, we determined
it couldn't function
without Trapars.
So Gen. Bleu quietly
took custody of it.
But who's controlling it now?
My appearance.
My awareness.
What happened?
Where am I?
What are you?
Or who?
Archetype?
But is that your
name or what you are?
Oh, well, whatever.
Who cares.
You and I are one now.
Aren't we?!
Faisal Arabia has said
they might be interested
in taking us in.
Well, good to know we've still
got allies out there, at least.
We all know how they
feel about the US.
They probably
just want a weapon.
Beggars can't be choosers.
We'll have to find a country
to land in eventually
in order to resupply.
Too bad we can't just stay
up in the air forever, huh?
There's more.
China and Australia have issued
official statements
denouncing us.
They say they'll open fire if
we violate their airspace, so--
We're in outer space and
you've still got cell reception?
Yeah.
It was easy.
I was able to hook it up
to a network using the
Triton's connection, I--Hey.
This is--
Is there any place
left for us to run to?
Where are we going to go now?
It's a pleasure
to meet all of you.
My name is Yamaoka,
and I am with the
Japanese Cabinet Office.
We have a standing agreement
with Christophe Blanc.
In accordance with which,
we will provide your
team necessary supplies,
such as food and fuel.
And offer you use of
the JAF air bases.
The Japan Armed Forces?
What are you playing at?
You people have
always had it in for us!
You don't fully
understand the situation.
We were the ones who
negotiated this deal with Blanc.
What?
The Secrets?!
Correct.
However, as we
are not accustomed
to the ways of humans,
we had the
Japanese government act
as our brokers
for the agreement.
And this agreement,
what does it say?
The terms are as follows.
The Nirvash and any other IFOs
and pilots that remain
will devote themselves
to the effort of
eliminating the Quartz
that lay inside the Scub Corals.
Until such time as that
objective is complete,
the Secrets will
refrain from appearing.
In other words, you will not
trigger any more Scub Bursts.
The mass of Quartz that
has fused together into
what you are calling
the Quartz Gun is
an incredibly dangerous object.
I am aware of that.
However, if you will
not accept these terms,
I guarantee you
that we will fire it.
Understood.
We will discuss all of this
with the Japanese government.
If I should die, this agreement
will pass to my daughter.
It will remain in effect
under the supervision
of Miss Fleur Blanc.
Without even telling me.
In the end, I've robbed
her of everything
a young girl should have,
a normal life, a loving mother.
There's nothing else
that I can leave her.
Only the future.
So that mankind
is never subjected
to the threat of
Scub Bursts again,
we will eradicate all trace
of the Quartz from Earth
and enter into a peace
accord with the Secrets.
To that end, we will hereby
sponsor Team Pied Piper.
To be continued!
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Adhering to the deal made
by Blanc, Team
Pied Piper lands in Japan.
Elena has decided to fight
beside the Allied Forces,
in hopes of finding the
world in which she belongs.
What will happen when Ao's
former friend stands in his way?
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 21:
"rising sun."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.