I told them the
Mark I was wasted
on the Smithsonian.
Now they know.
Very well then.
Let's see who's stronger.
The Mark I has reappeared.
The Mark I?
I've sent open calls.
But so far, neither the
JAF nor the Allied Forces
has responded to
our communications.
We're getting the cold shoulder.
What are they
hoping to accomplish?
Nothing, I'd guess.
They must not know how to
work their radios properly.
Huh?
That is one possible
interpretation.
Hey, Nirvash.
All this flashing
starting to get annoying.
Think you could cut it out?
Reset to easy mode.
Whatever, that's fine.
How about weapons?
It's all a bunch a technobabble.
I guess it won't be as
easy as it is in anime.
Wait, what was that?
Please summon your captain!
The JAF has claimed
ownership of that craft!
The OSDF doesn't--!
Awesome!
Conventional weapons
won't work against them!
With weapons like
that the Secret
can see their every move!
Elena go!
Yeah, yeah.
Sent!
Let's rock this!
Okay?
All Goliaths have
found their marks.
Prep for second wave.
Aw!
Were you scared?
I'm fine thank you.
Wait you did that on purpose!
Fleur. You need to
break away for now.
But that's not fair!
You're pulling me
from the front again?
No.
We need you.
There's another child
for us to protect.
Huh?
So that's what that means.
I'm getting the hang of this!
Okay, time to see you
in your humanoid form!
Forgot about that.
It's charging into the ZOA.
Fleur, no!
Watch out!
Oh, lovely!
We've got to get outta the ZOA!
Ow!
I knew it.
I was right about you.
You were the pilot, Ao Fukai.
Did I step on someone's toes?
Only you guys can
fight a G-Monster?
It's only outside the ZOA that
Secrets can't detect IFOs.
The ZOA?
Yeah.
It stands for
"Zone Out of Action."
Inside it Secrets are
able to find the location
of IFOs within twenty
to thirty seconds.
You were going to fight
without even knowing that much?
Oh, no!
Please get out of the way.
It's the G-Monster!
Oh, quit worrying.
We're outside the ZOA here.
We're fine as long as
we don't initiate combat.
Stay here.
We'll talk about this later.
No hide-and-seek, please.
You're still fighting?
Can you win?
Win or lose.
I'm not going to leave
my friend to do this alone.
Okay, I'm coming too.
What?
If the G-Monster
destroys the island,
it'll be catastrophic, right?
The magnitude of a Scub Burst
is typically four times
that of the combined size
of the Coral and the Sec--
I'm going to
protect this island.
I have to.
It's my home.
Or, well, it was anyway.
After all this, that's
probably going to change.
Fleur.
It's getting dicey here.
I'm going.
Stay here and you'll be fine.
Can you lure them away?
If the fighters are occupied,
I can get close
to the main ship.
Did you hear what
I just said about the ZOA?
I'll have twenty to
thirty seconds, right?
How interesting.
That would be
an effective tactic.
Who is that?
The Mark I primarily
uses physical projectiles,
meaning he is more
useful at close range.
Of course, with only one arm,
his offensive capabilities
are cut in half.
This is nuts.
He's green and how can we trust
our fate to a damaged craft?
Fleur, here are your orders.
Ivica!
It's about protecting
the children.
If it comes down to it, we'll
use the Triton to shield him.
Fleur, map out his course
and the countdown for him.
This enables communications.
We'll be able to hear you,
too, do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
First it was babysitting
and now playing a decoy.
This is not what
I signed up for!
Data sent.
Get ready, Ao!
Eighty seconds.
I can do this.
Let's go.
Elena, are you ready?
If I die, I can be replaced.
This is no time to be
spouting off manga quotes!
Well, it's not
manga; it's anime.
It's compatible with
Kyrie's replacement parts?
All the IFOs were built conform
to the general
standards of the Mark I.
After all, what could we
do but blindly copy it?
Now Nirvash! Open fire!
I'm detected.
Oh, well! Too late!
Oh, Ao.
It's him.
This has to be his doing!
Naru! Naru!
Naru.
Ao!
The Scub Coral may be releasing
toxic substances into the air.
Until authorities can
be certain it is safe,
the area within a radius
of three kilometers
will be restricted.
What about the toxic substances?
Gen. Bleu is in there and they
aren't wearing any masks.
I don't know.
Listen, Pippo, there
comes a time in life
when a man must make sacrifices.
Reo!
Papa!
Sorry!
Hey! Hold it!
Get back here!
Hey!
The Burst is dying down.
It's just like the Plant
near the main island.
I'll be damned if I let
those bastards take Ao!
It was years ago.
There was a young woman
who saved my life,
a woman with blue hair.
The boy, Ao.
He's Eureka's son?
Our company has
a program dedicated
to taking care
of children like him.
He's old enough to start
making his own decisions.
I will leave it up to him.
And you'll honor his choice?
What happened to Ao?
Where is he?
Please take me to him!
And you are?
Naru.
Naru Arata.
Now, please!
Ao needs me!
I know he does!
When you see my boy,
give him a message for me.
Please, tell him this.
Nirvash will be okay, right?
It'll be fine.
That beach is deserted.
Even the kids are staying
away from it nowadays.
You rescue me from the sea
and now all this,
I don't understand.
Don't worry about it, kay?
It's fine.
Amazing how it's grown
since we started mining
trapar ten years ago.
Okinawa has the highest rate
of FP ownership in
the world, you know.
Wow.
♪ We don't need
no Allied Forces. ♪
♪ I say let's
go independent! ♪
♪ Return the
trapar back to us. ♪
♪ Back to us! ♪
♪ I say let's
go independent. ♪
♪ We don't need
no Allied Forces! ♪
Return the rights
to the Coral Plant.
They belong to Okinawa!
Have you read Johansson?
The entire world is
crying out for the truth!
Let's go.
Yeah.
It's like that every
day on the main island.
Technically we're independent,
but with the Allies'
interference, tourism,
and fishing have been wiped out.
I guess I didn't realize how
many people were unhappy.
He's got no home to go to?
What're you going to do?
I figure he can bunk in
the dorm at my work for now.
It's good, huh?
I had a feeling you'd like
my big sister's cooking.
Yeah it's really delicious!
I just love your dye job.
Adorable!
You should try that, brother.
Maybe then you would get a date.
Thanks for this.
Your sister is really nice.
See there's this guy I met.
He's with Intelligence.
You would sell
him to the Allies?
He's just a boy.
You saw his hair, right?
Japan and the Allied Forces
are both after that IFO.
If he's involved,
I can get good money--
Well sis, thanks for the food.
Good things come your way
when you do what
the Americans want!
Hey, why are you doing this?
I was only a kid
when the G-Monsters
appeared on the main island.
You survived the attack?
I was saved by a giant.
What?
Sounds crazy, right?
It looked like the
one you piloted.
I think they're the same.
We're getting off soon.
This is it?
You work here?
Yeah.
It's the largest trapar
mining plant in the world.
You jerk!
I have a message for
you from your grandfather.
That giant you flew,
it belonged to your mother.
Ten years ago, she took the IFO
and headed for the Scub Burst.
As you know, she
hasn't been seen since.
If you decide
to pilot the giant,
the same thing
will happen to you.
Promise me, Ao.
Don't die.
Unfortunately, we still don't
understand her disappearance.
No one knows what
happened to Eureka.
But if I do it.
If I pilot the Nirvash,
maybe, maybe someday
I'll find the
path my mother took.
Maybe.
Please, sir.
I would like to join
Generation Bleu!
Target's at the Coral Plant.
I want them both.
Boy and the Mark I.
You've got wings after all, Ao.
They're going to take you
away from the island.
I guess so.
If my mom's alive,
I have to find her somehow
but I'll never forgive my dad.
There's something else Ao.
I need to...
Gram and Miyu will
take good care of you.
And try not to fight with
your dad too much, okay?
Yeah.
I know, maybe those
guys can help out.
They might know of
some way to cure you.
Are you talking about them?
Generation Bleu?
They take on G-Monsters right?
I'm sure they
know lots of stuff.
Take her with you.
Huh?
She seems to like the
Gen. Bleu people.
I can't.
I have nothing else to give.
You should take her with you.
What are those?
Look!
I think, they're Allied IFOs!
What are the Allied
Forces doing here?
The same thing we are.
They must've
hacked into the taxi
and determined his location
using the onboard camera.
Guess we're thinking along
the same lines and the Mark I?
The Mark I is currently
preparing for takeoff.
It shouldn't be much longer.
Thank you for keeping
it hidden away for me.
I wouldn't be here
if it weren't for him.
That's true for lots of us.
Not just me.
Naru, stand back!
I'm going now.
We'll bring you aboard
the Triton right away.
We're not fighting?
Why not?
It's the Allied Forces!
To another IFO we'll be
fully visible, like normal.
So, basically, you
wouldn't stand a chance.
Who's that?
Generation Bleu, huh?
I'll slap them with
a formal request,
demanding its surrender.
Sorry.
Has anybody seen Noa around?
She was just here a while ago.
I'm freezing!
Suck it up, Pippo.
If you hadn't been chased
by those Dobermans,
we'd be a lot
better off right now.
Oh, a sweater!
This sucks!
To be continued!
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Beyond the haze,
Ao sees a black tower
jutting above white clouds.
With this unfamiliar world
will come new doubts
and new insecurities.
The boy will begin to question
what he is doing there.
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 5:
"génération bleu."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.