Things are finally getting back
to normal around here,
I'm glad to say.
Oh, for the love of--!
Look, I don't
like the guy either.
But it's not our
job to catch him.
The IFO teams have a very
clear mission objective.
Take out the Secrets
before they detonate.
We don't have the resources to
be taking on extra work, kid.
Now, now.
I'm sure he feels
bad enough as it is.
So, what do you think his
punishment should be?
There's no precedent
for what he did,
but the severity of
this can't be ignored.
You already gave him
a stern talking-to.
That should suffice.
Are you serious?
Your thoughts Ivica,
do you agree with her?
We should keep in mind the
situation with Team Goldilocks.
Let's put this to bed, then.
What?
I trust you, Ao.
I know you're gonna
do the right thing.
Okay?
I shouldn't be telling you this,
but, you pilots are more like
my children than my employees.
And like any father worth his
salt, I believe in my kids.
I wouldn't know, sir.
How dare you say those
things to him, Dad!
Huh?
Is that guy a creeper or what!
Yeah!
Hey, Ao!
Doing some shopping?
Yeah.
Sweetheart!
Yeah, you in the apron!
Let's see if the coffee's
as hot as the barista!
Why're you guys
trying to follow me?
Oh give it a rest, Gazelle!
I'm not blind!
As if!
Why would I follow
such a pipsqueak?
Listen to me!
You guys seriously need
to stop following me around!
Ao's tough-guy routine
could use a little work.
If you're trying to keep
track of his whereabouts,
you and your friends
are approaching it
with all the subtlety of
a bull in a china shop.
Well, maybe we were
told not to be subtle.
You're being obvious about it,
to try and put
the squeeze on him!
If you're just following orders,
someone must have issued them.
It was the president, wasn't it?
Speaking of, what's
with all the static
between you and
your old man, huh?
Just like Ao.
He's in the same
boat with his old man.
We have a formal
request for intervention.
Mobilize at once, Ivica!
Consider it done, sir!
Faisal Arabia, huh?
As if that country weren't
embroiled in enough drama.
Mr. Blanc, you have a
call from the Allied Forces.
Speak of the devil,
and he shall appear.
Transfer the call.
I'll take it in my office.
That was one hell
of a hit your team
took in Columbia, eh Christophe?
And that attack on
your headquarters.
You've had it rough.
I appreciate your
concern, Mr. Secretary.
You'll forgive my saying
that Generation Bleu's
giving me a migraine.
I'm afraid I don't follow.
See, it's that damnable
Nirvash of yours.
Some of our congressmen
have latched onto the idea
that it's the Mark I,
which was in our custody
up until recently when it
disappeared without a trace.
Really?
Yes, really.
They're going to take
their case to the media
and lean on the President
until they get results.
It's an election year, so expect
the full dog-and-pony show.
Ain't that a bear.
Fortunately, our
Nirvash and your Mark I
are two utterly
different crafts.
Yes, but of course.
That said, if Generation Bleu
could do us a bit of a favor,
we'd be much more
inclined to stand down.
Faisal Arabia's the favor.
I assume?
The Secret is still a ways out.
Will retrieving the
Quartz be a priority?
And if the Secret should
suddenly hit the gas?
What're you going to do then?
I would just--
Once a Secret has manifested
in Earth's airspace,
you know that there's only
one proper course of action.
Huh?
What're you trying to say?
Those guys followed
me because the president
of Generation Bleu
put them up to it?
More or less.
What the heck?
And after all that
bull he spouted
about trusting me like
I was his own kid?
Where does he get
off saying that stuff
and then treating me this way?!
Having him feed you
that line is a rite
of passage around here.
"And like any father
worth his salt,
I believe in my kids."
Saying that in front of his own
daughter takes a lot of nerve.
Huh? His who?
Wait up!
Did we really never tell you?
Huh?
Miss Fleur here is our
company president's daughter.
What?
Enough idle chatter!
Georg has managed
to identify the Secret.
Indeed.
This Secret matches descriptions
of an unidentified flying object
that appeared in the skies
over Philadelphia in 1752.
According to historians,
its appearance
was accompanied by a
series of lightning strikes
that damaged the
surrounding area.
An interesting
phenomenon, lightning.
It occurs when a difference
in electric potential arises
in a space that exceeds the
dielectric strength--
Bring the Triton to base ASAP.
We're aborting the mission,
effective immediately.
Is this your idea of a joke?
Blanc just pulled the plug.
What, this is Blanc's doing?
But that Secret
is still out there!
Turn her around.
What do you mean?
Come on, Chief!
We're giving up, just like that?
What the hell!
Bringing her back to base.
Here's the game plan.
They made some kind
of backroom deal.
That's the only
reason I can think of.
And the only group
who can put the screws
to GB's president like that
is the government
of the United States.
Why would America do that?
The location of our current
Scub, Faisal Arabia,
is the most
anti-American country
in all of the Middle East.
The U.S. believes it to engage
in state-sponsored terrorism,
and tensions between the
two countries could erupt
into full-scale war
without much provocation.
Faisal Arabia's
thoroughly anti-U.S.
sentiments grew out of a schism
among the royals of the
former Saudi Arabia--
If the Secret is allowed to
make contact with the Scub,
the explosion will deal a
crippling blow to the country.
Plus it will deprive them of the
chance at their own coral plant.
That's why.
He's playing politics?
People could die!
Why is Blanc
rolling over on this?
Because they offered
him something, Ao.
Something worth turning a
blind eye to human suffering.
Just because you don't like
him doesn't mean he's--
That's enough.
So that's it?
Fly back home like
nothing's wrong?
I'm not going to sit back
and let these people die!
Hey, Fleur!
Are those two together?
He's my father, but I hate him.
You hate your
father too, don't you?
Gazelle mentioned it back at HQ.
I guess that's something
you and I share.
I don't get it.
Huh?
I mean, if you hate him so much,
why did you work
for his company?
Five years ago, my maman
and I were involved
in a really
horrible car accident.
There were only
enough viable organs
left between us
to save one of us.
Me or my beautiful maman.
When the doctors told
my father, he picked me.
And let her die on the table.
I loved her more than
I can put into words.
If I had died,
that wonderful woman
would still be
alive and well today.
Huh, but?
I hate him!
I hate him for killing her
and leaving me
with all the guilt!
That's why I fly
for the company.
Because it forces my father
to send me into harm's way.
Chief?
...bring you this footage
of the destruction
within Faisal Arabia.
We're looking at video shot
in the old capital
city of Abuha,
which bore the brunt of the
G-Monster's initial attack.
Thanks in large part
to this footage...
You ready to do some flying?
Huh?
That video struck a nerve.
Now that it's out there.
Folks are saying this country
needs all the help it can get.
And not wanting
to look like jerks,
the Allied Forces
had to get on board.
And that means!
It means the order to return
to base has been nixed.
We're going to
take that Secret out!
I'm not letting those bastards
get their way, not this time!
America and your dad are just
going to have to deal with it!
Sucks to be you today, Dad!
Okay, Fleur!
We've got even more reason
than usual to succeed!
You can say that again, Ao!
Look how fired up you are!
Time to transform
and combine, huh?
Huh?
We'll be entering the
ZOA in 180 seconds.
Locking onto target now.
Let's see what we're up against.
You would be wise to
note that the lightning
emanating from this
Secret is caused solely
by the charged particles
it releases into the air.
Since they are
enveloped in trapar,
the IFOs are not a
target the Secrets
can discern, as per usual.
However, the lightning bolts
are a natural phenomenon
independent from the Secret's
will and are capable of hitting
your craft at random,
so proceed with caution.
Also, lightning can
form outside the ZOA.
Your IFOs are equipped
with electromagnetic shields
to guard against precisely
this sort of threat.
That said, a direct
lightning strike may
well disable your system
and leave you dead in the air.
Please factor this
into your strategy.
Well that's easy for you to say!
But how exactly do I do that?
Don't get hit by one.
Captain Obvious strikes again.
Says the girl who doesn't have
to worry about getting zapped.
Ready to get this started?
You're out of the
lightning zone.
Good call!
Time to put your guns on, Dante!
Here it goes.
Fire!
Again!
The number of charged particles
is increasing by
250% every second.
The discharge zone is
growing exponentially.
Damn!
Retreat now!
No way!
Come on, reboot!
What's your status, Elena?
Are you reading me?
Alleluia and Nirvash, maintain
your positions!
But Chief!
With Elena out of the fight,
there's no safe way to engage
that Secret.
Something's
happening to it, Chief!
The Secret has released all
of its charged particles
with this sudden change of
course to a higher altitude...
Seventy-six seconds from now,
it will lose all momentum
and plummet to the Earth.
Now triangulating the
estimated crash site.
Wait, into the coral?
Son of a!
The Secret's going
for a Hail Mary!
Abort your attack!
You need to get
away from that thing!
What?
The situation changed!
We have no choice!
Damn it!
We always have a choice!
The bastards win this
if we run away now!
I'm sorry,
but letting innocent people
die is outta the question!
Listen to me!
You need to start using
your head out there!
But Chief!
Fleur, wait!
Talk to me!
Get back to the Triton, Fleur!
That's an order!
Sixty seconds remaining
until fusion explosion.
It's heading, for the coral!
Are you nuts!
Fleur, you know that
the Alleluia's firepower's
not going to cut it!
I'm not going to
stop it with my guns.
Huh?
Ao, this is one fight
I can't afford to lose.
Even if it costs me everything.
The Secret is
concluding its ascent
at 7,200 feet
over Faisal Arabia.
Its momentum has been expended.
Now commencing free-fall.
It shouldn't have to.
Fleur, I hate my dad, too.
A lot!
But it's because of that hatred
that I have to persevere.
No matter what happens,
I got to live through it!
So I can kick his ass someday!
If you hate your father,
you're not allowed to die yet!
I guess we're out of time.
Are you ready to do this?
Yeah!
The Nirvash and the Alleluia
have latched onto the Secret.
Time until fusion
explosion: 25 seconds.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
Georg, what's the
status of the IFOs?
The Alleluia and Nirvash are
both still operational.
I'm picking up
life-signs from each craft.
So I believe the
pilots to be unharmed.
Hey Fleur, you okay?
Well...
I'm alive!
You and me both.
Thank goodness.
Hey, where're you guys off to?
Reporting in to our dumb boss!
We're going to go rub
our victory in his face!
I wonder what he's
going to say to us?
I bet you the Americans chewed
him out and he's been crying.
That would be awesome!
I don't even care
if he fires me!
This is worth it!
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
It's still glued to
my face, you dummy!
Man, this prosthetic glue
really does the trick!
Hey, guys!
Look who the cat dragged in!
Ao, down here!
Check it out, we look
all war-torn and crap!
Huh?
Where've I seen those outfits?
I haven't forgotten!
The two of you ran
off without permission
while we were
docked in Faisal Arabia.
Believe you me, kids.
You'll have a thorough
debriefing about that.
After that Faisal Arabia
footage went live,
a rumor from who knows where
started making the rounds.
Apparently, we'd failed to
mobilize a strike team,
even though we'd received a
formal request for aid.
America had me on the phone
right away.
They seemed to think we had
started the rumor ourselves.
Really?
I told them I had no idea
what they were talking
about, of course.
Pardon my asking.
But why did you
remain in-country
after you'd been
ordered to return to base?
The engine gave me some grief.
Fixing it was a real pain.
Ah.
Huh? Where are you going?
Someone's got to scold the kids,
don't they?
He had Gazelle's
crew fake that footage.
And the whole world bought it.
Bastard!
But thanks to him lying,
the mission was a-go.
We saved a lot of lives we
wouldn't have been able to.
Hey, Fleur.
I know we won, but did we, win?
"We," huh?
Well aren't you
getting familiar!
Huh?
To be continued!
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
The young man known as Truth
dredges up a relic
of the past in order
to stoke the
fires of revolution.
Something appears in
the water's murky depths.
What will it offer
the young man?
And what will be
made clear to the boy?
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 9:
"enemy below."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.