Poor Noa, I wonder
what she's doing?
If we'd made her
a little spacesuit,
she could've come along.
This is not an anime!
There's no budget for
that stuff in real life.
Sounds just like
her dad, doesn't she?
Don't, I mean it!
She's got to be
feeling lonely, and sad.
She hasn't seen Naru
in a while, either.
Thanks for that.
It says it can breathe
much better now.
Come here.
I'm still getting used to this.
I can't believe how much freer
I feel when I'm near you.
That's because you
aren't actually ill.
It's just seemed so
because you have a piece
of Scub Coral growing
inside of you.
Why are you so kind only to me?
You think I'm kind?
First time I've ever heard that.
You do everything I ask.
And you're always by my side,
even though I've never
done anything for you.
We're the same, you and I.
Whatever helps you, helps me.
We are both seeking the truth.
We both see the
wrong in the world.
I still say you're kind.
You have done something
that was just for me.
You didn't kill Ao
when you could have.
So, thank you.
Ao Fukai.
In time, he too,
will see the truth.
Amazing.
Hey, this place is
pretty strange, huh?
Our headquarters was
built by recycling
unfamiliar structures discovered
in various Scub Corals.
I believe that was how
it was explained to you?
Uh... yes, sir.
I was also told the
Gazelle Agency was
an independent reserve
unit, and that we have
the freedom to go where
we deem necessary.
Yet, one hundred percent
of your funding
comes from our company.
So we expect to be kept
in the loop at all times.
It's no big deal.
We just wanted to see
this area for ourselves
to determine what the
US agent was investigating.
You see, nothing sinister.
It's just the
remains of a test site.
We have it sealed off due
to contamination concerns.
Oh man!
I thought there would be a heap
of Quartz so it's
not what I expected.
No, sorry.
You won't find Quartz here.
We're not buying that.
We know the teams
always collect them.
Still, as I said,
they're not here.
This whole space thing,
I'm not a fan of it!
I'm heading this way.
What for?
She's going to
transfer the Quartz.
The ones we collected
from the Corals?
They're all up here?
Silicon?
Well, depicting zero-G in
animation is pretty difficult.
What's that got to do with it?
We just finished
up in the kitchen.
You've got great timing!
Oh, cool!
Is that a butler?
Everyone, meet Chief
Hannah of Team Harlequin.
You must be Ao?
I knew you right away!
With hair like that,
who wouldn't?
Chief, it's nice to--
Awe, Mom.
That's what everyone
around here calls me.
Okay.
Wow! So you really are an alien!
An alien? What?
Come on, let's
all have some tea!
I think we should get
right to the meeting.
I've just got one
more set to go.
Liu Yin.
Okay!
Coffee for you,
I believe, Ivica?
Yet another thing
I hate about space.
The computer here is Georg, too?
I am one, Ao Fukai, no
matter where you see me.
Allow me to explain.
I am not, in fact, a computer,
but an operating syst--
That's him.
We're all set!
Come, have some cake!
That thing is for the
Planet War Initiative.
Yes, so I've heard.
It was created to intercept
ballistic missiles in space.
You can't just take
it out for a spin.
Why not?
It won't be hard.
I've already
hijacked its circuitry.
Firecracker strikes again.
I just thought you would
like to be kept informed.
Goodbye.
Professor J. Johansson.
Johansson committed
suicide several years ago.
But not before writing
the Johansson Book.
A work some of his
adherents consider
to be a book of prophecy.
The professor
had an adopted son.
And I'm looking at him
right now, aren't I?
Do you know what Johansson said?
He said however you look
at it, the world is wrong.
Ordinarily even if
a Scub Burst in space
should cause a fusion blast,
it would not harm us
here on Earth's surface.
However, the current
situation is much trickier.
The Scub has
appeared at an altitude
within the low Earth orbit.
Due to the high concentration
of satellites there,
a fusion blast could produce
massive amounts of debris.
Keeping that in mind,
the United Nations
has commissioned Generation
Bleu to eliminate the Secret.
Does that feel good, or what?
The entire world
is depending on us
to successfully
carry out this mission.
International rescuers
to global saviors!
Unless we fail, in
which case our sponsors
will wash their hands
of us quick enough.
Why are we the ones
they're sending out?
There's already a
team based up here.
Harlequin is different.
They get special treatment.
Kind of like you?
Technically, Harlequin's
our backup team.
But that title's
just window dressing.
They're really something else.
The guardians of the Quartz!
What does that mean?
Though the Seven Days
of Fire may come,
and all on the Earth's surface
be razed to the ground,
they will survive!
That's why there are multiple
families living here.
Seven Days of what?
That part was just
Elena being dramatic.
The rest of it is
probably true, though.
Even if all the rest of
us die, they'll survive?
Oh, just shut up and get ready!
Our IFOs won't move like
we're used to out in space.
We'll have to finish
this with one strike.
Ao?
Hey, did you hear me?
Something's wrong.
What happened?
The sky's different here.
The path in the wind,
I can't see it.
I was afraid of this.
You care to explain?
Listen get back here, Ao!
Fleur and Elena, you stand by.
Change of plans!
The Secret will make
contact before long!
Up here, Mom's word is law.
What's the path in the wind?
I've always been able
to see it, until now.
It was there, just waiting for
me whenever I was flying.
What was?
So, for as long as
you can remember,
you've been piloting FPs by
simply following that path?
Well, yeah.
You guys see it, too, right?
This is an approximation
of how he sees the world.
What Ao's seeing when he flies
isn't the wind it's the Trapars.
The boy is able to see Trapars?
There's a slight difference
in his genetic code,
involving his optic
nerve cells, remember?
That's what the lab found.
How's that possible?
The Trapars are tiny particles!
They're, what--?
Twenty nanometers in diameter.
No human can see
them with the naked eye.
But that's what he's seeing,
and it's also the reason
he's been performing
as well as he has.
I don't get it.
Why, why do you know
so much about me?
Because you're an
alien, of course.
Hey, Elena, have you
ever seen Trapars before?
No, but maybe
I need to try harder!
It's just crazy: Ao's
genetically programmed
to see the world
differently than we do.
That sounds like an anime line.
Yeah except it's real.
This occurred thirteen years
ago, on April 12th.
April 12th? That's!
You didn't know?
It's Nirvash!
The US forces in Okinawa
called for a scramble.
This is their footage.
Mama!
How dare you show him
this out of the blue?
This is something he should have
been told about a long time ago.
As you can see from this video,
the Mark I Nirvash
emerged from a pillar of light.
Just like the Scub Corals
and Secrets do.
In other words, it
came from another world.
Another world?
Really?
Where is it?
Well, according to Johansson--
You mean that
unscientific drivel?
And my, where is my mother now?
We explained it to you before.
She disappeared ten years ago.
Why are you hiding it?
After the Scub Burst
off the coast of Okinawa,
the Nirvash was recovered, but
there was no trace of its pilot.
It's pretty clear.
Most likely, the woman
Eureka is no longer...
Getting back to our situation:
there are almost no
Trapars in space.
Ao won't have
his usual advantage.
It would be too
dangerous to have him
participate in this mission.
As I have been proposing
for some time now,
he should remain here
aboard the Proteus
under investigative custody.
You could have
handled this mission
perfectly well without us.
You sent for Pied Piper
because you wanted to abduct Ao!
Abduct?
What do you call what you
people have done to him?
What I want to do is keep Ao
out of active
combat from now on.
It's possible he's being forced
to fight against his own kind.
I don't know, Ch--
I mean, Mom.
If you stay here, you'll be
just like one of my kids, okay?
Thanks, but I'm going.
You're what?
I'll prove that
I'm still a good pilot.
Okay, I'll take
care of navigation.
This time around, you're
just the Rocket Punch
that flies straight
and hits hard!
You guys are great.
Thanks a lot.
The Kyrie and the Alleluia will
divert the Secret's attack.
While they do, the Nirvash
will charge toward the Secret.
It will destroy the target
at maximum proximity
and then rebound
and change its orbit.
If all goes to plan, it will
work something like this.
Nirvash collides
with the Scub Coral,
causing it to decelerate
and change orbit,
allowing a rendezvous
with the Triton.
This is the best we can do
with the fuel they
can carry out there.
If he fails to make contact
with the Scub Coral,
he'll plummet
back down to Earth.
If that happens, I'll do
whatever it takes to save him!
I have a visual on the Secret.
It is approaching the
Scub at the same velocity
as when it first appeared.
It has no noticeable
propulsion apparatuses,
so there should be no worries
about it changing its orbit.
It is the same in space
as it was underwater.
You cannot rely on
Trapars to blind it.
The Secret has
already detected you.
Exercise full caution.
It looks like a jack-in-the-box.
I'm sending up the
flares to draw its fire.
Go ahead!
Igniting Stage Two rockets.
Now!
Good luck, Ao.
Crazy.
The islanders were right.
I really am an alien.
If my mother was,
then I am, too.
So tell me, where
do I come from?
Tell me that, Secret!
No!
Fleur!
We're almost out of fuel, also!
Please enter the orbit to
make contact with the Scub.
I'm trying!
All right.
First we pick up
Alleluia and Kyrie.
Then we adjust our orbit so we
can rendezvous with Nirvash.
Hold on!
What is this?
A railgun?
It's a Japanese satellite.
A malfunction?
Do they think we're stupid?
The situation is
not looking good.
What do you mean?
The Scub Coral's
orbit has shifted,
and it has begun to descend.
The direction of its velocity
matches that of the Nirvash.
Still don't understand
what you're saying!
My orbit hasn't changed?
It has begun to
descend on roughly
the same orbit as the Nirvash.
So, even following
the collision,
the Nirvash will
simply decelerate.
The orbit of both objects
will remain the same.
Drawn by the Earth's gravity,
the Nirvash and the
Scub will fall together.
This is an elementary
law of physics.
No way!
Nirvash's descent
remains unchecked.
Ao you need to get
away from the Scub!
Hurry!
He'll crash.
I wonder, Ao.
Do you think that I'm kind?
We have the
orbit calculated, sir!
As we predicted.
They're falling.
The Scub Coral will burn up
as it passes through
the atmosphere.
Fortunately, at least,
there are no satellites
in collision orbits with it,
so it will produce no debris.
However...
The Nirvash won't be able
to endure the
temperature of reentry.
It will burn up, as well.
We can't let that happen!
Do something, Dad!
Stay put!
The Triton will pick you up
in a matter of minutes.
There's nothing you
and Elena can do now.
Abandon him?
Why?
Because he's an alien?
Fleur!
I'm sorry.
I knew it would be
too much for him.
It's not your fault, Mom.
Listen, once you
enter the stratosphere,
there will be Trapars.
You may be able to use them
to slow down your descent.
I could be burnt
to ashes before then!
Don't give up!
You hear me?
My mom's already gone, anyway.
I don't care how nice she is.
Hannah is not my mother.
You never told me the truth!
What's done is done!
I refuse to let any
of you kids die!
I'll save you even if I have to
burn up the Triton up to do it!
I'm coming!
Wait for me!
Okay.
I'm waiting.
Ao!
Get inside Ao!
Go as far as you can!
What's that?
It's a ship!
Are you telling me
to use it as a board?
It's time to fly.
Hello.
My name is Eureka;
It's nice to meet you.
Oh, hey, your hair?
It's, you.
To be continued.
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
In an unexpected
reunion aboard the Gekko,
Ao struggles to
reconcile the alien woman
with the mother
he lost long ago.
It becomes apparent that Eureka
has brought with her a truth
that will shock the very
foundations of the world.
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 13:
"moonlight ship."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.