I wonder how long
they've had those things.
They definitely
woulda come in handy
during our showdown
with the Secrets.
Rumor has it they've
been saving 'em,
for a day like today.
You gotta be kidding.
They built those things just to
deal with a security company?
That's crazy.
It's a total outage.
Did something go wrong
at the power facility?
No!
I'd just removed
the copy-protection,
all that work and I was
finally about to burn it!
What's with you?
It's the version sent out
before the official release.
Parts of the CG
weren't completed
in time for distribution.
Huh?
Never mind.
It's not something
you'd understand.
Why don't you go and ask Daddy
Dearest what's happening here?
Run along.
Are we still doing this?
I thought we had
both put it behind us.
I've decided I'm
not going to hide
how I really feel anymore.
Attention.
We have received a report
from the Security
Department concerning
the recent power outage.
It wasn't an accident?
It seems the power company
has terminated our account
and halted all transmission.
Our contract's up?
What about the
on-site power station?
Our account with
the power company
is just a backup, isn't it?
The Generation Bleu power
station has been shut down
since yesterday due to
an emergency inspection.
The higher-ups ordered it.
When you say "higher-ups,"
do you mean the people
at our parent company?
Big Blue World or whatever?
Christophe.
I want an explanation,
immediately!
What the hell are
they playing at?!
Sorry, I'm still
a little jet-lagged.
Hold on a sec, will you?
Hey, Blanc! Hey!
Okay.
Let's go over
everything one more
before we wrap this up.
Very well.
First, a precondition.
If I should die, this agreement
will pass to my
daughter, Fleur Blanc.
It will remain in
effect under her control.
What's up, Chief?
Something wrong
with President Blanc?
Apparently, things aren't going
so well with the higher-ups.
The who?
Christophe acted right away
when he learned there was
a way to prevent Scub Bursts.
He knew the world needed an
organization like this one,
but to start it up, he needed
a colossal amount of funding.
So he turned to a PR firm,
based in the United States.
Hello, Fleur!
I hear you got your
Third Engine up and running.
Congratu--
Is it our fault that
this is happening now?
We used a show of
force to bring Ao back.
Is that why
Big Blue World is so angry?
I'll be blunt with you, my dear.
That is one reason.
Most definitely.
In that case,
it's actually my fault.
Well, then, why haven't
you punished us...?
Don't let me off the hook
because I'm your daughter.
Yes, I admit it: I'm
guilty of favoritism.
Even when you first said
you wanted to pilot an IFO,
I made sure you were assigned
a data recording craft
because it was the least
likely to get you hurt.
But I didn't get in the
way of you becoming a pilot.
I wanted you to be proud of what
you were doing with your life.
I never wanted you
to have any regrets.
Oh, one more thing.
Our company will no longer
spend time eliminating Secrets.
What are you saying?!
Things are gonna change.
Starting today we'll
focus our operations
on suppressing the
proliferation of Scub Corals.
In accordance with
the UN resolution,
we have made a decision.
Generation Bleu has shown itself
to have violent tendencies.
Tendencies that we here
at Big Blue World
cannot overlook.
We have advised
CEO Christophe Blanc
that the enterprise
will be liquidated.
Here you see the percentage
of shares our company holds.
Our withdrawal will essentially
force them to shut their doors.
But up until this point,
your company has completely
supported Generation Bleu.
Of course.
We had our own
people in place there
and were assured there were
no issues with compliance.
However, Blanc
retained possession
of the Quartz without
our knowledge.
He even had the audacity
to put it to use as a weapon.
So, they're finally
pulling the plug.
This will give Japan
an even greater advant--
Hah! What's the matter?
Think you'll fool people
by pretending to be asleep?
Oh, come on.
Couldn't you make an
appointment like everyone else?
What do you plan
to do about this?
It's past time to cut your
ties with this terrorist.
What's brought this on?
You're in a particularly
foul mood today.
Nothing's happening.
More Coral plants are
reactivating every day
across the globe, but not a
single Secret has appeared.
I'm sure there's
a reason for that.
The Quartz Gun is the key.
Nirvash's new weapon
is pushing the world
ever closer to chaos
and destruction.
But it can't happen
without the Secrets.
Be quiet.
No, I mean you, Truth.
I am speaking to you, not them.
Secret?
Is that you?
I will tell you what
you wish to know.
We are temporarily refraining
from launching a new attack.
But why?!
Generation Bleu is
public enemy number one.
The gun is giving rise to chaos!
It is time!
Think this through, Truth.
Recall what our objective is.
Chaos is not what we seek.
Our goal is order.
You said "we." What do you mean?
You are a Secret,
as well, are you not?
Is it possible that
you've forgotten?
Hey, Truth?
Hello?
What are you suggesting?
You're wrong!
That's ridiculous!
You do not have the
ability to destroy Secrets.
Naru. Naru.
You see, Truth.
The Allied Forces don't
know what to do with us.
We share their desire
to protect the Scub Corals,
so they may prefer
to leave us alone.
That isn't the
answer I asked for!
Fine.
You wanted to know
if you're a Secret.
Yes, you are.
I know because I saw you
inside the Scub Coral.
As everyone knows,
ten years ago,
there was an enormous
Scub Burst in Okinawa.
With it appeared a Secret.
One bigger than
anyone had seen before.
But then the
Quartz was taken away,
and the Secret's sense of
purpose was lost, as well.
And so, in order to find
a place in this world,
it took the shape of a human.
And I was that Secret.
I transformed into a boy,
and Johansson found me.
And now, you're the one who
gave me wings and let me fly.
You're the one who told
me what I have to do.
That, together, we
must change this world.
Humans must learn to become
one with the Scub Corals.
That union will give us
freedom and infinite power--
Don't you see?
You are no ordinary
Secret any longer, Truth.
You're the same as me.
By guiding you,
Naru, I was helping
the Secrets and Scub
Corals destroy the world.
That's what I've
believed all this time.
But now, I think, that maybe
you were the one guiding me.
This could never have
worked without you.
Ao would never have the
power that he has now.
Firecracker.
Yet another guise in
which this Truth appears.
Manipulating the
flow of electrons.
I can do that; is that ability
part of a Secret's power?
I know the living
quarters may not be able
to hold the entire staff,
but surely we can take in
all the IFO team
members, can't we?
It was originally meant
to be an ark, of sorts,
in case of a cataclysm,
so we do have extra space.
Wait.
Ao and the others are going
to be moving into
the space station?
It may well come to that, yes.
Okay, but then what
happens after that?
The CEO says we're not
fighting Secrets anymore,
so what are we going to do?
For now, avoid fighting
battles we don't have to.
Hey, Mom.
I'm detecting satellites
drifting into our orbit.
Then we'll move
to a different one.
Immediately.
We can't do that.
Multiple satellites have already
collided into each other.
There is metal
flying everywhere.
There's nothing we can do; we're
heading for the debris storm.
Multiple communication
satellites belonging
to the US and other Allied
nations have been destroyed.
We believe they were attacked
by Generation Bleu's satellite.
As the vanguard of the
Allied Forces the fight is ours.
We must take control of
this rogue organization.
There you are, Maggie.
How are you feeling?
Fine, thank you, sir.
Colonel.
Those children we
saw aboard the carrier
the other day are Generation
Bleu's IFO pilots, right?
Yeah.
They're the ones we're
going to be fighting?
Some think Gen. Bleu has
gotten away with child abuse
by using the children's ability
to pilot IFOs as an excuse.
I would like to find some way
to bring them in
under our protection.
You can count on my
full support with that.
Blanc can't leave
his post right now,
so I'll be-- Hey,
what are you doing?
I am temporarily deleting
our tactical support program.
Deleting Georg?
Seriously?
What'll happen once he's gone?
We won't be doing any
flying, that's for sure.
The Triton and the IFOs each
require high level controls.
Without Georg, we
can't pilot any of them.
There's nothing to worry about.
I'll roll him back to
the previous version,
so it's just like a
temporary downgrade.
Why are you doing it
in the first place?
Well, it's because of
the virus Han introduced.
You're talking about the Secret?
Yes.
When you were in Japan,
you brought Georg
into contact with it,
and in that moment,
all instances
of Georg were synchronized.
Because of that, Georg is now
a different kind of program:
one merged with the
awareness of a Secret.
It's far too dangerous
to continue using such an
unknown entity, so--
Did you make the
decision to delete him,
or did that come down the
pipeline from the higher-ups?
It would be the same either way.
We can't let it be known
that we had a Secret
burrowed into our system.
The Allies wouldn't
even negotiate with us.
Big Blue World already cut off
all our funding, didn't they?
What do you plan
to do about that?
I'm hoping the
decision can be reversed.
I want to make them
realize Generation Bleu
can still be of value to them.
To do that, dangerous
elements must---
Dangerous?
So now it's dangerous
to have contact
with a Secret again?
It always has been.
We were established to
fight against the Secrets,
and doing that is the only way
to keep this organization alive.
And what about Ivica?
How does he feel?
Does he want to keep fighting?
Leave him out of it.
No, I won't!
It's not about the company!
Tell me why you're
really doing this!
They've arrived.
The Poseidon was shot down.
We will avenge their deaths.
Is it true?
About the Poseidon?
We don't know yet, but
we're going to find out.
In accordance with the UN
resolution the Allied Forces
will seize all Quartz
possessed by Generation Bleu,
as well as the weapon
of mass destruction
that is believed to be a
product of that Quartz.
Furthermore, we
will prohibit them
from any further
use of IFOs or FPs.
Funding has been revoked,
and Generation Bleu,
as a business, has
already been shut down.
No one should remain
at headquarters
for any other purpose--
Ao, where's the Gun?
It's down in the basement
so it can be kept
under strict surveillance.
Places like this always tend
to have something
in the basement.
Things that look like this.
You don't want to
use it though, right?
You wouldn't understand,
even if I tried to explain.
No, I understand.
Oh, really?
If you fire it,
both the Secrets and the
Scub Corals will vanish.
The world will be changed.
It will become the
world I am from.
Uh, what?
I'm going to be
straight with you guys.
You should know.
I'm not a person of this world.
What?!
The manga obsession has to stop.
You've got it wrong, Fleur.
It isn't that I'm
obsessed with manga.
It's that I've experienced
something so manga-like,
that I can only have
faith in the impossible.
Which means what exactly?
Like I told you, I come
from a different world.
I want go back there--back
where I belong.
You'll return me to my world.
Right?
Why ask me?
Because it was Eureka
who brought me here
in the first place.
Hey, change of plans.
Whoops. Sorry.
You won't be launching
your IFOs now.
The Poseidon is okay after all?
Sorry.
Rebecka's just deleted
Georg from the IFOs.
We're reinstalling
an older version
of the program right now,
but it will take at least an
hour to reconcile the data.
But the Allies!
What if they launch
an attack against us?
I didn't mean to walk
in on you like that.
No big deal.
Ao was there.
You're totally fine
with him seeing it?
No, I'm not totally fine!
Oh, hey Dad.
What's up?
What're you doing here?
This is for your ears only.
Listen to me, Fleur, be
prepared to make a run for it.
What?
There's no saving
Generation Bleu at this point.
If it's just the two of us,
we can probably get away.
Give me a little while.
Don't be too mad at him.
First and foremost,
he's your father.
He's willing to abandon
the company,
if that's what it
takes to protect you.
That's kind of incredible.
Attention all IFOs.
Launch now!
Activating defensive grid.
Damn it, Christophe!
Where are you?
Come on, Fleur.
Let's get inside the Triton.
We'll be safer in there.
I have an idea.
Come with me.
Looks like they still
have power here.
But how's that possible?
What's that for?
Where's my-- the CEO?
He went inside.
Said something about
moving the Quartz Gun.
What is he thinking?
Sir?
Fleur, how could you?
Give it up.
My dad may be a stupid old man--
But he still knows me better
than anybody in the world.
Running away with him
like some cheap coward
and leaving everybody else
behind to clean up the mess.
He knows that's something
I would never do.
It's Truth!
You little brat.
What are you doing here, Ao?
I told you before.
I'm not letting you get
your hands on the gun.
Not ever.
It's the only link
I have to my mother.
It's not a weapon.
I won't let you use it like one.
That's enough!
I'll use this Quartz to change
the world, you can't stop me.
You okay?
Any injuries?
You're here!
I need a favor.
Look after Fleur.
Me? Why?
Today is the end
of Generation Bleu.
But there's still something
you and the others must do.
You have to find a way
to correct our mistake.
What mistake?!
What are you talking about?
It may be the Secrets were
not the enemy, after all.
But the Scub Corals were.
And theirs is the true
invasion of our world.
In countries all across the
globe, victims are being found
who have been
parasitized by the Scubs.
Like Naru, her illness.
Unfortunately, we
adults aren't very good
at rectifying this
kind of mistake.
We were utterly certain the
Secrets were malicious invaders.
We can't possibly admit
how wrong we've been,
but you, you of the younger
generation may figure out
a way to do what's right.
It's up to you.
Wait, Dad!
Come back!
The Nirvash will
still be able to fly,
even without Georg.
Get out of here.
Escape.
Fly away.
In the sky,
anything is possible!
What are you
playing at, old man?
Do you seriously think you
can take me on all by yourself?
You know, Truth.
I've read it, too.
The infamous book
that Johansson wrote.
I came away with a
certain hypothesis.
See, I think that you
are actually a Secret
who has lost his memories.
That's ridiculous!
You're wrong, both of you!
Did you know that when a
Secret encounters Quartz,
the result is a
gigantic explosion?
I imagine you'll
be no exception.
What do you mean?
There isn't much Quartz left.
Most of it transformed
into the Quartz Gun.
But, see, we have been
lucky enough to collect some
over the last few days.
And it's all stored right here.
Are you saying?
Wait! No!
Let's see if I'm right!
Dad, no!
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
In a last brave act,
Blanc sacrificed himself
to trigger a fusion blast.
To carry out his wish, Ao must
now reach for the Quartz gun.
As the boy searches
for the right path,
what will the adults do?
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 20:
"last message."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.