This feels so strange.
Flying alongside Japan.
Pied Piper One.
You good to go?
Yes.
Moving into flight formation.
He's got an
excellent visual on me.
Pretty impressive.
Sir?
Commence mock scenario
against the Allied Forces.
Roger that!
All looks clear in
the Hitoyoshi area.
Maintain 3000 altitude.
How are the fuel reserves?
Honestly, things are
looking pretty tight.
At this point the number
of sorties we're able
to field will depend
entirely on Han's father.
Wonderful.
Another problem
to add to the pile.
Nearing territorial waters.
Halt all ships!
Full reverse at once!
Warning.
Your ships are about to violate
Japan's territorial waters.
Please withdraw immediately.
This is Fleur Blanc.
She's officially
taken over leadership
of our company as
representative director.
It will come as no surprise
that the Allied Forces,
have again demanded that
we hand over Pied Piper.
And we have once again refused.
Thank you very much.
All right, now let's see to
hashing out the various details.
First, RA-301
regarding candidates
for the pilot of the Kyrie.
Yes.
Please let me
look over the list.
As of four-thirty p.m., the
special alert has been lifted.
The Allied Forces fleet
on the verge of violating
our territorial waters
heeded our warnings
and retreated to
international waters.
It's hard to remember now.
Was Okinawa like this, too?
Always on edge with
the rest of the world?
Yeah, I guess.
Good work in there.
You were very composed.
We might want to
take this suit in
a little in the back, though.
You think?
It used to be Rebecka's,
and Fleur can't quite fill--
Wanna grab something to eat?
My treat, of course, Miss CEO.
I just want to go
back to the hotel.
I have work to do there.
You guys go ahead and
have a good time, though.
Wait up, Fleur!
I'll be your bodyguard.
Maybe she's made peace
with her dad's death.
She is putting on a brave
face, but I doubt it.
So, what about the Elena issue?
Elena Peoples is
currently stationed
at the Allies' base in Guam.
Her betrayal of us is looking
more and more
real by the second.
Well.
Ivica and the others
should know.
Do you want me to tell them?
No, don't.
I would rather take
care of it by myself.
I can't breathe!
Everyone here is a
little on the old side.
They're IFO pilots?
I have heard Americans
tend to age more quickly,
so maybe that's it.
Actually, they're
all Coral Carriers.
This is the only unit in the
Allied Forces
to which Carriers
have been assigned.
That's enough.
It's the fruit of a
long-term research project
at Big Blue World.
We now know that Coral
Carriers have a high aptitude
for piloting IFOs,
even as adults.
Just me.
I'm the bad-ass loner that's in
every high school clique story!
Hi. I'm Maggie Kwan.
We girls should stick
together, don't you think?
Are you one of the
Coral Carriers, too?
No, of course not.
I'm younger than they are.
I grew up in Hong Kong,
you know, and we have
a Coral Plant located nearby
in the South China Sea.
I've been breathing Trapars
ever since I was little.
Same as you have.
So, what are Coral
Carriers, anyway?
Coral Carrier is the
term we use for somebody
who has parasitic Scub Corals
living inside their body.
At first the story was that
it was just an illness, but--
There's speculation that
it's actually the result
of a joint experiment
with Big Blue World
to artificially implant
Scubs into people.
Don't be shy.
You're a growing boy.
Order whatever you want.
Sky's the limit!
Right.
Yeah, This restaurant's a
regular haunt for pilots.
We love it.
You've been
living abroad, though,
so it might not be
what you're looking for.
No, really, this is perfect.
Everything's delicious so far!
Well, then,
give this a try, too.
So have you had any problems
with the new board, thus far?
No, it works great.
My guess is it's from the
research they were doing
when they thought they
were getting the Mark I.
The manufacturer
apparently has all kinds
of other equipment they
want you to try out.
Oh, that's right.
There're no FPs here, are there?
No, but we get along pretty
well without them, you'll see.
Where'd you get those?
They're really cute!
Can I have some?
Okay, I'm off to work now.
Naru dear.
I've been wondering.
What is you do
at work every day?
Lots of stuff.
We have discussions.
About the future of
the world, for example.
Sometimes we sing
with the Scub Corals.
Do the Scubs really sing, Daddy?
Coral Carriers, huh?
These last few months,
we've seen an explosion
in the number of cases.
There's a particularly
high concentration
of patients here in
the Okinawa region.
From what our analysis tells us,
Naru, you appear to be
the first one afflicted.
Interestingly, we've
noticed that many
of the patients seem to be
gathering on Iwato Island.
Right here.
In your vicinity.
What's your point?
You're looking at me like
I'm some kind of alien.
We're not really any different
than other people, you know.
Not at heart.
No more Coral plants!
Let the Scubs be free!
The Scub Corals are our friends!
No more Coral plants!
What's next?
What will you demand
once you've forced
the Coral plant to shut down?
All we want is for the Scubs
to be allowed to remain
in their natural state.
If we do that,
the Trapars will fill
this planet's atmosphere
on their own.
Hey, Naru!
You're late!
So, the Allies cut you off,
and you've been forced to
turn to our lowly country.
Yeah.
Well, here's a
friendly warning for ya.
They're just gonna take
advantage of you, too.
The smell.
The whole bar must be empty.
Take it easy.
Hey, what are
you looking at man?
Nakamura!
I think you've had enough.
Oh, yeah?!
You think you can
order me around
'cause of where you were born?
I'm a respectable
Japanese citizen, too!
Independence.
My old man and my grampa, hah!
Those stupid old men!
They called this place
their home, you know!
Yeah!
But then the Trapar boom came,
and they went back
to Naha, just like that!
I'll have you know.
So you're Okinawan?
I'm Japanese!
And I'm gonna make this
country a number one power!
Yeah.
Of course.
Number one, I tell ya!
You hear me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
"There is something deeply
wrong with this world."
A sentiment Truth liked to
repeat over and over again.
I'd thought the same
thing since I was little.
I wanted to find a
way to right the wrong.
To do that, I had
to join the JAF.
But does that justify
Truth's methods?
He wants to change the world
by plunging it into chaos.
Was that, some kind of vision?
We may have something
else in common.
Could be, you're from
another world, like I am.
So, there you have it.
There's not much
else to tell, really.
I was transported here
from that other world.
Where there's a heart
stamped on the moon.
That's me in a nutshell.
So, basically, you're an
alien from another dimension.
Ooh, lookin' at me
like I'm a troll.
An LFO?
So where?
Sorry.
Do know Ao?
A boy with blue hair?
And the Quartz--
what happened to it?
Eurekaaaaa!
I finally found you!
Now, take me back to my world!
Don't you remember me?!
Here, look!
Oh!
Are you that girl
from the other day?
You've grown up so much.
Not "the other day"!
Try five years!
Yes, it's been five years now.
Since you abandoned
me in the Caribbean Sea.
I had no other choice.
If I didn't do something,
you would have been
caught up in a Scub Burst.
I had to get you out of there.
Take me back!
I don't belong in this world!
I can't do that.
In my current state,
I have no control over
when or for how
long I can appear.
There's no way for me to return
you to your original time.
I'm so sorry.
What do mean original time?
Answer me!
Where I come from, there's
a heart mark on the moon.
It's a completely
different place than this!
A heart?
You saw that?
I still think you're mistaken.
This is the world
I saved you from.
It was just at an earlier
time, if that makes sense.
When you travel through time,
you can see my world, which
explains the mark on the moon.
How could I have been so wrong?
So, where is Ao?
Is he fighting against the Scub
Corals, like he's supposed to?
Damn you, Eureka!
Elena.
No, my name isn't Elena.
That's not me.
I don't belong here.
I'm from a different world.
A different world.
My wife was born on the
main island of Okinawa.
Ten years ago
she took the children
to visit the place
where she grew up.
I thought the Secret got them.
But now I know it was actually
because of the Scub Corals.
They did it.
So, let's do this.
Together, we can rid
the world of them.
Can we?
Really?
I hear that you're resigning.
So, what do you plan to do?
Yes, what are your
plans, Nakamura?
Nothing can change
my ultimate objective:
To see Japan as the world's
greatest superpower,
with the JAF at the helm.
Since coming to this world.
I have learned much
about human history.
Hitler.
Napoleon.
Alexander.
You are not the first human
to propose the things you
speak of, but in the end--
Well, goodbye.
Thanks for everything.
The year 2020, the Scub Burst
that occurred in
the Caribbean Sea.
There was another Burst in
the same area, back in 1981.
There were many children
who were caught in it.
some of whose bodies
were never found.
All members of the two-hundred-
and-fourth Special Squadron.
A Scub Burst appears
to have occurred
in the country of Indonesia.
If Eureka is
traveling through time
from one Scub Burst to another,
I have to tell Elena about this!
Elena.
Elena!
Please!
Answer me!
What the--?
The Secrets attacked
one of their own?
I don't understand.
The process is automatic.
We cannot stop it.
When a Scub appears,
so does a Secret.
But we have
resolved the situation,
as per our agreement with you.
In that case, it seems there's
nothing left for us to do.
Ivica, isn't there
something you're forgetting?
Done.
The Quartz is--
The Credo?!
I thought Goldilocks
didn't exist anymore.
It's me, Ao.
Elena.
Is it true that you
joined the Allied Forces?
Stop that!
Quit it, Nirvash!
That's Elena!
What's that about?
A guy high on
life being gracious?
Or maybe it's the graciousness
of a real-life chosen one.
Screw youuuuuu!
Wait, Elena!
Hey, stop it!
What's going on?!
Just like her!
Mother and son both
thinking I'm a fool!
Had enough?!
Son of Eureka!
I'll destroy you!!
Don't lock on, damn you!
We can't let Ao shoot Elena!
Get between them, quick!
Why, Elena?
No, you can't!
There's no choice.
He has to shoot!
How could you say that?!
We agree.
Whatever the cost, the Allied
Forces must not be allowed
to have the Quartz Gun
under their control.
Please, Elena!
Just listen to me!
I checked!
I looked into what
that Eureka woman said!
It was all true!
I know that voice.
Is that really you, Maggie?!
I figured it out.
I know who you are.
Long ago, your name was--
No, you're wrong!
It doesn't matter
what you say to me!
I'm going home, where I belong.
I'm from some place
better than this!
This isn't my world!
Shut up, you idiot!
This is the world you're from,
and you need to accept that!
There's no world for
you to go back to!
I see.
So that's why you were trying
to get me to fire the gun.
Elena.
Hold on.
This is all wrong.
I don't accept any of it!
That isn't my story!
No! This isn't how
it's supposed to be!
I'm a chosen one!
A mysterious character whose
true identity is unknown!
But like you, Ao, I'm destined
to finally return one day
to the world of my birth!
Elena.
Don't call me Elena!
It's all fake!
You're no fake, Elena!
You're still you!
Well?
Are you saying it was all a lie?
When you fought beside me?
When we were friends?
Shut up!
Listen!
I want to be with you, Elena!
Ao.
And Fleur, and the Chief.
and Noa!
I'm not leaving you guys.
I went looking for
my mother and found you.
You're my family now.
So, let's go home together.
What do you say?
Yeah.
I know.
The things I love.
I love them because they
will always be out of reach.
In the end, it doesn't matter.
However far I go, I'll
be under the same sky.
What's that light?!
It's him!
Truth!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
It'll be easy.
Shoot the Gun now.
Destroy them.
Destroy everything!
To be continued!
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Truth appears again, in
an even more dangerous form.
The war between him and
Ao has been a long one,
but now their
final battle begins,
and the real story of
Truth will be revealed.
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 22:
"coral carriers."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.