The Secret's distance to the
Scub Coral is four kilometers.
Not long now.
Georg, it's type?
Yes, Miss Halström, ma'am.
We're comparing notes with HQ;
several of its
forms seem similar
to the one that appeared in
South America back in the 1940s.
Unfortunately, as there
are few photographs,
this information is based
mainly on old sketches...
Estimated time of arrival?
Eleven minutes, sir.
Secret arriving at
Scub Coral in eight minutes.
At which point, a large-scale
Scub Burst will certainly occur.
Too late!
We can't wait until
we arrive to launch.
Let us out now!
Elena, you heard Fleur.
Do you agree with her?
Yeah, sure.
I'll go, too.
Good!
No! What?
I still haven't gotten a hold
of the Okinawa
Self-Defense force yet.
What the hell?
It can't be helped.
We don't have a
signed contract yet.
Those idiots should know better
than anyone what's
about to happen.
I'm not giving it to you!
I'm not giving it up!
Never, you hear me?
I mean it!
Never!
I guess you'll have
to come with us, then.
Wait, what?
It's not like we're
using the confusion
to hustle some little kid.
You're island-born, aren't you?
Look at everything
that's happened here.
You want the chance
to do something about it?
Attention, JAF transport
vessel: you are violating
the territorial waters
of United Okinawa.
This is a warning!
No response.
Damn mainlanders.
Captain!
We've received orders to
meet up with Generation Bleu.
You mean that
overblown rescue team?
And they want us to just
let the JAF ship go free?
The first Scub Burst
we've seen in ten years
and it's the same day the JAF
choose to violate our waters.
Am I supposed to buy that
it's all a big coincidence?
Guess they won't be
bothering with us, yet.
Looks like they've
got bigger fish to fry.
What does that matter?
If the Secret makes
contact with the Scub Coral,
this area won't be safe.
You hear that, men?
We're leaving these waters now!
Hey, look at that!
The G-Monster's going away!
The key to a military FP?
Yeah, the JAF folks
have been looking for it.
This thing?
I figure we can use it to
make them cooperate with us.
No way!
They are the enemy!
If they won't play ball,
we'll swipe the FP and drive
the monster away ourselves.
Look there.
Scub Coral?
That's the first time
I've seen the real thing.
Can you believe the size of it?
We've got to do
something about it quickly.
Huh?
We've got to do something?
Remember what the textbooks say?
In the wake of a Scub Burst
comes a G-Monster.
A monster that
destroys everything!
But that special rescue group
will take care
of it, won't they.
Yeah, and what if those
guys don't show up?
I still don't
know what we can do!
Me either!
But if we do nothing,
then the island is doomed!
That figures.
Those JAF bastards
are gone already.
We expected that.
Well, Han, where to?
Just a sec.
I used the SDF ships to
extrapolate their movements.
Location coming your way now!
Got it!
Let's go!
What's the meaning of this?
Secrets are supposed
to target Scub Coral.
So why is that
thing coming after us?
Yell all you want, I don't know!
Captain!
What is it?
There is an unknown
FP approaching us.
No.
They're back!
It's those couriers!
Are you crazy?
You're going to board a
ship while it's on the move?
Its relative speed is too fast!
Ha!
Not for us.
We've got this baby
for just such an occasion.
What?
Wow!
I had no idea you could use
an FP's anchors like that.
Cool, huh?
Hey.
There's something
moving down there,
and it doesn't look friendly.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
They're bringing us the key!
Keep your pants on!
We're just firing warning shots!
The Secret.
It's stopping!
What now?
Sir, from what we can tell,
it appears to be turning
its main gun on us!
What?
Oh, crap. Oh, crap.
Oh, crap!
This is bad!
This is very, very,
very, very, very bad!
Damn it!
Break the front windshield, kid!
Huh?
Just do it!
Okay!
Now we can see!
An FP?
Ow, that hurt!
Get in! Get in!
What?
That's the JAF's FP!
Get in it!
But...
Just shut up and do it!
You've got the key, remember?
If you don't use it,
who's going to?
Hey!
No way.
It's got power!
I can do this, I can do this!
Okay, the basic
layout's the same.
It'll be fine.
I know can do this.
I have to...
...for the island.
Ao.
It's the Aratas!
Naru!
Here, we've gotcha.
Thank you.
I swear, it's starting to seem
like our country can
never catch a break.
I need to hurry
or I won't be able
to save myself,
much less the island...
Hey, it's synching with the FP?
What the?
Welcome home...
Welcome home?
Welcome home, Eureka?
This is strange,
it suddenly activated.
What's the heck's going on here?
Whoa what was that?
The Mark I!
He did it!
Look at the kid go!
That's great but what
are we supposed to do?
Uh.
Hey there, need a lift?
I'll give you a
really good deal.
Jeez!
Took you long enough.
The Secret's rate of
advance is holding steady.
There's been no response
from Okinawa SDF, either.
Nothing we can do, huh?
Miss Hallström, there appears to
be a bug in the ID code system.
A bug?
What kind?
Well, the IFO that's rapidly
approaching the Secret appears
to have the same identification
code as the Mark I,
which was supposedly
expunged last year.
What did you say?
What, it has arms?
Don't tell me,
this thing is an IFO?
Okay.
Here we go.
Here we go. Here we go.
This is so kind.
And you haven't
even found Ao, yet.
It's not a problem.
The boy knows he can find
me at the Central Clinic.
I never expected you to help us.
I'm a doctor!
You're the one who
harbored that woman.
The island changed
when she showed up.
That woman brought suffering
and misfortune with her.
The children of this
island deserve better.
And what about the woman's son?
He's a child of the island.
Right?
I have to do something!
But I don't know what to do!
Wait, was that?
It can't be!
Have you come back to us?
Or, maybe?
Don't leave a single man behind!
Hear me?
Save every last person!
Captain! They're here!
About time!
You're beyond late,
Generation Bleu bastards!
Mark I.
The first IFO in
the whole world.
Except, it was
ruled non-functional.
So I thought it got
dumped in the Smithsonian.
Is there an
Allied pilot flying it?
But it's like amateur
hour out there!
He's deliberately bringing the
Secret closer to the Scub Coral!
The Scub Coral?
Oh crap! What am I doing?
If that G-monster
destroys the Scub Coral.
The island, no!
Ao.
Don't cry, Ao.
It missed?
No, wait.
I think.
It can't see me!
That giant bastard can't see me!
The trapar concentration
is at seventeen.
Maybe that's it?
At higher readings,
it can't see?
All-e-luia here.
The Scub Coral is alive.
So far, so good on that front.
What's with this trapar storm?
Its Third Engine is running.
Huh?
On the Mark I.
None of the researchers
could ever get it working.
They never even
knew what it did.
Wait, the Third Engine?
Impossible!
The IFO is up on two feet!
It's standing!
Feel it! I've got to feel it.
Work with the trapar winds!
Oh like hell it's lost!
Get it back!
It was ten years ago
that the Mark I was
last confirmed operational.
That was in Okinawa,
prior to independence.
The largest Scub Burst
in history occurred...
Hey, look at the guy who
was piloting that thing.
Yeah, you're right.
He's got blue hair!
What was that?
IFO.
Do you copy?
You're not broadcasting
your international call sign.
Identify your nationality
and affiliation.
No!
I repeat.
You are not broadcasting
your international call sign.
Identify your nationality
and affiliation.
Bye-bye!
I'll go after him.
You keep watch since we
haven't collected the Quartz.
Try to play nice, Fleur.
That's up to him.
That was incredible!
I can't believe he
took out the G-Monster.
I don't like this at all.
What's wrong?
You jealous?
Me? No way!
It's just.
I don't know what,
but there's something
I don't like about this.
Oh, come on!
Where'd that guy disappear to?
What?
Oh.
Welcome back.
You're, I mean that uniform.
Yup.
You got it.
I'm Generation Bleu.
Although, rescuing
boys who fall asleep
in the ocean isn't usually
part of my job description.
Oh.
Thank you.
So?
So what?
So, where'd you hide it?
Is it close by?
Hide what?
Oh.
You're playing it cool.
Uh, I'm sorry!
Such bad manners.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Fleur Blanc.
What's your name?
I'm Ao Fukai.
Oh that's cool, Ao Fukai.
Adorable name.
Huh, what?
Ouch!
Hey that hurt!
It is him!
He's got blue hair, but
that's Fukai's brat for sure.
I don't get it.
What's Gen Bleu want
with some little kid?
Hey you don't think she's
hitting on him, do you?
Why would you even think that?
Obviously, it's the FP
that they're interested in.
I've seen enough.
Let's get out of here, guys.
Uh, what?
Where are we going?
Well, let's see.
How about we go and
do a little caving?
It's been a while.
It's that kid of yours.
The base isn't happy.
Your brat was aboard that thing!
I know nothing about this.
I thought you
were of this island
but maybe I was
wrong, Mr. Niigaki.
You know I work
at the base, Fukai.
If it helps, you can think
of me as an SDF messenger.
Now, where is the boy?
I'm about to go look for him.
He's just a normal child.
This IFO stuff is nonsense!
Normal?
We have a witness who
says he's got blue hair now.
Mama! Mama! Mama!
Mama! Mama!
I'm so sorry, my Ao.
Impossible!
Are you saying it was Ao?
The boy operated that thing?
Rumor has it the
pilot had blue hair.
You think some other
mysterious foreigner
turned up out of the blue?
Naru! Lie back!
So, what do we do?
We catch him
before the SDF does.
Where'd he get a hold
of an IFO like that?
Was it Japan?
The Allies?
We'll do what we
must to make him talk.
Anything to reinforce
our independence.
Okay, I'll be right back!
Naru?
Using the ladies', maybe?
Sis said I can't tell you.
He's not here, either.
That only leaves one place.
Ao.
Dad and them are
looking for you.
So is the SDF.
And that group
called Generation Bleu.
You're a celebrity.
I thought I was
protecting the island.
What?
But maybe I was wrong.
Maybe I'm a freak like my mom.
Was it all my fault,
the monster coming here?
Stop that.
Look what's happened to me.
Pretty freaky, huh?
Blue hair.
I saw it in my dreams.
You had blue hair
and you were fighting in
the Sea Colossus for me.
Ten years ago, the giant
was protecting me, too.
It was like that.
Thank you.
Hey, Naru.
I have something.
Incredible!
That's it?
This, this is yours, Ao.
Your Sea Colossus.
To be continued.
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
When the dust
settles after the storm,
Ao finds more
danger awaiting him.
The boy is captured by those
who cannot lay the
ghosts of the past to rest.
Some fear him,
some want to use him.
But who will come to his aid?
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 3:
"secret operation."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.