Of course.
Everybody around
here knows Miller.
And this is the place
where she was singing
when she got recruited?
By Generation Bleu, wasn't it?
Who else could he be
talking about, Gazelle?
It's got to be her.
You heard about that?
Yeah, mate, it's not
like this is Las Vegas.
Did find it a bit
odd for a business
to scoop up a musician
like that, though.
It is Gen Bleu.
That big of a company has its
fingers in all kinds of pies.
Right.
And her contract was
only for six months.
What is it you blokes
are trying to find out?
The truth about the
woman known as Miller!
Hey, man.
Is this a photo of her?
Yeah.
So Miller definitely
was a real singer.
I still say this is impossible.
Either of you guys ever
seen Miller perform?
She's all sexy and passionate
when she's up on stage.
A true artist, you
know what I mean?
Compared to her, this other
chick's just a fan girl.
We have to go to America.
Again, why?
To visit the hometown of
Elena Peoples, right?
Kyrie! Kyrie!
Do you copy?
Elena?
Who's Elena?
Oh, sorry, are you
talking to me?
Is this another dumb manga game?
I don't think so, Ao?
There's still no sign
of a Secret around here.
There can be no
doubt that a Scub Burst
has recently occurred.
The appearance of Scub Corals
and Secrets is accompanied
by pillars of light.
And such pillars have indeed
been sighted on this occasion.
We can be certain
that the Secret is
closing in on the Scub.
That's something I've
been wondering about.
What are those weird lights?
Well, uh, That's difficult to--
Does anybody know
where Scub Corals
and Secrets come from?
Various theories
have been put forth
regarding the origins
of these phenomena.
The scientific community has
not yet reached a consensus.
Some believe that
the Trapars undergo
a kind of chemical change
and amass together.
This is the spontaneous
occurrence theory.
Others suggest that
there is another place,
different from our w--!
My nose!
We don't really have time for
an in-depth scientific lecture.
Okay, Ao?
Yes, ma'am.
The dust filters
can't take any more.
Head back for now an--
Oh.
I'm clear.
I have a visual on the
Scub Coral, but still no Secret.
What the hell is that thing?
Nothing in our data.
Maybe it's Truth pulling
another stunt or something.
Truth again?
That bastard!
Hold on!
You can't blindly
charge into the ZOA!
Currently, there is
no evidence of a Secret
or the life signs that would
indicate Truth's presence.
Are you sure, Georg?
Are you malfunctioning?
I didn't think I hit you hard
enough to cause any real damage!
Aww, you broke him!
No!
Are you seeing things, Ao?
There's no sign of Truth here.
He disappeared.
I saw him!
I know I did!
Right in front of me!
You know thinking about
your little girlfriend
is clouding your judgment.
Did someone wake up
on the wrong side
of the bed this morning?
Rumor has it
she got into another
fight with President Dad.
Don't call him that,
It's ridiculous!
Was there a fight, sir?
I don't understand what
all the fuss is about.
I just asked her how things
were going with Ao lately.
That stupid old man!
Could he be more wrong?
Like there'd ever be
anything between us!
You're younger than me!
And you're already
in love, anyway.
We're just friends!
Plus, she's got a
crush on someone else.
Don't you, Fleur?
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you!
You won't get away!
Not this time!
What's that?
Aww, jeez.
Good likeness.
Damn smug face!
Stupid old man!
It's Dad all marked up!
We can't say for certain
if we've completely
driven off the Secret.
There should be no
need for further action.
Just as long as you've
collected the Quartz
and stabilized the situation.
I'll advise the Australian
government to stay on alert,
just in case.
Uh, if it helps any,
it didn't look all that
much like you, sir.
Hello?
Hey, Mr. Blanc!
You listening?
Of course I am.
Tell me, how's the
investigation coming along?
The facility's been shut down.
Yes, I expected as much.
It makes sense;
I was told there weren't very
many children left anymore
by the time we took Elena in.
What kind of place
is this, anyway?
There's no data on it.
As you may know,
there are certain
children who are born
with the innate
ability to pilot IFOs.
Ao was like that.
It's not entirely clear,
but some believe that
being born in a region
with high Trapar
concentration causes changes
to occur in the brain.
Certain countries
conducted research
on the subject
by using children.
That's what they did there.
You mean Elena was
raised at this facility?
Are you still working
under the assumption
that she and Miller
are the same person?
You saw the footage
from the surveillance
cameras, didn't you?
They appeared to show Miller,
the musician contracted
to our company.
Yes, I'm aware of her
suspicious behavior.
I've taken a look at her logs.
Based on those, she's most
likely an intelligence asset
sent in by the United States.
But the idea that she
and Elena Peoples
are one and the same is
nothing more than conjecture.
Your own personal hypothesis.
Elena has been in training
with Generation Bleu
for over two years.
That's it, then.
So much for your grand theory.
She was in IFO pilot
training at the company.
So how could she be playing
music in Manchester?
What's the deal?
You look pissed off, man.
I'm thinking about
what Truth said to me.
You demand the truth of me,
but you can't even see it.
The truth reveals
itself only to those
who are courageous
enough to embrace it.
He called me out.
He said there's something
wrong with the world,
and I'm not brave enough
to see the truth of it.
Yeah, sure, we remember.
So what about it?
I don't know.
Come on, man.
Whatever it is though,
I don't like it!
This is twenty stories
beneath headquarters.
The emergency stairs
seem to end here.
But I believe that
there are levels
even further down than this.
This doesn't look
like it was built
by any civilization on Earth.
I know it may sound crazy,
but it's like it's from
a different world.
You're telling me
that this isn't Miller?
Correct, sir.
Miller was a covert
operative that
we had selected together
with British intelligence.
She was carefully prepared
so that she'd be able
to contract out with
Generation Bleu.
Yes, I remember.
Some funds from IFO procurement
were put toward that project.
Naturally, we collected data on
all identifying characteristics.
This woman looks very similar,
but her voiceprint shows
a subtle discrepancy.
Also, we have this from an asset
who's serving as her
producer I had him collect
a saliva sample and
we tested the DNA.
She's a completely
different person!
For the past two months
at the very least.
The person we have
been in contact with
has not been Miller.
Okay, then who the hell is she?
That's impossible!
Sure enough, we're going
to have to strip down
all the armor to
get it clean again.
Damn sand!
No fun!
How long is Stanley going to be
acting as our chief, anyway?
Whining won't help anything.
Did you notice he was marking
down changes in our weight?
That's got to make you
feel self-conscious, Sis.
What?
So I've put on a little weight,
what's the big deal?
It doesn't matter who it is.
No one can replace Bruno.
No of course not.
What I wouldn't give
for one last hug
from that big old teddy bear.
Chief!
Is Goldilocks being scrambled?
What are you talking about?
Sir look!
Stop them!
Bruno!
My name is, Miller.
My name is, Elena.
My name is...
It's Miller.
Elena.
Today was just a fake-out.
But I am going to
find Truth, then, I'll--!
Uh, what's up?
It's like I told you!
We're going together!
Yeah, I've been waiting!
Let's go!
The sky's so pretty!
Yeah!
The sky over Iwato!
What are you doing here?
Why isn't Ao with you?
That looks like Goldilocks!
Aw!
Why are you running away?
So many teddy bears!
Teddy! Teddy!
Come on!
Come to Chloe!
Alex!
The children are they ok?
I shut down their systems.
We're about to open
up the cockpits.
Let me go!
The teddy bear!
Right, bring them
here immediately.
Just hold still now, okay?
I have to save her!
Maman, Please!!
Maman! Maman!
Our medical team has
assured us that giving you
oxygen will stop
the hallucinations.
Start treatment.
Maman! Maman!
Georg's theory was correct.
The Trapars are
complicating things.
Those minute foreign
particles that got into
their bodies are reacting
with the Trapars in the air,
flooding their brains
with too many stimuli.
We adults aren't affected by it,
but their brains have
absorbed Trapars since birth.
That causes them to react
differently than we would.
The stimuli
induce hallucinations.
I can have maintenance reinforce
the air conditioning
filters so the Trapars
can be extracted from the air.
But we still need
to figure out how
to get that stuff safely
out of their bodies.
To think every one of those
tiny particles is a Secret.
I'm concerned about
how this will affect them.
In particular Ao.
You know he differs
from us genetically.
Ao, and Elena, as well.
Where are we?
Shh.
Wow!
That's crazy!
What is this?
Don't you remember
what you said?
You told me that you wanted
to see the real thing.
Here we are!
This venue is normally
adults only, so we're lucky.
Hey, Miller.
That's you, isn't it?
Where have you been hiding?
Your absence has
been noticed, Miller.
Anyway, your presence
has been requested, come.
Ao, Elena.
Come on!
We have to go!
Hey!
I thought we were
at headquarters!
We were being tricked
into thinking that.
This isn't the
real world anymore.
We're someplace else.
Some different world.
Ao, you can get us
back where we belong.
I'm sure of it!
Okay, I guess I can try.
Let's go!
That's the SDF!
Pippo's dad and some other guys.
Elena, take Ao.
I've got this.
Why would a member
of Team Pied Piper
be posing as an operative
and sending us information?
Feeding us fake intel, maybe?
No, that isn't it!
That's impossible.
Things will be different
when we're back in
the real world, Ao.
Yeah?
It'll be a lot easier.
We won't have to
fight anyone there.
We'll just--
Quit while you're ahead, Miller.
It's like you're setting the
flag for your own death.
Oh, it is, huh?
Uh, what was that about a flag?
Am I missing the joke here?
Should we fire a warning shot?
Not necessary.
The car's electric.
It's been adjusted to
block the direct intake
of air from outside.
Can you hear me?
Ao?
Elena?
Hey that's the chief!
Don't let them fool you.
We have to get out
of this place, together.
She's right, Ao.
I know, I've seen it.
A different place, somewhere
outside this stupid world.
You've been looking
for it, too, haven't you?
Don't worry, I'll do it!
I'll find a way to
get you off the island.
Island?
Naru, Mama!
You know, you remind
me a lot of myself.
I bet we could have been related
in a past life or something.
Then, maybe you know.
Huh?
Who am I?
Tell me!
You know, don't you Miller?
So, it's me.
Elena!
What're you doing?
She's a spy!
We've been infiltrated
by the enemy.
The enemy?
Fire!
Stop the car!
What did I say to you
about setting your flag?
Noa!
I've been looking
for you, fur ball.
Where have you been?
Really?
You're sure about that?
Yes, they were definitely
two different people.
Of course, Miller is nothing
more than a pile of ashes now.
I can't fund any
further investigation.
Wait, sir! Hold on!
Hey!
And after we finally
found somebody
who knew the Peoples family.
Her childhood's
ancient history, anyway.
So what does it
matter at this point?
We're going!
I'm surprised you're looking
into Elena's accident now,
after all this time.
Accident?
You're reopening the
investigation, right?
It was about five years ago.
Poor Elena was out on a
cruise in the Caribbean
when she was caught
in a Scub Burst.
The master took
her loss very badly.
He fell ill shortly after.
I don't understand.
Elena Peoples is with Gen--
Oh, that's Elena a year
before she passed away.
Wasn't she beautiful?
That means, the Elena
Peoples we know today is?
Elena, we're supposed
to be resting!
Just giving it some water!
I was feeling blue,
but I'm better now.
Good night, Miller.
Sleep well.
You too, Elena.
To be continued.
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
With the fate of the
world on their shoulders,
Pied Piper launches into space.
Combat among the stars
proves difficult for Ao.
When all seems lost, silver
wings appear in the sky,
and what they reveal
will shock Ao to his core.
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 12:
"heaven and earth."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.