Naru?
Come back.
Please, Naru!
At least tell me why!
Why would you choose Truth?
Just come back!
It's not too late!
What, is this?
Naru! Naru!
Wait!
Naru!
Ao! Ao!
Can't really say
I approve of this.
No, of course.
I'm sorry!
I was double checking something
and I guess I dozed off.
That's not what I meant.
On the contrary
I was talking about
all the long hours you've
been pulling lately.
Recovering your strength is
part of a pilot's job, too.
Yeah, I know that but still.
Since mine is the only
Third Engine that works,
it's important that
I stay on top of things.
I have to work to stay strong.
What did you do that for?
Go home and rest.
Our IFOs might be very forgiving
but they can't be
piloted by zombies.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Hey!
Ao!
Special delivery!
We finally got the
replacement parts in!
We've had you making do
with Kyrie's spare parts.
But starting with
the next mission,
the Nirvash will be
back to its old self.
Everyone's counting on you, Ace!
Yeah...
What are you doing
up so late, Chief?
Pulling some overtime?
Yeah there's just something
that's been bothering me.
I mean, doesn't it bug you?
This stuff with the Secrets?
Since the operation off
the coast of Ogasawara?
It's true the number of
appearances has risen.
And that's not all.
It started back in Arizona.
Since that mission,
the Secrets have been
rapidly learning more
about human beings.
And then there's that
radio wave Georg detected.
Has it been...?
The unidentified radio wave
registered near Ogaswara
has been detected seven more
times during subsequent battles.
Analysis of the wave
is not yet complete,
but with each appearance,
the gain on it had increased.
Christophe, what do
you think of this business
with the Japanese government?
That nonsense they're spouting?
That the Scubs are some kind
of inter-dimensional invaders
and the Secrets are
acting like white blood cells,
or whatever the analogy was?
We have to take it with
a grain of salt, of course,
but the fact is
that some countries
are actually taking
their claim seriously.
Our people are looking into it.
I'll have a report for you soon.
I look forward to hearing it.
Well, whether it's
the Secrets or the Scub.
The side we support will likely
end up being the right one.
I have one more question.
It's about that strange
Quartz substance
that you people
have been extracting
from Scubs and squirreling away.
I don't believe any of
that was ever found here.
Not even when you ran
that little undercover op.
You do realize I can easily
go over your head on this.
That sounds like
a hollow threat.
Big Blue World is simply
one of our shareholders.
Neither of us has
authority over the other.
We are conducting a
company-wide health screening.
All personnel should
consult the schedule
and follow instructions.
Anything unusual health-wise?
Like dizziness?
Or nausea?
Nothing, not really.
Well, maybe.
Excuse me.
It's time for
your shuttle ma'am.
Roger.
I have to go.
Send me the data later.
Sure.
Something wrong?
No.
It's nothing. I'm fine.
It's unusual, huh?
I mean, Mom Hannah
doesn't come down
from the space
station very often.
She's here because,
well, you know.
There are lots of
rumors going around.
About Ao and how
different he must be
because of who his mother is.
Eureka's supposed
to be pretty, isn't she?
I wonder if that's something
Ao got from her, too.
That woman's done nothing
but make Ao's
life more difficult.
By the way, Elena.
You were acting
weird the other day...
...after Eureka showed up.
What was that about?
That's classified information.
I'm done.
They said they want
to see Chloe next.
Oh thanks!
It's so obvious.
This company-wide
screening is a bunch of BS.
You just wanted a
chance to examine Ao.
What are you talking about?
I'm curious. What did
you discuss with Eureka?
Was it something about how
Trapars are harmful to humans,
by any chance?
Tell me something.
Eh?
Say there's a woman.
And she makes a
selfish decision.
She has a child, heedless
of the consequences.
What woman wouldn't
understand her actions?
Even if they changed the world.
Changed the world?
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
Do you have what I asked for?
Here. Sleeping pills,
as ordered.
No real side effects,
just don't take too many.
What do I owe?
This one is on the house.
We island boys
got to stick together.
Thanks a lot!
I felt weird asking for
the prescription mys--
This not being able to
sleep thing isn't physical.
It's what Eureka said, isn't it?
About how Secrets
aren't the enemy,
like we've always thought.
That's what's keeping
you up at night.
You don't always
know everything.
Shh!
So, onto the reason
you are all here.
This is it.
The Secret we found
and gave sanctuary to.
Now, are there any questions?
I have one!
The secret, is it
a type of machine,
or alive?
We've found both organic
and inorganic
substances in his body.
Neither infrared
scans nor x-rays
have shown anything
about his internal structures.
We cannot yet say whether
or not he is a living being.
However, unlike other
Secrets we've encountered,
he emits a radio wave within
a specific frequency band.
We determined that it was
a signal of some sort,
and so we sent back a
radio wave of our own.
This is first contact.
Did you follow IAA protocol?
What's the IAA?
The International Academy
of Astronautics.
That is correct.
We began with information
found in the natural world,
such as prime numbers,
after which,
we gradually taught him
the human linguistic system.
As a result.
Send him the message
"Can you understand the signal
we are broadcasting to you?"
That was unexpected.
I didn't think the Japanese
would go public so soon.
I wonder what they're up to now.
What's their
end game in all this?
Maybe it's not a trick.
What if their theory
actually is correct?
And the Secrets
really are helping
to guard this
universe from invaders?
No.
That's highly unlikely.
Sorry.
Blanc here.
What is it?
Go ahead.
What?
Mr. Han Juno, I believe?
I've had the pleasure of meeting
your father a couple of times.
What does your government have
to do with the Trapar business?
Our country has any
number of financial dealings.
Your father's company showed
an interest in doing business,
and we saw no reason
to turn them down.
On the US mainland?
I am certain we
extracted the Quartz
from that Scub Coral
and stabilized it.
So how could this be happening?
It is unprecedented.
There is not a single
recorded instance
of a Scub Coral
reactivating like this.
According to the database--
Forget what the database says.
We have reports that a Secret
has already appeared on-site.
It's simple enough, isn't it?
We just go in
and beat the thing.
I'm still outside the ZOA, but
I have a visual on the Secret.
Hold on!
It's humanoid!
Hey, Fleur!
Now's our chance.
Elena?
I'm ready!
Launching rockets!
We did it!
Or did we?
No way!
Not a scratch?
Super Alloy?
But the real stuff is
made out of zinc alloy.
Hey, guys!
Cover me, okay?
What?
Ao wait!
Long-range attacks don't
cut it against Secrets.
I'm taking the Nirvash in
for close-quarters combat.
No way!
Those don't look like missiles,
so how are they
homing in on him?
Ao move it! Hurry!
What do you think I'm doing?
Damn!
I'm not going to die that easy!
Ao was shot down?
I hope he's okay.
They say that his
life isn't in danger.
Pied Piper will rescue him
while we go in and
finish the mission.
This whole thing is just crazy.
We've never seen a plant
become active again like this.
Top priority goes to
protecting the plant.
We'll do what we can to
rescue the wounded later.
What are you doing?
No unauthorized personnel!
I hear that Ao and the
Nirvash were shot down.
If you don't have enough
people to retrieve him,
the Gazelle Agency will
gladly take the contract.
He's right, we're shorthanded.
Accept his offer.
Got it?
Great!
So what now?
You bastard!
Be careful how you approach it.
Once it locks on you
won't be able to shake it.
Wait what do you mean?
So is that it?
It homed in on the
Nirvash and took it down?
Ao! Ao!
This is the Triton, Ao.
Do you copy?
Testing! Testing!
This is the Rakan.
I've retrieved the pilot.
Please deal with the IFO.
Over!
It's that punk.
What is he doing here?
That's a surprise.
You're a good pilot.
Trying' to fly, here!
Five against one,
and we still aren't
making any headway.
A lot of calls are coming in.
From various countries.
Apparently, plants are
reactivating all over the world.
Impossible!
The plant is active again?
That can't be right!
My call won't go through!
We are in the process
of setting up a landline.
Please remain calm.
We're doing all that we can.
Demands are coming in from
every corner of the Earth.
We're going to have to split up
to deal with any
Secrets that appear.
That's the only way
we can handle them all.
Against these things?
We'll run the children ragged!
I don't see any other
option at this point, do you?
We have no idea how they're
reactivating themselves,
but every Scub has a Quartz,
so we need to act fast.
Okay?
Where am I?
Chloe.
We've traded places, huh?
What about the Nirvash?
Have I screwed things up again?
Kind of.
That's becoming a
habit of yours, isn't it.
I'm sorry.
Tell me something.
The Secrets are the
enemy, aren't they?
Huh?
They must be, right?
The enemy.
Wish I knew how to answer that.
What are you guys
sitting in the hall for?
Shh!
You see?
A Coral plant.
It's all lit up.
It's in Norway.
Specifically the
Vesterålen Islands.
It's where Maeve and
I lived before becoming pilots.
We're originally from Ireland,
but our family emigrated in
order to work at the plant.
We moved there not
long after I was born.
Where are your mother
and father now?
They still live in Norway.
I'm so scared I'm going
to lose them, too.
Like we lost Bruno.
I have to protect them.
No matter what,
I have to keep them safe.
I'm sorry, but we're
being scrambled.
You ready?
I've been thinking
about something.
Seems like this is all
connected to your mom.
It all started when multiple
Eurekas began showing up.
Weird things just
keep on happening.
Plants reactivating,
Naru going crazy.
That's ridiculous.
Think about it!
I don't need to.
There's no way that can be true.
Another Secret's appeared.
There are just too many.
We'd have a chance,
if there was a way to
gather them all in one place.
We can use me as bait.
It came after Nirvash
last time, didn't it?
You can't!
But there was more
than one Nirvash
involved in that
battle, remember?
Eureka isn't here now.
It won't work.
That's enough
arguing, you three!
Standby in your cockpits
'til we choose a plan of action.
But Chief?
Yes, sir.
We're going.
Hold on a sec!
Quit squirming.
Let me go!
That's enough, Ao.
We are in position.
We will use my
auto-translation algorithm.
That should make it possible
to analyze the radio wave
being sent out by the Secret.
We can then transfer the
data back to headquarters.
We're all counting
on you, Georg.
What the hell are
you two doing here?
This guy?
He was in the
auditorium earlier.
Boys.
Signal has been captured.
Contact!
Signal.
Analyze.
Respond!
Hey that didn't sound good.
You all right?
Yes, I am fine.
Who are you?
My name's Han Juno.
I work with Generation Bleu.
I am what you and your
kind refer to as a Secret.
Did the bastards hack us?
You're a Secret?
Tell us, what are you?
Where are you from?
Who or what created you?
I was created in
order to eliminate
unwelcome foreign
bodies from this universe.
There is no "where" or "who."
I am a natural
product of evolution.
Then explain what's
happening now.
If you're really a
Secret, you should know.
Why are Scubs across the
globe becoming active again?
I will tell you.
Ten years ago, a giant
Quartz disappeared
from the Scub near the
island that you call Okinawa.
What do you suppose has happened
to the Quartz over
the last ten years?
We get it.
Now, leave the Scubs to us.
We cannot do that.
Our sole purpose is to
eliminate the Scub Corals.
As long as the Scubs continue
to appear in this universe,
we will continue to
pursue and destroy them.
They have no choice.
The Secrets appear
automatically when something
from another universe
invades this one.
If that's truly
the case, I wonder.
Don't get any stupid ideas.
Big Blue World will want to
be kept in the loop on this.
Get me the
US Secretary of State!
Tell him it's urgent.
But there's no other way!
What are you going to do?
Disobey orders?
You wanted to discuss
something, Christophe?
We don't have much time,
so I'll cut to the chase.
We know why Scubs everywhere
are becoming active again.
It has to do with the
substance called Quartz,
about which you were
inquiring the other day.
That's my dad.
What's he saying?
Shut down communications!
Immediately!
We know why the Secrets appear.
Their objective is the
Quartz's destruction.
That means we can get
them all in one place.
We simply need a massive amount
of Quartz to lure them in.
An amount greater than
we've ever seen before.
And where do you suppose that
we can find so much Quartz?
That's enough!
Keep quiet, Blanc!
Generation Bleu has the answer.
For years, we have worked
in absolute secrecy
to collect the Quartz from
every Scub we have stabilized.
We have stored them in a
secure location, in space.
And we will now use that Quartz
to wipe out every single
Secret in this world!
It's time to end this!
To be continued!
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Operation Polaris
is set into motion.
Despite his exhaustion
and uncertainty,
Ao moves to the
forefront of the struggle.
When a difficult
decision must be made,
what will the boy choose?
And what consequences
will he face?
Eureka Seven AO, Episode 16.
"next phase."
Hear the cry of the
children of the stars.