[cicadas chirp]
I finally made it
back to the shop.
[grunts]
It's friggin' hot.
[clattering]
[gasps]
A crash?
[KOKONOTSU whimpers]
Hey, who's in there?
[HOTARU yelps]
[gasps]
It sounds like Kokonotsu
has finally returned!
Are you kidding me?
Have you ever heard about
blind wine tasting before?
You have to guess what
wine you're drinking
without seeing it first.
[KOKONOTSU grunts]
You do know I'm not in
front of you, right?
Huh? Yep, you're right there!
[KOKONOTSU]
Um, no, not even close.
Whatevs! Back to my point,
I want to try it, too!
It'll be awesome!
What? Wine tasting?
Please tell me this isn't
about Namaiki Beer again.
No offense but...
You're a lightweight when it
comes to non-alcoholic stuff.
[HOTARU giggles]
No, not wine tasting.
I'm talking about...
...a fugashi taste test!
Fugashi?
[HOTARU] You heard right.
It's a traditional dagashi
that almost everyone has eaten
as least once in their life.
Fugashi is made from a
wheat gluten called " fu "
and brown sugar.
A lot of women prefer
it over other snacks
since it has health benefits.
Because of that you see
it in a ton of stores.
Everyone is jumping on board
the healthy train these days
and people love it. For reals.
It's like its got
its own culture.
Fugashi , dagashi , and rice!
Wow, rice too?
[KOKONOTSU gasping]
[HOTARU]
There are many kinds of fugashi
made by different manufacturers.
And of course they're
all delicious!
Your taste buds will be
delighted by the combinations!
Now, prepare thyself!
For I have brought an
assortment for our taste test!
[KOKONOTSU sighs]
Jeez, that's a lot of snacks.
[HOTARU]
We're going to try them all!
The rules are simple! You have
to determine what you're eating
using only your mouth!
Whoever gets the
most right, wins!
[KOKONOTSU]
I suppose technically she just
issued a challenge to the wall,
but details don't matter
when pride is on the line.
[HOTARU giggles]
[KOKONOTSU]
I'll win this thing!
Fine, I accept!
I'll dominate this challenge!
Good! Let's get started!
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh. Hotaru?
I'm actually over here.
Yeah, I know. Come on.
[HOTARU] We can't start until
you tie my hands up, silly.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Tie her hands up?
Is she into S and M?
Tie it tighter.
[HOTARU]
Well, what are you waiting for?
Did you hear me?
Earth to Kokonatsu!
Yes! Sorry!
In order to judge
it solely by taste,
we can't be allowed
to use our hands!
Go ahead and tie
mine back please.
Oh, that makes sense.
[HOTARU giggles]
Next, stick it in my mouth.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU] Whoa, what am
I sticking in there?
[HOTARU]
Come on, where's the snack?
Oh, here!
[HOTARU]
Aah...
What do you think?
[HOTARU giggles]
This one is easy!
[KOKONOTSU] I mean,
fugashi is pretty simple.
It's just baked fu
coated in brown sugar.
Can she really tell what it is
without seeing or touching it?
The initial taste tells me that
this is a popular fugashi.
[gasps]
The fu in it has a very
particular softness.
[gulps]
Without a doubt,
it's Shikishima's Fuu-chan!
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
How the hell did she guess that?
Was I right? Was I, was I?
Fuu-chan are often
sold in value packs,
so the chances of getting an
edge piece are pretty good
since there are so many of
them, and they're delicious!
Yeah, you were right!
[KOKONOTSU] She could tell
it was from a value pack
just because it
was an edge piece?
Okay, Kokonotsu!
Now it's your turn!
I'm beyond excited!
Hurry up and untie my hands!
[KOKONOTSU] I won't
underestimate her again.
Things just got serious.
I won't lose!
[HOTARU]
And so.
I'm ready, bring it on!
Okay, give me just a minute.
Aha!
Try this one on for size!
Alright, open wide!
[gasps]
Aah...
Aah!
[KOKONOTSU]
Come on man, concentrate!
You've spent your whole
life around fugashi.
[gulps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Let's see.
The smell and taste
are both familiar.
I've definitely
eaten this before.
Just focus for a minute.
Think carefully.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU] What were some of
the snacks you saw on the table?
Is it Nido-gake Fugashi?
Maybe it's Fuu-chan.
It could even be
Kagiya's fugashi.
This isn't working.
What else stands out
about this particular one?
There must be a clue.
[plastic crinkles]
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
[KOKONOTSU chuckles]
[gasps]
I've got it.
Most of the snacks
you brought today
are in either large
bags or value packs.
When you take the food out
of a big bag like that,
it makes a specific sound.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
But the noise I heard,
it was more like an individual
package being opened.
What's more, there is
only one snack present
in a single package.
And that's Yaokin's
Kaku Fugashi!
[HOTARU squeals]
How do you like them apples?
A whole bushel!
I'm super impressed right now!
'Kay. It's my turn.
The brown sugar is
really overwhelming.
It's Nido-gake Fugahshi.
[grunts]
That's correct.
[KOKONOTSU] The texture is firm,
but it still melts in my mouth.
[KOKONOTSU]
Fugashi by Kagiya!
That's right!
You're a natural, kid!
[grunts]
[HOTARU munching]
[HOTARU]
It has a distinct square shape
and yet it's still small
enough to eat easily.
This is Yaokin's Fugashi.
You'll have to do
better than that!
[BOTH grunt]
A smooth texture and
a subtle sweetness.
Those two qualities
mixed together
can only mean one thing.
Without a doubt I can tell you.
This is Fuu-chan with honey!
[HOTARU] Impressive, you managed
to guess them all so far.
Yeah, you're pretty
amazing, yourself.
Thanks but it's
still not over yet.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU] Oh... There aren't
a lot left to choose from.
It doesn't matter
which one I pick.
Hotaru could answer correctly
just through a process
of elimination.
[grunts]
Crap, what should I do?
[gasps]
Excuse me for a sec,
I'll be right back.
[clattering]
[KOKONOTSU]
And I'm back.
[plastic crinkles]
[HOTARU] It sounds like
he opened something
in a single package, but that
doesn't make sense because
I didn't see anything like
that left on the table.
[KOKONOTSU]
'Kay, get ready.
Aah!
[grunts]
[HOTARU grunting]
What? It's huge!
Stop forcing it in!
Well, Hotaru?
Bet you can't guess it!
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
This fugashi is way different
than anything else
I've tried today.
It's taste is indulgently sweet.
[gasps]
There isn't brown sugar in it.
This taste can
only be real sugar!
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
--[HOTARU] Kokonotsu!
--[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Give me another bite!
[gasps]
No doubt. It's regular sugar.
Typically fugashi is
made with brown sugar,
but I have heard of them being
made with real sugar too.
What's more--
There are different types of
Fugashi made all over Japan
and some are unique
to certain areas.
Based on its taste and size,
this is one of them!
I never dreamed I would
encounter it in this place.
Huh?
The answer, is Sakura bou.
[gasps]
[grunts]
That's correct. Man!
Whoa! I really am good at this!
But, wait a second.
I thought this was only
available in the Shizuoka area.
Well, my dad really
loves the stuff,
so he special orders it.
[HOTARU] There's strawberry,
melon, grape, and even banana!
Kinda funny that they
named them all Sakura bou,
even though they're
not the same color.
As long as it's yummy,
who cares?
[HOTARU giggles]
"A" for effort,
but we're still tied.
Well, don't get too cocky,
because I plan on winning.
Time to finish this
once and for all!
Agreed, let's do it!
Oh wait, before we start,
I'm kinda thirsty.
Yeah, I'm kinda thirsty too,
also I've been wondering,
are we going to eat all
the fugashi we opened?
[HOTARU]
Of course!
Once the bag is opened,
there's no way to reseal it.
The rules say we have to eat all
of them so they don't go bad.
What? That's not a thing.
Wha-- How about this?
What if I go buy us
a couple of drinks?
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Wait, you can't leave!
[HOTARU] Be right back, I think
milk would really hit the spot!
[KOKONOTSU]
Come back and untie me first!
Okay. She really left
me here like this.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm...
[door clatters]
[gasps]
Hotaru!
Thank God, if my dad
saw me like this...
[KOKONOTSU chuckles]
I am your dad.
Oh, no. Dad! It's you!
Crap! Um, it's not
what it looks like!
[grunting]
[YO] So this is what you two
do when I'm not watching?
What?! No way!
[laughs] Well, I have
to go walk the dog now.
[KOKONOTSU]
We don't have a dog!
Uh, it's a metaphorical dog,
so yeah, bye.
[KOKONOTSU]
Get back here, Yo!
--Come back!
--[YO screams]
[TO] So anyway,
what do you think, man?
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm? What do I think about what?
Jeez, I might as well
be talking to the wall.
I was saying that we
should plan another trip
to the pool with Hotaru.
I think it'd be fun,
among other things.
Yeah, well you know
what's not fun?
Running into Captain Speedo
the Lifeguard again.
[TO groans]
Yeah.
Oh! You're drawing them.
Wha--
[TO]
This one is totally Hotaru.
And this one is Saya.
[KOKONOTSU] Oh! I wasn't
really trying to draw them
in particular, but yeah,
I guess I can see
the resemblance.
[TO] You know what
I think, Coconuts?
It's just my opinion,
but it's missing something.
You messed up the most
important part of the picture.
What are you talking about?
Uh-huh. This part right here!
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh? For real? You perv.
Huh?
We meet again,
fellow snack warrior!
[KOKONOTSU] Oh, I didn't
know you were waiting.
Sorry about that.
I was hanging out at To's place.
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
Hm? Hey, what's the matter?
Uh... I just realized I left
something at the café.
[HOTARU]
Oh really?
Was it important?
You know, I think Master Saya
said she's coming over later,
maybe you could ask
her to bring it to you.
Yeah. I guess.
I'm sure she wouldn't mind.
[KOKONOTSU]
On the other hand,
if Saya sees what
To drew in my book.
There's no doubt.
She's going to murder me.
[HOTARU]
I understand.
Judging by the look on your
face, time is of the essence
in retrieving this item,
so I'll help you.
Help me do what?
Huh?
Wait, why are you in a
starting crouch position?
Is that what I think it is?
Yes, they're caramels by Glico.
I'm sure you've already heard
about this snack,
almost everyone in
Japan knows what it is
because of its slogan.
According to the box,
"One caramel equals 300 meters".
Each caramel is
sixteen calories,
which should generate
enough energy for a person
to run three hundred meters.
Yeah?
[HOTARU]
If we eat these,
we'll have enough energy
to run to Café Endo.
Are you in?
[chuckles]
I'm totally in!
Random food fact time!
Did you know the company
who makes glico
was founded in 1921,
the same year the
caramel was born?
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh!
[HOTARU]
It's go time.
[BOTH]
Go!
Café Endo is roughly
1,500 meters away.
One caramel will
take you 300 meters.
Okay, and?
You'll be able to run exactly
1,500 meters with five caramels!
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh, that makes sense!
It seems so far away.
I hope we can make it!
[yawns]
I'm just gonna leave
these right here.
Yeah, that's fine.
[TO grunts]
[KOKONOTSU] To always drops
the dishes off with Saya.
and then she washes them.
Which means, she wouldn't even
have to go near the table.
If I hurry, I'll get to the
café and she'll never know!
[gasps]
Crap, I forgot!
She will have to go
over to the table,
because it needs
to be wiped down!
Oh man this is so bad!
How many more seconds will it
take for us to get there?
[HOTARU]
Not long now! Stay strong.
We're 562 seconds away!
Um, that seems pretty precise.
Yes!
One caramel is 16 calories,
so here is my math.
[HOTARU]
If you're 165 centimeters tall
and weigh 55 kilos, then you
should be able to run
approximately 160
meters per minute.
So if one caramel equals 312
meters exactly, that means?
That we should make it
there in about 500 seconds!
Well, I weigh in right at
55 kilograms, I bet you do, too!
[gasps]
[DISEMBODIED VOICE sighs]
I'm pretty sure I
weigh less than you do.
Uh, obviously!
Hey! Look!
If we cut over that hill,
It might not be much,
but we can save a little time!
Well, I say we go for it, then!
Yeah!
[KOKONOTSU] Okay.
We've already run 300 meters!
[grunts]
[HOTARU shouts]
Did you remember to
take out the garbage?
Yep.
[HOTARU]
Here! My hand!
[BOTH grunt]
--[HOTARU shouts]
--[KOKONOTSU grunts]
[HOTARU] A little over
1,000 meters to go!
[KOKONOTSU, HOTARU grunt]
[OLD COUPLE]
Hm?
[HOTARU] We can do this,
don't give up!
[KOKONOTSU, HOTARU pant]
[HOTARU]
Hm?
Hey, is something wrong?
Well, I don't know. Maybe.
According to the candy box,
Glico assumes that we can run
160 meters per minute.
But, I was just thinking.
It's not really a running speed.
I mean, doesn't that seem
a little slow to you?
--[HOTARU chuckles]
--[KOKONOTSU] Huh?
[HOTARU] The national average
of a tenth grade male's
50 meter dash is 7.41 seconds,
which equals out to
404 meters per minute.
So yeah, if you base it on that
math it does seem rather slow,
even if it was calculated
for long distance running.
But there's still
more to consider.
It's a 25 minute walk to
the nearest train station
from your store.
Huh?
What in the heck does that have
to do with running speeds?
Although I guess we are kind of
located in an inconvenient spot.
I'll explain it to you, then!
There are standards set
for measuring distance
from stations.
Real estate companies all agreed
that a patron could walk
about 80 meters per minute.
Okay, well that's good
to know, I guess?
Do you get what I'm saying?
If 80 meters per minute
is walking speed,
and 160 meters per minute
is double that...
[gasps]
It is fast!
It's a running speed after all!
We can make it!
[HOTARU] Looks like his
doubts are gone now. Hm.
He's going to be okay!
900 meters left to go!
[KOKONOTSU grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
Man, we still have
600 meters to run.
[HOTARU]
Come on, we're closer than ever!
Right!
[KOKONOTSU]
I know we can do this!
[HOTARU]
Yeah...!
[BOTH panting]
Only 300 more meters to go.
If I eat one more caramel,
it should be just
enough to get me there.
Our journey is
almost finished.
What the--?
[gasps]
How could I forget?
I'm so stupid!
There're only four pieces
of candy in a package!
[KOKONOTSU groans]
[KOKONOTSU] We'll never have
enough energy to finish.
we're not going to
make it in time!
[HOTARU]
Hey, heads up!
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[gasps]
[HOTARU] Don't throw
in the towel just yet.
Take this,
and finish your quest.
[sighs, grunts]
Hotaru!
[HOTARU]
You have to leave me behind!
I'll only slow you down
at this rate, just go!
Quick as you can.
You can make it.
I believe in you!
[whimpers]
Good luck to you, Kokonotsu.
[groans]
[KOKONOTSU] She saved one
caramel all this time.
She knew from the start,
one box wouldn't be enough!
Hotaru knew that all along,
so she sacrificed her
caramel for my sake!
[KOKONOTSU]
There it is!
We're gonna make it, Hotaru!
We're gonna...
--[CROWD cheers]
--[KOKONOTSU] ...make it!
[laughs]
There, all done!
[grunts]
[SAYA]
Hm? Oh yeah.
Hm! Huh?
Did Coconuts forget this?
He's hopeless. What a goof.
Hey guys, I'm back!
I forgot my--
Saya? You okay?
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm.
[gasps]
[growls]
Um, hold on,
please don't be mad.
I didn't draw that, it was To!
Oh, God, please!
[KOKONOTSU screams]
So, the prize was a watch.
[HOTARU] My collection
is finally complete.
[HOTARU]
Master Saya,
did you know women who
are dieting love fugashi?
[SAYA]
Yep!
But even though
they're low in calories,
you still have to eat
them in moderation!
[HOTARU] Yeah, because they're
totally scrumptious!
Maybe if you eat them fast you
could burn some calories!
[SAYA]
What?
[HOTARU] Sakura bou are
90 centimeters long.
If you eat it at a speed of
six centimeters per second,
you can eat it all in
about 15 seconds!
Whoa!
That's slow, should one
bite be ten centimeters?
But we wouldn't
enjoy it as much!
[SAYA]
Huh? Um? What?
[HOTARU] 1 kilogram
of your weight burns
.026 calories every minute.
[SAYA] Enough! Can't we eat
without all this math?