You never did say what brings
you all the way out here.
Uh, well, the thing is...
It started snowing
on my way home.
So my train got delayed
and I'm stuck.
[HOTARU]
Hm.
Ah, in that case, I guess
I'll wait with you.
[ANNOUNCER A] May I have
your attention, please?
Due to the inclement weather,
all delayed trains have
been officially canceled.
We apologize for
the inconvenience.
[KOKONOTSU groans]
Looks like we're staying here.
[KOKONOTSU] I can't believe
it's really Hotaru.
After all this time,
she's just here.
There are so many
things I wanna ask her,
but I don't know where to start.
What should I say?
[gasps]
So, uh, anyway,
what's up with you?
Like, what were
you doing, Hotaru?
Just some business stuff.
Too bad the trains got canceled.
That's not what I meant.
All these months,
what have you been doing?
[HOTARU]
Let's see.
All kinds of things, I suppose.
Mostly helping the
family business.
Nothing outta the ordinary.
I bet you did a ton of things
while I was gone, huh?
With Endo and Saya,
and the shop, too.
You'll have to tell me
all about it sometime.
[KOKONOTSU] I went to the
shrine and the bus stop.
I went to a lot of places,
but no one was ever there.
I found myself wondering
if you really existed.
As dumb as that sounds,
it's still a thought I had.
You should've said
something before you left.
Kokonotsu.
[KOKONOTSU] I did do a ton of
things while you were gone.
Our shop was in real trouble,
and then a new store
opened up near us.
Just when things
were getting better,
and I was starting
to have fun again...
...I realized that I had put my
dreams on hold, so I panicked.
I had my manga reviewed
by an editor today.
It was the first time a
professional looked at my work.
But it was a disaster.
And I kinda wanna...
wanna give up.
[KOKONOTSU] Dammit. This
isn't what I wanted to say.
Why am I taking out all
of my problems on her?
I wanted to show her that I
had changed for the better
since last summer.
But now I just look pathetic.
[HOTARU]
I see.
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
And I have the answer.
It's a power-up of sorts.
[KOKONOTSU]
Wait, I know this lead-in.
It's dagashi time.
Behold! Super Mario- kun
Comic Chewing Gum!
[KOKONOTSU]
Totally called it.
Wait, it's the Super
Mario- kun Comic Gum?
Yep!
Not only do you get to enjoy
some delicious gum,
you also get a chapter
of the Mario- kun manga!
There are ten chapters
all together,
and one of those chapters
is exclusive to the gum!
[KOKONOTSU]
Awesome!
Attach it here.
No way! It's just
like a real manga!
[HOTARU] Having to assemble
it makes it feel kind of like
putting together
a toy model, huh?
By the way, did you know it's
distributed by Top Seika?
They make Scary Story Gum, too.
It's pretty
appropriate, isn't it?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
It's almost too appropriate.
[HOTARU, KOKONOTSU laughing]
What the--? Ah!
I'm so sorry! I'll stop crying!
[HOTARU]
You can stop crying on command?
That's impressive!
[KOKONOTSU] Sorry, Hotaru,
it's like all my feelings
are trying to escape via my
tear ducts or something.
[HOTARU]
Kokonotsu.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
I'm happy for you
because you've had time
to seriously think about what
you want out of your life.
And I guess it's not my place
to tell you whether you
should give up or not.
But I think it's important
that you made a decision
and acted upon it.
Even so, the Kokonotsu I see,
doesn't look like he's ready
to throw in the towel just yet.
I'm still feeling kind of unsure
about some things, but I guess,
I wanted to sulk and
have my pity party.
Well, I think that's
important, too.
[HOTARU]
Hey, listen.
I'm sorry I left without
saying anything.
Anyway, now I'm back.
Once again, it's
been a while, right?
Uh, yeah. Welcome.
Wait, wha--?
Holy wow! It's so
cold! I'm freezing!
Ah! That's right!
Thankfully, I came prepared!
You did?
[HOTARU]
Feast your eyes... on this!
[KOKONOTSU]
Seriously?
You packed an entire
suitcase full of Buta-men?
Talk about packing lightly.
[HOTARU]
Come on!
We can melt some of the snow
from outside in the kettle
to make hot water.
Then it's Buta-men time!
We may not be able to
leave until morning,
but we won't starve!
It's so cold.
Hurry up, then!
[KOKONOTSU] I still had a lot
to say, and a lot to ask.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hotaru!
I'm starting to wish I'd
packed a coat, y'know?
[KOKONOTSU] But when I
really thought about it...
[KOKONOTSU]
...I felt like...
...we had plenty of time.
It's morning already?
Where'd she go?
[KOKONOTSU]
Hotaru!
Hota... ru!
[HOTARU]
Good morning. Are you okay?
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh, well.
Sometimes I wonder...
Ready for some good news?
The trains are running!
[KOKONOTSU]
What?
Yep! Let's go back
to Shikada Dagashi!
Hey, I'm back!
Ko--
Co--
It's Coconuts!
Jeez, what happened to
you? Did you get stuck?
Yeah. Sorry if I
worried you guys.
I was worried! I mean, you
never came home last night.
Knowing you, your phone's
probably dead, yeah?
[gasps]
Ah, man! It totally is!
[HAJIME]
Kokonotsu.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
I'm glad you're back.
Thanks, me too, Hajime.
It didn't go very well.
Even though everyone
worked so hard to help me.
No way, we were
happy to help you.
Besides, you can't succeed
without a few failures.
Cut yourself some slack, dude.
Yeah, there's always next ti--
[HAJIME]
Huh?
[TO]
Uh.
It's been a while, but hi!
Wait, wha--?
Oh, wow! It really
is you, Hotaru!
Well, yes, I suppose I do have
distinct facial features.
Since when do you
greet people that way?
[HAJIME]
Uh, Manager, I was wondering.
Yeah, what?
[HAJIME]
Is she a friend?
Right, I forgot to intro-- Ah!
[HAJIME gasps]
[HOTARU]
Hey, you.
Yes?
Did you call him "manager"?
[HAJIME]
Yeah?
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[gasps]
Wait, it's not what
you think, Hotaru!
It's just temporary, I swear!
Stop that smug laughter
right now! I'm serious!
[HOTARU]
Aha!
I never doubted your
talent, Kokonotsu!
Accept fate!
I was certain this
day would come!
Now is the dagashi shop
of our discontent!
At last, the day has
finally arrived!
Kokonotsu, you're
the one I want!
[ALL]
Huh?
Say wha--? I'm not even
sure what that means!
[SAYA]
Me either.
[HAJIME] You sure are a
smooth operator, manager.
[HOTARU]
Precisely!
We can't let his talent for
smooth operation go to waste!
Uh, hold on.
Anyway!
What's up? The Snack Review
Dude is finally back!
[HOTARU]
For my company,
I need Kokonotsu more
than I could ever need Yo.
In fact, forget Yo!
Uh...
Wait, your company?
That's right.
I'm thinking of creating
my own snack company.
But to make my dream
come true, I need you!
And by you, I mean your
talent, of course.
Oh. Yo, Yo.
Whoa, hey, Dad.
When did you get home?
Oh. Uh, I think it was
around the "Forget Yo."
[BENIYUTAKA]
What's all this?
Kids hanging out at a dagashi
shop in broad daylight?
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
Uh.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[HOTARU]
Hello, brother.
[BENIYUTAKA]
Hotaru.
[HAJIME, TO, SAYA, KOKONOTSU]
Brother?
Who is this?
Hold on. What's going on?
[HOTARU]
His name is Beniyutaka Shidare.
He's my big brother.
He was supposed to take
over the Shidare Company.
I never expected to run
into you way out here.
Well, ditto. Where on earth
have you been all this time?
[yells]
[YO]
Hey!
I've been gone practically
this whole season
and no one even cares!
Now there's some guy with
a mouthful of a name here,
Hajime is still at
my son's mercy,
and Hotaru is trying
to headhunt Kokonotsu!
I'll never let you take him!
He's my successor!
Aw, just hear me out.
[BENIYUTAKA]
I'm afraid I must intervene.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Kokonotsu is the perfect
candidate to be a team leader.
Me?
As if!
No, he's the legendary
successor, dammit!
[SAYA] Hold on, what
about Coconuts' manga?
We have tons of manga!
What'll happen to the shop and
my job if the manager leaves?
No one asked me,
but I'll follow Hotaru.
[YO] Kokonotsu's true
destiny is here!
[SAYA] I didn't mean
he wants to read manga!
[BENIYUTAKA] He'd be far
better off at my store!
Dagashi is his true calling!
[OTHERS shouting]
[gasps]
He escaped!
[OTHERS gasp]
[yelling]
Uh! Just leave me alone!
Manager!
[SAYA]
Coconuts!
Looks like you've still
got a long way to go.
Better not give up, Kokonotsu!
[KOKONOTSU screams]
[KOKONOTSU]
Hey, Hotaru?
So, uh...
Here.
Will you hold onto it?
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
Because then I'll always
have a good reason
to come back to Shikada Dagashi.
Fine.
Okay!
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh! Hey! Be careful!
Which dagashi do you think
we should discuss today?
[SAYA]
It's way too dangerous!