[HAJIME]
Okay.
This one's done,
wanna take a look?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah, sure. That was fast.
Whoa! You're good!
Aw. Thanks. Just let me know
if you want any changes.
No. In fact, it's great!
[SAYA] Sorry for the wait!
I made some coffee.
I used the coffee maker from
our café, so it's legit.
Thanks so much, Saya.
I brought you some as well.
Coconuts.
[OTHERS]
Hm?
A liquid slime joined my party.
Hell yeah!
Oh. Cool, that's great news.
Question. What time do you
need this done by again?
[KOKONOTSU] Let's see,
factoring in the travel time,
nine in the morning.
[HAJIME]
Got it!
There.
Okay. This page is ready.
Thanks a lot.
Man, the metal slime
I was fighting ran away!
[SAYA]
Stop being so damn loud
and go start on another
pot of coffee, loser!
[TO]
Ow!
[TO snoring]
[SAYA]
Here.
It's nice and fresh.
Thanks, Saya.
Hot!
Well, duh! I did just make it.
[BOYS laughing]
Hey! Hurry up, guys!
[BOY B]
Wait for us!
It's finally done.
We're a pretty awesome
team. Oh, yeah!
Well, I'm happy you finished.
Way to go! All right,
so what's next?
Coconuts?
Coconuts!
[HAJIME]
Manager?
[KOKONOTSU snores]
[SAYA]
At least he's not dead.
♪
[HAJIME] Hurry up,
or you're gonna be late!
Yeah, 'kay!
[CONDUCTOR A]
The next stop is Hata.
I repeat, the next stop is Hata.
Uh, let's see.
According to this, the
on-site manga review event
should be in that bookstore.
All right, it's time
to do this thing.
[MAN A]
Man, this is nerve-wracking.
The guy reviewing us is an
actual professional, right?
Yeah, I've participated before,
but it never gets any
easier, you know?
[bell rings]
[SAYA]
Miss Hajime!
Uh-huh, that's me.
It's freezing out there.
Wow, your café is
like super cute.
Uh, why'd I come here?
Oh, yeah, thanks for your
help yesterday-slash-today.
Ah, gee. I mean, all I
did was make some coffee.
And my useless brother
literally did nothing.
Uh, hey now, that's not true.
I cleared four entire games
yesterday-slash-today!
In what world is
that helpful, idiot?
Actually, your game did provide
some background noise,
which kind of helped.
It's not noise.
[SAYA] Anyway, I wonder how the
review is going for Coconuts.
Just thinking about him
out there makes me nervous.
Here's your coffee.
Seriously, she's been goin'
on like this all day.
So what?
Coconuts might become a
professional manga artist!
I think it's exciting.
[HAJIME chuckles]
This smells great.
Oh, hey, maybe we should throw
a party for him to celebrate!
Calm down, Saya.
If anything, it'd be more
like a wrap-party.
Yeah.
Still though,
we should probably hold off
on any party plans for today.
[KOKONOTSU]
Holy crap, I am so nervous!
[door opens]
[WOMAN A]
Mister Kokonotsu Shikada?
You're next.
[KOKONOTSU]
Here!
Really? Why's that?
[HAJIME]
Because...
I get the feeling he may
not be up to celebrating.
[EDITOR A]
You--
Uh, yes?
You are amazing!
At your level, you could
probably start right away.
Yeah! You might even
win best new manga!
Uh, say what?
[ANNOUNCER A] The manga Spin ,
by Kokonotsu Shikada,
is a sensation.
Bookstores can't seem
to keep them in stock.
[WOMAN B]
Spin is my favorite!
[WOMAN C]
Kokonotsu is the coolest!
[ANNOUNCER B] The Japan Best
New Manga Award goes to--
Spin , by Kokonotsu Shikada!
Congratulations!
Uh. Thank you, it's an honor.
Ho...
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh.
So, how long did this take?
Well, uh...
[KOKONOTSU] I started on
the story three months ago,
but the actual drawing
time was only around
two to three weeks,
give or take.
Two weeks, maybe?
Uh, well, yes, sir.
That's right.
Ah. Okay, that's good.
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah. I guess.
Of course, I had help.
Is there a reason you couldn't
spend more time on it?
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Um.
Look, I wish I could go
over it more page by page.
But since there are more people
to review, I'll sum it up.
You haven't learned how
to budget your time yet.
Perhaps you're having
a hard time focusing?
Although you're clearly aware
of your artistic strengths,
I think it's also clear
that you're avoiding
your weak points.
Stop making excuses.
If I had to guess, I'd say you
probably did most of this work
over the past few days.
I will give you credit
for at least finishing it
by the deadline, though.
But look on the bright side.
You have years to improve.
[KOKONOTSU]
It ended in five minutes.
It took me three
hours to get here,
and the whole review ended
in five friggin' minutes.
I can focus just fine.
And what excuses?
What did he mean?
I was just busy
running the shop.
If I don't look after
it... If I don't...
Wait, why am I the
manager again?
[HAJIME]
Um, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to bring
down the mood earlier.
Hey, it's cool.
Besides, I think I was the
one who got carried away.
[HAJIME]
Well, hopefully I'm wrong
and he'll get good news instead.
Oh, look.
It's starting to snow.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Due to the inclement weather,
some of the train routes
may be experiencing
cancellations or delays.
At this time, we are
unsure when the trains
will resume their
regular schedule.
We apologize for
the inconvenience.
[KOKONOTSU]
Just my luck.
[KOKONOTSU] I wonder when the
trains will start running again.
It's probably better
that they aren't.
I'm not sure I could face
everyone back home anyway.
Saya, To, and Hajime...
I let them all down.
[KOKONOTSU]
Maybe I should give up.
[door opens]
[HOTARU]
Oh.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
This is a nice surprise.
[gasps]
What brings you out
here, Kokonotsu?
Uh, hello there, Hotaru.
[HOTARU]
It's been a while, hasn't it?
♪
[HOTARU]
Next time:
"I'm back, Welcome Back, and..."
Did you miss me, Kokonotsu?