[rattling]
[sighs]
Not good.
I don't think it'll
hold out much longer.
Man, this really blows.
It's hot enough already.
If the AC breaks, we're screwed.
[groans]
[HOTARU grunts]
Oh, hey Hotaru!
What brings you by?
Need something cold to drink?
[HOTARU]
Hmph.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
Sorry.
I know, it's loud.
[screams]
Don't turn it off!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
It's so bright.
[HOTARU] Is your body
ready for the summer heat?
If not, then we need to
build up your stamina!
And the only way to do that is
with the number one snack choice
for hungry kids!
Check it out!
For real? With Butamen?
You betcha!
Enter!
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
--[gasps]
--[TO grunts]
There! Piece of cake!
[KOKONOTSU]
Wait, To?
[HOTARU]
And so...
[groans]
[TO groans]
So hot.
Yeah, it's summer, duh.
[sighs]
Oh hey. I was just wondering:
when exactly did
you meet Hotaru?
Well, it's quite the story.
[gasping]
[HOTARU sighs]
[HOTARU]
Uh?
[gasping continues]
Yep! Who nude? Knew!
Nude knew what?
Nothing! Ah...
Get your mind out
of the gutter, man!
Anyway, I saw her
with this big heater.
And I generously
offered to carry it here!
'Cause I'm a nice guy.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Dude, your nose is bleeding!
That's it!
Please turn the AC on!
What? No!
Request denied, soldier!
This unbearable heat is
a part of your training!
Only the best get
to eat Butamen!
But we have a man down!
[TO]
It's okay, Coconuts.
Huh?
[TO]
I can bear it.
As long as there's hope,
I'll keep fighting!
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh-- What are we fighting for?
[TO]
You'll see soon enough!
Looks like the water
is finally ready.
[TO]
Yes!
Did you know that Butamen
has many different flavors?
There's pork bone broth,
soy sauce, salted beef tongue.
The list goes on.
Personally, I prefer the pork
bone broth over the rest.
Unfortunately,
Butamen tends to be pricier
than most of the other snacks.
Kids don't have a lot of money.
If they're buying noodles,
they have to be picky.
And no way is a kid going
to walk into a snack shop
and waste his money
on any old flavor.
In the end, they're likely
to settle on pork bone broth
because it's tried and true.
[KOKONOTSU grunts]
I think I'm gonna die.
The temperature has
finally risen above
what any normal
human can endure.
True enough.
Just wait. Not long now.
--Uh?
--[HOTARU giggles]
[HOTARU]
Think about it,
all over the world there
are people who adore
pork bone broth, like me.
It's like we're
all tied together
by some noodle-y thread of fate.
The bond of pork bone broth
lovers is unshakable.
Preach it, girl!
Hallelujah!
[KOKONOTSU sighs]
Too hot.
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
All done! It smells amazing!
See?! Look there!
At what?
[HOTARU slurps, sighs]
[TO]
I told you!
That's what we've
been waiting for!
[gasps]
[sighs]
This is just what I needed
on such a hot, steamy day!
This is awesome, man,
watch her go!
Yeah.
I've never been so interested
in Butamen before.
But now, I'm feeling very
passionate about it.
[TO]
Sure, we'll go with that.
[gasps]
Wow! Delicious!
Oh! Your nose is bleeding again.
Uh... what? Oh.
[HOTARU] Now. I made these
two cups for you guys to enjoy.
Oh, um, I didn't know
we were eating too.
Of course, silly!
So here! Go on, dig in!
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[HOTARU sighs]
[HOTARU gasps,grunts]
[sighs]
[whimpers]
[TO]
Sorry, dude.
[gasps]
I'm done.
Please don't cry for me.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[TO grunts]
What the hell?!
That's it. We need to
turn the AC back on, now!
[HOTARU]
Huh? No sir!
A little heat stroke
never killed anyone!
Please, oh please,
what will I do if the
heat ruins all our snacks?
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
Ah-- Ah!
[giggles]
Well, looks like you passed.
This was actually just
part of an elaborate test!
[KOKONOTSU] A.K.A. she totally
forgot about the food.
The AC has kicked the bucket.
[TO]
For real?
No! What will we do
with the dagashi?
[whimpers]
[TO]
Lightbulb!
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh?
[TO] This will be our
required pool episode!
[KOKONOTSU]
Eh-- What?!
Yeah, it'll be awesome!
I'll call and invite Saya, too!
The pool.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[SAYA]
And so...
[TO]
The time has come.
Yes! Time to check out all
the hot girls in bikinis!
Dude, you've been saying that
since episode one! Aw, snap!
Well, snap back atcha!
You're just as excited as I am!
[giggles]
Uh, guilty!
[BOTH]
Let's go!
It's kind of lacking
in the girl department.
[TO]
Screw this. I'm gonna head out.
[gasps] But this whole
thing was your idea!
[TO]
I have a new idea!
It's called "go home!"
I'm not leaving, yet!
We only just got here!
--[whistle chirps]
--[BOTH gasp]
[YO]
Hey, you kids!
No roughhousing by the pool!
I know that voice.
[YO] You could slip on the
tile and hurt yourselves!
Um, Dad?
Ah! It's you!
What are you doing here?
I could ask you the same thing!
--[whistles weakly]
--[KOKONOTSU] Huh?
Okay, fine.
Income from our shop hasn't
been enough to pay the bills.
It's so embarrassing.
[whistles weakly]
[YO] This is my side gig.
I'm working two jobs
and you're neglecting the
shop to play at the pool.
But the air broke down.
We were hot!
Of course. Another expense.
[whimpers]
Wow, I'm sorry, Dad.
Then you could help by
watching the shop tomorrow!
That changed your tune.
[SAYA]
Hm? Hello there!
[YO]
Hey, Saya!
I haven't seen you in a while!
What's all the commotion about?
You seem excited.
My son has just kindly agreed
to watch the store tomorrow!
I'm so happy,
I feel like dancing!
[SAYA]
Huh?
[KOKONOTSU]
You can ignore Captain Speedo.
Okay. But, um...
Hey, I don't see
Hotaru anywhere.
[KOKONOTSU] Oh! We thought she
might be with you, actually.
[SAYA]
No.
[giggles]
Hope she gets here soon.
I bet she looks hot
in her swimsuit!
[BOTH gasp]
[yelps]
Listen, perv. If you're weird
around her, I'll murder you.
Is that clear enough, bro?
[TO]
Crystal.
--[whistle chirps]
--[ALL gasp]
Hey! Time to put in the
chlorine or whatever!
Just go ahead and do your thing!
[HOTARU]
Okay!
[ALL]
Huh?
Look, guys, it's Hotaru!
Hi, Master!
Oh man, why's she gotta
be wearing a hoodie?
[SAYA]
Were you here this whole time?
[HOTARU]
Yep!
[YO] Excellent, our plan
is working perfectly.
[HOTARU]
We got this, Yo.
What?
The boys are planning to go
hang out at the swimming pool?
Interesting. Well, in that case.
Once Kokonotsu
realizes how grave
our financial situation is,
he'll feel terrible.
[whimpers]
Wow, I'm sorry, Dad.
[YO] Naturally, he'll agree
to help out more.
--[YO, HOTARU chuckle]
--[YO] A foolproof plan!
Just what I would expect
from Shidare's daughter.
--And there's still more!
--[whistles]
Okay, you kids can get in now.
Alright! Screw this heat,
let's go swim!
Yay!
[BOTH cheer]
[KOKONOTSU] Get in, Saya!
The water's great!
'Kay, be there in a sec!
How about it?
Are you gonna swim too?
Yeah! Go ahead,
I'm right behind you.
[YO]
Is everything in place?
We are good to go.
They should be discovering our
"gifts" any minute now.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
--[water splashes]
--[HOTARU chuckles]
[KOKONOTSU] Um, hey dad?
I found something!
There was a Kuru Kuru Bou Jelly
in the water, awesome!
You think somebody
dropped it in here?
Oh, that little
thingamabob?
Think of it like a bonus prize
for the pool guests to enjoy.
It's my treat!
Huh?
[YO] You know, like a
promotional item.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Dude, check it! I found
some freebie snacks.
Oh my gosh, me too! Look!
Must be my lucky day!
They're purple and blue!
I wonder what flavors
they're supposed to be.
[KOKONOTSU]
I know!
One is soda pop flavored,
and the other one is grape.
Oh, cool!
I think they have a cream
soda flavored option, too!
I'll look around and
try to find one for you!
[SAYA] We can share
them when we're done!
[YO] This was all part
of our master plan!
If we make dagashi
fun for Kokonotsu,
he'll wanna take over the shop!
When it comes to this girl,
she's not afraid
to pull any punches.
[chuckles]
This is perfect.
[SAYA giggles]
Hm?
Hey, that sign says there's
no eating or drinking allowed.
[HOTARU]
Are you serious?!
[KOKONOTSU]
Well that sucks.
[TO] I guess we can't
eat these, after all.
[SAYA]
What a waste.
[TO]
Now the moment is ruined.
[BOTH chuckle]
[HOTARU, YO]
Curse you, pool rules!
[HOTARU humming]
Kokonotsu, prepare thyself!
[gasps]
Huh?
Oh hey, good morning!
[HOTARU] Did I show up
at the wrong store?
Are you looking for Coconuts?
He's running an errand,
so I'm watching the
shop until he gets back.
Okay. I see.
Hm... Hm...? Hm... Hm!
[HOTARU]
Where's all the dagashi?
[TO] Well, he had
to move some of it.
When the AC broke,
he put the stuff that
might go bad in a cooler.
I'm impressed!
Which is no easy feat!
Do you have any idea
when he'll be back?
Uh, he should be
back any minute now.
[HOTARU] Okay. Do you mind
if I wait for him, then?
[TO]
Knock yourself out.
[video game beeps]
[HOTARU] I've wanted
to ask you something.
[TO]
Go for it.
I was just wondering what sort
of dagashi is your favorite.
Huh? Which is my favorite?
Yep! What do you like?
Uh... Mm... Hang on,
just let me think.
[HOTARU giggles]
I can't decide.
[HOTARU]
"Eye Candy-Side"?
[HOTARU grunts]
[HOTARU]
That's a strange name.
I don't think I've
heard of it before.
Kind of a dumb answer, huh?
[grunts]
[HOTARU] Usually I can tell
about someone's personality
based on their answer,
but this time my discussion
technique has failed!
And hey. Since we're
already on the subject.
Yes?
Do you have a
particular preference
when it comes to dagashi ?
My favorite?
[TO]
Uh-huh.
[HOTARU chuckles]
[TO gasps]
[HOTARU] A good question!
I love all dagashi equally!
If we were to pick a specific
genre, I could narrow it down.
Otherwise I could never
choose just one thing!
Wow.
[HOTARU] A perfect answer,
if I do say so myself!
So basically,
you kind of consider all
of them to just be okay?
[HOTARU gasps]
"All of them are just okay?"
[HOTARU]
What the fue?
Why does he have that
smug look on his face?
Is he testing me?
I'm not sure how
I should respond!
Uh, I forgot.
Before he left earlier,
Coconuts said I could have this.
We could eat it together,
if you want.
Uh, let's see here.
I'm not entirely sure how
to get the wrapper off.
Give me a sec and
I'll figure it out.
[screams]
Sorry.
[HOTARU]
How has he gone through life
without knowing what
Bontan ame is?
The wrapper is made
from edible rice paper.
You don't take it off,
you just eat it!
Maybe his ignorance is
part of a ruse to test me!
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
Why didn't I see it before?
He knows about my mission,
and he's assessing me to see if
I have what it takes
to get the job done.
Ha! I see what's
going on here.
[TO]
Huh?
[HOTARU]
I'm on to you, mister!
I know this was a test
to see whether or not
I'm worthy to be
Kokonotsu's rival!
Challenge accepted!
Sit back and prepare to
be flabbergasted, Endo!
[TO]
Uh, what's going on?
Hey, I'm finally back.
Huh?
I see that rice paper wrapped
tight around your heart.
And this girl's gonna
remove it for you!
This got really weird,
really fast.
But my body is ready!
[groans] Man, I'm starting to
regret all of my life choices.
[HOTARU]
Kokonotsu.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[HOTARU]
Watch carefully.
It'll all be over in a second.
The time has come for action.
[HOTARU]
And it's through that action
I will solve this problem.
[gasps]
Oh yeah, you're going down!
Holy crap!
[TO grunts]
Mm. mm, mm. Mm!
[MYSTERIOUS MALE NARRATOR]
Due to the fierce rotation
from Hotaru's pitch,
and the entwined saliva,
the rice paper on the Bontan ame
that was thrown into To's mouth
began to dissolve at
tremendous speed.
Please dude. Don't choke
to death or anything.
I'm not, but I am
detecting hints of pomelo.
I love it! Good job!
Excellent! And the rice paper?
Did I remove it from your heart?
Yes. And it's all thanks to you.
[HOTARU chuckles]
[TO laughs]
What? Why the hell
are they laughing?
[CONTRACTOR]
Hi! We're here to fix the AC!
[KOKONOTSU]
Come on in!
Aha, so that's what
you were doing.
You want me to stay and help?
Yeah, that'd be awesome!
Sounds like a plan.
I'm sure it would
move things along--
If I offered you
my help as well.
Well um, it's already going
to be kind of crowded in here.
[gasps]
Oh, I know!
Hi, welcome!
[gasps]
Hotaru!
Well, good morning, Master!
Hey girl, what's going on?
You don't usually
come visit the café.
Oh, I was at Shikada,
but the AC is crowded, so...
Uh? Did you say
the AC is crowded?
[HOTARU]
Yep, sure did!
Kokonotsu suggested I come here.
I can go back when
it's less busy.
Uh. I don't think I
really get it, but okay.
Anyway, did you
wanna order something?
Two iced coffees!
Huh? Why two?
Duh! 'Cause I thought maybe
we could have coffee together.
[SAYA]
Mm-Hm.
I'm so excited! I've really
wanted to sit down
and talk with you
for a while now!
I feel the same way!
Well that makes me
so happy, Master!
Sometimes you need a
good old-fashioned chat
between girls!
Oh, alright, girl-talk!
How intriguing!
I was wondering.
You and Kokonotsu have been
friends for a pretty long time,
right?
Well, yeah.
[SAYA] She's not
beating around the bush,
but why is she asking this?
[gasps]
Wait, no way!
Does Hotaru like Coconuts, too?
[HOTARU]
I'm only asking because...
--[HOTARU] you... don't eat!
--[yelps]
Even though you're friends,
I've never seen you eat
any dagashi around him!
Not once!
I see. This is only about candy.
Well, why not?
I've never really
thought about it. Hm...
Don't you worry, Master!
There's a perfect
candy for everyone,
and I might know yours! Here.
Ta-da!
I don't know what this is.
Ha, ha. You only have
to try just one.
Then you'll see what
dagashi is all about.
[SAYA]
Hm...
Seven Neon?
[SAYA]
Hm...
Weird. How the heck
do you eat it?
[gasps]
[SAYA]
Geez! She's really excited!
This is a little more
intense than I expected.
But I can't let her down.
[SAYA gulps]
[SAYA] Okay! I guess I'll take
off the plastic part first.
[SAYA] Surely, you're only
supposed to eat
whatever's inside.
[SAYA]
Alright, I think I got it!
Oh, yeah!
[HOTARU whimpers]
[SAYA]
I don't got it!
Master?
[SAYA gasps]
Um, I was only joking!
[SAYA]
Crap, that was close! What if I?
[gasps]
[SAYA]
Yank it out with my teeth!
Oh, Master!
That was beyond perfect,
you really are so amazing!
Wow, are you sure?
Yes, like absolutely!
[chuckles]
But seriously.
Eating it this way,
well, it just seems like it's
more work than it's worth.
[HOTARU]
You're as observant as always.
Huh?
The reason why most dagashi
are so appealing to customers
is because they're
relatively affordable.
When prices are cheap,
then you can expect the serving
size to be smaller, too.
Kids don't have a lot of money,
so if they spend it on candy
that's gone in an instant,
then it's a big letdown.
[HOTARU]
Basically.
Manufacturers have to extend
your time with the candy.
They need to learn to
balance fun, flavors,
and frugality all together.
[giggles]
Whoa.
So cool! You're beyond amazing!
Every time I'm around you,
I learn something
new and unusual!
You're so awesome!
What? You mean it?
[SAYA] Do you know
any other random facts?
[HOTARU chuckles]
Yes, I actually do!
[SAYA]
Yay!
[HOTARU] You know how
the Seven Neon packaging
has letters from the
alphabet on it?
Uh-huh?
[HOTARU] There are eight letters
in all, ordered from A to H.
Does it stand for
something interesting?
Well, I heard...
...that it means
absolutely nothing!
Wow! For real?
You see, the packaging may
have eight letters on it,
but it only comes with seven
pieces of candy in the bag!
That's totally weird when
you think about it!
[HOTARU chuckles]
I know!
Sometimes I think the
whole thing is a fluke!
[SAYA] Right? But it's
also a neat fact!
[TO]
See ya later, man!
[KOKONOTSU]
Bye!
Hey wait, come to think of it,
Hotaru never made her
way back here, did she?
[HOTARU] And that's the
"God's Left Hand" technique.
[SAYA]
Awesome!
You seriously are the
best at everything!
Well, I don't like to brag,
but yeah, it's true.
That's for sure!
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm...
Oh, well.
[HOTARU]
Hey, Master!
Wanna hear the secret behind
what makes Butamen so tasty?
[SAYA]
Sure!
[HOTARU] Each flavor is riddled
with a different secret!
But the biggest secret
is in the powder!
The noodles are so yummy
because of the powder
and water they cook in!
The powder is produced by
simmering together meat, fish,
vegetables and seasoning!
I also heard that how they mix
the powder is super-secret!
It's like the most secret
of the secret-est thing
that ever secret-ed!
[SAYA] Whoa. That sure
is a lot of secrets.
[HOTARU]
Yeah! I know, right?
But that's what makes
them so darn delicious!