[ALL]
Uh...
[HOTARU grunts]
[TO]
Huh?
[KOKONOTSU]
Do I even wanna know?
[HOTARU grunts, sighs]
Oh?
Well, fancy running into
the three of you here!
[KOKONOTSU, SAYA gasp]
"Fancy" my butt!
You're the one who told us to
come meet you at the temple!
What?
So you wanna know what
I was doing just now.
That is not what I said at all!
Well, not out loud.
Maybe I was thinking it, though.
[HOTARU]
Okay then, I'll tell you.
Because you asked me nicely.
Hey, master?
[SAYA]
Um, yeah?
Since the beginning of time,
Japan has proudly been home
to over eight million gods.
Can you believe it?
Uh. Yeah, I guess?
Do you know where this is going?
No.
[HOTARU]
The gods can live anywhere,
like in the sun,
trees, or mountains.
There are even gods who
inhabit pots and pans!
Which has to mean,
there's totally a
god of dagashi!
I believe it in my soul!
So to pay tribute, I am
offering up a dance.
A dagashi dance.
[grunts]
Of appreciation!
Yeah, that makes sense.
If you're Hotaru.
Anyway, random subject change.
Let me ask you this,
when you guys were little kids,
did you ever get
in trouble for, like,
playing with your
food and stuff?
Yeah.
Sure.
Right!
Parents just don't understand.
What's wrong with a little
Kuru Kuru Bou sword fighting?
Who doesn't want a necklace
made from Fue Ramune?
So what if you stuff
your face with Watapachi
and drink soda until you burst?
Who cares?
No wonder you got in trouble.
Well, don't worry, 'cause,
I know a fun dagashi
which practically begs
you to play with it!
And that snack is!
[TO]
Maken Gumi, right?
[HOTARU yelps, groans]
[TO]
They're these gummy candies,
which are shaped like rock,
paper, or scissors.
Remember when we used
to play with these?
Oh yeah, good times!
[HOTARU]
Wait a second.
[KOKONOTSU, TO]
Hm?
Wouldn't it be hard
to play with those?
I mean, you have to collect all
three shapes, choose one to play
and then go through the trouble
of taking it out of the bag.
You think so?
Of course. I don't think
it's meant for playing.
It's way too complicated
for all that.
Well, darn.
Oh, I got paper.
Even though the package
is showing scissors!
Hey, you know what?
It reminds me of that toy.
What toy?
Remember?
It was shaped like a hand.
I think it was all rubbery and
you could stick it to stuff.
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh!
[TO]
Hm!
[HOTARU]
Hm...
Wait! An idea!
Ah crap, should I be worried?
[TO, KOKONOTSU grunt]
[SAYA gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
Look! A UFO just
appeared out of nowhere!
[KOKONOTSU, SAYA]
What?
Behold, Maken Gumi!
Witness its divine purpose!
--[TO lausghs]
--[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[SAYA gasps]
[TO] Coconuts, tell me
you saw that, man!
[KOKONOTSU] I don't know
what you're talking about!
--[TO] Whatever, you dog!
--[SAYA yells]
[TO grunts]
So! Moving right along,
I want to talk to you
about a different snack.
Voila!
Feast your eyes on the
world's longest gummy!
Super Himo Q!
Weren't you dancing
with that thing?
Wow, it's crazy long.
Hotaru, hold on.
What about it makes it
okay to play with?
Good question, Master!
By the way.
Your pigtails make
you look adorable!
Really?
Super Himo Q's
advertising slogan is,
"It's fun to play with
and it tastes great, too!"
Catchy, right?
In a nutshell,
the company actually encourages
you to play with your food!
We have to play!
It's the sole reason for
this candy's existence!
You can do so much with it!
Like practice braiding,
maybe tying knots.
Or jumping rope!
But, you have to jump in a way
so that the Himo Q doesn't touch
either the ground or your feet,
because then you can't eat it!
You can even construct
chain mail armor!
How cool is that?
"Cool" is not the
word I would use.
[HOTARU]
Let's put our heads together.
And come up with new ways
to play with Super Himo Q.
Hey guess what?
I've already got a great idea!
Yay.
[HOTARU]
Here, Kokonotsu.
Huh?
Hold this, please.
[KOKONOTSU grunts]
Okay, next.
I'll cross the
Himo Q strings like this.
Are you watching?
Uh, yeah!
[HOTARU]
Now take this side.
So what's the point
of this game, exactly?
We'll both pull on the string
and if your string breaks first,
you have to take
over Shikada Dagashi!
--[HOTARU giggles]
--[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Hey, that's unfair!
What happens to you
if your string is the
first one to break?!
Nothing, since I don't
intend to lose!
--[KOKONOTSU yells]
--[HOTARU grunts]
[BOTH shout]
[HOTARU]
Ugh! It looks like a tie.
That was a close call.
Well, do you have
any ideas, master?
[SAYA]
Hmm. Yeah, I might have one.
Tie the ends together to
make a circle, then do this.
[HOTARU] Whoa! No way, it looks
just like Tokyo Tower!
I can't make anything
else though.
[HOTARU]
Master Saya, you are so cool!
[SAYA gasps]
Nah.
By the way, here's a fun fact.
Do either of you want to
take a guess at how long
the very first Himo Q was?
--Let's see.
--[SAYA] Hm?
[gasps]
Only 30 centimeters!
Approximately one fourth of
the size of today's Himo Q!
Oh. It was small.
What're you doing?!
Quit trying to be Bruce Lee,
swinging the Himo Q around
like a pair of nun chucks!
In those days.
there were three pieces of
Himo Q in each bag of candy.
She ignored me.
[HOTARU] So even then, if you
were to tie them together,
it would just be 90 centimeters.
Currently it's 126 centimeters.
Hey!
You should probably stop
swinging it so hard!
We're so very lucky.
We get to live in a world
with longer Himo Q!
I feel like the candy's
about to snap.
[gasps]
[HOTARU] What the fue?
The string actually broke!
And now it's going to fall on
the ground, because of me!
[KOKONOTSU grunting]
He saved it!
[TO, KOKONOTSU grunt]
[SAYA]
Coconuts! Are you okay?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah.
How strange, my body
just moved on its own!
[HOTARU]
No surprise there!
Your dagashi- lover
instincts strike again.
That was a super epic save!
This totally proves
that you'll be
the best snack shop owner ever!
It does? I'm not really
following your logic.
You don't say?
[HOTARU giggles]
Well then.
Buy him out? No way!
[KOKONOTSU, SAYA]
What?
Stand your ground, dude!
Don't be tempted by
the power of money!
[SAYA]
Huh! Ohajiki?
I say we use this to settle the
candy store successor issue.
Aw, come on!
Give me a break already!
[HOTARU]
And so...
[HOTARU] Dagashi shops
commonly carry toys and games.
This toy's special.
It has a lengthy history and
most stores still carry it.
That toy is,
Ohajiki!
Here are the rules!
Choose which ohajiki piece
you want to capture,
and if you hit it, you get to
keep that one for yourself.
[HOTARU shouts]
[TO]
Aw, out of bounds!
[HOTARU]
Curses!
[TO grunts]
All right!
[SAYA grunts]
[gasps]
I hit one!
[chuckles]
[SAYA]
It's kind of sad though.
I mean, what if you're not good?
Wouldn't you just lose a bunch
of your game pieces that way?
[TO]
Ha, ha. You missed again!
I suck. I'm a total loser,
complete and utter garbage.
It's okay, Coconuts.
[HOTARU]
You know what? In a sense,
this game was kinda like
the start of trading cards
and stuff.
I guess so.
[HOTARU]
It's just one of those things
where it pays be a winner.
[TO]
Aw, out of bounds.
Yes, the winners take all,
and the losers go home!
[ALL] Guess that means
she's going home!
[HOTARU] No fair,
I'm supposed to win!
Anyway, it looks
like you're up, To!
Okay!
All right! Looks like
my pinky finger fits!
Huh? What's that mean?
What?!
You've been playing this whole
time without knowing the rules?
[SAYA]
Yeah.
That rule is called "shikiri".
It's for checking the distance
between ohajiki pieces.
If the pinky doesn't fit,
then you're not allowed to hit!
Oh!
[TO]
Go! Aw...
Pinky time!
[TO gasps]
Looks like your pinky
has betrayed you, Endo!
[TO groans]
The pinky rule
also applies here.
See, if your pinky
doesn't fit in the gap,
it means you didn't hit
your piece hard enough
to win the other one.
Oh, okay.
Guess it's my turn again.
Which one should I take?
[TO] No fair, you're like
some kind of game shark.
[SAYA]
Stop whining.
[HOTARU] Now that I think about
it, whenever we play a new game,
Master Saya always
picks up on it quickly.
She's just naturally
talented I suppose.
Hold on, a dagashi shop
employee who's good at games.
[gasps]
Of course!
Master Saya!
[SAYA]
Hm?
I've got it!
You should work with Kokonotsu
at his family's shop!
[SAYA]
What? What did you say?
[gasps]
--Me? Working with Coconuts?
--[TO yells]
Yes, you!
You'd be perfect for it, Master!
And you could put your
talent to good use!
[SAYA]
Hmph...
Whoa, close call! I thought
for sure it had hit my face!
Wow dude, you almost
lost an eye!
Good thing your
sunglasses blocked it!
[HOTARU]
Is something bothering you?
[gasps]
What? No, no nothing at all!
[laughs]
[SAYA]
And so...
[HOTARU]
Hm. I can't believe this.
I'm the only one here who hasn't
won an ohajiki piece yet.
[HOTARU] I guess you've
left me no choice.
Huh?
No way, it's a
forbidden ohajiki!
A.K.A., an "Ishi-Keri"!
What's that?
A bag of normal ohajiki costs
around a hundred yen.
But that costs just
as much all by itself.
I didn't want have to
resort to this little baby,
yet here we are.
I'm about to taste
sweet, sweet victory.
Dammit.
Yes. now is the winter
of our discontent!
--[gasps]
--[glass shatters]
[KOKONOTSU, SAYA gasp]
[HOTARU sobs]
[TO chuckles]
[KOKONOTSU] Since Ishi-Keri
is big, it's also kinda heavy.
If you drop it,
that beast is gonna break.
I've got it!
You should work with Kokonotsu
at his family's shop!
Was she serious?
I mean we've been
friends a long time,
but could I really
work in his shop?
Of course not. Duh!
H-Hm?
[gasps]
A game piece?
--[SAYA pants] Coconuts!
--[door clatters]
[panting continues]
Hey, Coconuts!
Let's go play!
Oh, hi, Saya!
[SAYA]
Whatcha doin'? Studying?
[KOKONOTSU chuckles]
Not even, check this out!
[SAYA]
Hm?
Yoguret?
Right! Awesome, huh?
It tastes kinda sour,
but also sweet,
and it melts in
your mouth, yummy!
It's sorta like Ramune.
It's sorta like a candy.
Isn't Yoguret amazing?
You and your dagashi.
This is cooler
than other dagashi.
Plus, it's way different
from the other snacks!
Look on the back!
Do you see where it says
"Food with Nutrient Function
Claims" on the box?
Um, yeah? So?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yoguret contains calcium,
which helps you grow strong!
The calcium is crucial to
forming your bones and teeth.
And it has bifidobacteria,
which helps with
pooping and stuff!
Basically, it's a tasty dagashi
that's good for you, too!
Yoguret is
super-duper remarkable!
Think about it,
kids are always begging their
moms and dads for sweets.
But because parents want their
kids to eat healthy stuff,
they might not buy
them candy very often.
And then Yoguret
comes in and is all,
"Hey mom! I'm a healthy snack!"
Okay, we can get this one!
Yay! You're the best, mom!
Thank you!
The inventors are so smart.
They made a truly awesome candy!
[SAYA] Wow, you really
know a lot about dagashi,
huh Coconuts?
Well, I know a little bit.
Oh!
Hey, if you thought
that was cool,
check out what the inside
packaging looks like!
[SAYA]
Hm? That's strange.
It looks like medicine.
Yep!
You're on point
as usual, good job!
Wanna know why it's like that?
The manufacturer of Yoguret
makes medicine as well,
And they use the same packaging
supplies for their snacks.
[SAYA]
Oh...
It's so much fun to pop the
candy out of the package!
[KOKONOTSU] Hm! It kinda makes
you feel like you're a grown up.
Everything about this candy
is just so cool, y'know?
[gasps]
Hey, know what?
This would be good for playing
something like doctor,
wouldn't it?
[SAYA]
What?!
Did... you say playing doctor?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yep.
Well, now, we are gonna
be fourth graders soon.
Honestly we're too
old for that game.
It's not like I
really wanna play,
but if you have your heart set
on such a silly game, we can.
Oh, no problem.
We can always
play something else.
[SAYA] Okay fine, we'll
play the dumb game,
stop pressuring me already!
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[SAYA]
And so?
[sighs]
What the heck?
This is lame.
--[knocking]
--[KOKONOTSU] Doctor!
[SAYA]
Huh?
Will you please examine me?
[KOKONOTSU chuckles]
What's wrong, young man?
My head feels kinda hot.
Well then, we should definitely
check your temperature,
but we don't have a thermometer.
Huh?
You might have a fever.
Or maybe not.
Do I?
Ooh, you do seem to
feel a bit warm.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU yelps]
Wait a minute. Why do I
have to be the doctor?
Why?
It's so weird!
It's weird, right?
[KOKONOTSU] Well, I'm sorta
weirded out, does that count?
[gasps]
And hey, why is
your face all red?
Maybe you have a fever for real?
Oh! Wow, it's
getting worse!
[gasps]
Wha--?
Fine, if you're so smart,
then it's your turn to
be the stupid doctor!
Huh?
[SAYA]
Excuse me, doctor.
I think I might be running
a teensy little fever.
Oh! Well I'll give you
some medicine then!
Huh? But wait, shouldn't you
at least take my temperature?
[KOKONOTSU]
Nope! Just eat these.
[SAYA]
Hm...
[KOKONOTSU] Okay, take good
care of yourself!
Thank you for seeing me.
Hey Doctor!
[KOKONOTSU] Huh? What seems
to be the problem?
[SAYA] My stomach! It hurts!
I think I might be dying!
[KOKONOTSU]
Dying is probably bad.
You have to examine me!
There's no need for that.
Huh?
This medicine will save you!
[SAYA]
Uh...
[sighs]
[KOKONOTSU]
How do you feel?
Do you maybe have a
new lease on life?
Yes.
What wonderful news!
Well then, take care!
Thank you for seeing me.
Doctor! Help!
I think I'm going
into cardiac arrest!
Oh no, that sounds terrible.
Right here the pain in
my chest is unbearable!
I'm most definitely
having a heart attack!
I beg you, doctor,
please give me a
thorough examination!
Sure thing. Sounds like
you need medicine.
Hey wait, shouldn't
you at least, like,
listen to my heartbeat
or something?
[gasps]
Of course, silly me.
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Sounds pretty good.
[gasps]
Here, take one of these.
Doctor! I think I have the
chicken pox! Please check me!
Here's some medicine.
What are you,
some kinda quack?
Huh?
[SAYA]
What's wrong with you?
Don't just prescribe medicine!
You should do things.
Do things like this, or that.
Look, just do something!
Are you ready, miss?
We'll begin the operation now.
Yes.
This is the anesthetic medicine.
Swallow it.
[KOKONOTSU screams]
[SAYA]
Hm? Hey, what's wrong?
There isn't any left.
There's no more Yoguret.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
And that was my only box.
Oh. I'm sorry, I guess
I ate them all.
Um, I know! I'll be the
doctor and treat you!
'Kay? Come on now,
don't be sad, Coconuts.
I don't wanna play.
Oh, jeez. Stop being childish!
[BOTH yell, grunt]
Huh?
[gasps]
[SAYA] What a strange thing
to remember just now.
No matter how old I get,
that memory never gets
any less embarrassing.
[SAYA] Knowing Coconuts,
he probably forgot all about it.
Boys are stupid.
Well, maybe it's not a bad
thing if he did forget all that.
Sometimes I really wish
I could forget it!
[SAYA]
Hi guys!
Oh ho, look who it is!
What's up? Need something?
Kind of.
So, um. I was wondering.
It's about what you
said at the shrine.
[HOTARU]
I'm so glad you stopped by!
What?
You're just in time, wait until
you see today's awesome dagashi!
I think you'll
totally like this one!
What kind of dagashi?
It's so cool!
This snack has, "Food with
Nutrient Function Claims"
right on the box!
It's Yoguret!
[KOKONOTSU, SAYA gasp]
Huh? Master Saya's
face is all red.
[KOKONOTSU whimpers]
[SAYA grunts]
Wow! I just remembered
I have to wash my hair!
[SAYA panting]
[SAYA] Well, I guess
he does remember it.
[HOTARU]
Master Saya!
Why do you think
Maken Gumi exists?
[SAYA] I don't really wanna talk
about that stupid candy, Hotaru.
[HOTARU gasps]
Right! I'm sorry!
You know, I never expected
to see stars at the shrine.
[SAYA]
What? Stars?
Oh, do you mean the
star gummy in Maken Gumi?
[HOTARU]
Uh, not exactly.
[SAYA]
Well then, what do you mean?
[HOTARU] I was surprised
that it was stars
instead of like
strawberries or hearts!
But stars are really cute too!
[SAYA] Wait, strawberries and
hearts were popular designs
on girls' underwear.
[SAYA gasps, screams]