[TO]
♪ Walkin' in the dark  ♪
♪ to get a late night
a snackie snack! ♪
♪ A late night
Eenie, meenie, miney, moe,
catch a tiger by his toes.
Toe?
♪ I don't remember how
the rest of it goes. ♪
[HOTARU]
Hey, Endo!
Oh. Hi, Hotaru. What's the haps?
[HOTARU]
Fancy running into you!
So, um, you jogging?
Nuh-uh. Just... going... out.
Yeah? Seems late
to be going out.
[HOTARU] Well, I have
a good reason for it.
I'm sure you do,
but be careful.
A lot of street lamps around
here aren't exactly dependable.
Plus I'm not sure a girl
should be out alone at night.
Oh my god. Uh, what's goin' on?
[HOTARU] Listen, Endo.
Fate has led me to you.
Thank goodness.
What?
[HOTARU]
So please. Please help me!
This is strange.
[door opens]
[SAYA]
Hello!
I'm sorry. But we're actually
already closed for the day!
[SAYA]
Hm?
Are you looking for something?
Well, yeah.
Have you seen Hotaru lately?
No.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hmm...
How weird.
What's wrong?
I'm worried.
She hasn't shown up at
our shop the past few days.
It just seems strange.
Strange?
Yeah! Come on, Hotaru eats,
drinks, and breathes dagashi!
And yet, she hasn't been
at our dagashi shop.
It's like the end
times or something.
Oh, I see. That is
pretty apocalyptic.
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah.
I hate to admit it,
but... I'm kinda scared.
[SAYA]
Sounds serious.
I guess.
I've got it. Why don't the two
of us go check up on her?
Honestly, now that
you've brought it up,
I'm pretty worried as well.
What if she's sick or something?
You know what else?
I think she lives alone.
Wow.
Wait, where are we going?
[SAYA]
Weren't you listening?
Hotaru's house.
[KOKONOTSU]
Geez. It's massive!
Yeah, there's a rumor that
her dad built this place
for while she's here.
What? Seriously?
He built this house just so
she could recruit my dad?
Talk about... excessive.
[SAYA]
That's the rumor.
[KOKONOTSU]
Her whole family is insane!
I mean, haven't they
heard of hotels?
Of course not.
That's too simple...
[SAYA] There's no answer.
Maybe she's out?
[HOTARU]
Yes? Who's there?
[SAYA gasps]
Hotaru! Hey, it's me!
[HOTARU] Master Saya? Hold on,
I'll... ow... be right there!
Thank God! Huh?
Are you sick?
Poor thing.
[HOTARU]
Oh!
Kind of. I feel really
tired. Ow! So... ow!
So I was just lying
down for a bit.
I'm sorry.
[HOTARU]
But thanks for stopping by.
[screams]
This is why rich people
are the worst. Huh?
[KOKONOTSU yelps]
I didn't see you there! Huh?
[HOTARU]
K-K-K-K-K-K-K-K-K-K...
Okay. What's up
with the stuttering?
[HOTARU]
Huh? What? Who, me?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yes, you!
[HOTARU screaming]
[SAYA, KOKONOTSU]
Hotaru!
She's hot. Really hot.
Like a fever?
Maybe.
Geez. All this over a cold?
Listen, a cold can be
pretty serious, so there.
[KOKONOTSU]
You know, I'm kinda surprised.
[SAYA]
Why?
She's crazy about snacks.
I thought for sure she'd have
some sort of wacky
dagashi wallpaper.
[SAYA]
Oh.
But there's nothing.
Yeah, bizarre.
[HOTARU groans]
[BOTH]
Uh?
[SAYA]
You're awake.
[HOTARU]
I passed out?
[SAYA]
Yeah, you did.
You had us both worried.
How are you feeling?
[screaming]
[KOKONOTSU]
For real?
Why do you keep
screaming like that?
Did I do something
to offend you?
[HOTARU]
No! Um... you're not... ow...
...guilty of anything. Ouch!
What?
[HOTARU] Never mind!
Don't worry about it! Oh!
This is not your
burden to carry!
Oh! I must carry it myself!
That's right! Kokonotsu's
presence won't sway me!
I will triumph over temptation!
[ DAGASHI CHARACTERS]
Yay, yay, Hotaru!
You can do it, we believe
in you! Yay, yay...
Oh, wow. Thanks everyone.
Thanks for believing in me.
I won't give up!
[KOKONOTSU]
Hey, Hotaru?
Your delusions are leaking.
I can see them!
Okay. Now what should we do?
She's acting really weird.
Well, I guess
weirder than usual.
I'd be worried if she
wasn't acting strange.
I'm actually relieved.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hmm...
That's a pretty fair
point but still.
Ah! Hey, Hotaru!
[HOTARU]
Uh?
[KOKONOTSU]
I almost forgot.
We brought you some
get well presents.
Yeah, we weren't exactly
sure what you would like,
so we tried to bring
a bit of everything.
In the end,
we decided on stuff with
the most nutritional value.
[HOTARU]
How sweet. What are they?
Look!
[screams]
[KOKONOTSU] It's all things
we sell at Shikada Dagashi!
Which do you want first?
[HOTARU]
D-D-D-D-D-D-D-D-D...
Do you mean dagashi?
[crying]
[KOKONOTSU]
No.
What's going on?
This... This can't be real.
She turned down dagashi!
Listen. Is this a joke?
It's either that or you're
actually an alien in disguise.
Because you would never
turn down a snack.
[chuckles]
Uh?
[SAYA]
Stop, Coconuts.
She probably can't eat any
because she doesn't feel well.
C'mon. It's obvious her
throat is bothering her.
[KOKONOTSU] No, that's
not the Hotaru I know.
She would never let sickness
keep her from dagashi!
[SAYA]
I dunno.
[KOKONOTSU] I'll check again.
I need to be sure.
[HOTARU]
And so...
[KOKONOTSU]
Ooh, what's this?
It's a famous snack with an
elephant drawing on the lid.
[HOTARU]
What?
Why an elephant?
Because the snack's
container resembles
the shape of an elephant's foot.
Inside the container is a
tasty sweet and sour yogurt.
[HOTARU]
Is it the irresistible-- Ow!
Morocco Fruit Yogul?
Yes! It's Morocco Fruit Yogul!
Thank goodness!
Geez, you really had me
goin' there for a minute.
Well. Go ahead and
take one if you want.
Now what?
[HOTARU]
I'm not hungry.
What? For real?
[KOKONOTSU growls]
Then...
...Ramen Shop taro!
Ika taro! Yakiniku-san taro!
No go?
Well, let's see you resist
the tantalizing scent of...
...cabbage taro!
I've got 'em all!
So which one would you
like to try? Pick one.
[sniffing]
[HOTARU]
Cabbage. Cabbage.
You want the cabbage taro?
[KOKONOTSU]
Dammit. I won't give up.
A-ha! Look at this!
Want some aji curry?
Here, little Hotaru.
[HOTARU]
Oh... Aji curry.
It's okay, come on out now.
Who wants a spicy
snack? Good girl!
She's not a dog.
And she shouldn't be eating
spicy food right now.
Maybe the scent is too weak.
[SAYA]
Huh?
Can you smell it now?
[HOTARU whining]
[screaming]
Gotcha!
[HOTARU crying]
Hey, it's okay.
Please tell us why
you're avoiding dagashi.
You haven't been
to Coconuts' shop.
And we just can't help but
be worried about you, is all.
Let us help you.
[HOTARU]
I can't-- Ouch!
Come on, Hotaru.
What's really going on here?
Whatever it is, we'll
do our best to help.
[HOTARU wailing]
[HOTARU]
Master Saya!
[KOKONOTSU]
Holy crap! It's God-Zit-A!
[HOTARU]
No, it's not.
Uh. Then What?
[SAYA]
Wait. Is that your...
...ulcer?
[HOTARU]
Mh-hm, mh-hm.
[SAYA laughing]
[SAYA] Wow, it seems to
have gotten much worse.
[groans]
You mean Hotaru had an ulcer?
[SAYA]
Yeah.
The watapachi she ate probably
didn't do her any favors.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Sounds painful.
Is that it? Why you can't eat?
It's hard to believe.
I thought it'd take
more than that
to keep you away from dagashi.
[KOKONOTSU]
Right.
I can't imagine you'd
let an ulcer stop you.
Well, to be honest-- Oh!
Hey, are you all right?
It's okay, just take your time.
[sighs] It all started
a few days ago.
I think it's getting worse.
Maybe eating watapachi
and Sakura Daikon
wasn't such a great idea.
Ah!
There's a brand new flavor
of Baby Star Ramen
coming out soon.
I really hope this
ulcer heals up.
I need to be in optimal
heath on release day!
Okay then...
I wish my ulcer..
...would go away!
I must not be
seeing things right.
All right. What does it say?
[HOTARU]
Please let my ulcer heal
so I can enjoy the new Baby
Star Ramen on its release day
and I'll donate money
to poor people!
My fate's in your
hands, dagashi gods!
[gasps]
[groaning]
[HOTARU]
Ouchie.
You used Popping
Fortune-Telling, really?
[SAYA]
Mh-hm.
If only you had some sort of
access to modern day medicine.
But what does that have
to do with not eating?
Is it because you
believed the results
of the fortune-telling
chocolate?
You've gotta be kidding.
That's not really the
reason why, right?
[HOTARU]
Mm-mm, mm-mm.
My story isn't over...
uh... quite yet. Ohh!
So, naturally, I panicked.
[HOTARU]
If I have to, I'll try them all.
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
Oh my gosh, a double circle!
Going out?
[HOTARU] Since I got a double
circle for going out,
I decided to leave right away.
[KOKONOTSU]
And go where?
[HOTARU] Nowhere in
particular, I just went out.
[SAYA]
Huh?
Good to see you "out" and
about! Get it? Get it?
[laughing]
[TO] Eenie, meenie, miney, moe,
catch a tiger by his toes.
Toe?
♪ I don't remember how
the rest of it goes. ♪
[HOTARU]
Hey, Endo!
Oh. Hi, Hotaru. What's the haps?
[HOTARU]
Fancy running into you!
So, um, you jogging?
Nuh-uh. Just... going... out.
Yeah? Seems late
to be going out.
Oh my god. Uh, what's goin' on?
[HOTARU] Listen, Endo.
Fate has led me to you.
Thank goodness.
What?
That's your big problem?
[HOTARU]
Well it is a big problem!
I have a solution.
[HOTARU]
Yeah?
[TO]
It's simple.
All you have to do is stop
eating dagashi for a few days.
Are you crazy?!
There's no way I
could quit cold turkey!
Dagashi is the reason
for my existence!
I need it like I need air.
Do you want me to suffocate?
But which one is more
important to you?
Do you wanna eat the
new Baby Star Ramen
when it releases or not?
Absolutely!
[TO]
Then you know what to do.
[HOTARU groans]
[TO] It kinda sounds
like overeating dagashi
is what caused the whole
problem in the first place,
you know what I mean?
Besides, with the way
things are going right now,
there's no way it's gonna heal
up before the release date.
But still!
Why don't you just try?
If anything it'll taste
even better that way.
Don't things taste better if
you haven't had 'em in a while?
Maybe you're right. Baby Star
is already super amazing.
[TO]
For sure. You fast then...
Pure bliss!
For a flash back it sure is hot.
I would kill for some AC.
Guess I'll settle
for a cold drink.
[giggling]
Now you know. I'm fasting.
For Baby Star Ramen-- Oh!
Geez.
[groaning]
Don't get me wrong.
I guess To's advice
sort of made sense.
Or he could've told her
to take some medicine.
What a relief.
At least now we know why
she isn't eating dagashi.
Deep down, she's the
same snack-loving Hotaru.
[SAYA]
I'm glad.
But now I feel bad about
bringing those snacks, y'know?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah.
[rustling]
Hey, relax. You should
be trying to rest.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[yelps]
No, don't!
Stop it! You've been
doing good, don't ruin it!
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Wait a minute.
She's moving like
some kind of zombie,
like she's not in control
of her own body!
[SAYA]
What?!
No!
You're better than this!
Don't let all your effort
go to waste! Hang in there!
Don't give up!
Please Hotaru, come back
to us! We believe in you!
Almost, got it!
Yeah!
[gasps]
[ALL yelp]
[HOTARU]
Uh...
Medicine.
Seriously? You have
some meds? Where?
In the fridge-- Oh!
[SAYA]
Here.
Take some.
Thank you, Master Saya.
You okay?
I'm fine.
The flavor's just a
little overwhelming.
What can you do, though?
[SAYA]
Uh...
[gasps] Hold on!
What the hell is this?
It's looks like a hippie
threw up in your bowl!
[HOTARU]
Well yeah.
The color is a bit crazy,
but it's effective!
[SAYA groans]
It's weird, though.
Right after I take it, I
start to feel a little better
and get some of my energy back.
Unfortunately, my ulcer
always feels worse afterwards.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
Whatever this is,
it smells amazing!
[gasps]
Wait a sec.
Can I see that?
Just for a minute.
What? Sure thing.
[sniffing]
[gasps]
It can't be. Hotaru!
[HOTARU]
Yes?
Tell me,
what are the ingredients used
to make this medicine?
Let's see. Hang on,
I'm trying to think.
[KOKONOTSU]
Pineapple.
Melon.
And lastly, its main
ingredient is...
...American Cola.
[SAYA gasps]
Wait, are you serious?
You're astute, as usual.
But no big surprise there.
As expected from my rival. Uh?
Hey, is something wrong?
I dunno, is it?
Hotaru.
We were sincerely
worried about you.
[HOTARU]
Uh? Uh...?
You really don't know
why your ulcer is worse?
[HOTARU]
Huh?
[KOKONOTSU groans]
[KOKONOTSU]
Look at these.
They're pineapple and melon
flavored drink mixes.
Made by the same company
who makes American Cola.
Normally they taste
pretty awesome,
but that's if they're separate.
[HOTARU] Usually I would
drink them separately
depending on the
symptom I wanna treat.
But desperate times call
for desperate measures.
So I mixed together everything
I bought at Kokonotsu's shop.
Hmm? Kokonotsu's shop.
[screams]
They're dagashi!
C'mon, Saya.
[SAYA]
Mh-hm.
Wait, you guys!
Don't leave! Oww.
[HOTARU]
Mmm.
Whatever this stuff
is miracle juice!
[BOTH]
It's not a miracle!
It's dagashi, dammit!
[HOTARU] There's pineapple,
grape, melon, and orange,
but did you know there's
a fresh soda flavor too?
[SAYA] Those are drink mixes,
like American Cola right?
[HOTARU]
Yes!
But I bet you didn't know
that there's another way
to enjoy them besides
just drinking them!
[SAYA]
Huh? What do you mean?
[HOTARU]
I mean you can mix them!
[SAYA] Didn't Coconuts
say they taste better
if you drink them separately?
[HOTARU] Yes, but it's more
fun to create new flavors
by trying out different combos!
[SAYA]
I guess.
[HOTARU] I said it's important
to make dagashi last, right?
The same's true for
these drink mixes.
[SAYA] Oh! I do remember.
Well played, Hotaru!