That you, Coconuts?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah, it's me. I wonder...
What is it?
Deep down inside,
have you ever wished you could
become super popular with women?
[TO]
How ridiculous.
I desire to be popular, so I am.
I am, so I desire to be popular.
[gasps]
[SAYA sighs]
[SAYA]
The shade feels so nice.
And the breeze is so refreshing.
[HOTARU]
Hey, Master Saya?
[SAYA]
Hm?
I wonder...
About?
About love, and what you
think it might taste like.
Uh!
Do you wanna know?
I could show you.
[SAYA]
Show me?
Yes, my darling.
[SAYA]
Um, who me?
[HOTARU] Are you ready...
to see how love tastes?
Well, uh...
I'll show you personally.
No! It's never crossed my mind!
[SAYA gasps]
Just relax.
Why should I?! What are
you gonna do to me?!
Lesbi-honest here,
do you swing that way?!
[SAYA gasps]
Now, close your eyes.
Nice and tight.
[SAYA]
What?!
This is all too sudden!
[SAYA whimpering]
[pop]
What the--? It's candy?
[chuckles]
[SAYA]
This flavor... strawberry?
That's not it.
Could be apple, maybe.
No, hold on. What is it?
[gasps]
[SAYA]
Wait, this tastes like cherry!
Yes, that's correct!
Behold!
The little round cherry, which
hails from a rainbow in the sky.
It embraces the flavor
of an innocent love!
[HOTARU]
Poem of Cherries!
[SAYA]
Huh?
You really are amazing!
I knew you'd figure out the
answer to that super hard quiz!
"What's the taste of love?"
Just ask my master!
What? This was
a quiz? Um, okay.
Duhn-dun!
Here's a question!
Coconuts desires to be popular.
His next move is critical.
What will he do now?
Ding dong!
He hits the buzzer!
As we discussed previously,
girls are way into
fortune-telling.
I plan to capitalize on that.
Orion Company's ramune!
"I'm gonna eat it! Hi!"
Dumbest looking snack ever.
Bro, your bright idea
relies on something
that looks like a crappy camera.
Well, um... Yeah, you're right.
It does look kinda cheap, huh?
[TO]
Definitely.
[BOTH laughing]
Still, i'm serious.
Yeah?
[KOKONOTSU]
This snack...
...can tell us our fortune!
[TO]
Cowabunga!
[KOKONOTSU]
Look on the back!
I get it. So this tells us
our fortune for tomorrow.
According to the
instructions on the box,
the colors represent
different types of fortunes.
So, we score a pink one,
and tomorrow the girls
will be all over us!
Dude, I am so psyched for
this lifestyle. Let's do this!
Hell yeah, To!
Now that's the spirit!
Aw yeah! Open it up!
Okay! Then let's see here... Oh?
You can pick first!
'Kay...
[gasps]
I shook it so hard
two pieces came out.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU] No fair!
Both of them are pink?!
[KOKONOTSU chuckles]
Hey! Let's put one back inside.
After all, you don't
need two, do you?
[yelp]
Why?! Why did you eat them?
What if those were the only two
pink pieces in the whole box?!
[KOKONOTSU screams]
Pull yourself together, fool.
[gasps]
Listen up. I can't
help but wonder.
You know, about how you
suggested I go first.
[gasps]
Deep down you were hoping that
my piece wouldn't be a pink one.
Maybe you thought I would
get a different color,
so your chances of getting
pink would be higher.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[TO] Would it make you happy
if that were the case?
Do you think I'm somehow
less deserving of popularity
than you?
Come on, Coconuts. By all
means, stop me if I'm wrong.
No?
Let me guess, if I did
get a different color
you would've been
all like, "Ohh no!"
But that's what you actually
wanted all along, isn't it?
Sound about right?
And now, this is divine justice
for your shameful actions.
[KOKONOTSU]
You're right. It's just that...
... I wanna be popular!
[TO]
Chill out, man.
[gasps]
I'm not even gonna lie, I would
have done the exact same thing
if I had been in your shoes.
But it's okay. We're
still cool, all right?
[KOKONOTSU]
Mh-hm.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
A pink ramune! But how?!
The truth is I only
ate one of them.
I hid the other piece
between my fingers.
I saved this one for you.
Whoa, no way!
It's cool! Eat up!
Thanks a lot!
Thanks to ramune,
we'll be way popular!
Yep, startin' tomorrow!
Yes!
♪ So pop-u-lar!
So pop-u-lar! ♪
--Aw yeah!
--♪ So pop-u-lar! ♪
[TO] ♪ We'll have to beat
women off with a stick! ♪
[KOKONOTSU, TO singing]
What are they doing?
Boys are weird.
♪ Again and again, we'll
be pop-u-lar friends ♪
♪ Oh! Tomorrow for sure!
We'll be so pop-u-lar! ♪
[TO] Hey. Look up on the bridge.
It's Saya and Hotaru.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[TO] I wonder what
they're thinking about.
[HOTARU] I'm looking forward
to seeing which dream
you will choose to pursue
when it's all said and done.
And until that day comes...
...I promise to wait patiently,
so take your time.
[TO yawns]
Man, I'm beat. You wanna
start heading back now?
[KOKONOTSU]
Mh-hm.
[SAYA]
They're leaving.
I wonder what that crazy
dancing was about.
Anyway, I'm curious.
You know earlier?
What was up with all that
poem and cherry stuff?
Poem?
[SAYA] Yeah, like the cherries
and rainbows in the sky.
Or whatever it was.
Oh!
You're talking about the poem
that was written on the
back of this package!
[SAYA] I see! So that's
where it came from!
It sure did and talk
about sap-tacular!
Even I couldn't write
something like that!
[gasps]
Oh, right! Yeah, it's
so dumb! Ridiculous.
[HOTARU]
But still...
I kind of like this
poem. It's nice.
Yeah, it sure is.
Strange though,
why do you think they chose
a cherry to represent love?
Maybe love is
sometimes bittersweet?
Well that's what I think anyway.
Works for me!
[HOTARU]
Bittersweet, huh?
[SAYA]
Uh?
[gasps]
[SAYA]
No, it can't be!
Does Hotaru have a crush
on Coconuts after all?!
Hey.
Yeah? What's up?
Have you ever... had a
bittersweet run in with love?
Do you know what it's like?
What?! Well I kind of have.
But I also haven't.
If that makes any sense.
[HOTARU giggling]
Oh my Pocchi.
Huh?
[SAYA grumbles]
Hotaru.
I get the feeling we're
not on the same page here.
[SAYA]
Hm?
[TO]
What's wrong, Coconuts?
Ya haven't even
touched your coffee.
Hey, uh, To?
Yeah?
Could I ask you something?
It's about Hotaru.
Am I tying her up?
What?! Tying her up?!
[moaning]
It eats less snacks or then...
--[KOKONOTSU yells]
--[HOTARU yelps]
...I'll whip it
with my crop again!
[HOTARU screams]
Forgive me, please!
--What?
--No,
--Seems kinda out of the blue,
--I must've misheard him
--but go on.
--or something.
[KOKONOTSU]
Okay. It happened yesterday.
Something wrong?
[KOKONOTSU]
Well,
am I the reason you haven't
been able to take those trips?
Is it maybe because
you've been busy
coming to our shop every day?
Gee, I hadn't really
given it much thought.
[KOKONOTSU] Then, get this,
she said it was because
I hadn't made up my mind about
taking over the shop yet.
Come on! Don't worry!
Honestly, when you said
you were tying her up,
I thought you meant
something dirty.
Am I right, Saya?
What?! Of course
I didn't think that!
[TO]
Whatever!
Do you want me to freakin'
cut you?! 'Cause I will.
'Kay, sorry. Anyway,
back to you.
Let me see if I can
understand your problem.
You're worried that because you
haven't made up your mind,
Hotaru can't be free
to do what she wants.
I guess.
You're way overthinking it.
[KOKONOTSU]
I dunno.
It's like,
I keep thinking about how my
dad makes me watch the shop,
and because of that I can't
do my own thing, y'know?
So you empathize with her?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah.
[SAYA] But you know what?
Hotaru is strong.
She's not the type of person
to let someone keep her
from chasing her dreams.
And she's a free spirit.
I can't imagine that anyone
could take that away.
That's true.
You're a super big help, Saya.
And thanks for the fresh coffee.
No problem.
I promise to wait patiently.
Take your time.
[TO] Look, bro, if you're
that worried about it,
why not just ask her yourself?
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
Be honest with her! It's faster
to just go ahead and ask.
[door opens]
[TO]
Hm?
Whoa! Speak of the
devil! Great timing!
Now's your chance, Coconuts!
Yeah.
Um, hey, Hotaru!
Table for one. Smoking please.
[gasps]
I'm confused. Did she
take up smoking or what?
[KOKONOTSU]
Mm...
I'm not really sure,
but why else would she ask
to sit in the smoking section?
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[KOKONOTSU]
Whoa, hold up!
That's Morinaga Milk Caramel!
I don't get it.
Why would she eat a milk
caramel in the smoking section?
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh...
[gasps]
Wait, I just
remembered something!
It was an anti-smoking
advertisement.
They used to pitch milk caramel
as an alternative to cigarettes.
What?! For real?!
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah!
In fact, it was originally
marketed just for adults.
Why? Is it because
it was expensive?
That could be a big part of it.
In the Meiji era,
it was kinda pricy.
For instance, one daifuku
and a piece of milk caramel
cost the exact same amount.
Wow.
But there's more!
This is what makes
milk caramel so special.
You see, back then,
Japanese people weren't that
used to dairy products.
Well, at first, the milk
caramels didn't sell very well
because a lot of
people complained
that it smelled kinda like milk.
Ohh. I get it, so they changed
up their marketing technique,
and called it a
cigarette alternative.
[KOKONOTSU]
Right.
It had fans though,
even before the anti-smoking
marketing change.
Guess who the
biggest fan was.
The one and only
Yukichi Fukuzawa!
Milk caramel candies are
seriously boss! Yummy!
[gasps]
[YUKICHI] Excuse me! I need
to restock my caramel stash!
Can you break a ten thousand?
[TO, SAYA]
Ohh!
[TO]
Hm?
Coconuts, check it!
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[TO]
"Not bad, young grasshopper.
But surely you can do better.
Impress me, if you can."
I speak fluent facial expression
and that's what she said!
Are you sure?
Impress her?
But that's all I know about it.
[KOKONOTSU] What else?
What else could there be?
[TO] "Maybe this question
is just too hard for you,
Kokonotsu."
Don't let her silently sass you!
You need to show her
you're the man, Coconuts!
I believe in you!
Coconuts.
[chuckles]
That's it!
It's all about flavor!
Milk caramels come
in many flavors.
Including nanko ume , azuki
bean, and matcha flavors!
And I saved the best for last.
The flavor that's my nickname!
It's the coconut's milk
flavored caramel!
Is that all?
Uh...
Not bad, I guess.
It will suffice for now.
That was bizarre.
Uh-huh.
Hey wait, aren't
you gonna stop her?
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
You needed to talk
to her, didn't you?
Ah! Crap, you're right!
[BOTH gasp]
Geez, close call.
It's comin' down hard.
[KOKONOTSU] I wonder where
Hotaru went. She's super fast.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hey, Hotaru!
Oh, hi! What are
you doing out here?
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Honestly, the rain doesn't
bother me that much.
I just really wanted to eat,
but it's hard to walk
and eat sometimes.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
What were you eating?
[HOTARU]
Ta-dah!
[KOKONOTSU]
Ah. Good ol' Sakuma Drops.
Yeah, it's one of my favorites.
But its normal packaging
isn't very convenient
for traveling and
eating, y'know?
But this package,
it's much more resilient.
Great for traveling,
but difficult to access.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm...
[HOTARU] With this lid I don't
have to worry about the rain.
Great job, Sakuma Drops.
Way to be tough!
[KOKONOTSU]
It's resilient all right.
It's even keeping Hotaru out.
Hey, um, can I see the Sakuma
drops for just a second?
[HOTARU]
Huh?
For those types of lids,
any coin will do the trick.
See?
[HOTARU]
What?!
This whole time I could
have been opening it
with just a coin?!
This is witchcraft I tell you!
There's no magic involved.
Anyway, how have
you been opening it?
Willpower!
For real?
[HOTARU yells]
[HOTARU] Yeah! It works
surprisingly well.
[HOTARU chuckles]
Actually, sometimes
it didn't work at all.
[KOKONOTSU]
Shocking.
Here!
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh, thank you!
Ew, mint.
[KOKONOTSU yelps]
[HOTARU] What were you planning
on doing with that drop?
Hey! Let go of me!
You were going to
put the candy back,
and then you planned on
picking a different one!
[KOKONOTSU gasping]
You can't do that!
It doesn't matter if
you don't like it
It's taboo to put it back!
Even if it's you, Kokonotsu.
There're simply no exceptions!
Fine, okay.
The mint is actually
pretty tasty.
Told you so!
And you thought you
wouldn't like it.
A lot of people judge it
before they even try it,
but I wonder why they do that.
It's pretty good!
It even has its own candy pack
where they're all mint flavored.
You should always try new
foods. You might like 'em!
[gasps]
Oh yeah. Hey, Hotaru?
I was looking for you 'cause
I wanted to talk with you.
Well, talk away.
Yesterday on the train you said
that you would wait patiently
for me to make my decision.
But still, I feel like
maybe I should hurry up
and try to make that decision.
Why do you think that?
Because if I don't
make up my mind soon,
you'll have to stay here
and keep coming to our shop.
I want you to be able to
travel whenever you want.
Staying here, it's only
going to hinder your dream
to be the world's number
one snack manufacturer.
That's not fair to you.
Also, yesterday you said you
wanted to tour snack shops.
[HOTARU]
Kokonotsu?
Uh, yeah?
Look, you're way off
the mark on this one.
[KOKONOTSU]
What?
[HOTARU] If I really want to
travel again, then I will.
Hey, come on! We'll go on
a trip together right now!
That's a little too spontaneous.
And regardless...
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
[HOTARU] Building the world's
number one snack manufacturer?
It's not a dream, it's reality.
[gasps]
[HOTARU] Also, yes, I go
to the shop every day.
And yes, I'm trying to convince
you to take over for your dad.
Most importantly though,
I just go to have fun, and
hang out with our friends.
[HOTARU chuckles]
[HOTARU]
But thank you so much.
I appreciate your
consideration on the matter.
Ah, well, it's not a big deal.
[HOTARU]
It's like the lid container.
What's that?
[HOTARU]
I told you.
There are times I can't
open it with willpower.
Okay, so?
But we opened it
with a coin instead.
[HOTARU]
That's your answer.
Huh? Hold up.
You're not makin'
any sense again.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
It's nice out, and so pretty!
[gasps] Uh, yeah.
Shall we go?
Okay!
[HOTARU]
Come to think of it,
I don't think I've ever seen
a bus come to that stop.
[KOKONOTSU]
Don't worry, it'll show up.
Eventually, anyway.
Oh really?
[KOKONOTSU] Guess you'll
have to wait and see!
[HOTARU laughing]