So, uh... Listen, Coconuts.
You may not have
noticed on the account
that you're kinda oblivious,
but this has been bothering me!
You need to be honest here.
[SAYA] Why is your shop
so run down looking?
[KOKONOTSU] It's been
three months since then.
You think so?
Duh, of course! It's like
a hobo snack shop!
[KOKONOTSU] Maybe, but we
seem to be managing somehow,
so don't worry!
See ya!
Hey, wait! Jeez, seriously?
Is their shop really okay?
Yo, I'm home!
[groans]
[YO]
The shop is a lost cause.
Oh, welcome home.
A lost cause?
[YO] I think... it's time
to admit we're done for.
[YO]
Are you okay?
Like, your eyes are even
more dead than usual.
♪
Look, there's no easy way to
say this, so I'll just be blunt.
We don't have that
many customers.
No customers means no money.
And no money means
there's no way
to afford repairs around here.
You're not even
listening, are you?
[KOKONOTSU] Honestly,
I already knew all that.
Deep down, I had
known for a while.
But for some reason,
I had this idea
that things would work
out if I stuck around.
[YO]
Earth to Kokonotsu?
[KOKONOTSU]
I was waiting for it.
Just waiting.
[HOTARU]
I'd like you to keep this.
[gasps]
Uh. You can't!
Please, you can't go
out of business, Dad!
I don't want to.
I've got a free bar!
A winner can only be exchanged
at the dagashi store
where it was purchased!
You know what?
I like that determined
look on your face.
Aha. It's Hotaru's, isn't it?
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh.
[YO]
I've seen it.
Sometimes you take the Homerun
Bar stick out of the drawer
and stare at it when
you think you're alone.
That's why I think its Hotaru's.
[yelps]
[YO] You're lucky I'm the
only one who's caught you.
If someone else saw
you doin' that,
they'd think you were a
total creeper, Konkonotsu.
What the hell?! The only
creeper here is you!
[YO]
Very well, let's do it.
It's time to revive...
our snack shop!
For real?
Right, first off, let's
clean up the store!
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah!
Come on, Dad, first
one outside wins!
Hurry up, ya slowpoke!
[YO]
I am!
Hey, no running
inside, remember?
[YO screaming]
[KOKONOTSU] And that's how
Dad wound up in the hospital.
For a whole month.
[YO] Try to hang in
there while I'm gone.
You've got this.
It's nothing you
can't handle, son.
Oops, I mean,
Manager Kokonostu.
[KOKONOTSU]
It is shabby.
It's not like I
hadn't noticed it.
I guess I was just pre-occupied
by Hotaru's disappearance.
[KOKONOTSU]
Why?
[SAYA] To, I'm really
worried about Coconuts.
I mean, like his eyes have
always looked pretty dead,
but lately, they're worse
than those deep sea fish.
Wow, spoken like a true friend.
Although, you might be right.
I know. We should go
try to cheer him up.
Oh, but whatever you do,
don't bring up Hotaru.
He makes super weird faces
whenever she's mentioned.
That sounds fun
though! I wanna see.
Hi, uh, it's kinda messy,
but you guys can come in.
I'm cleaning.
[SAYA]
Uh.
He seems okay.
Um. Sorry if I made you worry.
[SAYA]
Well, I was pretty worried.
I feel like a jerk for
making you guys help me.
It's all good, man!
We just feel bad that
Hotaru ditched you-- Ah!
[SAYA]
Shut your dumb face!
Uh. Sorry.
[KOKONOTSU chuckles]
Well, I'm okay now.
Besides, I'm sure
she'll come back.
I've made up my mind.
I am gonna make this
shop better than ever!
Good, Coconuts.
Plus, if we don't start
making some money,
the only food I'll
have is this dagashi .
Why did you wait for things
to get that desperate?
I'm gonna take this
to the dumpster.
[KOKONOTSU]
Thanks!
Let's see. What goes
after the umaibo ?
Hey, do you remember, Coconuts?
[KOKONOTSU]
"Get a Move On, You Cod!"
[grunts]
[SAYA]
Seriously? What the heck?
Was I being slow?
No, I wasn't, right?
And even if I was being slow,
where does he get off
calling me a freakin' cod
when I'm over here
sacrificing my free time to
help him clean up his shop?
[KOKONOTSU]
Did you hear me, Saya?
[growls]
[KOKONOTSU]
Ah! What? What did I do?
[SAYA]
"Get a Move On, You Cod!"
[KOKONOTSU] Its name is a
play on the word "cod."
Besides snacking, it's
also used as a side dish.
[SAYA chuckles]
Uh, sorry.
Give it a try. It's quite
popular with adults.
They eat it while drinking,
and some use it in soups.
You're right! It's delicious!
Still though, that's one heck
of a name and illustration.
And here, look on the
back of the package.
It says, "Let's have
a bite and shout,
'Get a move on, you cod!'"
Do you think... we're
supposed to do this?
Huh? Are we?
Nah! Of course not,
it'd be embarrassing!
[BOTH laughing]
[SAYA] Not that it would
ever stop Hotaru.
I wonder, why did she up
and leave town so suddenly?
Maybe Coconuts
knows why she left.
It's been a while since
we've hung out like this.
Talkin' about dagashi and stuff.
I know I've been acting weird,
but I also know you've been
trying to cheer me up lately.
Saya.
Thank you.
Uh.
I didn't do anything
that special.
[KOKONOTSU] You've helped
more than you know.
Anyway...
[KOKONOTSU chuckles]
I'm a little embarrassed!
[SAYA]
Ah! I'm so happy right now!
I could literally die
from happiness.
[TO] Hey, guys! Check it!
There's this crazy cat outside.
Oh, you're back!
How was the trash run?
Wait. Why does this
feel awkward?
Huh? It's not!
Yeah! We were just talkin'!
"You wanna get your
groove on, you cods?"
[SAYA] More like "How 'bout
you get a clue, you moron!"?
[TO] Man, this place
looks a lot better!
[SAYA] Yeah! It's back
to its former glory!
[KOKONOTSU]
Mh-hm!
Hold on. I have to
do better than this.
I can't just keep
everything the same.
I need some fresh ideas.
What do customers want?
What's convenient for them?
I have to try and put
myself in their shoes.
Whoa.
Dude, you sound kinda cool.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[chuckles]
It's true!
Dagashi customers are thinking
about more than just snacks
when they're here shopping.
From plastic models,
to stationery supplies.
The thing is, dagashi shops
are like the forerunner
to convenience stores.
Hey, there's an idea!
We don't have any convenience
stores around here!
If I can just
capitalize on that...
[SAYA]
Um, Coconuts?
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
So, uh, about that...
[KOKONOTSU]
What?
What?!
There's a new
convenience store?!
♪
[SAYA]
Next time:
"Convenience Store,
Job Magazine, and..."
Oh, no! This could be bad
for your dagashi shop!