[KOKONOTSU] Whoa, we really
have a convenience store now?
Aw, man. This blows.
That's for sure.
What do we do, guys?
[KOKONOTSU] Maybe we should
investigate it further?
[TO]
Like go inside it?
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh.
Well, I mean,
we should probably at least
make sure it's not a fake.
Wait, what? It's not
made out of cardboard!
[KOKONOTSU] Whoa. A real
live convenience store.
[SAYA]
Hey, Coconuts?
It kinda seems like
you're enjoying this.
Not to burst your bubble,
but this is bad news.
[TO]
She's right, dude.
Uh. I know! You don't
gotta tell me that!
I get it's a problem,
but it's not just me!
To's got a stupid smirk, too!
Well, what do you expect
out here in the boonies?
A new convenience
store is exciting.
[BENIYUTAKA]
Hey, you kids!
[ALL gasp]
[BENIYUTAKA]
Tell me.
Why are you loitering in
front of the store like that?
You're in the way of
the other customers!
♪
I get it. I bet the automatic
door comes off as scary!
[ALL]
Uhh...
I'll have to show
you then! Come on!
Uh-oh. Weird alert.
Yeah, for real. Who is he?
[BENIYUTAKA] The door opens
and closes on its own,
so be careful when you come in.
[ALL yelp]
Hello there!
[EMPLOYEES]
Wow, it's so shiny.
[SAYA]
For sure.
They've got a crap
ton of manga!
Uh, wait, if you greeted us...
Ha-ha. You've noticed.
My name is Yutaka Beni.
Convenience stores are a
brilliant and perfected part
of our culture.
And I've come all the way out
here to spread that love!
Here at the Kashigahama
Branch, I'm the manager!
It's a pleasure.
What a strange guy.
Agreed.
Anyway, convenience stores
have a versatile stock,
thus making them very popular.
And yet small towns such as this
stick to anachronistic shops.
Like that dagashi shop
across the way.
[ALL gasp]
[BENIYUTAKA] Just as the weak
in nature are eliminated
through natural selection,
a world that does not change
will only head towards death.
Therefore, I must revive it.
I will change this town.
I don't know what we should do.
He's using a lot of
big words and stuff.
He might have a
few loose screws.
Get a clue, idiots! He's gonna
shut down Shikada Dagashi!
Hey, I can't let you
just shut down that shop!
Huh? And why not?
Well, 'cause that's my
family's dagashi shop.
So we'd be ruined.
Oh? I suggest you take a
good, hard look at reality.
Our publications section has a
variety of magazines and manga.
[TO] Coconuts! Check it out man,
they have dirty magazines!
[BENIYUTAKA]
We have daily necessities,
as well as stationary and food.
We also carry tea,
alcohol, juice, and soda.
Not to mention our ready
to eat foods and bento.
We've got a copier, a fax, an
ATM, and friendly staff to boot.
In short, we're it! We have
absolutely everything!
It is impressive.
And dirty magazines!
[SAYA grumbles]
But wait, there's one thing
you haven't seen yet.
Our renowned snack section.
Behold!
These are made with
the finest ingredients
and by the finest pastry chefs!
It's Towns Mart Kashigahama's
specialty section!
I call it the "Special Sweets
Corner. By Yutaka Beni."
[KOKONOTSU, SAYA gasp]
[SAYA]
Wow, awesome! They're so cute!
I know.
Get it, now?
Things like dagashi
shops are nothing more
than old fashioned relics.
Coconuts.
What's wrong? Oh,
are you speechless?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yutaka.
Yes?
These cakes will never sell.
They're too expensive.
[BENIYUTAKA]
Seriously? Too expensive?
It's just that, I really
think most customers
would prefer something
more affordable.
[gasps]
Things that are
simple and cheap.
Maybe like... this.
Dagashi you can get for
around ten yen or so.
What? Dagashi ?
Yeah, this is what both
kids and adults enjoy.
If you carried more
things like this dagashi ,
I'm sure customers
would buy them.
[gasps]
[BENIYUTAKA]
I've been hit with knowledge!
Are you stupid?
What?
Do you want them to
start carrying dagashi ?
Ah! I guess not.
[KOKONOTSU groans]
[BENIYUTAKA It's true.
She's absolutely right.
Yet, he offered that information
without the slightest
hint of fear.
What a virtuous young man!
From now on, I'll face him
with respect as a rival.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh? Why are you crying?
I'm not crying. You're
the ones who are crying!
[SAYA]
And so.
[YO]
A convenience store?
Did you check them out?
I guess.
[YO] I see, men are vulnerable
to those things, so...
Uh, 'kay.
[YO] Listen, don't get
too carried away, okay?
[KOKONOTSU]
Whatever you say, Dad.
They sure do have a big crowd.
Meanwhile, we're over
here struggling.
[KOKONOTSU groans]
I'm home. Not that
there's anyone to gree--
[BENIYUTAKA]
You're late, dagashi shop boy!
What the--? How'd
you get in here?
[BENIYUTAKA]
Excuse me?
Shouldn't you be welcoming
your potential customer?
What?! I'm sorry?
[BENIYUTAKA]
To be honest,
I'm here because I have
business with you.
Okay, go ahead.
I'll cut right to the chase.
Kokonotsu! I want
you to work for us!
For real?
[BENIYUTAKA]
Mh-hm.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
I am very serious.
See, I love convenience stores.
Okay?
I love the relief you
feel when you stop at one
in the dead of night.
I love the scary sound
the bug zappers make
when they've just
electrocuted an insect.
I even love the ashtrays the
construction workers use
for their smoke breaks.
I also love--
Hold on, why are you only
mentioning the creepy parts?
That's because I love
all of it, Kokonotsu!
Now I will ask you one
more time: Join our team!
Look, man, I appreciate it,
but to be honest with you,
I've gotta focus on running
my family's dagashi shop.
The pay is 850 yen.
[chokes] Say what now?
A very generous wage,
wouldn't you agree?
Well, that's not
really the issue.
Oh, not a money man,
huh? Okay, then.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
Perhaps... you're into
the dirty stuff?
Convenience stores carry
a variety of magazines,
but of course, buying them
outright can be rather risky.
Exactly what are you getting at?
[BENIYUTAKA]
If you were to come work for us,
then you can buy these
without anyone seeing you.
[KOKONOTSU]
I could... buy them?
[BENIYUTAKA]
Of course,
that's just one of
the perks of the job.
Go ahead, take them.
But know that once you do,
you've agreed to be a
part of our little team.
Now, make your decision.
[KOKONOTSU]
Man, what should I do?
Hotaru.
The pleasures I'm looking
for aren't in these pages.
What I want, I'm going to
grab with my own two hands.
[BENIYUTAKA]
Hm. I understand.
Then I'll have to
use my last resort.
Wait, that wasn't it?
[BENIYUTAKA]
This is a job magazine
that has our store information.
The whole team made it together
so that anyone who sees it
will want to visit our store.
It makes you want to
work for us, right?
[KOKONOTSU]
Whoa.
They used the world's
most superficial phrase.
[BENIYUTAKA] There was one girl
who was like shy or whatever,
but with time, I'm
sure she'll open up!
[BENIYUTAKA laughs]
[KOKONOTSU]
Actually, I don't blame her.
He's kind of a weird
guy to open up to.
[BENIYUTAKA]
So are you going work for us?
[KOKONOTSU]
No. Heh. Probably not.
♪
[KOKONOTSU]
Next time:
"Hajime Owari,
Chocoball, and..."
Was hiring her
the right decision?