[KOKONOTSU grunts]
[KOKONOTSU sighs]
This looks like crap.
[paper crinkles]
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
Oops. I missed To's call.
[TO]
Hey, man!
How's the manga going?
I bet you're totally stuck.
I'm at the café with Saya.
Why don't you come hang with us?
Or we could go hit up the beach!
You know summer break
means smokin' hot ladies
rockin' out those swimsuits!
[TO giggles]
Either way, call me back!
See ya, Coconuts!
He knows it's Kokonotsu.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
Kokonotsu, we need to talk.
[HOTARU grunts]
[sighs]
So, you wanted to talk, Dad?
[YO]
Hmm... Honestly, it's not bad,
but I think you glorify the
girl character too much.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[YO]
Also, right here,
gotta say I don't entirely
understand the point.
Maybe you should rewrite it
so that it will make
sense to your readers.
What the hell, Dad?!
I didn't give you permission
to read my manga,
much less criticize it!
Excuse me?! You're supposed
to be my successor
and become the ninth owner of
our sacred family business!
Focus on that instead
of some 2-D world!
It's time to grow up!
I'll choose my own job!
I'm going to make manga, okay?
And stop trying to sound cool
by calling me a "successor"!
It's not some kingdom,
it's a small candy store!
[sobs]
[KOKONOTSU]
Crybaby.
[sighs]
I hate to break it to you, but
you really need a reality check.
[YO]
Why me?
[KOKONOTSU] It's this
thing called marketing.
Maybe you should try
putting the dagashi
in jars on a lower shelf.
As it is, when kids come
in they can't reach them.
Also, don't be afraid
to buy the dagashi
that have popular
characters on them.
I know that they cost more,
but they sell better.
Ya see? You're a
dagashi genius!
You're tossing around great
ideas without even trying!
You must be the chosen hero
to keep Shikada Dagashi going!
[grunting]
No way!
Manga for life, yo!
[YO grunts]
Kokonotsu, this is
it for me, so please.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Watch the store!
--Buh-bye now!
--[gasps]
Hey, no fair!
[sighs]
Hi, are you open?
Yeah!
Come on in.
[gasps]
[HOTARU sighs]
[HOTARU]
Can I ask you something?
Is this place the
Shikada Dagashi?
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
Is it? Spit it out already.
Oh! Yes.
Good. Can I please speak to Yo?
[KOKONOTSU]
He just stepped out.
Uh, so do you, like,
know my dad?
[HOTARU]
Indeed!
He's super famous after all.
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
How rude of me!
I'm Hotaru Shidare.
I'm Kokonotsu Shikada.
Hey, wait.
Your name sounds familiar.
--[KOKONOTSU gasps]
--So you've heard of me?
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh, maybe?
[HOTARU giggles]
[FEMALE VOICE singing]
♪Shidare! Shidare!♪
♪Shidare Chocolate! Yay!♪
♪When it comes to yummy snacks,
Oh, everyone wants Shidare!♪
Yep! It's the famous
snack maker, Shidare Company!
Not to brag or anything,
but it's my dad's business!
And my sacred duty in this life
is to make it the
world's number one
most famous snack manufacturer!
Cool, but please
don't drop our TV.
[HOTARU]
And so...
[HOTARU] It's too bad
that Yo isn't here.
So now what?
Hey, you're his son.
I challenge you!
Come on, we'll have
a snack battle!
Huh?
I need to know for sure,
and this is the only way to see
if you're worthy to be my rival!
Prepare yourself!
Are you the king of dagashi?
[gasps]
Now! This is Umaibou.
Um yeah, I know.
Umaibou is famous.
That's because it has
a variety of flavors!
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
[sighs] I could really go
for a delicious pizza.
But I'm also craving natto.
Truly, this is a
taste bud conundrum!
Whatever shall I do?
Glance.
[KOKONOTSU gasps] Why not
just eat both of those things?
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
Aha, now you get it.
See? There aren't certain
flavors in a single package,
but you can create whatever
tastes you want...
...using Umaibou!
[HOTARU]
So, I'm dying to know.
What kind of food combinations
can you make with it?
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh...
[HOTARU]
In other words,
I'm asking you to
create a new flavor.
Oh, and no pressure,
but you better impress me.
[KOKONOTSU]
She's like some kind of weird
final boss in a food game.
[HOTARU]
And so...
[KOKONOTSU]
How about...
...cheese with
octopus dumplings?
An "octo-cheese" flavor?
Meh, that sounds okay,
but it's still lacking.
[sighs]
[gasps] Alright, so better yet!
We could actually grill them!
Grill them? Grill Umaibou?
[HOTARU chuckles] Maybe, but it
still needs something.
[KOKONOTSU sighs]
Yeah, you're right.
[HOTARU gasps]
Mm...
[KOKONOTSU] Am I allowed to
combine more than two?
[gasps]
By all means, whatever works!
[KOKONOTSU]
'Kay...
What if we tried pizza and onion
salad mixed with corn potage?
Like an Italian mood combo?
Nah, that's dumb.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[whimpers]
Ottimo!
There's a French
party in my mouth!
H-Hey um, don't you
mean Italian party?
[HOTARU sighs]
Well, moving right along.
Consider me impressed.
[KOKONOTSU]
What?
Really? Thanks!
[HOTARU] Yes, I can sense that
you'll rise to greatness.
--As a dagashi shop owner.
--[YO chuckles]
[gasps]
[YO]
Ya see, son?
It's like I've been
saying all along.
[HOTARU]
If that's true, you must be Yo.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[YO]
Hm? Hm.
--[KOKONOTSU gasping]
--[HOTARU] Oo-wah!
[gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
You want some potato fries?
[HOTARU]
Yes, That'd be lovely.
[KOKONOTSU]
What the--? I'm so lost.
[YO] You just can't
beat potato fries!
[HOTARU]
Right?
Even though they're really thin,
they're packed with flavor!
The salt, the artery
clogging grease.
Staples for any foodie!
[YO]
Aw yeah, girl!
You know your stuff!
[HOTARU giggles]
Well, you do, too!
[YO laughs]
[sighs]
[HOTARU]
Oh hey, Kokonotsu.
Huh?
Do you want me to tell
you the most delicious way
to eat potato fries?
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh...
[HOTARU]
Here's what you do.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Careful with those.
[YO]
Hm!
[HOTARU] Eat them all
together in one shot!
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh...
--[gasps]
--[HOTARU] However.
This technique requires caution.
That spicy-spicy chicken
flavor is super-hot.
[YO]
Impressive!
She doesn't just like dagashi,
she's got a passion for it!
Kokonotsu.
I like your new girlfriend.
Girlfriend?!
Shut up, Dad!
Stop assuming things.
She's here for you!
I see.
You're from the Shidare Company.
Then that makes
this a tragedy.
If you two kids were going out,
our family business
would be secured.
Wha--? Don't be ridiculous.
That's crazy!
Can you believe this guy?
Yes, I can.
[gasps]
Unfortunately, I'm already
in love with someone else.
Ah. Of course you are.
Oh? A secret crush?
Tell us, tell us!
I shouldn't.
[YO] Your secret's safe
with us, come on!
[HOTARU]
Okay...
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
Over there.
The guy I love
is in front of me.
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh...
Huh? What does this mean?
[HOTARU]
Yes. I'm in love with... Pocchi!
He's beyond adorable!
Ooh!
I didn't know he was your type!
Who'd have guessed?
He's just so cute!
His widdle sailor
suit is too much!
[HOTARU giggles]
Random topic change.
Didn't you say
you came to see me?
Yes. I did.
The thing is,
my father has a request.
He wants you to join
the Shidare Company.
I came to deliver the
message personally.
Get out, Dad!
I guess you're kinda
famous after all.
Way to go!
One more thing.
I need your answer
as soon as possible.
I refuse!
[gasps]
What?
Okay, I'll tell my father,
but would you mind explaining?
[YO] It's simple. I grew up
here at Shikada Dagashi.
This place is my whole life,
and until my son takes
over as the ninth owner.
I can't yield!
I'll stay strong!
[KOKONOTSU] Stop with the
guilt trip. I said no.
Don't say that, Kokonotsu!
It's so rude when your
dad loves you so much!
Not to mention you've
got the talent
for running a successful shop!
This is a golden opportunity!
I'm not really sure
what the big deal is,
but crying isn't gonna
make me change my mind.
[gasps]
How about this.
If I can convince Kokonotsu
to take over your shop,
then will you agree to
join the Shidare Company?
Okay, sure!
[gasps]
You're gonna see
a lot of me, now!
A deal's a deal!
This'll be fun!
[giggles]
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh, what just happened?
Hey To?
Let me ask you; do you
think my dad is famous?
For real?
You have to be kidding
me right now, Coconuts.
So, you do?
[TO] Honestly, dude?
He stands out, y'know?
Everyone in town knows
who your dad is.
So, it's that kind of famous.
Okay, what's bugging you?
[sighs]
Well we had a
visitor yesterday.
They asked for my dad.
Were they local?
No, I seriously doubt it.
If someone like
that lived here,
I guess they'd be
pretty famous, too.
Uh-huh. Very interesting.
[SAYA]
Kinda' strange, yeah?
Living out in the boonies means
we don't get many tourists.
[TO]
True enough, sis.
Here. For you.
Wow, it smells great, Saya.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Oh. Thank you?
Hey, tell me more
about this visitor.
[KOKONOTSU sighs] Honestly, I
don't even know where to start.
Was it a girl?
[KOKONOTSU grunts]
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah...?
Awesome! Please tell
me she was hot!
[KOKONOTSU]
I guess, maybe?
She's pretty.
[TO]
Really?
Judging from your reaction I'd
say she's more than just pretty.
Uh-oh, Coconuts,
are you crushing on her?
[gasps] What? No, it's not
like that at all!
I just meant that
she's pretty strange.
[KOKONOTSU, TO]
Hm?
[gasps]
Scary!
[KOKONOTSU]
Hmph.
Hey, Saya? Could I have
some more coffee please?
With lots of extra sugar!
[SAYA]
Of course.
[KOKONOTSU]
U-Uh...
--[SAYA] You want extra sugar?
--[TO groans]
Well who am I to judge
if you like sweet things?
I'm only here to
serve you, right?
Just tell me when.
Is this enough for you, yet?
Don't be shy. Speak up!
Why do you need so much sugar?
Does my coffee taste bad?
So you hate my coffee?
Fine, no skin off my back.
[whimpers]
[SAYA]
Hmph. Go on, Coconuts.
Enjoy all your stupid sugar.
[gasps]
[TO screams]
[SAYA gasps]
Delicious!
[SAYA grunts] Didn't know
you liked sugar so much.
Next time just
order sugar cubes.
Don't force yourself.
You don't have to drink my
coffee if you hate it.
[gasps]
What? No!
The sugar just complements
your coffee, is all.
That's why I love it so much.
[KOKONOTSU] Truth is,
I'm not a big coffee fan,
but yours always
tastes really yummy!
Lucky me, without you guys
running this café, I'd miss out.
For sure. Good point.
[stutters, chuckles]
[SAYA] Well, since you like it,
I... can make you coffee.
You know, just, like, when
you're over here and stuff.
Sounds like a plan to me!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU] I should probably
get going now, guys.
[TO]
Okay.
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh, Saya.
Here ya go.
I almost forgot I
had them with me.
I brought them for you.
They're milk coffee
candies from our shop.
The pitch is,
"Even though it's candy,
the coffee flavor will make
you feel like a grown up!"
I realize you're not
really a fan of candy,
but you do like the taste
of coffee, don't you?
I thought maybe
you'd like 'em.
Thanks. I'll let you know.
[KOKONOTSU]
Cool.
Later, guys!
--See ya.
--[door clatters]
[SAYA]
Hmm.
[TO chuckles]
Uh!
What is it?
Oh, nothing. I just can't
believe how ridiculous
you're being right now!
What?
[TO]
Yeah, you and that candy.
What're you even talking about?
Did you know coffee candy
is like super sweet?
Cause it is.
Yeah, I know that.
We ate them together
at his house
back when we were little kids.
But what's your point?
[chuckles] My point is you
hate sweet stuff, Saya!
But not when Coconuts gives
it to you, am I right?
Then, you love it!
So? What does it matter?
It doesn't matter.
That is unless
you're crushing on him!
Shut up! It's not like that!
Oh yeah? Well I say it is.
[TO chuckles]
I think it's hilarious how
Coconuts doesn't see it, too!
But right now, the look on
your face takes the cake!
--[SAYA shouts]
--[TO groans]
Bye. I'm off to do
some grocery shopping.
Look after the café.
Yes, ma'am.
Huh?
[SAYA gasping]
Whoa, holy crap.
[SAYA whimpers]
[HOTARU]
Excuse me, miss.
Are you hurt? Do you need help?
[SAYA] Uh... No, I'm good, but
shouldn't I be asking you that?
I mean, you're the one who
fell into the rice field.
Oh, it's just wonderful!
[SAYA]
What's wonderful?
And so...
[SAYA]
Hey!
There's a towel and a change of
clothes out here for you, okay?
[HOTARU]
Uh. Thanks so much!
[washer beeps]
Let's see.
I'll go hang these
outside to dry.
[TO] ♪Toilet paper, out of♪
♪toilet paper, uh-oh.♪
[gasps]
[TO]
S'that you, Saya?
Are you back already?
[HOTARU sighs]
[gasping]
--[SAYA shouts]
--[TO grunts]
Hey, are you all right?
Did he do something to you?
[HOTARU]
No.
[sighs]
I am so sorry.
My brother is way rude.
Brother? How cool!
You didn't tell me
you had a brother.
[SAYA]
Mm-hm.
It's nice to meet you!
You've got a wonderful sister
and boy did she help me out
by offering up your shower!
I fell into the rice field
and looked inappropriate...
[SAYA] For the record, this is
totally inappropriate, too!
Here ya go, it's on the house.
[HOTARU]
On the house?
Yeah, you're in our café.
[HOTARU]
What?
This is really a café? Awesome!
[HOTARU squeals]
Isn't that sort
of obvious, though?
I've never been in one before!
[HOTARU gasps]
This coffee is amazing!
[SAYA]
Uh-- You think so?
Uh-huh!
[chuckles]
Oh, hey, I was wondering.
What made you fall
into the rice field?
"You." The word "you."
"You"?
[HOTARU]
Yes.
At least I think so.
[HOTARU hums]
[HOTARU]
Hm... Hm?
Hm...
[screams]
[HOTARU]
It's too bad.
That "you" will
forever be a mystery.
No offense, but I'm not
following this story at all.
[HOTARU]
If I could find the stick,
then I'd solve the mystery,
but it's buried in the mud.
[SAYA] Wait, what the
heck are you eating?
Oh, these?
They're called Young Donuts!
Bite-sized and perfect
for snacking,
Young Donuts come four in a bag.
The kids love 'em.
Oh.
These little guys are
the perfect pick me up!
So delicious!
I could seriously eat
these all the time.
They complement your
yummy coffee perfectly!
[SAYA]
Mm!
It's nothing special.
Oh! Um, when your clothes
are dry, I'll take them to you.
I just need your address.
[HOTARU]
Uh.
Listen, Saya.
[SAYA]
Mm-hm!
[HOTARU] There's a
reason why I came here.
I'm actually on a divine quest.
Uh...
[HOTARU]
You see,
I was given orders by a
high-ranking individual.
To journey to this
land and find a legend.
A legend?
[KING] Hotaru the Brave,
thank you for answering my call.
Please, I need you to
seek out the legend.
Oh, yeah!
[HOTARU] I had to overcome
a great many obstacles,
but I found the legend
the king was talking about.
[HOTARU grunts]
[HOTARU] But then, in order to
gain the power of the legend,
I was forced into a
contract with him.
So, the quest began anew to
release the sealed power of
"the Successor who
inherits the legend."
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
My destiny prevents me
from leaving this town.
Not until I fulfill
my obligation.
I must succeed!
No offense, but I'm not
following this story at all.
[HOTARU]
Anyway!
It looks like I'll be staying
here in this town
for a little while.
Let's be friends!
Uh, sure. That sounds good.
[HOTARU giggles] I don't
care what I have to do.
I will gain the divine
power of the legend!
Do you hear me, Successor?
Prepare yourself
for an epic journey!
[KOKONOTSU sneezes]
[KOKONOTSU] Someone must
be talking about me.
[HOTARU]
So it begins!
[SAYA]
Yeah, I guess so!
How about a trivia question?
[HOTARU]
My body is ready!
[SAYA] Tell me the
correct title of this show:
"Daga Shikashi" or
"Dagashi Kashi"?
Which is the answer?
[HOTARU gasps]
The Umaibou was really yummy!
[SAYA]
Uh?
[HOTARU] But I also
loved the potato fries!
[SAYA] That wasn't
part of the question.
[HOTARU]
Oh!
I could have eaten a lot more
of those tasty donuts too!
[SAYA] Forget about the food!
What about the trivia question?
[HOTARU] Are you going to
eat those Milk Coffee Candies
he gave you?
[SAYA]
What?!
Um, maybe. Yeah?