[KOKONOTSU] Hey, Hotaru,
I was just wondering.
Remember when we first met?
Didn't you originally
come to our shop
because you wanted
to recruit my dad?
What? Is that for real?
[KOKONOTSU]
You seem kinda shocked, Saya.
Well, it reminded me
of when I met Hotaru.
"I was given orders by a
high ranking individual."
Or something kinda
weird like that.
"I journeyed to this land in
order to seek out the legend!
I overcame a great
many obstacles."
Yadda yadda yadda.
"And then I had to sign a
contract with a dragon," maybe?
"My destiny prevents me
from leaving this town.
Not until I have fulfilled my
obligation! I must succeed!"
At least I think
that's what you said.
Indeed!
What're you talking
about? What legend?
[SAYA]
Huh?!
So you mean this whole
time you were talking
about Coconuts' dad?!
Sure was!
My mission was to convince Yo
to work for us at Shidare.
But he would only agree to it
if I convinced Kokonotsu to
take over the family store.
I'm surprised you
didn't tell Saya that.
Why the look?
Well, isn't Shidare
supposed to be
like a pretty renowned company?
Of course, duh!
[KOKONOTSU]
Okay, so tell me.
[HOTARU]
Uh?
Why come all the way out to
the sticks to recruit someone?
You don't get it?
[KOKONOTSU]
No.
[HOTARU sighs]
You are so naïve.
[KOKONOTSU]
I am not!
[SAYA]
Geez.
It's not as if we can
read your mind, Hotaru.
[HOTARU sighs]
Would ya stop
with the sighing?!
Fine, I'll have to show you.
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh?
[HOTARU]
Yo's awesomeness, I mean.
And so...
[YO] ♪ The pool was fun
and boobs are yum! ♪
♪ Yummy boobies!
Yummy boobies! ♪
♪ Yummy boobies in my tummy! ♪
[YO]
Hey, I'm back!
Wait, what the heck?
Kokonotsu! Are you in here?
Where'd that kid go?
I thought I asked him to
look after the store for me.
Did he go see his friends?
[YO] Guess it's up to me, then!
Can't leave the shop unattended.
I am a professional after all.
[HOTARU]
With this clever disguise,
we can observe Yo in
his natural habitat!
Yeah! Great idea!
[SAYA]
Um, Coconuts?
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh?
[yelps]
Crap! Sorry!
[SAYA]
It's okay.
[HOTARU]
Stop fidgeting!
Otherwise, Yo might
suspect we're all in here.
♪ Yo, Yo here we go, Yo!
Yo, Yo the more you know... ♪
Hey, is this really
going to prove anything?
I dunno.
[HOTARU gasps]
Something's happening!
[SAYA]
I can't see!
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Hold on,
it looks like maybe he's messing
with some sort of package.
[gasps] It can't be!
Bottle Ramune again?
Man, I told him to stop
eating all of our products.
Ya! This stuff is strong!
Now this is what I call
high quality grade powder!
I really wish he would
stop talking about candy
like it's an illegal substance.
It's ridiculous, right?
Not at all!
Yo's love for Bottle
Ramune shines brilliantly
He's my spirit animal!
I want some
Bottle Ramune too!
Quit it!
Calm down before
you blow our cover!
[KOKONOTSU, SAYA,
HOTARU yelling]
Wow, that hit
the spot! Yummy!
Know what? I think
I'm gonna have one more.
Yeah, whatever. He said
that five packages ago.
[HOTARU]
This Bottle Ramune is precious!
It's all mine! My own!
[SAYA] I'm really concerned
Hotaru's starting to crack.
[KOKONOTSU groans]
This has been such
a waste of time.
He's not even tending the shop.
At this point, we'd be better
off if I just did it myself.
[SAYA] Oh yeah. If Hotaru
succeeds in her mission,
then Mr. Shikada
will agree to work
for the Shidare Company.
When that happens, Coconuts will
take over his family's shop,
which means he'll
totally stay here forever.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
Something wrong, Saya?
[gasps] Uhh, no!
[HOTARU chuckles]
I'm familiar with that face.
It's the face of
Bottle Ramune longing.
[SAYA]
No, not even close.
[KOKONOTSU]
More importantly...
...why are we still hiding
out in this stupid box?
What exactly are
you hoping to see?
We've watched this
candy addict for hours.
And I still don't understand
why you wanna recruit him.
[HOTARU]
Fine, I'll tell you.
Our company wants to
create a dagashi shop
that resembles the
classic snack shop.
Create your own dagashi shop?
Yes.
When the new store is
ready to be opened,
the shop is going to
need a seasoned manager,
and we want Yo.
But what's so special
about my dad any--?
[HOTARU]
Shh! Shut it!
[YO]
Well, if it isn't Ono himself!
Hey there! I came
to buy some gum!
[YO]
Sounds good!
All right, let's go in.
[GIRL] Seriously?
Inside this dinky shop?
Yeah! It's cool, I promise.
If you say so, Ono.
Do you know those kids?
Kind of. Ono lives around here,
but I don't know the girl.
Maybe she's visiting
for summer vacation.
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah.
Hey.
Do they have that Cola Gum you
were talking about or what?
It's a snack store!
I'm sure they do.
Oh yeah, for sure! You
came to the right place!
We have Cola Gum
right over there.
[ONO]
Yay! That's the one!
All of the other
stores were sold out.
[YO] They were? Good
thing you came here!
Aw, how sweet.
He's just trying to buy some
gum for the girl he likes.
Luckily, Cola Gum
is pretty affordable.
Only ten yen per box.
Okay, I'll take two!
[YO]
Twenty yen, please!
[ONO chuckles]
What the--?
Oh no! No!
What's going on?
[ONO]
I only have ten yen.
[GIRL]
Ugh.
Talk about lame.
[ONO gasps]
[GIRL] I can't believe you
dragged me out here.
What? Aw, come on!
Whoa! She's high maintenance!
Huh? What's that?
Oh? Um, it's nothing.
Hey, don't be so down
on yourself, sport.
You know, some pieces
of Cola Gum are winners.
And if your piece
of gum is a winner,
then you get another
one free of charge!
Cool! I forgot about that!
Do you actually think
you're going to win?
You don't stand a chance.
[ONO]
Wait and see!
I'm feeling pretty lucky today!
[yelps]
[ONO]
My luck has forsaken me!
[YO]
Let's see what ya got!
Wow! Look there! A winner!
Huh, for real?!
[YO] You really know how to
pick 'em, don't'cha champ?
You must be special to
win at a time like this!
You get another piece of gum!
[gasps]
[GIRL]
Ono, you're so cool!
You seriously picked
a winning piece?
[ONO]
Yeah, I guess.
[GIRL]
I'm sorry I doubted you.
[ONO]
You are?
[HOTARU] This is why the
world needs these shops.
Everyone deserves
to make memories
in a place like Shikada Dagashi.
Yo doesn't just sell snacks,
he brings people together, he
strengthens their connections.
That's a pretty
admirable quality.
It's not something
just anyone can do,
but it comes naturally for Yo.
Get it?
As a dagashi shop owner, your
father is beyond talented.
But what do you think?
[KOKONOTSU]
Uhh...
Well, to be honest, his business
sense is still pretty terrible,
but I can kinda see what
you're trying to say.
I dunno.
[KOKONOTSU sighs]
Oh yeah. Remember when
we were kids, Coconuts?
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
You were showing me Cola Gum.
It was sort of like today.
Gum?
Yeah, Cola Gum!
And they only cost ten yen each!
[SAYA]
Umm...
You only have enough money
to buy one piece, though.
[KOKONOTSU]
It's okay.
Because if your gum is a winner,
you get another one for free!
[SAYA]
Huh?
Let's see.
I'll pick this one!
Oh, please be a winner!
Please be a winner!
You kids sure are
serious about this gum.
[SAYA]
Wow, I won!
[YO]
Uh?!
[KOKONOTSU]
You're so lucky, Saya!
I almost never get a winner!.
Must be your lucky day.
Yeah! Must be!
So can I get another
piece? Pretty please?
Of course.
Amazing! That's two
winners in a row!
I'll have one more gum, please!
Sure, no problem.
[KOKONOTSU]
You won again!
Whoa, another winner!
Wow, you're really on a roll!
I know, and I'm
having so much fun!
[KOKONOTSU]
Mh-hm.
[SAYA]
Another please!
Come on, another?!
I bet he was just letting me
have winners to be nice,
like he was today with Ono.
Deep down, Mister Shikada
is a big teddy bear.
Yo's such an incredible person.
[KOKONOTSU]
Mmm...
I'm not convinced he was
letting you win, Saya.
What?! After everything
we've seen today,
you're still hating on him?
I'm not! How should I say this?
I know my dad isn't
always a perfect person.
But his heart is
in the right place.
Sometimes I just forget that.
We all make mistakes.
[YO]
Oh? What is this?
And what do we have here?
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Crap!
I can't believe he found
the manga I was working on!
What's up? Something wrong?
No, no, not at all!
Everything's fine!
Everything is just peachy!
Looks like Kokonotsu's manga.
He must've been working
on it up here earlier.
Teehee! I'm totally
gonna read his stuff
before he comes back
from his friends' house.
Uh?
[KOKONOTSU]
Don't you dare!
[YO yelps]
[chuckles] Oh, hey, son! Uh,
were you here this whole time?
--[KOKONOTSU growling]
--[YO laughing]
[KOKONOTSU] I told you...
Don't ever touch my stuff!
[HOTARU]
Where's the train?
I'm kinda bored.
[KOKONOTSU]
Yep.
I guess since one came not
long ago, it'll be a while.
[KOKONOTSU]
Yep.
[HOTARU] Even though we ran,
it still left without us.
[KOKONOTSU]
Yep.
And you're sure we'll
be here for a bit?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yep.
[HOTARU]
We just gonna sit here?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yep.
Okay then.
Guess I'll suck on it.
[KOKONOTSU]
Yep...
[gasps]
Wait a second...
What did you say?
I have to do something
fun until the train comes.
I'm way bored,
so I'll suck it instead.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
"Suck it instead"? Suck what?
[HOTARU]
Hm?
Ah! I see you wanna
suck on something too.
Don't worry, I'll let
you suck my stuff.
[KOKONOTSU]
What? You will?!
Sure, it's only fair!
Yeah, I guess.
[KOKONOTSU] Is this really
okay to do in a public place?
What if we get caught?
[HOTARU]
Ta-da!
We can suck on kombu hamakaze.
For real?
[HOTARU]
What?
That's not exactly
what I had in mind.
Duh, of course it isn't!
Sorry, my mistake!
Whew! What a relief!
I thought you were talking
about something else!
[HOTARU]
Here. Miyako Kombu.
How silly of me.
You're probably more familiar
with this one, am I right?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yep.
[HOTARU]
And so...
[KOKONOTSU]
Damn it all.
When you wanna
suck on something,
Nakano's kombu is the best!
I've heard that Miyako
Kombu is considered
pretty popular as well!
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah, whatever.
Sour!
Bet you didn't know this
about the kombu series,
but the history of it
dates back to 1926.
Whoa. It's that old?
It is.
it started with Mister Nakano
the creator of Miyako Kombu.
He was working as a shop boy
at a wholesale kombu store.
They sold dried foods
and things like that.
[HOTARU]
Instead of eating snacks,
Nakano preferred to eat
the torn pieces of kombu
that the store couldn't
sell individually.
[NAKANO gasps]
Nobody wants to eat
us, we're useless!
Like trash!
Pure garbage!
[NAKANO gasps]
I'll flavor these and sell
them; it'll be delicious!
[KOMBU laughing]
[HOTARU]
After that,
Nakano began to visit places
where children would gather.
He sold them his new snack.
It would later be
named Miyako Kombu.
That's how the kombu we know
and love today was born.
Wow. But then, is it
really a dagashi?
We don't carry it at our store.
If it were a common snack,
then we would
definitely know about it.
[HOTARU chuckles]
Don't go making assumptions.
There's more to the story
that I haven't told you.
[KOKONOTSU]
There's more?
[HOTARU] Nakano wanted
to expand his business,
so he asked himself
where do large groups
of people tend to gather
that would also
want to buy kombu?
Do you know the answer?
Uhh... Where do groups
of people gath--?
[HOTARU]
Sorry, time's up!
No fair!
[HOTARU
The answer is...
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
Right here!
[KOKONOTSU]
Right here?
Oh! Train station gift shops!
Yep! That's right!
[KOKONOTSU]
But wait.
Huh?
[KOKONOTSU] This station doesn't
have a convenience store.
[HOTARU]
Correct again.
[KOKONOTSU]
Okay...
That's not the point I'm making.
It's that Miyako Kombu
is sold at train stations.
You don't usually see
at dagashi stores.
It's small enough
to conveniently fit
in a pocket or a woman's purse.
So kombu sells
better at the station.
Makes sense I guess.
I'm not usually
into sour snacks,
so I don't eat them that much.
But the yummy chewiness
of this kombu
makes it pretty darn addictive.
Ugh. Then again, it also makes
me really friggin' thirsty.
And it's already hot out.
[KOKONOTSU yelps]
You brought Ramune?!
It'd be ridiculous
not to bring Ramune.
We are eating quite the
sour snack after all.
It's just common sense to have
something to take off the edge.
Man. It's not fair.
[HOTARU]
Okay, fine.
Huh?
Here. You can have
a drink of mine.
[KOKONOTSU yelps]
Go on.
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh.
Um, thanks a lot.
[KOKONOTSU] This is totally
like an indirect kiss.
Any day now.
Oh! Uh, yes, of course! Sorry.
Is something wrong with it?
What?! Don't be silly!
Hey, here's a fun
fact about Ramune.
It's actually based on the
lemonade Perry brought
when he visited Uraga!
I bet you didn't know about
that little story, huh, Hotaru?
[HOTARU chuckles]
[HOTARU]
Of course I know about it.
Come on, you can do better.
We both know there's more
to Ramune than just that.
[KOKONOTSU]
What?
Prepare thyself for
Ramune: The Beginning.
Hey, you gonna open up
the country or what?
[OFFICIAL]
Hmm...
Geez, Japanese folks
are so stubborn.
I am seriously tired of waiting.
[OFFICIAL] You're so pushy.
We have our reasons, you know!
Yeah, like whatever.
You've forced me to
use my secret weapon!
[OFFICIAL]
A weapon?!
[OFFICIAL gasps]
What's this? It doesn't
look like a weapon.
It just looks like
water or something.
[PERRY]
Behold my power.
[OFFICIAL yelps]
What on earth was
that loud noise?!
Are we under attack?!
Am I going to die?!
[PERRY]
You won't die.
Promise?
Here. You should totes
drink this. It's amazeballs.
[OFFICIAL]
Drinking it won't kill me?
No, it won't.
Oh... And it really
is delicious? Uh?
Chug it, chug it, chug
it, chug it all down.
[gasps]
So good! What is this drink?!
Lemonade.
Isn't it like, awesome?
[OFFICIAL gasps]
What's that? Ra...
Ramun? Ramune?
No, lemonade. Listen, man.
[OFFICIAL] Listen man?
Listen to what man?
[PERRY] Anyway, I got some stuff
to do, so I'm gonna bounce.
Uh?
[PERRY]
I'll hit you up again next year.
Lemme know when you're ready
to open up the country
or whatevs, okay?
[OFFICIAL] Lucky me!
He left an extra behind!
Oh! What the--? Darn!
Do you twist or--?
I can't open it!
Wait, Perry! How do you open
this bottle?! Come back!
I'll do anything you want
me to, please help me!
[HOTARU]
And that's the story of how
the lemonade Perry
brought became Ramune.
Soon afterwards, Japan would
decide to open the country.
[KOKONOTSU]
Maybe it's just a hunch,
but I have a feeling this story
isn't all that
historically accurate.
Lemonade.
By the way,
you know what the difference
between cider and Ramune is?
The only difference is
that Ramune 's sealed
in a bottle with a marble
and cider is not!
[KOKONOTSU]
What?!
For real?! They're literally
the same thing?!
[HOTARU sighs]
Well, that was quite
the epic backstory.
Now I'm really thirsty!
Hey, Kokonotsu...
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh, yes?
Oh, here!
Why the long face?
[KOKONOTSU]
It's just self-loathing.
[HOTARU]
Geez, where is that train?
We've been waiting forever.
I think it should be
arriving fairly soon.
Good!
I'm really looking forward
to going on this tour
of dagashi shops.
What? Where did
you get that idea?
I'm going into town to get some
more manga drawing supplies.
Oh, I wasn't aware of that.
Are you serious?
But... why'd you agree to come
without knowing the destination?
It just seemed like fun.
Well then, next time let's
tour snack shops together!
You'd like to go tour again?
Meaning you've taken
this trip before?
[HOTARU]
Yep!
Uh... Though now
that I think about it,
it's been a while since
I've sought out the roots
of any dagashi.
I didn't realize
that was a thing.
But it's true you have an
impressive knowledge of snacks.
You're kinda like a master.
[HOTARU]
No.
There's still a lot out
there I need to learn.
It's the only way
I'll ever be able
to build the world's number
one snack manufacturer.
Oh yeah, that's right. Uh?
Something wrong?
[KOKONOTSU]
Well...
...am I the reason you haven't
been able to take those trips?
Is it maybe because
you've been busy
coming to our shop every day?
Gee, I hadn't really
given it much thought.
When I first came to this town,
I wasn't originally planning
on staying for so long.
[HOTARU gasps]
Wait a sec!
Yeah, I'm still here because
you haven't made up your mind
about takin' over
the family shop yet!
[KOKONOTSU]
Sorry, but I do have my reasons!
I'm totally kidding!
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh?
But it is a serious matter.
Which is it?!
[HOTARU chuckles]
This may surprise you,
but I do understand that
you have your own dream
apart from your family's
store, Kokonotsu.
Know this.
I would never force you to
take over Shikada Dagashi.
What? Really?
[HOTARU] I'm looking forward
to seeing which dream
you will choose to pursue
when it's all said and done.
Till that day comes...
[whistle blowing]
...I promise to wait patiently,
so take your time.
Come back! Hotaru!
[KOKONOTSU] Where is she
going to wait for me?
[SAYA] Hey, what do
you think the chances
of getting a winning
piece of gum are?
[HOTARU]
I don't know,
but I guess it would have
to do with a person's luck.
But I never win, which
is completely unfair!
[SAYA]
Yeah.
[HOTARU] Ah! I wonder if
there's a secret technique!
[SAYA]
In picking a winner?
--[HOTARU] Yep!
--[SAYA gasps]
[HOTARU]
Did you get an idea?
[SAYA] Sort of, but it's
really only a way for people
other than you to find a winner.
[HOTARU]
Aw, why not me?
[SAYA]
Well...
...if someone were to pick
after you already tried,
then their chances of winning
would increase, right?
[HOTARU]
Uh! Master Saya! That's so mean!