[KOKONOTSU] I guess we
need some part-time help.
Even if it just while
I'm at school all day.
Still though, it's tough.
[KOKONOTSU]
I wonder if we can really
afford someone right now.
[HAJIME]
Excuse me.
[gasps] Hello?
[gasps]
[HAJIME]
What's up? Are you the manager?
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh? Uh. Wha--?
Please, I'm begging you
to let me work here!
[KOKONOTSU]
Who are you?
♪
[KOKONOTSU]
Let's see... Hajime Owari.
Wait, it says here you
dropped out of college.
[chuckles]
Why'd you up and quit school?
Oh, well, I have my own reasons.
With your skillset,
can't you get a better job?
[chuckles]
[KOKONOTSU] I wasn't expecting
to interview her tonight.
Not that I'm complaining.
But why our shop in particular?
About the previous
job you had listed...
Ah, well I debated
listing it at all.
See, I worked at that
convenience store
until yesterday.
[KOKONOTSU]
Wait, what?
But the convenience store only
opened a short while ago,
and you've already quit there?
Not quite. More like... fired?
[KOKONOTSU]
Fired?
Yeah, they returned my resume.
So that was the end
of that. I guess.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU] Wait, so she just
reused the same resume?
[HAJIME]
Thing is,
I didn't really fit in
with my co-workers.
Awkward.
Didn't fit in?
Wait!
The job magazine.
Right here.
[HAJIME]
Yep.
That's me, all right.
So you're the one he said
was all shy or whatever.
Hey, that's not
entirely my fault!
The manager there gave
everyone nicknames.
Hello!
[EMPLOYEES]
Welcome and hello, sir!
Yes, excellent work!
You're already
functioning as a team!
And teammates use
nicknames with each other!
Mikimoto, you're "Micky"!
Yay!
Motoki, you will be Mokkun!
Yes!
Itagaki, you're Itacchi!
All right!
Hajime Owari.
You'll be... Four-Eyes!
So that became my new nickname.
Are you kidding me?
Why didn't he give you one
closer to your real name
like the other employees?
Plus, "Four-eyes"
is kinda outdated.
Yeah! It's not like my
glasses stand out. Right?
Well, um, maybe a little.
Anyway, that's not
really the point here.
[HAJIME]
Right.
Okay, so you basically got
fired for not fitting in?
Actually, that had
nothing to do with it.
If you must know the truth,
I was late, okay?
That's it?
Hey, it happens.
Oh, it happened all right.
Every single day.
What? That often?
Yeah. See, uh, gettin' up early
is hella hard. Uh. I mean...
Everything's A-okay!
I'll totally be on time!
I promise you!
Please, I really need this job!
[KOKONOTSU]
I get it. Now it makes sense.
This job is literally
her last resort.
Well then, thanks for comin' in.
We'll notify you via
phone of our deci--
[HAJIME]
Hold on, buster!
I can recognize a stupid
brush off when I see one.
Besides, I don't
have a cell phone.
Please! I can't take
being turned down again!
I can't even pay my rent, so I'm
practically a hobo right now!
This crappy minimum wage
job is my last hope!
You calling us crappy?
Look, I have
nowhere else to go.
Oh, by the way,
I never really asked,
but you are the manager, right?
Uh, technically my
dad's the manager.
I'm 15 years old.
[HAJIME]
Fifteen?
[KOKONOTSU]
We run the shop together,
but then he was hospitalized.
Meaning I need someone
to work during the day.
Uh, hey.
So you're saying...
there's a spare room?
And it's unused?
Uh...
[HAJIME] Please let me live
here and work in your shop!
[KOKONOTSU yelps]
Look, if I live where I work,
then I could never
be late, right?
[chuckles]
Well, uh, that mostly benefits
you, huh, Miss Owari?
[HAJIME]
Please, call me Hajime!
I barely know you.
Then why don't we do this?
If you let me live here,
that's all I want.
My wages could go towards
rent or whatevs.
What? This isn't like
a trap, is it? Right?
[chuckles]
[KOKONOTSU]
Whoa, you're serious?
[HAJIME]
See ya in the mornin', boss!
And so.
[HAJIME groans]
[KOKONOTSU]
Excuse me.
Uh, Hajime?
Could you like maybe... uh...
I dunno, explain something?
I was just wondering...
why you're sleeping down here?
Jeez, I'm pretty sure I told you
I have a tardiness problem.
But if I slept down here,
I'd at least be on
time for my first day.
Be on time every day.
And don't sleep in the shop.
Right, boss. Uh!
Six o'clock? In the evening?
No, the morning.
[HAJIME]
Eh?
I got up extra early.
That way I can explain things
before I leave for school.
Ah-hah.
Ah, you're a student.
Mh-hm. Memories!
Am I right?
Is that your impression
of an old man?
[HAJIME] Hey, buddy,
you got a girl you like?
[KOKONOTSU grunts]
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh, anyway.
Aw, tell your good
friend, Hajime!
[KOKONOTSU] Let's start
with this shelf over here.
Stock the Umai-bou
and Maken Gumi.
We have more Oyatsu Calpas
and Dice Caramel in the back.
Wow.
Something wrong?
Your instructions make sense,
but there are so many
types of dagashi .
I've only been in a dagashi shop
like twice in my entire life,
and that was as a kid.
What kind of monster are you?
[HAJIME]
Hey, I'm not a monster!
Look, I'm sure there
are people out there
with more experience than me,
but I guarantee you that
I'm not like a rare case!
'Kay.
So does that mean
you haven't eaten
very much dagashi
in your lifetime?
Uh. I guess not.
But I-- I was just kidding!
In fact, I saw one I love!
Here, found it! I used
to buy this all the time!
Kyoro- chan !
Ah, yes, Chocoball!
Like its name suggests, it's a
ball-shaped chocolate snack.
It's one of the biggest
players in dagashi !
A huge selling point is its
variety of flavors,
including caramel, strawberry,
and of course, peanut!
Ah! To think this is the
one that caught your eye.
I'm so impressed!
[HAJIME chuckles]
[HAJIME]
Yay!
Ah. But you know what
I loved most about it?
Better than the snack was
the can of toys you'd get
for sending in a gold ticket
or five silver tickets.
Uh-huh.
You liked the toys
better than the snack?
[HAJIME gasps]
[HAJIME]
Uh...
What am I saying?
A dagashi shop would
want its employees
to be more interested in snacks
than a can of dumb toys.
And yet, I didn't even
stop to consider
my employer's personal
feelings on the matter.
I'm so stupid!
I don't wanna get fired again!
[KOKONOTSU]
Miss Hajime Owari.
Eek! My full name.
Right there with ya!
Look, I've got four
silver tickets!
Oh, my. You scared me!
Wait, four tickets?
That's amazing!
Know what?
I actually found a can
of Chocoball toys
at a thrift shop once.
Like for sale.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[HAJIME] I remember 'cause I
had a job interview that day.
I wanted it so badly,
but it kind of felt like
cheating to buy it.
Did you?
[HAJIME] I debated about it
all day, but never bought it.
And on top of that,
I missed the job interview.
So you didn't get either?
Nah!
Which sucks 'cause I totally
missed out on the can of toys.
[KOKONOTSU]
For real?
Don't you think the job
was more important?
[HAJIME chuckles]
But hey, it all worked
out in the end
because now I get
to work here instead.
So it had a happy ending.
Well, as long as
you're happy, I guess.
Oh, I bet you
didn't know this.
This guy is Kyoro, right?
It looks like a normal cartoon,
but despite the fact
that he's looking sideways,
you can see both his eyes.
Kinda like the flounder fish.
Anyway, in the art world,
this sort of design is
commonly known as cubism.
It's where you combine
things from various angles
into one picture.
It's a technique
started by Picasso.
Isn't that such a fun fact?
[KOKONOTSU snickers]
Well, I bet you
didn't know this.
Their mascot wasn't
always Kyoro- chan .
Check it out.
Originally, it was a
different anime character.
[HAJIME]
Manager.
Huh?
[HAJIME]
The time.
What?
I gotta go! Look after
the shop for me!
Have a good day! See ya later!
[gasps]
[SAYA]
Next time:
"Roll Candy, High Eight
Chocolate, and..."
Who the hell is that
woman, Coconuts?