[YO]
Hotaru.
Thanks for meeting me so late.
[HOTARU] Sure, did you
get the good stuff?
[YO]
Only the best.
[HOTARU]
There's just one way to be sure.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
I told you it
was high quality.
[YO, HOTARU shout]
It's the middle of the night.
This is weird, even for you two.
Oh, Kokonotsu!
Wow, fancy meeting you here!
[KOKONOTSU] Um, is it?
My house, remember?
So what's going on?
Whoa, hold up.
Why the heck are
you hiding your face?
Because! I'm obviously
making a sketchy deal!
Yo, do you even hear yourself?
Sketchy deals aren't
supposed to be obvious!
[YO sighs]
I guess that's true.
I don't suppose I could
convince you to turn
a blind eye to this transaction?
[KOKONOTSU]
Hey! A Bottle Ramune!
I haven't seen one
of these in forever!
Our shop doesn't
carry it, right?
[BOTH gasp]
[KOKONOTSU]
Which is kind of strange,
because I remember selling
them at one point in time.
Yeah, about that.
I've actually been
ordering some, but...
But?
I kinda sort of
accidentally ate it all.
[KOKONOTSU]
All of it?!
Stop, just leave him alone!
Look, this isn't
Yo's fault, okay?
Hotaru don't.
I'm the one who asked
him to get it for me!
Besides, this stuff is legal!
We're totally innocent, dammit!
If you're so innocent,
then why are you shouting?
[HOTARU]
Everything's fine!
I mean, it's not like it's
super addictive or anything!
So, nothing to see here!
[YO groans]
I need my fix!
I'm going through withdrawals!
[KOKONOTSU] Only addicts
go through withdrawals!
Now, now, "addict"
is a strong word.
We're just fans!
Give it a try,
you might like it!
Well...?!
Don't just stand there,
hurry up already!
Go ahead and chug it like
there's no tomorrow!
Fine. Calm down,
and I'll try it.
Chug! Chug! Chug...!
[KOKONOTSU] Please stop,
you're freaking me out.
Alright, here goes nothin'.
[coughing]
The first time is always
the hardest. It gets easier.
[KOKONOTSU coughing] I just got
some powder stuck in my throat.
Don't worry.
Your body will adjust.
Right now you're
still a new user,
but you'll be a pro in no time!
Are you trying to make it sound
like you're a drug addict?
But I have to agree.
Even though I almost
choked to death,
the Ramune powder
was pretty good.
Like, the flavor is
really refreshing, y'know?
Oh, yes! Yes, I do know!
[KOKONOTSU] What a perfect
snack for a hot summer night
like this one.
For sure. Those rumors are lies.
It's in no way
dangerously addicting,
but metaphorically speaking,
you should try not
to consume too much.
[KOKONOTSU] Why did you wait to
say that until after I tried it?
Listen, I really
like this snack,
but you just ruined it for me,
maybe you should fix that.
[YO]
Oh, I know!
Look, this will
make you love it.
You can take out the straw...
[HOTARU chuckles]
[YO]
...and then eat the bottle!
Cool! Two snacks in one!
[YO grunts]
--[HOTARU, KOKONOTSU] Huh?
--[YO whimpers]
The wafer edges are sharp.
I think it cut the
inside of my cheek.
I got an ouchie.
Baby.
[HOTARU giggles]
Sharp edges aside,
good point number two
will really impress you!
Ha! The bunny on the
front is totally adorable!
And he knows it!
But the best part is
there are a ton of ways
to eat Bottle Ramune!
I know all of them!
First, I'll explain
the official method
as confirmed by the company.
You stick the straw into
the bottom of the bottle
and eat it that way.
Next is the standard method,
which you and Yo
were just employing.
It's simple.
I think most people prefer
the standard technique.
Thirdly,
hardcore foodies
puncture the Ramune bottle
and catch the yummy
powder in their mouths!
This way is called,
"Mischievous Boy"!
And finally, for the fourth
snack eating method.
You tear it apart
like an animal!
This is the Manly way!
Well, what do you think?
Do you love it again?
Yeah, I suppose.
I don't think it really
matters much though.
I mean, it's not like we
can actually sell them.
Especially since
Captain Speedo here
likes hoarding it
all for himself.
Eating all of the product
is really bad for business.
[YO gasps]
What should I do?
Well step one,
admit you have a problem.
Okay then.
[YO]
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
I'll fix this.
Once I'm clean you can be
proud of me again, deal?
--[KOKONOTSU] Uh...
--[HOTARU gasps] Wait for me!
You can't do this alone!
[gasps] What are you
two talking about?
Listen kid, You know this
won't be an easy journey.
I know.
Then let's get goin'.
[gasps]
Well, I'm going back to bed.
Weirdos.
[owl hoots]
[YO] Yo. Yo. Here we go, Yo!
Yo, Yo, the more you know, Yo!
You, you, snack review, dude!
You, you, gotta love food!
--Me. Me, what will I eat?
--What time is it?
Man, what is Dad up to now?
[YO] What's up snack lovers
from another mother?
It's that time again!
Today, I'm gonna review
the snack, Baby-Star Ramen.
Let's get ready to crumble!
'Kay! For my tenth video on,
"Dagashi Channel, Yo!"
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
It's the middle of the night.
What's wrong with you?
[YO]
Oh, hey.
[sighs]
Are you serious?
I can't believe you actually
started a video blog.
And it's all about snacks.
Big surprise.
Well, now. Don't knock it.
I'm just trying to make
a little extra money.
I've heard some people can
earn 20 million a year
making videos.
They get roughly around
10,000 views a day,
it's amazing!
[KOKONOTSU]
How many views do you get?
Uh...! Approximately speaking,
like thirteen.
That's pathetic!
No wonder you're so broke!
Aww... I guess you're right.
Do you think you
could watch me record
and tell me what I can
do to improve, maybe?
I'm not an expert, but sure.
[YO]
Yosh!
Okay then, I'll just
set it up real quick.
There, are you ready?
Yep.
Yo. Yo. Here we go, Yo!
Yo. Yo...
[KOKONOTSU]
He made up his own theme song?
[YO]
Behold!
Today's dagashi review is
all about Baby-Star Ramen!
Let's see.
-- Uh...
--[gasps, groans]
Uh, did you guys know this
is a ramen type snack?
And who here doesn't
love ramen, am I right?
[YO]
Hm...
Whoa!
Can you believe this
was invented in 1959?
Of course I already knew that!
The more you know, Yo!
Uh, even though it's
been around for a while,
my shop, Shikada Dagashi
has been around longer!
Back then it was only
called Baby Ramen.
The more you know, Yo!
Next!
I'll give it a try,
snack review dude!
Yep! Tastes awesome!
It's very ramen-like.
The texture is texture-y?
No, wait.
Texture. Is that the right word?
You suck at this!
One, there's no such
thing as texture-y!
And two, there are more
things to talk about!
For example, you could
tell them about how
Baby-Star Ramen was
born from instant ramen!
Yeah!
The company's owner didn't
want to waste the crumbs
that fell off the ramen
while it was drying.
So he flavored it all and
gave them to his employees!
They liked it, and so
Baby-Star Ramen was born!
That's right.
People like stories like that.
Your reviews should include
all kinds of facts.
There's way more to dagashi than
just how it tastes, y'know?
[YO]
Makes sense!
For instance.
You could even talk
about the mascot.
You mean, Bei-chan?
Right?
Actually, there are two mascots.
The boy is called Bei-chan,
and his sister is Bi-chan.
[YO]
Oh yeah!
Their mom is a fashion designer
and their dad is
an author, right?
[KOKONOTSU] Yes, and Bei-chan
goes on lots of adventures!
He wears special costumes
that his mom makes
and gets to travel.
He's had miso ramen
up in Hokkaido,
gyoza senbei crackers
in Utsunomiya,
and ate ramen yaki in Hakata.
Bei-chan has even traveled
to other countries!
It's pretty cool stuff.
Yeah, I knew all that.
So talk about it in your
stupid video, genius!
But I can't!
[whines] The other snack
review videos beat me to it.
Then we'll reveal
our secret weapon.
Something only a few
people know about.
[YO]
What?
[KOKONOTSU]
The meaning behind the star!
The word "star" in its
name expresses a wish!
A wish for the dagashi to
become the brightest star
in the sky of snacks!
Whoa!
[HOTARU]
And so...
[KOKONOTSU] Then we'll
reveal our secret weapon.
Something only a few
people know about.
--[HOTARU chuckles]
--[YO] What?
The meaning behind the star!
The word "star" in its
name expresses a wish!
A wish for the dagashi to
become the brightest star
in the sky of snacks!
Isn't it amazing?
I can't believe it racked up
that many views so fast.
Talk about awesome!
I know, right? His passion
for dagashi burns brighter
than the Baby-Star ramen star!
Is it okay if we watch it again?
For sure! It's so cool!
Then we'll reveal
our secret weapon.
Something only a few
people know about.
The meaning behind the star!
[KOKONOTSU]
I'm going to kill Yo.
[KOKONOTSU groans]
Jeez, I'm seriously
strapped for cash.
I need new drawing stuff,
but I'm too broke.
I'll spot you, man
Huh? For real?
How much you got?
Uh, like twenty.
I should be
lending you money.
Aw... I've watched
the shop a lot lately.
I should ask dad to
pay me or something.
[HOTARU] Well, well, sounds like
you need some dough.
Ha.
[TO gasps]
Oh, it's Hotaru!
Huh?
What's up?
[HOTARU]
Hey, Endo!
Good to see you.
[gasps]
That face.
And those sunglasses.
I can't put my finger on it,
but it reminds me of something.
[KOKONOTSU]
What's the matter?
[gasps]
Oh, it's nothing important.
Back to what I
was saying earlier.
I know an easy way to make
you guys some quick money.
But you'll have to act now if
you want in on my secret method.
[BOTH gasp]
You interested?
Yes, I'm totally interested!
Hold up, To.
Sounds like one of those
suspicious pyramid schemes.
[HOTARU]
Don't be silly!
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
It's legit!
There's nothing remotely
suspicious about this.
[KOKONOTSU] Wow. You literally
just made it more suspicious.
This is my super-secret
money making technique
that I personally developed!
I've never shared it
with anyone before!
Today, you are truly fortunate!
Whoa, who says we even
want you to tell us?
Slow your roll!
I, for one, would love to
hear about your method!
[KOKONOTSU whimpers]
[HOTARU]
Then I'll share it with you.
Yatta Men!
This is my get
rich quick scheme!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[HOTARU] When you eat
some snacks, you can win prizes,
usually other snacks,
like with popsicles.
But with Yatta men you win--
Cold hard cash which
rains down from the sky!
[TO]
Awesome!
Oh yeah!
It doesn't rain from the sky.
It's just a cash voucher.
Huh? What's that?
For example, if your ticket
says you won 20 yen,
you can exchange that voucher
for 20 yen worth of dagashi.
Aw, so no cash?
Man, what a stupid prize.
--[HOTARU] Anyway.
--[BOTH] Hm?
You can turn in your cash
voucher thing for more snacks,
increasing your chances
of winning again.
It's a fool-proof
money making machine!
You lose.
What?! That's not even
remotely fool proof!
And you just lost!
[HOTARU]
True, so true.
I'm a big fat loser.
I don't deserve a cash voucher.
But I can't give
up yet, because...
[KOKONOTSU, TO gasp]
...I have hope!
There's a rumor floating
around the dagashi world
that there's a way to tell
which Yatta-men are winners!
[KOKONOTSU]
Really?
Ah, I get it, so that's what
your money-making technique
is really about!
[HOTARU]
That's a bingo!
[chuckles]
[HOTARU]
Let's see...
[HOTARU gasps]
Here's one!
[HOTARU]
Notice anything?
Like maybe how the lid
is pressed in on it?
[TO]
Hm...
This is one is a winner!
For real?
[HOTARU]
According to the rumors.
Oh.
I don't know,
that's not what I heard.
See, what someone told me was,
If there's space between the
arrow and the corner where it
opens on the lid,
then it's a winner.
[HOTARU]
What?
There's another rumor?
Oh, but it does look like it
presses in pretty easily.
No way!
Ya see what I'm saying?
[gasps]
We have to find out!
We'll test all the rumors
and see which one is true!
Whatever floats your boat.
[register dings]
[HOTARU]
Okay, guys.
Let's do this!
Good luck!
--[TO] Hm...
--[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[KOKONOTSU cheers]
I won a hundred yen!
Alright!
[TO]
Look, I won, too!
20 yen!
[KOKONOTSU]
Congratulations!
--[TO giggles]
--What about you?
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh-oh...
[gasps] Well uh, looks like
you're both lucky.
I'm happy for you. Seriously.
[KOKONOTSU] Yeah, she's
definitely upset that she lost.
Okay, I'll give it
one more shot!
[HOTARU groans]
Oh! Hey, look at this one.
The lid is bent in,
maybe it's a winner.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[HOTARU gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
Don't give up.
The arrow on this Yatta-men
looks a little different.
--[HOTARU grunts]
--[KOKONOTSU gasps]
You lose.
You lose!
You lose! You lose!
[HORATU sobs]
Loser!
Ah! This tastes pretty rad!
It's less salty than
regular ramen, but good!
[chuckles]
I guess there's just
no way to beat you guys.
Oh, didn't know
we were competing.
[HOTARU]
Can I tell you both a secret?
Don't laugh, 'kay?
Sure.
I've never won anything.
Dagashi, or anything
else for that matter.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Nothing?
But then why did you
say all that stuff earlier
about makin' money by
finding winning snacks?
I just wanted to believe.
Believe that I can be lucky too.
Look, Hotaru,
even innocent gambling like
this can be dangerous.
[HOTARU]
I know.
[chuckles]
[HOTARU]
By the way, Kokonotsu.
Let's move on to the next event!
We'll use Sour Grape
to decide your fate!
Lose, and you have to
take over the store!
I just said that
gambling was dangerous!
Also, why do you think
I would make a stupid bet
that would decide my future?
Uh, now then. Endo to be fair,
I think you should be in
the competition, as well.
[TO]
Huh? Sounds cool.
[KOKONOTSU]
Don't ignore me!
[HOTARU]
And so...
[HOTARU] Each package of
"Watch Out for the Sour Grape"
has three pieces of gum.
They look the same, but one
of them is extremely sour.
Oh...!
The sour flavor
was unintentional.
The company accidentally
mixed in the wrong amount
of citric acid.
When their boss tried the gum,
he fainted in agony over
its unexpected sourness.
The company thought
it was hilarious,
so they commercialized it!
A story like that definitely
makes this a dagashi!
Life, like food, is full of
surprises and coincidences,
and sometimes you
gotta roll with it!
Basically, this match is
about picking a piece of gum
at random, and if it's
the sour one, you lose?
Yes, exactly right!
Sounds simple enough, Coconuts.
Um... Huh?
Wha--
Well yeah, about that.
It sounds dumb, but,
this match is actually
pretty important to me.
Because your whole future
hangs in the balance?
Dude, don't even sweat it.
It's the two of against her.
Remember how earlier she said
she's never won
anything in her life?
Yeah, I remember.
But despite that she
seems oddly confident.
I mean, what if she
actually wins, huh?
[HOTARU]
You're right to worry.
I just so happen to have
an ace up my sleeve.
As it turns out,
there's a very easy way
to know which piece of
gum is the sour grape.
[gasping]
Are you okay, Hotaru?
T-The sunglasses!
What, sunglasses?
Oh, on the package.
They changed it
up recently, yeah.
And got rid of the grape
with the sunglasses on it.
[TO]
Mm...
[HOTARU] Oh man, I have
majorly messed up!
There was a grape on the old
package wearing sunglasses.
You could depend
on the sour grape
always being right
beneath that one!
I was so positive that
I couldn't lose this match.
But how could I forget the
company went and changed
its stupid packaging! Now I
have no idea which one is sour!
[TO]
What about you?
[gasps] Oh, sorry,
did you say something?
Just wondering.
What happens if you're the one
who picks the sour grape?
[HOTARU]
Me?
Well, I haven't
thought about it,
but I'll do anything
you want, I guess.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Anything?
Coconuts.
It's obvious that you're
thinking dirty thoughts.
[gasps]
You shut your pervy mouth!
Anyway, let's do this.
Is it okay if I pick first?
Ah! Sure, yeah, go right ahead.
[KOKONOTSU]
Well...
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU]
This one.
Actually, wait!
As it turns out,
Would it be too much to ask
if I could choose first?
Um, no. Be my guest.
[HOTARU grunts]
[HOTARU]
Uh...
Which one?
If only the sunglasses-wearing
grape was here!
[gasps]
So, you gonna pick?
[HOTARU groans]
Yes! Of course.
This one looks good.
[HOTARU] Kokonotsu was going
to pick this piece earlier,
and he's luckier than me,
so it should be fine. I hope.
Alrighty then.
Got mine.
Okay. I guess I get what's left.
Are you guys ready?
Good luck.
--[KOKONOTSU] Yes!
--[TO] Mm-hm!
To the sour grape!
[BOTH]
[KOKONOTSU]
Mm! Oh, thank God!
Mine tastes super sweet!
[TO] Mm-hm! Yeah,
my piece is sweet too!
Guess who got the sour grape?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Check out the look on your face!
I dunno man, that gum looks
pretty sour, if you ask me.
[HOTARU whimpers] Of course I
would lose again, like always.
Behold the taste.
The taste of defeat.
[TO]
Tastes sour, huh?
Really?
Cheer up, Hotaru.
There are worse things in life
than being bad at gambling.
I mean, you're awesome
at so many other things
and you know a lot about food.
That's sweet of you,
but it's just no use.
Bye.
Guess I'll see you guys later.
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh, see ya.
Hey wait.
Didn't she say that if she lost,
she'd do whatever
I asked her to do?
[HOTARU yelps]
[HOTARU]
Fly you fool!
[HOTARU] Wow, Baby-Star
Ramen is pretty famous, huh?
[SAYA]
For sure!
[HOTARU] And, just like Yo said
on his online video channel,
this dagashi was originally
called "Baby ramen!"
[SAYA] Doesn't it also
mean something like,
"small pieces of
ramen for kids"?
[HOTARU] Whoa, how'd you
know that, master?
[SAYA] Oh. Well, Coconuts
seemed so passionate about it,
so I decided to,
uh, look it up.
[HOTARU gasps]
I'm so proud!
We definitely want to spread
the good word about Baby-Star!
[SAYA]
Yeah!
[HOTARU]
And so...
[BOTH] Make sure you
check it out online!