[BOY]
Coconuts! Look, I won!
[KOKONOTSU]
Whoa! Lucky you!
Well, then go ahead and
pick out another popsicle.
[BOY]
Hooray!
[giggles]
[door clatters]
--Hello, Kokonotsu!
--[gasps]
This street rat was
pilfering your popsicles!
Of course.
It's not what you think.
[BOY]
Wow!
♪Which one of you♪
♪will go in my tummy?♪
[HOTARU]
Oh, I see. What a relief!
I was certain that he
was an agent of darkness
sent by a higher power to
spy on Shikada Dagashi.
[KOKONOTSU]
Who'd want to spy on us?
Now that we're safe from spies,
what exactly are you doing here?
I am on a mission!
I made a sacred promise
to your father,
To unlock your true potential
as a dagashi shop owner!
[KOKONOTSU] Crap, I didn't think
she was serious about that!
Man, this sucks.
[HOTARU] Come on now,
this place is amazing!
Why wouldn't you want
to take it over one day?
[KOKONOTSU grunts]
[HOTARU] You guys carry
a bit of everything here,
ranging from donuts
to Ramune treats!
Whether they're an average
customer or a connoisseur,
you've got 'em covered!
It's a foodie's dream!
I'd kill to be in
your shoes, Kokonotsu!
I guess, but I'd like to be
able to do my own thing.
[HOTARU]
Oh wow, look at this!
You even have models!
Oh my God,
it's the car from the Reckless
Driving Cook Two series!
[gasps]
Talk about awesome!
[KOKONOTSU] You're the first
person to get excited over that.
[HOTARU] But honestly, the thing
that really grabs my attention
is the display over here.
"Bou-Kinako Ataru."
[KOKONOTSU]
For real?
What makes it so special?
Bou-Kinako Ataru's so
common it has its own,
if only slightly different,
nickname: Kinako-bou.
Uh...
There's more to it.
Dear Kokonotsu, allow me
to enlighten you.
--[KOKONOTSU] Hm?
--[HOTARU] Okay, pay attention.
The world of dagashi is
one big battlefield.
--[KOKONOTSU yelps]
--[elephant trumpets]
[HOTARU]
It's full of original ideas.
And beyond that are
the advertisements.
A lot of products even have
their own unique mascots.
Companies will do whatever it
takes to make their dagashi
the most appealing treat
in the marketplace.
[HOTARU]
It's about more than snacks.
It's a full on food war!
[HOTARU]
Kinako-bou is the lone wolf.
He doesn't need fancy packaging.
He must rely on his own power
while the battle rages on.
For he is the desert warrior,
the truest of the true!
Even now, Kinako-bou is
patiently waiting.
waiting for the fateful day
he'll get his powdery revenge.
When we least expect it,
he'll strike us down.
[gasps]
Why us? We didn't do anything!
[HOTARU] Okay, so now
you know the history,
next up is actually eating it.
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh, thank you.
Alas, even this part of the
process isn't so simple.
[KOKONOTSU]
It's not?
It'll be easier if I just
show you what I mean.
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
See there?
That's what I mean!
What a mess,
look at how much Kinako-bou
powder fell on my chest!
Hm? Hello, are you
listening to me?
Um yeah, your shirt
is messy, wow, how awful!
I said to look at my chest!
[KOKONOTSU yelps]
Yep! It is messy!
Okay, I get it.
The problem is the powder
gets all over your clothes!
[HOTARU]
That's not it.
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh... Huh?
The problem is you can't eat
all the powder that falls off.
Gee, what a conundrum.
No matter what you do,
it's gonna fall off.
Might as well accept that fact.
[HOTARU giggles]
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
So you think, but I
have a secret technique
to eating Kinako-bou
without losing any powder.
[HOTARU]
When you take a bite,
the stick shakes, which causes
the crumbs to fall off.
Taking that into account the
solution is very simple!
Behold!
[gasps]
My one-shot kill!
[HOTARU munching]
Just follow my technique and
you won't ever have to worry
about losing precious
Kinako crumbs.
[KOKONOTSU] Your face is
covered in the stuff!
Fine then, Mister Smarty Pants,
how would you eat it?
I assume your
technique is better?
Well, uh. It's nothing special.
What I do is hold it here
in my right hand like this,
then I keep my left
hand underneath it
to catch any of the
crumbs that may fall down.
[gasps] Aha! The old
"God's Left Hand" technique!
Very clever!
Yeah, I doubt anyone
calls it that.
[HOTARU]
You're a worthy rival.
Since you have demonstrated
that you understand the basics,
I'll show you something else.
This is my most powerful method,
so prepare thyself!
Feast your eyes on
the Devil's Swords!
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
Do you see it, Kokonotsu?
This approach allows for
the continuous eating of
Kinako-bou all day long!
But I thought the point
was to eat it without
getting the powder everywhere!
[HOTARU] Oh my God,
the taste is overwhelming!
[HOTARU gasps]
I can't help it. Sorry.
[HOTARU grunts]
[coughing]
Wow, it really did
wait to strike.
[HOTARU]
And so...
[HOTARU squeals]
Good stuff!
Oh man, this Ramune
is just what I needed.
You're a life-saver!
I'll never forget what
you've done for me!
Sure, no problem.
By the way, I haven't
seen your dad. Is he here?
[KOKONOTSU]
Nah.
Yo forced me to
look after the shop
and is out doing who knows
what around town somewhere.
I'm sure he's
probably goofing off
or something stupid like that.
[HOTARU]
Aw, cut him a break.
Huh?
[HOTARU] Adulting is a lot
harder than it looks, y'know?
We're still teenagers,
so we can't fully understand
what they're going through.
That's pretty deep.
[HOTARU]
I've got an idea, Kokonotsu.
Wanna do it with me?
Let's try to be adults.
Just you and me.
Wait, what? Us? Um, right now?
But we can't!
I mean maybe we should take
things one step at a time
and like get to know
each other, right?
[HOTARU]
It'll be fine.
[gasps]
We'll be careful.
There's hardly any risk at all.
Even knowing that,
I could never rush you into
that kinda thing, Hotaru!
[HOTARU]
Check it out!
Huh? Okay, what's that?
It's called "Namaiki Beer".
You dissolve the
tablets in water
and it looks like actual beer.
Pretty cool, huh?
I say we drink it and
pretend like we're adults.
Perhaps then we could
understand them better.
I know it looks
like the real deal,
don't worry,
it's non-alcoholic.
Yeah. Exactly what I
was worried about!
Remember being small?
Your family would get
together for whatever reason.
Everyone would gather
around the table,
the adults would all
drink wine or beer.
But because you were a kid,
you had to drink juice
all by yourself.
Didn't it make you
feel kind of left out?
Not anymore!
Because now you can
join the grown-ups
by drinking some Namaiki Beer!
You sound like a commercial.
[HOTARU]
And so...
Drop it in,
then you just add
some water, like this.
[gasps]
[KOKONOTSU] Whoa, it actually
looks like beer.
[HOTARU]
Of course it does!
Is this your first
time drinking Namaiki?
Uh, yeah.
I've heard of it before,
but we've never carried it here.
I guess there's a first
time for everything.
[HOTARU]
You don't say!
Allow me to show you the ropes!
Uh... Okay.
[HOTARU]
Sweet!
Good to hear!
We can't drink without snacks!
Next, we toast!
Here's to our first
pretend drinking party!
Cheers, friend!
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh, cheers?
Mm! Wow, tastes good!
The flavor is pretty similar to,
like, a soda or fruit juice!
Don't you agree?
--Oh.
--[HOTARU giggles]
Yeah, I agree.
I agree with your face,
Kokonotsuwhatsumacallit.
Hah!
Oh lookie, Umaibou !
[HOTARU] Mm? There's a
big hole in my cup.
Hey Kokoyourface.
--[HOTARU grunts]
--[gasps]
I want another beer, please.
What? For real?
I told you we don't carry
that here, remember?
[sobs] Why are you so mean,
Koko-umai-bou?
I just wanna refill.
Aw, come on now, don't cry!
Wait, what if I find you
something else to drink instead?
I have so many regrets.
Let's see.
Look, Hotaru!
Do you like this flavor?
Geez. Are you fermenting
that beer yourself or what?
The service in this
bar totally sucks!
Hey, why'd you go away?
Come sit down and
let's have a drink!
[sighs]
Aah!
Huh? I didn't say you could
sit there. Talk about rude!
Uh. You literally just
told me to sit here.
Be the shepherd,
not the sheep, baa!
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh...
Contestant number one,
Hotaru Shidare,
will now sing Umaibou!
Umai!
Umai-bou-bou-bou-bou-bou-bou!
You get more for your money,
so you better eat it right!
--[HOTARU yelps]
--[gasps]
Are you okay?
Contestant number two,
Dotaru Shitare will
now go to sleep!
[snores]
Uh, Hotaru?
This is kind of a bad
place to fall asleep.
Come on, get up.
And contestant number C,
Hot-hole.
[sighs]
[KOKONOTSU]
Adulting is super hard.
Hey.
Question for ya.
Oh, yeah? What's up?
Did you start
your homework yet?
Of course not.
Yeah, me either.
I'm not worried about it,
summer break just started.
--We've still got loads of time.
--[whistling]
Hm?
What was that noise?
Do you hear a whistling?
[KOKONOTSU]
I do.
Maybe it's a bird or something?
[HOTARU whistles]
Or not.
Man... Which means.
[SAYA]
Hm? No way!
[HOTARU]
We meet again.
Long time no see.
[giggles]
Dammit, I was right.
[SAYA] Uh-- But we just saw
each other a few days ago.
Huh? Oh, really? I didn't
know you had met Hotaru.
Ah, well, yes.
It's quite the story.
Thank you again for
everything you did for me.
By the way.
Just now.
Did you two happen to
hear a whistling sound?
Like a bird?
[SAYA, KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
Yeah?
Well, I know where
it came from.
Where?
[SAYA]
Uh...
It was me, suckahs!
Oh! That's cool, I guess.
Yep!
And you're simply dying to
know how I made those sounds?
Well, uh...
[chuckles nervously]
Yes. we are?
[HOTARU]
Okay.
Here! With this!
Ah, Ramune candy!
I forgot you can make
sounds with them.
That explains the whistling.
The tasty dagashi that
combines food with fun,
perfect for kids of all ages!
[crunching]
Mm!
Just one of my many favorites.
Huh? There's also a
toy inside, right?
They're usually
totally precious!
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm? Oh, yeah. Who knew?
You can have the toy, Saya,
since you like 'em so much.
[SAYA gasps]
Wow, really? Awesome!
O.M.G. He's adorable!
Don't you agree, Coconuts?
Sure, real cute.
Mole dude.
Right there.
--[HOTARU whistles]
--Huh?
[SAYA]
Huh?
[whistling continues]
She's about to
start something.
Yeah. Probably.
Allow me to spin you the tale
of the whistle snack series.
It began in 1953,
when Fue Gum first went on sale.
The gum was created by
using a mold which produced
a whistle like shape,
very similar to a fue ,
hence its namesake.
It would be twenty long
years before Fue Ramune
would finally
emerge on the scene.
Can you imagine?
Living in a world without
Fue Ramune in it.
He must have had so many
difficulties to surmount.
Fue Ramune just wanted to
be a whistling snack, too.
[KOKONOTSU grunting]
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh... Dammit.
Why?
Why can't I make a sound?
Hey look there!
Check out the
wannabe snack candy.
Yeah, what a soundless loser!
Ha, ha!
What's going on?
[RAMUNE GIRL B,C]
Huh?
Talk about a lame hole.
Ew, it's hideous.
Fill it in already!
[gasps]
Whoa!
Oh no, it's raining!
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
[RAMUNE GIRL C]
Aw, he left.
[HOTARU] Fue Ramune couldn't
tolerate their cruel words
any longer, so he ran away.
He almost gave up hope of ever
learning to whistle, until...
Why?
Why?!
[YO]
Yo.
Huh?
[YO]
What's wrong?
If you stay out here,
you'll catch a cold.
Come with me.
Oh, Fue Gum, it's you!
I see. so you want to
give up on whistling?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yes.
The truth is I've wanted
to be a whistler like you
ever since we met,
but I'm failure.
[KOKONOTSU grunts]
The only noise I can manage
sounds like a squashed,
dying cricket.
It's pathetic.
I have to give up.
[YO]
You're wrong.
[KOKONOTSU]
Uh?
Don't be so hasty
to throw in the towel.
Hold on to hope.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hold on to hope?
[laughs] There are kids
out there waiting for us.
When that day comes,
they'll be so happy.
You have to be strong not
for yourself, but for them.
It's our purpose as candy.
Oh, Fue Gum.
[whistling]
What's this?
That beautiful sound is... you!
[gasps]
Whoa, it is me!
Yay! I did it! Yay! Ha, ha!
[HOTARU]
And that's how Fue Ramune
grew up into a
full-fledged dagashi .
[whistles]
I'm not following this at all.
[KOKONOTSU]
I get it.
Uh-- Wait, seriously?
You're comparing us!
I'm Fue Ramune and my dad
is supposed to be Fue Gum,
am I right, Hotaru?
You're very astute, Kokonotsu.
You think telling me a sappy
story about candy, kids,
and sunshine will make
me change my mind
about taking over the shop?
Well, you're wrong
because I'm not going to!
[chuckles]
Oh, I think you'll be
swayed sooner or later.
No, I'm never taking
over this shop!
Never say never.
Never, never, never, never!
Um, I'm not really
sure what's going on,
but please don't fight you guys.
I don't want to run
the stupid shop!
[gasps]
[HOTARU]
Oh, you will.
[KOKONOTSU]
Stop saying that!
[SAYA] But, if Coconuts
doesn't take over the shop,
will he leave?
[SAYA panting]
[SAYA]
Wait! Coconuts!
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
I think dagashi is
your true calling!
You should totally do it!
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Oh my gosh, Saya!
Do you really mean
what you said?
Well, uh, yeah!
[gasps]
How wonderful!
Want to play together?
Uh...
[SAYA]
Mm-hm!
And so...
Take this! Yah!
Huh?
That was really pathetic.
Come on, you know it's
not as easy as it looks.
Hey, can you teach me the rules
for playing Menko cards?
[gasps]
You don't know?!
That's a crime against humanity!
Well, I doubt it
qualifies as a crime.
Boo, boo, boo, boo--
There aren't really any rules.
You just kind of
fight over the Menko.
Fight over them?
You slam your menko
down on the ground.
If your card makes any of
the other cards flip over,
you keep it.
Then you can use that
card to flip more cards.
You could theoretically
start with one card
and end up building
a huge collection,
if you're good enough.
Sounds like it
can be ruthless
if you're not that
great at card throwing.
Well, you don't always
have to play with them.
Some people just collect
them because of the anime
and artwork illustrations
on the front.
It's whatever you wanna do.
[SAYA]
Huh...
[HOTARU]
Well?
Are you ready to
give Menko a try?
Yeah. Let's see...
[SAYA grunts]
Oh?
She's starting with
"Edge Holding".
This method uses
centrifugal force.
Usually you start off
with "Pinch Holding".
[yells]
Yes! Hooray me!
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
[SAYA]
Uh... Or not?
Beginner's luck.
I won't go easy on you!
No! Not "Tuck Holding"!
That's a really cool
throwing pose.
It's more than that and
very difficult to use.
Only experts can use
this advanced move.
[chuckles] And, you're about
to see an expert.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Prepare yourselves.
This is my diagonal
slicer long throw!
[HOTARU]
Two Flipper!
Whoa, No way!
Two cards flipped
at the same time?
How did you do that?!
[HOTARU] Hmph. A technique this
powerful can only be mastered
after at least two
years of training.
[gasps]
For real, two years?
[HOTARU]
But I suppose I could try
and teach you at least
the basics behind it.
[KOKONOTSU]
You'd really do that?
[SAYA]
And so...
[smack]
[KOKONOTSU]
I can't do it.
Man, I suck at this move.
Don't give up just yet.
Honestly, I think
you're really close.
[KOKONOTSU]
Fine.
[HOTARU]
Adjust your wrist a little.
[KOKONOTSU]
'Kay, like this?
[HOTARU]
Yeah, go ahead and throw.
[KOKONOTSU]
All right.
Two flipper!
Or not.
[HOTARU giggles]
Now let's see.
Position the card here, like so.
Then you throw it
down diagonally.
[SAYA grunts]
[SAYA]
Diagonal Slicer!
[BOTH gasp]
Ha, ha. Kidding!
Hm?
[SAYA gasps]
Hey, look guys!
I think I just flipped over
three cards at the same time!
[BOTH gasp]
Is that hard to do?
[HOTARU]
Wow, Saya.
Come on, be honest!
[HOTARU]
Well...
I'll call you master.
Huh?
[HOTARU]
You win, Master Saya!
[SAYA]
Master?
And what? I win?
[HOTARU] Please take
me on as your student!
[SAYA]
Huh?
[HOTARU]
Master Saya!
[SAYA]
Question, Hotaru!
When you buy Kinako-bou,
how do you know if you've won?
[HOTARU] Easy, if the tip
of the stick is colored red,
then you're a winner!
[SAYA]
Oh! Way cool!
I wonder if coffee would
go well with Kinako-bou?
[HOTARU] Huh? Are you thinking
of a collaboration between
Café Endo and Shikada Dagashi?
[SAYA]
Uh, no. Not really.
[HOTARU]
There's no time to waste,
we need to see if Kinako goes
well with coffee right way!
[SAYA]
I didn't say that!
But, we could try.
[HOTARU]
Okay!
[BOTH] You guys should
try it together too!