You know what?
Seems my idea was a failure.
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh?
My poor gorgeous cakes
did not manage to sell.
Instead...
They went bad, didn't they?
Indeed. May they rest
well in cake heaven.
[BENIYUTAKA] Behold! I call it
the "Special Sweets Corner"!
[BENIYUTAKA] So I switched
to a made to order system.
Would you believe there's
a demand for that
way out here in the boonies?
Now they're selling fabulously!
That's great.
[BENIYUTAKA]
Customers can order in store,
over the phone, or even
via the Internets!
Thank you for coming!
The "Internets," huh?
[HAJIME]
Let's see.
Hey, welcome back!
[KOKONOTSU]
The Internets. The net?
The net. The net.
The Internets, huh?
[gasps]
That's the answer!
[HAJIME screams]
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh, am I interrupting something?
I was just writing
in my journal.
[KOKONOTSU]
Gotcha.
Anyway, I've got an idea.
We should totally use
Internet shopping, too!
[HAJIME]
Uh.
Okay, is there like
a manga you want?
♪
[HAJIME]
I get it.
So what you're saying is that
you wanna sell dagashi and
stuff on the Internet as well.
Now that I think about it,
a lot of companies
are online these days.
I know! We should be, too.
So we need to make a
website for our shop.
I agree. I'm way ahead of you.
First draft. Boom.
Huh? Whoa!
Already? You're like
an Internet wizard!
It's this thing called
Hypertext Markup Language.
I learned it in college.
Ah, the famous HTML
coding language.
The home page is still kinda
bare, but check this out.
[KOKONOTSU]
Cool!
Love the sparkling effect,
it follows the
cursor everywhere!
How did you pull that off?
[HAJIME]
Good question!
It's a little code
called Java Script!
Ah, the famous Java
Script coding language!
This is amazing, you can do
anything with a computer!
[HAJIME]
Welcome to technology!
We should probably add
some more information.
For example, I dunno, your
selling point or something.
'Kay, that should
be easy enough.
Let's see.
[gasps]
"We sell dagashi ."
Yes, we do.
[BOTH laughing]
That's just ridiculous!
For real! And the text is just
scrolling forever and ever!
[BOTH laughing]
Hold on a sec, I can fix it.
Great job! It's much better!
I know, right?
I mean, it's not like
it's super obvious
that we're selling
dagashi in this store!
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah, it's not like
it's in the name
Shikada Dagashi!
[BOTH laughing]
Wow. I'm actually having
a lot of fun with this.
Me, too!
[gasps]
Oh, yeah.
Perfect, hold that pose.
Right, say cheese.
Now we import the picture
and put it at the
top of the page.
[BOTH laughing]
This is so stupid!
C'mon, it's so funny!
Watch what happens
when I do this.
[BOTH laugh]
[KOKONOTSU]
It's an army of me!
[HAJIME]
Okay, okay, me next!
It's only fair after all.
I'll do this so I don't have
make a black censor bar.
Oh, we can also say that
we deliver dagashi .
What else should we add here?
How 'bout the nostalgic
feeling our shop has?
Maybe that would be
a good angle to push.
[HAJIME] Yeah, a reminder
of a simpler time.
Here goes.
Uh. That works.
Yeah.
[HAJIME] Doesn't seem to
advertise the shop though.
[KOKONOTSU]
Right.
Ah! Hold up, we also sell toys!
I'll add that in!
We've got toys, too.
Let's refresh.
This is what it looks
like all together.
It's a bit much, isn't it?
Maybe a little.
[HAJIME]
You actually mean "a lot," huh?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah.
[HAJIME]
I should start over.
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah.
[HAJIME]
And so.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hey.
Just a heads up that our order
should come in later
this morning.
Oh, yeah? I didn't know
you ordered anything.
[KOKONOTSU]
What?
Because I didn't.
It's the order you said you
would take care of yourself.
Uh, did you forget
to make the order?
No. Come on, don't
be ridiculous.
Uh, I was testing you,
and you passed grasshopper!
[KOKONOTSU]
Thank goodness.
[HAJIME] Okay, have a
great day at school!
I can't believe I forgot! Crap!
I wonder if it's possible
to do a same day delivery.
Ugh! What was it again?
Uh, Super Ball?
Well, it's not like it's
the most popular item here.
The end.
Whoa, cool.
Hi, welcome!
Wait, what the--?
They're out of Super Balls?
[BOY C]
Seriously? How lame can you get?
Uh.
I'm sorry. We're ordering
more today, though.
Yeah?
Well, fat lot of good that
does me right now, huh, lady?
Why did you even bother
to open up the store?
You guys are useless.
[BOY B] No wonder you're
going out of business.
[BOY C]
This place sucks.
[HAJIME] Oh, no, if I don't
do something quick,
they'll stop coming here.
I can't let that happen.
Think, Hajime!
[HAJIME]
Hold it right there, boys!
A huge super ball!
I can get you the most
super-est Super Ball
that has ever dared to super!
[ALL]
Huh?
[BOY A]
What is this?
[HAJIME] Oh, it's salt,
laundry starch, and...
Who cares? We want Super Balls!
That's right!
I know. Try and be patient.
Good things come to those
who wait, young man.
First, you add the salt
to a glass of water.
Then stir it.
Well, at least until
the salt dissolves.
The next step is adding
in the laundry starch.
Okay. Let's start with
Mister Impatient.
What's your favorite color?
Uh, that's not my
name, you stupid!
Well, it is now!
It's blue.
[HAJIME]
A solid choice.
In that case,
I'll use my favorite color,
peacock blue, for yours.
Squeeze a bit of the paint
in to the mixture.
And then stir, stir,
and stir some more!
And voila! One
custom Super Ball!
That's way gross.
[BOY A]
That's not a Super Ball.
Now, now, now.
You have to be patient.
Seriously, girls don't
go for that attitude.
We just have to roll it
around and shape it a bit.
Some water is going to come out,
and when it does, wipe it
off, then keep rolling!
Okay. Ta-dah!
You have your own
special Super Ball!
It's just for me?
Thank you!
[BOY B] Whoa! You're like some
kinda crazy alchemist!
[BOY C]
Hey, I want one, too!
--[BOY B] I've got next!
--[BOY A] Whoa! It's so cool!
Okay! But that's
30 yen for each ball.
[BOY A]
Oops, gotta run!
Well, at least I solved
that conundrum.
What do I do?
I still need to make an order
for more Super Balls.
Or do I?
[HAJIME]
And so,
I spent the rest of the
day making Super Balls.
The only thing
that kept me going
was my determination
to not get in trouble.
I felt a strange sense of
fulfilment while I worked.
I couldn't remember the last
time I'd worked on something
with such a clear
sense of dedication.
It felt good. It felt right.
[HAJIME]
I'm finished!
That batch should last us
for a little while! Yep!
[sighs]
I sure have worked up
quite an appetite though.
Time to get some grub.
[HAJIME gasps]
[HAJIME screams]
[SAYA]
But that's To for you.
[BOTH gasp]
So, uh, what happened?
Um. Hey, welcome back?
[KOKONOTSU]
Don't change the subject.
♪
[HAJIME]
Next time:
"Monjiro Squid, Manga
Manuscript and..."
Tell me the truth, manager!