[SAYA]
Closed early?
Oh, that's right.
The festival's tomorrow.
[BOY]
I love the ring toss!
[GIRL]
I wanna do goldfish scooping!
What? Seriously? It's so stupid!
[GIRL]
Ugh! No it's not!
[BOY]
That game is for babies!
[BOY laughs]
[YO]
All right! Hop on out, kiddo!
[groaning]
Man, my back is killin' me!
You're the one who asked to
ride back there, remember?
Yeah, but... I didn't know
the ride would be so bumpy.
[YO]
Come on.
Help me unload this stuff.
Okay.
I was wonderin'...
Isn't this hot plate
for making monjayaki?
But I think you would know that.
I mean, we make monja every
year, so why bring it up now?
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh.
Uh. Well, I guess I'm
just a little bit curious.
[YO]
About?
[KOKONOTSU] A dagashi shop
setting up a monja stall?
Doesn't that seem weird to you?
Boo!
What's with that goofy face?
It was totally a
legitimate question!
[HOTARU chuckles]
[HOTARU] As always,
you have a lot to learn.
I know that voice!
[HOTARU] Once again,
looks like it's up to me
to give you a lesson.
[KOKONOTSU]
And you're in a tree.
I guess we're all gonna act
like that's perfectly normal.
Monja and snacks are a pair.
Why, they're like
peanut butter and jelly!
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[HOTARU] During the first four
decades of the... Showa Era,
it was common for dagashi shops
in the working
class neighborhoods
to serve monjayaki.
Am I close, yet?
You know; we could just
talk after you get down.
[HOTARU]
Yo, if people ask for it,
can they get monja
at your store?
[YO]
Mh-hm. They sure can.
Hm? Seriously?
Yeah, of course.
But I've never seen any
advertisements for it.
I didn't know that's a thing.
Well, it is a lot of work.
So? That's part of your job!
Uh...
[TAMAI]
Yo!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Hey, who's she?
Well, uh...
She's kind of like an old
acquaintance of my dad's.
Tamai! What brings you from
the okonomiyaki stand?
Me, right?
Shut your hole,
you shameless louse!
Is it true you're selling
monja again this year?
That's the rumor.
What the hell?
That's our thing!
Didn't I tell you last
year to stop selling it?
What's the big deal?
Don't you sell okonomiyaki?
[TAMAI] The big deal is we had
dibs! Stick to candy! Ugh!
[HOTARU]
How odd.
Actually, it's pretty normal.
They're always like
this. Every year.
Oh.
[TAMAI]
Whatever!
I'm serious! No more selling
after this year! Understand?
Yeah, I do, but
sure sucks for you.
Why's that?
You forced me into this.
No more Baby Star Ramen.
[gasps]
[TAMAI]
No.
You wouldn't! That's dirty!
You can't eat monja
without Baby Star on it!
What a cheap trick!
It's not fair!
Yep! Now you see
what I meant earlier.
Dagashi and monja are
like two peas in a pod.
Huh?
You've probably eaten it before.
I've seen them topped with
cheese and tempura bits.
But it's also pretty common
to use dagashi on
top of monjayaki.
[KOKONOTSU]
I see.
[HOTARU] Not only can
you eat dagashi as is,
but you can also
cook with them!
They are truly a gift
from the heavens above!
Thank you for giving
us such bliss!
[KOKONOTSU]
The heavens sure are economical.
[crying]
[gasps]
Come on. You know I'm just
givin' you a hard time.
We're still cool, right?
You jerk. You're impossible.
Let's have another
great festival.
I bet we can sell
more monja than you.
Bring it on!
That's surprising.
They made up fast.
Of course they did. I told
you it's an annual thing.
[YO chuckling]
Huh?
See ya later, Kokonotsu!
We're off to kill some drinks at
the festival eve drinking party.
Do me a favor. Set up
the booth, 'kay?
Good luck there, buddy!
We believe in you!
No fair, you guys!
Get back here!
They freakin' ignored me.
Festival eve party.
What's that all about?
Uh... Ah, yes.
It's the "get sloshed
before the festival" party.
A festival?
Yeah, hence the monja booth.
You didn't know that?
No way.
[gasps]
A real life festival!
Am I dreaming?
Is this really happening?
Yep, it sure is.
I've never been to a
festival before! Oh!
It looks like a lot of fun, huh?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah.
[HOTARU]
I never realized this before,
but your town has quite a
lot of people living in it.
Not exactly.
Most of the people here are
from neighboring towns.
The festival draws in
all kinds of visitors.
[HOTARU]
Huh?
Where's Master Saya?
Uhh, she's being all
girly and getting ready.
Cool.
Now, the more
important question is...
How much money
did you guys bring?
I'm packin' 3,000!
I've got 25 hundred yen.
And I brought 200 yen!
[BOTH]
What? So little?
You can get maybe one thing
with that. Like shaved ice!
Not even.
I think they raised the
price to 250 this year.
[TO]
For real?
Now now, cool your jets, fellas.
Check it, I have a plan.
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh... The die-cutting booth?
[HOTARU]
Yes!
The idea is quite simple.
You choose a design
for die-cutting,
and then try and carve
it as neatly as possible.
If you do well, you
can earn prize money!
The more difficult the design,
the more money you can win!
I'll just choose a hard pattern.
After that, I'll have
more than enough money!
Maybe, but...
How do I say this?
Don't get your hopes up.
Why not?
Well, to be honest,
the owners of those stalls
don't wanna have to pay out
to winners, so they try to
find faults with your design.
Mister! One for me, please!
[POPS]
Sure thing!
Why does she never listen?!
[HOTARU]
And so...
[HOTARU] The most important
part of die-cutting
is to start with breaking
off any unnecessary pieces
around the design.
That leaves you with only
the detailed parts to do.
Then you just use a toothpick
to slowly carve out the rest.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hey, Hotaru?
[HOTARU]
What's on your mind?
Didn't you mention to me earlier
that this was your
first festival?
[HOTARU]
Correct.
So how is it that you know
about die-cutting techniques?
[HOTARU] Die-cutting isn't
just for festivals.
I happen to like it, so I have a
pretty big collection back home.
I used to practice quite a bit.
[KOKONOTSU]
She's full of surprises.
[HOTARU]
However,
I've never had an audience watch
me die cut anything before.
That makes it all
the more thrilling
when you add in distractions.
[TO chuckles]
Then should I interrupt you
with stupid comments?
Don't make it too thrilling.
She's pretty good at this.
[KOKONOTSU]
Mh-hm.
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
I think Saya would also
be great at this, y'know?
Yeah, you're probably
right, Coconuts.
She's pretty good
at games and stuff.
This tastes horrible.
It's about as tasty as
sugar and starch can be.
[TO] "She's super cute
when she's concentrating."
Your face says it all, buddy.
What? My face
didn't say anything!
Stop making crap up!
So defensive! You can't
hide from the truth, though.
Just shut up!
Finished!
Hey, mister!
Wow, done already?
She sure does work fast.
Which design was it?
I dunno, a tulip maybe?
[KOKONOTSU, TO]
Whoa!
Five thousand yen?
[KOKONOTSU, TO] He'll definitely
find something wrong with it!
Well then? How is it?
[POPS]
Hm...
It's amazing!
[KOKONOTSU, TO]
Huh?
There's not one single
thing wrong with it!
[chuckles]
[POPS] No one's ever finished
on me that fast before.
You sure surprised this old man!
Sounds kinda pervy, right?
[KOKONOTSU]
Yeah.
Oh, before I forget!
Let me get you your prize money.
I hope you'll enjoy
the festival, Miss.
I'm sorry, I never
got your name.
I'm Hotaru Shidare.
Of Shidare Company.
Don't forget it, okay?
[POPS]
As if I could.
Yes, as long as I live,
I'll never forget
you, Miss Shidare.
[HOTARU] I'm gonna go
look for Master Saya.
Then we'll eat all the food
our stomachs can hold!
Good luck with that.
She'll never find Saya
in this huge crowd.
You know? What do
you think? Huh? To?
I think I wanna try die-cutting.
[KOKONOTSU]
What?
[TO]
Hey, Pops!
Whoa, hold up a sec!
You don't even
have any practice!
Finally!
Are you done?
I am!
See? I told you I'd
succeed sooner or later!
Yeah, good for you.
Even though you blew
all your money trying.
[chuckles]
All right, man, time
to get my money back!
[TO]
Hey, Pops!
--[thud]
--[TO groans]
[KOKONOTSU]
To!
Are you okay?
[groaning]
[screams]
Listen.
--[TO crying]
--It'll be okay.
If you want, I can
share my money.
[TO]
Coconuts.
Sorry, but I don't
feel like having fun.
Not anymore.
I'm wondering.
What about?
Uh, the usual.
Like why am I stuck working
when I should be out having fun?
Thanks! Visit us again!
Sorry, kid, but the booth
started getting really busy.
[KOKONOTSU groans]
[KOKONOTSU]
This blows!
I didn't think I was gonna have
to work during the festival.
Stop pouting!
Later I'll make some monja
just for you, sound fair?
You food bribing me?
[TO] Mister Shikada!
Thanks for the monja!
No problem!
I'm so freakin' hungry!
Whoa, so good!
This is the best monja I've
ever eaten in my entire life!
You guys are on fire
with this tonight!
I bet you'll sell a
ton of these things!
[YO]
You think so?
Maybe we should
make a bunch then!
Or at least have
Kokonotsu do it!
[TO]
Totally!
[TO, YO laughing]
[YO]
What a sucker!
[SAYA]
Coconuts.
[KOKONOTSU]
Wha--?
Oh! Hey, Saya! Welcome!
Uh...
[YO]
Well, look who it is!
[SAYA]
Uh?
Long time no see,
Mister Shikada!
How are things? Have you guys
had a lot of business today?
Hope so!
[YO] For sure, the festival
keeps us pretty busy.
Oh, whatever!
If by "us" you actually
mean me, you slave driver!
Uh! Wait, does that mean
everyone's already gone home?
Like Hotaru and my brother?
Well, no. In fact,
To's right over there.
[SAYA]
Uh.
Hey, what's up, Saya?
Want a monja sandwich?
They're pretty awesome!
Oh, and check it!
You can get one pro bono!
[KOKONOTSU gasps]
Yeah right.
Free for him maybe, but
I'm workin' my butt off.
So, where's Hotaru?
She's around. I'm sure
she'll swing by later.
Okay. Well, um,
what about you?
Are you really busy?
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh?
[SAYA]
Um...
I mean, uh... never mind!
You're obviously working
pretty hard right now.
Oh, uh... yeah.
Right, of course!
[KOKONOTSU]
What the hell?! That hurt, Yo!
Go on, sport. Why don't
you take a break?
What?
Maybe check out the competition.
Y'know, let me know
how they look and stuff.
Besides, you shouldn't make Saya
walk around the festival alone.
She just got here. Why don't
you chillax with her for a bit?
[KOKONOTSU]
Huh? For real?
[YO]
Sure.
Yay!
You ready? Let's go!
[SAYA]
Oh. Okay!
[chuckles]
Back to work!
Excuse me.
Oh. What's up, To?
Could I maybe help?
Like with the cooking?
Huh? Are you sure?
Yeah. I wanna at least
repay you for the sandwich.
[CUSTOMER A]
Is my order ready?
[YO]
Uh! Comin' right up!
Here ya go, sorry
about the wait.
Thanks and have a great night!
All right, who's next?
[CUSTOMER B]
I'd like five monja sandwiches.
[YO]
Yes ma'am!
Whoa! You're a natural!
You think so?
Sure, you're a big help, kid.
Man, I'm so glad to be free!
It's nice to finally
walk around a bit.
Yeah. I'm glad you could come.
Oh! I should've
invited To along.
No! Forget that loser!
Huh? Why?
[SAYA]
Uh...
Well, he was eating.
And he's happy when
he eats. Why ruin that?
I guess.
Oh, and I noticed you're
wearing a uniform today.
You and your dad totally match!
Yeah, this thing?
Yo was insistant that
I wear it today.
And I had to comb my hair back.
I feel like I look
really dumb, y'know?
Nah, I think it makes
you look kinda cool.
[KOKONOTSU]
Seriously?
[SAYA]
Yep.
Hey, forget about me.
Just look at you, Saya.
You're really
rockin' that yukata.
[KOKONOTSU]
Hm?
Somethin' wrong?
[chuckles nervously]
No everything's perfectly fine!
So rockin'! You charmer you!
I hate to ruin the
moment, but it hurts.
Oh! Sorry about that!
[SAYA] It's been a while, but
I'm glad I wore a yukata today.
[SAYA]
Look, cotton candy!
Hey, you ever notice festivals
always have cotton candy?
Yeah!
Kids sure seem to like it.
Isn't it pretty much
made from pure sugar?
[KOKONOTSU]
Granulated sugar, to be exact.
Cotton candy actually has
a long and unique history.
It originated in Russia
during the Meiji era.
[SAYA] Really? So it's
not a Japanese snack?
[KOKONOTSU]
Nope.
And guess where the first cotton
candy machine was invented?
It came from America.
Oh, wow!
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh.
Look there, speaking of America.
Did you know that candy
apples are also American?
Typically you see them around
Christmas time though.
How crazy. And we eat
them in the summer!
It is all backwards!
[BOTH laughing]
If they were here, I wonder
what an American would think.
Do we look weird for eating
candy apples in the summer?
Yeah, maybe.
Who knows for sure?
[inaudible]
[SAYA] This night is
the best night ever!
Man, those games sure were fun!
Well now, where should
we head to next, Saya?
Any place in particular
you wanna go?
Huh? Uh... Where to?
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh! Goldfish scooping, huh?
Looks fun! I haven't
played in ages. Wanna try?
[SAYA]
Uh...
Heh. What's wrong?
We can do something
else if you want.
[SAYA]
No, I'd like to.
It's just... Remember
when we were kids?
Which time?
[WOMAN A]
Hey there, you two!
You guys wanna play?
Only a hundred yen per try!
Oh well. I don't know.
Right. I feel lucky.
[SAYA]
Huh?
[KOKONOTSU]
I'd like to try please.
[WOMAN A]
Okay!
[SAYA] Listen, I'm not
trying to be mean,
but winning these games
isn't really your forte.
[KOKONOTSU chuckles]
Don't you worry!
In goldfish scooping, there's
a sure fire way to win!
Step one, gently place
the scoop in the water.
Make sure it's at
a 45 degree angle.
Step number two, while
keeping the scoop sideways,
slowly move it while trying
to avoid any water resistance.
Step three, target the
goldfish and attack!
[yells]
That's too bad.
Your scoop broke.
One more please! Thank you!
[WOMAN A]
Heh. Good luck!
[SAYA]
Oh, Coconuts. He hasn't changed.
It's funny,
but he said the same thing
about winning back then, too.
[yells]
Rats, your scoop got torn.
[KOKONOTSU]
Mister, one more please!
[SAYA] He spent all
his money at that booth,
and yet he never won
even one single fish.
But since he tried so hard,
the stall owner gave
him a fish for free.
I don't think I'll
ever forget that day.
[SAYA] And that special goldfish
still lives with us at the café.
[KOKONOTSU]
Look, Saya.
Here! For you.
[KOKONOTSU] I really tried,
but I couldn't catch a fish.
So the lady gave
me one for free.
Wait. You don't
want it? Sorry...
No, yes! I really do want it!
I was just surprised is all.
Oh, you were?
Well, good! You looked like
you wanted one, so ta-dah!
Thanks a lot. I love it!
[HOTARU]
Master Saya!
[SAYA]
Uh...
Kokonotsu!
Quick! Come and see this!
Endo's got mad
monja -making skills!
[TO laughing]
I started making these
in Coconuts' place,
and it turns out I'm
like crazy awesome!
[KOKONOTSU]
Oh...
Shall we go?
[SAYA]
Mh-hm!
[HOTARU] Wanna know my secret
trick on how to eat for free
at a festival?
[SAYA]
Yeah!
[HOTARU]
Well,
all you have to do is go to
the stall with the food ya like
when the festival's almost over,
then you get what's left!
[SAYA]
What? They just give 'em away?
[HOTARU]
Indeed!
They don't wanna carry
it all back home.
[SAYA]
Whoa!
[HOTARU]
So if you're low on cash,
you can just hang around and get
free snacks when it's all done!
[SAYA]
A-ha!
Something tells me
that you actually blew
all the money you won at
the beginning of the festival
on more die-cutting, didn't you?
[HOTARU]
Guilty as charged!
[SAYA]
I knew it!
[giggles]