- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ( laughs )
THIS IS THE VERY FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER BEEN TO A SPA RESORT!
I'VE HEARD THERE ARE
MANY BATHS HERE
OF ALL SORTS OF DIFFERENT
TYPES AND STYLES.
- YEAH!  AND THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE HUGE, LIKE HOT SPRINGS!
- IT ALSO LOOKS LIKE THEY HAVE
A LOT OF OTHER ATTRACTIONS
AROUND THIS PLACE
BESIDES THE BATHS.
- OH MY.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO ALL THIS.
- SO LET'S GO! ( laughs )
- ( both gasp )
- ( chattering )
- ( gasping )
- WOW.
- ( Tina laughs )
THEY HAVE AN ARCADE!
- Aoi: AND A SOUVENIR SHOP.
- Chika: A MOVIE THEATER, TOO!
- Taeko: EVEN A PLAYHOUSE?
- Mayu: HEATED POOLS,
A RESTAURANT DISTRICT,
A BOWLING ALLEY.
- Miyabi: IT SEEMS THEY EVEN
HAVE A BANK HERE.
- BUT THE BATHS COME FIRST!
THE BATHS!
- Kaoru:
WELL, LET'S GET IN THE TUBS.
- Women: YEAH!
- ( gasps, whimpers )
- UH... ( chuckles )
- PAPA!
- ( sighs )
I HAVE TO ADMIT
THESE WIDE OPEN BATHS
FEEL SIMPLY WONDERFUL.
- Tina: YAHOO!
- HUH?
- YAY! ( laughs )
MUCH BETTER.
THIS HAS GOT TO BE PARADISE.
- SOAKING IN A LARGE BATH IS
SUCH A PLEASURABLE EXPERIENCE,
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- WOW!
THERE'S SO MANY
DIFFERENT KINDS OF BATHS.
- ALL RIGHT! SINCE WE'RE HERE,
LET'S MAKE SURE TO TRY
ALL OF THE BATHS!
- Girls: YEAH!
- HERE GOES
THE WATERFALL BATH.
NOW THE JACUZZI.
- ( giggles )
THIS IS A TICKLISH BATH.
- THIS IS THE GOEMAN BATH.
- SOMEHOW THIS JUST FEELS
LIKE WE'RE BEING BOILED ALIVE
IN A BIG POT.
- ( vibrating ) WE'RE IN
THE ELECTRIC BATH NOW.
- ( vibrating )
MY WHOLE BODY'S GOING NUMB HERE.
- THIS IS THE STREAMING BATH.
- HEY, ISN'T THIS BATH
JUST A REGULAR POOL?
EXCEPT IT WINDS A LITTLE.
- Tina: AND NOW
FOR THE JUNGLE BATH!
- TAKE THAT!
- ( laughing )
- AND THAT!  AND THAT!
AND THAT!
- MUST THEY ALWAYS BE SO UNRULY?
MAYU WOULD LIKE TO ENJOY A BATH
IN PEACE AND QUIET FOR ONCE.
- Miyabi: IF YOU PREFER
SOME TRANQUILITY,
THEN WHY DON'T WE GO
TO THE SAUNA?
- ( shower running )
- UH...
- WHEN I TAKE A DEEP BREATH,
MY CHEST STARTS FEELING SO HOT.
- IF YOU PERSPIRE A GOOD DEAL,
THEN YOUR SKIN WILL BECOME
NICE AND SMOOTH TO THE TOUCH.
- Aoi's voice: I'LL DO MY BEST
TO MAKE MY SKIN NICE AND SMOOTH
THEN SHOW KAORU-SAMA.
- Miyabi's voice: I'VE BEEN
EATING TOO MUCH LATELY,
SO I NEED TO LOSE
A LITTLE WEIGHT.
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( all yell,
breathing heavily )
- I THINK THAT WE PERSPIRED A
GOOD DEAL, WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- THOUGHT I WAS GONNA SHRIVEL
UP AND TURN INTO A MUMMY.
- Kaoru: WHERE IS EVERYONE?
- Aoi: I THINK THEY'LL
BE COMING IN A BIT.
KAORU-SAMA?
- HMM?
- HERE, LOOK AT THIS.
MY SKIN HAS BECOME
THIS SMOOTH NOW.
- WOW.  LET ME SEE.
IT SURE HAS.
- ( giggles )
- IT'S SO SMOOTH.
- OH, KAORU-SAMA,
YOU'RE TICKLING ME.
- ( laughs )
IT'S ALL RIGHT, ISN'T IT?
LET ME FEEL THE SMOOTHNESS
A LITTLE LONGER.
- OH.  BUT...
STOP, IT TICKLES.
- ( both laugh )
- ( clears throat )
- ( both gasp )
- KAORU, MS. LANDLORD!
THANKS FOR WAITING, YOU GUYS!
- COME ON, LET'S EAT!
LET'S EAT!
( both chuckle )
- ( beer can hisses )
- ( sighs )
NOTHING BEATS THE TASTE OF A
COLD BEER AFTER A HOT BATH.
- HEY, WAIT.
WHERE'S MS. MIYABI?
- IF YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR MS. MIYABI,
SHE WENT OVER TO THOSE
AUTOMATED MASSAGE CHAIRS
AND HASN'T COME BACK.
- ( humming )
- ( moaning )
( moaning louder )
- HMM.
OUT OF ALL OF US,
IT LOOKS LIKE SHE'S THE ONE
WHO'S ENJOYING THE RESORT
TO ITS FULLEST.
- HEY, GUYS, WE SHOULD
ALL TRY GOING SOME PLACES
OTHER THAN THE BATHS, TOO.
- GOOD IDEA!
THEN AFTER THIS,
EVERYONE GETS
TO GO OFF ON THEIR OWN!
- Girls: YEAH!
- EVERYONE, WE TRULY
THANK YOU ALL
FOR BEING HERE WITH US TODAY.
WE'RE CURRENTLY HAVING
A STAMP RALLY
THAT WILL HELP YOU ENJOY ALL
WE HAVE TO OFFER AT THIS SPA.
WE WILL GIVE
A WONDERFUL PRIZE
TO THE PEOPLE WHO MANAGE
TO COLLECT ALL THE STAMPS.
PLEASE TRY TO PARTICIPATE
IF YOU HAVE THE TIME.
- SHE SAID THERE'S
A WONDERFUL PRIZE!
- LET'S DO IT!
- AH!
THERE REALLY IS
NOTHING TASTIER
THAN A COLD BEER AFTER HOT
BATH, HUH, MS. MIYABI?
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- ( moaning ) OH YES.
- ( clatters )
- ( gasps )
- YES! ( laughs )
- I WON'T LOSE THE NEXT ONE!
- HUH?
- AH!
- ( giggles ) ONE FOR MAYU.
- ( both chuckle )
- MS. LANDLORD!
- HUH?
- OH.  MS. TINA.
- HEY, SINCE WE'VE COME
ALL THIS WAY,
HOW ABOUT YOU AND I
TAKE ONE MORE BATH?
- OH. ACTUALLY, I, UH...
- AW, COME ON, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO!
- MS. TINA, HOLD ON A SECOND.
- DON'T BE A SPOILSPORT!
- GUESS I'M ON MY OWN.
MAYBE I OUGHT TO GO TAKE
ONE MORE BATH, TOO.
I WASN'T ABLE TO ENJOY
MY LAST ONE, AFTER ALL.
THEY HAVE RESERVABLE
OPEN-AIR BATHS HERE?
GREAT.
I'LL TRY THIS ONE.
I JUST SPIN THIS, HUH?
- WHAT IS THIS THING?
- ( both laughing )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE?
- HUH?
- LET'S GO, KIDS.
- OKAY.
- IT'S TIME FOR US
TO START THE STAMP RALLY!
- Natsuki: FIRST UP IS
HOT SPRING PING PONG!
- GOTCHA!  WHOA!  OH.
- Chizuru:
HOT SPRING STEAMED BUNS.
- Girls: YUMMY!
- HOT SPRING CALLIGRAPHY.
BUT SINCE WHEN
DID HOT SPRINGS
HAVE ANYTHING AT ALL
TO DO WITH CALLIGRAPHY?
- THE HOT SPRING EGG EATING
CONTEST WILL BE THE NEXT EVENT.
- ( water trickling )
- ( sighs )
A BATH THAT'S RESERVED
JUST FOR YOU
SURE IS RELAXING.
I THINK I SHOULD'VE JUST
COME HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- Tina: THAT'S FUNNY.
I HEARD IT WAS
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
OH, THERE IT IS!
THAT'S THE PLACE!
- GUESS WE FINALLY FOUND IT,
BUT LOOKING FOR THIS BATH
SURE TOOK A LITTLE WHILE.
- A RESERVABLE OPEN-AIR BATH?
- WELL, LET'S GO ON IN.
- ALL RIGHT.
- ( door opens, closes )
- HMM?  DID--
DID SOMEONE JUST COME IN?
BUT ISN'T THIS SUPPOSED
TO BE A RESERVED BATH?
- Tina: WHOA-HO-HO!
YOU'RE COMING ALONG NICELY!
- MS. TINA, HONESTLY.
- ( gulps )
THOSE VOICES ARE--
- AH!
LOOK, MS. LANDLORD!
( laughs )
- MY!
IT'S LOVELY HERE.
- Kaoru's voice:
I THOUGHT SO.
IT IS AOI-CHAN AND TINA.
- WAHOO!
- Kaoru's voice:
B-B-- WHAT NOW?
THERE'S ONLY ONE EXIT.
- ( sighs )
THIS IS HEAVEN ON EARTH.
OPEN-AIR BATHS ARE
DEFINITELY THE BEST BATHS EVER.
- BEING ABLE TO RESERVE
A BATH AS LARGE AS THIS
IT SOMEHOW MAKES
ME FEEL SELF-INDULGENT.
- Kaoru's voice: THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN GET OUT LIKE THIS.
- MS. LANDLORD,
I'M SORRY.
- HUH?
- ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW,
THE TRUTH IS I HAVE SOMETHING
I WANTED TO SAY TO YOU.
THAT'S WHY
I BROUGHT YOU HERE.
- W-- WHAT DID YOU WISH TO SAY?
- THANKS FOR TAKING CARE OF ME,
EVEN THOUGH I'M A HANDFUL.
I'M HONESTLY GRATEFUL FOR THAT.
- OH.  THAT WAS
A RATHER SUDDEN THING TO SAY.
- WELL, THINGS LIKE THAT HAVE
BEEN ON MY MIND A LOT RECENTLY,
SO I WAS THINKING THAT
I OUGHT TO GIVE YOU
A PROPER THANK YOU, YOU KNOW?
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN I'M GONNA
STOP CAUSING YOU TROUBLE!
( laughing, splashes )
YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
I HAVE TO SAY
THAT I REALLY LOVE THE LIFE
THAT I HAVE RIGHT HERE.
HEY, DO YOU REMEMBER?
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE FIRST DAY
THAT I STAYED OVER AT THE HOUSE.
YOU AND THE MANAGER
SURE WERE SURPRISED,
SEEING SOMEONE LIKE ME POPPING
OUT OF NOWHERE THAT MORNING.
THEN TAE CAME
SOMETIME AFTER THAT,
ASKING FOR A PLACE TO LIVE.
WE STARTED
KEEPING UZUME AROUND AS A PET,
ALL 'CAUSE OF MY SELFISHNESS.
AND CHIKA CAME ALONG, TOO.
I ENJOYED LAUGHING
DAY AFTER DAY WITH EVERYONE.
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D LIVE TO SEE THE DAY
WHEN I'D HAVE SUCH GOOD MEMORIES
ABOUT BEING HERE IN JAPAN.
YOU SEE, I LIVED IN JAPAN
FOR 10 YEARS STRAIGHT
STARTING FROM WHEN I WAS FIVE.
BUT AT FIRST, I WASN'T REALLY
ABLE TO MAKE FRIENDS HERE.
- OH.  BUT YOU'RE SO--
- WELL, I WAS ABLE TO MAKE
QUITE A FEW IN JUNIOR HIGH,
BUT LOOK, IT'S EASY
TO TELL I'M AN AMERICAN--
I'VE GOT THE BLONDE HAIR
AND EVERYTHING.
EVEN GOT BLUE EYES TO BOOT.
THERE'S NO WAY ANYONE
COULD EVER LOOK AT ME
AND THINK I WAS NORMAL.
THAT'S WHY I DECIDED
TO GO TO HIGH SCHOOL
IN AMERICA.
AND WHAT DO YOU THINK HAPPENED
WHEN I DID THAT?
THIS TIME, SINCE I WAS KINDA
JAPANESE ON THE INSIDE,
I WASN'T EVEN ABLE
TO MAKE A SINGLE FRIEND.
( laughs )
ISN'T THAT FUNNY?
BUT NOW--
NOW, DESPITE EVERYTHING,
EVERYONE AT OUR HOUSE JUST
ACCEPTS ME, WARTS AND ALL.
I'M NOT JAPANESE
AND I'M NOT AMERICAN,
BUT YOU ALL ACCEPT ME AS I AM.
THE WAY I FIGURE IT, THAT MAKES
EACH AND EVERY ONE OF YOU
HONEST TO GOODNESS FAMILY TO ME.
AND SO, ONCE AGAIN,
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR LETTING ME
LIVE HERE WITH YOU,
MS. LANDLORD,
FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
- N-- NOT AT ALL.
OH, PLEASE DON'T BOW, MS. TINA.
I REALLY HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
EXTRAORDINARY, AFTER ALL.
- ( giggles )
( laughing )
- ( gasps )
- THAT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
I JUST LOVE ABOUT YOU!
- STOP!  PLEASE DON'T SQUEEZE
MY BREASTS LIKE THAT.
WOULD YOU PLEASE
STOP THAT, MS. TINA?
HONESTLY.
- ( sighs )
- YOU KNOW, YOU'RE SUCH A
NATURALLY NICE PERSON,
MS. LANDLORD.
I REALLY LOVE THAT ABOUT YOU.
THE MANAGER MIGHT BE
A LITTLE STRICT,
BUT I LOVE HER, TOO.
SHE MAY BE CLUMSY,
BUT THAT'S THE TAE I LOVE.
HOW COULD I NOT LOVE
THE ALWAYS PEPPY CHIKA?
THERE'S NO WAY
I COULD LOVE MAYU,
BUT IT'D BE KINDA LONELY
WITHOUT HER AROUND.
AS FOR KAORU...
( sighs )
SAY, MS. LANDLORD,
DO YOU LOVE KAORU?
- WHA...?
- ( grunts )
- NO! WELL, THAT IS-- I--
YOU SEE--
HOW CAN I PUT THIS?  I, UH...
- YOU KNOW,
THIS MIGHT SURPRISE YOU,
BUT THE VERY FIRST TIME
I MET KAORU...
- HEY!
TOP OF THE MORNING!
- HUH?
( flatly )
YEAH, GOOD MORNING.
- ...HE WAS A REALLY
UNTALKATIVE GUY.
ALL YOU GOT WERE HALF-HEARTED
REPLIES WHEN HE DID TALK.
- WHAT?
THAT'S WHAT HE WAS LIKE?
- BUT WHEN I SAW
KAORU LOOKING LIKE THAT,
HE SEEMED LIKE ME, LIKE WHEN I
WASN'T ABLE TO MAKE ANY FRIENDS.
SINCE THEN, I GUESS
I JUST HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO LEAVE HIM ALONE
FOR SOME REASON.
- Kaoru's voice:
TINA.  SO THAT'S HOW IT WAS.
- YOU KNOW HOW HE IS--
KAORU'S A NICE GUY.
HE WORRIES TOO MUCH ABOUT OTHERS
AND NOT ENOUGH ABOUT HIMSELF.
AND THEN, DESPITE THAT,
HE DOESN'T SHOW
HIS TRUE FEELINGS MUCH.
- Kaoru's voice:
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- Aoi: YES, THAT'S TRUE.
- ( gasps, splashes )
- HMM?
MS. TINA, DID YOU HEAR
A STRANGE SOUND A MOMENT AGO?
- NO, I'M PRETTY SURE I DIDN'T.
- HMM.
IS THAT SO?
- YOU KNOW,
LATELY I'VE BEEN WONDERING
WHETHER OR NOT KAORU--
WHETHER OR NOT KAORU
HAS SOMEONE TO SUPPORT HIM
THROUGH IT ALL.
- HUH?
- ANYWAY...
( moans )
WE TALKED ABOUT SOME
PRETTY HEAVY STUFF, DIDN'T WE?
WELL, WE'D BETTER GET OUT NOW.
DON'T WANNA GET OVERHEATED.
- RIGHT.
- ( door opens, closes )
- ( sighs )
- CONGRATULATIONS
ON GETTING TO THE GOAL.
GOOD WORK, EVERYONE.
WELL DONE.
NOW, DID YOU HAVE FUN
PARTICIPATING?
- Girls: YES!
- THEN HERE'S YOUR
HARD-EARNED PRIZE.
THIS IS OUR SPA MASCOT,
"JUST OUT
OF THE BATH SABAO-KUN"!
- YAY!
WE DID IT, GUYS! ( laughs )
- ( laughing drunkenly )
IF THERE'S ANYTHING BETTER THAN
A COLD BEER AFTER A HOT BATH,
I'D LOVE TO KNOW
WHAT IT IS, TINA-SENPAI.
- HEY, TAE.
I'M OVER HERE, JUST SO YOU KNOW.
- WHAT THE...?
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
- THEY ALL WENT TO HIT
THE SOUVENIR SHOP.
- I SEE.
- AH.
- TINA, UM, YOU KNOW--
- HMM?
- WELL, THAT IS,
THANKS A LOT, TINA.
- HMM?
- THANKS FOR WHAT?
- UH, THAT DOESN'T MATTER,
DOES IT?
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN, KAORU?
- ( sighs )
- THAT KINDA CREEPS ME OUT,
YOU KNOW?
- BIG BROTHER,
I WON THIS AT THE RALLY!
- WOW.  WHAT IS IT, ANYWAY?
- ( cellphone ringing )
- EXCUSE ME A SEC, GUYS.
- ( dings )
- HEY THERE.
SORRY TO KEEP EVERYBODY WAITING.
- HUH?
( gasps )
- HMM?
IS SOMETHING WRONG, MAYU-CHAN?
- I-IT'S REALLY NOTHING AT ALL.
- ( cellphone beeps )
- ( Mayu chuckles )
- OH, SORRY, EVERYONE.
DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE
YOU GUYS WAIT.
- WELL, WE'RE ALL HERE NOW,
RIGHT?  SHALL WE GO?
- YES.
- YEAH.
- Aoi: I'M SO GLAD WE WENT
ON THIS LITTLE GETAWAY.
- Mayu's voice:
JUST NOW I'M CERTAIN
I HEARD HER SAY...
"I'LL COME BACK TO THE U.S."
SHE'S RETURNING TO AMERICA.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Tina: SPACE, THE
FINAL FRONTIER.
- HUH?
- THEY'RE BEING FIRED UPON
BY ENEMY BATTLESHIPS.
MY SISTERS, MY SISTERS!
OH, HOW WONDERFUL THEY ARE,
SISTERS UNRELATED BY BLOOD.
- WE'LL FIGHT FOR MY
ELDER BROTHER!
WE'LL FIGHT FOR JUSTICE!
ON EPISODE 11 OF "PLEASE
SISTERS"-- ( grunts )
- Miyabi: ON THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "AI YORI AOSHI: ENISHI,"
"MOONLIGHT."
- Tina: YOU ARE
ON THE FAR SIDE OF THE--
- Miyabi: THAT'S REJECTED!
- ( grunts )
- Chika: BIG BROTHER.
( gasps )