- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- I SUPPOSE THERE IS A NEED
TO CONFIRM THIS AFTER ALL.
PARDON ME.
MS. TINA.
- HUH?
- MAYU?
- YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN
TO BE HIDING ANYTHING FROM US,
BY ANY CHANCE,
NOW WOULD YOU?
- HIDING ANYTHING?
NOT REALLY.
AT LEAST I DON'T THINK SO.
- MAYU-CHAN,
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- WELL, YOU SEE,
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
I OVERHEARD SOMETHING.
IT WAS WHEN WE WERE
AT THE SPA RESORT.
SHE WAS TALKING
WITH SOMEBODY ON HER CELLPHONE
ABOUT RETURNING
BACK HOME TO AMERICA!
- WHAT?  TINA?
IS THAT REALLY TRUE?
- WELL, I--
NO, THAT IS--
- TINA-SENPAI.
- TINA.
- IT'S, UH...
( laughing )
- HUH?  OH.
- SENPAI?
- TINA.
- ( laughing hysterically )
- Taeko and Kaoru: HUH?
OH, MY STOMACH HURTS!
I WAS WONDERING WHAT
YOU WERE TRYING TO GET AT,
BUT ME GOING BACK
TO AMERICA?!
I THINK SOMEONE'S
JUMPING THE GUN A LITTLE.
YOU REALLY THINK YOU KNOW
IT ALL, DON'T YOU, BRAT?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
BACK THEN I'M SURE
I HEARD YOU SAY--
- NUH-UH.
I SURE DID SAY THAT--
THERE'S NO DENYING IT--
BUT WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
A YEAR-END HOMECOMING THING,
NOT A FOREVER DEAL.
- HOMECOMING?
- YOU MUST'VE BEEN BACK HERE
IN JAPAN FOR SO LONG,
YOUR EAR FOR ENGLISH MUST'VE
GONE BAD OR SOMETHING.
- ( exhales sharply )
FIRST OF ALL,
YOUR ACCENT IS SO STRONG,
I CAN BARELY UNDERSTAND YOU.
- THAT'S A SORRY EXCUSE
FOR AN EXCUSE.
( laughing )
- ( growls )
WHY YOU...!
- ( both sigh )
- COME BACK HERE!
- I DON'T WANNA!
- ( sighs ) TINA.
DON'T SCARE US
LIKE THAT.  JEEZ.
- STOP RUNNING AWAY!
- I TOLD YA I DON'T WANNA!
KAORU, LOOK WHAT I GOT!
TADAH!
I BOUGHT MYSELF
A BRAND-NEW DIGITAL CAMERA!
- OH YEAH, YOU'VE BEEN
WANTING ONE FOR A WHILE NOW.
- ( beeping, clicking )
- I CAN TAKE LOTS OF PICTURES
OF EVERYONE WITH THIS.
AND WHEN I GO HOME, I CAN
SHOW 'EM TO MY MOM AND DAD.
- UH, MS. TINA?
- HMM?
I REALLY DON'T MIND HAVING YOU
TAKE A FEW PICTURES OF ME,
BUT THIS OUTFIT IS...
- ( Taeko and Chika laughing )
- ( clears throat )
- ( groans )
- IF WE SHOOT PHOTOS,
WE GOTTA SHOOT
COSPLAY PHOTOS!
- THAT'S JUST WRONG,
REALLY WRONG.
- WELL, IT'S ALL RIGHT WITH ME.
HOORAY!
GO, MS. TINA!
( laughs )
- JUST ONE MINUTE!
WHY AM I THE ONE WHO'S A HIPPO?
- THERE WAS NO HELPING IT.
IT HAPPENED TO BE
THE LAST COSTUME, YOU KNOW?
OKAY, WE'LL BE STARTING
THE PHOTO SHOOT
WITH MS. LANDLORD!
- ( camera clicking )
- ( sighs )
- COME ON, MS. LANDLORD,
SMILE, WILL YA?
- YOU KNOW,
THIS IS
A LITTLE EMBARRASSING.
- ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
GIMME A BIG SMILE!
OKAY, GUYS,
IT'S TIME TO GO ALL-OUT!
- YEAH!
- ( camera clicking )
- OH MAN!
THAT'S A SEXY LOOK
YOU GOT GOING ON THERE,
MS. MANAGER!
FOR THE NEXT ONE, WHY DON'T
YOU POSE LIKE A LEOPARDESS?
- YAY!
- UH, A LEOPARDESS?
UH, LIKE THIS?
- ( cat meows )
- GOOD, GOOD!
NICE LEOPARDESS POSE!
- Kaoru:
WELL, I'M GONNA GO SHOPPING NOW.
- Tina: HEY, WAIT UP, KAORU,
I'LL GO WITH YA.
- ( holiday music playing )
- ( laughing )
- HEY, TINA.
I GUESS IT FIGURES.
DAIKON AND THERE,
LOOKS LIKE
THAT'S ALL OF IT.
TINA, WE CAN GO-- UH?
WHAT THE...?  TINA?
- ( explosions )
- I SAID I'M NOT AN UNDERDOG!
- Tina: TAKE THAT, AND THAT.
AND THAT, AND THAT.
OH.  WHOA.
WHY YOU...!
- ( sighs )
TINA, WE HAVE
TO GET GOING, YOU KNOW.
- YEAH, SURE. JUST A LITTLE
WHILE LONGER, OKAY, KAORU?
( screams )
( whines )
AND I ALMOST HAD
THE STAGE CLEARED, TOO.
KAORU!
THIS WAY!
WE GOT HERE
AT THE PERFECT TIME.
- ( panting )
WHAT'S OVER HERE, TINA?
- YOU'LL SEE.  LOOK.
- AH...
WOW.
- ISN'T THIS A GREAT VIEW?
I WAS THINKING OF TAKING
SOME PICTURES OF IT.
YOU KNOW, THIS VIEW HERE,
I REALLY LOVE IT.
- ( camera clicking )
- THE SUNSETS
FROM HERE LOOK A LOT LIKE--
LIKE THE ONES I USED
TO SEE WHERE I LIVED.
- BACK WHERE
YOU USED TO LIVE?
SO IN KYUSHU.
- HM-MMM.  AMERICA.
BUT YOU KNOW, I DON'T HAVE
ANY GOOD MEMORIES OF THIS PLACE.
- HUH?  WHY IS THAT?
- 'CAUSE WHENEVER
I FELT SAD OR KINDA BLUE,
I'D COME HERE.
- HAS SOMETHING HAPPENED?
- HUH-UH.
IT'S NOT THAT.
I'D JUST LIKE TO HAVE
SOME GOOD THOUGHTS
FOR WHEN I'M STROLLING DOWN
MEMORY LANE.
THAT'S ALL
I WAS THINKING ABOUT.
( giggles )
- I SEE.
THAT'S FINE, I GUESS.
I WAS A LITTLE WORRIED
AFTER THAT OTHER THING
HAPPENED BEFORE.
- THAT OTHER THING?
- THAT TALK ABOUT GOING HOME...
TO AMERICA.
- OH YEAH, THAT THING, HUH?
YOU TOOK IT SERIOUSLY?
- IN YOUR CASE, I CAN'T REALLY
TAKE THESE THINGS LIGHTLY.
YOU DID SOMETHING
LIKE THIS BEFORE, AFTER ALL.
- ( laughing )
AH!
- HUH?
I SEE SOME CARDBOARD!
LET'S GO SLIDE DOWN
THE HILL ON IT TOGETHER!
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS, TINA.
- COME ON, KAORU!
- JEEZ, THERE'S NO HELPING YOU.
- HERE WE GO!
- ( screams )
- ( laughing )
- ( whimpering )
- YEAH!
- Kaoru:
IT'S GETTING CHILLY.
WELL, I THINK
I'LL GO BACK TO MY ROOM NOW.
- KAORU!
- HUH?
- ( sighs ) FORGET IT.
IT'S NOTHING, REALLY.
- TINA.
HONESTLY, DO ME A FAVOR
AND CUT ME A BREAK
ON THIS DISAPPEARING-
OUT-OF-THE BLUE STUFF, WILL YA?
SEE YA.
- ( door closes )
- I'M SORRY, KAORU.
YEAH, HOW IS EVERYONE?
( laughs )
THAT'S GOOD.
WHAT WAS THAT?
MM-HMM, I'M DOING ALL RIGHT.
I TOLD YOU BEFORE--
THE WEATHER'S NOT AS COLD HERE
AS IT IS OVER THERE.
YEAH, I REMEMBER.
THAT'S WHAT I PROMISED YOU GUYS
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
WE AGREED BACK THEN
I COULD ONLY STAY
IN JAPAN FOR COLLEGE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL COME HOME...
TO AMERICA.
( echoing )
( crying )
I CAN'T TELL HIM--
THERE'S NO WAY I CAN--
THAT WE'LL BE APART SOON.
IF I TELL KAORU THAT...
( whimpers )
I CAN'T KEEP
BEING MYSELF ANYMORE.
I LOVE KAORU.
I CAN'T HELP THAT.
THAT'S WHY I HAVE TO SMILE.
I HAVE TO SMILE A LOT...
LAUGH A LOT WITH THEM ALL...
AND MAKE A LOT OF MEMORIES.
AFTER ALL,
I-- I LOVE THEM ALL SO MUCH.
- Chika: TAEKO!
HURRY UP ALREADY!
- ( door closes )
- ( panting )
( yelps, thuds )
( chuckles weakly )
- OH, YOU AREN'T HURT THERE,
ARE YOU, MS. TAEKO?
- UH, UH, NO.
WELL THEN,
WE'LL BE GOING NOW.
- TAKE CARE ON YOUR WAY.
I HOPE THAT YOU'LL
HAVE A GOOD NEW YEAR,
MS. TAEKO, MS. CHIKA.
- Both: THANKS.
HAVE A GOOD NEW YEAR,
EVERYBODY.  SEE YA!
- Tina's voice:
TAE.  CHIKA.
- BY THE WAY, TINA,
WHAT DAY WILL YOU
BE GOING HOME?
- HUH?  OH YEAH, RIGHT.
I WON'T BE AROUND
THAT MUCH LONGER, EITHER.
( chuckles )
HEY, TAE, CHIKA!
WE'LL SEE YOU GUYS LATER!
BYE-BYE!
- Chika: BYE-BYE!  OOH!
- Aoi: OH MY!
- Kaoru: ARE YOU ALL
RIGHT, CHIKA-CHAN?
- ( giggling )
LOOK.  I GOT SOME PICTURES
OF YOU TOO, UZUME.
- ( squeaks )
- ( giggles )
OH.
- ( clock ticking )
- Tina's voice:
TOMORROW'S THE DAY, ISN'T IT?
- HMM?
( sighs )
- MS. LANDLORD.
- WOULD YOU CARE
FOR A LITTLE TEA?
I ALSO TRIED BAKING
A CHEESECAKE FOR THE FIRST TIME.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WILL SUIT
YOUR TASTES OR NOT,
BUT PLEASE TRY SOME
IF YOU'D ALSO LIKE A SNACK.
- THANKS, MS. LANDLORD.
- ( dish clatters )
- YOU'VE CERTAINLY TAKEN A LOT.
- YEAH, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO LOOK AT 'EM, TOO?
- I WOULD.
OF COURSE.
OH.  THIS IS
FROM THE OTHER DAY.
ARE PICTURES LIKE THESE
REALLY APPROPRIATE?
YEAH, SURE THEY ARE.
MY MOM AND DAD'LL BE HAPPY
TO SEE ALL OF 'EM!
AND THERE THERE'S... TADAH!
- WHAT?
MI-- MS. TINA.
WHEN DID YOU TAKE THAT?
- ( laughs evilly )
I HAVE ONES LIKE THIS, TOO!
- OH MY!
- THIS'LL SHOCK MY MOM
AND DAD FOR SURE!
- YOU CAN'T SHOW THEM THESE!
- ( laughs )
WHY NOT?  HUH?
THINK IT'S HARMLESS.
- All:
THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD.
- TINA, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
OR IS IT
THAT YOU'RE NOT HUNGRY?
- HUH?  NO, IT ISN'T
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW,
I WAS THINKING NOW THAT
CHIKA AND TAE ARE GONE,
IT KINDA FEELS ALTOGETHER
TOO QUIET AROUND HERE.
- SOMEHOW
IT FEELS LIKE IMPORTANT MEMBERS
OF OUR FAMILY ARE GONE.
IT DOES SEEM LONELY NOW.
- YEAH.
TAE AND CHIKA ARE IMPORTANT
MEMBERS OF OUR FAMILY,
AREN'T THEY?
IT REALLY IS LONELY NOT
HAVING THEM AROUND HERE.
THAT'S WHY-- THAT'S WHY-- HEE!
- UH...
- ( laughs )
- ( whimpers )
- LET'S DRINK TONIGHT!
WE'LL DRINK THE NIGHT AWAY
AND BE MERRY!
- Kaoru's voice:
SURE, SHE SAID SHE WAS LONELY,
BUT SHE REALLY WANTED
AN EXCUSE JUST TO DRINK.
- ( cackles )
LET'S DRINK!
WOO-HOO!  YEAH!
( grunting )
THERE.
( sighs )
I GUESS
THAT ABOUT DOES IT.
- HONESTLY, DO ME A FAVOR
AND CUT ME A BREAK
ON THIS DISAPPEARING-
OUT-OF-THE BLUE STUFF, WILL YA?
- ( sighs )
( whispers )
KAORU.  YOU AWAKE?
- ( snoring lightly )
- ( door closes )
- YEAH, WHO'D BE AWAKE NOW?
LET'S TALK FOR A LITTLE BIT.
OKAY?  AFTER ALL,
IT'S THE LAST TIME YOU HAVE
TO DEAL WITH MY SELFISHNESS.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY, KAORU.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I CAN'T STAY
IN JAPAN ANYMORE.
I HAVE TO GO
BACK HOME TO AMERICA...
BECAUSE...
I PROMISED
MY MOM AND DAD...
THAT WHEN I FINALLY
GRADUATED FROM COLLEGE,
I'D LEAVE JAPAN
AND GO HOME.
AND AFTER I DO,
I PROBABLY CAN'T...
KAORU.
I WANTED...
TO KNOW MORE--
TO KNOW MORE ABOUT YOU.
I WANTED...
( crying ) TO MAKE MORE
HAPPY MEMORIES WITH YOU,
AND I WANTED--
I WANTED YOU TO KNOW
MORE ABOUT ME, TOO.
BUT-- BUT THE TRUTH IS...
( sobbing )
I DON'T WANNA GO!
I DON'T WANNA GO HOME, KAORU.
I WANNA BE WITH YOU...
NOW, ALWAYS...
AND FOREVER.
BECAUSE IN THE VERY END, KAORU,
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT I--
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT I...
- ( mumbles )
MMM.  AOI-CHAN.
- ( footsteps )
- ( sweeping )
- OH.  MS. TINA?
- MS. LANDLORD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP
SO EARLY IN THE MORNING?
- I'M JUST CLEANING UP.
I ALWAYS SWEEP
THE FRONT GATE AT THIS TIME.
- ARE YOU SAYING YOU WAKE UP
THIS EARLY EVERY DAY,
MS. LANDLORD?
- OH.  MS. TINA,
DOES THIS MEAN
THAT YOU'LL BE RETURNING HOME
TO AMERICA TODAY?
- UH, OH YEAH.
IT'S AN EARLY FLIGHT
AND I DIDN'T WANT
TO WAKE EVERYONE UP
IN THE WEE HOURS OF THE
MORNING JUST TO SEE ME OFF.
- YES, I SUPPOSE NOT.
- OH, MS. LANDLORD,
SORRY ABOUT THIS,
BUT COULD YOU
LOOK AFTER UZUME FOR ME?
I'VE BEEN AWAY A LONG WHILE
AND I NEED TO SPEND SOME QUALITY
TIME WITH MY MOM AND DAD,
SO I MIGHT NOT
BE BACK FOR A WHILE.
- OF COURSE.
THAT'S NO PROBLEM WHATSOEVER.
- THANK GOODNESS.
- ( rattles )
- WELL, GUESS I'M OFF.
- HAVE A GOOD TRIP.
AND A GOOD NEW YEAR.
- YOU TOO, MS. LANDLORD!
BYE-BYE!
- ( laughs )
- BYE-BYE!
- ( gate closes )
- ( squeaking,
scratching )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Aoi: SPRING ARRIVES,
FACES SUMMER,
BECOMES AUTUMN,
AND GOES ON INTO WINTER.
- Miyabi: THAT IS
THE CONTINUING CYCLE OF SEASONS.
Women:
AS TIME MOVES ON,
WE CAN NEVER RETURN
TO THIS MOMENT.
THE PATH
OF A NEW JOURNEY OPENS UP.
NOW LET US GO
AND LET US LOOK FOR THE ETERNAL
FLOWER IN THAT HEART.
- Kaoru:
ON THE FINAL EPISODE
OF "AI YORI AOSHI: ENISHI."
- All: "BONDS."