- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( Taeko screaming )
- TAEKO, WHAT HAPPENED?
- OH!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'M ALL RIGHT.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO CLEAN
THE AREA AROUND THE BATHTUB
AND I GUESS I SLIPPED A LITTLE.
- TAEKO!
YOU REALLY OUGHT
TO KNOW YOURSELF BETTER BY NOW.
- OOH.
( burbling )
( humming )
OH!
- ( grunts ) HUH?
TAEKO-CHAN!
- OH!
( whimpering )
( humming )
OH!  OHH!
OH NO!
- ( doorbell rings )
- ( sighs )
GOOD NIGHT, MISS AOI.
- Aoi: THANK YOU
FOR THE HARD WORK.
GOOD NIGHT.
( laughs )
- ( snoring )
- ( rumbling )
- HUH?  AH.
- ( rumbling continues )
- HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT SOUND?
- ( rumbling )
- HOLD ON A SECOND!
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT IS THAT?
( yawning )
- Taeko: MMM, DELICIOUS!
- YEAH, AOI-CHAN'S BENTO ARE
ALWAYS THE GREATEST,
AREN'T THEY?
TODAY'S BROILED YELLOWTAIL
IS OUT OF THIS WORLD.
- ( yawns )
- WHAT'S UP WITH YOU, TINA?
YOU'VE BEEN YAWNING
PRACTICALLY THE WHOLE DAY.
- MAYBE YOU'RE
NOT SLEEPING ENOUGH.
- MMM. HUH?
I GUESS SO.
IT COULD BE.
- Mayu: I'M CERTAIN SHE JUST
STAYED UP LATE PLAYING GAMES!
- HUH.  I WAS WONDERING
WHEN YOU'D SHOW UP.
AND YOU'RE WRONG. I WASN'T
PLAYING GAMES LAST NIGHT.
- THEN WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY
HAVE BEEN DOING IF NOT THAT?
- UH, WELL, I WAS--
- ( squealing ) SEE?
YOU CAN'T SAY.
WHICH CAN ONLY MEAN
THAT YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
PLAYING GAMES AFTER ALL.
- IF I SAY THAT I WAS SO SCARED
OF THAT CREEPY SOUND LAST NIGHT
THAT I COULDN'T SLEEP A WINK,
I'LL NEVER HEAR THE END OF IT
FROM THAT BRAT.
HEY,
CAN I ASK YOU GUYS SOMETHING?
LAST NIGHT,
DID YOU HEAR ANY WEIRD
NOISES BEFORE GOING TO BED?
- WEIRD NOISES?
HMM, I WAS FAST ASLEEP
AND PRETTY DEAD TO THE WORLD,
SO I DIDN'T NOTICE ANYTHING.
- NEITHER DID I.
- I SEE.
- OH, AND SPEAKING
OF BEING FAST ASLEEP,
I HAVE TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU,
SENPAI.
- HUH?
- I MEAN FOR THIS MORNING.
CHIKA-CHAN CRAWLED INTO YOUR
FUTON AGAIN, DIDN'T SHE?
- WHAT?
- OH, YEAH.
I DON'T REALLY MIND IT ANYMORE.
I'M ACTUALLY KIND OF
USED TO IT BY NOW.
- UH UH--
WELL, HOLD ON.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
HANABISHI-SAMA?
YOU'RE SAYING
THAT YOU SHARE A FUTON WITH HER?
- WELL, CHIKA-CHAN SOMETIMES
CRAWLS INTO MY FUTON
HALF-ASLEEP DURING THE NIGHT.
SO ON SOME MORNINGS
THERE ARE TIMES WHEN I WAKE UP
AND FIND US SLEEPING TOGETHER.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
- WHY THE HECK ARE YOU GETTING
INTO SUCH AN UPROAR ABOUT THIS?
MMM, THIS IS CHIKA
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HERE.
- I'M VERY SORRY,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
- I JUST REMEMBERED SOMETHING
IMPORTANT I MUST ATTEND TO,
SO PLEASE EXCUSE ME.
FAREWELL.
- UH, MAYU-CHAN?
- I NEVER REALIZED THIS BEFORE,
BUT LIVING TOGETHER WITH
HANABISHI-SAMA IN THAT MANSION
AFFORDED
SUCH SPECIAL PRIVILEGES.
OH, WORDS CAN'T DESCRIBE
THE JEALOUSY I FEEL.
I JUST CAN'T LET THIS STAND.
I'LL SEIZE MY OWN OPPORTUNITY
TO SLEEP WITH HANABISHI-SAMA,
NO MATTER WHAT!
- Taeko: AAH!
I-- I'M REALLY SORRY, MA'AM.
OHH!
COME BACK!
( gasping )
OH!
- NEXT TIME, PLEASE,
PERFORM YOUR DUTIES
WITH THE PROPER CARE.
- YES, MA'AM.
I'M VERY SORRY ABOUT TODAY.
GOOD NIGHT.
JEEZ, WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU'RE HORRIBLE.
OH?
UZUME, DID YOU CATCH
ANOTHER BUG?
IF MISS MIYABI SEES THAT--
HUH?
THIS IS A KEY.
UZUME, WHERE DID YOU
FIND THIS THING?
- ( squeals )
- OH.
I WONDER WHAT THIS KEY OPENS.
- ( Tina snoring )
- ( rumbling )
- HUH?
WHAT THE--
OH, I GUESS
IT WAS JUST A DREAM.
MMM.
- ( thudding )
- AAH!
- ( rumbling )
- KAORU!
( crying )
- UH, IS THERE SOMETHING
WRONG, TINA?
- LISTEN, KAORU!
LISTEN TO THAT.
CAN YOU HEAR THE MONSTER?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THERE'S SOME WEIRD NOISES
COMING FROM UPSTAIRS
IN THE ATTIC!
IT'S GOTTA BE A MONSTER.
- Kaoru: COME ON.
- I'M SCARED!
I'M SCARED, KAORU!
- CALM DOWN, TINA!
- I'M SLEEPING IN YOUR BED!
I'M SLEEPING WITH YOU!
- COME ON, ALREADY!
QUIT IT, TINA!
- ( crying )
- Girls: A MONSTER?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I HEARD SOME SCARY NOISES
COMING FROM THE ATTIC
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
IT'S GOT TO BE COMING
FROM A SCARY MONSTER UP THERE.
- NO OFFENSE, TINA,
BUT I REALLY DON'T THINK
IT'S A MONSTER.
- Chika: BUT I HEARD
ALL THOSE WEIRD NOISES TOO.
- All: HUH?
- NOW THAT I THINK OF IT,
I HAVE HEARD NOISES
COMING FROM THE ATTIC SOMETIMES.
- YEAH, THAT'S IT.
I'M SURE THE ATTIC
HAS TO BE THE PLACE
WHERE THE MONSTERS
ARE COMING FROM.
- OH, COME ON, TINA.
- IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN WHY DON'T YOU
LEAVE THE INVESTIGATION TO ME?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
IF WE'RE GONNA DEAL
WITH MONSTERS,
THEN WE SHOULD LET THE EXPERT
GET TO WORK.
GOOD LUCK, TAE.
WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU.
- RIGHT!
I WON'T LET YOU GUYS DOWN.
SO LET'S EXTERMINATE THEM
TOGETHER.
- All: TO-- TOGETHER?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- Tina: OH, OW!  OW OW!
MY STOMACH HURTS.
OW OW, OOH OOH!
- HMMM.
IT ISN'T ANY USE, TINA-SENPAI.
- SHH!
- YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO BROUGHT ALL OF THIS UP.
- Tina: NO!
I DON'T LIKE SCARY THINGS!
- Taeko: THIS SHOULD BE THE DOOR
THAT LEADS TO THE ATTIC, RIGHT?
HUH?  IT WON'T OPEN.
- THAT DOOR CAN'T BE OPENED.
- OH.  WHY IS THAT SO?
- THE KEY HAS BEEN MISSING
FOR QUITE A WHILE NOW.
SO SINCE THEN,
THIS HAS BECOME KNOWN AS
THE ROOM THAT CANNOT BE OPENED.
OF COURSE, THE ROOM COULD BE
OPENED IF WE CALLED A LOCKSMITH.
BUT THERE
WAS NO SPECIAL NEED TO,
SO IT WAS LEFT LIKE THIS.
- YOU KNOW, THIS KEY HOLE--
MAYBE IT COULD--
- THAT'S TOO BAD!
I GUESS THE MONSTER
EXTERMINATING WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU WANTED TO DO
THIS, BUT THAT'S THE BREAKS.
THERE'S NOT MUCH WE CAN DO
IF WE CAN'T GET THE MONSTER.
- BUT THAT MEANS THE MONSTERS
WILL STILL BE THERE.
- AAH!
I DON'T WANT THAT EITHER!
- ( all chuckling )
- ( door clicks )
- All: HUH?
- Taeko: HEY, IT'S OPEN!
WELL THEN, EVERYBODY,
LET'S DO OUR VERY BEST.
- OH.
- Aoi: UM, MISS TAEKO?
WE'RE ALL READY NOW, BUT--
- WOW!
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW GREAT
EVERYBODY LOOKS.
- HEY, TAEKO-CHAN,
WOULD YOU MIND EXPLAINING TO ME
WHY WE HAVE TO WEAR
THESE OUTFITS?
- SENPAI, WHEN YOU'RE DOING
SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
IT'S IMPORTANT TO LOOK THE PART
SO YOU'RE BELIEVABLE.
- GOOD LUCK WITH THE MONSTERS,
TAE.
I'LL DO MY BEST TO
COVER THE PHONE CALLS
WHILE YOU GUYS ARE UP THERE.
- TINA-SENPAI!
- OH, NO FAIR.
TAE'S BEING MEAN TO ME.
- I'M SURPRISED
YOU'RE COMING WITH US.
- I AM THE MANAGER OF THIS
RESIDENCE, IF YOU RECALL.
I CANNOT STAND IDLY BY
WHEN SOMETHING SO SERIOUS OCCURS
DUE TO MY OBLIGATION.
- ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
DO YOU HAVE YOUR SALT WITH YOU?
- All: SALT?!
- SALT HAS THE POWER
TO DRIVE OUT SPIRITS.
SO PLEASE MAKE SURE
TO HAVE SOME CLOSE BY.
- YEAH, I'M NOT LETTING GO
OF THE SALT.
- ONE SMALL SACK
OUGHT TO BE ENOUGH.
IN ANY CASE,
PLEASE BE CAREFUL, EVERYONE.
IN ORDER TO KEEP THE MONSTERS
FROM GETTING AWAY FROM US,
I'VE PUT UP SEALS AND TRAPS
ALL OVER THE MANSION.
THEY'RE DANGEROUS, SO PLEASE
DON'T GO WANDERING OFF ANYWHERE
WITHOUT ME THERE
TO GUIDE YOU.  AND ALSO--
COULD YOU ALL PLEASE WAIT HERE
FOR A MOMENT?
- Kaoru: SURE.
- ( Tina murmuring )
- ( rattling )
- UH, UM, KAORU-SAMA?
WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
IF I HELD YOUR HAND?
- MM-HMM. HUH?
- YEAH, ME TOO!
PLEASE, KAORU?
- BIG BROTHER!
- UM.
- ( all crying )
( all screaming )
- HUH?  IS THERE SOMETHING
THE MATTER, EVERYONE?
- ( all gasping )
- TAE-- TAEKO-CHAN, THE POWER!
- OH. THIS MAKES IT A LOT EASIER
FOR US TO SEE THE SPIRITS.
- WHO SAID WE WANTED TO?
- COME ON.
WE SHOULD GET GOING, EVERYONE.
- Mayu: HMM! THERE IS NOT
A THING IN THIS WORLD
THAT IS PERMITTED TO HER
AND FORBIDDEN TO ME.
PLEASE BE PATIENT,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
THIS NIGHT YOU'LL BE SHARING
YOUR SWEET AND ROMANTIC DREAMS
WITH MAYU.  MM-HMM.
( giggles )
- ( wood creaking )
- TAEKO-CHAN, WHAT'S UP HERE?
- THERE SEEMS TO BE
A LOT OF THINGS IN HERE.
- Miss Miyabi: I BELIEVE
SOMEONE ONCE MENTIONED TO ME
THAT THIS ATTIC WAS USED
AS A STORAGE AREA.
THE VARIOUS OBJECTS
THAT THE PREVIOUS RESIDENTS
NO LONGER USED
AND ITEMS THAT COULD NOT BE
THROWN AWAY WERE KEPT HERE.
- IT'S AS IF THE VERY HISTORY
OF THE HOUSE
IS STORED HERE.
- ( gasps )
I WONDER WHAT THAT IS.
- WHAT DO YOU SEE THERE, TAE?
- All: IT'S A GHOST!
- HUH?
( laughs )
IT'S ONLY A MANNEQUIN.
A MANN-E-QUIN.
YOU SEE?
- TH-- THAT WAS QUITE A SHOCK.
- I THINK THAT MY HEART MIGHT
HAVE STOPPED FOR A MOMENT THERE.
- I KNOW MINE
DEFINITELY DID.
- OH, YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE MAKING TOO BIG A DEAL
OUT OF THIS.
WELL, SHALL WE MOVE ON?
- ( all shouting )
( all screaming )
- AAH! AAH!
STOP IT, TAE!
YOU'RE DOING THIS ON PURPOSE.
YOU'VE SO GOT TO BE DOING THIS
ON PURPOSE.
- HUH?  DOING WHAT?
THERE'S SO MANY ANTIQUES
IN HERE.
- Kaoru: I WONDER WHAT THEY
USED TO DO WITH ALL THIS STUFF.
HUH?
- ( bones rattling )
- HELLO!  IS THERE ANYBODY
AT ALL WHO'S HOME?
HMM.
COULD THEY BE AWAY?
THIS IS SO UNUSUAL.
HANABISHI-SAMA
ISN'T IN THE OTHER BUILDING,
AND NEITHER ARE
ANY OF THE OTHERS.
- ( all screaming )
- HUH?  WHAT WAS THAT?
- ( ground rattling )
- WHAT-- WHAT THE HECK IS
A SKELETON DOING HERE?
- HMM?
OH, SENPAI, IT LOOKS LIKE THIS
IS JUST A MODEL SKELETON.
- WHAT?
IT REALLY IS.
IT SAYS "SAKURABA SCIENCE" HERE.
IT SEEMS THE SAKURABA GROUP
EVEN HAS ITS HAND IN EDUCATION.
( laughs )
- ( both laughing )
- ( rattling )
- HUH?
- ( both panting )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, LADY AOI?
- YES, I THINK SO.
- THERE IS NO REASON FOR YOU
TO BE AFRAID, LADY AOI.
EVEN IF I MUST
GIVE UP MY LIFE TO DO SO,
I, MIYABI KAGURAZAKI,
WILL PROTECT YOU.
WE CAN'T DO MUCH
IF IT REMAINS SO DARK IN HERE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST-- WE
SHOULD TURN THE LIGHTS BACK ON.
- YES.
I WONDER IF HE'S ALL RIGHT.
KAORU-SAMA.
- LADY AOI?
- EXCUSE ME!
IS ANYBODY AT HOME?
HANABISHI-SAMA?
HUH?
WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THIS?
HONESTLY,
THIS IS SUCH A BOTHER.
HUH? AAH!
( screaming )
WHAT IS THIS?!
OH, WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS GOING ON?!
OH, THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
( screaming )
( grunting, screaming )
- SO, THE MONSTER HAS APPEARED.
I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU TO LAY EVEN
A SINGLE FINGER ON LADY AOI!
- AAH!
- ( gasps )
WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS THIS PAPER MADE OF?
- AAH!
- SENPAI, IT'S A DEAD END
OVER HERE.
- WE'VE SEARCHED EVERYWHERE AND
HAVEN'T FOUND ANYTHING AT ALL.
WHICH MEANS THE SOURCE
OF THE NOISES
DEFINITELY WASN'T A MONSTER.
- THAT CAN'T BE.  HUH?
- HMM?
- ( footsteps approaching )
- IT LOOKS
LIKE A PRETTY OLD PICTURE.
HEY,
THIS IS THE SAKURABA MANSION.
- I GUESS THAT MEANS
ALL THESE PEOPLE WERE THE ONES
WHO USED TO WORK IN THIS MANSION
A LONG LONG TIME AGO.
- IT SURE LOOKS THAT WAY, HUH?
- HMM?
AND WHAT'S THIS?
AAH.
- I'M SCARED, I'M SCARED!
- COME ON, MISS TINA. YOU'VE
GOT TO TRY TO CALM DOWN, OKAY?
- BUT I'M SCARED, CHIKA!
- ( Mayu crying )
- HMM?
- WHAT THE HECK WAS THAT THING?
- STOP RIGHT THERE!
- ARE THEY RACING?
- I'M SCARED.
- HEY, TAEKO-CHAN, THIS MAID
LOOKS A LITTLE LIKE YOU.
- YEAH, THERE REALLY IS
A RESEMBLANCE.
- IT LOOKS LIKE IT FELL
FROM OVER HERE.
- UH-HUH.
YOU KNOW, I WONDER,
COULD SHE HAVE BEEN
A KLUTZY MAID TOO?
- SHE MIGHT HAVE BEEN. SHE
DOES LOOK LIKE YOU, AFTER ALL.
- SENPAI, THAT WAS MEAN.
- ( laughs )
I'M JUST KIDDING WITH YOU.
YOU'RE A HARD WORKER,
TAEKO-CHAN.
AND NO MATTER WHAT THE JOB IS,
YOU DO YOUR BEST.
I'M SURE
SHE WAS EXACTLY THE SAME WAY.
- SAY, SENPAI?
I-- I JUST WANTED--
THAT IS--
I WANTED--
- WANTED WHAT?
- ACTUALLY--
ACTUALLY, I WANTED--
- ( rustling )
- ( gasps )
- AAH. A GHOST?
- SENPAI,
PLEASE STAY BACK THERE.
( chanting in Japanese )
( panting )
- ( sighs )
- MMM.  AAH!
- ( squeals )
- IT'S UZUME!
- UH, UZUME?
- ( squealing )
- AAH!
- ( both shout )
- OHH!
- WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THIS?
- OH.
- ( both scream )
- Taeko: IT LOOKS LIKE THE TRUE
IDENTITY OF OUR MONSTER
WAS UZUME ALL ALONG.
- DURING THE NIGHTTIME,
I GUESS HE SNUCK UP HERE
AND PLAYED AROUND AS HE PLEASED.
I GUESS WE OUGHT
TO BE HEADING BACK.
- YEAH.
YOU'RE COMING TOO, UZUME.
- ( squeals )
- Both: HUH?
OH!
- WHAT'S THAT?
- ( squeals )
- ( scrubbing )
- ( sighs )
I GUESS THAT OUGHT TO DO IT.
THIS WHOLE THING
WAS REALLY ALL YOUR WORK,
WASN'T IT?
YOU WANTED TO BE NEAR HIM,
NEXT TO THE MAN THAT YOU LOVE.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Mayu: I HAVE A DATE
WITH HANABISHI-SAMA!
- Tina: WHAT?
YOU STAY AWAY FROM HIM!
- HE'LL LOOK AT ME IN MY DRESS
AND SAY, "YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL"!
"OH, NO, YOU MUSTN'T..."
AND THEN THIS MIGHT HAPPEN,
OR THAT MIGHT HAPPEN!
- Tina: HELLO?
- AND THEN OUR NEW LIFE
TOGETHER WILL BEGIN,
AS SWEET AS THE SWEETEST HONEY
OR SUGAR.
- UH...
- OH, THIS IS WONDERFUL!
SO WONDERFUL!
ON THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"AI YORI AOSHI: ENISHI,
PIANO."
- Tina:
AS SWEET AS HONEY AND SUGAR?
PEANUT BRITTLE.