- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ( crickets chirping )
- ( yawns )
- Itsuki: THINGS GOING WELL?
- HUH?
PROFESSOR ITSUKI.
- YOU SEEM A LITTLE BORED,
MR. HANABISHI.
- I'M NOT BORED.
IT ISN'T LIKE THAT AT ALL, SIR.
I JUST HAVEN'T BEEN
GETTING MUCH SLEEP LATELY.
- HEY, KAORU!
HOW ABOUT A MATCH OR TWO?
- HANABISHI-SAMA, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO GO TO A CONCERT WITH ME?
- SO, SENPAI,
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD HELP
ME PREPARE FOR MY FINALS?
- OH, BIG BROTHER,
I NEED HELP WITH HOMEWORK!
- ( squeals )
- ( all clamoring )
- THAT'S YOUR THESIS PAPER
THERE, ISN'T IT?
IF YOU MISS THE DUE DATE,
THEN THE PENALTY WILL BE
TO ASSIST ME WITH ESSAYS
EVERY SINGLE DAY OF
THE SUMMER VACATION
WHILE LOCKED AWAY IN MY OFFICE.
PREPARE YOURSELF
FOR THE WORST.
- UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
- WELL, DO YOUR BEST.
I HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS
OF YOU.
- UH... ( laughs nervously )
- YES, I UNDERSTAND.
THEN IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
THE MISTRESS'S CONCERN
IS ONLY NATURAL.
SHE HAS APPROVED
OF THEIR RELATIONSHIP,
BUT WHEN ONE SPECULATES
ABOUT LADY AOI'S HAPPINESS,
WHAT IS SIR KAORU THINKING?
WHAT DOES HE HAVE IN MIND
REGARDING THE FUTURE?
- All: IT WAS DELICIOUS!
- ( sighs )
- EXCUSE ME, KAORU-SAMA?
- KAORU!
- ( howling )
- I JUST BOUGHT A NEW GAME!
LOOK, IT'S CALLED
"SUPER UNDERDOG."
LET'S GIVE IT A WHIRL.
- UH, ACTUALLY, TODAY'S NOT--
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HE'LL BE WATCHING THE MOVIE
"PRETTY UMA" WITH ME TODAY,
THE ENCHANTING TALE OF A
CORPORATE MOGUL AND HIS HORSE.
- UM?
- "SUPER UNDERDOG"!
- WE'LL BE WATCHING
"PRETTY UMA."
- THE DOG!
- THE UMA!
- TODAY'S NOT REALLY A GOOD DAY.
ACTUALLY, I'M KIND OF BUSY.
- Both: WHAT?!
- WELL, YOU SEE,
MY THESIS ISN'T DONE YET.
AND IT HAS TO BE FINISHED
BY TOMORROW AT THE LATEST.
PLUS I HAVEN'T
HAD A LOT OF TIME LATELY,
SO I'M ONLY
ABOUT HALFWAY DONE.
- Both: OH.
( both gasp )
- ( all clamoring )
- KAORU-SAMA, COULD IT BE
THAT THE REASON YOU'VE LOOKED
SO TIRED WAS BECAUSE OF--
- YEAH, I'VE BEEN UP ALL NIGHT,
JUST TRYING
TO FINISH WRITING IT.
- PLEASE BE SURE
NOT TO OVEREXERT YOURSELF.
- I KNOW.
DON'T WORRY, I'LL BE FINE.
- KAORU-SAMA.
( knocking )
EXCUSE ME, KAORU-SAMA?
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT LIKE SOME--
( gasps )
- ( all grunting )
- QUIT IT!
I SAID JUST ONE OF US
IS GOING TO GIVE KAORU A MASSAGE
AND IT AIN'T YOU!
- IF A CAVEWOMAN MASSAGES HIM,
IT'LL ONLY MAKE
HIS SHOULDERS WORSE!
- Tina: WHY YOU--
- HEY, STOP IT, TINA!
MAYU-CHAN!  HUH?
- SENPAI, IF YOU
STICK THESE CHARMS ON YOUR DESK,
YOUR CONCENTRATION
IS SURE TO IMPROVE.
- HEY, LOOK HERE, BIG BROTHER!
WHY DON'T YOU USE
ONE OF MY ERASERS?
- ( all clamoring )
- HMM.
EXCUSE ME!
WHAT DO YOU ALL
THINK YOU'RE DOING?!
- ( all whimpering )
- THANKS A LOT
FOR THE SAVE, AOI-CHAN.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
KAORU-SAMA?
- ( moans )
- LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE BEEN KIND OF
TAKING UP KAORU'S STUDYING TIME
FOR A WHILE NOW...
- WHICH IS WHY WE WANTED
TO MAKE UP FOR THAT
BY GIVING HANABISHI-SAMA
A GOOD STUDY ENVIRONMENT TODAY
- AT THE LEAST.
- YES, BUT EVEN SO--
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THEY WERE ALL JUST TRYING
TO HELP ME OUT,
AFTER ALL, RIGHT?
- All: MM-HMM!  MM-HMM!
- ( sighs )
WELL,
THEN WE SHOULD ALL GO NOW.
KAORU-SAMA IS VERY BUSY,
AFTER ALL.
- Women: OKAY!
- I WILL GO AND GET YOU
A FRESH CUP OF TEA.
- MMM.  THANKS, AOI-CHAN.
- ( pen scratching )
- ( knocking )
- COME IN.
- OH, KAORU!
- TINA.
- HAVE YOU GOT A MINUTE?
- UH, YEAH.
- SORRY ABOUT BEFORE.
I WANTED TO MAKE UP FOR IT
SO I MADE YOU SOMETHING NICE.
- HUH?
- TADAH!
IT'S TINA'S DELUXE JUICE MIX.
DRINK IT AND YOUR HEAD
WILL FEEL NICE AND CLEAR.
I GUARANTEE YOU'LL FINISH YOUR
THESIS PAPER WITH NO PROBLEMS.
- WOW.
THANKS A LOT, TINA.
THE COLOR'S
KIND OF INTERESTING, HUH?
- GO AHEAD, DRINK IT UP.
- OKAY.
- ( laughs )
- ( laughs nervously )
( gulps )
I AM NOT...
AN UNDERDOG!
- YEAH!  ALL CLEAR!
I BEAT THE FIRST STAGE!
- KAORU?
KAORU?
- UH, TINA,
THIS STUFF IS--
- IS WHAT?
- THIS-- THIS STUFF IS--
- ( gurgling )
- THIS STUFF IS...
( gulping )
- WHOO!  GO, KAORU!
- ( panting )
- I'M GLAD YOU LIKE IT,
'CAUSE I MADE A LOT.
- HUH?
- WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
DRINK SOME MORE?!
- HANABISHI-SAMA!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT THERE?
IF YOU DRINK ANY MORE OF THIS
UNIDENTIFIABLE CONCOCTION,
YOU'LL ONLY GIVE YOURSELF
A STOMACHACHE.
- HEY, WHAT WAS THAT?
- IN ANY CASE,
WOULD YOU CARE TO HAVE
SOME TEA WITH MAYU?
I BROUGHT SOME
OF MY SPECIAL HOMEMADE COOKIES,
AS WELL AS SOME GOURMET TEA.
- YEAH?
SO THEN YOU MADE
ALL THESE COOKIES, MAYU-CHAN?
- WHY YES!
I POURED MY HEART
INTO BAKING THESE COOKIES
FOR YOU, HANABISHI-SAMA.
- YOU KNOW, THESE LOOK PRETTY
GOOD FOR COOKIES THAT YOU MADE.
- LIKE THIS LITTLE PANDA--
- IT'S CLEARLY A RABBIT.
UH, THEY ARE SLIGHTLY BURNED
AND MAYBE JUST A LITTLE BLACK.
- Kaoru's voice:
I THOUGHT IT WAS A TANUKI.
THANK GOODNESS
I DIDN'T SAY SO.
- DOWN THE HATCH IT GOES!
( coughing )
IT'S BITTER!
- MMM.
THANKS A LOT, MAYU-CHAN.
- ( sighs )
HANABISHI-SAMA!
- MISS TINA, MISS MAYU.
- HUH?
- KAORU-SAMA IS
VERY BUSY RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S SO DIFFICULT TO GRASP.
- Both: I-- I'M SORRY.
- ( laughs )
- ( dog howling )
- ( elevator dings )
- ( key turning )
- I'M BACK HOME!
( sighs )
I'M TOTALLY EXHAUSTED,
AOI-CHAN.
- WELCOME HOME...
KAORU DEAR.
- IT-- IT CAN'T BE!
IT'S GOT TO BE A DREAM.
IT'S GOTTA!
AH!
SOMEONE SAY
IT'S A DREAM, PLEASE!
- DEAR?
IF I MAY,
MIGHT I ASK
WHETHER OR NOT
THAT PAPER OF YOURS IS DONE?
- WHAT?
WHAT? WHAT?
AH!
IT WAS A DREAM.
- ( alarm beeping )
- ( gasps )
( screams )
I FELL ASLEEP!
AND I'M STILL NOT DONE YET!
WHAT DO I DO?!
- Chika:
BIG BROTHER!
- HUH?
- HEY!
( giggles )
- HI, AOI-CHAN,
CHIKA-CHAN.
- WE'LL WALK YOU BACK,
BIG BROTHER.
- AND WELCOME YOU
HOME, KAORU-SAMA.
- THANKS, YOU GUYS.
- IT'S GOOD
THAT YOU TURNED IT IN TODAY,
AND ON TIME.
- YEAH.
THOUGH I'VE GOT TO
SAY I FEEL LIKE
I MADE IT BY THE
SKIN OF MY TEETH.
- SO THEN
YOUR SUMMER VACATION IS...?
- SOMEHOW I MANAGED
NOT TO LOSE IT.
- ( laughs )
WELL, LET'S GET HOME.
EVERYONE'S WAITING.
- Kaoru: SURE.
- All: WE'RE HOME!
- Tina: OH, YOU GUYS ARE BACK.
( bowl clatters )
YO!
- All: UH...
- COME ON, HURRY UP
AND JOIN THE PARTY!
- HANABISHI-SAMA!
- SENPAI, WHAT TOOK
YOU GUYS SO LONG?
- ( laughs )
- I GUESS IT FIGURES.
THE PARTY'S ALREADY
WELL UNDERWAY.
- All: KANPAI!
- ( sighs )
THINGS HAVE BEEN ROUGH LATELY.
BUT EVEN SO, DON'T YOU THINK
THIS IS A BIT MUCH?
- HEY, DON'T SWEAT
THE SMALL STUFF, YOU KNOW?
BESIDES, THIS LITTLE SHINDIG'S
A PART
OF HOW WE'RE GOING
TO MAKE THINGS UP TO YOU,
SINCE WE GOT IN THE WAY
OF YOUR PAPER AND ALL!
- OH, SO THAT'S IT.
THAT'S NICE OF YOU.
- MORE IMPORTANTLY,
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING
SO GLOOMY FOR?
KNOCK BACK A FEW, WILL YA?
- SURE.
- CHUGALUG, CHUGALUG, CHUGALUG!
( laughing )
- ( gulps ) TINA!
- ( laughs )
- ( sighs )
- Mayu: HEY.
HANABISHI-SAMA.
- ( stammers )
- SINCE YOU'RE ALONE HERE,
WOULD YOU CARE TO HAVE
SOME CHATEAU MARGAUX WITH MAYU?
- COME ON NOW.
- WE ALSO HAPPEN TO HAVE
SOME DELICIOUS
CHEDDAR CHEESE AS WELL.
- UH...
- JUST LOOK.
MAYU'S BODY HAS GOTTEN THIS WARM
FROM DRINKING THE WINE.
- AH!
- ( laughs )
HANABISHI-SAMA!
- C-- COME ON, MAYU-CHAN.
HUH?
AHH!
MAYU-CHAN,
COULD IT BE THAT YOU--
AH!
- ( giggles )
- WHY, WASN'T MISS MIYABI
SAVING THAT WINE
FOR A SPECIAL OCCASION?
- HUH?
- OH, SHE WAS ALSO
SAVING THIS CHEESE.
- WHAT?  REALLY?
THAT'S BAD NEWS.
- BUT I THINK TODAY
IS A SPECIAL OCCASION.
MISS MIYABI WILL UNDOUBTEDLY
FORGIVE US THIS TIME.
- UH, I WONDER.
- WELL,
NOW WHY DON'T YOU DRINK
SOME MORE
CHATEAU MARGAUX WITH ME?
MMM.
- HEY, KAORU!
LET'S DRINK SOME MORE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- ( streamer guns exploding )
- ♪ I'M VERY SORRY
TO ALL OF MY FANS ♪
♪ WHO REALLY DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT... ♪
- Chika and Kaoru: ♪ WE TRIED TO
MEASURE THE LOVE THAT WE SHARE ♪
♪ MY FEELINGS NEVER REACHED YOU
NEAR ENOUGH, MY DEAR ♪
♪ WE TRIED TO REACH OUT
FOR THE HIGHEST TRUE LOVE ♪
♪ LOOKING DOWN FROM... ♪
- WHOO! ♪ YOU'D BETTER FIND
SOME STRENGTH IN YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ AND MAKE
SOME MUSCLE AND BONE ♪
♪ YOU HAVE TO FIGHT ON,
BE RAGING MAD ♪
♪ SON-IN-LAW! ♪
YEAH! ( laughs )
- WOW, KAORU.
YOUR CHEST IS WAY HARDER
THAN IT LOOKS,
LIKE POLISHED OAK--
SO STRONG AND SMOOTH.
- ( Taeko gulping )
AH!  HEY, GUYS.
ISN'T ANYONE DRINKING MORE?
WE'VE STILL GOT
A LOT OF BEER LEFTOVER.
- ( horse neighing )
- ( sighs )
- HERE...
KAORU-SAMA.
- OH.
THANKS A BUNCH, AOI-CHAN.
- WOULD YOU TELL ME
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT?
- HUH?  OH, SURE.
I WAS JUST THINKING
THAT IT'S ALREADY BEEN
TWO WHOLE YEARS
SINCE THEN.
- YOU'RE REFERRING TO
THE TIME WE MET AGAIN,
CORRECT?
- YEAH.
IT ALMOST FEELS LIKE NO TIME
HAS PASSED AT ALL.
- YES, IT DOES.
THE YEARS FELT SO BRIEF.
- ( sobbing )
- THAT'LL DO IT.
HERE, THIS SHOULD WORK,
AOI-CHAN.
- WOW!
THANK YOU, KAORU-SAMA!
- ( laughs )
- ( Aoi laughing )
- UM, KAORU-SAMA?
- YEAH?
- ONCE YOU COMPLETE YOUR
GRADUATE STUDIES, KAORU-SAMA,
WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU PLAN
ON DOING WITH YOURSELF?
- THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
ACTUALLY,
I HAVEN'T DECIDED YET.
IT ISN'T LIKE BEFORE.
EVERYTHING'S UNCERTAIN NOW
AND I'M BUSY DOING ALL THE
THINGS THAT I HAVE TO DO.
EVEN SO,
I'M NOT FOLLOWING
SOMEONE ELSE'S TERMS.
I WANT TO DECIDE THINGS
OF MY OWN WILL,
WITH MY OWN THOUGHTS.
IT'S JUST...
I DON'T WANT THINGS
DECIDED FOR ME,
NOT EVER AGAIN.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- ( chuckles )
- ( switch clicks )
- ( both laugh )
- Kaoru: WELL, I GUESS I'LL
HEAD BACK TO MY ROOM.
- UM, KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
WHAT IS IT, AOI-CHAN?
- WELL, I-- THAT IS--
- HMM?
- THE LIFE THAT YOU CHOOSE,
KAORU-SAMA,
NO MATTER WHAT KIND
OF LIFE IT IS,
WILL BE ONE
THAT WILL INCLUDE ME
RIGHT BY YOUR SIDE.
AFTER ALL,
THE LIFE THAT YOU CHOOSE,
KAORU-SAMA,
WILL ALSO BECOME THE LIFE
THAT I LEAD AS WELL.
- AOI-CHAN.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Chika: YAY, A SUMMER RESORT!
SOMEONE WHO WORKS
FOR A COMPANY PRESIDENT!
- ( monkey chitters )
- Chika: THAT'S A SUMMER INTERN.
UM, THEN IT'S LIKE IF I BECAME
AN IDOL IN THE SUMMER.
- Tina: HEY, I CAN BE
A SUMMER SENSATION!
- ( screeches )
- CHIKA THE SENSATION
WILL HAVE A BIG PART
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "AI YORI AOSHI: ENISHI,"
"SUMMER RESORT"!
YOU WON'T WANT TO MISS IT!
- ( Taeko squeals )