- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Chika: DEAR GRANDMA,
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M DOING MY BEST
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
THE SCHOOLWORK'S
BEEN TOUGH
AND THE BEACH
ISN'T VERY CLOSE,
WHICH MAKES ME
KIND OF SAD.
BUT I'VE GOT
GREAT FRIENDS HERE,
SO I'M FINE.
- HEY, CHIKA.
- HUH?
- I'VE BEEN MEANING TO ASK YOU
THIS FOR A WHILE NOW,
BUT WHAT IS THAT THING?
- WHAT?
IT'S-- IT'S A DOLL.
- I CAN SEE THAT
FOR MYSELF,
BUT IT'S HANDMADE, RIGHT?
WHO'S IT MODELED AFTER?
- WELL, UM...
- HOW ABOUT MISS MINAZUKI?
- YES, MA'AM.
- IN THE YEAR 1756,
WHAT WAR OCCURRED
BETWEEN THE EUROPEAN NATIONS
OF AUSTRIA AND PRUSSIA?
- UH, LET'S SEE.
IT WAS
THE SEVEN-YEARS WAR.
- YES, INDEED IT WAS.
- ( sighs )
- IN REGARD TO WORLD HISTORY,
THIS WAR WAS CAUSED IN PART
BY THE RIVALRY BETWEEN...
- ( Chika's voice ) THE ALWAYS
CHEERFUL AND LIVELY
NATSUKI KOMIYA
AND CHIZURU AIZAWA,
WHO'S A LITTLE BASHFUL
BUT REALLY NICE.
THE TWO OF THEM ARE MY BEST
FRIENDS IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
- YEAH!
- NO WAY.
OH, MAN, YOU REALLY ARE
FAST, CHIKA.
- YAY.
- ON THE OTHER HAND...
- ( whimpering )
- MAN, YOU REALLY ARE
HOPELESS, CHIZURU.
- I'M SORRY.
- THE THREE OF US
ARE THE ONLY ONES
WHO ARE TAKING
THE SWIMMING CLUB SERIOUSLY.
SO YOU'VE GOT TO TRY
A LITTLE HARDER, OKAY?
- OKAY.
- HEY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
CHIZURU-CHAN'S DOING
THE BEST SHE CAN.
I MEAN, SHE ONLY HAD TO STOP
AND STAND IN THE MIDDLE
OF HER LAP TWICE TODAY.
RIGHT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- JEEZ, CHIKA.
YOU'RE TOO EASY ON HER.
- I'M SURE YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO SWIM
FOR AN EVEN LONGER TIME
TOMORROW.
- THANKS FOR THE PEP TALK,
MISS MINAZUKI.
- OH, COME ON.
I TOLD YOU IT WAS ALL RIGHT
TO CALL ME CHIKA.
- HUH?
- CHIKA, YOU DROPPED YOUR WALLET
OVER HERE.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS
PICTURE, CHIKA?!
- MY GOSH, IT'S A PICTURE
OF SOME MAN AND MISS CHIKA.
- WELL, THAT'S A--
YOU SEE--
- CHIKA, DON'T TELL ME
THIS GUY IS YOUR--
- NO.
YOU SHOULDN'T JUST LOOK AT THAT
WITHOUT ASKING.
IT'S SOMETHING SPECIAL TO ME,
YOU KNOW?
- OH, WHAT'S THAT 'TUDE?
- IS THAT PERSON THERE
REALLY YOUR--?
- ( giggles )
WELL...
- COME ON,
WHO'S HE SUPPOSED TO BE?
- HE IS JUST SOMEONE
WHO'S LIVING TOGETHER
WITH ME RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT?
- WHAT WAS THAT?
YOU'RE-- YOU'RE LIVING...
- TOGETHER?
- A LITTLE BABY
LIKE HER?
- SHE'S GONE THAT FAR
ALREADY?
- ( giggles )
- HEY, CHIKA.
- WH-- WHAT,
NATSUKI-CHAN?
- ( birds chirping )
- Chika: WHAT?
TOMORROW?
AND SO MY FRIENDS
WERE SAYING,
SINCE IT'S SUNDAY,
THAT THEY WANTED
TO COME OVER TOMORROW
IF THAT'S ALL RIGHT
WITH EVERYONE.
- YEAH?  SO YOUR FRIENDS
WANTED TO COME OVER HERE, HUH?
- I LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
- YEAH.
- OH, REALLY?
IT'S OKAY TO BRING THEM HERE?
- Aoi: YES, OF COURSE IT IS.
- Tina: IF THEY'RE FRIENDS
OF YOURS, WE'LL GIVE THEM
A WARM WELCOME.
- ISN'T THAT GREAT NEWS,
CHIKA-CHAN?
- YAY!
ALL RIGHT!
BANZAI!
- ( Miyabi clears throat )
WELL, I SUPPOSE IT ISN'T LIKE
THEY WILL BE COMING OVER
EVERY SINGLE DAY, SO I HAVE
NO OBJECTIONS AT ALL.
- ( sighs )
THANK GOODNESS.
BUT NOW...
WELL, TILL TOMORROW.
- DEFINITELY.
WE'VE JUST GOT TO CHECK OUT
YOUR BOYFRIEND, NO MATTER WHAT.
- I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO MEETING HIM TOO.
- WH--
- SEE YA.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY CALLED HIM MY BOYFRIEND.
BUT IF NATSUKI-CHAN
AND CHIZURU-CHAN COME HERE
AND THEY MEET
BIG BROTHER,
THEY'RE GONNA ASK HIM
ALL KINDS OF QUESTIONS.
THAT'S NOT A GOOD THING,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
HE DEFINITELY WON'T BE
EXPECTING IT.
AND MAYBE HE'LL EVEN
START HATING ME
FOR PUTTING HIM
THROUGH THAT.
( moans )
WAA!  WHAT NOW?
WAA!
( wailing )
OW.
- THANK GOODNESS.  IT LOOKS LIKE
BIG BROTHER'S OKAY.
- ( people chattering )
- AND IN THE END, I COULDN'T
FALL ASLEEP AT ALL.
- HEY, CHIKA!
HEY!
WHAT'S WITH THOSE EYES, CHIKA?
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'M OKAY, REALLY.
( giggles )
- OH, ALLOW ME
TO WELCOME YOU HERE.
- GOOD MORNING,
MISS AOI.
- OH, H-- HELLO.
- I'M PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
- I'M PLEASED
TO MEET YOU TOO.
- HUH?
- OH, YEAH, WHY DON'T WE
GO INSIDE AND HAVE A SNACK?
- WHAT'S UP WITH THIS?  IT ISN'T
JUST THE TWO OF YOU HERE, CHIKA.
- I NEVER SAID IT WAS JUST
THE TWO OF US LIVING TOGETHER.
- THANK GOODNESS.
SHE HASN'T GONE THAT FAR.
- WHAT?
- EVERYBODY, THANK YOU
FOR STOPPING BY TODAY.
- MISS AOI IS
THE LANDLORD,
IN CASE I DIDN'T
MENTION THAT BEFORE.
- I BROUGHT SOME TEA
FOR YOU ALL.
- HOW PRETTY--
A KIMONO.
- MM.
- Chika: THANKS FOR
THE SNACK.
- WOW, THIS IS DELICIOUS.
- OH, MAN, TASTY.
UH, D-- DELICIOUS.
- THIS IS
A CHERRY BLOSSOM PIE.
- Chizuru: CHERRY BLOSSOM PIE?
- IT'S MISS AOI'S
ORIGINAL RECIPE.
- WHAT?  MISS AOI'S THE ONE WHO
MADE THIS?  IT'S REALLY GOOD.
- THERE'S RED BEAN PASTE
INSIDE IT.
OH, AND IT DOES SMELL A BIT
LIKE CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
- IT'S IN THE FILLING.
THE CHERRY BLOSSOM PETALS
WERE FIRST SOAKED IN VINEGAR.
- Girls: WOW.
- I KNOW-- WHY DON'T YOU
ASK HER TO TEACH YOU
HOW TO MAKE IT, GUYS?
- YEAH.
( both giggle )
- THESE ARE ALL OF
THE INGREDIENTS THAT WE'LL NEED.
- WOW, THERE'S A LOT LESS
THAN I THOUGHT THERE'D BE.
- WHICH PART OF THE PIE
DO WE START ON FIRST?
- Aoi: THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
- ( giggles )
- ALL RIGHT, NOW THAT
THEY'RE BUSY WITH THAT,
I'D BETTER GO EXPLAIN
WHAT'S GOING ON TO BIG BROTHER.
OH MY GOSH!
NATSUKI-CHAN AND CHIZURU-CHAN
MIGHT BE ASKING MISS AOI
ABOUT BIG BROTHER.
WAA!
- Aoi: FOR THE PIE DOUGH,
YOU NEED TO SIFT
THE BREAD AND WHEAT FLOUR
UNTIL THEY ARE WELL INTEGRATED.
BY DOING THIS, IT INSURES THE
CRUST REMAINS NICE AND CRISP.
- WOW.
- HMM.  I THINK
IT MIGHT BE ALL RIGHT
FOR THE DOUGH TO BE
JUST A LITTLE BIT SWEETER.
THE REASON I AM SO CAREFUL
ABOUT THE SWEETNESS
IS BECAUSE I WANT TO MAKE
WHAT KAORU-SAMA LIKES.
- KAORU-SAMA?
- OH, HE HAPPENS TO BE
ONE OF OUR BOARDERS.
- ( yells )
- HUH?
- STOP TALKING ABOUT THAT
RIGHT NOW!
- ( all exclaim,
coughing )
- Chizuru: OH, THAT WAS
SUCH A FRIGHT.
- Natsuki: WHAT THE HECK
WERE YOU DOING, CHIKA?
- ( giggles )
SORRY.
( sighs )
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE I MADE IT
THERE JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME.
- Aoi: HOW IS THE WATER,
EVERYONE?
- IT'S PERFECT.
THE WATER FEELS WONDERFUL.
- I'M GLAD.
PLEASE TAKE YOUR TIME
AND ENJOY THE BATH.
- EXCUSE ME, MISS AOI.
- YES?
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
- HMM?
OH, PLEASE DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, MISS CHIKA, REALLY.
- BUT YOU GOT COVERED
HEAD TO TOE IN FLOUR TOO.
YOU WANT TO COME IN HERE
AND WASH UP WITH US?
- MY BATH WILL HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL I FINISH
CLEANING UP THE KITCHEN,
BUT IF YOU NEED ME FOR ANYTHING,
PLEASE DO NOT HESITATE
TO CALL FOR ME.
- IF THINGS KEEP UP
LIKE THIS,
THEN WE'LL END UP
BEING A BOTHER TO EVERYONE.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
WHAT SHOULD I DO,
BIG BROTHER?
- ( footsteps )
- HUH?
WHAT?
BIG BROTHER?
W-- WAIT A SECOND.
WAIT, THERE ARE
ONLY GIRLS IN HERE.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
WAIT!
- Tina: WHAT THE--?
CHIKA?
AH, IF AN AFTERNOON BATH
AIN'T A GOOD THING,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS.
- MISS TINA.
- ( squeaks )
- WOW, IT MUST BE NICE
TO BE A BLONDE.
I WANT TO DYE
MY HAIR TOO.
- THIS IS
MY NATURAL COLOR.
I WAS BORN WITH IT.
- NATURAL?
- DESPITE HOW MISS TINA
SOMETIMES ACTS,
SHE'S AN HONEST-TO-GOSH
AMERICAN.
- OH, SO THAT'S WHY--
- HEY, CHIKA,
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN, HUH?
- ( giggles )
- NO MERCY.
YOU'RE GONNA BE PUNISHED.
- NO!  I SAID
I WAS SORRY.
- TOO BAD.  TAKE THIS.
- NO!
- THEY'RE STILL
KIND OF SMALL, AREN'T THEY?
I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO SEEING
HOW BIG THEY GET
WHEN YOU GROW UP.  TAKE THAT.
- COULD IT BE SHE'S INTO
THAT SORT OF THING?
- HUH?
- ( squeaks )
- ( giggles )
- AH, I FEEL
MUCH BETTER NOW.
AFTER A BATH, A GENTLE BREEZE
SURE FEELS NICE.
I TOLD YOU,
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT AT ALL.
- OKAY THEN, NOW THAT
WE'VE ALL HAD A BATH,
MAYBE WE SHOULD GO SOMEWHERE
AND DO SOMETHING TOGETHER?
- GO SOMEWHERE?
WHAT FOR?
- OH, WELL...
( giggles )
( Chika's voice ) I GUESS
GETTING THEM AWAY FROM HERE
ISN'T GOING TO BE THAT EASY.
IT'S NOT LOOKING GOOD.
I REALLY DID WANT TO INTRODUCE
THEM BOTH TO BIG BROTHER,
BUT WHEN I THINK
ABOUT IT...
- HEY, CHIKA'S BOYFRIEND,
TAKE GOOD CARE OF HER.
- EXCUSE ME,
MR. BOYFRIEND,
BUT JUST WHAT IS IT
THAT YOU LIKE ABOUT MISS CHIKA?
- HUH?  BOYFRIEND?
LIKE ABOUT HER?
UH, WELL, YOU SEE...
- OH, NO, NO.
IF THEY MEET HIM,
SOMETHING HORRIBLE WILL HAPPEN.
- ( door opens )
- COULD THAT BE
BIG BROTHER?
THIS IS BAD.
I HAVE TO DISTRACT THEM.
LOOK, THERE'S A SQUID
THAT'S OVER 10 YARDS LONG.
- UH, WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU DOING, CHIKA?
- WHAT?  WHERE IS IT?
I DON'T SEE A GIANT SQUID.
- OH, HI, CHIKA-CHAN.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOUR FRIENDS
GOT HERE SAFELY.
- OH,
IT WAS JUST YOU, TAEKO.
( sighs )
- Taeko: THE LIGHT BULBS
WERE GETTING A LITTLE OLD,
SO I THOUGHT
I'D REPLACE THEM.
- Chika: TRY TO BE
CAREFUL, TAEKO.
- I'LL BE ALL RIGHT,
REALLY.
AAH!  OH.  OH.
WHOA.  OH.
- THEY'RE HUGE.
- HEY, WHY DON'T YOU
LET ME CHANGE THEM?
- DIDN'T I JUST TELL YOU
I'D BE ALL RIGHT?
I THINK YOU'RE STARTING
TO BECOME MORE OF A WORRYWART
AS YOU GET OLDER,
CHIKA-CHAN.
- HEY, CAREFUL.
- HMM?  OF WHAT?
- ( flesh hisses )
- HOT!
( screaming )
- IT'S READY NOW.
- OKAY.
- OH, THANK YOU FOR THE HELP.
IT WAS SO NICE OF YOU.
- ( car approaches )
- HMM?
- YOU'RE TOO SURE OF YOURSELF
SOMETIMES, TAEKO.
- ALLEY-OOP.
I THINK I JUST SAW SOMETHING.
- WHAT DID SHE
JUST SEE?
- WHO KNOWS?
BUT IF IT WAS IN THE GARDEN,
IT COULD BE SENPAI.
- SENPAI, HUH?
WHAT?!  BIG BROTHER?!
NO, ANYTHING BUT THAT!
- WOW, IT'S GORGEOUS.
IT'S AN IMPORT,
A REAL IMPORT.
IT'S SO COOL.
I WANT TO BE THE KIND OF WOMAN
WHO WILL LOOK GOOD
WITH THIS CAR.
OH, IT FEELS
SO SMOOTH.
- ( panting )
THANK GOODNESS.
- ( car door opens )
- EXCUSE ME, WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING TO MY CAR?
- YOU MEAN THAT THIS IS
YOUR CAR?
- YES, IT MOST CERTAINLY IS.
IS SOMETHING WRONG WITH THAT?
- HUH?  WHAT?
NO WAY.
IT LOOKS WRONG WITH YOU.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- OH, MAN.
I SHOULD STOP
TELLING PEOPLE THE TRUTH.
- HOW DARE YOU?
- CALM DOWN,
MISS MAYU.
- Taeko: ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO?
- OH, YES.
- YOU'RE SHY, AREN'T YOU?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
I'M JUST A LITTLE SLOW,
I GUESS.
- HUH?
- I'M NOT AS QUICK
AS OTHER PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHY
I'M ALWAYS TROUBLING
MISS CHIKA AND MISS NATSUKI
ALMOST CONSTANTLY.
- ( giggles )
YOU'RE LIKE ME.
I'M THE SAME WAY.
YOU SAW WHAT HAPPENED
BEFORE, RIGHT?
BUT I NEVER GET
DISCOURAGED,
BECAUSE THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO SUPPORT ME.
EVEN THE THINGS
I DON'T THINK I CAN DO,
I CAN DO
IF THEY'RE THERE WITH ME.
THEY HELP ME KNOW
WHAT I'M CAPABLE OF.
AND THAT'S WHY
I CAN DO MY BEST.
- BECAUSE OF THE PEOPLE
WHO SUPPORT YOU.
- YOU HAVE PEOPLE THAT
SUPPORT YOU TOO, DON'T YOU?
- YES.
- SO TRY YOUR BEST.
- I WILL,
MY VERY BEST.
SO THEN, IF I DO EVERYTHING
I CAN AND TRY MY BEST,
WILL MY BREASTS
GET TO BE AS BIG AS YOURS?
- HUH?
UH, WELL, THEY MIGHT.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
( giggling )
- I'LL DO MY BEST.
- IN ANY CASE, WOULD YOU PLEASE
NOT TOUCH MY CAR AGAIN
WITHOUT MY PERMISSION?
YOU'LL GET IT DIRTY.
- WHAT'S THAT?
I DIDN'T HEAR YOU.
- I SAID, DON'T TOUCH MY CAR.
YOU'LL GET IT DIRTY.
- YEAH?
LET'S SEE IF I DO.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- THIS IS DEFINITELY
AN IMPORT ALL RIGHT.
- COME ON, STOP IT.
COME ON, YOU TWO,
STOP IT ALREADY.
- ENOUGH.
I WON'T TOLERATE THIS.
- TRY AND STOP ME.
- SOMEONE HELP ME
OVER HERE!
MISS AOI, MISS TINA, TAEKO!
ANYBODY!
( Chika's voice )
BIG BROTHER?
BUT IF HE MEETS NATSUKI-CHAN
AND CHIZURU-CHAN...
- HA-HA!
- STOP HITTING MY CAR ALREADY.
- HEY, BIG BROTHER,
I NEED HELP.
WHAT?
- WHAT DO YOU TWO GIRLS THINK
YOU'RE DOING HERE?
A SAKURABA HOUSEHOLD
STANDS BEFORE YOU.
AND AS ITS MANAGER, I ASK
THAT IF YOU MUST CONTINUE
THIS CHILDISH DISPUTE,
THEN DO SO ELSEWHERE.
- YES, MA'AM.
I SINCERELY APOLOGIZE.
- HE'S NOT HERE.
- IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR KAORU,
I THINK HE LEFT A WHILE AGO
TO HELP HIS PROFESSOR
PREPARE A LECTURE--
SOMETHING LIKE THAT
ANYWAY.
- SO YOU MEAN THE WHOLE TIME
HE WASN'T EVEN HERE?
- HEY, ARE YOU OKAY,
CHIKA?
- ( people chattering )
- Natsuki: THANKS A LOT
FOR TODAY, CHIKA.
- Chizuru:
I'M GLAD I CAME.
- OH, R-- REALLY?
BY THE WAY,
I'M REALLY SORRY
THAT YOU DIDN'T GET THE CHANCE
TO MEET HIM AND ALL.
- HUH?
- WHO?
- YOU KNOW, THAT YOU DIDN'T
GET THE CHANCE TO--
TO MEET MY--
MY, YOU KNOW-- THE ONE YOU--
- OH, YEAH.
YOUR BOYFRIEND, RIGHT?
I TOTALLY FORGOT
ABOUT THAT.
- IT SLIPPED MY MIND TOO.
- HUH?
- ( giggles )
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
THAT WAS THE REASON
WE WENT THERE.
- SOMEHOW JUST SPENDING TIME
AROUND ALL THOSE PEOPLE
WAS SO FUN,
I FORGOT.
SEE YOU, CHIKA.
LATER.
- TILL TOMORROW.
- BYE-BYE.
- WE'LL COME BY AGAIN.
- MM-HMM.
BIG BROTHER!
- ( train signal ringing )
- OH, HI THERE, CHIKA-CHAN.
I'M BACK.
- OH, BIG BROTHER,
BACK THERE.
- ( train horn blows )
- SEE YOU TWO TOMORROW.
( Chika's voice )
MAYBE NEXT TIME.
Chika: WHAT?
OH, IT'S STARTING TO RAIN.
- Kaoru: YOU'RE RIGHT.
- ( Chika's voice ) GRANDMA,
I'M HAVING FUN AT SCHOOL,
SO I LIKE IT AND ALL.
BUT WHAT I REALLY LOVE
IS THIS HOUSE
AND MY WONDERFUL
FAMILY.
- Chika and Kaoru: WE'RE BACK!
- Girls: WELCOME HOME!
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Tina: THE NEXT EPISODE'S
ABOUT TENNIS, CHIKA.
- YEAH, A SPORTS EPISODE.
- GLISTENING SWEAT, FLAPPING
MINISKIRTS, PURE WHITE THIGHS,
UNDERSKIRTS
AND-- AND--
- Chika: AND?
- AND BOUNCING BOOBIES!
BOOBIES, BOOBIES, BOOBIES!
HA-HA!
THAT REALLY FIRES ME UP!
- Chika: ON THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "AI YORI AOSHI: ENISHI,
TENNIS."
- OH, MAN, I JUST CAN'T WAIT.
- Chika: WAIT, BUT I DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH UP THERE TO BOUNCE.