- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( playing piano )
- ( up-tempo song continues )
- PARDON ME, MADAM.
- OH, SAIONJI,
EXCELLENT TIMING.
PLEASE MAKE SURE
THAT THIS GETS TO MY MOTHER.
- AS YOU WISH, MADAM.
- IS THIS FOR ME?
- YES.
IT'S FROM PARIS.
- FROM MAMA!
- Mother: "DEAR MAYU,
I'VE DESIGNED
A ONE-PIECE SUMMER DRESS.
IT'S ONE-OF-A-KIND
AND IT'S JUST FOR YOU.
IT WOULD PLEASE ME
IF YOU LIKED IT.
FROM, MAMA."
- IT'S BEAUTIFUL!
I LOVE MY MAMA!
( giggling )
- IT IS A WONDERFUL DRESS.
- YES!
OH, WOULD YOU GIVE ME BACK
THE LETTER
I JUST HANDED TO YOU, SAIONJI?
I NEED TO ADD A THANK YOU
BEFORE I SEND IT TO HER.
- CERTAINLY.
- IT'S SUCH A BEAUTIFUL DRESS.
OH, I KNOW!
- WHAT?
GO ON A DATE?
- THAT'S RIGHT!
WOULD YOU GO ON A DATE
WITH ME TOMORROW?
THERE IS SOMETHING
I SIMPLY MUST SHOW YOU.
- UH, TOMORROW, HUH?
UM, WELL, TOMORROW,
UH, UM...
- IT LOOKS LIKE TOMORROW'S
WEATHER WILL BE PERFECT TOO!
SO WON'T YOU PLEASE,
HANABISHI-SAMA?
PLEASE?  OKAY?
- WELL, YOU SEE--
- I'LL COME PICK YOU UP
AT 10:00 TOMORROW MORNING.
TILL THEN, GOOD NIGHT,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
- UH...
( sighs )
- ( fist pounding )
- UH!
- KAORU!  WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST
MAKE IT CLEAR TO HER
AND TELL HER NO?!
SHE WALKED ALL OVER YOU.
- A DATE!
I'M SO JEALOUS.
GO ON A DATE WITH ME NEXT TIME,
BIG BROTHER, OKAY?
- ( squeaks )
- AH, COME ON, CHIKA-CHAN.
- HUH?
- ( laughs nervously )
- MMM.
- WELL, I DON'T SEE A PROBLEM
WITH IT.
- EH?
- MISS MANAGER?
- HE IS AN ELIGIBLE BACHELOR,
AFTER ALL.
AND HE IS ONLY ONE SINGLE DATE.
YOU AGREE, DON'T YOU,
LADY AOI?
- UH, OF COURSE.
- SO GO AHEAD.
BE SURE TO HAVE AN ENJOYABLE
TIME WITH MISS MAYU.
- UH...
( laughs nervously )
( whispering )
AOI-CHAN?
- HUH?
KAORU-SAMA?
- ( footsteps )
- Aoi: WHAT SEEMS
TO BE THE MATTER?
- UH, WELL, ABOUT THE THING
WITH MAYU-CHAN EARLIER--
- OH.
PLEASE GO
AND HAVE A GOOD TIME.
OH!
I'M SORRY.
THAT DIDN'T COME OUT RIGHT.
- I'M SORRY
I COULDN'T TURN HER DOWN.
IT'S JUST SHE LOOKED SO HAPPY,
I COULDN'T BRING MYSELF TO.
- THAT'S LIKE YOU,
KAORU-SAMA.
- I'M SORRY.
- PLEASE DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
OKAY?
- AOI-CHAN.
- BUT--
- HUH?
- NEXT TIME,
WHEN YOU GO ON A DATE,
PLEASE GO WITH ME.
- YOU'VE GOT A DEAL.
- ( both giggling )
- HONESTLY.
- Mayu: GOOD MORNING,
HANABISHI-SAMA!
- WOW!
- All: WOW.
- WHOA.
- AH!
- Taeko:
WHAT A LOVELY DRESS.
- Chika: YOU LOOK LIKE A MODEL
OR SOMETHING, MISS MAYU.
- ( laughs )
OH, I COULDN'T LOOK
THAT BEAUTIFUL.
- YOU LOOK NICE
IN THAT DRESS-- REALLY NICE.
- DO YOU HONESTLY MEAN IT?
- Tina: I GUESS IT'S TRUE
THAT THE CLOTHES
MAKE THE WOMAN.
- OH!
- TINA-SENPAI!
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- I'M SORRY,
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME?
I SAID IT'S THE CLOTHES
THAT MAKE THE WOMAN.
- IS THAT SO? SAY THAT AGAIN,
YOU BEAST OF A WOMAN!
- FINE!  I'LL SAY IT
AS MANY TIMES AS YOU WANT.
CLOTHES MAKE THE WOMAN!
- ( grunts )
I'LL HAVE YOU DEPORTED BACK
TO THE JUNGLE WHERE YOU BELONG!
- YEAH?  GO AHEAD AND TRY
IF YOU CAN!
- COME ON,
CALM DOWN, YOU TWO.
- WELL THEN,
WE'LL BE ON OUR WAY.
- All: AH, RIGHT.
- GUESS WE'RE OFF NOW.
SEE YOU.
- ( makes teasing sounds )
- NYAH NYAH NYAH NYAH NYAH!
- WE'LL SEE YOU GUYS
WHEN YOU GET BACK!
- THAT BRAT REALLY KNOWS
HOW TO TICK ME OFF.
- BUT EVEN SO--
- All: HMM?
- LOOKS LIKE MR. SAIONJI IS
GOING WITH THEM AFTER ALL.
- Mayu: LET'S ENJOY TODAY
TO THE FULLEST, HANABISHI-SAMA!
- YOU'RE ON.
SO WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- EH?  WELL, I GUESS WE'LL--
THAT IS, WE'LL--
SAIONJI, WHERE ARE WE HEADED
EXACTLY?
- I'M JUST DRIVING AIMLESSLY.
- OH.  YOU MEAN
YOU NEVER DECIDED
WHERE WE'D BE GOING TODAY?
- AH!  WELL, I--
OH NO!
I WAS SO PREOCCUPIED
WITH SHOWING HIM THE DRESS
THAT THE THOUGHT OF PLANNING
OUR DATE NEVER OCCURRED TO ME.
UH, AND ALSO,
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
THIS IS ACTUALLY THE FIRST DATE
I'VE EVER BEEN ON.
( sighs )
OH, SAIONJI!
PULL THE CAR OVER THERE.
I'M SORRY, HANABISHI-SAMA.
THERE'S A BOOK THAT I NEED
TO BUY HERE BEFORE WE GO.
I'LL BE BACK SOON. PLEASE WAIT
HERE FOR A MOMENT OR TWO.
- UH, SURE THING.
- SAIONJI, ENTERTAIN
HANABISHI-SAMA, WON'T YOU?
- AS YOU WISH, MADAM.
- AH, THAT'S IT THERE!
- AND THAT'S
HOW MY CLASSMATE TAKAHASHI
BEGAN CULTIVATING
YELLOWTAIL FISH.
- UH, I SEE.
- WE ARE ON A DATE AFTER ALL.
I NEED TO MAKE SURE
HANABISHI-SAMA ENJOYS HIMSELF.
I SEE, I SEE-- THE SECRET
TO A FUN DATE IS--
- Man: AHEM!
- HMM?
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE STANDING
AND READING HERE.
- UH, I'M CROUCHING
- HUH?
- ( door bells jingle )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
I HAD TO BUY THIS IN THE END.
- Kaoru: MAYU-CHAN!
- AAH!
- ( laughs nervously )
- MOTIVATED BY OLD RIVALRIES,
MY OTHER CLASSMATE SATO
TOYED AROUND WITH THE IDEA
OF STARTING
AN ABALONE CULTIVATION BUSINESS.
- HUH?
WHAT DO I LIKE?
- RIGHT! WHAT PASTIMES
DO YOU ENJOY, HANABISHI-SAMA?
- HMM.
LET ME THINK.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
BUT, MAYU-CHAN, ARE YOU SURE YOU
REALLY DON'T MIND GOING BOWLING?
- OF COURSE I DON'T MIND.
( laughs )
THIS IS ONE OF HANABISHI-SAMA'S
FAVORITE GAMES.
I'M SURE
HE'LL ENJOY PLAYING HERE.
- HERE IS YOUR BOWLING BALL.
- THANK YOU.
( grunting )
IT'S HEAVY.
HEY, I TOLD YOU TO GET ME
THE LIGHTEST ONE, DIDN'T I?
- I'M AFRAID THAT'S THE LIGHTEST
ONE I COULD FIND, MADAM.
- ( grunts )
- ARE YOU OKAY, MAYU-CHAN?
- OH, YES,
I'M PERFECTLY FINE.
WOW!  YOU'RE INCREDIBLE,
HANABISHI-SAMA!
- I WAS JUST LUCKY.
WELL, IT'S YOUR TURN NOW,
MAYU-CHAN.
- RIGHT!
OKAY NOW,
IF I CAN GET A STRIKE
WHILE SHOWING OFF
MY BEAUTIFUL FORM,
I'M SURE
IT WILL PLEASE HANABISHI-SAMA!
( grunting )
NOW TO SHOW MY FORM.
- MAYU-CHAN?
- I HAVE TO GET A STRIKE
FOR HANABISHI-SAMA.
( grunting )
( panting )
AAH!
( panting continues )
( whimpering )
- DON'T SWEAT IT, MAYU-CHAN.
- ( grunting )
MY FINGERS, MY ARMS,
MY HIPS.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT THERE,
MAYU-CHAN?
WE DID BOWL THREE GAMES.
- I-- I'M PERFECTLY FINE.
DON'T BE DISCOURAGED.
YOU HAVE TO DO YOUR BEST, MAYU.
SO, HANABISHI-SAMA,
WHERE WOULD YOU LIKE-- OH!
- ( cracking )
- UH, MAYU-CHAN, DID YOU HEAR
A LOUD CRACK JUST NOW?
- NO, IT WAS PROBABLY NOTHING.
( laughs nervously )
- Kaoru: THIS PLACE
WAS JUST FINISHED LAST MONTH.
I WANTED TO COME HERE
AT LEAST ONCE.
- Mayu: OH, IS THAT SO?
- WHAT KIND OF GAMES
DO YOU LIKE?
- OH, I DON'T PLAY VIDEO GAMES
MUCH.
- OH, YOU REALLY DON'T?
THEN MAYBE WE SHOULD HAVE
JUST GONE TO SOME OTHER PLACE.
- NOT AT ALL.
I DON'T MIND COMING HERE.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO PLAY VIDEO GAMES WELL.
BUT IF PLAYING THEM
MAKES HIM HAPPY, THEN--
- ( camera shutter clicking )
- Man: WHOA!
- Man #2: LOOK AT THAT.
- ( laughing )
- ( groans )
HUH?
- WHICH ONE WOULD YOU LIKE?
VANILLA OR CHOCOLATE?
- UH, LET'S SEE.
UH, WHY DON'T YOU PICK
WHICHEVER ONE YOU LIKE FIRST.
- HUH?
- ( laughs )
- MMM.
- AFTER WE FINISH OUR ICE CREAM,
WHERE WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO?
OH, THE PARK.
- YEAH.
MAYU-CHAN,
LET'S RIDE THAT.
- HUH?
- OH, HOLD ON.
- MMM?
HERE, YOU SHOULD
CLEAN YOUR SEAT.
- BUT--
- YOU DON'T WANT TO GET YOUR
DRESS DIRTY, RIGHT?
MAYU-CHAN, LOOK,
THE SUNSET'S GORGEOUS.
MMM.
- UH, HANABISHI-SAMA?
- HUH?
- DID YOU--
UM, DID YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME
WITH ME TODAY?
SOMEHOW IT FEELS
LIKE I'VE DONE NOTHING
BUT INCONVENIENCE YOU
THIS ENTIRE TIME.
- I HAD A GOOD TIME.
- HMM?
HONESTLY?
- YEAH.
BUT DID YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME,
MAYU-CHAN?
- UH...
- IT LOOKED LIKE YOU WERE
KIND OF FORCING YOURSELF.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT WHAT I WANT.
UH...
- I-- I WANTED TO PLEASE YOU,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
AND YET
I DIDN'T REALLY KNOW HOW TO.
I'M SORRY.
- MAYU-CHAN.
- I'M SO SORRY.
- IT'S KIND OF AMAZING.
- HMM?
- THE TWO OF US ALONE IN A
RESTAURANT THIS BIG, I MEAN.
- WELL, IT'S BECAUSE
THIS RESTAURANT
BELONGS TO THE MIYUKI GROUP.
- RESERVING A PLACE LIKE THIS
ISN'T SOMETHING
YOU EXPERIENCE VERY OFTEN.
OH, BUT I GUESS
IT'S NOT SO UNUSUAL FOR YOU.
HEY, MAYU-CHAN, WHAT EXACTLY
IS IT THAT YOU LIKE DOING?
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THE THING
NO ONE CAN BEAT YOU AT?
THE ONE THING
THAT YOU'RE BEST AT?
- WHAT I'M BEST AT?
I DON'T HAVE ANY SUCH THING.
- REALLY?
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
ANYTHING SPECIAL.
ISN'T THERE ANYTHING
YOU'VE KEPT DOING TILL NOW,
ANYTHING
YOU'VE NEVER STOPPED DOING?
- I HONESTLY DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
LIKE THAT.
HUH?
- HUH?
THE PIANO?
MAYU-CHAN, YOU CAN PLAY?
- UH, YES, I CAN.
- HOW LONG
HAVE YOU BEEN PLAYING?
- WHEN I WAS FIVE,
MY PARENTS BOUGHT ME A PIANO.
- WOW.  AND YOU'VE BEEN PLAYING
EVER SINCE THEN?
- YES.
- YOU LIKE THE PIANO, DON'T YOU?
- HUH?
- IF YOU HADN'T LIKED IT,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE KEPT PLAYING.
I'D LOVE TO HEAR.
- IT'S NOTHING EXTRAORDINARY.
- I'D STILL LOVE TO HEAR.
- ( playing up-tempo song )
- HANABISHI-SAMA IS SMILING.
HE IS HAPPY.
I'VE BEEN ABLE TO DO MY BEST
BECAUSE HANABISHI-SAMA
WAS THERE FOR ME.
I WAS ABLE TO FORGET
ALL MY SORROW
WHEN I REMEMBERED
WHAT HE DID FOR ME.
BUT I WASN'T ABLE
TO REPAY HIM.
I NEVER HAD THE OPPORTUNITY.
BUT TODAY
I'VE MADE HIM HAPPY.
I WAS FINALLY ABLE
TO REPAY HIM,
IF ONLY JUST A LITTLE.
FINALLY.
- Kaoru: THANKS FOR TODAY.
IT WAS FUN.
- Mayu:
NO, THANK YOU, HANABISHI-SAMA.
TODAY WAS VERY VERY ENJOYABLE.
- REALLY?  I'M GLAD.
- ( stomach growls )
- Both: HMM?
- ( stomach growling )
- Both: HUH?
( both laughing )
- WELL, WE DIDN'T EAT EARLIER,
AFTER ALL.
- I'M SO SORRY.
THAT WAS MY FAULT.
- IT'S OKAY.
FORGET ABOUT IT.
WE MIGHT MAKE IT.
- HUH?
- IT'S NOT A HIGH-CLASS
RESTAURANT OR ANYTHING,
BUT I KNOW A PLACE NEARBY
WHERE WE CAN
GET A REALLY GREAT DINNER.
LET'S GO THERE.
- OKAY!
- Kaoru: I'M HOME!
- HUH?  THEN THE PLACE
WITH GOOD FOOD WAS--
- MM-HMM.
FOOD'S A LOT BETTER
WHEN WE ALL EAT TOGETHER.
- ( giggles )
YES, THAT'S CERTAINLY TRUE.
- OH, HI!
WELCOME BACK, MISS MAYU.
- WHAT?
YOU'RE BACK AGAIN?
- HA! I WAS INVITED BY
HANABISHI-SAMA TONIGHT,
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW.
- WHAT?!
- ( blows raspberries )
- HEY, SO HOW WAS YOUR DATE
TODAY, GUYS?
- HUH?
- YOU HAVE TO TELL ME!
- WELL, NATURALLY...
( giggles )
IT WAS A WONDERFUL DAY, WASN'T
IT THOUGH, HANABISHI-SAMA?
- AAH! GET AWAY FROM HIM,
YOU LITTLE BRAT, NOW!
- Mayu: I DON'T THINK SO.
- WELCOME HOME,
KAORU-SAMA, MISS MAYU.
- WE'RE BACK NOW.
AOI-CHAN, ACTUALLY,
WE, UH, KIND OF
DIDN'T HAVE DINNER YET.
- THANK GOODNESS.
THEN THE TABLE IS SET
JUST RIGHT.
- Mayu: AH, THIS ALL LOOKS
SO DELICIOUS.
- Tina: HEY, HOLD ON, MAYU!
DON'T JUST GO SIT
NEXT TO KAORU!
- Mayu: OH,
BUT THIS IS THE GUEST SEAT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
GUEST SEAT?!
THAT'S WHERE I USUALLY SIT!
- HEY, STOP!
- Kaoru: WELL, HEY, TINA--
- Chika: OH, COME ON ALREADY,
MISS TINA!
- Taeko: WOULD YOU
PLEASE STOP THAT, TINA-SENPAI?
- Tina:
AW, SHUT UP, ALL OF YOU!
MOVE IT, MAYU!
- Miss Miyabi: MISS TINA!
SIT DOWN.
- YES, MA'AM.
- ( Mayu giggling )
- Aoi: WELL THEN, EVERYONE?
- All: THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD!
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Miss Miyabi:
SIR KAORU, ONE'S LIFE
CAN BE BOTH
PROSPEROUS AND MEANINGFUL.
BUT IT BECOMES THAT WAY
THROUGH TIRELESS EFFORT.
- OKAY.
- YES, IT IS.
FOR EXAMPLE,
LIKE THIS CHATEAU MARGAUX.
- YOU MEAN THIS EMPTY BOTTLE?
- WHAT?!  THE WINE
THAT I SET ASIDE IS--
- Kaoru: ON THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "AI YORI AOSHI: ENISHI,
JOURNEY."
LIFE IS LIKE A BOTTLE
OF RED WINE.
IT'S SOUR AND BITTERSWEET!
- ( bell dings )
- Miss Miyabi: THE CHEESE TOO?!