- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- MR. HANABISHI!
HOLD ON!
HELLO, DO YOU HAVE
SOME TIME TO SPARE?
- PROFESSOR ITSUKI.
- SO HOW'S IT GOING?
WHAT WE DISCUSSED
THE OTHER DAY, IS IT CLEAR?
- HUH?
- YOUR DILIGENCE IN HELPING ME
WITH PAPERS IS GOOD AND ALL,
BUT IT'S ALSO IMPORTANT
FOR YOU TO MOVE FORWARD
AND INSURE
A FUTURE FOR YOURSELF.
- I KNOW.
I'M STILL THINKING THINGS OVER.
- WELL, I'LL TRY
TO HELP YOU OUT,
AS MUCH AS I CAN,
AT LEAST.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- SURE.  I HAVE
HIGH EXPECTATIONS OF YOU,
SO KEEP UP THE GOOD
WORK THERE.
- YES SIR.
- OH NO NO NO.
THE REASON I INVITED
YOU HERE WASN'T TO SAY THAT.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO GIVE YOU A LECTURE.
HERE.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- JUST SOMETHING I GOT
FROM AN ACQUAINTANCE OF MINE.
YOU'RE ALWAYS HELPING ME OUT
WITH PROJECTS AND SUCH,
SO THIS IS A THANK YOU.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AND TAKE
YOUR GIRLFRIEND THERE?
- HUH?
- ( boat horn toots )
- Aoi: WOW.
IT'S NICE HERE, KAORU-SAMA.
THE AIR IS SO FRESH.
- YEAH.
- I'M SO HAPPY WE WERE
ABLE TO GO OUT,
JUST THE TWO OF US.
- IT WAS GOOD TIMING, WASN'T IT?
- WITH LADY AOI?
- TH-- THAT IS...
- WELL, I'LL AGREE TO IT.
- ( camera clicking )
- MS. TINA IS
ON A PHOTOGRAPHY TRIP
WITH THOSE FRIENDS
OF YOURS FROM COLLEGE,
MS. TAEKO AND MS. CHIKA ARE
PUTTING THINGS AWAY
AT THE BEACH HOUSE,
AND LADY AOI DOES SEEM
A BIT BORED RIGHT NOW.
- SO THEN
TOMORROW'S OKAY, RIGHT?
- ( sighs ) SIR KAORU.
- YES?
- I ASK THAT
YOU PLEASE BE SURE
TO TAKE GOOD CARE OF LADY AOI
DURING YOUR OUTING.
THE BEST OF CARE.
- UH, SURE.
- OH MY, HOW WONDERFUL!
- ( both laugh )
- ( jazz music playing )
- Aoi: THIS IS CHINATOWN,
ISN'T IT?
I'VE NEVER BEEN HERE BEFORE.
- ACTUALLY,
IT'S MY FIRST TIME, TOO.
- BY THE WAY,
I THINK
I'M A LITTLE HUNGRY NOW.
- ME TOO.
WE'VE COME ALL THIS WAY,
SO WE NEED TO ENJOY CHINATOWN
TO THE FULLEST, RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- I MAY SAY THAT,
BUT A REALLY EXPENSIVE PLACE
WOULD BE--
- KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
- OH.  AOI-CHAN,
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- I'D LIKE TO EAT ONE OF THOSE,
IF IT'S ALL RIGHT WITH YOU.
- HUH?
CHINESE ROAST PORK BUNS?
- THAT'S RIGHT. ( laughs )
- OH MY.
IT'S SO HUGE.
- YEAH, IT REALLY IS.
- I COULDN'T POSSIBLY EAT
THIS ENTIRE THING BY MYSELF.
WHY DON'T YOU AND I
EAT IT TOGETHER, KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
OH, BUT I THOUGHT--
- I'D REALLY LIKE US
TO EAT IT TOGETHER.
- MM-HMM.
- HERE YOU GO.
- SURE.
- IT'S DELICIOUS.
- THE NEXT TIME WE COME,
I HOPE I CAN AFFORD LOTS
OF DELICIOUS FOOD
FOR AOI-CHAN TO EAT.
- IT'S IMPORTANT TO MOVE FORWARD
AND INSURE A FUTURE
FOR YOURSELF.
- MY FUTURE.  HMM.
- ( crowd gasps )
- HUH?
- WHAT COULD THAT BE?
- MAYBE THEY'RE RECORDING
FOR A TV SHOW.
SHOULD WE GO TAKE A LOOK?
- SURE!
- ( "Wedding March" playing )
- ( applause )
- A WEDDING, HUH?
- LOVELY.
- AOI-CHAN WILL LOOK
REALLY BEAUTIFUL, TOO,
WHEN SHE'S ALL DRESSED UP
IN HER WEDDING GOWN.
HMM?
I WONDER...
IF I'LL REALLY BE ABLE
TO MAKE AOI-CHAN HAPPY.
I WONDER
IF WE'LL BE LIKE THIS COUPLE
AND BE ABLE TO GET
A LOT OF PEOPLE'S BLESSINGS.
- ( footsteps )
- ( gasps )
- SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
- NO PROBLEM.
- KAORU-SAMA,
I GOT THIS FOR YOU.
- OH, THANKS.
UH, YOU DIDN'T
GET ONE YOURSELF, AOI-CHAN?
- I THOUGHT WE COULD--
WELL, THAT IS,
I THOUGHT WE COULD SHARE
THE ICE CREAM TOGETHER
IF THAT'S ALL RIGHT WITH YOU.
- OH, SURE.
- ( chuckles )
- ( kids laughing )
- LET'S HURRY BACK!
- OKAY!
- WE WERE AROUND THAT AGE
WHEN YOU AND I MET
FOR THE FIRST TIME...
- HUH?
- ...AND YOU'VE BEEN THINKING
OF ME THE WHOLE TIME SINCE THEN.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- ( laughing )
- KAORU-SAMA.
- HUH?
- CONTINUING TO THINK
OF ONLY ONE PERSON
REQUIRES A LOT OF COURAGE.
- HUH?
- I WORRIED A GREAT DEAL
ABOUT WHAT I WOULD DO
IF THE ONE I CAME TO LOVE
GREW TO HATE ME
FOR WHATEVER REASON
THERE COULD BE.
THAT FEELING CONTINUED
TO DISTURB ME EVERY DAY.
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
DURING THAT TIME,
ALL OF THE OTHER FEELINGS I HAD,
I THREW AWAY,
AND I FILLED MYSELF UP
WITH ALL THE FEELINGS
INSIDE OF ME
THAT I HAD FOR YOU.
WHEN I DID THAT,
I THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
"I'M ABLE TO THINK
ABOUT KAORU-SAMA THIS MUCH."
I THOUGHT, "I'M ABLE TO LOVE
KAORU-SAMA THIS MUCH."
JUST BEING ABLE
TO LOVE YOU--
THAT ALONE
MAKES ME HAPPY BEYOND WORDS.
THAT'S WHY...
I ALWAYS THOUGHT OF YOU.
THAT'S WHY I WAS
ALWAYS ABLE TO THINK OF YOU
WHOLE-HEARTEDLY.
KAORU-SAMA...
PLEASE LET ME LOVE YOU...
FOREVER AND EVER,
AS I ALWAYS HAVE.
- AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- SHOULD WE...
STAY HERE FOR THE NIGHT?
- ( gasps )
- ( echoing ) SHOULD WE...
STAY HERE FOR THE NIGHT?
- WHAT SHOULD I DO?
STAYING THE NIGHT--
WOULD THAT BE ALL RIGHT?
BUT STAYING
THE NIGHT MEANS--
- THANKS FOR WAITING, AOI-CHAN.
- ( gasps )
- I'M ALL FINISHED
CHECKING US INTO THE HOTEL NOW.
- OH!  OKAY, GOOD JOB.
THANK YOU
FOR ALL YOUR HARD WORK.
- I'M SORRY...
- HUH?
- ...FOR SUGGESTING SOMETHING
LIKE THIS OUT OF THE BLUE.
- OH, IT'S FINE.
I'M PERFECTLY ALL RIGHT
WITH THIS AFTER ALL.
- I RECEIVED SOME VOUCHERS
FOR THIS PLACE
FROM PROFESSOR ITSUKI.
I WASN'T EXACTLY SURE ABOUT
WHAT I OUGHT TO DO WITH THEM,
BUT I STILL WANT TO SPEND
SOME MORE TIME ALONE WITH YOU,
AOI-CHAN, SO...
- KAORU-SAMA.
WOW!
- THIS ROOM IS A LOT BETTER
THAN I THOUGHT IT'D BE.
- KAORU-SAMA, LOOK OUTSIDE.
- WOW.
IT'S REALLY PRETTY.
- YES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS FOOD CAME WITH THE ROOM.
- IT LOOKS DELICIOUS,
DOESN'T IT?
- SURE DOES.
WELL THEN, SHOULD WE EAT?
- OF COURSE.
THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD.
OH.  OVER THERE.
- HUH?
- THAT'S A CLOCK, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH, IT IS.
- I THOUGHT IT WAS
A REGULAR FERRIS WHEEL.
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING
THAT DOESN'T CHANGE, IS THERE?
- WHAT?
- THIS MOMENT RIGHT NOW
ONLY EXISTS HERE.
A DIFFERENT TIME
WILL BE MOVING TOMORROW.
THE SAKURABA MANSION
IS THE SAME, ISN'T IT?
WE ALL LIVE
UNDER THE SAME ROOF.
WE'RE ALWAYS TOGETHER.
EVERY DAY IS SO ENJOYABLE,
BUT SOMEDAY THAT WILL END.
IT'S SAD TO THINK SO,
BUT I BELIEVE IT'S THE
REALITY I HAVE TO ACCEPT,
AS MUCH AS I LIKE
HOW THINGS ARE.
- AOI-CHAN.
- ( chuckles )
THAT WAS DELICIOUS.
- IT WAS. THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR DINNER.
- WELL THEN...
AOI-CHAN, WAIT HERE
FOR JUST A MOMENT, OKAY?
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'LL JUST BE GONE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE
TO GIVE MS. MIYABI A CALL.
- OH MY GOODNESS!
I COMPLETELY FORGOT THAT
WE HAVEN'T CONTACTED MS. MIYABI!
I FIGURED THAT CALLING HER
AFTER WE FINISHED DINNER
WOULD BE FINE.
- OH, IN THAT CASE,
I'LL GO CALL HER.
- IT'S OKAY.
I'M THE ONE
WHO INVITED YOU HERE,
SO LET ME TALK TO HER.
- KAORU-SAMA, I--
- ( door opens )
- OKAY, I'LL BE BACK
IN A LITTLE WHILE.
- ( sighs )
- MS. MIYABI, I'M SO SORRY.
I WAS JUST ENJOYING MYSELF.
I WONDER
IF HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
IF HE SAYS
WE'RE STAYING THE NIGHT.
- SPENDING THE NIGHT IS
COMPLETELY UNACCEPTABLE!
UNDERSTOOD?!
- ( cries out )
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
- ( ringing )
( shower running )
( shower stops )
- KAORU-SAMA IS REALLY LATE.
I'M SURE MS. MIYABI
MUST'VE GOTTEN ANGRY AT HIM.
( sighs )
- ( sighs )
- I'D LIKE TO ADMIRE
THIS NIGHTLINE A BIT MORE
WITH KAORU-SAMA
BEFORE WE GO HOME.
I'D LIKE TO BE AFFECTIONATE
A LITTLE LONGER.
- ( door opens )
- I'M BACK NOW.
- KAORU-SAMA!
- WHAT'S WRONG, AOI-CHAN?
- I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
SHE GOT ANGRY AT YOU
BECAUSE OF ME, DIDN'T SHE?
- WHAT?
- IT'S MY FAULT.
I'M NOT PROPERLY
TAKING CARE OF THINGS,
SO I'VE CAUSED YOU PROBLEMS.
- ACTUALLY, AOI-CHAN...
- YES?
- I GOT HER PERMISSION
TO STAY TONIGHT.
- HUH?
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
IS THAT REALLY THE TRUTH,
KAORU-SAMA?
- MM-HMM.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
MS. MIYABI AGREED.
- SHE WAS AGAINST IT
AT FIRST...
- I THOUGHT SO.
- ...BUT I TALKED WITH HER.
- Miyabi:
I UNDERSTAND.
I'LL PERMIT YOU TO STAY OUT.
- Thank you so much,
Ms. Miyabi.
- PLEASE TAKE CARE
OF LADY AOI.
I WILL.
- YOU TALKED?
- YEAH.
AND WE SPOKE ABOUT YOU,
AOI-CHAN.
- WHAT?  YOU HAD
A DISCUSSION ABOUT ME?
- YEAH.
WHENEVER I SIT DOWN
AND THINK ABOUT MY FUTURE,
THE FIRST THING
I ALWAYS CONSIDER
IS WHERE YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO FIND YOUR HAPPINESS
IN WHATEVER LIFE
WE MAKE FOR OURSELVES.
I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT SOME WAY
TO RETURN YOUR FEELINGS,
THE FEELINGS OF SOMEONE
WHO'S CONTINUED TO THINK OF ME
EVER SINCE
WE WERE FIRST ENGAGED.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT HOW I CAN MAKE YOU HAPPY.
AND THEN I REALIZED...
AOI-CHAN,
YOUR TRUE HAPPINESS
ISN'T FOUND
WITH THE HANABISHIS
OR THE SAKURABAS.
I REALIZE THAT THE PLACE WHERE
YOUR HAPPINESS LIES IS HERE,
WITHIN ME.
I'M SURE THAT YOU'RE
INSIDE MY HAPPINESS
AND THAT I'M ALSO INSIDE
YOUR HAPPINESS.
IN THAT WAY
I WOULD IMAGINE
THAT OUR HAPPINESS
IS THE TWO OF US BEING
IN EACH OTHER'S ARMS
AND NEVER LETTING GO.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- THAT'S WHY RIGHT NOW
I BELIEVE
THAT I HAVE TO DO MY BEST
AS I MOVE FORWARD IN LIFE,
SO THAT I'M ABLE
TO SUPPORT YOU, AOI-CHAN.
I HAVE TO RETURN
YOUR FEELINGS,
THE FEELINGS OF THE ONE
WHO'S LOVED ME
EVER SINCE
WE FIRST MET AS FIANCES...
TO BE WITH YOU...
TO DO MY BEST.
I WONDERED
IF THAT MIGHT BE THE WAY
THAT I COULD
MAKE YOU HAPPY, AOI-CHAN.
- ( crying )
- AOI-CHAN?
- KAORU-SAMA.
YOUR THOUGHTS
FOR ME MAKE ME...
SO HAPPY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
KAORU-SAMA.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- PLEASE DON'T CRY.
- KAORU-SAMA.
KAORU-SAMA.
I TRULY LOVE YOU.
- AND I DO TOO, AOI-CHAN.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
- HMM?
- TINA.
KAORU, MS. LANDLORD!
I'M BACK
FROM THE PHOTO SHOOT!
- WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I'M ROASTING SWEET POTATOES.
- ( crackles )
- AH!
- Chika: THIS IS BAD!
- HUH?
- IT'S FIRE!
WHAT THE...?
- HEY, YOU GUYS!
WELCOME HOME!
- WELCOME.
- WELCOME BACK HOME.
- I GOTTA SAY,
YOU TWO PICKED
A PRETTY GOOD TIME
TO COME HOME.
- WHAT?  WHY?  OH!
ROASTED SWEET POTATOES?
- UH-HUH.
- THEN I THINK IT'S ONLY RIGHT
FOR US TO ROAST
THE SOUVENIRS THAT WE BROUGHT
FROM THE BEACH HOUSE, TOO.
- ( laughs ) YEAH!
- SOUVENIRS?
- RIGHT, CUT AND DRIED
HORSE MACKEREL.
- ( groans )
- YOU WANT TO ROAST MACKEREL
WITH SWEET POTATOES?
- SURE, THAT OUGHT
TO BE DELICIOUS.
THAT'S STRANGE.
I DON'T SEE THEM.
THEY'RE ALL GONE.
- WHAT?
I'M SURE THEY HAVE
TO BE AT THE BOTTOM.
- Mayu: OH!  OH NO!
- HUH?
- SOMETHING'S ON FIRE!  OH.
MARSHMALLOWS ARE SCRUMPTIOUS
WITH THE OUTSIDE TOASTED
AND THE INSIDE GOOEY.
- THIS BONFIRE HERE IS
FOR SWEET POTATOES ONLY!
- THEN WHY EXACTLY IS THIS
DRIED HORSE MACKEREL HERE?
- WELL, OKAY,
THIS MATCH GOES TO MAYU.
- THE FIRE'S CHOCK-FULL
OF SWEET TATERS AND FISHIES.
IT WON'T FIT!
- HONESTLY, WOULD YOU MIND NOT
SAYING SUCH CHILDISH THINGS?
- WHO'S A CHILD?
BESIDES, MARSHMALLOWS ARE
BETTER UNTOASTED
IN THE FIRST PLACE!
- THEY'RE MORE DELECTABLE WHEN
THEY ARE TOASTED.
- ( scoffs )
HEY, MS. LANDLORD,
THE BRAT IS
BEING MEAN TO ME!
- ( laughs )
- ( crying )
- SHALL I MAKE
SOME TEA, EVERYONE?
- YEAH.
- YEAH!
- ABSOLUTELY!
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- AUNTIE AOI, WHAT ARE
WE STUDYING TODAY?
- ( laughs )
IT'S JAPANESE HOT SPRINGS!
- YAY!
HOT SPRINGS, HOT SPRINGS!
- ( speaking quickly )
A HOT SPRING SPA UTILIZES
BOTH WARM
AND MINERAL WATER OBTAINED
FROM SUBTERRANEAN SOURCES
AND THE STEAM
THAT IS CREATED...
( speaking very quickly )
- ON THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "AI YORI AOSHI: ENISHI,"
"BATHROBE"!
- KAORUA-KUN,
ARE YOU PAYING ATTENTION?
- YES!
- THEN I'LL CONTINUE.
AMONG THE MANY DIFFERENT TYPES
OF HOT SPRING SPAS...