- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
TWO, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
- ( sighs )
- SERIOUSLY THOUGH, GUYS.
SUMMER'S ALMOST OVER NOW,
YOU KNOW,
AND THE SENIOR MEMBERS
OF THE SWIMMING CLUB
HAVEN'T SHOWN THEIR FACES
EVEN ONCE IN PRACTICE.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
OR IS IT...
THAT THERE REALLY AREN'T
ANY OTHER MEMBERS
IN THIS CLUB BESIDES US?
WELL, LOOKING BACK,
WE HAVEN'T HAD ANY NEW MEMBERS
SINCE I JOINED UP.
I'M SURE THAT THEY'RE ALL JUST
VERY BUSY WITH THEIR STUDIES.
THIS IS
A PREP SCHOOL AFTER ALL.
- BUT YOU KNOW...
( giggles )
WE HAVE THE POOL
ALL TO OURSELVES EVERY DAY.
THAT MAKES ME HAPPY,
EVEN SO.
- ( sighs )
WELL, THAT IS TRUE.
ALL RIGHT.  GUESS THAT'S
OUR CUE TO GET SWIMMING!
- YAY!
- WAIT UP, CHIKA!
- UH...
- WAIT UP ALREADY!
- NO!  NO WAY!
- ( both laugh )
- THE WATER
REALLY DOES FEEL NICE.
- ( both gasp )
- ( giggles )
- MAN, NOTHING BEATS THIS.
- HUH?  CHIZURU-CHAN?
- ( cries out )
- SHE'S DROWNING AGAIN.
CHIZURU!
- CHIZURU-CHAN!
- ( Chizuru coughing )
I THINK I SWALLOWED
WAY TOO MUCH WATER AGAIN.
- ARE YOU OKAY, CHIZURU-CHAN?
- JEEZ. YOU STILL HAVEN'T GOTTEN
ANY BETTER AT ALL, CHIZURU.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- ( sighs )
WE SURE SWAM A LOT TODAY.
HUH?
- WHAT IS THIS?
- LET'S SEE HERE.
IT'S THE DISTRICT
SWIMMING COMPETITION?
- "RELAY TEAM MEMBERS
CHIKA MINAZUKI,
NATSUKI KOMIYA,
CHIZURU AIZAWA.
THAT IS ALL.
THE SWIMMING CLUB PRESIDENT"?
- UH...
- SO THE SENIOR MEMBERS
OF THE SWIMMING CLUB
REALLY DO EXIST.
- BUT I WONDER
WHO THE CLUB'S PRESIDENT IS.
- IF THEY CAME ALL THE WAY HERE,
THEY COULD'VE AT LEAST
PRACTICED WITH US.
- BUT STILL, WE'RE ALL GONNA BE
IN A SWIMMING COMPETITION!
- THERE WAS A POINT
TO PRACTICING EVERY DAY.
- ALL RIGHT!
LET'S KEEP ON SWIMMING!
- YEAH!
- UH...
- UH, CHIZURU-CHAN?
- I WONDER IF IT'S OKAY
FOR SOMEONE WHO CAN'T SWIM
LIKE ME TO BE
IN THE COMPETITION.
- I DON'T THINK
THAT IT'S ALLOWED, USUALLY.
- IT'S DEFINITELY BETTER
IF YOU CAN SWIM, YOU KNOW?
- YES, OF COURSE.
WHAT'LL I DO?
IF YOU PRACTICE, YOU'LL
DEFINITELY BE ABLE TO SWIM.
AND WE'LL BE ROOTING
FOR YOU, TOO.  RIGHT?
- YEAH, YOU BET!
- SO LET'S ALL DO
OUR BEST, OKAY?
- CHIKA-CHAN.
NATSUKI-CHAN.
- ( giggles )
- BY COMBINING
THE MARRIAGE REGISTRATION
AND THE ONLY-DAUGHTER CARD,
I WILL SUMMON FORTH
THE SON-IN-LAW.
SON-IN-LAW!
USE THE SLENDER SHOULDER BEAM!
- I AM NOT AN UNDERDOG!
- YES!  ALL RIGHT!
ANOTHER VICTORY FOR TINA!
( laughs ) I'M ON A
REAL HOT STREAK TODAY!
- UH, I LOST AGAIN.
( sighs )
- COME ON, KAORU, LET'S PLAY ONE
MORE TIME. WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- ( sighs )
- ( clatters )
- ( water splashes )
- HUH?
- OW.  OW.
- WHAT THE HECK
HAPPENED HERE, TAE?
- OH, I STUMBLED OVER
THE BUCKET. THAT'S ALL.
( sighs ) WHAT THE HECK DO
YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING, TAEKO?
AND I STILL HAVE TO GO DO ALL
THE SHOPPING AFTER THIS, TOO.
MY GOSH,
THE HALLWAY'S TOTALLY SOAKED.
- WHY DON'T I HELP YOU OUT, TAE?
IT'LL GET DONE QUICKER
WITH TWO PEOPLE.
- OH, THANKS SO MUCH,
TINA-SENPAI.
- AH, DON'T MENTION IT.
- I'LL GO BRING
ANOTHER MOP HERE!
- ( humming )
- DID SOMETHING GOOD HAPPEN
TO TINA OR SOMETHING?
SHE'S BEEN PRETTY WOUND UP
LATELY, BUT NOW...
- HEY, BIG BROTHER!
I'M HOME!
- CHIKA-CHAN.
WELCOME HOME.
- HEY, I'VE GOT SOME NEWS
TO TELL YOU ABOUT.
GET THIS. I'M GONNA BE COMPETING
IN A SWIMMING COMPETITION.
- YEAH?
THAT'S PRETTY EXCITING.
CONGRATULATIONS.
- ( laughs ) YAY!
- ( Chizuru splashing,
whimpering )
( breathing heavily )
- ARE YOU OKAY, CHIZURU?
- NO, THAT'S NOT THE WAY,
CHIZURU-CHAN.
YOU'VE GOTTA
FIRST JUMP IN WITH A BOING,
AND THEN YOU PADDLE,
SPLISH-SPLASH!
AND WHEN YOU START
RUNNING SHORT ON AIR,
YOU HUFF-PUFF
AND TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
GOT IT NOW?
- ACTUALLY, CHIKA-CHAN--
- BOING, SPLISH-SPLASH
AND HUFF-PUFF?
HOW CAN SHE GET IT IF YOU'RE
JUST MAKING SOUND EFFECTS?
- OH, YEAH, I GUESS
YOU'RE RIGHT. ( laughs )
- LISTEN, CHIZURU,
THE REASON THAT YOU'RE NOT
GETTING ANY BETTER
AT SWIMMING
IS BECAUSE YOU ALWAYS THINK
THAT YOU CAN'T SWIM.
IT'S THAT KIND
OF BACKWARDS THINKING
THAT KEEPS YOU FROM LEARNING
HOW TO SWIM PROPERLY!
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- THE ACTUAL ACT OF SWIMMING
TAKES SPIRIT AND GUTS.
YOU DON'T NEED MUCH MORE.
SO IF YOU'VE GOT THOSE
AND A POSITIVE ATTITUDE
TOWARDS SWIMMING,
THEN YOU'LL DEFINITELY
BE ABLE TO DO IT!
YOU HAVE MY GUARANTEE
THAT YOU WILL!
- NATSUKI-CHAN.
- COME ON, CHIZURU.
LET'S DO IT AND SWIM
INTO THE SUNSET!
- ( bird caws )
- HUH?  WHAT?
- READY, CHIZURU?
- I'M READY, COACH.
- HUH?
- SEE?
WASN'T THAT EASY?  HUH?
- ( gasps )
- ( whimpers )
- CHIZURU, HANG ON!
- NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
YOU AND I CAN SWIM, BUT--
- SWIMMING AND TEACHING
SOMEONE HOW TO SWIM
ARE TWO DIFFERENT THINGS.
HAVE A COACH AROUND
WHO COULD FOCUS
ON TEACHING CHIZURU
HOW TO SWIM
WOULD BE THE BEST
AND FASTEST SOLUTION.
BUT OUR SWIMMING CLUB
DOESN'T HAVE A COACH.
- OH!  IN THAT CASE,
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
ASK SOMEONE TO BE OUR COACH!
PROBLEM SOLVED!
- THEN YOU'VE GOTTA HAVE
SOMEONE IN MIND WHO CAN BE
OUR COACH, RIGHT, CHIKA?
- HM-MMM.  NOPE.
- THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
- ( sighs )
- EVERYONE,
HOW ABOUT TAKING A LITTLE BREAK?
- WE EVEN BROUGHT YOU SOME OF
THE LANDLORD'S HOMEMADE CAKES!
THEY'RE OUT OF THIS WORLD!
- ARE YOU GETTING THROUGH
YOUR HOMEWORK OKAY?
IF THERE'S ANYTHING
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND,
I CAN HELP OUT.  HUH?
- ( girls sigh )
- HUH?  WHAT'S WRONG, GUYS?
- SO THAT'S HOW IT IS, THEN.
I WISH I COULD HELP
YOU GUYS OUT WITH THIS,
BUT THIS IS
KIND OF OVER MY HEAD.
I CAN SWIM,
BUT NOT WELL ENOUGH
TO BE A SWIM COACH
OR TEACH SOMEBODY ELSE.
- I'M NOT ABLE
TO TEACH PEOPLE EITHER.
- ( laughs evilly )
- All: HUH?
- UH, WHAT IS IT, TINA?
- GLEAM.
YOU CAN LEAVE
EVERYTHING TO ME,
'CAUSE TINA FOSTER IS
THE ANSWER TO ALL YOUR PRAYERS!
- HUH?
- DESPITE WHAT YOU MAY THINK,
I WAS ACTUALLY A
SWIMMING ATHLETE
DURING MY HIGH SCHOOL YEARS.
AND I WAS EVEN A STUDENT ATHLETE
RECORD-HOLDER TO BOOT...
- OH.
- ...AND A PART-TIME JOB
I HELD BACK THEN
WAS AS A SWIMMING SCHOOL
INSTRUCTOR!
- I-- I NEVER KNEW.
- YOU'RE INCREDIBLE, MS. TINA!
- NOW DON'T WORRY ABOUT A THING.
WITH ME AS YOUR COACH,
YOU'RE DEFINITELY
GONNA LEARN HOW TO SWIM!
( laughs )
- AH.  RIGHT.
- ( whistle tweeting )
- ( grunting )
- OKAY, THAT'S IT FOR THE
WARM-UP DRILL! GATHER AROUND.
THERE ISN'T MUCH TIME
UNTIL THE COMPETITION,
SO I'M NOT GONNA
TAKE IT EASY, OKAY?
YOU GUYS BETTER
BE READY FOR THIS.
- RIGHT!
- THERE'S JUST ONE THING.
BEFORE WE START YOUR TRAINING,
THERE'S ONE VERY IMPORTANT THING
THAT CAN'T BE AVOIDED.
- ( all gulp )
- AND THAT IS...
- AND THAT IS...?
- ( laughs evilly )
AND THAT'S THE BREAST CHECK
WE DO EVERY DAY!
- ( yelps, whimpering )
- ( laughs )
YOU'VE STILL GOT ROOM TO GROW,
BUT THEY'RE PRETTY NICE.
ALL RIGHT,
NEXT UP IS CHIKA!
- OKAY.
- WHOO! YOU'RE DEFINITELY TAE'S
COUSIN ALL RIGHT.
I CAN TELL
YOU'RE COMING RIGHT ALONG.
I FORGOT... MS. TINA'S SOMEONE
WHO'S INTO THAT SORT OF THING.
- ( laughing )
- ( gasps )
- NOW IT'S YOUR TURN, CHIZURU!
- ( screams )
- HEY, DON'T RUN AWAY!
- NO!  I'M NOT
INTO THAT KIND OF THING!
- STAY STILL AND TAKE YOUR
BREAST-SQUEEZING LIKE A...
- COME ON!  YOU'VE GOTTA
EXTEND YOUR ARMS MORE!
DON'T BEND YOUR KNEES!
( sighs )
YOU FINALLY MADE IT
TO FIVE METERS.
IF YOU'RE GONNA
BE IN THE RELAY,
THEN YOU'VE GOTTA BE ABLE
TO SWIM A MINIMUM OF 25 METERS.
- ( sighs )
- HEY, CHEER UP, OKAY?
THERE'S STILL SOME TIME
BEFORE THE COMPETITION.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO RUSH THINGS.
- ( whistle tweets )
- TODAY'S PRACTICE IS OVER!
- CHIZURU-CHAN, LET'S GO.
- GO ON... AHEAD.
I'LL BE... RIGHT THERE.
- OH, OKAY.
- CHIZURU.
- HUH?
I KNOW THE COMPETITION'S
NEXT WEEK
AND I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU WANNA RUSH,
BUT IF YOU PUSH TOO HARD,
YOU'LL NEVER GET BETTER.
- UM, THAT'S NOT IT.
- HUH?
- IT'S NOT BECAUSE OF THE
COMPETITION OR ANYTHING.
IT'S BECAUSE I DECIDED
THAT BEFORE THE END
OF THE SUMMER
I'D BE ABLE TO SWIM 25 METERS
NO MATTER WHAT.
THAT'S WHY I WANT
TO SWIM THOSE 25 METERS--
NOT FOR THE COMPETITION
BUT FOR MYSELF.
AFTER ALL, I WANT
TO BE ABLE TO SWIM
WITH CHIKA-CHAN
AND NATSUKI-CHAN.
I UNDERSTAND, AND THE
SUMMER'S NOT OVER JUST YET.
LET'S DO THE BEST WE CAN
TILL THE VERY VERY END
AND LET'S MAKE
THE GREATEST MEMORIES!
- MS. TINA.
- ALL RIGHT, THE EXTRA
TRAINING TIME STARTS NOW!
- I LEAVE MYSELF
IN YOUR CAPABLE HANDS, COACH.
- HEY, YOU'RE BENDING
YOUR KNEES AGAIN.
- UNDERSTOOD, COACH.
- STRAIGHTEN YOUR BACK!
- RIGHT.
- ( jazz music playing )
- CAN I HAVE A MISO PORK
CUTLET BURGER, FRIES
AND AN ORANGE SODA PLEASE?
YOU KNOW...
THERE'S NOTHING
MORE SATISFYING IN THE WORLD...
THAN A NICE MEAL
AFTER A HARD WORKOUT.
HMM?  I'M PAYING
FOR EVERYTHING,
SO WHY DON'T YOU STOP HOLDING
BACK AND EAT UP ALREADY, OKAY?
- THANKS A LOT
FOR THE FOOD, COACH.
- OH, BY THE WAY,
I THINK I SAW--
- I'M JEALOUS.
- HUH?
- HUH?  I WAS
JUST THINKING TO MYSELF
THAT I WISH I COULD'VE SPENT MY
HIGH SCHOOL YEARS HERE IN JAPAN.
IT'D BE LIKE
THE UNIFORM AND ALL.
I THINK THEY'RE CUTE.
AND I KINDA LIKE BEING
JUST LIKE EVERYONE ELSE.
FITTING IN, YOU KNOW?
IF I HAD GONE
TO A JAPANESE HIGH SCHOOL,
WOULD THIS BE
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE?
I WONDER IF I WOULD'VE HAD
FUN TIMES LIKE RIGHT NOW.
- UM, MS. TINA?
- ( crowd cheering )
- WHAT?  THAT TARZAN WOMAN
IS THEIR SWIMMING COACH?
ARE YOU SURE THEY'LL BE FINE,
HANABISHI-SAMA?
- YEAH, THEY'VE ALL GOTTEN
SO MUCH FASTER
AT SWIMMING
AND IT'S REALLY NOTICEABLE.
- LADY AOI?
MS. CHIKA AND THE OTHERS
WILL BE GOING SOON.
- NATSUKI, CHIZURU, CHIKA.
WE'LL BE GOING
WITH THIS ORDER.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
FOR ME TO TEACH YOU.
ALL THAT'S LEFT IS
TO GIVE IT EVERYTHING
AND MAKE SURE YOU
HAVE NO REGRETS.
- OKAY!
- BUT IN THE END,
I NEVER MANAGED TO SWIM 25
METERS EVEN ONCE.
- LET'S DO OUR BEST,
CHIZURU-CHAN.
- YES, LET'S DO OUR BEST.
- We will now begin
the girls' 25-meter relay.
Starters,
please take your mark.
- ( cheering )
- OH, I CAN SEE THEM.
- CHIKA-CHAN!
- WHERE?  WHERE?
- I'LL DO MY BEST.
- COME ON, YOU CAN DO IT!
- ON YOUR MARKS,
GET SET...
- ALL RIGHT,
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE TO TAKE
THE LEAD ON THE FIRST PASS.
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- ( cheering )
- GO, NATSUKI!
BLOW 'EM AWAY!
- LOOK AT THAT.
- WHERE?  WHERE?
- CHIZURU, GO!
- UH, WAIT.
( screams )
- HUH?
- THAT LOOKED PAINFUL.
- OH NO, THE OTHERS
HAVE MANAGED TO PASS HER.
( gasps )
AND AGAIN.
CHIZURU!
GIVE IT YOUR ALL!
- ( woman laughs )
WHAT'S WITH THAT GIRL?
- HOW DID SOMEONE AS SLOW
AS HER GET INTO THIS RELAY?
- OH MAN, IS SHE FOR REAL?
- ( scoffs )
- SILENCE! SILENCE,
SILENCE, SILENCE!
- MS. CHIZURU!
DO YOU BEST OUT THERE!
- GO FOR BROKE,
CHIZURU-CHAN!
- I CAN'T LOSE.
AFTER ALL,
I DECIDED FOR MYSELF
THAT I'D SWIM 25 METERS.
I WILL BE ABLE
TO SWIM THAT DISTANCE
BEFORE THE SUMMER... ENDS.
I WILL BE ABLE
TO SWIM WITH MY FRIENDS.
I WILL, I WILL, I WILL!
- ALL RIGHT!
- CHIZURU!
- YOU DID IT,
CHIZURU-CHAN!
HERE I GO!
CHIZURU-CHAN WORKED SO HARD,
I CAN'T LET US LOSE!
- LOOK, KAORU-SAMA.
- YEAH.
IT LOOKS LIKE CHIKA-CHAN
JUST MIGHT MAKE IT.
CHIKA-CHAN,
YOU CAN DO IT!
- ( yelling )
- ( crowd roars )
- THAT'S TOO BAD.
JUST A BIT MORE
AND WE WOULD'VE WON.
- ( laughs )
EXCEPT MY LEG CRAMPED UP,
SO IT'S ALL MY FAULT THAT OUR
TEAM ENDED UP IN LAST PLACE.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
CHIKA-CHAN?
- BUT YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY
DID YOUR BEST, CHIZURU.
- NOT AT ALL.
- YEAH, REALLY DID WORK HARD.
YOU DID A GREAT JOB AT
SWIMMING THOSE 25 METERS,
YOU LITTLE TUNA GIRL.
- OH, BUT THIS IS
ALL THANKS TO YOU, COACH.
- HM-MMM. THIS HAPPENED
BECAUSE OF ALL YOUR EFFORT.
- MS. TINA.
- OKAY, THEN TO CELEBRATE
YOU REACHING YOUR GOAL...
- HUH?
- ...IT'S TIME FOR YOUR
BREAST CHECK, CHIZURU!
- WHOO-HOO!
YOU MAY BE A SMALL FRY
AND DEAD LAST
WHEN IT COMES TO SWIMMING,
BUT YOU'RE FIRST
WHEN IT COMES TO BOOBIES!
- HEY, YOU GUYS!
- OH, IT'S CHIKA'S BOYFRIEND.
- I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
HE'S NOT.  OW!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- PLEASE DON'T PUSH YOURSELF.
IS YOUR LEG OKAY,
CHIKA-CHAN?
- YEAH.
- ( chattering )
- WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE I'VE MADE
YET ANOTHER PRECIOUS MEMORY.
I NEED TO MAKE EVEN MORE.
MORE HAPPY MEMORIES
WITH EVERYONE.
IT'S ALREADY AUTUMN,
ISN'T IT?
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- WHERE EXACTLY CAN
KAORU-SAMA'S HAPPINESS BE FOUND?
MY HAPPINESS IS RIGHT HERE.
WHEN I CAN'T SEE HIM,
AND WHEN I'M WITH HIM--
MY HAPPINESS, YES,
IS WITHIN KAORU-SAMA.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE OF "AI
YORI AOSHI: ENISHI," "WHITE."
WHEN I THINK OF KAORU-SAMA,
THAT ALONE IS ENOUGH
TO MAKE ME HAPPY.