- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( knife chopping )
- I'M BACK.
- OH, KAORU-SAMA!
WELCOME HOME.
YOU'RE EARLY.
- UH, YEAH.
WHAT THE-- WHAT AM I DOING
IN A BUSINESS SUIT?
THIS-- THIS SITUATION.
COULD IT BE?!
THAT AOI-CHAN AND I ARE MARRIED
AND WE'RE HUSBAND AND WIFE NOW?
THAT'S IT, RIGHT?
AOI-CHAN?
- YES.
- SO THAT MEANS
THIS IS...
A DREAM?!
- IS THERE ANYTHING
AT ALL WRONG?
BECAUSE FOR SOME REASON,
KAORU-SAMA,
YOU SEEM STRANGE TODAY.
( giggles )
- ( laughs )
- KAORU-SAMA, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HAVE DINNER
OR WOULD YOU RATHER
TAKE A BATH?
- UM, WELL, UM...
MAYBE DINNER.
- OH!
YOU WANT IT NOW?
- YEAH.
- THEN PLEASE WAIT
WHILE I GET READY.
ALL DONE.
PLEASE EAT AS MUCH
AS YOU DESIRE.
- UH, "PLEASE EAT AS MUCH
AS YOU DESIRE"?
WHAT?!
YOU MEAN DINNER'S--
- KAORU-SAMA,
IF YOU DON'T HURRY UP
AND EAT,
YOUR DINNER WILL GET COLD.
- THIS-- THIS IS A DREAM.
IT'S GOTTA BE.
IF THIS IS A DREAM,
I DON'T WANT TO WAKE UP!
AOI-CHAN!
- ( Aoi laughs )
- KAORU-SAMA,
PLEASE, I ASK YOU,
EAT AS GENTLY AS POSSIBLE.
IF YOU DON'T,
I FEAR I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN TAKE IT.
- AOI-CHAN!
- Aoi:
PLEASE DON'T, KAORU-SAMA.
- MMM.
ISN'T IT OKAY? WE ARE HUSBAND
AND WIFE, AFTER ALL.
HUH?
AAH. AAH!
WHAT THE--
AOI-CHAN, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY FUTON?
- OH, I-- I APOLOGIZE
FOR STARTLING YOU SO.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
WELL, I JUST WANTED
TO SPEND A LITTLE TIME
IN THE SAME FUTON WITH YOU,
KAORU-SAMA.
- HUH?
- BUT THEN SUDDENLY--
- OH.
AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- Taeko: TINA-SENPAI!
TIME TO WAKE UP!
- ( knocking )
YOUR BREAKFAST
IS GETTING COLD.
- Tina:
COME ON, JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
- PLEASE HURRY UP
AND WAKE UP!
- ( both chuckling )
- I APOLOGIZE,
KAORU-SAMA.
BUT I THINK I HAD BETTER
GO AHEAD OF YOU.
- UH, YEAH.
- ( door closes )
- ( sighs )
- All: THANKS FOR THE FOOD!
- ( plates clattering )
- TENNIS?
- YEAH.
IT'LL BE ON THE NEXT
OPEN-EVENT SCHOOL FIELD DAY.
IT WAS THAT OR SOCCER.
- WHOA!
ARE YOU A GOOD TENNIS PLAYER,
CHIKA?
- ( laughs )
I STINK.
THAT'S WHY I'D LIKE
TO GET SOME PRACTICE.
- Kaoru: TENNIS, HUH?
I'D LOVE TO PLAY SOME TENNIS
WITH AOI-CHAN.
THAT'D BE FUN.
- SPEAKING OF TENNIS,
MISS MIYABI IS QUITE
THE EXPERIENCED PLAYER.
- YOU ARE, MISS MANAGER?
- THAT'S INCREDIBLE,
MISS MIYABI.
GEE, WHAT CAN'T YOU DO?
- I MUST ADMIT THAT I HAVEN'T
HELD A RACKET IN SOME TIME.
BUT IF YOU'D LIKE ME TO,
I WILL JOIN YOU
WHEN YOU PRACTICE.
- REALLY?
ALL RIGHT!
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
MISS MIYABI!
- YOU WANT TO PLAY TENNIS TOO,
KAORU?
- HUH?  OH, SURE.
- ALL RIGHT!
THEN I GUESS THAT SETTLES THAT.
WE'RE HOLDING
A TENNIS TOURNAMENT TODAY!
- YEAH!
- ( laughing )
- Taeko: THEN WE'LL HAVE
TO PACK SOME LUNCHES.
- Aoi: YES, THAT'S TRUE.
- Kaoru: I GUESS
THIS IS ALL THAT'S LEFT, HUH?
- YES, I DON'T THINK
THAT WE'VE FORGOTTEN ANYTHING.
WELL, THEN...
- ( heartbeat )
- SO SHALL WE GET GOING?
- UH, YEAH.
MM-HMM.
- OH!
SORRY ABOUT THAT,
KAORU-SAMA.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
AOI-CHAN?
- ( clock ticking )
- AHEM!
- OH!
MIS-- MISS MIYABI.
- LADY AOI, MISS TINA IS
CALLING FOR YOU.
- OH!  ALL RIGHT.
- I SHOULD GO TOO.
- SIR KAORU?
- YEAH?
- WHILE IT'S TRUE THAT OUT OF
CONCERN FOR LADY AOI,
I HAVE APPROVED
OF YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH HER,
HOWEVER, THIS IS NOT THE CASE
WITH THE ENTIRETY
OF THE SAKURABA GROUP,
WHICH HAS THUS FAR
NOT GIVEN ITS FORMAL APPROVAL.
IT IS THEREFORE IMPORTANT
THAT YOUR RELATIONSHIP
STILL REMAINS A SECRET
OUT OF NECESSITY.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?
- YEAH.
- COME ON, BIG BROTHER!
HURRY UP ALREADY, WILL YA?!
- ( all chattering )
- COMING.
- Girls: ROCK, SCISSORS, PAPER.
- TINA SENPAI,
YOU CAN STOP NOW!
THIS IS PAINFUL.
MY BACK WILL SNAP IN TWO!
- IT'S BEEN SO LONG,
MY ARMS ARE FEELING RESTLESS.
HMM!
- YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
IT'S KIND OF HARD TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE I SHOULD BE LOOKING.
- KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA,
IS THERE SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- IT'S NOTHING.
JUST THINKING THAT'S DIFFERENT
FROM WHAT YOU USUALLY WEAR.
- OH.  PLEASE DON'T LOOK AT ME
LIKE THAT.
I'M A LITTLE EMBARRASSED.
- THERE'S NO REASON TO BE.
IT'S CUTE ON YOU.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN.
- PANTIES! HA HA!
- MISS TINA, HONESTLY.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT!
AFTER ALL,
YOU ARE WEARING AN UNDERSKIRT.
- IT IS NOT ALL RIGHT.
- PANTIES!
- AH!
- SENPAI.
- YOU SHOULD TRY THIS
AND RELIVE YOUR CHILDHOOD TOO!
DIDN'T YOU EVER FLIP SKIRTS
WHEN YOU WERE A KID, KAORU?
- NO WAY!
- WELL, THEN, WE WILL FIRST
BEGIN WITH RECEIVING PRACTICE.
PLEASE TRY TO RETURN THE BALLS
THAT I WILL BE SERVING TO YOU.
- All: OKAY!
- THEN FIRST UP, MISS TINA.
- 'KAY!
LET'S DO THIS!
BRING IT ON!
THAT'S A PERFECT BALL--
HIGH AND ON THE OUTSIDE.
TAKE THIS!
WHOO-HOO! WHAT A SHOT! THAT'S
GOTTA BE AT LEAST A DOUBLE.
- HEY, MISS TINA, WE'RE NOT
PLAYING BASEBALL, YOU KNOW.
- SENPAI, YOU SHOULD BE
MORE SERIOUS ABOUT THIS.
- MMM.
- KAORU-SAMA?
- HMM, WHAT?
- YOUR SHOELACE
HAS COME UNDONE.
- OH.
- THERE, ALL BETTER.
- THANKS A LOT, AOI-CHAN.
- Miss Miyabi: MISS TAEKO,
YOU'RE NEXT.
- OH!
( grunts )
- ( laughing )
- HEY, TAEKO,
ARE YOU OKAY THERE?
- OH!
- AW, MAN,
WHO NEEDS ENTERTAINMENT
WHEN WE'VE GOT TAE HERE?
- ( giggles )
- Miss Miyabi:
MISS CHIKA, YOU'RE NEXT.
- OKAY!
( grunts )
AH!
( giggles ) IT LOOKS LIKE I DID
JUST ABOUT AS WELL AS TAEKO.
- I GET THE FEELING THAT TENNIS
ISN'T A MINAZUKI THING.
- Miss Miyabi: LADY AOI,
YOU'RE NEXT.
- RIGHT.
- AOI-CHAN-- I WONDER
IF SHE'LL BE OKAY.
IF SHE'S ANYTHING
LIKE TAEKO-CHAN...
- OH NO!
- ( giggles )
- READY?
- YES.
- All: OH!
- NEXT ONE.
- NEXT ONE!
- All: OH!
- YOU WERE TOTALLY AMAZING,
MISS AOI.
- I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU COULD PLAY TENNIS SO WELL.
- YES,
THOUGH I ONLY DABBLE IN IT.
- OH, I KNOW-- WHY DON'T WE
TRY A DOUBLES MATCH NEXT?
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- OH!
WANT TO PUT WHAT YOU LEARNED
INTO PRACTICE?
HUH, CHIKA?
- ( giggles )
- KAORU-SAMA, LET'S ENJOY
THIS CASUAL GAME.
PLEASE DON'T BE SO TENSE.
- UH, RIGHT.
( whimpers )
HOW CAN I PLAY
A CASUAL GAME LIKE THIS?
- ( blows whistle )
- HERE I GO!
- THERE!
- AAH AAH!
HA!
- THIS DOESN'T LOOK
MUCH LIKE TENNIS, DOES IT?
MORE LIKE PING-PONG,
I'D SAY.
- AAH!  AAH!  AAH!
OH NO!  SORRY,
GUESS I MESSED UP A LITTLE.
- COME ON, CHIKA!
YOU HAVE TO PUT MORE BANG IN IT
IF YOU WANT TO WIN!
BANG, ZOOM!
I'M GONNA SERVE NOW
AND SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE!
HA!
- WHAT?!
WAH!
- GUESS I MESSED UP
A LITTLE THERE.
I'M SORRY.
- OKAY, I'M GONNA SERVE.
- RIGHT.
- Both: HUH?
- KAORU-SAMA?
- ( laughs )
AOI-CHAN,
MAYBE WE SHOULD SWITCH PLACES.
- ( ball bouncing )
- ( grunts )
- ( panting )
- ALL RIGHT!
I WON, I WON!
- AW, DAMN IT ALL!
I WON'T LOSE THE NEXT TIME.
- ( grunts )
- Chika: TAKE THAT!
- ( all grunting )
- I NEVER WOULD HAVE GUESSED.
WHO KNEW AOI-CHAN
WAS SO GOOD AT TENNIS?
WHEW!
- YEAH, REALLY.
- ( girls grunting )
- SHE'S INCREDIBLE.
- ( grunting )
- Tina: LOOK OUT, BIG BROTHER!
- HUH?  AAH!
- ( laughs )
SORRY ABOUT THAT, KAORU.
MY CONTROL
STILL NEEDS A LITTLE WORK.
- IT'S OKAY.
FORGET ABOUT IT.
- ( grunts )
- HA!
GAME, SET AND MATCH.
ISN'T IT, THOUGH?
- YES.
IT APPEARS I LOST.
- YOU PLAYED A GOOD GAME,
THOUGH.
- I STILL
CAN'T BEAT MISS MIYABI, CAN I?
- BUT YOU'RE STILL
A GOOD TENNIS PLAYER, AOI-CHAN.
- IF IT'S ALL RIGHT,
KAORU-SAMA,
WOULD YOU CARE
TO PLAY THE NEXT ONE WITH ME?
- YEAH, SURE.
- ( groaning )
I'M EXHAUSTED!
- PLAYING TENNIS SURE TAKES A
LOT OUT OF A PERSON, DOESN'T IT?
- YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
AFTER ALL THAT RUNNING AROUND,
I PROBABLY LOST 10 OR 20 POUNDS.
- Mayu: THAT'S QUITE IMPOSSIBLE,
I ASSURE YOU!
- TENNIS IS AN ELEGANT
AND BEAUTIFUL SPORT.
IT'S NOT MEANT TO BE
SOME SORT OF WEIGHT-LOSS PROGRAM
FOR BEASTS LIKE YOU.
- HEY, WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU
DOING HERE, MAYU?
- I'LL SAY THIS ONCE.
LEAVING ME BEHIND TO GO PLAY
WITH HANABISHI-SAMA
ISN'T AS SIMPLE A TASK
AS YOU WOULD THINK.
HANABISHI-SAMA!
- HEY, WAIT UP.
- UH, HOLD ON THERE--
- YOU AGREED TO PLAY
THE NEXT TENNIS MATCH WITH ME--
- WOULD YOU GET YOUR DAMN DIRTY
PAWS OFF OF KAORU ALREADY?
- WELL, NOW THAT IT'S AGREED,
HANABISHI-SAMA,
SHALL WE GO?
- HEY, WAIT!
- Mayu: TAKE THAT!
- ( Kaoru grunting )
- ( Mayu laughing )
AND THIS!
- WHOA!
- ( Mayu giggles )
- ( sighs )
MAYU-CHAN,
YOU'RE REALLY GOOD AT TENNIS.
THAT'S TENNIS AS PLAYED
IN ITS HOMELAND OF ENGLAND.
BUT SINCE YOU WERE MY OPPONENT,
HANABISHI-SAMA,
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN RUDE NOT TO
PLAY TO MY FULLEST OF ABILITIES.
- ( laughs )
I SEE.  HMM?
- HERE, SOME COLD TEA.
- OH, THANKS.
- UH, HUH?
- ( gulping )
AHH!
I FEEL ALIVE AGAIN.
- Chika: MISS TINA, WE'RE STILL
IN THE MIDDLE OF A MATCH!
- THANKS.
OKAY, I'M COMING!
( grunting )
- ( both chuckle )
- OH, IT'S ALREADY EMPTY.
- I'M PRETTY SURE THERE'S
ANOTHER THERMOS IN THE CAR,
MISS AOI.
- ALL RIGHT,
THEN I'LL GO AND GET IT.
- OH, I'LL GO WITH YOU.
- Tina: LOOK OUT, BIG BROTHER!
- HMM?
- Mayu: HANABISHI-SAMA!
- Taeko: OH, ARE YOU OKAY,
SENPAI?
- ( Tina laughing )
SORRY ABOUT THAT, KAORU.
- Kaoru: FORGET IT, FORGET IT.
( laughs weakly )
- ( shower running )
- Tina: HEY, CHIKA!
- YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
- ( laughs )
GOT YA!
- WHOA!
UH, WOULD YOU CUT THAT OUT
ALREADY?!
- Tina:
BREAST-EXAMINATION TIME!
AND NOW IT'S TAE'S TURN.
TAE?!
- CHECK!
- Taeko: NO, PLEASE STOP THAT.
- Tina: AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR MAYU'S BREAST EXAM!
CHECK!
- Mayu: WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- I CAN HEAR EVERY WORD
OF THIS, YOU KNOW.
- Tina: AND NOW
FOR MISS MANAGER!  CHECK!
- Miss Miyabi:
NOW JUST ONE MOMENT, MISS TINA!
- ( Tina laughing )
AND NOW MISS LANDLORD!
- AOI-CHAN?
- Aoi: NO, PLEASE STOP
THAT, MISS TINA!
- AW, COME ON!
THIS HAS TO BE DONE.  CHECK!
- ( Aoi screams )
- YEAH!
OH!  HOT HOT HOT HOT HOT!
( sighs )
I DIDN'T HAVE MANY CHANCES
TO BE ALONE
WITH AOI-CHAN TODAY, DID I?
BUT IF I WAS LIVING IN THAT
APARTMENT I DREAMT OF
WITH AOI-CHAN,
JUST THE TWO OF US...
WE'D GO SHOPPING TOGETHER,
WE'D TAKE BATHS TOGETHER,
AND WE'D SLEEP TOGETHER TOO.
A LIFE
FOR JUST THE TWO OF US.
THAT'D BE NICE.
- ( both grunting )
- HEY, THAT HURTS.
THIS IS NICE
IN ITS OWN WAY, THOUGH.
( laughs )
- ( squeaks )
- ARE YOU LOOKING FOR SOMETHING,
SENPAI?
- UH, NO, NOT REALLY.
- KAORU-SAMA?
- HI.
I JUST SMELLED THE FOOD,
THAT'S ALL. ( laughs )
- I KNOW EVERYONE MUST BE
EXHAUSTED FROM TENNIS TODAY,
SO I THOUGHT I WOULD
MAKE SOMETHING SPECIAL
TO REPLENISH OUR ENERGY.
- OH.
IS THERE ANYTHING
THAT I CAN HELP WITH?
- NO, WE CAN HANDLE EVERYTHING.
- OH.
- DINNER WILL BE READY
IN A MOMENT.
- OKAY.
- OH, YES, KAORU-SAMA,
THERE IS SOMETHING THAT I
WOULD LIKE YOU TO HELP ME WITH.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
- OH, SURE.
- I APOLOGIZE, MISS TAEKO.
WOULD YOU PLEASE TAKE CARE
OF THINGS FOR A LITTLE WHILE?
- SURE.
- UM, AdOI-CHAN?
DIDN'T YOU SAY YOU NEEDED HELP
WITH SOMETHING?
- YES, I DID, KAORU-SAMA.
I'D LIKE YOU TO TELL ME
WHAT IT IS YOU WANT.
- HUH?
OH, WELL, WAS IT OBVIOUS?
- ( giggles )
- YOU KNOW, IT WAS STRANGE TODAY
TO FIND OUT
YOU WERE SO GOOD AT TENNIS.
- ( giggles ) REALLY?
- ( laughs ) YEAH.
THERE'S STILL A LOT OF THINGS
THAT I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
AOI-CHAN.
- DID I SURPRISE YOU?
- YOU DID SURPRISE ME.
- THEN FROM NOW ON,
I'LL TRY TO SHOW YOU
MORE AND MORE OF MY SECRETS.
- ( both giggle )
- UM, AOI-CHAN?
- YES?
- COULD I-- IF IT'S OKAY,
AOI-CHAN,
COULD-- COULD I--
UH, COULD I KISS YOU?
- AH, YES.
- I'M SORRY.
I KNOW THAT KIND OF CAME
OUT OF NOWHERE.
- NOT AT ALL.
TO HAVE YOU BE SO AFFECTIONATE
TOWARDS ME
MAKES ME VERY HAPPY.
AFTER ALL, I'VE WISHED
TO BE AFFECTIONATE WITH YOU TOO.
ACTUALLY,
THAT WAS TODAY'S SECOND KISS.
- HUH?
SO YOU KISSED ME
BEFORE I WOKE UP?
- ( giggles )
I LOVE YOU, KAORU-SAMA.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( Taeko chanting )
- WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- WELL, TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
THERE'S SOMETHING BEHIND YOU!
OH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S JUST A GHOST.
I'LL BANISH IT RIGHT AWAY!
- AAH!  WHERE?
- ON THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "AI YORI AOSHI: ENISHI,
PHANTOMS"!
UH-OH, I THINK I MESSED UP.
( giggles )
- Miss Miyabi: WHAT?  THE GHOST?
IS IT STILL BEHIND ME?
AAH! MISS TAEKO!