[MUSIC PLAYING]
VOICES (VOICEOVER): Funimation.
You should be watching.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN (ON RADIO): We've
secured the bridge.
All platoons head for the city.
MAN (ON RADIO): Hurry, before
they bolster their defenses.
Hostiles on the bridge.
Blow it!
MAN (ON RADIO): Incoming!
Once the assault teams
have cleared these bridges,
destroy them.
We can't let the
enemy reach our soil.
Move out!
[SHOUTING]
MAN: We'll make a smaller
target by splitting up.
MAN: Nina's not here yet, sir.
MAN: Too bad for her.
Now move it!
TROOPS: Sir!
[GUNSHOTS]
Cover me.
No, I'll go.
Hey.
Wait!
[GUNSHOTS]
Ah!
Almost there.
Just a little farther.
Stop!
What the?
MAN: It's a trap!
[EXPLOSION]
If you'd gone any
further, you would
have been blown to pieces.
[ALARM BLARING]
MAN: Zuellni's flag
has been captured.
If you hadn't pulled me
down, we would have won!
If I hadn't pulled
you down, you'd
be dead right now, maggot.
Well, if it would've
saved Zuellni,
it would have been worth it!
MAN: We got injured
coming through.
Out of the way.
We trained for months, and
we came so close to victory,
but in the end, we failed.
That's gonna cost
this city dearly.
NINA (VOICEOVER): I
can't lose ever again.
I have to win.
No matter what it takes.
[THEME MUSIC]
Argh.
He's late.
I'll kill him if I find
out that he ran away.
You dragged him in against
his will, so if he did,
I can't say that
I blame the guy.
What's that?
I meant where could he be.
This is a pretty big place.
Maybe he just got lost.
I doubt it.
You're just making excuses.
Yeah, so that
Nina won't kill him.
Argh.
I meant I'm sure
he'll be here soon.
Uh, hey.
Sorry I'm a little late‐‐
Guys.
Allow me to introduce
you to Layfon Alseif.
The newest member
of the 17th platoon.
Uh, yeah.
Look.
About that.
I‐‐
NINA: This is Sharnid Elipton.
He's our fourth
year sharpshooter.
Hey, how's it going?
NINA: And that's Harley Sutton,
our third year DITE mechanic.
Nice to meet you.
Um, actually‐‐
And this is Felli Loss, our
second year Nen‐I operator.
Um, you see, the thing is‐‐
Then there's me, Nina Antalk.
Third year Military Arts student
and the leader of this platoon.
I gave you a membership badge.
Why aren't you wearing it?
It's because I
can't become a member.
I've got a night job cleaning
the machinery department.
Oh, you can handle both.
Trust me.
Restoration.
There's no need to get nervous.
I'm just gonna give you a test.
Harley.
Could I get a little
assistance, please?
You'll be in our
next competition,
so let's see how you fight.
What do you mean
next competition?
Here you go, Layfon.
Take a practice DITE.
Hm?
HARLEY: None of them have been
loaded with any user data yet.
Which one do you wanna use?
Well, any one
will do, I guess.
Restoration.
I just hope you're
ready for this.
Ha.
That's the first time I've
seen anybody shrugging
off an attack from Nina.
Wow.
You're actually
pretty good at this.
But I'm even better.
Can you use External
Ballistic Kei?
Huh?
I said External Ballistic Kei.
Of course.
Then use it.
Ah!
Hey.
What'd the doctor say?
With some rest, Layfon should
be able to rejoin us soon.
Well, that's good.
No, it's not.
Huh?
Was it just some
fluke that he managed
to block my first attack?
When I saw that, I thought, wow.
What a great addition
to the platoon.
But then why the hell
didn't he try to move when
I launched that blast of Kei?
By bringing this guy in,
have I made a big mistake?
Look.
It was his first day.
Don't worry.
He'll get better.
Yeah.
And with the right training,
we'll whip him into shape.
Sure we will.
Hey!
What are you doing?
That shouldn't hurt, you know.
Not with the amount
of Internal Augmenting
Kei that you have in your body.
If you say it hurts,
you're just faking.
I just fell to the
floor, so it does hurt, OK?
Why would you think
I'd be faking?
You were earlier.
Um, Senior Felli.
Now I know the reason
for my brother's deception.
It was all about getting you
in the 17th platoon, Layfon.
Brother?
What do you mean by
deception, anyway?
Huh?
The resignation of one of our
former members and that fight
outside the auditorium.
They were both just
schemes devised
by my brother, the
student council president,
to get you to join the platoon.
I'm sure this
sounds crazy to you.
Actually, my left arm is
slightly longer than my right.
Since I was a last
minute addition,
this uniform shouldn't fit
so perfectly, but it does.
I was wondering
why it fit so well.
Guess that answers
my question, huh?
Exactly.
Now, why don't we talk about
your deception, Layfon.
The
Wait.
What are you talking about?
Your inability to
beat Nina earlier today.
It was all an act, wasn't it?
Do you know much about
Nen‐I operators, Layfon?
We have the ability
to manipulate objects
through telekinesis
and extract information
through psychometric touch.
We can also see and sense
that which can't be seen,
and whenever we project
our Nen‐I outwards,
we can speak with
others telepathically.
Nen‐I isn't the kind of thing
you can just pick up and learn.
It's more like something
you have to be born with.
Isn't that right?
That's correct, and I just
so happened to be born with
an abnormally large
quantity of Nen‐I.
My brother wanted to take
advantage of this for Zuellni,
so I was forcibly
transferred into the Military
Arts department, just like you.
I truly despise my brother.
He'll do whatever it
takes to win, no matter
how underhanded that may be.
So just continue to keep
your strength a secret, OK?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALARM BLARING]
So this is the
heart of the city.
Excuse me.
Of starting work here
tonight and don't
know where to check in.
WOMAN: Give me a sec.
I'll be right up.
[WHIRRING]
It's been tough since
our other guy quit,
so I'm glad to get some help.
Nina?
Layfon?
What the hell are you already
doing out of the hospital?
I, um, got better,
so they released me.
Besides, I couldn't
exactly be absent
from my first night of the job.
Not that I don't
appreciate your dedication,
but I don't know how a guy like
you could recover so quickly.
Now I understand why she
said I could handle both
my platoon duties and this job.
Um, if you don't mind me asking,
why are you working up here?
Yeah, well, that's
kind of a long story.
My parents were totally against
the idea of me coming here,
so I ran away.
As a result, they don't send me
any money at all for tuition.
LAYFON: Ah.
NINA: So what brought you here?
Zuellni was the only school
that offered me a scholarship
and I thought that it
was better than nothing.
Especially for an
orphan with no money.
I'm really sorry.
I had no idea.
Huh?
It's fine.
NINA: Want some?
Thanks.
This tastes delicious.
That's the most popular
meal to go that you
can order from the cafeteria.
Speaking of meals, this was
delivered to my room today.
Want some?
It sure looks good.
And smells good too, doesn't it?
It's making my mouth water.
Then help yourself.
All right.
If you insist.
Looks tasty.
I just hope it tastes as good
as the food that you brought.
NINA: Mm.
Are you nuts?
This is incredible.
It puts the meal I
brought to shame.
LAYFON: Wanna trade?
NINA: Um, sure.
As long as you're
OK with doing that.
LAYFON: Course I am.
NINA: Thanks.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
[GIGGLING]
I wonder if he'll say
it's the most delicious
thing he's ever tasted.
You're acting weird tonight.
Who are you talking about?
‐ Oh, no.
Sorry.
I wasn't talking.
I was just, uh, singing.
Yeah right.
[GIGGLING]
NINA: That was so delicious.
Consider this my way
of saying thank you.
Huh?
You're welcome.
That's really good.
Did you order this stuff too?
NINA: No.
I made it.
You need to make your own
drinks if you live in Zuellni.
The drinking water
here tastes stale.
Living in a Regios
can get stale too.
The thought of spending your
whole life inside the same one
can make you feel
like a bird in a cage.
That's probably why some people
get on the roaming buses that
travel to the other cities.
They get to experience things
that the rest of us don't.
I was jealous.
I wanted to be one
of those people,
so I decided to come here.
But my parents didn't share
my enthusiasm and told me no.
So you ran away, huh?
And that's the reason why
I have this glamorous job.
It's hard work, but
it does pay well,
and a Military Arts
education isn't cheap.
But that's where my
true passion lies.
Not that I'd expect
you to understand that.
Well, back to work.
Hm?
We need to finish up since
the competition's tomorrow.
Wait.
It's tomorrow?
Oh yeah.
Did I not mention that before?
If you knew we had to
clean all this tonight,
then why did to let us
spend so much time talking?
I told you it was gonna be
a long story, so quit griping.
LAYFON: But I've
gotta get some sleep.
If I don't, I'll be
no good tomorrow.
NINA: Hey.
You had the time to talk,
so you got the time to work.
Move it!
LAYFON: It's getting late.
NINA: Who care?
Work!
LAYFON: I am!
NINA: Go faster!
So sleepy.
It's good that you're
made of such strong stuff,
because if you weren't, we
would have had to withdraw,
so thanks for making it.
Let me wish you all good luck.
If anyone needs
luck today, it's
you and your platoon, maggot.
With you in command,
I'll be surprised
if your unit lasts more
than five minutes out there.
This match will
determine our standing
in the next municipal
challenge, so stay sharp.
I sure hope Layfie does well.
Of course he
will, especially now
that he's got one of Mayshen's
delicious homemade meals
in his belly.
Oh my.
Why did I get
a chill just now?
The rules are simple.
The 17th platoon will attack and
the 16th platoon will defend.
He's the head
of Military Arts.
Treat this like a real
municipal challenge.
Yes, sir.
Now take your positions.
WOMAN (OVER SPEAKER):
The competition
between the 16th and 17th
platoons will now commence.
As a safety precaution,
we must request
that all spectators
remain seated
behind the protective
barriers at all times.
NINA: Since we're attacking,
there are only two ways to win.
Wipe out the enemy
platoon or take down
the flag behind their lines.
LAYFON: And how can the
defending team win this?
NINA: They can either protect
the flag until time runs out,
or they can take down the
opposing force's leader.
In this match,
that leader is me.
Since I'm their primary target,
I'm gonna act as a decoy
and lure them away.
They'll be one fearless move.
NINA: ‐ Layfon,
get to that flag.
Sharnid, you cover him.
Roger that, boss.
Enemies are approaching.
NINA: Restoration.
Gotcha.
Watch out.
Get out of here!
Restoration.
Sharnid.
Layfon could use
a little backup.
That's easier said than done.
That new student's
responses are pretty pathetic.
And his Kei channeling
is rather poor too.
KARIAN (ON PHONE): Trust me.
Don't write him off yet.
What exactly are you hiding?
KARIAN (ON PHONE): Zuellni
always gets students
who are young and immature.
Perhaps the importance of
this match hasn't sunk in
and he thinks it's
just child's play.
MAN (ON SPEAKER): He needs
to look at it more like it's
a matter of life and death.
I tried to impart how
important his skills were
for this city's survival,
but for some reason,
our new student is still
lacking in motivation.
Seems he's not the only one.
Your sister is as well.
Those two are uninspired.
And Sharnid's undisciplined.
The whole platoon's a mess.
You should reassign Nina
Antalk to another platoon
so she has a chance to succeed.
KARIAN (ON PHONE):
offered, but she
refused, so let's see
how she and her platoon
do in this match.
Who knows?
They might surprise you.
I doubt it.
Knowing this bunch, I think
the only thing they're
gonna achieve is failure.
Sometimes the fear
of failure is all
the motivation that one needs.
Restoration.
NINA: Sharnid, what gives?
Why aren't you helping Layfon?
He's too close to
his sparring partner,
so I can't get a clear shot.
NINA (VOICEOVER): Felli,
what's taking so long?
Why haven't you found
the enemy's base?
'Cause I'm
currently at my limit.
LAYFON (VOICEOVER): Keep
my strength a secret.
[SCREAMING]
Layfon!
FELLI (VOICEOVER):
Layfon's vanished.
Damage unknown.
Oh no.
[SHOUTING]
SHARNID: Dammit.
Finally, a clear shot.
Thanks a lot, tubby.
LAYFON (VOICEOVER): Are you sure
it's OK if we lose this thing?
Nina.
You haven't improved
over the last two years
at all, have you?
I'm not surprised.
Argh!
It's impossible.
You still had that
much strength left?
I sure did.
Now I'm gonna use the rest
of it and take you down!
Just like last
time, you came close,
but ultimately you failed.
[SHOUTING]
Get out of there.
Run.
[SHOUTING]
Start the countdown.
This match is almost over.
KARIAN (ON PHONE): I wouldn't
be so sure about that.
Come on.
At this point, the
17th platoon would
need a real miracle to win.
If you want to fight alone,
then you're gonna lose alone.
How does it feel to know
you failed once again?
NINA (VOICEOVER): No.
I can't lose again.
But I can't hold on much longer.
LAYFON (VOICEOVER):
She's about to lose.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXPLOSION]
External Ballistic Kei!
Dragon Spiral Kei.
Huh?
Ah!
Internal Augmented Spiral Kei.
Was that Layfon?
Yeah.
It sure was.
[ALARM BLARING]
[CHEERING]
Yay!
All right!
Layfie did it!
You were incredible!
You won't think that
when you see this.
Huh?
I'm really sorry, but
somehow, I burned out my DITE.
I've never seen
that happen before.
Your Kei must have been too
strong for the DITE to contain.
But don't worry about it.
We'll just figure out
some new settings for you.
Dude.
Way to go.
Where have you been hiding
those claws you just unleashed?
Scratchy scratchy.
[NERVOUS LAUGHTER]
Oh, Nina.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You're a traitor, Layfon.
MAN (VOICEOVER): Nina's
still angry at Layfon
for hiding his powers, but
she has more pressing matters
to deal with when Zuellni
suddenly comes to a halt.
Can Nina find the mysterious
enemy behind this plot
before it's too late?
Next time, Electronic Spirit
Zuellni and Restoration.