[MUSIC PLAYING]
Funimation.
You should be watching.
The Kei‐Ra cannon
is ready to fire.
Beginning countdown.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2‐‐
ready?
Fire!
[THEME MUSIC]
Stand by.
Confirming a direct hit.
Hurry up!
What's the status?
Scattered burn‐related
injuries, but‐‐
No damage to the cannon.
Can we fire again?
Confirming.
Did we do it?
Checking on bio signs now.
It's a direct hit!
Yeah, we got him.
Wait.
It's not dead.
I'm confirming life readings.
What are you saying?
Something isn't right here.
There's static mixed in
with the sound of its heart.
It's like‐‐ there
are two heartbeats.
What does that mean?
There's more than one of them?
Did our attack cause the
contaminoid to divide into two?
Vanze, listen.
It will come back to life.
There will be two of them now.
This can't be.
Prepare the cannon.
How long will it take
for them to recharge it?
To round up a group
of military artists‐‐
we're going to need at
least two hours, sir.
Wouldn't it be better to
dispatch some platoons?
Let's kill it
before it wakes up.
I'm concerned about Glendan.
It's too early for
that, commander.
Yes, sir.
The leg section elevators
has reached ground level.
Its door is opening.
Nina Antalk has left the city.
And now, the primary issue.
Currently Zuellni's
completely motionless.
The reason is unknown.
And at this rate,
the contaminoid
will most certainly revive.
Then the city will
again be in danger.
Before the Kei‐Ra
cannon fires, I want
you to retrieve Nina Antalk.
She has left the city.
We need her.
You see, without her the
city won't be able to move.
What exactly do you plan
to do after we've found her?
We have to remove
the fallen one.
It's our only choice.
If we don't, Zuellni will
continue to run amok.
But if it's forcibly removed,
she'll end up just like Dinn.
The city's safety
is our priority.
It the fallen one
cannot be extracted,
Zuellni must be driven from
Nina Antalk's body at once.
You're actually suggesting
we should kill her?
We estimate you
have about two hours.
Your team must
carry out your duty.
Return Nina to the city.
But if you exceed
your time, we'll
have no choice but to
fire the Kei‐Ra cannon
and the contaminoid.
And we will do so whether
you've made it back here or not.
Since we're about
to lose the city,
you've got no other alternative.
You're the president, after all.
We're just the
expendable peons, huh?
No, Sharnid!
Don't!
Next time.
Just when I thought I
had a good look at him,
the creature split
apart into two beings.
This is exactly what
they wanted, isn't it?
Your majesty, a
message from Delbone.
Tell me.
She wants us to be aware
that someone is plotting
to infiltrate the inner palace.
At a time like this?
I'm assuming the seal
has not been broken?
No.
The entrance is
blocked by a maze,
and a covert approach is
thought to be impossible.
Send Barmeleen at once.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll go first.
Roger.
Yes, sir.
Damn.
Piece of junk.
Sorry, friend.
Gotta go to Glendan, so I
need to borrow your ride.
But don't worry.
I promise I'll return
it after I'm finished.
Why me?
I can't believe this.
That stupid queen's
got some nerve.
Damn.
This is disgusting!
So you're him?
The shit head intruder.
Hey.
There's no reason to curse.
Shut up!
Die, you bastard!
I figured I'd
see you guys here.
It's your presence.
You are a conduit.
You are what connects
our world to this one.
The simple fact that you're
here causes many other beings
to become involved.
It drags them in.
It's difficult to live
in this world, isn't it?
All you have to
do is come back.
You're responsible for
my home being destroyed.
You murdered my
dad, and my brother.
You killed everyone,
and everything.
You tried to destroy
my entire life.
All the people who I loved.
You stole them from me.
Do you remember that?
Restoration!
I'll show you what happens to
those who try to take things
away from Dickserio Muscaine.
You're going to wish
you'd never crossed me!
What's his deal?
Does this guy think we're done?
Don't screw with me, buddy.
Now I'm really pissed off!
I'm on your side!
I don't care about
sides, you shit head!
Die!
All you bastards can die!
That girl sure
has a mouth on her!
It's the Wolfmask Mob.
Wolfmask Mob?
Intruders at a time like this?
I don't think
it's a coincidence.
We're distracted.
The contaminoid's yours.
Make sure your team puts
an end to that situation.
Meanwhile, six Heaven's
Blades will remain in Glendan.
I'll retire to the inner palace.
Have you neglected your math?
If six stay with you, that
leaves me with less than half.
Lintens, you ought
to know that I don't
like men who are disagreeable.
You know, you don't
have to go with us.
The 17th Platoon was the only
team ordered to mobilize.
Plus, we could all die today.
You don't really
mean that, right?
Think about it, Dalsiena.
Have I ever lied to you?
Oh, please, Sharnid.
Lies are the only
thing I hear from you.
I prefer truth.
When do I finally
get to hear it, huh?
I've been waiting.
And I'm a member of
the 17th too, OK?
Try not to forget that.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, guys.
I'll head directly
for the contaminoid.
You two need to spread
out, and do everything
you can to find Nina.
Understood.
Got it.
Wait for me.
I'm coming, too.
My range won't be that
great, but I should be
able to use my Nen‐I terminal.
What is that?
Vanze urgently needs
to speak with you, sir.
I'm here.
What's going on?
The team just left the city.
That was the 17th Platoon.
They're headed straight
for the contaminoid.
Everything's fine.
Oh.
That's all right, then.
There are no changes to the
Kei‐Ra cannon's fire time.
VANZE: Of course.
Things are going
very well on our end.
You sound a bit tired, sir.
KALIAN: Should personal growth
be cause for celebration?
Does it even matter?
You all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Goodbye.
Yes, but why would you go?
We just fired the Kei‐Ra cannon.
There'll be too
much interference.
You won't be able to
use your terminal.
If you go, you'll be in the way.
You've ordered the
17th Platoon to do this,
and I'm a member of that unit.
No.
You've done more than enough.
You need to get some rest.
I'm fine.
And I'm going.
Felli, I want you to
listen to me carefully.
The order to fire the cannon‐‐
I can't delay it.
‐Goodbye.
‐No!
Felli!
Deactivate your Nen‐I terminal!
Do it now!
Understand?
Stop it.
Drop your guns.
You've made up your
mind, haven't you?
Yes.
If I don't make it
back here in time,
go ahead and fire the cannon.
It's the only way that
we can protect the city.
[LAUGHTER]
Dude, come on, man.
I was such a young girl.
I didn't know
anything back then.
[LAUGHTER]
He was always there,
right by my side.
Hey.
You burned it.
Listen, mister, I
know what I'm doing!
Sure smells good.
When Layfon came
back from a battle,
his smile was enough for me.
I never tried to learn
about any of his burdens.
How hard they were on him.
There you are.
You've got to keep
your strength up,
so I brought you
something to eat.
I saw it!
What's the situation outside?
Zuellni's legs
aren't moving anymore.
The city stopped going rogue?
It's about time,
because if we couldn't
escape from the contaminoid‐‐
I think we just
lucked out, guys.
With circumstances
being what they are,
I'd appreciate it if you'd keep
unconfirmed info to yourself.
We don't want to give
people the wrong idea.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
But there's no need
for us to worry now.
The 17th Platoon‐‐
they've been sent
out to destroy the contaminoid.
Layfon's team?
Oh, how cool!
The 17th Platoon?
I'm going!
Wait!
I have to find Layfon!
No!
What are you saying?
He's headed for the contaminoid.
If you follow, you could die.
You don't understand!
I have to give this to him, now!
Leerin, whatever
that is, I'm sure it's
very important to Layfon.
I wish I could take
you there myself,
but I just don't have the power.
Listen, this is not
Glendan, understand?
No one here can do that.
No one can take you
close to a contaminoid.
Not here in Zuellni, anyway.
What about Gorneo?
Help me find Gorneo Lueckens.
Come on!
Bring it!
Take that!
They've been giving you
hell for a while now.
What gives?
Are you a Heaven's
Blade, or aren't ya?
OK, buddy!
Try this!
Have you killed them yet?
Look, just give a girl
some time, all right?
Her majesty is sending more
Heaven's Blades to help.
Whatever we do, we
can't let them get away!
Not again.
The regios will finish,
and will of Ricksario
shall turn to dust.
Even as we speak, Ignatius'
dreams are becoming a reality.
Before the end, Dainsleif, the
emissary from the aurora field,
shall bring all to fruition.
We shall drag
forth the sleeping
child that defies
the will of Ignatius,
and expose its identity.
Do you see the
contaminoid, Dainsleif?
Are you blind to this?
Saya, are you asleep?
Where are you?
What are you thinking?
What is your plan?
Are you trying to
protect Leerin?
What's going on?
Who gave you
permission to be here?
Please forgive
me, your majesty.
I'm sorry.
My purpose here is of
the utmost importance.
What is this?
Why are you here,
and not in Zuellni?
I did as you
asked, your majesty.
I protected Leerin, and
got her safely to the city.
And now I've come for
my Heaven's Blade.
If I'm to deliver you the fallen
one, I'm going to need it.
You do know defeat
is unforgivable?
You shouldn't confuse
me with Layfon.
That may be.
But he hasn't been defeated yet.
Be back soon.
Nina!
You.
Stay out of my way.
You fool.
What are you trying
to make me do, here?
Restoration.
I'll destroy
anything in my path!
Restoration!
[SHOUTING]
What do I do?
I can't attack her full force.
I already warned you, Layfon.
Maybe you don't understand.
[SHOUTING]
[GASPING]
[COUGHING]
Are you all right?
Nina!
Why didn't you tell
us you found her?
I'm sorry.
The contaminoids are moving.
They're not completely revived
yet, but once they are,
they'll catch up to you.
Understood.
I'm getting her out of here.
Tell everyone to head for the
rendezvous point immediately,
and I'll meet them
there as soon as I can.
FELLI: Layfon has found Nina.
Head for the rendesvouz point.
Roger that!
Layfon?
I don't know what to do anymore.
Don't worry.
Just hang in there!
I'm so lost.
I prayed that I
would grow stronger,
so I could protect
my loved ones.
But I'm not strong.
I'm not.
Power is all I ever wanted.
I know.
It's Zuellni's will that
this city be protected,
and I am that will.
Don't you see?
The fallen one's inside me!
What's going to
happen to me now?
I'm so scared.
Nina, can I tell you something?
What?
This whole time, I've
tried to reject fighting.
But I still remained a
member of the 17th Platoon.
Yeah?
Looking back on it
now, I don't think I
was really rejecting fighting.
I needed atonement.
Atonement?
Yeah.
For Dirk.
The man who raised me.
My teacher.
I made a lot of money
participating in
those underground tournaments.
Doing that was a
betrayal to him,
so I forbade myself from
using the Saiharden technique,
and single edge blades.
But then, during that fight
earlier, I felt it again.
The desire to use
those techniques‐‐
it rose up inside of me.
I know I haven't found a way
to atone for my sins yet.
I know I haven't been forgiven
for betraying everyone,
and bringing them such sadness.
But still, I felt it.
Layfon‐‐ don't change who
you are for other people.
You have to do what
you feel is right.
I promise you, none of
the other reasons matter.
The desire should be yours.
It should come from inside.
The same goes for your goals.
You don't fight because
others are fighting.
You do it because
that's who you are.
Put yourself in the
position of someone
with the same objective as you.
Decide.
Assist.
Take action.
I'm sorry.
I know that I have
made mistakes.
I got you wrapped up
in this whole thing.
You shouldn't have
had to come rescue me.
I'm so sorry.
I don't feel wrapped
up in anything.
I dragged you into this.
I forced you to join
the 17th Platoon.
Listen to me‐‐
I'm here because I choose to be.
Now, stop talking like
you're going to die,
because you're not.
You're so powerful.
You're saying that, Nina?
Sorry.
I'm not myself.
I'm so tired.
Get some rest.
Looks like the Heaven's
Blades have arrived.
I guess I'd better
get started, then.
I have some business
of my own to settle.
I'm counting on you.
You're really OK
being left here?
Don't worry about me.
I'll figure this out.
I've got to slow down
those contaminoids somehow.
Fon Fon?
Huh?
Don't forget about
Kei‐Ra cannon.
The fire time cannot be changed.
I know, Felli.
Thank you.
FELLI: Please make
sure you come back.
Idiot.
[SHOUTING]
WOMAN: Attention!
The contaminoids have
resumed activity.
Zuellni is now switching to
threat level B. I repeat‐‐
Return to your posts at once!
We're at threat level B!
The contaminoids
have started to move.
There's a chance the
train may stop before we
reach the exterior edge.
Restoration!
[GRUNTING]
Ha ha ha!
What is it?
We were attacked.
Fon Fon, Nina's been kidnapped.
Huh?
FELLI: He had a weapon, and was
a keeper of the Heaven's Blade.
[THEME MUSIC]
Listen, men.
We are now on standby.
Yes, sir!
You're Gorneo
Lueckens, aren't you?
Hm?
Who are you?
I'm Leerin Marfes.
Layfon and I were in the
same orphanage together.
Hey, Gor!
I need your assistance.
Please‐‐ will you help
me get this to Layfon?
Wait.
Is that a Saiharden blade?
I need your help.
I can't go alone.
I want you to take me
to the contaminoids.
NARRATOR: A man who
controls a fallen one.
A sleeping princess
inside of a maze.
The location of the
12th Heaven's Blade.
The girl whose
eyes hold the moon.
When all these
things come together,
the regios shall move again.
Next time, The Stirring
Cities, and restoration.