[MUSIC PLAYING]
VOICES (VOICEOVER): Funimation.
You should be watching.
HARLEY: So.
What do you think?
Are you gonna be
able to use this?
Well, it's a little
heavy, but Yeah.
I think I can make it work.
Man.
That is unbelievable.
FELLI: I hope you're satisfied.
Thanks a lot.
You ruined my hair, Fon‐Fon.
[THEME MUSIC]
HARLEY: Well, I'm out of here.
I've gotta get back to the lab
and go over all this data ASAP.
But what about your classes?
Who cares about that?
It's hard to think
about classes when
Zuellni could run into
Contaminoids at any minute.
And while we're
on the subject.
[YAWN]
To avoid unnecessary panic,
my brother's asked that we
keep this matter between us.
Yeah.
I know.
I got it.
LAYFON: So is that
why you came here?
To pass that along?
‐ You're upset?
‐ No.
No way.
[GONG]
‐ Ah!
Why?
Gah.
You're very cooperative,
aren't you, Fon‐Fon?
Huh?
If you dislike it, then
why don't you say something?
Because it's the only
option we have, isn't it?
Unless we know more about the
Contaminoids, we won't make it.
You do realize if this
mission goes according to plan
and you succeed, my brother
will continue using you?
Yes, that's true.
But I don't think of
myself as being used.
I'm just helping out.
The truth is, if somebody died
because I just stood by and did
nothing, I couldn't go on.
And I guess that's it.
You know what, Fon‐Fon?
You're such an idiot.
Hey.
That's not very nice.
Such an idiot.
That Layfon sure is awesome.
This thing is gonna
keep me super busy.
Hey!
Ah!
Sharnid.
Sup?
So you guys stayed out
all night too, huh?
Uh, no.
I‐‐ not exactly.
We just, uh‐‐
Hey, man.
If you guys are out partying,
you should let me know.
Sure.
Whatever.
I gotta go!
Damn.
MAN: Get ready.
Fight.
[WHISPERING]
Hey.
Are you all right?
This is why the
third year students
don't want to spar with you.
Sorry.
Come on.
Don't even worry about it.
And please don't take
this the wrong way,
but you do remember that I'm
a girl, don't you, Layfie?
Listen.
I'm not stupid.
I know they're not the biggest
things you've ever seen,
but it's still pretty
unflattering when
a guy doesn't even notice them.
Uh, no.
That was just a‐‐ honest.
I really didn't
mean to, uh‐‐ um.
[LAUGHTER]
Sorry.
No.
I'm just kidding.
It's no big deal, OK?
Hey.
What's up with her?
Do you think she's
acting a little strange?
Yeah, she is.
I noticed that.
Listen.
There's something I
should probably tell you.
You really saw Nina going
somewhere all by herself
in the middle of the night?
MAYSHEN: Ah‐huh.
NARUKI: You're positive she just
got off work, right, Layfie?
LAYFON: Yes.
All right.
Here it comes.
MAYSHEN: I wonder where
she's going so late.
MIFI: Could that be my
scandal sense tingling?
Is the leader of
the 17th Platoon
having a hot,
torrid love affair?
MAYSHEN: Hey.
Stop that.
MIFI: What do you mean?
I hope she's OK.
MIFI: I don't get it.
What in the world could
she possibly be doing?
[BELL RINGING]
Restoration.
Ah!
NINA (VOICEOVER): I have to
get stronger, more powerful.
Whoa.
Dedication.
Well, I'm impressed.
Does she train like
this every single night?
That's reckless.
She's pushing herself too hard.
If she isn't
careful, she could
end up getting really hurt.
That poor thing.
Now she's practicing outside
of her normal classes.
On top of her cleaning duties
at the machinery department,
this is just too much.
Why is she doing this?
Because her platoon lost
the last competition?
No.
That isn't the only reason.
Huh?
I think I understand
why she put herself
through something like this.
It's because of you.
You're too powerful, Layfie.
Remember that time you helped
me out on the data theft case?
I felt the same way then.
It would be almost
impossible for me
to fight alongside someone
like you in a battle.
And that made me feel
awful, and frustrated,
and, to be honest,
a little jealous.
Your platoon leader wants to
become as strong as you are.
And can you blame her?
After all, she your commander
and a fellow military artist.
I mean, it's only
natural for somebody
like her to want to become
stronger and more capable.
At the end of the day, a
warrior has to stand alone.
If you want to
become stronger, you
have to do it all by yourself.
Yeah, but the 17th Platoon's
a team, not one person.
Huh?
So to get stronger,
why don't you guys
try and do it together?
[THUD]
LAYFON: Nina!
You bitches will
regret coming after us.
[GUNSHOTS]
Saya.
To the left.
DOCTOR: I swear.
I never thought I'd see the
day when a third year student
collapses like some amateur.
Seems her Kei artery is shot.
Well, will she get better?
The procedure I just performed
should strengthen the Kei flow,
but she won't be able
to move for a while.
Now, I'm sorry, but I have
other patients to attend to.
Look.
Don't worry.
Once we're finished
with your friend,
I promise she'll be good as new.
Right.
Thank you very much.
Well, I suppose things
could be a lot worse.
I swear, she's always
been like this.
Once she sets her
mind on something,
it's like she gets
tunnel vision.
Ah!
Um, you think we should
cover her up with a sheet?
LAYFON: Well, the doctor
didn't say anything,
so maybe we shouldn't.
You perverts.
Ah!
Where'd you come from?
You got it wrong.
We weren't looking.
Only a pervert would
say something like that.
As for why I'm here, these
are the results that the probe
brought that this morning.
Zuellni isn't
changing its path.
At the rate we're traveling,
we'll reach that Contaminoid's
location by tomorrow.
Oh crap.
That's not good.
I better get going now.
I have to finish the Adamandite.
My brother has an
assignment for you.
He wants you to go
out this evening.
I understand, Felli.
OK.
See you later!
Will Layfie be OK out
there all buy himself?
With the platoon
leader in the hospital,
there'll be lots of
things he'll need, right?
Then we'll just have to
take care of him, won't we?
Layfie won't be able to do
this all alone, you know.
Mm.
Huh?
NINA: Where am I?
LAYFON: Well, you're
already awake, huh?
Typical.
Layfon?
Guess I must've collapsed
from fatigue, didn't I?
Yeah.
You used too much
Augmenting Kei.
Have you been here
watching me this whole time?
Uh, well, no.
I screwed up, huh?
No way.
I don't look at it
like that at all.
Why don't you?
Getting that close
to death teaches
us something about ourselves.
Something we wouldn't
have known otherwise.
It's a journey we
have to go on alone.
Yeah, but look
where mine ended.
What a joke.
At first, All I could think
of was the 17th platoon.
I just wanted to be
strong enough to win.
But then I got a little greedy,
'cause you're so strong.
When I first saw your
power, it terrified me.
I thought, is he even human?
I realized that you
were, of course, and one
whose strength could
finally put our unit on top.
And you did that.
In fact, you did it so well that
I became convinced our platoon
was stronger than the others.
But then we were defeated,
and I tried to tell
myself it was a good thing.
Because I was wrong,
and that event
showed me the error of my ways.
But if that's true,
what can I do?
How can I win?
Nina.
Were you aware of the
disruption in your Kei Soku?
When that type of
disruption happens,
your body's telling you you're
wasting too much energy.
I mean, it's your
entire life force.
It's the foundation of your Kei
and the source of your power.
And ideally, we should
live our lives by it.
The Kei Soku?
Mhm.
You need to realize that
you're not in this alone,
and how important
you are to us all.
When it comes to
fighting, I know full
well how to get into a
battle all by myself,
but when it comes to leading
a team, I'm worthless.
The whole crew needs you now.
Whether or not we become the
most powerful platoon we can be
depends on you, Nina.
So lead us.
Don't give up.
Don't toss us aside.
Layfon.
You idiot.
That's the last thing
I would ever do.
FELLI (VOICEOVER): Those
sounded like last words to me.
LAYFON: So I guess
you were listening.
FELLI (VOICEOVER): I used
my Nen‐I to eavesdrop.
Those weren't my last words.
FELLI (VOICEOVER):
Given the situation,
it wouldn't be
unusual if they were.
I don't know.
FELLI (VOICEOVER): I do.
Well.
I don't plan to lose.
FELLI (VOICEOVER): How is it?
LAYFON: It's a male.
Probably a fourth
or fifth stager.
You can tell by how much
the legs have atrophied.
Typically, Contaminoids cast
off their legs every time they
molt. Anyway, now's my chance.
I better make my move
while he's sleeping.
[SHATTER]
He's molting.
They're hungry after
they've molted.
[ROARING]
Felli.
He waited 'til the last
possible moment to molt.
When a food source was near.
FELLI (VOICEOVER): Wait.
What are you saying?
LAYFON: We've got to hurry.
We don't have much time.
This is a first term elder.
We're in big trouble.
We'll be lucky if we can
defeat this thing before it
destroys half the city.
Restoration 02.
Yo.
Hey.
Feeling good?
You know, that's not
really a smart question
to ask a sick person.
Abso‐freaking‐lutely not.
Still, I never figured you the
type to collapse from fatigue.
You gave everybody
a bit of a scare
there, Miss Platoon Leader.
Sorry.
I feel pretty bad about that.
Aw, come on.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Nobody expects you to apologize.
Anyway that's not the issue.
I dropped by to talk about
something else, actually.
What exactly would that be?
Sharnid, stop!
What's going on?
I know what I'm doing here.
I think it's about time
our friend Harley filled
us in on his little plan.
So what do you say, bud?
Everybody's got secrets.
But certain things,
well, sometimes they're
better off out in the open.
Don't you agree, Harley?
So tell me.
What are you guys up to?
Huh?
What are you getting
Layfon to do?
No.
I can't say.
Trust me.
One way or the other,
you're gonna tell
me everything I wanna know.
[RUMBLING]
[CRASH]
Restoration AG.
[ROARING]
After all that, I
barely got one wing off.
FELLI (VOICEOVER): Fon‐Fon.
Felli.
How long have I been out here?
FELLI (VOICEOVER):
A little over a day.
Zuellni already changed
course during that time.
It did?
FELLI (VOICEOVER):
I tried to tell you.
Right now, it's moving
away at considerable speed,
so get going and come back
here as quickly as you can.
I can't do that.
FELLI (VOICEOVER): You must.
If we allowed this male to
develop the ability to fly,
he'd be able to reach Zuellni
in a matter of minutes.
I have to stop him right here.
FELLI (VOICEOVER): Fon‐Fon.
Wait.
No.
If I could cut off his wings,
that'll buy us some time.
Trust me.
We'll need it.
I'll fight him off
as long as I can.
Ah!
[ROARING]
NINA: Layfon!
Nina?
SHARNID: What'd you think?
We we're gonna let you come
out here and hog all the glory?
[GUNSHOT]
NINA: Layfon.
LAYFON: What are you doing here?
SHARNID: We're here
to pick you up.
We figured you might
need a lift home.
LAYFON: You've gotta go.
A rescue team will come
for me if I defeat him.
NINA: But can you do it?
Look.
Your DITE's pretty fried.
You really think you
can beat a Contaminoid
with your weapon like that?
LAYFON: All I need
is one more blow.
If I could get one could strike
on the forehead, he'll be done.
NINA: All right.
Let's create a diversion, then.
LAYFON: Huh?
NINA: That monster's hungry.
If a food source is
directly in front of it,
he'll make right for it.
Trust me.
LAYFON: Nina.
NINA: Use your enemy's
actions to bring the situation
to your advantage.
Come on.
It's the only way.
LAYFON: No.
Nina.
I can't let you do that.
NINA: Lets hope there's a canyon
nearby we can draw him into
or we might be in big trouble.
FELLI (VOICEOVER): Nina.
I can sense one
20 kilmils ahead.
NINA: Felli.
You can project
your Nen‐I this far?
[WHISTLE]
FELLI (VOICEOVER): The
Contaminoid has begun moving.
Hurry.
LAYFON: Roger.
Don't worry.
I'll keep us safe.
NINA: Look, Layfon.
I'm the platoon leader.
It's my job.
I'll protect us.
LAYFON: Right.
I've got your back.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BANGING]
FELLI (VOICEOVER):
Mission point reached.
NINA: Roger.
[GUNSHOT]
SHARNID: Gotcha.
LAYFON: All right, guys.
Let's go!
FELLI (VOICEOVER):
Get ready, Fon‐Fon.
It's coming.
NINA (VOICEOVER): Layfon.
This is the kind of world
you grew up in, isn't it?
From now on, I won't
let you do it alone.
You have us to back you up.
We're a team.
[EXPLOSION]
We fight together as one.
[RUMBLING]
We're with you.
Ah!
You were amazing out there.
SHARNID: Ah, man.
Talk about lame, huh?
We take that monster
out looking all cool,
and this is how it ends?
What a major bummer.
[ZAP]
Ow.
NINA: In the end, I got a
little bit off kilter, didn't I?
LAYFON: As far as I'm concerned,
you saved our lives back there.
But you know what?
This victory belongs
to the whole platoon.
Our team.
We can keep counting
on you, right?
Can't we?
NINA: Yes, of course.
SHARNID: : Hm.
NINA: What?
SHARNID: : Well, uh, it's
really not that big of a deal.
It just occurred to
me that you might
have a thing for younger guys.
Or am I imagining things.
LAYFON: What?
Where'd that come from?
NINA: Oh, please.
Give me a break.
I do not think of him that way.
He is my subordinate, you know.
SHARNID: : [SIGH] You're no fun.
NINA: What?
What did you say?
SHARNID: : Uh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey!
ALL: Hey!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN (VOICEOVER): Gorneo
Lueckens, the leader
of the 5th Platoon, has a
reason why he refuses to forgive
Layfon, but they have to
work together with the 5th
and 17th platoons are ordered
to go on a joint expedition.
Next time, A Former Enemy
Reduced to a Ruined City
and Restoration.