And as for Layfon,
Your Majesty,
can he never come
back here again?
Leerin.
I'm terribly sorry, My Queen.
No, please, it's
fine, because there's
simply no question in my mind
that for him, this is home.
I understand that he is
an extremely important
person to you as well.
Yes.
QUEEN ALSHEYRA:
It's not impossible
for him to be allowed
to return here, however
it would take some time.
Then it's‐‐
That said, even if something
like this were possible,
are you certain that he
would want to come back here?
The way I see it, that is
a major problem that must
be addressed and not by me.
You, Saiharden, your kind tends
to leave our city, don't they?
Yes.
A large number of
our citizens left
to follow the first
generation Salinban,
and many were disciples
of the Saiharden
two generations before.
Even your own brother
joined with those
who began calling themselves
the Salinban Mercenary
Training Group, did he not?
Riyuho Gaju, a man whose
skills far exceeded my own.
By all rights, he should
have been the successor
to Saiharden family name.
QUEEN ALSHEYRA: He's dead.
No, it can't be!
QUEEN ALSHEYRA: He fought
against the contaminoids,
after which he was
unable to cleanse
the horrible contamination
that remained within.
Is that so?
The Saiharden Marshall
family is a national treasure
to the city of Glendon.
You must pass on your skills
to the next generation.
Leerin Marfes?
LEERIN: Yes?
Because your friend is a
member of the Saiharden line,
it simply cannot be denied
that leaving our city
is a part of his nature.
You should resign
yourself to that fact.
THEME SONG: (SINGING) Brave
your truth and brave yourself,
so we can go somewhere
with the dite.
Keep hope alive.
Now we wanna find the new world.
[JAPANESE]
Being unable to
hide your presence
is bad news for a shooter.
Maybe you should try stalking
a guy you have a crush on.
Trust me, it'll be
good practice for you.
Uh, I couldn't do that.
Who are you, and
what is this about?
This little spectacle isn't
the reason you're here.
You're correct, bub.
Perhaps you've heard of me.
My name is Haia Salinban Lyia.
The Salinban Mercenary
Training Group?
I'm their leader.
My friend with
the bow is Myunfa.
Hi, it's a pleasure
to meet you, sir.
What exactly are
you doing here?
I sincerely doubt that
you were asked to instruct
our military art students.
Unfortunately, I'm not
here to ply my wares.
But I did come a
hell of a long way.
See, I need to ask
for your assistance.
You're from a noble
Glendon family.
So I suppose it wouldn't be
that strange if you knew.
I'm speaking, of course, of the
secret origin of the Salinban
Mercenary Train Group.
[GASP]
Based on the look on
your face right now,
I'm assuming you do know.
Gor, what's this about?
Shante, go wait
outside, all right?
Hey, how come?
That's not fair!
There's no reason
to keep secrets.
One way or the
other, we'll all be
sure to meet them soon enough‐‐
the fallen ones, that is.
I thought those
were just old legends.
You're saying they really exist?
Well, I can see
that you're a skeptic.
But, yes, they do.
In fact, there was one
at that ruined city
that you guys investigated.
I checked it out myself
but couldn't find anything.
So now I'm looking
for it out here.
I don't get it.
What are the fallen ones?
If you want to get
all fancy about it, when
a regios is destroyed,
they're the destructive power
that remains.
But to put it more
accurately, they're
the spirits of the cities
that they once dwelled in.
The cities are destroyed,
but they live on.
The neni operator
of the 17th platoon,
she may have noticed
something in there.
I hope you're not
giving me the run around.
Listen, if the fallen ones
do truly exist, as a Lukens,
I cannot turn my back on this.
Fair enough.
All right, then
Gorneo, why don't you
take me to this neni operator.
We should chat.
Look, it's all
smashed up, Layfon.
I wouldn't get your hopes up.
It'd be nearly
impossible to repair.
I should probably
make a new one.
LAYFON: Oh, well, thanks anyway.
I still have all the data,
so I can make another one.
Shouldn't take that long.
In the meantime, how about
trying this one on for size?
OK.
Restoration.
Yeah, but it's a single edge.
Yep.
It just hit me when I was
watching you practice‐‐
rather than a sword that
takes force to hack with,
you're more suited to a
blade that can cut and stab.
That's how you move.
What's wrong, no good?
It's not that.
It's just that I don't know‐‐
Using this will let
you draw in more power.
I thought you'd like that,
not back away from it.
I mean, if that's the case,
what's the power even for?
What is the power for?
Hey, what's wrong?
Hm?
Ah!
Honestly never
thought I'd see the day
someone would sneak up on you.
You have a fever?
Still tired from yesterday?
Uh, no, it's nothing
Hey, wait!
(SIGH)
[SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
Circuit?
You're the Inspector that goes
around to different cities?
Well, I don't know.
To be completely
honest with you,
I've never actually
seen one before.
So what do you want
from me and Gadosh?
It's pretty simple.
He accepted a plea
bargain from me.
We protect you.
He gives us pertinent
information‐‐
information about
a person who is
connected to the Kalfa family.
A person who is connected
to the Kalfa family?
Who is it?
Gadosh is going
to tell me that.
I want you to meet him now.
Is that OK with you?
Yes, but if it's
going to take awhile,
I need to make a phone call.
[GRUNT]
You see, I need to call home
because my daughter's up
waiting for me, and I
should probably tell
my mother I'll be home late.
Is that all right?
Sure.
Use that phone there.
Thank you.
[SIGH]
Oh, come on now,
be honest with me.
What's the matter
with you anyway?
No, really, it's nothing.
You liar!
Just spit it out.
Why are you so
worried about it?
I told you it's no big deal.
I'm worried about it
because you're one of my men,
and I deserve to
know what's going on.
OK, but I already told you.
It's‐‐
Layfon, tell me what's up now.
[KNOCKING]
Naruki.
Did I catch you at a bad time?
I'm here on behalf
of Chief Gerin
to deliver a message to you.
OK, what is it?
What's the message?
It's about all the
commotion yesterday.
The investigation of the
overload smuggling ring
has been stepped up,
and he wants to know
if he can ask for your help.
Do you think people are
actually buying that crap?
How ridiculous.
I mean Zuellni students
aren't stupid enough
to get into stuff like that.
Yeah, well, I'd like to
think that you're right.
But given the situation with
the military arts competition
getting closer each
day and with all
of the platoon
members so intensely
devoted to their school‐‐
What proof do you have?
Unless you agree to join us
and help us solve this thing,
I'm strictly forbidden
to say anything else.
If that's the case,
then why did you
let me hear the word overload?
It's not just Layfon.
I can tell by the
way you're acting.
You either need my help
or need my consent.
Why's that?
Unless you agree, I
can't tell you that either.
Just say yes, and
I'll fill you in.
The suspect, it's someone
we know, isn't it, Naruki?
Well, is that all?
Uh, yeah‐‐ yes.
Let me make sure
I understand you.
Fon‐Fon, you've been recruited
to help out the municipal
police for some unknown reason.
Isn't that correct?
Yeah, that's it.
I understand now.
[WHIMPER]
Senior!
Felli?
[POUNDING]
Hiding things,
keeping secrets‐‐
I've had enough!
Oh.
Uh, hello there.
How are you?
And you are?
SHARNID: Man, you
sure kept us waiting.
Restoration.
[MUMBLING]
Calm down.
We won't do anything.
That's not too different
from a suspicious person
saying there's nothing
suspicious about me.
You know, I normally
don't go for your type.
Excellent,
because, similarly, I
do not wish to be liked by you.
Felli.
Ah, I guess it looks like
the gang's all here, huh?
Good, you're just
in time, Felli.
So tell me, do you
know these people?
[GRUNTING]
[SOUNDS OF FIGHTING]
Come on now.
Keep your spear up, Siena.
Our suspects are Dinn
Dee and the 10th platoon.
It would be best if you can
catch them either in possession
of or actually using overload.
Any questions?
I can't believe it.
How could he?
Well, he wouldn't do this
out of self‐interest, right?
The only way he would
try something like this
is out of a desire
to protect the city.
Even so, no matter what
his intentions might be,
we can't accept the
use of overload.
Sacrificing yourself to save
something you love dearly‐‐
it may seem like an
honorable thing to do,
but it's still self‐serving.
Dinn thinks it's for some
kind of a noble cause?
He's such a fool.
If it were me, I would
protect everything,
including my own life.
[DOOR OPENING]
MAN 1: Oh, I, uh‐‐
MAN 2: Yeah, good job, man.
Dinn, hold on.
Hm?
I really think
we need to talk.
Hm, don't make that face, OK?
I mean you're the 10th platoon's
good luck charm, Siena.
We need you to be as fearless
as ever, you understand?
Don't you worry.
We're definitely going to win.
I'll see ya.
[GASPING]
Dinn?
We need to talk.
I have nothing to say, and I
won't waste my time listening.
Just wait, it's important.
Stop with this
overload business.
I don't know what you mean.
Look, the municipal
police are on to you guys.
But you can still make it.
Get out of this while you can.
You've got some nerve
talking like that.
So now you treat me
like a criminal, huh?
Once they find the
evidence, it'll be too late.
And if I were to stop
them, what would happen?
NINA: Why go this far,
destroying yourself?
To protect this city,
I have no other choice.
The first platoon
commanded by Banzai
is the one to beat, not
just in the competitions,
but in our overall grades.
For my plan to be
truly successful,
the 10th platoon must dominate
and surpass their achievements.
Hold on.
Just forget about the
grades for a second.
If your plan could really work,
then you should be able to go
about it without cheating.
Don't be so naive.
It's not naive.
And if you're given your
team an unfair advantage,
tell me this, how will you ever
prove that your plan was valid?
With your betrayal,
you destroyed
everything I worked for!
And you're talking
to me about validity?
(ANGRILY) You used your dirty
little tricks to steal Sharnid
away from us, and now you're
standing here preaching
to me about right and wrong?
If you want to go and tell
the police what I'm doing,
knock yourself out.
But I will never deviate
from the course that I'm on.
Understand what I'm saying?
The only person who will
protect the city is me!
And do me a favor,
would you, Nina?
Tell Sharnid we'll make good on
that promise, even without him.
So has there
been any progress?
No, nothing yet.
(SIGHING) I guess they
won't show their true colors
quite so easily, will they?
NINA: Naruki, wait!
Hold on!
(PANTING) I'm sorry,
but I talked to Dinn.
I wanted to take care of it
myself, the way I saw fit.
Try to understand.
(IMPATIENT SIGH)
What were you thinking?
The way you saw fit?
Just what does that have
to do with anything?
All you did is tip them off
and give them enough info
to get away with it!
Listen to me.
I had to meet with Dinn.
I had no other choice, I swear.
You see, he and I have some
history between our platoons.
Wait, what do
you mean history?
This is about
Sharnid, isn't it?
It happened way before I'd
ever formed the 17th platoon.
Back then I was assigned to
a completely different unit.
From their first battle,
Dinn's group was special.
They were young, but they
dominated the upperclassmen.
They were so powerful.
To us, they
symbolized a new era.
They were unstoppable.
Then, one day, out
of nowhere, Sharnid
left the platoon in the
middle of a big tournament.
That broke up the trio that
had sustained the platoon,
and it fell apart.
Dinn was absolutely
furious, so furious,
in fact, that he challenged
Sharnid to a duel.
But he didn't defend himself.
Sharnid just took it.
He didn't even fight back.
Jeez.
I don't know.
Aw, come on now, ladies.
What's the worst
that could happen?
[LAUGHTER]
NINA: Not too long after, I went
to Sharnid with a proposition.
I was starting a platoon,
and I wanted him to join me.
In Dinn's mind,
it's as if I stole
Sharnid from the 10th platoon.
Yeah, but that's not
what happened, is it?
No, he'd already quit
when I approached him,
but they don't see it that way.
And now the 17th
platoon is the strongest
it's been since I started it.
We're strong enough to be
a major threat to the 10th.
[YAWNING]
Dinn's history
notwithstanding, you know I
have to report this to my boss?
Yeah, I know.
Hey!
Guys, I ran into Felli just now.
She's not gonna make it today.
What's up?
Hm?
Oh, just wanted to
say, don't try so hard.
What do you mean?
Listen, about Dinn,
if the municipal cops
are showing up in person,
it means that they're close.
And unless I'm
completely off here,
I'd say they're zeroing
in on their target.
You knew about this?
But how?
Hey, nobody knows
what the 10th platoon
is capable of better
than me, do they?
Now, I'm no detective,
but a person's K doesn't
just suddenly increase, right?
[SIGH]
(SIGH) The upperclassmen
will probably denounce
the military arts department.
Vanze could even lose his job.
They'll have to get rid
of him in order to make
the student federation happy.
The competition looks
pretty bad for us.
LAYFON: What about Zuellni?
If they graduate before it
happens, then who cares, right?
With things like this,
there's only one person
we can go to for sound advice.
I'm talking about our
student council president.
Are you sure we
should do that?
It can't be helped.
I mean, what other
choice do we have now,
since they decided to
take things this far?
Yes, I understand.
And what exactly would
you like for me to do?
Mr. President, I'm sure
you don't want there to be
commotion any more than we do.
We'd like you to deal
with it privately.
Well, dealing with it
privately is relatively simple.
All I have to do is
convince the chief of police
to close the investigation.
Mr. President,
that isn't going to‐‐
Of course, that alone
won't be enough, will it?
This will require your
participation, too.
What would you have us do?
You face the 10th
platoon in competition
very soon, don't you?
Wait a second, you
want us to destroy them?
Oh, no, I don't want
you to take it that far.
I just want you to render
them incapable of remaining
a platoon.
And if that were
to happen, I could
use my absolute
authority to order
them to disband immediately.
NINA: That would rob them
of their sense of purpose.
Well, better that than robbing
the students of their own city.
So Layfon, can you do it?
Hm?
Come on, if you can't,
then just say so, all right?
He can do it!
It's him!
What makes you so sure he can?
Tell me, Haia.
Because people trained
in the Saiharden style
have that kind of technique.
Stabbing someone with
a needle of ballistic K
makes it easy to heal
or break someone, even
for a guy like him,
who's a former keeper
of the heaven's blade.
But still, Saiharden
techniques only
work with a single‐edged blade.
They're impossible with
a dual‐edged sword.
Put converse, though,
with a single‐edged blade
it is possible for him, yes?
Sir, this one's the
leader of the Salinban
Mercenary Training Group.
But many of us suspect he's
also involved with the overload
smuggling ring.
That's what you yahoos
are doing here, am I right?
Isn't that precisely why you
came up here today, to get
together and cover it up?
Stop it!
Fon‐Fon!
Next time won't be so easy.
That's fine by me.
But I won't let you
use the Saiharden
name if you can't even
master a single‐edged blade.
Enough, you two.
Haia, listen, the only
reason that I called you here
is because you said you
had words for Layfon,
and not to allow
you both to fight.
Wait, what words?
It's the fallen ones.
You must have seen one in that
ruined city you went into.
They're unlike anything
you would have seen before.
They're mysterious and power.
Trust me, you don't
want that thing coming
anywhere near here,
which is exactly
why I'm going to capture it
Hey, what's the
matter, Naruki?
Oh, sorry about that.
I'm just mad because
of work stuff.
Everything's been put on hold.
What's going on?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
No big deal.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Mining operations
are almost completed.
Sir, can we proceed with the
platoon battles as scheduled?
[RUMBLING]
[WIND BLOWING]
[CROWDS CHEERING]
(LAUGHING) Now, now.
[GASPING]
I've got a favor
to ask of you guys.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
ANNOUNCER: The competition
against the 10th platoon
has finally arrived.
Dinn, although
backed into a corner,
will not bend from
his convictions.
But in the background,
an unsettling shadow
creeps forward, next
time, "The Fallen
Ones Appear" and restoration.