[MUSIC PLAYING]
VOICES (VOICEOVER): Funimation.
You should be watching.
AILEIN: I was hoping the
highway would have gotten
us out of their turf by now.
I'll step on it, then.
AILEIN: Do it.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
RAMIS: What's that?
What is that?
Hey there, Ramis.
Zidd!
Have you heard
of inhuman beings?
They're literally
non‐human creatures.
Near the boundary,
aurora particles
can leak from insulation space
and cause major deformities
in the natural laws.
That's how the damn
things are created.
RAMIS: Wait a second.
Are you talking about
that rumor about the holes
in our aurora field?
Ah‐huh.
RAMIS: Yeah.
I've heard about that.
It's some kind of
pollution, isn't it?
But they say it's not
really dangerous to people
as long as you're not close
to the field's boundaries.
Isn't that right?
AILEIN: Oh yeah?
[SCOFF] Try telling them that.
[THEME MUSIC]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Ah!
MAN: What are you, stupid?
What kind of spider gets
trapped in its own web?
Even a baby spider knows rushing
past strand transformation
and going straight
for web making
is biting off more
than you can chew.
Now, get on your feet.
LAYFON (VOICEOVER):
When I was young,
all I cared about
was getting stronger.
But then I came to Zuellni
looking to change my life.
NINA: Motion response.
Look out.
Layfon!
What's going on?
We're practicing.
You're gonna need to get
your head in the game.
Yeah.
Right.
NINA: Tomorrow is the
big competition between
the 3rd and 11th platoons.
That means we have the day off.
You can come with me and
watch the competition
or get some rest.
I'll leave that
decision up to you.
You don't have
to tell me twice.
See you.
Hey.
What are you gonna do?
Watching the other
platoons compete
might be a good
learning experience.
Uh, well, the thing is, I‐‐
I've already made
some plans, actually.
OK.
Looks like it's just
you and me, Nina.
Guess I'll see you there.
Right.
Layfon.
Hey, Nina.
What's up?
I don't know what
you did in the past
to fail in the Military Arts,
and to tell you the truth,
I don't care.
But in order for
the 17th platoon
to keep on winning, to
keep growing stronger,
we're going to
need your strength.
Think about that, Layfon.
To keep growing stronger.
Right.
FELLI: But for that to
happen, they're going to need
your strength, aren't they.
Hello, Fon‐Fon
Oh, hey.
Where'd you come from?
Ah!
Ow.
Come on!
What was that for?
I simply opened the
eyes of a certain someone
so that our leader's words
don't influence him or make
him act foolishly again.
You heard what she said to me?
Worry about what
other people say
and you're guaranteed to make
a fool of yourself, you know.
That‐‐ that's just‐‐
What?
Do you disagree?
Uh, if that's the case,
then you're guilty too.
Because the other
day, even you‐‐
What's that?
Uh, nothing at all.
That whole incident
was nothing but a fluke.
Besides, I'm
continuing to explore
other alternatives in
order to figure out
what I want to do with my life.
Hey.
I'm doing everything
that I can too, you know.
Like going out to
eat with Naruki
and her friends on my day off.
FELLI: That's rather small.
LAYFON: Well, you start
small, and slowly but surely‐‐
FELLI: That's too
small, Fon‐Fon.
MAYSHEN (VOICEOVER):
Where is he?
LAYFON: Look.
There are lots of things
I'm thinking about doing,
but I just can't.
You know, between
training and cleaning
at the machinery department,
I just don't have the time.
You're just making excuses.
Hey.
They're not excuses.
FELLI: Go away.
Don't follow me.
LAYFON: I'm not.
We just happen to take
the same route home.
Layfie.
Oh no.
He's gone, isn't he?
Those two seem close.
I wonder what their deal is.
Hey.
What are you two doing here?
MIFI: They are in
the same platoon.
You know what that means.
They've spent a lot more time
together than the two of you
have.
If I were you, I'd be careful.
Poor Layfie.
What if he gets snatched
up by a senior, huh?
Hey, I'm just kidding!
Besides, we wouldn't
let that happen to you.
We've totally got your back.
You don't need to
worry about anything.
This from the girl who's
always stirring things up.
It all comes down to tomorrow.
Stick to the plan and
it'll work out, right?
Right.
LAYFON: Oh.
So Naruki and Mifi
can't make it?
MAYSHEN: Well, you
see, Nari has to work
security for the competition.
They were kind of understaffed.
And Mifi he had to, um‐‐
well, she's‐‐ she's, uh‐‐
she's working on a big story
for the "Weekly Look'n."
Wow.
Those two sure are working
hard these days, huh?
Well, what should we do then?
Should we call it off?
We could all get
together some other time.
Oh.
Either way is fine with me.
I mean, uh, whatever
you think is best.
Sorry for the wait.
Enjoy your meal, folks.
This looks great.
They say there's usually
a line out the door here,
but it's empty today.
Yeah, that's true.
I guess it's not
as busy today as it
usually is because everybody's
off watching the competition.
Well, I think we
got lucky, actually.
There's nothing wrong with
a little peace and quiet,
you know?
I suppose you're right.
Quiet's good.
[BLOWING]
I wonder how
Meyshie's doing tonight.
I hope everything
goes as planned.
Well, it's gotta be
more fun than sitting here
eating noodles with us, right?
Guess so.
[CHEERING]
NINA (VOICEOVER): Hm.
So he didn't show after all.
Layfie.
Is everything OK?
What's wrong?
Are you worried about
the competition?
Uh, no.
I just‐‐ I'm fine.
No big deal.
MAYSHEN: That was delicious.
You know that place is
famous for its sweets.
I've been dying to eat
there for a long time now.
Oh.
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't realize you
wanted anything else.
I guess we should have
ordered some dessert, huh?
It's OK.
Here.
Wow.
Did you bake these
cookies all by yourself?
Yes, I did.
I made them for you.
Do you want some?
Uh, yeah.
Sure.
LAYFON (VOICEOVER): I
probably should have
told her I don't like sweets.
Uh.
All right.
Let's dig in.
Well?
Do you like it?
Ah.
Delicious.
I'm so glad.
Mifi told me that you
wanted to become a baker,
but I didn't know
you already knew how
to make such delicious cookies.
Amazing.
Mm mm.
Thank you, but I think
that you're the amazing one.
You were incredible at the
competition the other day,
and were so cool.
So confident.
Making these desserts is
the only thing I'm good at.
Hey.
That's not true.
You have a specific goal
in mind for yourself,
and now you're already
making some major strides
towards achieving it.
I'm sort of envious,
to tell you the truth.
MAYSHEN: Huh?
LAYFON (VOICEOVER): I wonder
if I'll ever find my purpose.
Will I, Leerin?
[RUMBLING]
Ah!
Mayshen!
What the heck's happening?
[RUMBLING]
Are you all right Mayshen?
What?
What was that, Layfie?
LAYFON (VOICEOVER): No.
It can't be.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
KALIAN: Our situation is grave.
Over 30% of Zuellni's
legs have sunk
deep into collapsed ground.
As a result, movement
is no longer possible.
So we can't get out, sir?
Under normal circumstances,
we would be able to extract
ourselves unaided.
But this, it's not normal.
At the moment, we're completely
overrun by these larvals.
Did he say larvals?
Does he mean
young Contaminoids.
But sir, I don't get it.
The city should be moving
to avoid things like this.
It shouldn't be happening.
It doesn't make any sense.
The city can
only avoid threats
if they're attacking
from above ground,
but I'm afraid we've
stepped into a nest.
A dormant mother went
underground to lay eggs
and we're right in
the middle of it.
Every last one of those
newborn larvals are starving.
Normally, the mother would
offer herself up for food
once she's finished
laying the eggs,
but this time, it's different.
Because another nutrient
source is close by,
the mother won't
sacrifice herself.
I hope you all understand
the danger we're in.
I've already advised that
citizens evacuate the city.
All right.
Now listen up, students.
Get your DITE's ready.
The municipal police will handle
the guiding and evacuating
of all civilians.
You'll serve as the core of
the Contaminoid offensive.
This isn't a drill, people,
so you'll have to fight
with everything you've got.
[CHATTER]
Do you really think we'll
be able to beat these things?
KALIAN: It's our only option.
Students, we must
defeat these creatures.
The only alternative is death.
For the sake of the city
of Zuellni, our home,
we have no choice
but to defeat them.
NINA: We've been assigned
to the Northwest sector
along with the 9th Platoon.
Where's Felli?
Why can't we get a hold of her?
Nina.
Where have you been?
Don't you know that
we've come under attack?
I know all about it.
We're in big trouble.
We have to get out
of here right away.
‐ What are you saying?
‐ Listen.
We need to get to the shelters.
We have to evacuate.
Evacuate?
Don't be ridiculous.
There's no way I'm
running from this.
You don't get it.
Those are Contaminoids.
A bunch of students with
no real battle experience
banding together won't‐‐
NINA: Won't have a prayer?
That's right.
They won't.
This isn't a game, Nina.
It's not just some
competition between students.
Every one of them
is going to die.
And so what if we do?
What's your point?
Tell me, what else
are our powers for?
Why do they live
inside each of us?
To protect those who
are important to us,
to defend our home.
No, I'm not running away,
and you shouldn't either.
Your life's been peaceful.
You don't know
what you're saying.
Layfon, you're different.
You're not like the
rest of us here.
So you tell me why.
With all the power you have,
why are you running away?
Why won't you stay
here and fight with me?
Because you have no
idea how terrifying
the Contaminoids really are.
You're naive.
You don't know what it
means to take them on.
If we don't stand up
to them now, then when?
Now move!
Nina.
[BUZZING]
All right.
No turning back now.
Artillery, fire!
[GUNFIRE]
Concentrate all your fire
on the ones in the air.
We've got to keep those
things away from the city.
Yeah, roger that.
I've got a date tomorrow.
There's no way I'm
gonna die today.
Not like this.
[GUNFIRE]
I won't let these
monsters be the end of me.
Restoration.
Now, move out!
[CHEERING]
The shell.
It's so hard.
LAYFON (VOICEOVER): There's
no reason for me to fight.
[WIND BLOWING]
But I‐‐
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[SCREAMING]
Harley.
You're here.
Layfon.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I need you to make
two different settings
for this DITE.
Hold on.
Two settings?
You heard me.
LAYFON (VOICEOVER): Senior.
Fon‐Fon.
I mean Felli.
There's something I
need your help with.
The larvals are
doing the attacking.
That means the mother has to
be sleeping somewhere nearby.
I need its precise location.
Find it, Felli.
FELLI (VOICEOVER):
This is a surprise.
Now even you tell
me to use my Nen‐I.
If you don't help
me, everyone will die.
LAYFON (VOICEOVER): Felli.
Were the only ones
who can save them.
Please.
Amazing.
You're so hopelessly
soft hearted, aren't you?
There's way too many of them.
Fall back.
Fall back!
Wait.
Don't run away!
Stay at your posts!
If we don't stop
them, we're finished!
Dammit.
[SHOUT]
[SCREECHING]
SHARNID: Nina, look out!
Ah!
Damn.
Nina.
Get out of the way.
NINA: I'm gonna die.
What the?
How?
LAYFON: You all right?
NINA: Layfon.
It's you!
I found the nest.
It's like you said.
She's not too far from here.
I'll find a way
in and guide you.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Nina!
NINA: Layfon.
How‐‐ how did you do this?
Did you‐‐
‐ Look.
There's no time to
explain right now.
Just get out of here, please.
I don't‐‐
You have to go.
Look.
I can handle the
larvals myself, but
if the mother calls for back up,
then we're all in big trouble.
Ah!
Handle the larvals.
Layfong.
How can you‐‐
FELLI (VOICEOVER):
You'll only have five
minutes outside of the city.
Any more than that, and
even your lungs won't last.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Don't die on me, Fong‐Fong.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CREAKING]
The reason I came to
Zuellni to begin with
is because I wanted
to stop fighting.
Restoration 01.
But now I fully understand.
If I wanna keep living, this
is the only option I have.
This is it, because this is
the world that I live in.
WOMAN: Just talk to me.
Tell me where it hurts.
GIRL: Are you‐‐ are
you all right, sir?
MAN: Thanks.
I'm OK.
Layfon!
Nina.
I'm so glad you're all right.
You're an idiot.
Did you know that, Layfon?
To go flying out of
the city with no gear?
You must be crazy.
I suppose that was a little
on the careless side, huh?
Layfon.
I'm sorry about that.
I think maybe I overdid
it just a little bit.
I'm gonna take a quick nap.
Huh?
Uh, hold on.
What exactly do you
think you're doing?
Hey!
Now, wake up!
I'm serious.
Get off of me!
Layfon.
Oh, forget it.
Rest up.
You did a great job.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN (VOICEOVER): Mayshen
mistakenly receives a letter
addressed to Layfon
and the girls
become concerned with the
sender's relationship to him.
Meanwhile, for some
unknown reason,
Layfon gets invited
over to Felli's house.
Next time, The Letter from
Glendan and Restoration.