[MUSIC PLAYING]
Funimation.
You should be watching.
You do not have the ultimate
sentiment to sustain me,
but your sympathy
for your city will
allow me to become your blade.
Stay back.
Stop it!
No!
Zuellni?
You want me to go?
But where?
Where am I?
[THEME MUSIC]
How many?
500.
And all of them are juveniles.
But I'm not reading
any other bioactivity.
Felli, begin the next search.
It's my fault. I shouldn't
have told her to go.
Restoration 02!
Another group of
contaminoids, and we're
already in their territory?
Yes, sir.
There have been three
encounters with juveniles
in the last two days alone.
Based on our intel,
we should expect more.
And the electronic spirit?
It remains missing.
Hey, nice work.
I'll need this repaired
really quickly, Harley.
Layfon, I could get that single
bladed DITE really faster.
Do you remember the
experimental one that I made?
You could use your full power.
It shouldn't burn out at all.
What do you‐‐
I'll take the
same one as always!
Dude, you need
to get some rest.
It's been three times
since yesterday, right?
If Nina were here, she'd
tell you to sleep, you know?
Any word?
Hm?
Is there any word?
Nina's still missing, Fon Fon.
Then we're going back
out again in six hours.
Please, get everything ready.
Hey!
Fon Fon's heart‐‐
it will not rest.
Not until‐‐
Felli!
Grab her!
This has certainly
thrown a big monkey
wrench into our travel plans.
They've got guns.
Do you think they're
going to shoot us?
Hey, don't worry about it.
This is Maya.
It's an academic city.
I doubt they'll start shooting,
but they might put us in jail.
I'm telling you, I've
got nothing to do with it.
Nothing‐‐
I'm sure you don't,
and I'm very sorry.
However, an item that's
extremely valuable to this city
was recently stolen,
so we're questioning
all passengers on roaming
buses scheduled to depart.
This item that was
stolen‐‐ what was it?
I can't tell you.
It's classified information.
Once again, I am truly
sorry about this, Leerin.
We're treating you like you
were just some common criminal.
Well, you could stop.
Use mine.
I must insist.
I'm innocent, so I don't
know why you're holding me.
Can't I just get
on the next bus?
Tell me, what is this, exactly?
They're stopped.
Police!
Get your hands up, now!
Since you protect the
city, I'll do as you say.
He said they can't
clear me of suspicion
because I have a DITE.
And on top of that, I'm not
supposed to leave this room,
except to eat.
Then you're going to get fat.
You don't have
any couth, do you?
Naw, I guess not.
Well, see ya.
Huh?
But the game's
not even over yet.
I would have won, anyway.
Bye.
Hey!
Wait, you don't know that.
You jerk.
And it was my turn, too.
Look at that.
I hate that guy.
Electronic spirits
that have gone mad
from losing their cities.
Fallen ones.
They can make a
military artist who's
already powerful stronger.
Unstoppable.
I'm not going to
let you do that.
[LAUGHTER]
So, you're an
inhuman being like me?
Enjoying your visit
to this dimension?
I'll enjoy it a hell of a more
once I've gotten rid of you!
[GUNFIRE]
MALE VOICE: Then you're
going to get fat.
You're putting it back?
So does that mean the
food's really awful here?
No.
It's just‐‐
[SHRIEKING]
Are you OK?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
I'm so sorry.
No, it was my fault. I
did startle you, after all.
Oh, that's OK.
By the way, my name is Leerin.
Leerin Marfes.
If you don't mind, could
I ask what yours is?
Leerin?
No, you couldn't
be the same one.
It's nice to meet you, Leerin.
My name's Nina Antalk.
So tell me, Nina‐‐
I guess you don't care very
much for chickpeas, do you?
No.
Not really.
What brought you here to Maya?
Don't know.
I just woke up, and I was here.
Weird, huh?
I guess there's a
good reason for that,
even if I don't know what it is.
Sorry, I must
sound crazy to you.
No, go on.
Have you ever had a
dream like that before?
You don't know why
you are where you are,
but you have something
important to do.
And you have to do
it quickly, too.
There's a real sense of urgency.
You know what I mean?
Yeah!
The 100 pies.
Hm?
I don't know why, but I have
this dream where I'm working
in a bakery, for some reason.
Customers are pouring
in, and I have
to make 100 pies all by myself.
It's just this crazy, reoccuring
dream that I keep having.
Does that sound like what
you're talking about, Nina?
Well, to be honest,
it actually does.
I also have‐‐
I'm sorry, Nina.
This is a strange thing to
be talking about, isn't it?
It is.
But that's OK In fact,
it's pretty interesting.
Please, keep going.
Kay.
MAN: Another group of
juveniles has been spotted.
Estimated time of
contact is 18 hours.
And Felli's condition?
The exam results showed fatigue
due to prolonged Nen‐I use,
Mr. President.
I see.
Keep me apprised.
Contaminoids just keep coming.
What do we do?
There's a limit to how
much we can rely on one man.
We have to assemble
our platoons,
and tell everyone the truth.
That's going to cause a panic.
I don't think so.
I won't let it.
Just trust me on this.
Fon Fon?
Finally awake?
You're one to talk.
Ow!
What was that for?
Because it infuriates me.
Wait, what does?
You being here.
Nina‐‐ shouldn't you be
looking for her if you've
got the time to spare?
Well, Fon Fon?
Yeah, you're right.
[GUNSHOT]
‐No!
Fon Fon!
Wow.
This bird isn't very timid.
I wonder if it might have
been someone's pet once?
What do you think, Nina?
This one!
All right.
You should get back
to your friends now.
OK.
Are you up for another game?
What is it?
It's acting so strange.
What, the bird?
Yeah.
Instead of flying away, it
came straight back here.
[CHIRPING]
What are they doing?
What's going on?
An electronic spirit!
Nina!
Wait!
[ALARM]
Hey, what's going on?
Aren't you going
to let us evacuate?
I'm glad I found you.
Oh.
Hey, Savaris.
That noise‐‐
Yeah, it's an alert.
Contaminants are approaching.
No need to panic, everyone.
Head to the shelters,
and rest assured
that we, the military
artists of Maya,
will do everything
to defend this city.
Good luck, Loy.
Thank you.
Now get to the shelter, OK?
Yes, sir.
How long is that siren
going to keep blaring?
Don't know.
Make it stop!
But sir‐‐
Just do it!
Time to go.
Go?
But where?
Hey!
Just what do you
think you're doing?
Exactly what I've
been told to do.
To keep you from getting hurt.
Who told you to do that?
Sorry.
Can't say.
I thought so.
What's that?
Wait.
What?
I think that's an
electronic spirit.
What is?
That glowing thing.
Can't you see it?
Glowing thing?
There's nothing there.
Let her do what she wants
and protect her, huh?
That's easier said than done.
An electronic spirit‐‐
I get it.
If that's what was
stolen, then this
is all starting to make sense.
The reason why this
city's on edge.
Why its legs have
stopped moving.
Maybe it's time to
do whatever I want.
What's with the mask?
Such power‐‐ come
with us, Nina Antalk.
You know me?
Wouldn't you like
to change the world?
You can.
The aurora field
makes that possible.
Rickario's ideology‐‐
It is nothing but dust
before the dreams of Ignatius.
Ricksario?
You don't mean‐‐
I understand.
Something's trapped
your friends, hasn't it?
This thing, huh?
Leave it to me.
Almost‐‐ Ah!
You saved me!
Hold on.
This bird is‐‐ an
electronic spirit.
It really is amazing.
A gathering?
That's right.
All of the citizens
and military artists
will be assembling soon.
Well, I guess the
former Heaven's
Blade couldn't handle it alone.
Even if that is the
case, you were still
unable to beat him yourself.
Hey!
Easy.
It's painful, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Thanks to your tranquilizer gun.
You didn't leave me with
much of a choice, Layofn.
You hurt your
shoulder by fighting,
and you're still recovering
from your back operation‐‐
so I couldn't allow you
to do anything physical.
Up till now you've
told me to fight.
Now you're telling me not to?
That's because in the
past it's been necessary.
More contaminoids
are only hours away,
and until then you must rest.
Look, there's no way I
can do that right now.
Why not?
Because laying around
here doing nothing
would be unforgivable,
you bastard!
And why is that?
Who is it that
wouldn't forgive you?
What do you mean?
You're staying.
And you do know what I mean,
and who I'm talking about.
You're not considering
this city's condition,
nor are you concerned
about the contaminoids,
or that you must be well rested
for the battle against them.
No!
That's not true.
There's only one thing on
your mind right now, Layfon.
Instead of Zuellni, it's
Nina Antalk, isn't it?
I can't let you squander your
power on personal matters.
I can only let you
use it for our city.
Zuellni's survival is critical.
More than Nina's ever could be.
He must rest, even if I
have to force him to do so.
You are all intelligent
and mature man and women,
and I'm sure you've
heard that our city
is facing a grave danger.
In a few hours, Zuellni will
be surrounded by contaminoids.
However, it is far too
soon to abandon hope.
Our platoon class
military artists
have already been apprised
of our current situation.
They do not consider it
to be one of despair.
Rather, they have pledged to
face this difficulty head on!
They are courageously putting
their lives on the line.
Not just for Zuellni, but also
for each and every one of you
who calls it home.
So, will you see them off with
looks of anguish on your faces?
I've heard it said before
that great orators never
die pretty deaths, Kalian.
You're just too good.
Or will it be with
expressions of faith
that they will save our city?
[APPLAUSE]
Felli?
Kalian and the
doctors have told
me that I'm forbidden from using
Nen‐I until I'm fully rested.
Sounds familiar.
But if you need me to do it,
I can send out Nen‐I for you
without using my terminal.
And if you wish, I can even
count the number of scales
on each contaminoid out there.
If you want me to do
this, I'll be happy to.
What shall I do?
Absolutely nothing at all.
But Fon Fon‐‐
[THEME MUSIC]
NARRATOR: Leerin and
Nina have finally
met in the academic city Maya.
As a result of the contaminoids,
the fallen one inside Nina
once again manifests.
Meanwhile in Zuellni,
a Kae‐Ra blast
is prepared to stop
the contaminoids.
Next time, A Guided Encounter.
And restoration.