[MUSIC PLAYING]
VOICES (VOICEOVER): Funimation.
You should be watching.
Well, that cerneum mine
may not be much to look at,
but to me, it's
absolutely beautiful.
Hm.
And seeing as it's the
only one that Zuellni has,
I feel the same way.
We can't lose it, Vanze.
If we do, we're dead.
Isn't that the 10th
Platoon leader?
VANZE: Yeah.
Dinn Dee.
Heh.
It's funny.
The previous leader
of his platoon
used to do the same thing.
That rolling bus
looks unfamiliar.
[THEME MUSIC]
[WHOOSHING]
NINA: I heard a municipal
battle might be coming up soon.
Yeah.
Those things are pretty
big deals, aren't they?
Yep.
They sure are.
There's a cerneum mine at stake.
We only have one mine left, and
we can't afford to lose it, so
what are you guys
standing around for?
Now come train with me.
The loser buys dinner.
What do you say?
That sounds good to me.
Who else is in?
Uh.
The possibility
of a free dinner
is too food to pass up, so sure.
You can count me in as well.
And you, Fon‐Fon?
Uh.
If you can't hit a ball
back or if it touches you,
it counts as one point.
Whoever ends up with
the most points loses.
Restoration 01.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
NINA: I want a rematch.
Hey.
I don't mind chipping in.
Uh‐uh.
No way.
She's the one who
lost the bet, dude.
I'll take this pasta
dish that's listed here.
Since she's paying, I'll
have the ginger pork.
Wait.
I never said I was
buying you dinner.
HARLEY: Oh, really?
NINA: Of course not.
HARLEY: Will you at
least buy me a drink?
NINA: No.
Hey.
How's it going, Dinn?
Good.
Much like the 17th's been doing.
That's Dinn Dee, Fon‐Fon.
The leader of the 10th Platoon.
But then again,
I'm sure that success
has nothing to do with you and
more to do with your teammates.
Wow.
Thanks for the vote
of confidence, buddy.
DINN: You know, the 10th
has grown closer as a unit
ever since you left, Sharnid.
Aw, really?
That's so touching.
And would you look at that?
Siena seems to be
in fine spirits.
DINN: Hey.
You're not one of us
anymore, smart ass,
so don't call her that.
Chill out.
Oh.
Have you heard?
My platoon is gonna be
pitted against yours
in the next competition,
and I really can't wait.
Since you abandoned the 10th
Platoon the way you did,
Sharnid, I'm looking forward
to getting some payback,
and I promise, it
won't be pretty.
[BELL CHIMING]
They used to be teammates.
Sharnid was in the 10th
platoon until last year.
And then one day he
just left all of a sudden?
That's right.
But why?
Seems to be a really big bone
of contention to that Dinn guy.
It is.
I don't know why he left.
But when, well,
that's another story,
and it was during a competition.
As a result, the 10th's
standing dropped considerably
because of him doing so.
He left during?
FELLI: Not very
responsible, huh?
Bye!
See you!
[GIGGLING]
LAYFON: But.
FELLI: But what?
Well‐‐
NARUKI: Layfie.
I'm glad you're here.
Can you come with me right away?
OK.
Come on!
See you, Felli.
[SIRENS WAILING]
What's going on?
From the looks of things, this
isn't a routine investigation.
You're right.
It's not.
We received a tip that
people posing as students
were selling Overload.
That drug that
accelerates Kei flow?
GAREN: Yeah.
It causes an explosive
increase in both Kei
and Nen‐I production.
It would be incredibly useful if
it wasn't for the side effects.
LAYFON: I don't get it.
Why would they wanna sell a
drug like that here, Zuellni?
It's an academic city,
not a military one.
Would it even be profitable?
With rumors of a municipal
battle coming up, yeah.
I think it would be.
The dealers probably assumed
there'd be a greater demand
for it in a city like this one.
There's 10 of them.
Luckily, they're not
Military Artists.
No.
They are.
You sure?
So our intel was wrong.
Are they hiding?
Ah‐huh.
But they're trying
to provoke us.
What?
[LAUGHING] Hey.
What's going on, man?
You taking off already?
No way.
I'm just changing locations.
See you later, guys.
Have a good one.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOTS]
All right.
We're gonna win this.
[WHISTLE]
Huh?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
They're coming.
[EXPLOSION]
NARUKI: Down!
Restoration 01.
Layfon!
[SHOUTING]
[LAUGHING]
Real funny look on
your face there, buddy.
LAYFON (VOICEOVER): A sword?
[LAUGHING]
No you don't.
NARUKI: Layfon, wait!
All forces, move in.
Where are they?
GAREN (VOICEOVER):
Don't let them escape.
NINA: The police.
Layfon.
[SCUTTLING]
Was that Layfon?
Damn.
NINA (VOICEOVER): What's going
on, and why is Layfon involved?
Who's there?
MYUNFA: I'm sorry.
But you see, I can't
let anyone get past.
NINA: Restoration.
I don't have time to
deal with you right now.
[EXPLOSIONS]
[LAUGHING]
So we meet again.
It's you.
Where are you off to, Ramis?
To see your friends?
[INAUDIBLE]?
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMING]
Well, I guess the highway's
no longer an option.
Yes, but I plotted
some alternative routes.
I'm ready at any time.
You're the greatest.
[GUNSHOT]
HEADS: I can't see!
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAM]
Go!
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Wow.
You got pretty close there, bub.
You're good at sensing
my attacks too.
But is that all
the famous Layfon
Wolfstein Asleif has got?
Hey.
You're holding back, aren't you?
Come on.
You've gotta be.
I know you're a former keeper of
the Heaven's Blade, but still.
You should be able to do a
whole lot better than that.
You must be from
Glendan, aren't you?
Yeah.
It's a pleasure to
meet a fellow native.
Haia Salinban Lyia
at your service.
LAYFON: That tattoo.
The Salinban Mercenary
Training Group.
HAIA: Yep.
I'm the third generation leader.
LAYFON: Is that so?
I never thought I'd
see the day when
a member of a group with a
proud history such as yours
would be selling Overload.
Hmph.
I couldn't care less
about those scumbags.
I only used them
to get here, and I
have no intention
of helping them
sling that crap in this city.
Used them?
Then what is it
that you're after?
You're not the sharpest tool
in the shed, are you, buddy?
Well, since I'm not
here to sell Overload,
there's only one thing
that it could be.
That's the Fallen
Ones, of course.
What are you talking about?
HAIA Yeah.
The Fallen Ones.
LAYFON: I don't understand.
Hold on.
You mean you really don't know?
Jeez.
You weren't a Heaven's
Blade for long, were you?
I guess I was spot
on when I said
you're not all that sharp, huh?
Look.
Just forget it.
Hey, did you know
that your teacher
and our second generation
leader were brother disciples
under the same master?
I guess that makes you and
me cousin disciples then,
doesn't it?
We're a part of the same
Saiharden style lineage,
aren't we?
But still.
I can't help but
wonder why you're using
a DITE instead of a real sword.
You know, bub, until
you get serious,
I'm gonna keep attacking you
with everything I've got!
Ah!
What's the deal?
You holding back like this
isn't a challenge at all.
Instead, you're boring me!
Man, what happened to you?
Don't tell me that
losing your blade
made you lose your nerve too.
Watch your mouth.
Call for backup.
Roger, captain.
SIENA: What are you doing here?
Me?
What can I say?
I enjoy taking nightly strolls.
Like you do, as I recall.
But my walks don't
normally end with a weapon
pressed against my back.
Now, how about yours?
SIENA: You always
were a smartass.
Don't move.
I'll ask you one more time.
What are you doing here?
I told you.
I like taking my
evening strolls, Siena.
SIENA: Yeah?
Since when do you
like things like that?
SHARNID: People do
change, you know.
Really?
Is that right?
They sure do.
Siena, listen.
I'm telling the truth.
I was out taking a walk and
came across this commotion
just by accident.
That's why I'm here.
I promise.
I'm assuming that's
why you're here too.
Of course it is.
You see?
Now that we know
neither one of us
caused that ruckus, I'm
gonna put my hands down, OK?
Well, I gotta go.
See you, Siena.
Sharnid, wait.
Why'd you run out on us?
You really don't know?
That's why I'm asking.
Sure about that?
Tell me.
I wanna know why.
The three of us all made
a solemn promise together.
Did you forget that?
No.
Of course not.
How could I?
Then why?
I'm gonna uphold
the pact we made,
but I have to do it in
my own way, all right?
And you believe
that you can do
it so much better with the 17th
instead of with our platoon.
Is that it?
I really don't know, Siena.
It's just‐‐
It's just what?
Well, it's just when you
start wanting everything,
you usually end up losing
everything in the process.
In other words,
don't end up like me.
Later.
[LAUGHING]
[EXPLOSION]
No.
Not another one.
NINA: Layfon.
Nina.
What are you doing here?
I'm the one who
should be asking that.
What the hell happened?
Um, well, you see, guess I
kind of got in a little fight.
[SNORING]
GORNEO: Hey.
Wake up.
Shante.
I swear.
All you ever seem to
do is eat and sleep.
Come on Shante.
Ah, wait a minute.
I better get that report.
[CREAKING]
Who's there?
HAIA: Well.
I guess you passed that test.
Hold on.
Please.
Make yourselves at home.
I insist.
Gee, thanks, but this
happens to be my room.
Argh.
[HISSING]
Now, why don't you come
out of there, Myunfa.
MYUNFA: K.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Your majesty.
We cannot thank you enough
for your generosity, and are
now forever in your debt.
No.
Think nothing of it.
Are your wounds healed?
DIRK: Yes.
They are, your majesty.
I've made a full recovery
thanks to the care
that you kindly granted me.
Please It was nothing at all.
Just a minor medical expense.
And one that was
painfully little
compared to all the
efforts that you've
expended for this city, Dirk.
I'm undeserving of
such words, my queen.
You've helped Glendan time
and again, both by your own hand
and by the countless Heaven's
Blades you've trained.
But your majesty, I
have also failed you.
You didn't.
He did.
His fate was brought about
by his own immaturity
and a lack of awareness
regarding the world.
You are by no means responsible.
Hm.
And speaking of Layfon, how
is he faring these days, Leerin?
I do recall that both you
and he were fairly close.
The two of you have been
exchanging letters ever
since he left, haven't you?
Yes.
Um, I mean, yes, your majesty.
We have.
Well, then.
Where is he and how is he doing?
He's good, your majesty,
and currently in a city
called Zuellni.
The academic city.
He was never very
good in school,
so it's a miracle
that he even passed
the entrance examination.
Was it you who
taught him to study?
Yes, ma'am.
QUEEN: Good for you.
So tell me, what
do his letters say?
Are his studies difficult?
Well, he seems to be
doing OK, and he said
he's made some new friends.
Oh, I see.
And so that weighs heavily
upon your mind, does it?
Yes, ma'am.
Um, my queen.
DIRK: Hm?
What is it, Leerin?
Layfon.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Your majesty.
Can he never return?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
KALIAN (VOICEOVER): The
municipal police move
in to apprehend those
suspected of using Overload,
the illegal substance
being sold on campus,
and Sharnid begins
to suspect that some
of his former comrades
may be involved.
Next time.
The Sentiment that
Lies in the Barrel
of a Gun and Restoration.