[MUSIC PLAYING]
NARRATOR: Funimation.
You should be watching.
[WIND GUSTING]
[ELECTRICITY ZAPPING]
MAN (ON LOUDSPEAKER):
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have just been informed
that contaminoids
are currently approaching the
lower section of the city.
As a result, we'll be
delaying our departure until
the situation is under control.
Please remain calm and seated.
As a reminder, this
vessel has been designed
to withstand an attack.
However, things might
get a little bumpy.
[SHOUTING]
[SCREAMING]
[ROAR]
You can do this.
Don't get nervous.
Worrying about it will
only make you sick.
Just remember to relax.
Oh, come on.
What kind of advice is that?
All the kid needs to remember is
to strike hard and strike fast.
It doesn't take
that much effort.
You're wrong.
As a Heaven's Blade, you have
to strike with everything.
When battling contaminoids,
you grant no quarter
and show no mercy,
giving it all you've got.
You must use your strength
and techniques to the fullest.
That is the only way you can
achieve absolute victory.
[ROAR]
[SCREAMING]
Ah!
[SCREAM]
If you're getting to test
your skills against a six‐stager
like [INAUDIBLE] here,
then Her Majesty must
have a lot of faith in you.
Hope you're ready for this.
Restoration.
Mighty pierce and smash.
You idiots, move.
[EXPLOSION]
Well, that could
do some damage.
I guess that's
why the old crone
told us to fight it
in the outer areas
and not near the city proper.
DELBONE (VOICEOVER): That old
crone can hear you, Lintens.
I can also hear
Inbeeku regenerating.
Let's see what the kid's got.
Uh.
[SHOUTING]
External Ballistic Kei,
Tempered Transformation.
Serpent Wave.
LAYFON: It's already
been decided.
It can't be undone now.
Nor would anyone want it to be.
Not Her Majesty and not me.
[HONKING]
LEERIN (VOICEOVER):
But what if I want it?
Is that not enough
to make you stay?
NINA: Wait.
You have to reconsider?
SOLDIER: Oh?
NINA: If you just up
and leave, what's going
to happen to the 17th platoon?
I'm assuming
it'll be disbanded,
and you'll all get reassigned.
I do appreciate you wanting
me to stay in your unit, Nina.
But I've already
made up my mind.
OK.
NINA: At least, give me until
the end of the competition.
You have to follow my orders.
I'm your platoon leader.
Well, not anymore.
You're not.
[SIGH]
Restoration.
[WHISTLE]
Once I've turned
in my badge, I'm
no longer part of this unit.
[CLINKING]
And I'm unarmed.
Attacking me would get
you nothing but expelled.
Wait.
Get a hold of yourself.
All right.
Let go of me, Harley.
You've got to calm down.
I can't just sit back
and let our platoon
get disbanded like this.
Let go.
Hmph.
Bang.
We just have to
find a replacement.
Today's the entrance ceremony,
so there should be plenty
of new students to choose from.
And who knows?
Sharnid's legendary
skill at picking up girls
might actually come
in handy today.
Ooh.
I'd welcome having more
chicks on the squad.
I bet you would.
Look.
There they are.
WOMAN (ON LOUDSPEAKER):
New students,
please assemble inside
the main auditorium.
[GRUNT]
Uh‐oh.
She's got that look.
Whoa.
Check out the big guy.
We could use him on defense.
See his uniform?
He's not even in Military Arts.
NINA: Then, that guy.
HARLEY: No.
He's already been recruited.
NINA: How about him?
SHARNID: He's been
snatched up too.
What the hell?
Has everyone new
already been taken?
Well, it does look like all
the good ones have already
decided which platoons to join.
See?
It's good to have you aboard.
Besides, with the
way our luck's going,
I don't even know
if we could find
a replacement willing to join
our sad little group anyway.
Maybe I'll replace you.
Nina.
NINA: He's in Military Arts.
Look, Dinn.
I'm sorry, but I saw him first.
OK.
He's mine.
So hands off.
Have you've forgotten how you
failed this city two years ago?
Hey, wait.
Well, I haven't.
So don't talk to
me that way again.
Understand?
NINA: Dinn.
Don't let him get to you.
Yeah.
You're right.
HARLEY: There has to be
some new students left.
Let's try another area.
NINA: OK.
HARLEY: We can probably find
some new ones before they
go into the auditorium.
I'm not going to make it.
NINA: We're too late.
Crap.
Now, it looks like most
of the new students
have already gone inside.
In that case,
why don't we come
back once the ceremony's over?
NINA: All right then.
[CLICK]
Hi.
I'm with "Weekly Look‐In."
Mind if I take your picture?
Oops.
I already did.
I'm sorry.
So pleased to meet you.
You're not in a uniform,
but you're a new student,
aren't you?
So you got a name?
Yeah.
My name's Layfon Alseif.
So, um, what exactly
is "Weekly Look‐In"?
You mean you've
never heard of it?
It's only the number
one selling magazine
in Zuellni Academic City.
I'm currently working on
a potential cover story
for the magazine, and
it's titled "Who's
the Most Handsome New Student?"
You don't mind if I ask you
a few questions, do you?
NARUKI: You are such a phony.
Shh.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
NARUKI: You don't
work for the magazine.
You're a new student
who just got here.
Well, that is sort of true.
I am a new student here.
And I guess I should have
clarified that I don't
actually work for the magazine.
Not yet at least.
But I really hope to.
I'm sorry.
But you'll see.
When I submit this article,
the editors of "Weekly Look‐In"
will buy it on the spot.
It'll knock their socks off
and take their breath away.
[COUGHING]
NARUKI: She goes a
little overboard.
But she has a lot of spirit.
Doesn't she?
That's one of the
reasons we're friends.
And speaking of which, let
me introduce you to everybody
here.
First of all, I'm Mifi Rotten,
an aspiring journalist.
This is Naruki Gerni,
aspiring police officer,
and Mayshen Torinden
here wants to be a baker.
It's nice to meet you.
The three of us are
first year students
from Yoltem Transit City.
So what city did you
come from Layfon?
Uh.
What's going on?
GUY: It's the two new guys.
GIRL: Somebody has to stop them.
GUY: No.
Let them do it.
That's Kei energy.
I smell a scoop.
Mifi, wait.
It's too dangerous.
[GRUNT]
I think I just found
another cover story.
Geez.
Those guys should be fighting
in a training hall, not outside.
Restoration.
GUY: He's got a DITE.
GIRL: Oh no.
GUY: All right.
That's it.
We're going to need
a senior Military
Art student to break this up.
I'll go find one.
You do that while
I go snap some pics.
Mifi.
[GRUNT]
Restoration.
Mayshen.
Danger.
Help her.
Gorneo.
That's him.
That's Layfon down
there, isn't it?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Over there.
Stop it.
Right now.
[KNOCKING]
May I come in?
Please do.
I'm Kalian Loss, president
of the student council.
HARLEY: Come on, Nina.
It's the day of the
entrance ceremony.
Can't we knock off
doing this today?
Sharnid and Felli
aren't even coming.
Hey, Harley.
What did you think about him?
Who are you talking about?
The new student, the one
who saved that girl today.
Nina, come on.
Drop it.
He wasn't wearing a uniform.
So he's more than likely a
general education student.
But even if he's not, I
heard the student council
president sent for him anyway.
Maybe he's getting expelled.
Oh no.
I'll be right back.
Hey, nice catch.
Try to be more careful
with these things.
KALIAN: As you're
aware, Zuellni Academic
City is operated solely by the
students who live within it.
My being president of
the student council
essentially means that I'm
in control of this city.
Therefore, I have the
authority to make decisions
in Zuellni's best interest.
So you're a first year
general education student.
Yet earlier today you
demonstrated skills
that would make a
senior Military Art
student look like an amateur.
I take it you know a thing
or two about fighting.
I suppose you could say that.
Layfon Alseif, is it?
A student on the
work study program.
It says here your
job is cleaning
the machinery department.
That's certainly not the most
glamorous job to have here.
Also, your scholarship
is only at a D ranking.
What you'll earn from
all your hard work
will barely cover your tuition.
LAYFON: I'm aware of that.
It will also be rather
physically demanding.
Won't it?
‐ Yeah.
Don't worry.
I'm strong enough.
I think that
strength would be put
to better use in Military Arts.
Huh?
I've bumped your
scholarship to an A ranking.
And I've waived your tuition.
That should make your
transfer a little easier.
My transfer?
Wait.
Hold on a minute.
I don't want to be
in Military Arts.
Over the past two
years, we've lost
sernium mines by being defeated
in the municipal challenges.
And now, there's only one mine
left powering the whole city.
If we lose that
one, Zuellni's dead.
Huh?
Which is why we need
your strength to fortify
our military, Layfon.
Look.
Thanks.
But all I want to pursue in
Zuellni is general studies.
I'm sorry.
But the welfare of the
city has to come first.
Therefore, as of right now,
you're in Military Arts.
Wait.
You can't‐‐
Pardon me.
Oh, ladies.
[SNAP]
[GIGGLING]
He's going to be getting
all new clothes now.
So please dispose
of his old ones.
‐ Wait.
‐ Yes, sir.
Stop it.
Those are my pants, you know.
GIRL: Not anymore.
[KNOCK]
Excuse me.
Mr. President, I
came to ask you‐‐
Oh, well, if it isn't the
captain of the 17th platoon.
I'm busy.
Can this wait?
I guess it can't.
Miss uh‐‐
Nina Antalk, sir.
And I'd like to request
that I be allowed to take‐‐
maggot, tell me your name.
It's Layfon Alseif, ma'am.
Well, Captain Antalk.
What is it that
you're requesting?
Layfon.
Please let me have
him for my platoon.
[BELL DINGING]
All right.
I'll see you tomorrow
in the training hall.
The men's dorms are
right over there.
See ya.
By the way, that uniform
is a perfect fit.
[SIGH]
What the‐‐
FELLI: Lousy, no good‐‐
[GRUNT]
[CLANGING]
Damn it.
How dare you?
The nerve.
Help her.
You're nothing but a coward.
I'm going to rip your
bleeping head off
and bleep down your
bleeping neck for this,
you lousy bleeping bleeper.
Uh.
Hello.
Did you hear that?
It was kind of hard not to.
I'm sorry.
But when I get really angry,
I scream into this tank.
Then, I feel a lot
better afterwards.
Really?
Um.
Hey, were you the
person who sent me
that Nen‐I energy
earlier to let me
know that girl was in danger?
FELLI: You decided to
transfer to Military Arts.
Not exactly.
It was more like
I was forced to.
Oh.
It's the same badge.
I guess that means you're in the
17th platoon too, aren't you?
I'm almost there, you guys.
Just a few finishing touches,
and my sure‐to‐be‐award‐winning
article will be
ready for submission.
[YAWN] Good.
I can't sleep with
all your typing.
Huh?
[SIGH]
NARUKI: Meicchi,
your face is all red.
Are you feeling OK?
Don't worry.
I'm not sick.
No.
You're sick all right.
Huh?
Love sick, because of him.
Whoa, May.
Can you hear me?
Wow.
She's got it really bad, huh?
Big brother.
And‐‐
Coward.
Are you trying to
kill me, Savalis?
I saw you up there, kid.
I was just testing
your reflexes.
[BOOM]
Oh great.
This bastard's hard
to kill, isn't it?
LAYFON: We keep hurting it,
but it keeps regenerating.
How do we stop it?
DELBONE (VOICEOVER):
[INAUDIBLE] appears
to be a lifeform comprised
of millions of cells,
each one is an organism
existing independently.
I see.
Hacking off a piece or
two won't do a thing.
If we want to kill it, we
have to kill all of it.
A series of fast
attacks might work,
but we'll have to
keep attacking it
until there's nothing
left to the damn thing.
This is going to require all
of our individual techniques
and all the Kei we can summon.
If we blow this, we
won't get another chance.
Let's go.
The only thing you'll
find up here is me.
Well, he did OK.
I guess.
But he was a little showy.
What are you saying?
A Heaven's Blade
is supposed to show
off their strength and
abilities to achieve victory.
And that's exactly what
that boy did today.
Sure.
Whatever, old man.
Old?
Silence.
Of course, he's going to
show off with that blade.
And can any of you
here blame him?
He's like a child with
a new toy right now.
Let the boy have his fun.
LEERIN (VOICEOVER): These mobile
cities we live in, the Regios,
to us they're our entire world.
But when someone we
care about leaves them
that world becomes
a lonely place.
I really wish you weren't going,
and I'll miss you terribly.
But I do understand why
you want to leave and start
over somewhere else, Layfon.
And I'll respect
your wishes to do so.
However, one day‐‐
[SHOUT]
[EXPLODING]
[SHOUTING]
LEERIN (VOICEOVER): I pray that
you'll return home and set foot
on Glendan soil once again.
[THEME MUSIC]
NARRATOR: Layfon is now
in the 17th platoon,
and it's time for him to tackle
his first training exercise.
Can Nina whip her group into
a cohesive fighting force,
or will they face
the agony of defeat?
Next time "Capture the
Flag and Restoration."