[MUSIC PLAYING]
Funimation.
You should be watching.
I've got a favor
to ask of you guys.
[THEME MUSIC]
Let me take care of Siena.
OK, guys?
I'd appreciate it if you would.
Sharnid no.
Wait!
Kalian's proposal‐‐ we
haven't accepted it yet,
so you don't have to do this.
Actually, Nina, I do.
It was years ago, but
it seems like yesterday.
We'd been friends
since our first year.
We all got along well, and
grew so close to each other
that we were like family.
But the three of
us could never have
achieved anything without
her, the former leader
of the 10th Platoon.
We loved her so much.
She looked out for us, and being
the naive kids that we were,
we wanted to do anything
that we could to please her.
[GUNSHOT]
[ALARM]
SHARNID: When we lost the
last municipal challenge,
she was crushed.
She hated knowing that
she'd graduate without being
able to help defend Zuellni.
After seeing her like that,
we all swore a solemn vow‐‐
the three of us would
protect Zuellni ourselves.
But despite our promise,
and our dedication
to our former leader,
riffs had already
started to form between us.
I thought my leaving would
have broken the platoon apart,
but I only fractured
it, instead.
Then Dean took the
remaining pieces
and tried to make
them fit together.
So that's why.
Will you let me?
Yeah.
Good luck.
Did you see that, Sharnid?
The 10th can still do
it, even without you.
[WHISTLING]
Keep moving!
Don't stop until we've won!
Traps one and two have
both already been destroyed.
Dammit.
That was fast.
They didn't even slow them down.
You're good, Dinn.
[INAUDIBLE].
What the‐‐ every
member except Sharnid
is in front of the flag.
Then that must mean‐‐
Everyone watch out for a sniper!
Dinn!
Don't worry about me!
Go on ahead!
Right.
I can't lose to them.
And I won't.
Is that the best you can do?
You've got to be kidding
me with those things.
Nope.
I'm dead serious.
Just like these things are.
[SHOUTING]
There you are!
Hey, not bad.
Why you?
To tell you that
you're an idiot.
What?
Knowing something but
doing nothing about it?
Sounds like an idiot to me.
I also came here to end
this, and ask you a question.
The other night you
asked me why I left.
Well, why didn't you stop me?
What gives you the
right to ask me that?
Why do you think we're
fighting right now?
It's because of you!
You broke the promise
that we made, Sharnid.
Just ask yourself this‐‐ was
our promise worth anything?
Come on.
Be honest now, Siena.
Did you truly take
it that seriously?
When we all made that vow,
it wasn't sincere at all.
You know that as well as I do.
The three of us were
just fooling ourselves.
What we felt wasn't real.
I'm right, aren't I?
Shut up!
Do you really mean that?
Yeah, of course I do.
Unlike you, Dinn's priority
is defending this city.
Understand?
His dedication may have
sprung out of his feelings
for our former leader,
but he's honest.
He'd do anything
to protect Zuellni.
Yeah, and I believe that.
Then why do you insist
on interfering with it?
Because it's wrong.
The way he's doing it.
What?
Have you gone insane?
How is trying to
make your abilities
match how you feel wrong?
Bastard!
What nerve!
How can you say that?
Well, if what Dinn's
doing isn't wrong,
then why didn't he tell you
about the overload he's taking?
And why didn't he
let you use it?
You shut up!
He felt guilty, so
he didn't tell anyone.
Not even you.
That's it, isn't it?
If you don't stop
this, I'll make you!
They're coming.
Aw, shit.
Already.
[SCREAMING]
But why?
I had an understanding
with a local family here.
I guess Gedosh has
got something big.
Please work.
We're in luck.
Saya!
Yes?
You stay here and
hold down the fort,
and I'll go give
them what for, OK?
Sure.
This room is already
under my protection now.
So, he has no power
over machines, huh?
Be careful.
Why so sad?
You're going
somewhere fun, I hope?
Because you look like you
could use some cheering up.
Just home.
Hm.
What are you doing?
Leerin, I hate
seeing you down.
Let's get a drink, hm?
Huh?
I can't, Shenora.
I'm underage!
In that case,
get a soft drink.
I know that Layfon getting
expelled couldn't be helped.
I also know that he's created
a new life for himself
in Zuellni.
Apparently he's happy there,
and doing really well, too.
But still, is it
foolish of me to hope
that one day he can come
home to Glendan again,
and resume his life here?
Is that just a pipe dream?
Hm.
Wait, so you think it is?
Hey!
I'm serious.
Please listen.
I have been listening.
For six hours now.
You know what
the queen told me?
You should resign
yourself to that fact.
How cruel.
It sounds to me like she's
already saying that Layfon
won't ever be coming back here.
Really?
I won't do it, though.
I won't resign myself.
Not ever.
That's admirable, Leerin.
But maybe the queen has a point.
What if he doesn't
want to return?
His kei outut's incredible‐‐
but if he keeps this up,
it'll rupture.
Impossible.
Who are you?
Restoration.
Here.
Find out.
[GROANING]
Just stay down.
You don't want to overdo it.
At the rate you were
going, you would
have ruptured your kei artery.
If that's what it would
have taken, then so be it.
I would give anything to win.
You have no idea what it's like,
having a duty forced upon you,
and knowing full well
that you don't have
what it takes to fulfill it.
Oh, really?
Well, this might surprise you,
but not everything in my life
has gone so perfectly.
In fact, I'm in Zuellni
because of my failures.
I've found that people
give up and start
neglecting things
they can't do well,
which leads to bad choices.
You couldn't do things
well, now, could you?
And that led you to
make the worst decision
that you possibly could.
Oh, really?
Who do you think you are?
Dinn‐‐
[SCREAMING]
What the hell?
A fallen one.
Good.
Everyone's finally here.
The fallen ones always bring
misfortune to the strong.
Misfortune?
And they're sensitive to
conflict, so I need a favor.
If you happen to
pick up its presence
during this competition
you're about to be in,
I'd appreciate it if you'd
like yours truly here know.
If you don't, what happened
at that ruined city
you guys explored
will happen here, too.
If I sense it, I
just have to tell you?
That's right.
It's a win‐win situation.
Your city gets rid of
a destructive force,
and we get our fallen one.
Then everybody goes home happy.
Hey, thanks for the heads up.
You deceived me, Haia.
Oh, come on.
That's a little harsh.
I didn't deceive you.
I was just selective about
what info I gave out.
All you said was
the fallen ones
bring misfortune to the strong.
But you weren't just talking
about military artists who are
physically strong, were you?
What the fallen
ones want are those
with more spiritual power.
People with strong
wills and hearts.
That's it, isn't it?
HAIA: Bingo!
No wonder the president
relies on you so much.
I've got a fallen
one to capture.
See ya.
Wait!
Fon Fon‐‐
What do you want with him?
So it's got Dinn
under its control?
All right.
Then I'll‐‐
Uh‐uh.
No way, bub.
It's our prey.
Besides, we're just about done.
Subdue its host, and capturing
a fallen one is easy.
And making things even
easier is that it picked
this guy, for some reason.
Baldy here may have some
really lofty ideals,
but what he doesn't have are
the skills to back 'em up with.
And that's why he
can't make full use
of the fallen one's gifts.
Capturing him was a breeze.
Once you've gotten
Dinn back to Glendan,
what will you do with him?
Seeing that you're
not even allowed
to return there, that's
really none of your business,
now, is it, bub?
Stop!
I'm not going to let
you take Dinn away.
Well, that's just
too bad, because I am.
Look, don't get me wrong‐‐
what he did wasn't right,
but he's also a fellow
military artist, a comrade,
and a citizen of Zuellni.
I will not have you
deciding his fate.
I refuse.
You let him go, now.
Release Dinn Dee, or else!
And what are you
going to do if I don't?
Fight?
Against yours truly?
Please.
We're the Salinban
mercenary training group.
You wouldn't last a second.
I wouldn't get so
cocky if I were you.
Did you say something?
What do you want,
former Heaven's Blade?
To be your opponent.
So, what do you say?
My Saiharden skills are rusty.
Normally I'd use
a practice dummy,
but I think you'll suffice.
Restoration.
You're still using
a dual‐edged sword?
Jeez, you really
are a joke now, bub.
But sure, because
once word gets out
about how I mopped
the floor with you,
I might even be able to
get the Heaven's Blade
you left behind when I
return home to Glendan.
Layfon?
I'm not letting him take Dinn.
Felli.
Yes?
You've been in contact with
Kalian the whole time, right?
I want to speak to him.
I hear you.
Did you know things
would turn out like this?
Haia failed to mention the
specifics on just how he was
going to capture the fallen.
But even so, that doesn't mean
he can simply take Dinn away,
so we must come up
with a solution.
Do you have any suggestions?
Here's one.
Is there not some
way to separate
the fallen one from Dinn?
Why did that thing choose
him, in the first place?
Do any of us even have a clue?
FELLI: I have an idea.
Huh?
The fallen ones
may select the host
they possess based on the
strength of their sentiment.
Because the fallen ones are
out of control city spirits,
that sentiment may be the
desire to protect a city.
Does that remind you of anyone?
So this fallen one feels
the same way as Dinn?
We do, too, so why possess him?
Perhaps it's because
Dinn's sentiment
had reached its zenith.
Think about how
he must have felt
when he was defeated by Layfon.
His sense of responsibility,
his dedication to protecting
the city was crushed.
It was at that moment when
his sentiment was at its peak.
This fallen one and Dinn
have a great deal in common,
don't they?
Seems both of them
are bitter at the loss
of their sense of purpose.
You're right.
But at this point,
how in the hell
are we supposed
to separate them?
We've only one choice.
Somehow we have to break
Dinn's spirit once again.
SHARNID: We can arrange that.
Just leave it to us, OK?
Wait, you two?
But‐‐ can you do it?
Somebody has to, right?
Why don't you use
a proper blade, bub?
That's supposed to be
your specialty, isn't it?
Let's just call
it a trade‐off.
You're a total idiot.
You've got weapons and
techniques available,
but you mock the art of battle
by refusing to use them.
It's a choice I've made, Haia.
It's all part of
following my convictions.
Someone who fights for no
one's benefit but their own
wouldn't understand, so why
am I even wasting my time?
I've had enough of your crap.
Aw, dammit.
Where could they have taken him?
Restoration!
Siena!
[SHOUTING]
Dammit!
No!
Show me where you are.
Ah!
Siena!
Got it!
Up ahead.
Hurry!
All right.
Go do what I've failed to do‐‐
break us all up.
Hey there.
Dinn‐‐ Dinn, it's OK.
It's over now.
Look, the 10th Platoon‐‐
there's no need for it anymore.
There are other people who have
the same commitment to Zuellni
that we do.
We can leave it to
them, and in that way
the promise we made
still won't be broken.
OK?
You've done
everything you could.
The 10th Platoon is finished.
Dinn‐‐
[LAUGHTER]
Come here.
I had so much love for you.
But like our platoon,
it's gone, too.
And this is goodbye.
[THEME MUSIC]
NARRATOR: In preparation
for their next competition,
the 17th platoon holds an
intensive training camp.
Mifi, Meishin, and
Naruki tag along to learn
more about Layfon's past.
Will they be successful
in digging anything up?
Next time, Feelings
That Are Not Received.
And restoration.