[MUSIC PLAYING]
VOICES (VOICEOVER): Funimation.
You should be watching.
LEERIN (VOICEOVER): Guess what?
I'm studying management now.
I figured that if you could
make a big change in your life,
then so could I. Of course,
I made mine here, and you‐‐
[WIND BLOWING]
[WHIMPERING]
Hm?
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I don't really know,
to tell you the truth.
It's my heart.
It‐‐ it just felt so full.
SYNOLA (VOICEOVER): Saya.
Is that‐‐ could it really be?
LEERIN: (SNIFFLING) I'm sorry.
Hello, there.
I'm Synola Areisler.
And you are?
Leerin.
My name is Leerin Marfes.
You know, I think you and
I are gonna be great friends.
[GASP]
[LAUGHING] Not too
big, not too small.
Stop!
They fit right there
in the palm of your hand.
What do you
think you're going?
With just a little
extra left over.
‐ Don't do that!
‐ This.
‐ Please!
‐ Yes, this.
I'm telling you no!
This is what I've
been looking for.
Ugh.
No!
Oh, Leerin.
You're the best.
Would you please let me go?
[THEME MUSIC]
[CHEERING]
Ladies.
Thank you.
I'll be here all week.
Winning that contest has
really helped with our fanbase.
There's twice as many as usual.
Dude, don't you think
you're being a little rude?
It wouldn't kill you to
sign an autograph or two.
GIRL: I love you, Sharnid!
Thanks.
What's your name?
Um.
Whew Shower before a night
out sure is great, huh?
You gotta make a
good impression,
especially on a first date.
Hey.
What's wrong, fella?
You don't take showers.
It's very easy to
be spied on here.
I don't think you have
to worry about that.
Not 'til you fill
out a little more.
Oh, sorry.
Hey.
How'd your DITE
hold up out there?
Perfectly fine.
Well, if you need an
adjustment, all you have to do
is let me know.
SHARNID: Um, I'm
good to go, buddy.
NINA: No issues here.
Man.
You guys are no fun.
Where the heck is Layfon?
KALIAN: You were really quite
impressive at the competition.
Of course, that's
to be expected.
In the sphere shelled
city of Glendan,
the Keeper of the Heaven's
Blade is a title of honor given
to the 12 most gifted warriors.
These elite military
artists possess
mysterious weapons that are
beyond the comprehension
of most outsiders.
Yeah.
So what's your point?
I'm sure you
realize I don't have
the Heaven's Blade anymore.
If there's nothing
else, I'll be leaving.
I don't understand.
Why are you still working
in the machinery department?
Your tuition has
already been waived.
What else could you need?
Nothing at all.
I don't wanna be in your debt.
I didn't know it bothered you.
The Layfon Alseif I heard of
was a man in need of money,
not a man of honor.
A man that would use
his special abilities
for his own financial gain.
Well, I don't
know where you're
getting your information,
but it's not accurate.
That's not me.
I see.
Then who is Layfon Alseif?
I'm dying to know.
If I'm mistaken, enlighten me.
I'll pass.
It's really none
of your business.
KALIAN: Don't be so
naive as to think you can
give anything but your best.
Believe me when I
tell you, to ensure
the survival of this city, I
will use whatever I have to.
And what about your sister?
Her too?
Yes.
That's exactly right.
Her too.
LAYFONG: Nina.
Hey.
Do you feel like trading
dinners again tonight?
Your test to
enter the platoon.
You lost it on
purpose, didn't you?
Layfon.
With powers as
incredible as yours,
why would you hide
them away like that?
I don't get it.
LAYFON: I was born in Glendan.
The city is constantly
moving, gravitating
towards Contaminoids.
See, I grew up in a
world of violence.
For military artists
like me, it was
normal to fight the
Contaminoids on a regular basis.
But you know what?
I never felt afraid
during a battle,
or worried what the
outcome might be.
Victory was the only option.
The other alternative was death.
That's the kind of
place I grew up in.
I used to love fighting.
There was a time
when the Military
Arts meant everything to me.
But now I think I'd like to try
searching for a different path.
But why?
That life just
isn't for me anymore.
What's the point of continuing
on when you've already failed?
[RUMBLING]
NINA: Zuellni stopped.
LAYFON: Huh?
[ALARM BLARING]
Zuellni!
The city?
NINA: The city's consciousness.
An electronic spirit.
NINA (VOICEOVER):
What is it, Zuellni?
Did something happen?
What are you doing?
Zuellni.
Let her go, now!
Wait.
Stay back.
Don't go near them.
MAN: What are you
doing here, you worm?
Oh, I have close
ties to this city.
What?
You maggots didn't know that?
Nina!
What is it?
Nina.
Nina?
Zuellni.
Don't interfere.
NINA: You're a spirit thief?
Wolfmask Mob.
3Rd Platoon.
Charge.
Restoration.
It's time to squirm
around in Ignacius'
flask, little fishies.
Don't!
These things are way
too dangerous for you.
Ah!
That sure is one
hard headed young lady.
But I guess stubbornness does
have its virtue sometimes.
By the way, you won't be able to
get a connection from Zuellni.
Guess somebody must have given
you some bad information.
Huh?
No!
MAN: Don't look!
[WHISPERING]
Shit.
Augmenting Ballistic
Kei transformation.
Swift Lightning!
Huh.
You're OK!
Sorry you had to get
mixed up in all this.
Hey.
Who are you?
No hard feelings.
I would tell you my name
is Dickserio Muscaine,
but it won't matter,
because when you wake up,
you won't remember anything.
Nina.
An electronic spirit.
[GIGGLING]
Stop it!
Put it back, now!
That spirit was just born!
Let go.
If I sell this thing, I could
get a whole lot of money, kid.
Sheneibel is the only city‐‐
‐ No, I won't let you do this.
‐‐with a copy system
that can create them.
That belongs to us!
So stay out of
my way, you brat.
The electronic fairies
mean more to this city
than you'll ever know.
Shut your mouth.
Shit.
Learn to mind your own business!
Mm.
Am I going to die?
You're OK.
Oh, thank goodness.
I'm glad nothing
happened to you.
It's really her.
Sheneibel.
So that's why the
city stopped working.
I'm glad it wasn't a mistake.
I know that I did
the right thing.
Ah!
What are you doing?
No, please.
You can't.
You mustn't do that.
Don't do this.
Please don't!
[CRYING]
HARLEY: That electronic fairy
gave its own life to save
Nina so she could live on.
But she changed after that.
Nina decided that
weakness was a sin.
Being unable to protect who
you want, losing the people
you die to help.
She doesn't want to
experience that ever again.
And that's exactly why Nina's
desire to become strong
is so powerful.
She was like this even back
when we were little kids.
Me and Nina grew up
together, so I've got
a good idea of how she feels.
I'll be right back, OK?
LAYFON: Thanks for coming.
You really helped.
HARLEY: Sure.
I was happy you got
in touch with me.
Bye.
MIFI: I found Layfie.
There he is!
Layfie?
MIFI: A successful capture.
NARUKI: Roger that.
Mission complete.
You remember meeting us
at the entrance ceremony.
My name's Mifi,
and this is Naruki.
Uh, what?
Now, come on, Meyshie.
You've got something
to say, don't you?
Uh, thank you so much for
saving my life that time
at the entrance ceremony.
Hey.
Don't even worry about it.
It really wasn't
that big of a deal.
What?
Oh, yes it was.
I wrote an article all about
your exploits, and now, bam.
I'm on staff at "Weekly Look'n!"
Anyway.
Based on the heroism you
displayed at the entrance
ceremony, and also transferring
to the Military Arts,
joining a platoon, and then
winning your first competition,
I'd say you have a knack for
the limelight, wouldn't you?
Uh, yeah.
Sure.
So what's up with the rope?
MIFI: Oh, remember?
Narie wants to join
the Municipal Police.
Yeah.
That's why I practice my
rope binding techniques
almost every single day.
And Meyshie wants to work in a
cake shop, so all she ever does
is make delicious sweets.
Uh, I‐‐ um.
Um.
Yeah.
LAYFON: Look who it is.
She's from the 17th Platoon.
Capture her at once, Narie!
NARUKI: Roger.
I got her.
Let her go.
What are you doing?
I'm Mifi Rotten, journalist
with "Weekly Look'n" magazine.
I'm doing a follow up
piece on your newest
platoon member, Layfie Alseif.
Could I get a few words
from you and the rest
of the 17th Platoon?
FELLI: What?
MIFI: For the magazine.
FELLI: The what?
LAYFON: They're
pretty OK, actually.
I don't think
they're bad people.
I'm not concerned.
That bit with the
rope was the most
fun I've had in a long time.
You actually enjoyed that?
But I am disappointed in you.
Huh?
Your actions seem
contradictory to things
you've said.
Yeah, I know.
Honestly I don't think I
should stay this way either.
Then I forgive you.
Huh?
But as punishment, from here
on out, I will refer to you
by your new name, Fon‐Fon.
Hey.
You're joking, right?
Senior, please.
I don't like being
called Senior either.
It's far too formal for me.
I will require a
different term of address.
But‐‐
What will it be?
We should keep things
as simple as possible,
so for now, you
shall call me Felli,
and you shall be
known as Fon‐Fon.
But I don't like tha‐‐
Were you or were
you not called
Layfie by those girls earlier?
Well, yeah.
But that wasn't my idea.
If you don't care for
Fon‐Fon, I will have to think
of a different name for you.
Lay.
Lay‐Lay.
Way‐Lay, May‐Lay, or Hay‐Lay.
So which one do you prefer?
Well, all of
them are sort of‐‐
Fine then.
How about I call
you Lay of the Land?
Top of the morning to
you, Lay of the Land.
Well, good afternoon,
Lay of the Land.
Have a lovely evening,
That's embarrassing, isn't it?
If you know that,
why are you saying it?
Ugh.
Fine.
Fon‐Fon it is.
Hm.
[HORN BLOWING]
MAN: Madam Alsheyra.
Wait.
ALSHEYRA: It's out
of the question.
MAN: Please.
Now that Layfon
Alseif is gone, we
must proceed according
to the customs,
so the 12th Heaven's Blade must
be decided in a competition.
You fool.
Do you even know what it
means to be a Heaven's Blade?
Any keeper merely chosen
by rote can eat shit.
And never mention a
competition again.
SYNOLA: Kanaris.
You've gotten quite good at
being queen, now haven't you?
Oh.
Your majesty!
Still, I'd like to think
I'm more beautiful than that.
How the people around you
haven't noticed at all
is simply a mystery to me.
Of course.
Even with surgery, a
lowly person such as I
would pale compared to
Her Majesty's beauty.
Think not of me.
Though I may be harassed,
I may be tormented
if Her Majesty has decided
to return to the palace,
I'll gladly‐‐
Mm.
It might just be a
little longer now.
Wait!
What do you mean might?
You can't!
And stop using Kei to
look younger and then
lie about how old you‐‐
Just who the hell do you
think you're talking to anyway.
Sorry!
No matter how skilled
of a Heaven's Blade keeper
you may be, the power of a
queen is infinitely greater.
Got it?
But it doesn't make any sense!
You said you
already had for fill
of the life of a normal woman!
You were just about sick of it!
It's quitting time.
That's what you said.
Well, didn't you?
Please, please, oh
please come back.
We need you!
The other Heaven's
Blades won't obey me.
They won't listen
to anything I say.
Stop crying.
I do recall what I told
you, but I've encountered
someone whom I have to protect.
Huh?
Do you understand now?
I can't stop being
Synola Areisler yet.
LEERIN: Thanks a lot.
Meeting that girl was
extremely important for me.
That was the moment that
Synola Areisler became real.
[BEEPING]
Saya.
We have got to get out of here.
Right now.
MAN: Stop, or I'll shoot.
[GUNFIRE]
AILEIN (VOICEOVER): I
can see the bullets.
My right eye and my
left arm, they're‐‐
SAYA: Here.
Use these.
Are they yours?
Where were you keeping them?
Because I've decided
to accompany you,
everything that I have is yours.
Good.
You can count on me.
I'll protect you.
Now stay close to me and
we'll find our way out of here
and figure out how to survive
in this world together.
This is our bond.
This is the deal
between you and me.
Yes.
MAN: There they are!
Freeze!
Don't move!
Now, where's the fun in that?
[GUNFIRE]
[THEME MUSIC]
MAN (VOICEOVER): Felli
Loss, the Nen‐I operator who
hates her own special
abilities, casts
off her fatigues
once and for all
to discover future
possibilities.
Next time, Disarmament.
Put on That Maid's Outfit!
And Restoration.