[MUSIC PLAYING]
LAYFON: Huh?
Wait, what's going on?
MAN: Layfon.
LAYFON: Mr. President?
MAN: You can't
escape me, Layfon.
LAYFON: Mr.
President, why did you
ask me to come see you here?
MAN: Because, Layfon, my
dear boy, you will be mine.
THEME SONG: (SINGING) Brave
your truth and brave yourself.
So we can go somewhere
with the dite.
Keep hope alive, now we
wanna find the new world.
[JAPANESE]
(VOICEOVER) Why?
Why?
Why, Kalian?
I don't get it.
What am I even doing
in a place like this?
Because of my terrible
ordeal yesterday.
I was in the midst of my
duties when I collapsed,
[GROANING]
Sir!
Mr. President!
The doctor said
I was overworked.
But I should make
a full recovery
with two to three days of R&R.
[GIGGLING]
Right.
I know that.
You, I get.
What I don't get is why
you insisted that I come
along with you, big brother.
Well, seeing that you didn't
have any training scheduled
for the next two days, I thought
it was the perfect chance
for a brother‐sister
getaway, one for just
the two of us [INAUDIBLE].
Ah!
Are you OK?
What happened, sir?
(SIGHING) How pointless.
[INAUDIBLE]
Oh, Felli.
You're here, too.
What a weird coincidence.
All right, Nina.
That was a killer dive.
What the‐‐ Felli!
You're here?
That's awesome.
Thanks, [INAUDIBLE].
What are you doing here anyway?
Well, I thought a
few days here might be
a good team bonding exercise.
Mm‐hm.
That's right‐‐ to bond.
But without me, huh?
Is that it?
No.
You've got it all wrong.
You see‐‐
Heard about what
happened to the student
council president, Felli.
Since he's your bro, we
thought you'd be busy
taking care of him and stuff.
The reason why we
didn't invite you
is because we didn't think
you'd be able to join us.
But somehow you still did.
[NERVOUS LAUGHTER]
Kalian, how's he doing?
Much better, thanks.
Take a look.
[GIGGLING]
Oh, my.
Oh, Mr. President,
sir, you're so funny.
Well, well, why, hello there.
(WHISTLING).
I'm so jealous.
(LAUGHING).
Wow, what an
incredible coincidence
to run into the entire
17th Platoon here.
Boy, I'll say.
You know, Felli.
Since she is here, perhaps you
could ask Captain Antalk if she
could teach you how to swim.
What?
Felli's a terrible swimmer and
could really use some lessons.
Stop!
Why are you telling
them all this?
Addressing one's
weakness is critical
if one wants to be rid of it.
You're right.
Now, don't worry, Felli.
By the time I'm finished,
you'll be swimming like a fish.
Well, let's get started.
Here!
Got it!
Need a hand, babes?
There you go.
GIRL 1: You're awesome.
GIRL 2: And hot, too.
So, um, why did you
bring that thing along?
we?
We are planning on getting
in the pool, aren't we?
If I don't have this thing,
I'm going to sink like a‐‐
Uh, no, this is
the only thing you
need when learning how to swim.
I don't understand why it's
so important that I know.
Hey, come on.
I mean, it's better to know
how to swim than not to, right?
And why is that?
Why?
Oh, um, well,
because we might all
have to fight in a marine
battle one of these days.
We live in a regio.
So the chances of us ever having
to fight in a marine battle
are zero to none.
Um, no, you don't
know that, 'cause what
would happen if some of the
water tanks were damaged‐‐
[CHUCKLING]
It's not gonna be
easy to tire her out.
Tire her?
Um, no.
I mean, it's not going
to be easy to teach
Felli how to swim.
She's kind of hard‐headed and
set in her ways, you know?
He is here!
You're right.
See, I told you my information
was on the money, you guys.
It's the man of your
dreams, Mayshen‐‐
those two and the rest
of the 17th Platoon.
(LAUGHING CRAZILY) They're my
weekly look and cover story.
Oh, so that's the
reason why you came here.
No, of course not, Nari.
It's so I could hang around
my two BFFs and help Mayshen.
Now, let's go get your guy.
[WHIMPERING]
Layfee!
Oh, hey, ladies.
You're here, too, Layfee?
Small world.
Yep, sure is.
We came here to teach
Mayshen how to swim.
Tell him, Mayshen.
[WHIMPERING]
Hey, don't be scared.
Jump in.
Well, I, um‐‐
I don't know.
In fact, I don't think I can.
You're gonna do it.
Come on.
Get a grip.
You can't chicken out now.
Go for it.
Come in.
We'll have some fun.
[WHIMPERING]
I think getting her
into a bathing suit
may not have been a
good idea, you know?
Oh, no, it was.
Trust me.
I know what I'm doing.
All my sources tell me that
Layfee can be a real bone
head when it comes to girls.
So we had to do
something like this.
Hey, Mayshen, if you want
to learn how to swim,
I bet Layfee could teach you.
Yeah, and you said you wanted
to learn while you were here.
We really appreciate
this, Layfee.
I hope you're ready, (TOGETHER)
'cause here she comes.
Wha!
[SCREAMING]
[WHIMPERING]
[LAUGHTER]
Nice catch.
You two have fun.
Good luck, guys.
And be careful, OK?
[LAUGHTER]
Hey!
I'm so jealous.
And another reason
why it's important
that you learn how to swim is
because, um, well, you see‐‐
mm.
I want to do it.
Huh?
I want to learn how to swim.
All right, you're doing great.
Just don't bend your knees when
you're kicking your legs, OK?
OK, I think I've got it.
See, you're getting
better already.
We've covered one of the
most important things,
and that's getting
used to the water.
So now let's practice holding
your breath under the water.
OK, try moving your legs next.
Yeah, that's it.
You're doing great.
You're a really fast
learner, Mayshen.
Here goes, 1,
2, 3, 4, 5, great.
Come up.
Nice job.
Let's try it again, OK?
[PANTING]
1, 2, 3.
That's great.
‐‐4.
All right, you're doing it.
NINA: ‐‐5.
Way to go, Mayshen.
I'm really proud of you.
[LAUGHING]
[GRUNTING]
How could I have forgotten!
Oh, no, Felli!
I swear.
I really thought I
was about to die.
Felli, again, I am so sorry.
But, hey, look on
the bright side.
At least you know can float now.
But dead bodies
can, too, you know.
Yo, stud, well done, man.
Those are some pretty
smooth moves you made
with that cute chick today.
No, I was just helping
her learn to swim.
This looks great.
Hey, what's with the weird
spelling on our shirts?
It's ancient text.
Oh, huh.
Mm.
That girl.
Huh?
Tell me, is she
able to swim now?
Um, uh‐huh.
Maybe a little.
How nice of you.
Hey, Layfon, you
all right, dude?
Yeah, never been better.
We have to check our
dites before we go in.
Here you are.
Enjoy your bath.
So Biggie's in
one of those, huh?
Looks like time's running out.
I'm gonna get big boy
his birthday present.
[SQUEALING TIRES]
What the hell's going on?
Aw, it shut off.
Well, put some
more money in it.
Me?
I did it last time.
Don't you want to
see what happens?
All right, fine.
(SIGH) This
herbal low‐frequency
bath hits the spot, huh?
It really relaxes the
muscles, doesn't it?
[WHIMPERING]
It's the electricity
that does it.
Sure, you might feel a
little jolt the first time.
But once you get used to
it, it feels really good.
FELLI: Oh, so you mean
you've done this before?
Wow.
Yeah, I come here a lot
whenever I have free time.
Speaking of which, I didn't
believe you when you told
me why you were all out here.
Felli, it was
the honest truth.
Please, a coincidence?
You were lying
through your teeth.
I am not!
It was one.
FELLI: Yeah, right.
Come on, Nina.
With all due respect, why
would a guy like Sharnid
want to hang out with his
platoon leader on his days off?
NINA: Well, because‐‐
because of the pool.
Yeah, that's the reason
he came out here.
When I said I was going,
he begged to come.
He just did it so he
could stare at girls
in bikinis, the dirty perv.
Sounds like him.
It does, and it's just a
happy coincidence that all of us
are here.
I'll help you with
your swimming tomorrow,
and I won't take
my eyes off you,
so nothing bad will happen, OK?
No, not again!
Felli!
(SIGH) I want to forget
today ever happened.
MAN: Just calm down.
There's nothing to worry about.
WOMAN: But sir, she suspects
that something's off.
I'm afraid we're
going to be found out.
MAN: Nonsense.
You don't need to
worry about a thing.
It'll be all right.
WOMAN: I hope.
Look, I'm sure
things will be fine
as long as you just keep your
cool and act natural, Nina.
I didn't see you
helping much today.
You were too busy with those
two bimbos at the pool.
Hey, come on, you
guys, play nice.
Mr. President, we still have
the same agreement, don't we?
Yes, Harley, of
course, we do‐‐
if you succeed.
WOMAN: We will sir, don't worry.
(VOICEOVER) Those things
I heard, did I dream that?
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
Is that true?
(VOICEOVER) I must have.
Kalian's too busy
being fawned over
by his assistants to have met
with the platoon last night.
It had to have been a dream.
NINA: So tell me, Felli.
Hm?
You ready to swim today, huh?
No, thanks.
What?
You have to.
Because if you don't do it, then
the platoon will never get to‐‐
No!
We'll never get to
see you swim, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Hey, now, come on, Felli.
Don't be like that.
Offering to teach
you how to swim
was a really kind and selfless
thing for Nina to do, you know?
Yeah, it's so selfless.
Yo, Felli?
What?
How would you feel if
Layfon here taught you
to swim today instead of Nina?
FELLI: Huh?
With a different
teacher, you might have
a whole different attitude.
What do you say, Layfon?
Yeah, sure, I'd
love to teach her.
OK, then.
[WHIMPERING]
Oh, crap!
Guess we showed up too late.
What you looking at?
You see something that
makes you jealous?
I don't know what
you're talking about!
Come on, what's the problem?
You're always training
alone with Layfon,
and Felli never gets to.
So why don't you
quit hogging him?
Don't you think it's
about time you let
somebody else have a chance?
Restoration.
You've really gotten
the hang of this.
You're doing so well.
Maybe you should try
it all by yourself now.
No!
No, I can't.
I don't have the hang of it yet.
If you let me go, I'll drown!
Trust me, you'll be just fine.
No, I won't be.
I'll be dead!
Please don't let me go, Layfon!
I'm begging you!
Um, well, in that
case, hold on tight.
Are you ready to keep going?
Mm‐hm.
Thanks, I'll see you later.
Sure thing.
President Loss has
requested to speak with you
about something Layfon.
Can he have a few
moments of your time?
Um, OK?
[FOOTSTEPS]
Um, Mr. President?
So where is he?
Hey!
What's going on here?
MAN: You can't
escape me, Layfon.
Huh?
Escape?
What are you talking about?
We're in an emergency
shelter below the resort that's
both soundproof and reinforced.
Even if the resort above was
trampled by contaminoids,
this place would still survive.
Why did you ask me
to come see you here?
There's something
that I need to ask you.
Oh, yeah, what would that be?
Tell me, Layfon‐‐
Yes, sir.
My dear younger sister, Felli,
you've got a thing for her,
don't you?
Huh?
I've seen you two together.
And since you're the type who's
strings lots of women along,
let me warn you right now.
Layfon.
if you do anything at all to
hurt my sister whatsoever,
I will kill you.
Got that?
‐ No, sir!
You're mistaken!
I was just helping
her learn how to swim!
Don't try to talk
your way out of this!
And don't underestimate
how powerful I am!
[INAUDIBLE] my power
is virtually limitless.
Having the sleeves of
your uniform tailored
to fit your arms, arranging a
fight between two new students
on the day of the
entrance ceremony,
and even forcing you to
enter the 17th Platoon
would be mere
child's play compared
to what I can have done to you!
I knew it!
So you were behind all those
things, after all, weren't you?
Uh, certainly not.
I was just saying I could do
those things hypothetically.
Yeah, but you did
do them, didn't you?
Uh, now back to
the matter at hand.
You better not hurt Felli
in any way, shape, or form.
Because, Layfon, my dear,
dear boy, you will be mine!
No, stop!
We're just friends!
I promise!
(SIGHING) Nice.
I wonder what they're going
to serve for dinner tonight.
[SCREAMING]
Evening there, ladies.
Now, get your heads up
where I can see them.
[GUNFIRE]
[SCREAMING]
Don't try anything funny.
If you do, I'll blow
you away, you hear me?
‐ Well, Nina?
‐ Not now.
GUNMAN: Hey, you
two, get over here.
You, inside, you're
completely surrounded.
We've got your
friends in custody,
and we have the data
chips they stole.
There's no reason for
anyone to get hurt.
Just put down your weapons
and let's end this peacefully.
Then you better
meet our demands, cop.
We want safe passage
on a [INAUDIBLE] bus,
or we start killing
the hostages.
[GUNFIRE]
[SCREAMING]
Dammit.
(WHISPERING) Damn it.
Wish our dites weren't
behind the counter right now.
(WHISPERING) Thanks
for reminding me.
I'll look for them.
Look for them?
No, don't.
Those guys will notice.
FELLI: Don't worry, Nina.
At this range, I won't have
to use strong nanni at all.
They probably won't even
realize what I'm doing.
Felli, You don't know that.
If they figure out
what's going on‐‐
Felli!
Hey, man this
girl's using nanni.
40 degrees.
GUNMAN: Don't just stand there.
Shoot her!
Directly to your right.
Hah!
Restoration!
Ah!
And as always, nice
shooting there, Sharnid.
[SIGH]
All right, move it.
Why are you guys really here?
Uh, I thought we
already told you why.
Yeah, it was
just a coincidence.
We came because your
brother asked us to.
That was supposed
to be a secret.
Come on, why don't
you tell her the truth?
Felli, look,
you've told us before
that you were born with a
large amount of nanni, right?
You've also told
us there were times
when your nanni discharges
without you even noticing.
And for a nanni operator,
that's like wetting the bed.
That used to happen
sometimes, but only when
I was younger, not recently.
Actually, it has.
You just didn't
realize it, Felli.
Then what I heard
last night was real.
NINA: Kalian said if
your body got tired,
your nanni would get
weaker, which is why I kept
insisting on swimming lessons.
FELLI: He bribed
you guys, didn't he?
I'm sorry!
He said that if we did
this, then the platoon
would get a special bonus.
I couldn't say no.
I needed the money to
make some new dites.
As for me, I
said, hey, as long
as I can hang out with chicks
in bikinis, I'll go, too.
And Layfon, did he also know?
Nah, we never
told him the truth.
We didn't think old
Fon‐Fon could lie to you
and get away with it because
you'd see right through him.
Layfon didn't know.
Speaking of
Layfon, where is he?
Hey, I don't see Kalian
around here either.
After all that commotion,
that's a little weird.
Where are those two?
Now spit it out.
Confess.
In that twisted
little head of yours,
you're already calling
me brother‐in‐law.
Yes, you are, aren't you?
Don't try to deny it.
I told you, I was just
helping her learn how to swim!
That was it!
Ah!
What the hell?
This entire place is reinforced.
Oh, no, Felli!
So you found out, huh?
Wait, I can explain.
I did this all for you.
It was for the best.
You understand, right?
Come on, Felli.
Oh, can't you just forgive
and forget, please?
Ah!
Guess not.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
ANNOUNCER: Sharpshooter
Sharnid Elipton was previously
assigned to the 10th platoon.
Its leader, Dinn Dee, has
never forgiven Sharnid
for his alleged treachery.
Can they ever be friends again?
Next time, "A Tender
Lie" and "Restoration."