[MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, any luck?
We can't do a thing.
Go call Nina Antalk
and get her down here.
Come on.
Cut the crap.
What's going on with her?
Hey!
Zuellni!
THEME MUSIC: (SINGING) Brave
your truth and brave yourself.
So we can go somewhere
with the DITE.
Keep hope alive.
Now we wanna find the new world.
[JAPANESE]
[ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING]
It's unavoidable.
Just as [INAUDIBLE]
said, we cannot
keep the seat of the last
heaven's blade empty forever,
now can we?
Perhaps the only‐‐
Savaris.
Greetings, Queen
Alsheyra Elshira.
I hope all has
been well with you.
But it doesn't appear that way.
Is it because the fallen one
evaded capturing Zuellini?
Your Majesty, I beg you to
let me be of service to you.
You wish to go there?
I've great
interest in doing so.
You want it, don't you?
Yes, very much.
The fallen one has
incredible power.
By harnessing it, I could
become even stronger.
Hm, I'll consider it
once my task is finished.
Task, my Queen?
An important one that
I must take care of.
[SIGHING]
What ya doing?
(LAUGHING)
Um, yeah, shouldn't
I be asking you that?
I've been here for a while.
I'm surprised that
you haven't noticed.
I'm starting to get
embarrassed just
lying around here like this.
You're embarrassed?
What about me?
How cruel.
Hey, wait, don't be like that.
Huh?
Hm.
I didn't mean any harm.
Let me make it up to you by
taking you out to eat, 'kay?
No, thanks.
And not just because you always
take me to expensive places
and refuse to let
me pay, but also
because of all of your groping.
Oh, did you say groping?
Oh, well, OK.
I told you before to
please stop doing that!
I couldn't stop it,
even if I wanted to.
They're just too much to resist.
I couldn't very well rob
myself of this pleasure.
Then I'll rob of you
your hand by ripping
it right off your arm!
All right, now calm down.
From what I saw back
there, you're planning
on leaving Glendan, huh?
The person you're waiting
for won't come back.
So you're going to see him.
With what you've told me
and after seeing that map,
it wasn't hard to figure out.
Have you thought
this thing through?
Only a city's
electronic spirit knows
where that regios will go.
Even if you were lucky
enough to find it,
you still have to worry
about getting attacked
by contaminoids along the way.
Come on, Leerin,
there's no reason
for you to put yourself in
so much potential danger,
now is there?
And this child had boyfriend
of yours, help me out here.
What was his name again?
Layfon Alseif.
Yes, that's right‐‐
Layfon.
Anyway, I'm certain he
wouldn't want you to do that.
He'd want you to stay here
and be safe, wouldn't he?
Well, knowing him, absolutely.
He'd want me to be as
careful as possible.
And then naturally, he'd
tell me to stay right here
and get an education
so I could protect
the orphanage and the
children who live there.
And besides it just
wouldn't be right to use
the money that Layfon left me to
pay for all my travel expenses.
Yeah, you're right.
But then again, [INAUDIBLE],
I mean, think about it.
What if I'm wrong?
What if Layfon's in
trouble and needs my help?
It wouldn't be right
for me to stay.
I've got this sinking
feeling that he's in danger.
(VOICEOVER) I wonder if
this was counterproductive.
LEERIN: ‐‐especially
since he hasn't responded
to any of my recent letters.
I've been wondering if he
could be sick or injured.
Who knows what trouble he's in.
No, of course not.
Come on, there's absolutely no
way that guy could get hurt.
Huh?
Wait, how could you know that?
Uh, well, you see, it's 'cause
you told me how strong he is.
I'm sure he's just dandy.
No news is good news.
Layfon.
Come on, what are
you, some kind of idiot?
What, no get well soon?
You've had us
all really worried.
The doctor said if
you lost even a little
more blood you would have died.
LAYFON: I'm sorry
if I worried you.
To be honest, I never thought
I'd get this banged up.
Well, what kind of prognosis
have the doctors given you?
It looks like my biggest
problem right now is my back.
In fact, I'm about
to have an operation
so they can remove a broken
fragment from my spinal cord.
Then you won't be fighting in
the next competition, will you?
No, but don't worry, Nina told
me that she's not forfeiting.
What?
She said it'd be crazy to
do since the next match is
the big win against
Vanze's first platoon.
She got really fired
up and said that she
could pull it off without me.
Oh, so she came up here, huh?
Yeah, this morning.
She missed her classes
just to come see you?
Huh?
Uh, well, yeah, I guess she did.
How kind.
You two are pretty
close, aren't you?
Ah!
That's kinda harsh.
I mean with me being
so injured and all.
You're just lucky
they didn't leave
you in critical condition.
Get well soon, dummy!
[LAUGHTER]
Ahh!
Still, talk
about unlucky, huh?
I can't believe
Layfon's surgery got
scheduled on the same day as our
match with the first platoon.
That's enough.
Even if Layfon got
released early,
it still wouldn't
make any difference.
We would have to give
him time to heal up.
Yeah, sure, I know that, but
isn't going into this match
without him really
pushing our luck?
Don't worry.
There are ways to
fight without him,
and we will get through this.
Man, I really hope so.
(VOICEOVER) When it happened‐‐
Hey, where are you?
Layfon?
Answer us, dude!
[CRYING]
NINA: (VOICEOVER) ‐‐I could
only think of one thing‐‐
the next competition.
The thought of going
into it without Layfon
made me feel anxious
and depressed.
I felt like it was all over.
(ALOUD) But it's not.
Huh?
I've gotten a lot
stronger, Harley.
And I can't just keep relying
on Layfon to help the 17th win.
Ah!
Oh, Sharnid.
Hey.
So how's Dinn?
Is he doing OK?
DALSIENA: If you're concerned,
then why don't you go see him
yourself?
I don't think
he'll forgive me,
so I guess I'll
hold off on that,
at least for the time being.
Is that all, or is there
something else you wanted?
Yep.
I'm sure you've heard
the rumors, haven't you?
Our MVP's been injured, so
the 17th's down a member.
Hold on a minute.
You're not actually going to ask
me to take his place, are you?
Of course I am, and as
a full‐fledged member,
if you want to be one.
I refuse.
There is no way I'm ever
going to fight alongside you.
The bonds the three of us
shared are gone forever.
Don't you know that?
Well, sure.
But that's OK.
And do you know why?
I didn't ask you because I
wanted to do things the way
we did it in the old days.
Besides, without Dinn, there's
no way that we even could.
What the 17th needs
is a new fighter,
and I can't think of
anyone better than you,
Siena, and not just as a
replacement for Layfon,
but as a permanent member.
I mean, the bonds the three of
us had may very well be broken,
but not the promise
we made that day.
That's something I still
haven't given up on.
I know you haven't.
And if I'm right,
neither has he.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just grabbing
something to drink.
I can't believe you're already
out of bed and moving around.
Yeah, all the doctors say
I'm a pretty fast healer.
Mm.
So Dalsiena's
gonna take my place?
Yeah, she's gonna be
with the 17th platoon
for the big competition!
What a scoop!
When I heard about it, I
ran over here lickety split
so I could tell you the news!
Oh, really?
That Dalsiena can
sure hold her own.
I'm relieved to hear
that they got her.
But if that's true, then
what's with the long face?
Oh, well, I'm
happy, but, well, it's
just knowing that my
platoon will be fighting
in the competition without me.
I guess it just makes
me a little sad.
Aw.
Hey, don't be down, Layfee.
I mean, the competition would
be much better with you in it.
Well, yeah, of
course it would.
And all your buddies in
the 17th would agree too.
But since you can't be there,
they're doing whatever they
can to make things work out.
Like he would!
Oh, really?
Doing it just like I would, huh?
Mm‐hmm.
Mayshen's not here with us.
Do you know where she is?
Uh‐‐
Hey, something's
wrong, isn't it?
What's going on with Mayshen?
Come on, you have to tell me.
OK, you see,
Mayshen's convinced
that you got hurt because of
her, and she blames herself.
I can't let her think that.
No, don't worry about
that right now, OK?
We'll try and do something
to change her mind.
But let us handle it.
She's right, Layfee.
The only thing you need
to concern yourself with
is getting better.
All right, then.
Thanks a lot, you guys.
Uh, can I help you?
I've been waiting
for you, Layfon.
President Loss
wishes to see you.
He'd like to have a word
with you in private.
Here we go again.
What the hell?
Damn.
I'm gonna freakin' kill you.
Well, well, you can
still talk, can't you?
Even so, you'll
never defeat me, pal.
I guess not if I'm
here all by myself.
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
[WHISTLE]
[SIRENS]
You can't come up here.
Yes, we can, and you're going
to give us all the details.
Yes, sir.
The aura particle ratio in
this area peaked so high,
it went off the
charts completely.
Have you heard any
strange reports?
Nothing except
this so far, sir.
We want to interview
the eyewitnesses.
They're en route to the
hospital, and none of them
are in very good shape.
It'll be a while before they're
up and talking again, sir.
I see.
ANNOUNCER: Today's
competition is about to begin.
Will [INAUDIBLE] number‐one
ranked first platoon
be the one that
comes out on top?
That's how we'll play this.
Sir!
ANNOUNCER: Or will it be the
17th platoon with Dalsiena
Matelna serving as a
last minute replacement
for the injured Layfon Aseif.
This is going to be a
match to watch, folks.
Your plan, captain?
I'll begin by moving
in on their right flank.
That'll get their attention.
I'm gonna need you to
back up Sharnid and Felli.
You three will attack
their left flank
and open up a route to
their sniping point.
As the platoon leader,
that's a major gamble.
You get taken out, and
your entire team loses.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah, I am, and don't
you worry about me.
That's an order.
Well, let's do this thing.
And not just that,
let's win it, too.
[CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER: It's been
awhile since we've
seen this fan favorite,
Dalsiena Matelda, folks.
[CHEERING]
I love you!
[STREETCAR BELL]
[CRYING]
All right, coming and
get me, first platoon.
FELLI: Two enemies are
moving on the right flank.
The rest are headed this way.
What the hell?
They must have seen
through her plan.
‐ So what now?
‐ Don't worry.
Leave it to me, all right?
Ah!
I'm so sorry.
I really am.
Well, you shouldn't be.
I know that it was
just an accident.
You didn't do anything
wrong, Mayshen.
How are you?
Are you better?
Yeah, enough that they just
released me from the hospital.
So soon after surgery?
I know you're strong.
But why would they do that?
I know.
You're going somewhere
again, aren't you?
You are.
This is the train that
heads out of town.
Are you going off to
fight alone again?
Huh?
Mm.
Thank you, Layfon.
Huh?
You've protected
me so many times now.
But I suppose you'll
never let me do it.
Isn't that right?
Even though I want to, you
won't let me protect you.
I know you won't.
Ah!
You still haven't found
their sniping point yet?
Ah!
FELLI: I'm searching.
So you've gotten stronger.
Layfon was a big
motivator, wasn't he?
I knew I shouldn't completely
rely on him all the time.
I understand.
It's good that Layfon
inspired you to push yourself
and your platoon to improve.
But you being platoon leader
and using yourself as a decoy
is just reckless.
Maybe you should save
your thoughts on that
until this match is over.
Very well.
But I'm going to
prove that I'm right.
Restoration!
Ah.
Ah!
That's really delicious.
[SOUNDS OF FIGHTING]
He's so fast.
It's like he can read
all my movements.
Ah!
ANNOUNCER: It's all over, folks.
The 17th platoon
has been defeated.
The first platoon is the winner!
What?
You've got to be kidding.
That wasn't a battle at all.
So much for not
relying on a Layfon.
[SIREN]
Thank you for being
so kind as to come here.
Cut to the chase and tell
me what this is all about.
There's something very
wrong with the city.
What do you mean?
For some reason, Zuellni's
suddenly begun to run amok.
A probe has detected
contaminoids directly ahead
of the city's current path.
But rather than change
course, Zuellni is
heading towards them instead.
Heading towards them, but
why would Zuellni do that?
Why?
Because of the fallen one, bub.
Duh.
Haia, you're still here?
Oh, jeez, from the
look on your face,
I can tell you're really
not all that happy about it.
I need you to defeat
the contaminoids.
That lie ahead of us.
Haia brought this
information to my attention
so I want you to do
this task with him.
Are you kidding me?
I wish, but the contaminoids
are only one of two problems
that we're facing right now.
The second problem involves
what befell you the other night.
What if that collapse
you experienced
wasn't just caused
by deterioration?
The fallen ones are city
spirits run amok and bring
ruin wherever they go.
Similar incidents
to that collapse
are occurring
throughout the city.
Face it, this ain't a
coincidence, all right?
That fallen one is trying
to destroy Zuellni.
No!
We need these
men to stay here,
not only to capture
the fallen one,
but also to aid us
against the contaminoids.
Haia, you told me that you have
a specialist in that field?
That's right.
We sure do.
And I suppose there's no
better time to introduce
you to him than right now.
Gents, say hello to our
group's resident neni operator.
His name is Fellmouse.
His vocal cords are
all shot to hell,
so we can only talk with
the aid of a vocalizer.
It's an honor to meet
you, Layfon Alseif.
Fallmouse here's not
only a genius at neni,
but he's also got a
really unique talent.
Believe it or not, this guy
knows the contaminoids' smell.
Wait, their what?
I have a particular
sense of smell
when it comes to contaminoids.
However, to detect their scent,
I must be physically outside,
beyond the air filters.
Hence the current
condition of my body.
But even that hasn't been
enough to kill this dude.
Trust me, he's
pretty damn tough.
I don't know whether
it's a genetic abnormality,
or if I succeeded
in acquiring some
special metabolic immunity.
If my body were
examined, perhaps the day
will come where people could
survive the toxic atmosphere
outside of the regios.
I humbly ask of you, please
place your trust in my senses,
you who been recognized
by our queen.
You will do this, right?
Fine.
I'll do what you want.
I'll go.
But you're going to have
to do something for me.
Never have I lost something
so disgracefully‐‐ never.
Joining this platoon
was a huge mistake!
Hold on, you don't
mean that, Siena.
DALSIENA: Don't
address me like that.
Calm down.
(VOICEOVER) I was too
confident in my own abilities.
I never realized that I relied
on Layfon to such an extent.
[DOOR OPENING]
You.
What are you doing here?
Has anything happened
to my brother?
No, I'm here because
I've been entrusted
to deliver a message from
Layfon Alseif to Nina Antalk.
A message for me?
I'd like you to deliver
this to Layfon for me.
I've prepared it for him.
If he asks, tell him that
it's a reward for learning
all the [INAUDIBLE] techniques.
I'm to give this to Layfon?
MAN: Will you do it?
Of course!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
ANNOUNCER: Together with the
Salinban mercenary training
group, Layfon
heads out to engage
a group of 12 contaminoids
and to investigate
why Zuellni is running amok.
Nina goes it alone in the
machinery department next time,
"Salinban Mercenary
Training Group, Move Out!"
and restoration.