[MUSIC PLAYING]
Funimation.
You should be watching.
Why's the battle with
Myath been suspended?
Hey, have you heard that
Glendan's getting closer?
What are you talking about?
It's the spear‐shelled city,
famous for its military arts.
That must be why
command has us on standby.
Zuellni's just
an academic city.
If we go up against
Glendan, we're dead meat.
Hey, I wouldn't
worry about it.
There's no way they
can take our mine.
Come on, use your head, Sharnid.
They couldn't go
against the treaty.
Yeah, but treaties
don't mean shit, Harley.
If that's what the city
wants, then there's nothing we
humans can do to stop it.
And treaty or not,
Glendan's heading
towards Zuellni as we speak.
Haven't you noticed?
Which reminds me,
isn't that the same city
Layfon comes from?
[THEME MUSIC]
Glendan, huh?
We continue to hail them.
Whether our signal's obstructed
or just being ignored,
they remain silent.
Not a single peep from them.
If we do end up
fighting Glendna,
then we have no hope of winning.
Our one remaining cernium
mine will be taken,
and then this whole
city will die.
How is this possible?
An academic city
battling one that's
renowned for its military arts?
Only the wills of the cities
themselves would know that.
And right now, those
wills are a mystery.
Myath is increasing speed.
It should be clear of the
battle zone in two hours.
At present there are no
contaminoid readings.
Understand.
Please continue your probe
until further notice.
Even after all that
Felli's been through,
you still won't let
her rest, Kalian?
This was actually her idea.
She offered to help.
Let's have every platoon
member remain on standby.
As for the other
military artists,
order them to go
and get some rest.
Understood.
And one more thing‐‐ call
the 17th Platoon to duty.
Does that include Layfon?
Yes.
No, wait!
Please‐‐ he injured
himself saving me.
And besides, the city of
Glendan is Layfon's home.
KALIAN: That is precisely
why we require him now.
Big brother,
since you obviously
don't have a clue why
I've chosen to help,
let me spell it out for you.
Please don't get Layfon
involved in this fight.
He's still hurt.
Vanze, I'll just
contact Layfon myself.
What is that?
That strange aurora‐‐
I know I've seen it
somewhere before.
That's right‐‐ I saw
it in the sky long ago.
It was near Glendan then, too.
Thank goodness‐‐ Layfon.
I'm sorry.
I didn't get to say goodbye.
It's OK.
I'm just glad that
you're all right.
When you disappeared from
Myath, I feared the worst.
I'm sorry for
worrying you like that.
I didn't mean to, and in
fact, I still don't understand
exactly what happened.
Funny that we both
ended up here, isn't it?
Yeah, I know.
How's Layfon doing?
He's sleeping right now.
This way.
Um, thanks, but I think
I'm going to pass, Leerin.
But why?
You're already here.
It won't make any
difference if all I do
is see him sleeping.
Guess I just wanted to
know how he was doing.
Oh.
You take good
care of him now, OK?
[BEEPING]
So I guess it wasn't
a dream, after all?
Oh, you're awake?
Even though you hit
me, I'm glad you're here.
I am surprised, though.
I never thought I'd
see you in Zuellni.
And I never thought I'd
see you fighting again.
The doctor said you'd been in
this hospital several times.
Right before you left
Glendan, you said you were
giving up fighting altogether.
What happened to that?
You did it again, huh?
Who for?
Nina?
That Felli girl?
Some other platoon member?
You sacrificed yourself again
for the sake of the people you
fight alongside, didn't you?
Look, that wasn't
my intention.
Don't lie to me!
There's no point.
I spoke with Nina.
And she told me enough, Layfon.
She said she couldn't
forgive her own weakness,
and relying too
much on a comrade.
It's obvious to me now that the
person she referred to is you,
isn't it?
I know how she feels.
You're still the same.
You always take on
anything and everything
alone, just like
you used to, Layfon.
So Nina thinks she
relies on me too much?
It's hard not to when you're
always protecting everyone.
I always wished you'd
rely on me for once,
instead of the other way around.
Wow.
You just met Nina, and she
shared all that with you?
Yes, but we didn't just meet.
We met when we were in Myath.
Myath?
Wait, Nina was in Myath?
You're sure?
Huh?
Of course.
I'm positive.
Place, Leerin, tell
me everything, OK?
Sure.
Well, let's see.
So that regios is
your home city, Gor?
Sure is.
And that's who we're
gonna fight next, right?
I doubt it.
There's no precedent for
an academic city fighting
a regular city like Glendan.
I can't say it's
impossible, though.
Who really knows?
If we do end up
fighting, whose side
are you going to be on?
Someone's here!
Yo.
Big brother?
Who is that?
It's been quite
a while, Gorneo.
Savalis?
What are you doing here?
I'm on a mission
for her majesty.
I spent a whole lot of time
on a rolling bus to get here.
Just after I arrive,
Glendan shows up.
Go figure.
By that answer, I take it
that you don't know why Glendon
is approaching Zuellni, either.
Nope.
I don't have a clue.
The only thing I
can assume is either
it's the whimsy of
her majesty, or she's
become unable to
control Glendan's will.
In any case, I'm still
going to follow my orders
and capture the
fallen one that's
somewhere here in Zuellni.
Should be fun.
So, little brother,
have you heard anything
about fallen ones in the city?
A military artist named
Dinn Dee was possessed by one.
It was forcibly
removed from him,
and since that happened he's
basically been a vegetable.
Really?
Also, while searching the
ruined city of Gandoweria,
Layfon Alseif claims
that he encountered one.
He described it as looking
like a golden goat.
A golden goat, huh?
I didn't see it myself.
[LAUGHTER]
I guess that means the
fallen ones can only appear
to those who are truly strong.
Now, you take that back!
Speaking of which, I'm looking
forward to seeing Layfon again.
I'm hoping I can catch a
glimpse of the strength he had
when he was a kid in Glendan.
You should have
seen him back then.
When he fought his first
battle as a Heaven's Blade,
Layfon was something.
And so young, too.
Thinking back, the only
way to describe that fight
was a whole lot of fun.
Battles are the
only thing I really
get excited about these days.
No matter how skilled you
are, you can die at any time.
That's what makes the whole
thing so invigorating.
I sensed some of that
same attitude in him.
Has he changed
since coming here,
or is he still the
same old Layfon?
All right, I've had
just about enough!
Is this the only thing
you can talk about?
Gorneo, this guy's
a total creep.
Is this jerk really
related to you?
Yep.
And Gorneo is, indeed, my
weaker younger brother.
I've got to admit, Gorneo,
you working with Layfon
really surprised me.
Poor Gerhard is probably
rolling over in his grave.
Wait just a minute‐‐ you
mean you didn't know?
No one told you your
friend was dead?
Gerhard is dead?
Gorneo?
You're lying!
I'm telling you the truth.
I know, because I killed
Gerhard with my own two hands.
Boy, was he a pitiful sight.
His body had been
possessed by a contaminoid.
Thinking of him still
makes my skin crawl.
No‐‐ it can't be!
To be honest, I should
thank Layfon for making
him a whole lot easier to kill.
Layfon cutting off one of his
arms made Gerhard much simpler
to defeat, even though
he was possessed.
In the end, his death
served its purpose.
Speaking of which, it
was pretty spectacular.
You should have seen it.
No.
You're lying!
You have to be!
I'm not.
And the tiny bit of
Gerhard's consciousness
that remained despised
Layfon until the bitter end.
Come on, Gorneo.
I'm sorry.
[CRYING]
Zuellni, please,
I need your help.
Are you still inside me?
[RUMBLING]
This certainly
doesn't bode very well.
Vanze, Zuellni has
just changed course.
We're directly facing Glendan.
That's great.
What do we do now?
Wait, I know.
Since Glendan's within firing
range of the Kei‐Ra cannon,
should we take a shot at them?
Use it in a municipal battle?
I never considered it, but
that could be an option.
VANZE: I wasn't being serious.
I was joking.
Besides, it would
violate the treaty.
It's inexcusable.
Even so, get it ready.
We'll only use it
for intimidation.
As for violating the treaty,
Glendan will be doing just
that if it attacks us first.
[PHONE RINGING]
Layfon, can you hear me?
Yes, sir.
Zuellni is running amok.
Again?
Yes.
And it's rapidly
approaching Glendan.
Glendan?
Are you kidding?
And after everything I went
through on that roaming bus,
too.
That must have been waht
caused all that shaking.
It probably won't be
too long before the cities
reach each other.
But we've yet to receive any
communication from Glendan.
Sir, do you have any
idea where Nina is?
I've called her and
your platoon to duty.
Understood.
Be there right away.
Don't go!
Leerin‐‐
Layfon, for all we know,
her majesty may have come
here to welcome you back home.
But even if not, I'm sure
she'd let you come to Glendan
if you simply asked her to.
I just know that she
would forgive you.
So, I think we should
go see her together.
Please.
[ALARM]
Get the Kei‐Ra cannon
primed and ready.
Sir!
Leerin, listen‐‐
you said I keep
sacrificing myself for other
people, but you're wrong.
The truth of the matter is
that you and all the others
mean everything to me.
That's the real
reason why I've always
tried to protect everyone.
It wasn't because
it was something
that I felt I had to
do, but because it's
something I truly wanted to do.
There may have been some
other way to do that,
but I did things the
only way I knew how.
I'm sorry, Leerin.
But I'm going.
Goodbye.
Layfon, wait.
Hold on.
You'll come back, won't you?
Great.
Why did I even come here?
Reporting in, sir.
We've been waiting.
Captain Antalk hasn't
arrived here yet.
Actually, that's who I
need to talk to you about.
Go on.
Well, you see, my good friend
Leerin recently arrived by bus.
She said that on the way there
she met up with Nina in Myath.
Wait, what do you mean?
I asked for specifics,
but unfortunately I
couldn't make sense of it.
However, apparently just before
Nina vanished from Myath,
Leerin saw a golden
goat hovering over her.
That would explain things‐‐
both Nina's disappearance and
her reappearance in the desert.
But that would also mean
something else, then.
That's right.
It would mean‐‐
Nina is possessed
by the fallen one.
If that's a joke, I
ain't laughing, dude.
No.
It just can't be possible.
That might explain
something else, too‐‐
why Zuellni began moving
again at the exact moment
that Nina returned.
But why is it running amok?
Layfon, do you have any inkling
as to why this city is racing
towards Glendan right now?
I have no idea.
Well‐‐ and this
is only a theory‐‐
but it's what I
believe has happened.
Nina has Zuellni and the
fallen one inside her.
In the beginning the two
achieved equilibrium,
but for some reason
that balance is broken.
As a result, Zuellni is now
more deeply under the influence
of the fallen one.
But is forcibly removing
the fallen one from Nina
our only option at this point?
Because if that is
truly the only choice‐‐
What should I do?
She'll suffer the
same fate as Dinn Dee.
Please Zuellni‐‐ what do I do?
Preparations are complete.
We can fire at any time.
Hey, what's that?
[PHONE RINGING]
Vanze?
Something strange is
happening with that aurora.
What is that?
Contaminoid!
What?
From inside the aurora?
This is an emergency.
Move us to threat level B!
I had a feeling we'd be
meeting the Kei‐Ra cannon.
You may fire at will, Vanze.
VANZE: Wait‐‐ don't tell
me you knew about this?
WOMAN: Emergency alert.
We are at threat level
B. All civilians,
please head to the
shelters at once.
I repeat, emergency alert.
We are at threat level
B. All civilians,
please head to the
shelters at once.
I repeat, emergency alert.
We are at‐‐
Please move in
an orderly fashion.
This way!
But please, no
pushing or shoving.
There's plenty of room for
everyone in the shelters.
I don't understand why
Glendan would attack.
It doesn't make sense.
Hey, are you all right, miss?
Thank you.
I‐‐
Dainsleif must be stopped.
Your majesty, what
is that contaminoid?
The youngster for
which I have longed.
However, for it to suddenly
appear at the same time
that Leerin is inside Zuellni‐‐
it must be more than just
a simple coincidence.
Saya, what is it
that you're after?
An escape elevator in the
leg section has been activated.
Sensors confirming one occupant.
Let me verify the name.
Just got a match.
It's Nina Antalk.
What the‐‐ the 17th
Platoon's captain?
You, huh?
So, just where do you
think you're taking me?
VANZE: The Kei‐Ra
cannon is ready to fire.
Beginning countdown.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2‐‐
Ready?
Fire!
[SCREAMING]
[THEME MUSIC]
NARRATOR: A giant
contaminoid has emerged from
the strange aurora in the sky.
Meanwhile, having learned
that the fallen one inside her
is the reason for
Zuellni running amok,
Nina leaves the city to
face the contaminoid alone.
Next time, Ignatius'
Fragments, and restoration.