[MUSIC PLAYING]
VOICES (VOICEOVER): Funimation.
You should be watching.
LEERIN: Let's see.
5,876 kilmils plus‐‐ oh.
No, dummy.
You have to add it to
this sum, not that one.
OK.
Just calm down, take a deep
breath, and start over.
This isn't the easiest
topic to write about.
Come on!
The significance
of communicating
information in terms of
inter municipal exchange?
I wish I could write a
report about a subject that's
more inspiring than that.
I just know you're
going to excel,
and best of luck in the future.
Most sincerely,
Layfon W. Alseif.
Since when has he been able
to write so eloquently?
[SNIFF]
So I'm curious.
Are you in love with
the smell of paper
or with the person who
sent you that letter?
[SQUEAL]
Are you OK?
No.
You scared me.
You shouldn't startle
people like that.
My apologies, miss,
but there's something
I need to talk with you about.
With me?
Yes.
But before we go any further,
let me assure you that I
am not trying to pick you up.
Why would you even
say something like that?
Because most
girls are thinking
that when I approach them.
I just figured you would too.
Pretty overconfident,
aren't you?
Do you really think so?
Because people have
told me that before,
but I don't have a clue where
they're getting it from.
Huh?
What's going on?
Wait, is this‐‐ it's the roof.
I was taking care of
things nice and quiet
like, so why did you have
to go and screw it up?
Because time is too crucial
for you to waste it talking.
But we were ordered to
be discreet about this.
Using your power is
anything but that, Lintens.
Wait, did he say‐‐
both of you are Heaven's Blades.
You're Savaris and you're
Lintens, aren't you?
What you want with me?
[THEME MUSIC]
Fon‐Fon.
FELLI (VOICEOVER):
They're coming.
One from the front,
one from the back.
Got it.
Thanks, Felli.
So two, huh?
How do you wanna
deal with both of them?
Well, I'll leave them to
you while the rest of us
stick to the plan, all right?
Yeah.
Roger that, Captain.
With the way they're
working together,
the 17th should win this match.
KALIAN (ON PHONE): Maybe, but‐‐
But what?
There are wild
cards in this game.
And not just for the 17th,
but also for the 5th.
The man that many call
Zuellni's greatest warrior
has just appeared.
The captain of the 5th
Platoon, Gorneo Lueckens.
A Lueckens?
But how?
Oh, that's right.
Gorneo hails from Glendan,
the same city as Layfon,
doesn't he?
KALIAN (ON PHONE):
Yes What's more,
he's the younger brother
of Savaris Lueckens,
a keeper of the Heaven's Blade.
You could almost
say it's fate.
Not likely.
No matter how far you run,
the past will always catch
up with you, won't it, Layfon?
Tempered Transformation
Hardened Steel Strike!
I'm not done with you yet.
In fact, I'm just
getting started!
He repelled my entire attack.
SHANTE: Leave him to me.
Shante.
What are you doing out here?
Fire Kei Great
Projectile Flash!
Dammit.
I really thought that move
would have taken him out.
Why aren't you guarding
the flag right now?
Because if we take
him out right away,
his platoon won't have
a chance of winning.
Don't be stupid.
They can still win
this without him.
SHANTE: Look!
[HISSING]
[SHOUT]
Uh?
What is he doing?
The thousand man attack.
KALIAN: To think, he's even
mastered this technique.
Shante.
Find him.
There he is.
You're mine, pal!
[GUNSHOT]
ANNOUNCER (OVER SPEAKER):
And that's it, folks.
Today's win is another
victory for the 17th Platoon.
That was excellent
Tempered Kei.
Hey, listen.
I never thought I'd run into a
Lueckens here, of all places.
Do you think complimenting
my Kei technique
will get you a
hand shake from me?
No, I don't.
Hey, you!
This isn't over!
You're going down, you hear me?
If it's the last thing I‐‐
GORNEO: Shante.
SHANTE: God dammit, Gorneo!
Let me go!
That guy's toast!
You better watch your
back, buddy, because I'm
gonna be coming for you!
All right.
We did it.
Let's celebrate.
MIFI: Thanks, everybody.
Now, in honor of the 17th
Platoon's second straight win,
I'm singing one more
song for those guys!
[CHEERING]
(SINGING) Won't you tell
me what you're thinking?
You know, you should
sing next, handsome.
If you don't, that little girl's
never gonna let go of that mic.
I don't think so.
I do sing, but I never do it
for crowds in places like this.
When exactly do you
sing, then, gorgeous?
SHARNID: Only when I'm alone
and with a special someone.
BARTENDER: Mhm.
And is there a
special someone here
you want to sing to tonight?
Uh, this is awkward.
Hey Sharnid.
You did really great today.
Thanks, Nina.
It's been quite a
while since you've gotten
to fight in the front lines.
So how was it?
Not bad.
I loved the looks
on the 5th's faces
when they saw I could
use Jusho Jutsu.
It took time to learn,
but their expressions
made it all worth it.
Yeah, I'm sure it did.
Your mastering close
range combat skills is a
serious benefit to the platoon.
These new techniques you
and Layfon have learned
will increase our strategies.
Won't be long before we're
totally undefeatable.
Come on, Nina.
Admit it.
I'm the bomb, aren't I?
Yeah, all right.
I suppose so.
But just this one time, I'm
admit it, you're the bomb.
Think you better
watch it or that's
gonna go straight to his head.
I know.
That's why he's never
gonna hear it again.
That's mean.
NINA: Sorry.
HARLEY: You'll like this, Nina.
It's good.
NINA: Thanks a lot, Harley.
SHARNID: Hey, I'll
take some too, dude.
HARLEY: The bomb can
go get his own things.
SHARNID: The hell?
Hurry up and do it, Mayshie.
No.
I don't think now's
the right time.
What are you saying?
If you're not gonna give it
to him now, when will you?
Layfon just left.
What's the deal with
that guy tonight anyway?
FELLI (VOICEOVER): I
want to feel the world.
This world.
And beyond the vast darkness.
SHANTE: I just don't get it.
He's your enemy, right?
GORNEO: Of course he
is, but I mean, come on.
We couldn't just throw
away a competition.
SHANTE: But it was the
perfect opportunity.
You don't know when you'll
get one like that again.
GORNEO: It's OK.
And trust me.
No matter how much time passes,
my anger won't fade a bit.
Really
Mark my words, Layfon Alseif.
I'm gonna make you pay for
your crime one way or another.
It's her.
Why are you here?
I'm not obligated to answer
that for either of you.
Oh yeah?
That's the 17th for you.
The same guys who let a
coward into their ranks.
I guess you're a coward too!
What do you mean?
What the?
You don't even know?
GORNEO: Shante.
Hmph.
What did she mean?
[GUNFIRE]
So Biggie's in
one of those, huh?
Looks like time's running out.
LAYFON: Nina?
NINA: What's up?
LAYFON: Don't you come in later?
NINA: I thought I'd
come in a little
early so I could see
Zuellni for a bit,
but she won't show herself.
Oh.
OK.
‐ Hey.
When we're finished,
do you think
you could spare a few minutes?
Huh?
I came up with
this great strategy
for the next competition.
I'd like to hear what you think.
What is it?
Well, to be honest, it's you.
Uh.
You enjoy fighting, don't you?
You even look forward to it.
No.
That isn't true at all.
OK.
Who am I trying to fool?
Of course it is.
And I enjoy every
bit of it, Layfon.
I'm really happy now.
We're winning, and
that's something I've
dreamed about for a long time.
There was a municipal challenge.
It was two years ago.
At stake was ownership
of a surname line,
which is critical for the
survival of every Regios.
It was a grueling and
dangerous challenge.
We came so close.
Victory was almost ours.
But in the end, we lost.
And the other
platoon, I remember
they were so happy, cheering
and hugging one another.
That's when I thought,
that's what I want.
To stand with my team
after we've successfully
protected our city.
To be victorious and share
our happiness together.
Bit by bit, my dream's
finally coming true at last.
I feel it.
If we can keep
fighting, we'll win.
Fighting?
That's why you're happy?
NINA: Yeah.
That's where you and I differ.
I've never been
happy about fighting.
Not once.
It doesn't matter
what kind of victory
you achieve either, because
in the world we live in,
winning has no real
meaning at all.
What are you talking about?
MAN: Oh, there you are.
The student council
president's calling you.
I wonder what he wants.
[KNOCKING]
NINA: We're here, sir.
Argh.
KALIAN: Thank you
all for coming.
Do you have any idea as
to why I've summoned you.
Not again.
The Contaminoids?
Not for us, thankfully.
But they may be involved
in this matter, though.
What happened?
Hm?
LEERIN (VOICEOVER): Wait.
I'm being targeted?
Me?
SAVARIS (VOICEOVER):
It appears so.
Sorry, but just to be
safe, Lintens and I will
be watching over you covertly.
LEERIN (VOICEOVER):
I don't understand.
Who's after me and why?
LINTENS (VOICEOVER): I
believe we said no questions.
Guess I'm just
imagining things.
SYNORA: No doubt about
it, these are the best.
These.
So perfect, so
round, so squeezable.
You've got the best
ones I've ever seen.
Oh, Synora.
It's you.
In fact, I'd rate your
chest a million points.
LEERIN: Synora!
You shouldn't assign
points to a person's chest.
SYNORA: Or jump around on
a steep flight of stairs.
Hm.
You don't say.
LEERIN: It is reassuring to
know that I've got two Heaven's
Blades watching over
me, but even so,
I'm really worried about this.
Well, you shouldn't be.
They said they were doing it
just to be safe, didn't they?
They did.
But still.
The only thing we
can tell you right now
is this has something to
do with Layfon Alseif.
Hm?
It's getting dark.
I better get home now.
SYNORA: Promise me you'll
be careful, all right?
I will.
Bye.
Savaris.
Yes, your majesty.
What can I do for you?
Now, didn't I tell you
that you were forbidden
from calling me that here?
Right.
You certainly did.
I'm sorry about
that, Queen Alsheyra.
Uh, that's something else
I'm not supposed to call you,
isn't it?
I do apologize, Synora.
Jeez.
You're such an idiot.
MAN (ON INTERCOM): They
eighth gate is now on standby.
Please complete Land
Roller inspections ASAP.
The current temperature is 13‐‐
SHARNID: It was attacked
by Contaminoids?
NINA: We don't know.
All we do know is that
it's along our current path
and has stopped moving.
Unless something
changes, Zuellni
will reach it in three days.
[YAWN]
OK.
So you go and check it
out and see if it's safe,
and then come back, all right?
Good luck with that one, Nina.
You're coming too, so wake
up and start getting changed,
you slacker.
Yes, ma'am.
HARLEY: If we weren't
in such a rush,
I might have had
your new Adamandite
ready for you to take along.
LAYFON: A new one?
HARLEY: Yeah.
It's more of an anti‐personnel
weapon, and lighter too.
But because of that, you can't
trade out different DITEs.
I need a little more time with
it and it should be ready.
Well, better get back to it.
FELLI: Fon‐Fon.
Huh?
Yes, Senior Felli?
Ah!
Sorry.
I don't understand why we're
going out with the 5th Platoon.
Oh.
Well, according to the
student council president,
none of the other platoons
have enough atmosphere suits.
That's what he told you?
I think he's full of it.
Huh?
Hmph.
Monkey.
Well, I'm ready
to move out when
you are, oh fearless leader.
Oh, hey.
Sharnid.
Sorry, but could
you do me a favor
and ride with Felli instead?
SHARNID: Uh, sure, I guess.
SHANTE: Here's an idea.
GORNEO: What's that?
SHANTE: We could settle it now.
Make it look like an accident.
GORNEO: It's not that easy.
You saw how powerful
he was, didn't you?
SHANTE: Yeah, but still.
Couldn't we try to
take him by surprise?
GORNEO: If you think he
could be defeated like that,
you've got another thing coming.
Remember, he's not some pushover
but a former Heaven's Blade.
SHANTE: Yeah, well, so what?
Who cares?
I still think you're a
lot stronger than he is.
NINA: And I thought
I finally understood
things a little better.
LAYFON: What?
NINA: But I don't
get you at all.
LAYFON: That came
out of nowhere.
NINA: So did winning
has no real meaning.
I still can't get over
you telling me that.
LAYFON: I wouldn't give
it too much thought.
I just said what I was thinking.
That's all.
NINA: But you still
meant it, right?
Winning a competition
means gaining
strength and confidence.
Winning a municipal battle
means gaining a cernium mine.
Something we need to survive.
Do those things have
no meaning either?
LAYFON: Look.
There it is.
Coming up to the west.
NINA: Are you gonna answer me?
LAYFON: Let's
discuss this later.
SHARNID: The outer
gate's busted.
Looks like we're gonna
have to enter from the top.
NINA: Before we do that,
Felli, can you tell
us how things are in there?
FELLI: I'm only
getting fragments,
but I don't sense anything
dangerous right now.
MAN (ON RADIO): Captain Antalk.
This is the 5th platoon.
We've finished our recon
around the east gate.
NINA: How's it look?
MAN (ON RADIO): The dock
is completely destroyed.
Captain Lueckens and
some of the others
are now trying to enter through
a damaged external section.
NINA: Layfon.
Can you get in?
LAYFON: Yeah.
Restoration 02.
FELLI: Will you take me as well?
LAYFON: Sure thing.
Hold on tight.
NINA: Get ready.
We're going up next.
SHARNID: Roger, boss.
FELLI: You don't
have to do that.
I can guarantee this
place is safe, Fon‐Fon.
LAYFON: It's kind
of a habit of mine.
I always like to make
sure for myself, you know?
FELLI: But it's unnecessary.
If you're going to waste
energy like that, at least
try to be more polite about it.
LAYFON: Sorry, Felli.
NINA: Well?
LAYFON: No bioactivity.
NINA: Air filters?
FELLI: They're working fine.
As you can see.
SHARNID: Whoa.
Creepy.
This place is a real ghost town.
LAYFON: I think it's
safe to say this place
was attacked by Contaminoids.
NINA: Yeah.
We should look for survivors.
LAYFON: Right.
SHARNID: I don't know if we
should get our hopes up, guys.
FELLI: If they sought shelter,
what about that plaza up ahead?
NINA: Yeah.
Let's go.
FELLI: Oh no.
LAYFON: The monument's
been overrun.
NINA: This is‐‐
What's the matter?
FELLI: Do you know
this place, Nina?
NINA: Yes.
It's Gandoweria.
The city we fought
two years ago.
SHARNID: Yeah.
You're right.
And they defeated us in that
battle too, didn't they?
So what the hell happened here?
And just how long has it been
since the city was attacked?
SHARNID: Who knows?
Maybe they got hit right
after they beat Zuellni.
No.
No, this is impossible.
After beating Zuellni,
Gandoweria had plenty
of mines to power itself with.
And the city's fighting
strength and coordination
were second to none.
LAYFON: That means nothing.
I told you.
You can't be right.
You can win a battle or a
mine, but it doesn't matter.
Not to the Contaminoids.
Nina.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
It's all meaningless.
Can I ask you a question?
LAYFON: Of course.
What is it that you
would consider a victory?
For me, it's just
about surviving.
Both for myself and all
those I want to protect, too.
Victory is when none of us die.
[SHATTERING]
Hey.
Look out!
[CRASHING]
GORNEO: Just surviving is a
disgrace for a military artist,
but you know all about that.
After all, you are
the one who forever
sullied the name of
the Heaven's Blades
and was expelled for your crime.
Is that true?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN (VOICEOVER): In the
midst of their expedition,
Gorneo tells Nina of
Layfon's past crime.
Meanwhile, in Glendan, the
mystery behind Leerin's stalker
grows deeper.
And Savaris and Lintens must
stop them before it's too late.
Next time, the Right to be a
Heaven's Blade and Restoration.