Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
Feel the dizzy
ocean swell and roll!
The waves shall crush anything
that stands still and unmoving.
We must reject
the facade of safety.
Hmm, that is one
fine lady, indeed.
What a shame to waste such
a specimen on a crazy cultist.
The Dizziness of the
many hath no center!
It lives behind the
eyes behind the neck.
Everywhere, everywhere.
Fizzier. Tizzier. Dizzy, Dizzy!
Give swirlingly,
openly to the tides of love.
Sing sweetly, surely, silkily
with the melody of matrimony!
Now, then.
Onto the wedding program.
The bride and groom seal their
vows with a kiss. Smooch!
Such passion. It's enough
to make a guy jealous.
Next, the couple will
ascend to the top floor.
Father Dizzy will use the
pendant key around his neck.
And then, I'll treat
the wedding guests
to a surprise fireworks show!
What the hell is happening?
So pretty!
Hey, now, old man, what are
you crashed out here for?
You are what I would call...
A mighty fine lady!
Huh?!
Wavering, quavering,
but not falling.
I guess the
sedative didn't work?
Dizzy, dizzy!
Dizzy, dizzy?
Dizzy.
O! Sinful woman!
Thy black heart hath
erecte a wall of doom
in the dizzy sea of love.
Standing still,
steeped in stagnant sin.
The wall must
be toppled quickly.
The execution will occur
tomorrow at sunrise!
The world's spinning.
So the cult leader's beautiful
bride is really a thief.
What an unexpected
turn of events.
Your presence is
unexpected, as well.
Lupin the Third.
Oh, you've heard the
name before, have you?
As you said, I am a thief.
Don't let the dress fool you.
Lupin the Third, master thief,
grandson of the original Lupin.
He gives warning before
every crime he commits.
And he always
gets what he's after.
You are a man of great
talent and prestige.
I wouldn't think to find you
in a backwater like this.
Say, Lupin, may I--?
Fujiko Mine.
A lady looter unafraid
to use her feminine wiles.
With a voracious
appetite for treasure.
A pleasure to finally meet you.
You've done your homework.
Didn't you know? I have a
passion for knowledge.
This is the Order
of Fräulein Eule.
Its members let themselves
be covered in the dust
emitted by their leader's body
and abandon sense for the
pleasure of a dizzying high.
A bit like mass hypnosis.
And here we are
on Fräulein Island,
an isolated
community of believers
who offer up their fortunes
for the chance to dwell
in that hypnotic state
of perpetual bliss.
I have to admit,
getting in was not easy.
The Dizzy sect has
a secret treasure
that is closely guarded and only
unveiled on special occasions.
The pendant the leader
wears is the key.
And the treasure, of course,
is the dizzy dust itself.
So, you were going to kidnap
your new husband, eh?
I had quite the
honeymoon planned.
The drug must be very potent
for him to be able to control
so many believers with it.
Who knows what it could
sell for on the street?
The wedding would have
provided the perfect cover.
It was going so well.
And then you showed up.
You ruined my plans,
too, you know.
Fortunately, thieving is more
fun as a competitive sport.
Tell me, you have anything
in your bag of tricks
other than seduction?
Something that would make
you a worthy opponent?
Oh, dear. What if you're right
and I am a one trick pony?
Ah, my poor, virgin eyes!
I may have to let you
have your way with me.
In exchange for half your take.
Wouldn't that take some
of the fun out of our rivalry?
Perhaps we could
join forces, instead.
Until I find an opportune
moment to double-cross you.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Help me! It's awful!
He tried to.
Hold on! I'm not the one
who started stripping
off my clothes here!
Take him away.
Hey come on,
you've got it all wrong!
Give a guy a break, will you?
Let me go! Hey,
don't touch me there!
Thank you. You saved me!
Sure, I guess.
Yes, I know. You have
saved me for the moment,
but my life will
still end tomorrow.
Perhaps, one last
time before I die.
The time is at hand.
We must kill the vermin,
using these blades
to let forth a frothing
flood of their inner filth!
Take the male first!
And now the female!
O, poor woman,
wretched and vile.
I shall bestow one final
kiss upon thy corpse.
Dizzy, dizzy!
Thieving is more fun as a
competitive sport. Right, Lupin?
No hard feelings, huh?
I was duped! Tricked!
Led astray by an evil woman!
And I paid with my life!
But perhaps I can take
revenge upon her lovely flesh.
Hah! Gotcha.
What's going on?
Look at this!
That's nothing
but a stuffed sack!
Look! They're over there!
Oh, I see.
You're a thief and a killer.
Only when it's necessary.
"Necessary."
Like right now, maybe?
I know!
Let's make it a race.
A race?
Yeah, it'll be groovy. The first
one to grab the Dizzy treasure
and make it
out of here wins.
Huh?!
Hey! On the wall!
Alright, Fujiko. Game on!
Don't disappoint me!
Blast that woman and her male
accomplice. How dare they!
I will not let them
play me for a fool.
They will never get their
hands on the Dizzy treasure!
Behind the breasts and
the legs. Yes, everywhere!
Fizzy-uh, fizzy!
Tizzy-uh, tizzy!
Dizzy! Dizzy! Dizzy! Dizzy!
What is going on here?
So, I was right.
After our wedding kiss,
I realized drugs don't affect
you the way they do others.
You!
Don't worry, Pops.
This is only a sleeping powder.
Unlike that Dizzy
dust of yours.
The Fräulein Eule,
is it called?
The dust dissolves
easily in liquids.
You simply mix it in with a
solution of sodium acetate.
Then you smear the mixture
on every inch of your body.
Add a little stimulation,
and it crystallizes.
Aw, it melted! I must have
misjudged the temperature.
You're a piece of work.
Pretending to possess
mysterious powers,
when really you're just
getting your followers stoned.
Now, you're going to take
me to the secret stash
and don't forget to
bring the pendant.
Well, Lupin. I've made
my move. What's yours?
Fujiko Mine. That is one
unbalanced woman.
Infiltrating a dangerous
place like this all alone.
Nonchalantly killing to
get what she's after.
And masochistic enough
that she doesn't bat an
eye at the risk to herself.
I like that in a lady.
Oooh!
Looks like a massive drug lab.
The ultimate Dizzy
treasure is further on ahead.
Although, I have no
intention of handing it over
to a filthy vermin like you!
Exterminate that
woman, immediately!
Kill her! Fill her
filthy body with bullets!
You talk too much.
Open sesame!
Turn that wall back around!
I don't think I can!
The switch isn't working.
Is that what I think it is?
Yep! This baby is made of
100% Fräulein Eule crystal.
It looks like the drug and the
god are one and the same.
Must be a pretty
fun cult to belong to.
How did you find a way in here?
I'm that good.
Should we settle things here?
You are something. I admit.
I'm disappointed, Fujiko.
Desperation doesn't look
good on a fine lady like you.
Ah, well. I'm not
a "fine lady," am I?
Don't you remember, silly?
You said as much yourself.
I'm what you call
"a mighty fine lady!"
It's over, Lupin! I win!
You can run, but you can't hide!
Never a dull moment
with this firecracker.
She's even better
than I thought.
Give up already!
Hey! Watch where
you're grabbing!
Father Dizzy, it's the police!
The police are here?!
Inspector? Is Lupin the Third
really on that island?
Yep.
I've known for a while
that this place was a hub
for narcotics smugglers.
If that's the case,
may I ask why
we haven't searched
it before now, sir?
The more tempting the bait,
the better when you're trying
to catch a rat and sure enough,
the vermin went right for it.
We're taking Lupin along
with the trap he's caught in.
Got it, Oscar?
Yessir!
Seriously?
You announced the crime?
Why tie the noose
around your own neck?
Mere theft isn't enough.
I like more of a challenge.
Of all the stupi--
Ouch, a buoyancy tank.
What do you mean?
You see, this place isn't
really what it seems.
It's a fake island. It used to
be a giant offshore platform.
All this guy did was
plop a palace on top of it.
The idea is to
mass-produce the drugs here
and then ship them out through
underwater loading docks.
The platform has another
feature that's very helpful
for the business I do.
At the touch of a button, it'll
sink any evidence of my crimes.
To the bottom of the sea!
Well, it's been fun,
but it's time to get
out of this dizzy place.
You haven't won yet!
Serves you right,
you thieving vermin!
Great. I'm glad
you could make it.
Oh yes!
Lupin?!
What?
Too bad, Fujiko! I win!
I think you're getting a little
ahead of yourself. Bye, now.
No problem.
Sorry, not good enough!
Then is this good enough?
The stash! It's melting!
Oh, well. Nothing to be
done here. Hey! You, there!
What do you say
we take a little trip?
Quick, arrest them all!
Inspector!
Sir, we can't go any farther!
Lupin.
Damn it! If he hadn't shown
up, it would have worked.
"Fujiko Mine will be mine.
Lupin the Third."
He must've.
Lupin the Third.
Fujiko Mine.
A mighty fine lady
who just might cure
me of my boredom.
We'll meet again soon enough.
And when we do.