Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
Fujiko Mine!
Where am I?
Have they been doing
human experimentation?
What are these?
Fräulein Eule.
Who's there?
Did he say Fräulein Eule?
Ugh, not the nicest way
to start a story, is it?
Well now I know that
this is only the beginning
of the nightmare.
Fujiko Mine!
I would like for you
to steal Fujiko Mine.
Barging in like this, how rude!
And I'll pass on
the job, thanks.
This is something you
already intended to do.
I am just asking you to make
good on your threat promptly.
My threat, huh?
Oh that one.
So they've been watching me
all this time.
The one job where
it's not about impulse.
This is the woman I want.
And I don't like to share.
And here I thought
it was a point of pride
that you always stole what
you said you were going to.
Go back to your tree.
Cause we're done here.
Am I to assume you are
declining our request?
Right now all I wanna do
is count some sheep.
In that case, I shall
leave you for the time being.
Nighty-night.
I don't care much for owls.
Their night vision is too good.
But there are questions
I want answered.
What do these feathered
freaks want with her?
Just who is Fujiko Mine?
Inspector Zenigata.
Thank you for coming.
Let's get to it.
I want you to find me
immediate transportation to
the country home owned
by Count Almeida
of Glaucus Pharmaceuticals.
Oh I see.
Although it would be pretty late
if you left there now.
Why not stay the night
at the precinct--
No, thank you.
Just take me to the Count.
Yes, Sir.
This isn't much of an airport
that they've got here.
Such a tiny country.
Coming all this way
for a visit.
He better be grateful.
Count Luís Yu Almeida.
Naturally, this is only
the advance payment.
Momma!
Now that's a haul!
Fräulein Eule.
One of that cult's
facilities is home to
a drug manufacturing lab.
I would like you t--
A cult?
Sorry, but that's a brand
of crazy I don't like
to get involved with.
The job is simple, Lupin.
This woman will be
making an appearance
at their headquarters.
I'd like you to steal her.
That shouldn't be too difficult.
That is one fine looking woman.
Something else to deal with.
I'm going in.
Wait here.
Right.
And me, sir?
I presume Count Almeida
is at home?
May I ask your business?
I have some questions.
Where is he?
It's rather late to be visiting,
even for a police inquiry.
The night's still young.
I think we're showing more
than enough courtesy
by not just raiding the place.
Oh?
And why would you do
something like that?
Let us speak to the Count now,
our you'll find out.
I can come back with
a warrant if I need to.
Is that really how
you want this to play out?
It's as good as admitting
the Count is involved
with a low life thief.
Oscar enough.
I just want to ask the Count
about Lupin the Third.
Very well.
Right this way, please.
So uh you got a lot of
owl decorations in here.
Is the lord of the manor
an ornithologist?
The owl is the
servant of Minerva.
Among other things,
she is the goddess of wisdom
and of medicine.
I get it.
Perfect for a pharmaceutical
company, huh?
Here we are.
This is the count's bedchamber.
That's good to know.
Thanks, Inspector.
I already know that you've
approached Lupin the Third.
What I don't know
is what you're after.
The pharmaceutical
you're backing
has made millions on black
market transactions.
Does the word "dizzy"
mean anything to you?
The cult that reeled in
believers using a certain drug.
It was wiped out and Lupin
had something to do with it.
Somebody hired him, of course.
And I think you know who.
I see.
The cult was a front, a way to
disguise that the drug company
was doing human experiments.
It's mind control.
The deliberate overwriting of
the subjects' personalities.
Just like the CIA's
MKUltra experiments.
LSD, truth serums,
sensory deprivation,
hypnosis and that's
just the beginning.
Scary stuff!
The medical mafia uses
the Cold War to cook up
their conspiracy theories.
In the end,
it's all about fear.
Using fear to control
people. Breeding mistrust
and capitalizing on the
conflict that follows.
It's a disgustingly
profitable business.
One of your people
interrupted my beauty sleep.
Sorry, count but
I can hold grudges.
Mechanical.
Now that's elaborate.
Fräulein Eule.
"The owl of Minerva
takes flight only when
the shades of night
are gathering."
Heh why thank you, Hegel.
Tell me, then, Lupin the Third.
When does the
butterfly take flight?
I don't really care.
When Napoleon was in his prime,
Hegel referred to him as
the "Soul of the World." A man
who heralded the end of an era.
Minerva, not only a goddess of
war but of music and wisdom,
as well.
I hear her owl taking flight.
Listen, can you hear it?
Fräulein Eule.
The owl flies,
and the end comes with
the gathering shades of night.
The end comes.
And I say again.
I would like you
to steal Fujiko Mine.
Lupin the Third.
Keep on going straight.
There used to be a town
up there called Eulenspiegel.
Oh it's a ghost town now, sir.
Nobody's allowed in.
That's okay just take us there.
Yes, Sir.
"Fräulein Eule," huh?
I collected some sample crystals
of the drug Lupin said
he was after and had
the lab analyze them.
Why do that?
Manufacturing a new drug isn't
something a fringe group
like that could
do on their own.
I knew they had backers.
And those same backers just
approached Lupin again
for some reason.
What are they after?
I want to find out and
the answer should be in
the old Glaucus
Pharmaceuticals lab.
Fräulein Eule.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
The likes of you aren't welcome.
Tell me who you are first.
Very well, I am
Dr. Fritz Kaiser.
I was left behind in this town.
"Doctor," huh?
So where are we?
A deserted town, whose name
has been forever erased
from living memory.
This is Eulenspiegel.
And there we have the
Glaucus Pharmaceuticals lab,
built long ago to manufacture
and study the fear of death.
Here, in the utmost secrecy,
they researched the human soul.
Several scientists
who had fled from Japan
were once employed here.
My wife was one of them.
One of the lab's experiments was
a water-soluble hallucinogen
made from a compound extracted
from a certain plant
and crystallized.
The short-term physiological
effect was euphoria.
In cases of acute poisoning,
we observed heightened levels
of aggression.
And in some cases, subjects
began to look like owls.
Like owls?
Yes.
One incident stands out
in particular.
After taking a dose,
the subject's mental state
deteriorated quickly
and permanently.
The subject kept screaming:
Fräulein Eule.
"Fräulein Eule." What does
that mean, anyway?
It's German.
It translates as "Miss Owl."
Fascinating story.
Look, if everybody else is gone,
why are you still here?
I am here because
I'm looking for my tochter.
The daughter's name
is Fujiko Mine.
Congratulations.
Hmm?
The results of the
experiment aren't in yet.
That's not what I mean.
It's your birthday, isn't it?
Ah.
I suppose I forgot.
The whole lab celebrated your
daughter's birthday, so we--
I robbed my daughter
of her birthday celebration.
So I don't see any reason
why mine should be recognized.
Doctor.
Birthday celebrations are
meaningless rituals, anyway.
The same goes for
funerals--what's the point when
no man can attend his own?
There is no special difference
between the experiences
of birth and death.
"Memento mori," again?
Right.
What matters is a
person's recognition of
their approaching
death and their fear.
Urgent!
There has been a spill, C Block
will be closed off immediately.
Doctor!
Sir, your mask.
Hurry sir!
We need to get out of here.
The drug is still in the lab and
my tochter's in the sick bay!
Come back!
I can't go.
I have to find my tochter!
And that's how
this place came to ruin.
An entire town wiped out and
it never made the headlines?
Of course not.
To Glaucus Pharmaceuticals,
making the truth known
isn't what's important.
What's important to them is fear
and the suppression of it.
Yes, fear itself became my hope
but now-now, even fear is gone.
And in its place I'm left
with nothing but despair.
That's her, my tochter.
Where did he--?
This is Fujiko.
A town the whole world
has forgotten.
Thanks to an accident
thirteen years ago.
They rescued their
experimental drug,
which hadn't gone
to clinical trial yet.
Then they shut the place down.
Thirteen years.
Yeah, right around the time
that cult started to take off.
The Order of Fräulein Eule made
a convenient testing ground
for Glaucus Pharmaceuticals.
But that doesn't explain why
Lupin would get involved.
Inspector, you knew all
this from the beginning?
But why didn't you ever--
Why didn't I ever tell you?
Who do you think you are?
Really?
Do I work for you now?
No, sir.
I didn't mean to-
Don't get in my way again.
You can keep tagging
along if you want to
but Oscar this is
my case, got it?
Inspector how far
are you willing to go?
Where did you go, Doctor?
I knew you would show up, Lupin!
You know, I could say
the same to you, Inspector.
I guess it must be something
about the Dizzy drug.
If it's involved,
you always show up
when things are gettin' good.
Don't even bother
playing dumb with me.
You aren't here because
you're after the Dizzy drug
or the pile of cash you
could get selling it.
What are you saying?
It's Fujiko Mine, right?
She's what you're really after.
The woman used in this lab
as a human experiment.
She's unassailable
evidence of the crimes
that tie the cult
to this company.
Sorry to interrupt such
a masterful speech.
But there's assailing evidence
right behind you.
Shit!
What the hell?!
Lupin, who are those guys?
Illusions!
There's Fraulein Eule
all over this place.
In that case, it shouldn't
matter if they hit me.
You wanna test that theory?
You're the one
they want, not me.
You know too much now.
Too many of the secrets
the Count wants kept quiet.
We're outnumbered.
You think?
Doctor!
What are you doing here?
What's going on?!
Answer me!
How much of this
is an illusion?
Dammit!
Hey, you!
This way!
Come on!
Hurry!
Where are we?
This is a part of my tale
and the whole of it, as well.
It's her.
You used your own daughter
in your experiments.
I truly believed, you see.
I thought the experiments
we were doing would
finally end the war.
So I did it.
I offered up my beloved
daughter, and then-
They buried you along
with the rest of the town.
They stole your research
and your daughter.
But what am I doing here?
I brought you here because
I want you to save my tochter.
Morning has come again.
Night time has gone away.
Do you know why
you're so special?
Why makes today
so different today?
Why am I so special?
It's your birthday!
Doctor where are you?
He's not here anymore.
There's no reason
for him to be.
This is my tale.
No.
These are the effects
of the drug, that's all.
When I wake up,
things'll be back to normal.
Are you sure?
Some people get lost here.
They don't know where the exit
is, so they get stuck forever.
The doctor?
Exactly.
So how do I find the exit?
You just have to use
something that's connected
to reality to capture me.
Like maybe-
Like pain!
Why are you here?
Don't be silly!
I already told you:
because this is my tale.
Dammit, I guess
I'll have to play along.
This way!
Too bad!
I'm over here!
What am I chasing?
An illusion?
Fujiko Mine?
Right, Fujiko.
Ow-ow-ow!
That's it.
I'm done.
You're giving up?
We just started!
You're just gonna disappear.
Well, do what you want.
May I really do what I want?
Sure, go ahead.
I win!
Gotcha!
Don't be so rough.
It'll hurt.
Lupin.
Fräulein Eule.
What a magnificent twilight.
Perfect for the end.
Shut up.
I know you're dead, Doctor.
You're not real.
None of this is.
It's all just a tale.
A tale with no salvation.
Do not forget.
The moment you grasp the
butterfly, it takes flight,
and everything perishes.
Oh, no!
Inspector!
Wake up!
Are you okay?
Glaucus Pharmaceuticals
covered up their accident
by obliterating the town.
They also hid the fact that they
were doing human experiments.
There's even a sick rumor
that this doctor was using
his own daughter
as a test subject.
He referred to her using
the German word "tochter."
Whoa, hold on a second.
Eulenspiegel is
still private land.
You want to indict this guy with
evidence you got illegally?
And where is Lupin
in all this?
These guys are
after the same thing.
Both Lupin and Count Almeida
want to get their hands
on that woman.
Lupin will show up there.
I'm sure of it.
Fujiko Mine!
This is-
It isn't a dream but
does that mean it's real?
Fräulein Eule.
Or is this nightmare just
another installment in the tale
of the woman
called Fujiko Mine?