Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
Georg Trunk, King of Astria.
A perfect opportunity to make
a name for yourself.
By assassinating a king?
Don't worry.
It's a nothing country that uses
casinos to draw in tourists.
That said, the pay's
plenty for a novice hit man
looking to make his bones
in the underworld.
Who's the client?
A relative?
It's not your place to ask.
But there shouldn't be any
international repercussions.
Well, Mr. Ishikawa?
Look at it.
Practically a museum's worth
of world treasures.
I-I-I-I-Ice cream!
Yea, yea yea! Yea!
Bully-Bully-Bully-Bully-Bull
dog!
Go, go, go, go!
Pu-pu-pu-pu-pudding parfait!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Yeah!
Everybody come together!
Freunde auf der ganzen...
Hey! Look, it's a samurai!
Marco!
He's so cool.
Papa really liked
this picture, huh?
Samurai!
Samu-Samu-Samu-Samu
Samu-Samu-Samu...
Samurai Freund!
Those are not the words from
the song Mama wrote, Marco!
Well, I'm adding it!
Samu-Samu-Samu-Samu
Samurai Freund!
Whoa, whoa, whoa whoa!
Hey, look guys!
Now, children.
These men are busy working.
You mustn't get in their way.
Fraulein Maria!
You've got a long trip
back home tomorrow.
So let's all go back to
the hotel and get some rest.
Okay, Fraulein!
And I'll tell you what.
While we're walking, we can sing
that song you love so much.
Yea!
Let's hear it!
I-I-I-I-Ice cream!
Yea, yea, yea!
Yea!
I-I-I-I-Ice cream!
Yea, yea, yea!
Yea!
Bully-Bully-Bully-Bully-Bull
dog!
Go, go, go, go!
Samu-Samu-Samu-Samu-Samurai
Freund!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Marco!
Clear for departure!
You must be quite weary, sire.
Diplomacy can tax a man sorely.
I'm glad I was able
to spend some time
with my grandchildren, though.
And that governess, too.
Fraulein Maria.
She'll only be
with us 'til fall.
She's doing fine work.
Yes.
If only my daughter were
as dependable as she is.
There is nothing to be
done about that now, sire.
My young mistress is formally
a part of the Shumate family.
It won't work.
My father would
never hear of it.
Well then it's time
to face facts.
The Crown Prince is dead.
Yes.
My father grieves for my
brother's death day and night.
You are the next in line
for the throne.
And I'll be by your side.
No, dear.
I'm sorry.
My late brother's son
Marco is the heir now.
He's a little boy!
He can't rule a country!
We owe it to the people
to take charge.
That's a decision
for the king to make.
What did I tell you?
I don't intend
to babysit those brats.
Oh, Grace, look
at their dresses!
They're so lovely!
Real ladies!
Like Mama.
Hey now.
You know Mama is gone.
I know!
But I miss her so much!
No crying, remember?
We promised.
I-I-I-I-Ice cream!
Yea, yea, yea!
Grace, Louise,
look what I got for us!
Marco, look out!
Honestly, you are so clumsy!
Sa-Sa Samurai Freund.
Too soft!
What's wrong, children?
Marco is quite taken
by samurai, you see.
He was enthralled by some
prints at the Louvrun Museum.
Too soft.
Uh, I'm sorry?
I am curious.
The boy said something
about a Samurai Freund.
What does this mean?
It's just a song they sing.
As for "Samurai Freund"
Well sounds a lot
like "friend," huh?
So "Freund" is "friend"?
You taught your
children this song?
Hold on!
I'm not their mother,
just their governess.
Their parents were
both killed three years ago
in an automobile accident.
I'm Maria.
It's nice to meet you.
What's your name?
My name, uh.
We brought you tea,
Samurai Freund.
Your name is Marco.
A man should never cry over
something like ice cream.
Understand?
Promise me, man to man.
Right!
I promise!
Man to man!
Who knew there was
a samurai on board!
Yeah. How come we didn't
notice you on board before?
Who are you, exactly?
Oh, cool!
It's a bunny!
Yes, it is a rabbit.
Children like rabbits.
I know these things because
I am a traveling entertainer,
Goemon Ishikawa.
It's wonderful.
You're talented.
Yank! Yank!
Stop that!
What are you wearing?
It's so weird!
They believe Shumate
will be the heir?
But we know Prince Marco
is the true heir.
Best not to look
at that too long, sire.
Marco will rule and
until he's ready, I will.
"Best not to look." Once more,
I have cut a worthless object.
I shall not be led astray
by feminine charms.
Your life is forfeit.
Opa!
It was so cool!
Have you scamps been
exploring the train?
Another time.
Honor demands that
I take your life in private.
Damn, too soft!
What could that be?
Goodness!
What happened to you?
So, I suppose
a samurai like you isn't
an uncommon sight in Japan--
No.
I am sad to say there
is no place in Japan
for samurai anymore.
Is that what made you
want to travel?
Perhaps so.
That is not all, however.
You're not alone, you know?
I feel the same way.
Like there's no place
for me, anywhere.
But you have the
children to look after.
You have Freund.
Yes, I guess I do.
Still, I am just
a lowly governess,
and a temporary one at that.
Well, I guess
I'm going to turn in.
Goodnight, Samurai Freund.
She's lovely.
He's no ordinary
entertainer at all.
Clear for departure!
Time to say goodbye, King Trunk,
and you as well, Ishikawa.
The train...
Stop! Slow down!
I have an emergency report!
There's an out
of control train!
It's no use, sir!
I'm not getting an answer!
Your Majesty.
If we continue at this speed,
we'll derail before long.
Opa!
What in the world?
Don't worry,
it will be all right.
We've met with foul play.
The train engineer--
Someone killed him.
I think I know
what has happened.
Mr. Samurai!
Just what are you
talking about?
Cheap stage performer.
What would you know?
Seize that man!
Put down your weapon.
Go ahead, men.
Shoot him!
--Stop! No! No!
--Don't shoot! He's nice!
My sword is sharp.
The Zantetsuken cuts anything.
Whoa, amazing.
Who are you, really?
My name is Goemon Ishikawa.
I came here on a mission
to take Your Majesty's life.
And you pretended to be
some sort of entertainer?
Are you the saboteur, as well?
No sir, I'm not, this
situation was not my doing.
I will hear
what you have to say.
Majesty!
We have no time to waste.
Maria, evacuate the children
and other passengers
to the rear car.
Okay.
Quickly now, children.
My inexperience
is to blame for this.
--Mr. Ishika--
--I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Fraulein Maria!
Marco went to rescue
Papa's painting!
All right.
You two go on ahead.
Two separate attempts?
They have done this because they
did not believe I would succeed.
No.
I imagine this was
the plan from the outset.
That's how he operates.
Schemes within schemes.
By trying to kill me, as well,
they have broken the contract.
I have no obligation
to kill you now.
Instead, I will do
what I can to help.
Miss Maria!
What is wrong?
It's Marco.
He's gone to the freight car.
Papa's samurai.
Marco!
Fraulein Maria!
We have one chance.
If we cut loose the cargo,
we should be able
to slow the rest of the train.
But we're carrying
national treasures!
Maria, what's more important?
Those or the children?
Very well.
We have to go, Marco.
Okay, I understand.
It's Opa!
Marco!
Sire!
We need to hurry!
They made it back!
Don't worry.
Our Samurai Freund
is going to save us.
I won't cry!
I promised!
That's a brave young man.
We don't have much time left.
Right.
I'll make sure
the children are secure.
But I'm going to need
all of your belts.
Oh. It doesn't reach.
Maria, here. Use my belt.
All right!
Brake!
Once more, I have cut
a worthless object.
Ah, well.
So much for the museum
of world treasures.
I-I-I-I-Ice cream!
Yea, yea, yea! Yea!
Bully-Bully-Bully-Bull dog!
Go, go, go!
Go!
Samu-Samu-Samu-Samu-
Samurai Freund!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Everybody come together!
Freunde auf der ganzen!
Fr-Fr-Fr-FrFreunde!
You saved all of us.
You have my thanks.
I have no need for thanks but
now the shadows are calling.
I must go.
Wait.
The children.
At least say
goodbye to Marco.
My Freund, I wish them well.
Sorry.
Grace!
Louise!
Marco!
Come here!
Opa!
Well, shall we go home now?
There they are!
Thank goodness
they're all safe!
What is this?
This is Ishikawa's doing!
What in the world
is going on here?
I'm sure the baron
can explain it all to you.
I'm sorry, Boss.
I slipped up.
I suggest you come with us,
Baron Schumate.
Good night, you three.
Sweet dreams.
Samu-Samu-Samurai Freund.
Dear boy.
Be an excellent king,
you hear me?
Well! How long
have you been there?
Are you on my side of the law?
I suppose you could say that,
Mister Samurai.
An assassin, then.
Or are you a thief?
All that treasure
gone up in flames.
What a criminal
waste of effort.
But the children all survived.
That was thanks to you.
Please, I'm no hero.
Not my style.
Who are you?
What is your real name?
Who am I, huh?
I'm just a woman.
Beautiful!
Isn't it?
This has been in the royal
family for generations.
They say Auguste Rodin
secretly gave it to his lover,
Camille Claudel.
It's called
The Supplicant King.
That's what you were
after the whole time?
Yes.
It was all an act.
Aw, are you shocked?
But I'm just like you--
it's part of the job.
Not so.
You helped me see past that.
I mean, you don't have any
place where you belong, either.
That's what you said and likely
you don't have any true Freund.
But if you were with me,
you could have a true--
With you, I could
have a true what?
Do tell.
I'm Fujiko Mine and I
hope we meet again,
my adorable samurai Freund.
A true boyfriend.
That's what I was
going to say.
See you around, Goemon!
Her name is Fujiko, huh.
Who goes there?!
Fire!
Once again, I have
cut worthless objects.