Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
It was such
a tiny thing, really.
Almost insignificant.
If I'd just given it to them,
they probably would have
left me alone.
Don't you move!
But I couldn't.
It was so beautiful,
as if someone had scattered
a handful of gems.
And among them
there was one black gem that
gleamed the brightest of all.
So, you're awake.
Here, kid.
But what you were
protecting was your pride.
"I will protect this, too,"
I thought to myself.
This priceless gem.
A necklace has been stolen-- an
heirloom of the Bourbone family.
There were hundreds
of police guards on site,
but it was stolen from
right under their noses.
Who did it?
Fujiko Mine again.
Last month it was a golden
ring from Mycenaean Greece.
Seems like she's got a taste
for the gaudier items lately.
Also, she's been taking
a page from Lupin's book.
Woman doesn't know her place.
This time it's the
Duchess of l'Angoulée's tiara,
housed at the Musée des
beaux-arts de Marséne.
What now?
I've been reassigned
to Fujiko Duty.
I'm on her case full time now.
I can't hunt Lupin
'til she's caught.
I hate wasting time on some
third-rate female thief.
Even as we speak,
Lupin could b--
Inspector!
I will dedicate myself
to arresting Fujiko Mine.
On my life, I'll get her!
What is this slop?
The substance is called
"oatmeal." I tried boiling it
in fish stock.
You don't like it?
What the hell is with you?
Do you think
you're my guardian?!
What's in this for you?
If you want to sleep with me,
be a man and say so!
You'll catch cold.
Just get out.
Without a doubt, she is
an unapologetic seductress.
In the beginning I revered her
as something almost holy.
Have my powers of
observation been corrupted?
A deadly flaw for one
devoted to the path
of the sword but perhaps
I wasn't wholly incorrect.
And now we bring you
breaking news on the theft
of the Bourbone necklace.
Investigators have released
the name Fujiko Mine
as the party who had
allegedly given them
advanced notes of the crime.
This comes to us via
press conference
held only moments ago.
This comes on the heels of the
Mycenaean ring theft last month.
She's a mystery,
the woman called Fujiko Mine.
I must learn
the truth about her.
It will give me a chance
to practice my swordsmanship.
Update, sir:
Security is airtight.
I've stationed fifty
guards at the front door,
thirty at the back,
and another three hundred or so
around the building's perimeter
and in the neighboring streets.
An ant couldn't sneak in here,
let alone a thieving rat.
Gas masks, everyone!
Tear gas released
from the sprinklers.
Everything is going
according to plan.
Hold your ground.
Protect the tiara!
Inspector, perhaps Fujiko
decided not to make her move.
Yeah, maybe.
Contact the lab.
I want this authenticated now.
Too close.
The perfect crime,
preceded by a written warning.
The MO of this is much too
flashy for it to have been
Fujiko's work.
Unlike Lupin, who gets
off on the experience
of stealing itself. Fujiko
only has eyes for the loot.
She doesn't go out
of her way to take risks.
There are four
possible points of entry.
But none show any trace
of being forced which means
the tiara wasn't
stolen that night.
The reasonable assumption,
then, is that it had already
swapped out with a fake.
Except that the museum had been
sealed off the whole week since
the warning note was sent.
We had the tiara analyzed
two days before the theft,
and it was the genuine article.
And if that wasn't enough,
the police have apparently
discovered her hair and
fingerprints at each crime scene
as if she were deliberately
leaving clues behind.
How transparent.
What we've got here is-
A dirty cop.
It has to be.
And that means-
Inspector!
We've received
another note from Fujiko.
Her target this time is
Marie Louise's engagement ring,
which is housed at the
Musée Archéologique.
Oscar, you swore on your life
that you would get Fujiko Mine.
Yes, Sir.
In that case,
I'll leave it in your hands.
What will you do, sir?
Until this case is solved,
you can't go after Lupin!
But why?
Why is the inspector
abandoning the case?
There!
It's Fujiko Mine!
Get her!
Why isn't he trying
to capture Fujiko?
By now shouldn't
he want her, dead or alive?
There you are!
Wait, Lieutenant Oscar?
Ah that's it.
I know what to do.
Huh?
Fujiko Mine isn't
wanted for murder yet.
That could change everything.
What was that?!
Find her!
Lieutenant Oscar.
Please, don't be alarmed.
We have a common interest.
An owl?
We've taken the liberty of
looking into your background.
Inspector Zenigata took you
in when you had no one else.
With his help, you clawed your
way to the rank of Lieutenant.
In time, the respect and
admiration you felt for him
evolved into love,
and then passion.
Now, you will
even kill for him.
What do you know?!
I know you want him
to pursue you.
Shut up!
Why dress as Fujiko Mine then,
when disguising yourself
as Lupin would surely draw his
attention that much faster?
Just shut up, you stupid bird!
I know why.
You want Inspector
Zenigata to "interrogate"
you the same way
he did Fujiko Mine.
The sharp, sweet
intimacy of that room.
The deep,
penetrating questions.
No!!!
We can help you, Lieutenant.
We can give you what you want.
We can make
your dreams come true.
Simply follow the path
until it leads you
to The Bride of Terror.
Fujiko sent warning of
a crime during this week's
Fete Nationale.
The festival centers on
"the bride of the year,"
who symbolizes faithfulness
to the Revolution until death.
Fujiko's stated target
is the gown worn by the bride.
The dress is adorned with
precious gems from all over
the world, each more
beautiful than the last.
The gown is lovely enough to
outshine the bride who wears it.
I'll be commanding
this operation
in Inspector Zenigata's place.
Just like I thought.
Breaking news, the theft of
Marie Louise's...
He acts all noble but in the
end, all men are the same.
...to Fujiko Mine. The suspect
is said to have shot an officer
to death before fleeing
the scene with the ring.
What?
What ring?
In contrast to the theft
of Duchess l'Angoulee's tiara,
this crime was
extremely brutal...
A tiara?!
I shall adorn
your head with a tiara.
...Growing frustration within
the precinct and anger
over the loss of one of
their own has prompted them
to bring in reinforcements,
so the case can be resolved...
I-I have to.
I have to kill her.
I have to kill Fujiko Mine.
Count Almeida.
Excellent news.
A new page is about
to be written
in the tale of Fujiko Mine.
One please.
A man cannot fight on
an empty stomach.
Ooh! Yummy!
Now, then.
A bomb threat?!
Yes, sir.
The perp claims to have planted
a bomb somewhere in the city.
How do we know this isn't a ploy
to distract our attention?
Celebrating the Fete Nationale
is an important part
of our culture.
We can't simply
cancel the parade!
Damn that woman.
What is Fujiko thinking?
Nothing at all, I would guess.
Inspector!
No way is this
Fujiko Mine's handiwork.
She would never pull
a stunt like this.
W-what?
Consider what
we know about her.
About how she operates.
This recent string
of crimes isn't her style.
It's far more likely that
somebody else is behind them.
But sir how could that be?
There's plenty of evidence
to place her at the--
Evidence?
I believe in what I can see.
I believe what
I can see-can see-can see...
I believe in Fujiko Mine.
You believe in Fujiko Mine?
A parade.
A hidden bomb.
Vile, filthy spittoon!
There are some things that
can only truly be understood
between a man and a woman.
Things that cannot be
felt or realized until
the two have joined.
Go away!
We have not come here
to fight you.
We wish only a moment
of your time to speak about
the plans for the parade.
I can't take much more of this.
Haven't you already
manipulated me enough?!
Fine, have it your way.
What else do you want from me?
Start chirping, you damn birds.
Attention: the Bride
is approaching point S
The parade will proceed down
the Avenue des Chandeliers and,
finally, to the bridge.
Just before it reaches
a bridge, there will be
a shower of fireworks.
At about the same time,
a bomb planted at the
bridge's center will detonate.
The bridge will explode.
As chaos ripples through the
crowd and the police scramble
to control the situation,
you will arrive.
You will whisk the Bride of
the Revolution away to safety.
Or so it will seem.
Instead, you will
seize her dress.
What's taking so long?
I can't get through to anyone.
Why not?
What's going on?
Sir!
Trouble on the parade route!
The road's been blocked!
Look!
A ninja!
Cut!
Alright let alter the route!!
We are the keepers
of this city!
The parade will continue!
Now, where is it?
Gotcha.
Again with the owls?
I gotta say, the guy
who set this up
is one determined bastard.
Let's see.
You have to disable
the vibration-triggered
detonator first.
If the owl's talons so much as
brush that stick, it's all over.
Let's see if we can immobilize
it with a little adhesive.
I'm a thief, not a bomb expert.
But I don't like people
who pull this kind of crap.
Please remain where you are.
Good news, Inspector!
We've been able to keep
the parade going.
I almost forgot how
many years have passed.
How long it's been since
I took a low-paying,
thankless job in this city.
Didn't take much time
for corruption to get me.
That was the only way for
a guy like me to make it
to the top or so I thought.
But right here in this
spot I met a grubby kid
who did whatever it took
to protect one measly franc.
Inspector Zenigata.
I learned something from
the little brat that day.
He taught me there's one thing
you should never let go of,
no matter how dirty
your hands are.
It may seem like a trivial
little thing but it's all
that a man's really got.
You let it go
and you're finished.
Everything you've done
will turn to dust.
So I reported my superior.
I lost all chance of promotion
but I don't regret it.
I believe in people who do what
it takes to protect their pride.
A gem.
A black gem.
It's over.
I almost lost what
I really cared about
by trying to protect it!
Oscar!
I didn't give a damn
about my pride.
There was something
else I wanted,
no matter how dirty I had to
get or how far I had to fall.
But now...
Still armed.
It didn't work.
You--
There's no time to stop it.
What are you doing?
Now.
I know, I held it
in my hand all along.
Hey!
As wretched as I am you
believed in me, all this time.
That belief is all that matters.
It's what I really
want to protect.
It's mine forever now.
My gem.
My priceless black gem.