Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
Amazing!
Picture!
Can we have a picture, please?
Say, "Geisha!"
Say, "pretty geisha!"
Too bad.
A miss!
Hey!
A blind man could tell
I made that shot dead-on.
You want to win, you got to
hit exactly the right spot.
Miss by even a little bit,
and there's no joy for anyone,
mister.
Dammit!
You win some, you lose some.
I'm curious, Jigen.
What was it that made you
accept my invitation?
Well, let's see, here.
I'm homeless and I'm broke.
A job that came with a spa
vacation sounded pretty good.
So, what made you
invite me along?
Handling perishable
merchandise on your own
is a tricky business.
I'm just trying to
keep things fresh.
It's about time we got started.
Thanks for playing, sir.
I'll just take
this one, thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen, step right
up and take a closer look!
No charge until
the show's over!
The most frightening event of
the evening is about to begin!
Do you hear those noises?
Those are the moans
of the Snake Woman!
Please, come on it!
Disturbing, yet fascinating.
How can you look away?
She is but one exhibit in
our museum of living art,
a mere prelude to the
night's main attraction.
Oh, sorry, fellas.
It starts to get a
little difficult around
the fifteenth time or so.
And finally, we are proud
to be showcasing the work
of the last artistic genius
of the twentieth century:
Aiden Nartar.
The great master
of magical realism.
Prepare yourselves for
the truly incredible!
Said to be the fruit of an
unholy union between human
and beast deep in heart
of the Amazon Jungle.
Behold!
These patterns were
tattooed on her body
shortly after her birth.
For the sins of the parents,
the child must pay.
Turn your gaze and look upon the
Kaleidoscope Woman, if you dare!
Look at that!
This woman's body became
Aiden Nartar's canvas
when she was still an infant.
She is a living painting!
This is a once in
a lifetime opportunity.
Never again will you see
a woman so valuable.
Take a moment, ladies and
gentlemen, and consider
the worth of such a prize.
Let us begin.
Bidding starts at
one million dollars.
One and a half million!
Do we have two million?
Three million!
Three and half million!
Four million!
I bid four point two!
Four point three million!
Four and a half!
Four point eight million!
Is it time?
Sure is.
What are you doing?
That was too soon, man!
It wasn't me!
You see what I mean?
That game was rigged--my shots
always hit dead-center.
Whoa, there.
That's far enough.
Stop running, you freak!
You're a pretty
foxy lady up close.
This poor kid.
She's even got 'em
on her tongue.
Ow.
I'm thinking she
can't talk, either.
Not surprising.
She's a piece of art:
a living, breathing,
ever-shifting canvas designed
for the viewer's enjoyment.
That's the idea, at least.
Her creator would have treated
her like any other painting.
And why would anyone
waste time trying to teach
a painting how to speak?
This artist is a
seriously twisted guy.
Turning her entire life
into some grotesque exhibit.
Here you go.
Easy, Casanova.
We can't have the loot
getting a crush on you.
That would just be awkward.
Hey, I'm just bein' nice.
Screw you!
Hand over the goods, boys.
I figured it was you.
Great. Her again?
Give me the woman.
She belongs to me.
You know I've got
a soft spot for fine ladies.
Now that I know she's
such a fox, I can't just
turn her over to you.
All right, then.
We'll do this the hard way.
Hey, catch!
Stay close to me.
Is it just me, or does she
seem a lot more wound up
than usual today?
That time of the month, maybe?
Eeny, meany, miny, moe,
catch a geisha by the toe!
If she--
Hollers!
Let her go!
Oh, dear!
Catch you later!
Tell me, Fujiko,
is there anything you want?
And now, viewers, we have a
display of rare treasures
from around the world.
First up, we have a
solid-gold teapot studded
with three-carat diamonds.
Next, a durian--the
king of fruits!
This fine specimen is one
of the largest ever recorded.
And, finally, the
masterpiece of the century!
Not too hard on
the eyes, is she?
This is truly incredible.
A work of art with
its own biography.
A painting with a riveting tale,
the tale called life!
You can find her in the circus
tent at Hatami Hot Springs.
Fujiko?
What's wrong, Fujiko?
I swear.
One way or another.
I will make it mine.
Careful, it's a long way down.
Here we go.
Is she trying to kill us?
She's barely aiming.
It's like she doesn't even
care if the loot gets damaged
in the process.
This is insane!
What's with her?
I think she's finally lost it.
Crazy.
It's like she's possessed.
Time to get out of here.
What?
From this height it's suicide!
Let's go!
One, Two, Three!
Four!
Sorry.
Think she's dead?
I don't know.
If she dies in a place like
this, she's not the woman
I thought she was.
Oh, yeah?
Fujiko's not the only one
with a secret.
Lupin's hiding something, too,
the dirty, scheming bastard.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
Happiness doesn't come
easy with so much baggage
to carry around
but--Try anyway.
Just do your best, okay?
The only description we
have is "painted lady."
You think we're gonna
recognize her?
From what I hear, she's worth
quite a pretty penny.
I just hope there aren't
any big-time crooks
looking for her, too.
What a mess.
But did it actually kill her?
Pretty amazing, huh?
Man, I wish I'd brought
a camera with me.
That would sure give
the wife a surprise!
What the--?!
They're trying to
run us off the road!
What the hell
are they after?!
Here we go.
I got ya!
It's time to go-go-go-go-go!
You're not getting away.
Dammit!
I can't move.
A-ba ba ba ba-ba,
a-ba ba ba ba ba ba ba
The water feels great!
Why don't you come on in
and join us, Fujiko?
Hah!
You missed!
Toodle-oodle-oo!
You better be careful!
It gets really hot at
the source of the spring!
Judges give it
a ten point oh!
You've hit a dead-end.
Be careful!
We're surrounded by extremely
volatile natural gas.
One spark from this baby
and we're all crispy critters.
What do want from
this lady, anyway?
Wha--?
Think about it.
Why do I steal anything?
I can sell her to the highest
bidder for a ton of ca--
If that was your game, you'd
want her in pristine condition.
Wouldn't want to scratch her.
Any damage tanks the
price and you know it.
So what are you
really after, Fujiko?
You want to kill
the poor girl?
No, that's not it.
That's not it at all.
It's yourself
you want to kill.
Your life's been
manipulated by strangers.
When you steal, when you eat,
even when you breathe.
Everything you do is part
of somebody else's plan.
People you don't even know
threw your destiny off-course,
but you have to go on living;
powerless and pathetic.
You see yourself when you look
at her, and you can't take it.
Isn't that right, Fujiko Mine?
And if it is?!
What then?
What am I supposed to do?
Do you think I'm
the best one to ask?
Hey now!
I wouldn't do that.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
That's actually a squirt gun.
Sorry.
Don't take
another step, Fujiko.
Shoot, and you blow us all up,
just so ya know.
Damn.
Right, that's it.
Tell me what you know
about that woman.
Sorry, but I'm not letting
that cat out of the bag.
My life's a lot more fun,
thanks to Fujiko.
And that's not something
I'm willing to give up.
So much for the
living painting.
I think she deserves
a blank canvas.
What the hell,
what the hell, what the hell.
what the hell, wha--.