Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
Dying day.
Is there any particular
reason for the shades?
It's still light, you know.
I want you to
exact revenge for me.
I'll pay you well
for your services.
You just have
to do one thing.
Ruin the man who stole
my dying day.
Shitoto.
A fortune teller who
specializes in predicting
when his clients will die.
Takes guts to
find that out, huh?
It wasn't really something
I was interested in knowing.
I'm not really the kind
who likes to have
my fortune told or anything.
He came to me with the offer.
Yeah, sure and once
he said he could tell you,
you just had to know.
That's right.
Curiosity, idle,
half-doubting curiosity.
But the closer I get to the time
he foretold, the more I believe.
This is where you
come in, Jigen.
If I do die, I want you
to destroy the lithograph
that Shitoto values more than
his own life and end his career
as a teller of doomed fortunes.
It may not make sense to you.
But that's the best revenge
I can think of.
That man stole the peace
of my final hours
and filled them instead
with the fear of death.
He must pay.
Hold on, you're saying
today is the day?
I'm counting on you, assassin.
There was this man who wanted
to know when he would die.
But as soon as his
question was answered,
he wanted that
knowledge taken away.
Some ego, huh?
Interestingly, he died the
day he was told he would.
Coincidence?
Or is there really
a fortune teller who can
predict when
you're going to die?
We have eleven
seemingly unconnected,
unexplained murders
and accidental deaths.
Yeah, so what?
If they're unconnected,
why should we treat them
as one case?
Because they do have one
interesting thing in common.
The deceased were all victims
of Lupin's thefts.
There's more, sir.
Their ages and causes
of death vary
but they all had ties
to one other person.
Shitoto Chandra.
The "dying day fortune
teller." Every single victim
on our list met with this man.
We should look into him.
I'm sure he can give us
information on Lupin.
Don't make me waste any bullets.
Your forehead isn't my target.
Just tell me where the
"dying day" lithograph is.
I don't consider myself
a death-teller, you know.
In fact, my interest is in
the whole of a client's life.
Everything from his past, his
present, his future, and yes,
his final hour, as well.
What's that thing?
That's the lithograph.
As you can see,
it's already been robbed
of its power by arson.
So somebody got here ahead
of me and did the deed.
I guess it doesn't
matter who did it,
as long as you're
outta work now.
You know what they say, "To
everything, there is a season."
You're an awfully good loser.
You set me up.
Hands in the air.
You're completely surrounded.
You are both under arrest.
Lieutenant!
It isn't Lupin!
Lupin?
Just what kind of joke is this?!
It could be him in disguise.
Let's make sure.
Oh, come off it.
I'm not Lupin.
The name's Jig--
You got a smoke?
These things?
Crappy French brand.
You should be nicer to the man
who just saved your ass.
I am offering you
great fame and fortune.
All you have to do is
foretell the dying days
of Lupin the Third's victims.
They will all die on
the days that you predict.
I guarantee it.
It will be done, my lord.
I have set all the
necessary events in motion.
Ahh, tasty!
Home cooking?
From you?
It's my grandma's recipe.
Oh, yeah?
I remember a movie
from a while back.
About a criminal
who said he could cook.
He made dinner, and nobody but
him survived the second course.
And now for the
secret ingredient:
a ten-year-old Chateau
Le Pin. Uh-oh!
Ow! Hot! Hot!
Hot, hot, hot!
So, why'd you bust me out?
I wasn't planning to, but
when you see a guy screw up
that bad-- Well, it was hard
not to take pity on you.
Besides, I felt like
we bonded over
that whole near-death thing.
Oh, you are so full of crap.
Aw, don't be so cynical.
Eat, it's getting cold!
Here we have a
potato gnocchi with
a special ragu alla Bolognese.
Shitoto, the man you
were picked up with,
went from being a no-name
hack to the psychic star
of the underworld about
three years back.
So this guy makes a living
telling people when
they're going to die
and he's popular?
That isn't the only reason
he's become so well known.
His clients are all people
whose possessions I've,
shall we say "liberated?"
And there's someone else
involved I'm interested in, too.
From that stupid grin,
I'm guessing it's her.
What a buncha crap, but I
don't want to be in your debt,
so what's the plan?
You're in an awfully good mood.
Lupin?!
Seriously, though.
You seem very chipper,
considering you just
lost your most prized possession
or so Daisuke Jigen tells me.
I don't know what
you want from me.
I'm a fortune teller.
My clients simply want me
to tell them what day
they're going to die.
I receive compensation for doing
my job, just like anybody else.
That's all it is.
Except that you
fabricate the dates.
Perhaps you used hallucinogenic
incense in your parlor
to make them susceptible
to hypnotic autosuggestion.
It could be,
their cars were sabotaged
or targeted by
third-rate hit men.
Or, maybe--
You have a capsule about
yea big that you can design
to activate on
a certain date and time,
even years into the future.
I'm just guessing
all this, of course.
But still, there are parasites
out there that can lie dormant
in the human body lying in
wait to spread their poison.
Really, there are all kinds of
ways to make sure a man dies
on a certain day, even if he's
behind bulletproof glass.
You sure as hell don't have
any special psychic powers.
So, how about you tell me.
Why are you killing
the people I've stolen from?
Please!
You don't understand
what you're talking abou--
If you're not gonna talk, then
I'm afraid we're all done here.
Give my finest regards
to your departed customers.
Wait, don't shoot!
He wanted me
to test you, that's all.
To figure out if you were worthy
of his interest or not.
He wanted to determine
whether you were truly fit
for Fujiko Mine.
"He," you say.
Huh.
Well, anyway,
you're on your way
to buy back the
lithograph, right?
I'll tag along.
Magnificent.
So this is how you preserved
the World Tree lithograph.
Only Fujiko Mine.
You're surprised, aren't you?
That's right: I'm the one who
set up this little exchange.
How pathetic.
Don't play dumb.
Somebody was checking out
my rear end from behind
a pillar during the heist.
Men like you always go for
the complicated women.
You're a career thief.
The only things you care
about are yourself and money.
My motives shouldn't matter
to you, as long as I pay up.
That's true.
Other people's agendas
do tend to bore me.
If I get my fee, there's
no problem, usually, anyway.
So?
Ogling costs extra, old man.
Oh, I see.
All comes down to money.
There's one other thing.
I'm curious about why
you felt the need
to put on this little act.
It wasn't even
a good performance, Lupin.
You've been hanging around
that fortune cookie jerk
twenty-four-seven,
watching his every move.
Did you really think
I didn't know?
I have my own reasons for being
interested in the lithograph.
Gotta say, I'm embarrassed
you figured me out so easily.
Well, if you want
your precious toy back,
you'd better pay the woman.
Yes, and don't forget my bonus.
"You sure as hell don't have
any special psychic powers."
That's what you said
earlier, isn't it?!
Easy, there.
What's got you all worked up?
You're wrong, you know.
I really could predict
my clients' future once.
I could tell them exactly
when they were going to die.
My power gradually faded,
however, until, eventually,
I couldn't read
the lithograph anymore.
I'm far past caring
whether you believe me
but what I'm telling
you now is true.
More than anything, I just
wanted to feel the old power
flowing through my veins again.
Then he came.
Listen closely, now, Fujiko
Mine, for my final job
is to reveal to you
your dying day.
Oh, really?
Not that that doesn't sound
absolutely fascinating,
but didn't you say you'd
lost your psychic powers?
And, of course, that's
assuming you ever actually
had any to begin with.
You don't know
how right you are.
As I said, this is my last job.
After I complete it,
I will be freed from
this false power forever.
Hands up, Lupin!
Drop your gun.
We have you surrounded.
Good.
The more characters you
introduce the more entertaining
the play or so I've
always thought.
Go get him!
More than one?
Shit!
Damn, what a boring job.
I'm only doing this
because I owe you one.
No dying on me now.
Least not until after
I've slept with you.
If they do kill me, you
can always ask Zenigata
for a description.
See you, Lupin.
Wha-! Hey wait!
Wait, this is--Yes!
I see now!
It's come back!
My powers returned!
I see!
I see everything!
It's as I said it was,
Fujiko Mine!
I'll tell you the day you
will depart this world.
At long last!
I shall reveal the future
to you and thus fulfill
my final contract with
Count Luis Yu Almeida!
Luís Yu Almeida.
No!
It can't be!
It's today?
My dying day?!
Wait, what are you doing?
Stop!
Oh, please, no!
Look at that.
You really did predict
someone's dying day.
These are the crime scene
photos taken from the area
where the fortune teller
died last night.
I guess this case was
too much for a rookie.
What do you know.
That crazy old bastard went and
died on the day he predicted.
How conscientious of him.
Still.
That doesn't change anything.
People don't die
because their day comes.
No.
We simply die and
that makes it our day.
In the end, that's not
something anybody can choose.
Isn't that right, Fujiko Mine?