Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
You might as well talk.
Who are you working for,
you sneaky bitch?
We know your media
credentials were faked.
You're wrong.
I don't know wha--.
Who do you work for?
You better start talking!
You're safe now.
Princesa.
Have you heard of
the Doomsday Clock?
In 1947, the clash
between communist
and capitalist camps
began to intensify.
That year marked the birth
of the Cold War Era
and of the Doomsday Clock
which symbolically marks
the time remaining
until global disaster.
When the clock's hands are moved
to the midnight position,
they say it's the beginning
of the end of the world.
Here we see the small Central
American nation Carib
in upheaval.
A revolutionary group,
The Bloody Vow,
has toppled the
nation's dictatorship.
The group's leader, Philadel
Kest, is making an appearance.
Kest is scheduled to address
the UN Headquarters soon,
where he will likely extol
the virtues of communism
and declare independence.
This is Fujiko Mine, reporting
to you from Nahava in Carib.
Politics?
I'm afraid I'm not interested.
I heard assassination
was your forte.
Then you were misinformed.
No, I don't consider
that a job.
Okay, then what is it?
It's just training.
That woman.
Ah, Fujiko Mine.
A Japanese journalist.
Recently, she's become
a favorite of Philadel's.
She's helping us out a bit
with this particular project.
"Journalist"?
So, she's still pretending.
I feel like there's
no place for me anywhere.
Do you know her?
What is it you want?
We want it done before his
speech to the United Nations.
Long time no see,
Mister Samurai.
This is our golden opportunity,
Mr. General Secretary.
A nuclear threat in Carib,
right in their own backyard.
They're a new state, still.
If we want to tie a bell
around the leader's neck,
these first hours are crucial.
A bell, eh?
I like it.
How?
I have bribed some of
the more volatile men
from the ousted government.
The situation is
grave, Mr. President.
We must act now before the man
has public opinion on his side.
The revolutionary?
Ordering the assassination
of a foreign leader.
I don't see how I can agree
to something like that.
Sir, we can't wait for them
to make the first move.
All right.
Deploy a unit to
Central America.
I'm bound for
the United Nations.
The time has come to tell the
whole world of our revolution.
We must learn who shares our
goals and then join with them!
Princesa!
Shall we?
It's like you're a rock star.
More than anything else,
this job is about timing.
And you're sure this
is what you want to do?
What are you talking about?
Uncertainty can kill.
I'll keep that in mind.
Thanks for the advice.
Miss Maria.
The leader of a revolution must
be willing to give everything
he can and expect no
material reward in return.
That's what true
revolution looks like.
The revolutionary
as vanguard.
You're an idealist, then.
Ideals are what
drive a revolution.
You were born in South America
not in Carib.
Why do you fight for
your adopted country?
Because I made a vow
to the people of Carib.
They accepted me,
believed in me.
I fight for honor.
Goodness!
Quite a statement.
You're from Japan, yes?
Your country also had warriors
who fought for revolution.
During the bakumatsu?
You're talking about samurai?
That's right.
Samurai.
That's what we are.
Sit down!
We've got questions
for you, too, journalist.
Today your revolution is
going to die along with you.
Let me guess.
You're members of
the former government?
This is pointless.
The revolution will
live on long after me.
I wouldn't be so cocky
if I was you.
We aren't the only ones
who don't want you
to address the UN.
Philadel Kest is our hostage.
We'll release him on
the following condition.
We want asylum until our
government is restored to power.
We're running low on fuel here.
Refuel in the air.
Or Philadel won't be the only
one getting a watery grave.
We've been promised asylum
in exchange for you.
Once we get off this plane,
our safety is guaranteed.
You think so?
These things tend to go wrong.
How's the operation?
I've dispatched
a unit to the scene.
We don't have intel on the
number of hijackers just yet.
We acted recklessly.
I don't see how
this can end well.
I apologize.
Once again, I have dragged you
into my country's struggle.
I understand.
It's all right.
So, where do you think
they're taking us?
Who knows?
They're likely backed
by a Communist state.
That right?
We don't have to
explain ourselves to you.
Now, tell me.
What are the coordinates
of the oil field?
I see, so that's it.
I'd heard the rumors
that the old regime had
a secret oil field
on Cariban land.
They aren't rumors!
It's true!
No it isn't.
It's nothing more than a story
they made up to give themselves
an edge in the negotiations.
You're the one
making things up.
There is no such
treasure hidden on our land.
You know what they want?
To build their missile bases.
Lie all you want but
you're coming with us.
Refueling.
Preparing to attack.
Wait, what's that?!
It's them.
We've got visual
on the decal.
That's a Red Star plane.
So it is.
We've got company.
Looks like there are more dogs
in this fight than you expected.
Detecting an unknown craft
in our airspace, sir.
This is no time to negotiate.
We need to end this!
You know what the consequences
of fighting are.
A clash between us will mean the
beginning of World War III.
If they so much as look like
they're going on the offensive,
attack them!
Hey, Mister, that's our--
That's really him!
Okay, ready, catch!
Gracias!
Looks like fun.
Yes but it's also serious.
For them, baseball
isn't just a game.
Carib has baseball and music.
Those are the only things
that give a kid a shot
at a better life.
The world isn't following
your country's revolution
because of its ideals.
You have to know that.
It's the oil field
they care about.
I know but this
is still my fight.
We do what we must,
even if it isn't pretty.
You know that.
And, of course, let's not
forget the country that's
supporting you only because
they like the idea of throwing
a nuclear threat in
their enemy's face.
That kind of deterrent
is necessary.
For now, it helps us to
remain under their umbrella
but in time, our revolution
will sweep across the world
like a great tide.
South America, Easten Europe,
then Asia, and before long,
the entire globe.
I wonder, are you after
revolution or chaos?
I just want to dance
to my own beat.
That's all.
I'm so tired of being a puppet
on a bigger country's strings.
Philadel?
Dance with me, Princesa.
You've got more than
enough for your story,
but you're still with us.
Is it for the coordinates?
The oil field?
What do you want?
Very well.
Since you asked, I'll tell you.
We're in attack formation.
What the hell are they doing?
Damn it!
This wasn't our deal!
They're starting
a shootout right here?!
Looks like it.
Seems like you guys
have been set up.
You know, Princesa,
that isn't very ladylike.
Now, then.
You asked what I want.
I'm in place.
Ready to fire, on your order.
Let me knock those capitalist
dogs clear out of the sky.
A battle of wills.
Who fires first?
Them or us?
Sir, we need to make
a preemptive strike.
The only way we're going
to survive this is if
we take the enemy out first.
Whoever strikes goes down
in history as the one
who started the
third World War.
How can we?
History won't mean much
if the human race
is obliterated, Mr. President.
Hey, pilot!
Try making contact
with that fighter jet.
Okay, but which one?
I don't care.
Just stop them
from attacking us!
Right, this is our chance.
What you said before, about
the oil field not being real.
Were you lying?
In my UN speech,
I'll say it doesn't exist.
That will become reality, and we
won't be dragged into more war.
How naïve.
Have you forgotten that whole
thing about nuclear missiles
being stationed in Carib?
You've already been dragged in.
That's true but
this staring contest
between superpowers
will end eventually.
And, in time, the scars of war
burned into our land will fade,
as well.
When that happens
what we'll need is--
The oil field's--
Shh!
That's for you.
Your exclusive.
But why me?
You know, I love to dance
and I fell in love
with the rhythm of Carib.
Their lovely beaches, delicious
rum, and beautiful women.
What more can a man ask for?
I don't understand.
It's okay.
Someone should know
Carib's secret.
I don't know who it is
you're working for,
but better you than
the nuclear powers.
Even if you're
not a journalist.
How long have you--?
Since the day we met.
You could have been
killed saving me.
I couldn't help myself.
You were too beautiful.
Philadel.
We don't want to become
the trigger for the next war
that tears the world apart.
Whatever we do, they still
might pull the trigger.
Affirmative!
The first move is ours.
Missiles launched!
I just heard word,
we're under fire!
They've fired?
Missiles launched!
We've struck first.
They fired?!
It's the end of the world!
Hold on.
Is that a samurai?!
A samurai took out
our missiles.
Uh, Command.
I think I just saw a samurai.
What? Have we been saved?
But why?
And by whom?
He's right on time.
Though this wasn't exactly
the original plan.
What the hell is that?
A samurai friend of mine.
I asked him to come get us.
Shall we?
Sir, the incoming missiles
have been neutralized!
What are you tell me?
I'm saying, that for the moment,
we've avoided World War III.
Our missiles were
destroyed before they hit!
No.
Not our missiles.
You acted alone.
What?
No, sir, please--
I won't be exiled for this!
Come on.
Where are you planning to go?
You're not getting away!
By all means,
go ahead and shoot.
Huh?
What're you talking about?
You would become a pawn for
people who barely even know
the name of your country,
let alone your name?
That's real smart.
Silence!
What we do today will
go down in history!
We're changing the world,
right here and now!
So, you think
you're rock stars, huh?
Yeah, welcome to
the real world.
This isn't some game.
I just have to kill
Philadel Kest.
The whole world will
remember my name!
In that case, why not
just kill the Beatles?
Shut up!
Please, no rock.
I like something with
a little more rhythm to it.
Sorry, you'll have
to wait for the rum.
That's our ride, comrade.
Shall we?
A samurai.
Moments ago we witnessed
the arrival of Philadel Kest,
the man who led the
overthrow of the dictator
in the small Central
American nation of Carib.
Comrade Philadel,
everyone is waiting for you.
Just listen to them
cheering, sir!
Indeed.
Like I'm a rock star.
Yes.
This will be an historic day.
But please, no rock.
In his address to the UN,
Comrade Philadel shockingly
revealed that claims that the
previous regime was concealing
the location of an oil field
were entirely fictitious.
Why didn't you carry out
the assassination?
Did you get cold feet?
Hey, would you rub oil
on my back?
Are you planning
to go straight?
You didn't complete the job
but you did carry out justice.
In that sense, I suppose
it would be a fitting way
to end your career.
I have no intention
of going straight.
What?
Then why didn't you kill him?
My true goal was always
the oil field's location.
So that's what you
really wanted all along?
What I really wanted, well.
Never mind.
I checked out the coordinates.
So where is the oil field?
Right here.
It's like the Comrade
said: an oil field is not
what the country most needs.
This is.
I see.
What about you?
You said before that there
is nowhere you belong.
Has that changed now?
Do you love him?
Rock stars really aren't
my kind of thing.
Who is?
Maria!
I'm not Maria.
The name is Fujiko Mine,
Mister Samurai.
See you around.
Bye, Fujiko.