Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
Yes, right there!
Man, she's going to town!
Where do you think "there" is?
Yeah, right. Like I'd know.
Don't you have work to do?
Oh, Lieutenant Oscar!
Do your job properly,
or I'll kill you.
Understood?
Yes, Lieutenant. Got it. Sorry.
When did this place
become a pig farm?
Ooh, so good!
Squealing like a pig.
Your terms?
Yeah.
I'm not gonna release you unless
you agree to my terms first.
You want more?
You've had plenty
of fun already.
That was just a small perk.
Thieves are cheap rides.
It's not enough.
Now, if you could croon
like that Aiyan Meier,
I might consider it.
Aiyan?
That famous masked
opera singer?
Aiyan is a soprano
drammatico d'agilita.
Her voice has all the
rich fullness of a goddess.
But a tragic accident
left most of her face
burned beyond recognition.
I heard some obsessed fan
went crazy and attacked her.
After it happened, she began
wearing a mask onstage
for all of her performances.
Not just any mask.
This one's covered in gems.
It's worth more than the federal
budget of a small country.
Oooh!
Now there's a delicious rumor.
Well, it gets even juicer.
Supposedly, the mask was given
to her as a courtship present
from a ghost haunting
the Palais Gerniar.
Let's get to business.
All right.
I'll lay out the terms
of our deal for you.
First off, take a look at this.
Is this wise?
I mean, leaving a
notorious thief in charge
of guarding Aiyan's mask.
I don't see how we can
trust that woman.
Every doll out there
is a double-crosser.
Of course we can't trust her.
But the best way to catch
a thief is with a thief.
Those two will
trip over each other,
and Lupin will fall
into our hands.
The architecture of the
Palais Gerniar is as complex
as it is ancient.
I doubt if anyone who works
here, save for my humble self,
of course, knows
all of its secrets.
There are simply too many.
Up here on the roof
is where we keep our bees.
They produce honey, which
we sell to famous suppliers.
These are the aqueducts.
They say water once flowed
through them to points
all over the city, but as you
can see, they're dry now.
I'm told that while
the water still ran,
it was called the
River of Oblivion.
That's quite a name.
In reference to the river from
Greek mythology. It washes away
your past, allowing you
to forget everything.
And now we're backstage.
"Don't be distracted
by shadows?"
The ghost of Palais Gerniar.
Legend has it, if you pay him
attention, he'll have power--
It's far more than a legend.
It's quite true.
The Palais itself has fallen
in love with the agilitá Aiyan.
Da Renzo!
This "Lupin the Third"
may try to steal the mask.
But if so, it will be the
last thing he ever does.
O Palais Gerniar,
please forgive them their greed.
That's one creepy man.
That's Da Renzo, our carpenter.
People who work backstage in the
theatre are a superstitious lot.
And now, allow me
to present Aiyan.
Hello!
So Tosca is on
the program tonight?
Yes.
The love story of a painter
and an opera singer.
It's a truly tragic tale.
Forgive me, Lady Tosca.
Would it not be best
for you to leave this place
and return home now?
I must stay.
If I do not see him,
my voice and heart will wither,
and I will never sing
songs of love again!
You!
I know you have
hidden the traitor.
Reveal him to me now!
I know no traitor.
Whatever do you mean, sir?
Do not play the innocent.
I know Angelotti
is here somewhere!
What just happened?
Explain yourself.
Intruding upon me like this!
How can you expect me
to practice my singing?
Ah, well, you see, my lady.
I--
Well?
Lu--
Hey there, Fujiko.
I've missed you.
Running into you like this.
It just feels so good.
I can guess why you're here.
You're after the mask,
aren't you?
Hey!
Was that Lupin?
Lights!
Oscar! Get him!
I don't believe it.
The ghost of the Opera?
Tosca?! But I'm Tosca!
Aiyan? What are you--?
The devil himself
seeks to tear me apart
from my darling Caravaggio!
I beg you, have mercy!
Even the devil himself
would possess her heart!
Such is the power
of this prima donna!
[singing Puccini's
"Vissi d'arte, vissi d'amore"]
Lupin?
Is that how it goes?
They may have
adlibbed a little.
Hey!
Whoa!
Aiyan!
Are you all right?
What's going on here?
This is the ghost's work.
He sent a message
written in blood because
we have angered him tonight.
It's all over now, Aiyan.
How are you feeling?
I should be well enough
to stand before the next song.
Have someone fill in for a bit.
But there's no one
who can replace you!
Sure there is.
Right here.
Huh?
You got pretty much
the same build.
Put on the fake mask
and no one will have a clue.
Honestly!
What'd I say?
We're counting on you.
Knock 'em dead.
A cheap ride, was it?
Then why do you keep
groping me like a prize pony?
Cool it, doll.
It's just a pat.
Now, live up to your part of
the bargain and reel Lupin in.
Are you sure you're not
overestimating this woman?
I'm sure.
Take it from me.
She's a good enough actress to
fake a pretty convincing orgasm.
Oh, Inspector!
You flatter me.
Now, stay in costume--
Hey guys.
I have the headpiece
for Miss Aiyan's next
costume change here.
You just stay where you are.
The stage manager
will come fetch you.
Oh! My dearest love!
Why have you not
come for me today?
Without you,
my life is nothing!
I am nothing!
Heh.
She isn't half bad.
What's the timing for
her switch with Aiyan?
It's right before
the end of the act, sir.
In about twenty minutes,
I believe.
...Would that I could abandon
this foolish jealousy...
The stage elevator will
lower her down to the cellar,
where the real Aiyan
will be waiting.
A dramatic trap door
switch beneath the stage.
The thieves won't be able to
resist that kinda opportunity
to snatch the mask.
Fujiko may or may
not trip him up
down there but when
she's done with him,
Lupin won't be walking
straight, that's for sure.
Yes, sir.
We have officers
in place, as well.
Already?
Something's up.
It's not time to change yet.
Let's get down there.
Hey!
That hurt!
Take it easy.
It's the ghost!
Let me out!
Right now!
What the--?
[Aiyan singing Puccini's
"Vissi d'arte, vissi d'amore"]
Aiyan!
Hold up.
This isn't how we planned it.
What's this?
"Go to the fifth spike
mark from the right"?
I get it now.
It was all a set up.
Somebody used the prop
letter to get Aiyan to move
to the right spot on the stage.
Her life was never in danger.
It was only meant to look
like someone wanted her dead.
Mission accomplished.
So, that means the ghost
of the Opera is--
Lupin the Third.
I will stop you.
No matter what it takes, I won't
let you touch Aiyan's mask.
I am coming to you, my beloved.
We shall be
together again soon!
Aiyan is mine!
Aiyan!
What's going on?!
Sorry, pal,
you can't have her.
I know that voice.
It's Lupin!
Are those--?
They're the bees
we keep up on the roof!
Hey!
Where do you little rascals
think you're going?!
No!
Ow! They're stinging me!
--It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
--No, stop!
You mustn't take off the mask!
I planted a device
in the headpiece.
It makes this sound
that bees just can't resist!
Pretty nifty, huh?
Wait a minute,
that's not Aiyan!
No, that's Nora!
She was working here
as a prop mistress
up until five years ago.
I'm sorry, Da Renzo.
I didn't mean to!
Alrighty, then,
just one thing left to do.
Get my hands on that mask!
Huh?
Damn you!
You're not getting away!
Zenigata!
You go after the guy
in the cape.
Right!
What a pain.
Lock-picking is so beneath me.
It's tedious grunt work.
Hey!
Do your part, pig lady.
Excuse me?!
"Pig lady"?!
Hurry up, pig!
Run like your bacon
depends on it!
Think you can lay off
the pig comparisons?
Fine.
"Spittoon," then.
"Spittoon"?!
Yeah, that's right.
You're nothing but
a receptacle for male lust.
That's all you're good for,
you worthless piece of trash.
Split up.
That way, Spittoon!
I can't believe him!
Great!
Where am I?
At last, we meet again.
It's been too long.
You dirty rat.
You're persistent, Zenigata,
I'll give you that.
But what about the mask?
Don't you want it?
The mask?
I don't give a damn about that.
I'm here to settle the score.
Once and for all!
My good tie!
O Zenigata!
Wherefore art thou, Zenigata?
Wherefore am I Zenigata?
'Tis 'cause the very blood
in my veins cries out.
To stamp out the
entire line of Lupin.
I'm told that while
the water still ran,
it was called the
River of Oblivion.
That's quite a name.
In reference to the river
from Greek mythology.
It washes away your
past, allowing you
to forget everything.
I carry the Zenigata family
name, and you the name
of a thief!
Blood will always tell!
It's blood you want, eh?
It's done!
Wh- I can't see!
A lovely red sauce mixed with
a touch of chili powder.
Here, I'll give you
some extra, on the house.
It's in my eyes!
They're burning!
I got turned around.
How did I end up here?
Inspector!
Your blood-soaked form!
So horrible,
and yet so beautiful!
No.
None of that now.
Hang in there, sir!
Don't let gooooo!
Da Renzo.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to do this.
But now that you know the secret
of the Opera ghost, I must!
Th--there's another
ghost in the Opera?
Da Renzo wait!
Aiyan!
My love!
Oh, Da Renzo, we'll be okay.
Yes, Aiyan.
This isn't the kind of room you
expect to find in the catacombs.
That couch is made out
of one of the stone tombs.
It's nice, don't you think?
Yes, lovely.
It's very avant-garde.
So, you two have been living
down here all this time?
Yes.
You see, it felt like the entire
world was opposed to our love.
If it meant I could be
with him, I was willing
to give up everything; my name,
my career, even my face.
When I realized that the prop
mistress, Nora, had real talent
as a singer, I began training
her to take my place as Aiyan.
And then, One day, it was time.
Hold on, you mean you
did that to your face?
Yes.
It burned a little bit.
Even so, it was worth it
to be with the love of my life.
My dear.
What a perfect plan.
In one stroke, we made Nora's
dreams come true and made sure
no one would ever
bother us again.
What could anyone suspect?
Aiyan was still on stage.
You chose to live
for love, instead of art.
I understand that.
What I don't understand is how
you could leave that gorgeous
opera house to live in a
disgusting old crypt like this.
But it's not a crypt.
This is the most
stimulating stage there is.
The stage of love!
This mask is no use to us now.
We could sell it and
buy a house somewhere.
This thing?
I would rather use it
to heat up the soup.
No!
Well, it'll be a lot less
valuable burned to a crisp.
Lupin!
Oh, another guest!
How lovely!
Well then?
What do you say?
Would you two like
to join us for dinner?
We would love to.