Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
Who's there?
Where's the excitement
in swiping something like that?
Such a gaudy piece.
It's plenty exciting, Lupin.
Nothing looks gaudy if you
know the right way to wear it.
Besides, every treasure
is further proof of how
exceptional I am.
Well, I guess there's
no arguing with that.
So, why are you here?
I got you a little something.
This is a straightforward
approach for a man like you.
I thought you would
enjoy a gem rose bouquet.
They are pretty enough.
Although, red does tend
to be a overdone choice.
Oh yeah?
Then please, allow me.
Ah, alexandrite,
it's color is dictated
by the light that hits it.
Appears blue when seen
by sunlight and turns red
in fire light. Pretty princely
gift, don't you think?
This pays for
the peep show you got.
But you'd need the
biggest alexandrite stone
there is to have
a shot with me.
The biggest one?
The one they've got in
the Smithsonian, you mean?
Drive a hard bargain.
You keep raising
the bar like that,
and you just might
trip over it.
Thanks for the friendly warning.
So, you really
want me that badly?
The threats I make
are never empty.
When I say I'm gonna
steal something, I mean it.
Then I have a
proposal for you.
You've heard all about
the new pyramid
they discovered
in Egypt, I take it?
Yeah, the one that was
hidden under the sand?
That's the official line but
unofficially, illegal diggers
have known of its
existence for a long time.
Criminals have always been in
the know before anybody else.
It's been like that
for centuries.
Have you heard about a certain
treasure said to be inside:
the red-feathered
Laughing Peacock?
I've heard rumors
about it, but nothing more.
According to legend,
whoever gets their hands
on that peacock will
become rich beyond belief.
"On one side of the scale
is the Feather of Ma'at,
the goddess of truth. The
deceased places his own heart
on the other side of
the scale to weigh it."
"If his sins in life were heavy,
the scales will tip. This is
a sign that the deceased will
never be reborn into the world."
"The ritual is known as
the Judgment of the Dead."
You know better than that.
There's notelling what
that scary man will do
if you get too close.
Sorry.
Guess it doesn't
matter where I go.
There's no hiding my past.
It's written on my face.
It's not like I came here
thinking I would be reborn
or something like that.
But can't a guy catch a break?
Hey, mister.
Mister.
Wanna know what
your sins weigh?
It won't cost too much.
Against a feather,
I'm guessing?
Like a real-world version of
the Judgment of the Dead.
I don't have to tell
the story, then.
Good.
You can see they're
the same weight.
Now all you have to do
is pick up the heart.
Think of your past sins and
then put it back on the scale.
And what?
It magically changes weight?
'Cause that would be
so difficult to rig.
Are you afraid?
You must've done
some pretty rotten stuff.
What?
I can tell just by your face.
Oh, give me a break.
Not so fast.
This your partner? Huh?
You little!
Even the monkey was in on it.
Least there's one thing
they didn't get.
This is little better than
a hunk of scrap metal.
Besides, don't you
need it to make a living?
No way you can go straight.
That's obvious.
Leave me alone.
You know what?
If it's money you need,
I might be able to help.
I've got a job that would be
right up your alley.
You want me to steal
the--what was it?
The Laughing Peacock?
There are a great many people
eager to get their hands on it.
That peacock has become
the stuff of legend among
the inhabitants of
this city's underworld.
Story goes that when
its feathers shine crimson,
it will bestow great riches.
That sounds pretty formulaic.
What do you expect?
That's how legends tend to be.
There are some
variations to the story.
One version says that
when the peacock's feathers
are blue, death is near.
An old well leads inside.
Few who have entered have
ever come back out alive.
They say there's a curse
around every corner.
I guess that guy was after
the Laughing Peacock, too.
Blasphemous trespasser.
Leave now while you
still have your life.
Let's see.
An oil spray set alight.
An oil drawing of
a pharaoh on the wall.
And a well-placed
loud speaker.
Neat trick.
I'm definitely not
the only one in here.
There's no curse.
It's just the tomb raiders.
Each man out to
protect his own loot.
Leave now!
Or face the consequences.
Are you deaf? I said, leave!
Nice.
This is the thanks I get for
giving you such a kind warning?
You're gonna pay dearly for
being a grave robber, you know.
What, and you're not?
I'll be fine.
I'm just a generic robber.
A pro among pros; I specialize
in hard to get items.
Pretty petty tactics
for someone so professional.
I thought you might
like some entertainment.
This next question's important.
What are you here to steal?
I don't know.
What if I said a peacock?
Bad answer.
Back where we started.
Three.
And two.
One!
Zero
I take it this isn't
one of your traps?
Of course not.
My work's a lot
classier than this.
Now, drop the gun.
I've never known a Magnum
to fire a seventh round.
Or a Walther to fire a tenth.
Uh oh--
Damn.
That's some lousy art.
It's a dead-end.
This again.
Looks like something goes here.
Like a hand with that?
So you did make it out alive.
You really should return
the things you borrow.
Otherwise, people will
think you're a thief.
Yeah?
And what do they think
about somebody who
messes with another man's ammo?
Here's a free tip.
I found a neat trick
to getting past traps safely.
All you have to do is let a
hotshot gunslinger lead the way,
and then you're
as good as gold.
My explosive shells saved
your sorry hide, didn't they?
Those babies are top-notch.
Explode only on impact.
You could've at least
reloaded all six.
Sorry about that, but five
shells was all I had on me.
None of your fancy little
tricks are gonna help you
open this lid, are they?
Like I thought.
You were waiting for me
'cause you don't have a clue
how to open it.
See that?
I think that scale
is the trick.
The weight of
a person's sins, eh?
How intriguing.
So it'll open if
the scale balances?
Probably.
But that'll never happen.
The scale will
tip no matter what.
Not even good people
are sinless and us---
Well, you and I are
sinners down to the core.
Obviously.
So what is there
to be afraid of?
Why would you need some deity
to tell you how heavy your sins
are when you already know
what you've done in this life.
Besides, even if you're
rewarded with rebirth there's
no guarantee your new life
is gonna be a good one.
Doesn't matter.
My future is dark, either way.
Let's just try it out for
the sake of entertainment.
It's all make-believe, so why
not have a little fun with it?
There isn't any harm in that.
No way!
Why, hello there!
And up we go.
Damn it.
It's too steep!
Hurry!
Put the mummy on the platform!
Those are scorpions!
Yeah, poisonous ones!
Not good!
It's rigged to make us
fall no matter what.
A whirlpool?
It's been fun, but I think I'd
like to get off the ride now!
Oh, dear.
You two don't look so good.
What are you doing here?
You're that woman!
Oh, hey.
Mister Mini-Magnum.
I remember you.
Your lower half, anyway.
Hold on!
Don't tell me
you slept with this guy?!
There's no need to be jealous.
There's a reason
I called him Mini-Magnum,
if you catch my drift.
Isn't that right, Tiny?
Don't be stupid!
There's nothing
'tiny' about me.
This whole time you were just
using me to get past the traps.
Of course not.
It would be downright
inconsiderate to do that
to somebody who was just
trying to get me a present.
Instead, I took an alternate
route listed in an old
grave robber's log.
Traps along this way are
mostly out of commission.
You love your secrets,
don't you?
Take a woman's secrets,
and what does she have left?
Besides, how do you ever
hope to win the heart
of a princess without
taking a few little risks?
I made it this far, but I
did need help getting past
this last obstacle. It's a
tricky one. Works like a juicer.
Fall into that chamber
and you'll be pulverized.
Say what?
The blood of the
victim is infused
into the picture
of the peacock.
The bird then spreads its red
feathers and flaps its wings.
Incidentally, the "juicer" will
stop after one of you falls.
So, uh, if you want to
live, I suggest you give
Mini-Magnum the old heave ho.
Bye now.
Hey, Tiny!
What happened
between you and her?
Sounds like more
than's happened to you.
That mouth is gonna
get you in trouble.
She's the reason you're here?
You came to this
hellhole for her?
And that oughta tell you
just how much she's worth.
More than any other
treasure that I've ever seen.
Seems to me that all she does
is go around spreading trouble.
If there's no trouble,
it's not worth stealing.
That's the code of
the Lupin family.
Lupin?
Then I guess that would make you
the infamous Lupin the Third.
Well, it's a good thing
you told me, isn't it?
Can't make you a gravestone
if I don't know who you are.
Thanks for the thought
but I've still got
a lot more life to live.
Let me know what you want
on your tombstone, though.
Thing is, I'm not in such
a hurry to die anymore.
And I suppose
I owe that to you.
Huh?
Well, that's that.
I wonder whose blood
is going to dye those
pretty feathers
of yours crimson?
Huh?
Hey, what's going on?
So, scorpion blood
is blue, huh?
Learn something new every day.
Lupin!
But how?!
Then this blood came from---
Scorpions that were
nesting inside the mummy.
So very sorry
to disappoint you.
What the--?
What's happening now?
Oh, crap.
A blue-feathered peacock
means that death is near.
Oh, please.
That's ridiculous!
There it is!
The Laughing Peacock!
It's sculpted entirely
out of alexandrite.
It's huge.
Makes the Smithsonian's
sixty carat stone
look like a worthless pebble.
This is the actual
Laughing Peacock.
So much for blue feathers
and certain death!
We're looking at
red feathers and big riches!
Ew!
No you don't!
That's my peacock!
Hey!
We're about to be
burned to a crisp here.
Hmm.
It should have a secret exit.
Traps like this one pretty
much always do, don't they?
That way the builders
don't have to worry
about whoever commissioned
trying to seal them inside.
And sure enough.
There it is.
It's just an air vent!
We can't get out through there.
Don't get hysterical.
This wall opens up.
See, there's a keyhole.
Huh?
It's shaped like--
No!
Don't even think about it!
Do you know how much work
it took me to get this?!
Huh?
Alexandrite turns blue
when it's hit by sunlight.
Just give it up.
It's only a red-feathered,
fortune-bestowing peacock
while it's inside the pyramid.
I guess you could choose to be
locked up in here with it.
Then you could be
a legendary peacock, too.
I'll give you another chance
if you'd like.
You do want me, don't you?
How about the
Smithsonian's stone?
Sixty carats
is still pretty big.
No.
The bar's just
been raised even higher.
I hope you don't
disappoint me again.
Maybe letting her stay
in there and be a peacock
would've been
the better option.
For her and for you.
No matter where
that woman goes,
she's always
a beautiful peacock.
If that's the
kinda thing you're into.
Well, shall we go ahead
and settle this?
You know?
I think I can wait.
I won't forget, Mini-Magnum.
It's Jigen.
Daisuke Jigen.
That's a lot less memorable
than the other name.
A wild one.
Fujiko.
Doesn't she know that when they
want to, even peacocks can fly?