Cease what you are
doing and gaze at me.
Stop everything, save for
the thrumming of your heart.
Theft. It is an
especially sweet vice,
more elegant than vandalism
and more complex
than simple robbery.
A beautiful blend of secrets
and crime and mischief and fear.
Like dear Heathcliff,
I am defined by my
all-consuming passion.
Stealing is my greatest
carnal pleasure,
a pleasure for which
I will risk my life,
a sexy prison from
which there is no escape.
Why am I this way?
Who can know?
Who is the slave and
who's the master?
Do divine eyes fall
upon me any longer,
or have the given up?
The rush of a theft
allows me to forget all,
and yet to distantly
remember all, as well.
Run and speak not.
Hide and run not.
When you've found
me, punish me.
When you've punished
me, kill me. Save me.
Little boy, there is nothing
left to steal from you.
You have long been an
empty shell. Just as I have.
And so, if you would gaze at
me, cease what you are doing.
Stop everything save for the
thrumming of your heart.
They say everyone
gets lucky once in a while.
Every gambler knows
the touch of fortune's smile.
Perhaps today
will be your lucky day.
But who can know?
They also say
Fortune's a fickle lady.
Then why don't we
put it to the test?
I'm sure you must be growing
bored with such low stakes.
I appreciate it.
Things were getting a bit dull.
Excellent.
In that case, I wager
the whole casino.
Quite a wager.
Well, it's entirely
mine to bet.
I own the place, you see.
Indeed?
Unfortunately, I don't have
anything of equal value
to put up.
You do, though.
Bet your lovely self.
I'd say your beauty is equal
the worth of my casino.
Bet myself?
That's dangerous.
And intriguing.
Count me in.
You have an incredible body.
I can see why all men--and some
women, even-- are so easily
wrapped around
your little finger.
Fujiko Mine.
Ah, so you know who I am, then.
I had you looked
into, naturally.
Seductress, thief, spy.
You wear many hats
and yet your true identity
is shrouded in mystery.
And now your future
is in my hands.
I could kill you or let you live
or give you a living death.
You are mine.
However, I am not
a woman without mercy.
Do two things for me,
and I shall set you free.
Is that so?
Yes.
First I would like you to steal
a gun from a certain man.
And second, I want you to
see this through to the end.
Penne, get the car.
This town is Borgata territory.
Has been for a long time.
But the old boss got
whacked a while ago,
and his wife Ciccolina
took over the business.
It's been dicey.
The Chinese Mob's been
gaining a lotta power.
And it doesn't help any that
the guy who iced the boss
went over to the other side.
You mean Daisuke Jigen?
Yes.
He has a three-fifty-seven
Magnum that I want you to steal.
What's he like?
A quick draw for one thing.
And the best
bodyguard out there.
Likely one of the most dangerous
men you will ever come across.
And you want me to steal
a gun from somebody like that?
Don't worry,
you have an advantage.
He has one weakness.
Women frighten him.
That Magnum's his baby.
He values it at least
as much as his own life.
If we take it, he's sure
to come here and get it back.
And then, I'll kill the man
who murdered my husband
and defected to the enemy.
With my own hands.
I forgot to tell you my name.
Ciccolina.
It's nice to meet you.
All right, then, where
exactly are you taking me?
We're going to
the audition hall.
"Audition"?
Yep.
Lin Chin-Chin is in
the market for a mistress.
Hey!
Bodyguard guy!
This is my new woman,
Fujiko Mine.
I want you to take
good care of her.
Good afternoon.
It's nice to meet you.
Baby-sitting little girls isn't
part of my job description.
Sorry.
That's where you're wrong.
Your job is to
protect what's mine,
and I expect you to do that.
Come in!
I was afraid you wouldn't come.
But I'm so glad you did.
Where's the boss?
He went out.
It could be a while
before he gets back.
Don't go!
Come on.
Let's have some fun, I knew
I wanted you from the moment
I laid eyes on you.
Thanks for the offer,
but I think I'm gonna pass.
Oh?
Loyal to the boss?
Or are you just spineless?
Neither.
I just hate women.
Oh, no!
That can't be true!
Surely you don't hate all of us.
What, do you want me
to beg or something?
Huh?
The boss has got more than
his fair share of enemies.
Including some who would play
"mistress" to get close to him.
And some who would
be happy to kill me.
Some tea?
Oh, fine.
You go through life suspecting
everybody who gets close to you.
Doesn't that get
a little lonely?
Oh, I see, you've been
burned before, haven't you?
A bodyguard who's not suspicious
isn't doing the job right.
Very well then.
I can see how
trust is a liability.
At least in your line of work.
Still, your suspicions
of me are silly.
I carry a knife
for protection, that's all.
Though right now, I'm unarmed.
Hold on.
Guarding me is
part of your job, isn't it?
How can you do that
if you're not with me?
I knew I could appeal
to your sense of duty.
Yeah, well, I'm an
old fashioned man.
Oh really?
So then what was it that led
you to kill your former boss
and take a job with
the rival family?
Was it money?
Or perhaps was it a woman?
My past is none of
your business, lady.
Daisuke Jigen.
I heard the rumors about you.
Everyone says you're
a damn good shot.
Why don't you give us
a little demonstration?
William Tell, huh?
Talk about a stunt
that's overdone.
I think I'm going
to like this one.
Hey!
Wake up!
Call a doctor.
Yessir!
Leave me alone!
There's nobody left
in my life I can trust.
I can't live like this anymore.
So please, just go.
Leave me.
Why didn't you
just let me die?
It's not like you've
been a stranger to death.
Killing people
is part of your job.
Don't try to tell me
you're sentimental.
Stop talking.
There are plenty of
hard-hearted, callous people
in this world, but no one is
completely without sentiment.
There are also plenty of people
who are disgusted with life.
But no one is
completely without hope.
You included.
You don't really wanna die.
That's why I saved your life.
So what do you
think I should do?
What are you talking about?
My wife.
This isn't the first time
she's tried to kill herself.
She finds living too difficult,
so she's constantly flirting
with death.
Frankly, she's more than
I can handle sometimes.
Thing is, I love her anyway.
This kinda thing isn't my area.
I'm just a hired gun,
that's all.
You'll see what I mean.
Just keep a close eye
on her for me, will ya?
You want my bodyguard
for a day?
Yes.
You don't mind
if I borrow him.
A girl likes to go out
every once in a while.
Go ahead.
Do whatever you want.
Come dance with me.
Dancing isn't part
of my job description.
Oh, how disappointing.
You aren't man enough
to play escort for one evening?
Don't leave my side.
You're a walking
contradiction, you know.
Say what?
Cruel, but also kind.
Confident, but also hesitant.
I find it fascinating.
What's going on?
What does your body
tell you is happening?
What was that?
Oh, it's just a type
of Taoist energy joining.
And what's that?
An ancient sexual art that
the Chinese are known for.
How is it?
You should be starting
to feel pretty good.
Damn.
There just let your body relax.
Would it be so bad to do
what you really want to?
She requested
I deliver a message.
"Tell him that I'll be
waiting for him where
we first made love."
That woman is as much
trouble as she looks.
This is it.
You are good.
Will it work?
Will he really come?
He'll come.
I'm sure of it.
And when he does,
you'll kill him?
Don't forget the second part
of the bargain we made.
I want you to see this
through to the end.
Oh, no.
Ciccolina, where are you?
Can you hear me, woman?
You in here? Huh?!
Hey.
If you go out there now,
then we're both as good as dead.
This is the only thing
that makes the pain go away.
Having someone in my arms.
It helps me to forget.
Please.
What are you playing at, anyway?
And where have you
been all day long?
Were you with
that damn bodyguard?
And if I was, what then?
You going to shoot me?
That's fine.
If you love me, then kill me.
Please, I won't stop you.
I won't kill you.
But he's going to die!
No, don't!
Get down!
--Stop this!
--Let go!
Cicciolina.
Alright, you need
to snap out of it!
Listen to me.
I was the one who shot him.
You had nothing to do
with it, understand?
Was that a shot?!
Over here!
There he is!
--Traitor!
--He's getting away--
Don't let him go!
So you actually did come.
Don't mind me.
I'm just seeing things
through to the end.
What you stole from me
was more than just some gun.
It was my past.
It was my life.
Long time no see.
Enough.
Let's skip past the small talk.
I hear you're the one
that's running the show now.
You hear right.
I played you like
a well-tuned instrument.
And considering how much I know,
it would be in your interest
to shut me up.
You think you're so tough?!
You ain't nothing but a joke.
I'm the one she
was sleeping with.
Aw, does that bother you?
Wait, you didn't actually
think she loved you?
I should thank you.
I've finally met a woman
who I won't mind killing.
Time to settle old scores.
Watch it!
I've got one bullet left
and it's got your name on it.
I'm not so sure.
Do you really think
you can shoot me?
Like hell you can.
Good bye at last, Jigen.
It's not loaded.
It was true.
I really did plan to use
you at first but then,
Somewhere along the line,
you became the only thing
tying me to the world.
My only hope.
I've felt like an empty shell
ever since I lost you.
I didn't know what to do.
I thought about killing you.
I thought about killing myself.
But then I decided,
If I was going to die,
I wanted you to be
the one to kill me.
I don't understand.
I really just don't understand.
I definitely saw this
through to the end.
It was your own end you were
talking about, wasn't it?
In some way.
She reminded me of myself.
I guess that's why I did it,
played along with
her little thief act.
Oh, shut up.
The two of you
are nothing alike.
Guess the thing that ultimately
killed her was her past.
That won't be me.
I'll escape any past
that tries to hunt me down.
So maybe the best assassin out
there is a person's own past.
I'm getting out of
the killing business.
In this line of work, a moment
of hesitation means death.
Getting emotionally
involved is suicide.
I can't hack it anymore.
So, what are you going to do?
Good question.
The life of a thief
might not be so bad.
Are you propositioning me?
Don't you worry.
I would never team up
with you for anything.
I don't know.
"Never" is a very long time.