[BEAR] There are
two kinds of worlds...
Those that die
out on their own...
and those that are destroyed.
[MORTE] Wow, you're
really trying to look
cool up there, aren'tcha?
You know you're
just a bear, right?
[BEAR] I'm a hero and I won't
dignify that with an answer.
So have either of you
figured out a plan yet?
We've just been drifting here
ever since our fuel ran out.
Besides, I'm
getting really hungry.
Well I'm not worried...
This is supposed
to show us the path
we need to take for
world destruction.
Really? It glows and it
acts like a compass too?
Well, unless it
can make us some food
we're gonna die before we get
a chance to end the world.
Real helpful...
Oh... What do you think
the chances are that thing
comes with a hidden
can opener function?
Are you insane...?
The only thing it does
is destroy the world.
That's it;
nothing else.
[KYRIE] But you know
what everyone says!
More is better, right?!
[MORTE] Give it back
before you drop it!
[BEAR] How did I get
myself into this mess...?
I never would have
thought in a million years
I would end up
with the likes of these
World Destruction
Committee goof-offs...
'Bout time I did something
about that Destruct Code.
Uh... Hey, you guys...
Canned food's great and all,
but can we open
this bottle first?
[KYRIE] Oh no! Not
another sand octopus!
Or is it a sand whale?!
No, that's a World Salvation
Committee subarenine!
Subarenine?
[SUB CAPTAIN laughing]
Lucky us!
We actually found them!
Fire!
[WSC SOLDIER A] But what
about the Destruct Code?
Our weapons can't hurt it.
Very soon we will take it
from their cold dead hands.
[SUB CAPTAIN] Now
shut your mouth and fire!
They're shooting at us!
Abandon ship... kuma!
Hm...?
There's no sign
of their bodies
or the Destruct
Code, Captain.
Hm... They
must've jumped ship.
[SUB CAPTAIN] But they
couldn't have gotten far.
Call for more reinforcements
and search the entire area.
And make it snappy!
[WSC SOLDIERS] Yes, sir!
♪
[PRIEST] May we
bid our final farewell.
♪
Morte...
[MAN] Are you awake?
Where am I?
You're on my sand ship.
This guy here helped
us out back there.
You were just barely
clinging to a board
and floating in the
middle of the Sand Sea
when I came across you.
[MAN] Yeah... Had I
not found the three of you,
you'd probably be
all chewed up in the
belly of a sand snake
at the bottom of the sea.
Well thank you!
Wow. You're more
polite than I thought...
for a member of the
World Destruction Committee.
[MAN] I saw this
posted at the harbor
I stopped at this morning.
Wait a second, I'm
not who you think I am.
Yeah, same goes
for me, kuma.
[MAN] Easy. There's no
need to get all worked up.
I'm not your enemy.
I'm Agan and I'm a smuggler.
If you got money, I'll
carry anything you want.
And that does not
exclude outlaws who are
trying to destroy the world...
How much... you got?
Are you trying
to threaten us?
It'd be in your best interest
to remember who we work for.
Wait... She's
speaking for herself.
You're still holding
that? Give it back.
So is that really
the Destruct Code?
[AGAN] I used to hear stories
about it when I was a kid.
The legend of an all powerful
secret hidden treasure...
The Destruct Code
that will end the world.
[AGAN] I think the idea that
it's is hidden is only a myth...
Some say that it lies
at the bottom of the sea,
while others claim
it's buried under glaciers
in the winter continent, but
I don't believe any of that.
And if that thing is
the real Destruct Code,
you guys are
sitting on the most
sought-after
treasures ever known.
Don't touch it! And
of course it's real.
Well... all she does is talk
about destroying the world
when in reality she doesn't
even know how to work it.
That's enough
out of you.
Oh... Okay...
Hold on, if you don't
know how to use it
then how can you be
certain it's genuine?
The person who
had it before me...
would never lie to me.
Fine... That's cool...
I believe you...
Now if you just hand over
the Destruct Code to me...
I'll take you and your friends
anywhere you would like to go.
Oh please, you know I
can't give it to you.
Fine, cash
will work too.
This is all we
have for right now.
Wow, that's not much...
The only thing
you can buy from me
is this can
of sand whale.
That's it, kuma!
It's time I step in
and do something, kuma!
Hello...?
Who said that?
I said it...! You can
talk to me now, kuma!
What's up with this bear?
It knows how to talk?
Don't call me
bear, kuma!
Why not? That
is what you are.
[BEAR] Idiot, kuma.
That's more like it!
This should settle up
on the bill just fine...
I'm delivering a shipment
to the pleasure ship Jifnil
anyway so it's no
sweat taking you guys.
♪
[KYRIE] What's a pleasure ship?
[AGAN] It's just
what it sounds like.
It's just a regular ship,
but it offers anything
you consider
to be pleasure.
Whatever that might
be. Illegal gambling,
bars stocked with
beautiful women...
Even secret nightclubs that are
normally off limit to minors.
[AGAN] The ship
literally has everything.
[AGAN] Okay,
that's the last of it...
Or I guess technically you
guys are the last of it.
Hurry up and get off.
Say what? Not here!
For what you paid me
this is all you get...
Looks like the rest of
your trip'll be on the Jifnil.
Don't try to screw us, kuma!
C'mon, there's no
need to be like that.
The Jifnil is an outlaw zone.
Beastmen,
humans, no one cares...
In fact, it's the
perfect place for a group of
fugitives to
hide from the law.
So why don't you
enjoy yourselves?
Heh. Sounds like fun
to me. Come on... bear.
Kuma!
[AGAN] You too. Get going man!
[KYRIE] Uh...!
[AGAN] See you around!
And if we ever meet again,
bring more money!
Trust me, you'll find me much
more accommodating that way!
♪
Well hi there,
little bear...
How about a drink
with some pretty girls?
No thanks, kuma.
The last thing we need
is to hang out in some
seedy club and get
in more trouble, kuma.
The smart thing to do is to lay
low and mind our own business
until this ship
pulls into port, kuma.
Sure, that sounds good
to me. But would you
stop saying "kuma" at
the end of every sentence?
She's got a point. I
mean you actually sound
pretty cool when
you don't say it.
That I cannot do, kuma.
That word is a proud symbol
of my native tribe, kuma.
[BOTH] Hm...
Sorry 'bout that!
What's a little
girl like her
doing on a
pleasure ship?
Beats me.
[knock knock]
[SHIP CAPTAIN] Come in.
Who in the
hell are you people?
[MAN] It's a
pleasure to meet you.
My name is Nadja
and we are with
the World Salvation
Committee...
My partner's
name here is Lia.
The rest of them are with us.
[SHIP CAPTAIN] And?
So what exactly is
the World Salvation
Committee doing on my ship?
Some members of the
World Destruction Committee
recently disappeared in a
region not far from your ship...
And we have reason to believe
that they may be on board.
If that's true we'd appreciate
you turning them over to us.
No way.
[grunt]
Wait... Would you care
to elaborate Captain?
I do not care about my
patrons status in society.
There is only one place
on this entire planet
that is not under
the control of the law...
and that place is right
here on my ship, the Jifnil.
So if you would like to
look around then be my guest,
but don't expect us to lift
a finger to help you, got it?
I understand... That
should work out just fine.
[chatter]
Here's that can
of sand whale I had.
And here. I found a
bottle opener for ya.
Wait... Where's Morte?
I swear she was around
here just a minute ago.
Huh, kuma.
I don't think
you've lost even once.
You got that right...
Guess I'm a lucky girl...
There's no way I'd be
alive today without luck...
I'd like to put it
all on black... Got it?
You're betting all of it?
[MORTE] Mhmmm.
A ha... Well
look who it is.
Not quite yet, Lia.
Nadja why are
you stopping me?
When in Rome, do
as the Romans do...
Since we're on this ship,
why don't we do things
the way they would
prefer to do them?
[sigh]
There's no sense in
looking for her, kuma...
After all, it's
not like I hold
any allegiance
to her, kuma.
But the three of us
have come such a long
way together. And
what if something
bad has happened to her?
Hold on...
Do you have a
crush on Morte, kuma?
Huh...? Why
would you say that?
Oh, nevermind, kuma...
My point is there's
no reason for us
to stay involved
with her anymore, kuma.
But we're on a casino
ship, she could be
getting ripped
off as we speak!
I don't see her as the kind
of girl to take a fleecing
lying down, if you
know what I mean...
She's one of the luckiest
girls I've seen, kuma.
I guess...
Seems I underestimated you.
Well now... it would
certainly appear as though
the goddesses of good
fortune from around the world
have surrounded
you this evening.
I was hoping... you
would be interested in
playing a game
of cards with me.
Hmph.
[BEAR] There are
two types of women, kuma.
Women who can take
care of themselves...
and women who can't.
Morte is the type who can
get by on her own, kuma.
You're saying
just because she can
take care of herself
means we can't help her?
Mister Hero.
Hero's got places to be...
There's always gonna
be plenty of other people
in need of our
assistance, kuma.
Wait, her again?
A girl like her's
exactly the type
to need my help, kuma...
Find a way to get
her attention, kuma.
Me...? What
for...? You can.
Just do it
already, kuma!
[KYRIE] Excuse me.
Is everything alright?
This isn't the best
place for a young girl
to be walking
around by herself.
Get lost...
Leave me alone...
What I'm doing here is
none of your business.
Hey Toppy, I'm
starting to think this is
one of those girls like Morte.
Wait, kuma!
If there's
something going on
then you can tell us, kuma...
You never know, we may
be able to help you out.
What's with this bear?
Don't call
me bear, kuma!
Woah... easy...
Maybe she's just looking
for someone she knows, huh?
I came here to bring
my father back.
He's spends all
his time on this ship
feeding his
gambling addiction.
But he racked
up a ton of debt
and now they're
holding him hostage.
That's too bad.
It serves him right if
I may say so myself.
If you really wanna help
then give me some money...
It could go a long
way towards saving him.
We don't have
any money, kuma.
Then you're
useless to me.
Hey, wait!
Oh oh!
[TOPPY] Kuma!
Mmm...
Now then...
What's your move?
I'll stand.
Excellent.
[crowd gasps]
[crowd chatter]
[heavy exhale]
Unlike your roulette,
card games require
cool-headed decision making
as well as careful analysis.
You can't win on luck alone.
It's necessary to use this too.
Are you suggesting I'm
incapable of using my brain?!
I said no such thing.
Shall we go on... my lady?
You got that right!
Watch, I'm gonna win it
all back with this hand.
That is quite a wager.
Are you sure about this?
It seems the
goddesses of good fortune
have decided to
come over to my side.
[crowd cheer]
Now all of this
belongs to me.
So tell me, would
you be interested
in trying to win this
back with one last hand?
[MORTE] You cleaned me out.
I don't even have
a coin to my name.
In that case,
maybe you could put up
something else as collateral.
Say... Oh I don't know,
perhaps something
like the Destruct Code...?
Miss Morte Urshela.
If you win, this
gigantic stack of chips
will be all yours...
But if you were to lose,
the Destruct Code
would belong to me.
This is taking too long...!
I don't understand why we
have to pussy-foot around
when we could just
force her to give it over
and be done with it.
That is quite
an offer...
I'm always up for a
challenge, so I accept.
Music to my ears.
[MORTE] What the--?
Is there a problem...?
Getting cold feet?
You think I'd give up
that easily...? Let's play.
[GIRL] Dad?! Dad?!
[GIRL] Where's my father?
I want him back!
[SHIP CAPTAIN laughs]
What a sassy
little thing you are...
Well I don't mind
giving him back to you
but he owes me
a very large debt.
[SHIP CAPTAIN] Do you have that
kind of money, little girl?
No money, but I do
have something else.
[GIRL] It's a
priceless treasure with
the power to
destroy the world...
It's the Destruct Code!
Hey...! That's mine!
Where'd you get that...?!
[MORTE] Hand it
over you little thief!
[gasp] You bet
with a can of fish?!
♪
Not bad for a kid.
Oh, look...
It's sand whale!
[click, click]
See, I knew we
should have just taken it
from her in the first place.
Now get over here,
you little brat!
There's nowhere to run.
Now hand over
the Destruct Code.
♪
[LIA growls]
Uh, huh...? Ahhh!
[growls]
Uh...
Uh-hu...
[exhale]
Kyrie!
Lia!
[power yell]
[crowd panicking]
[distant yelling]
[MAN] Stop them!
[TOPPY] We gotta go now, kuma!
Come on. Hop in.
Uh... Mm-mmm.
I can't go with you. I have
to save my father first.
You can come back
and save him later.
Right now we all just
need to get to safety.
I'm not
scared of them.
Besides, they're
not after me,
they're after the World
Destruction Committee,
which is you guys.
You know what?
She's right.
We gotta go. Now!
Wait, hold on.
That can should fetch you
at least one silver coin.
I'm sorry but I can't
give you the Destruct Code.
But you can use
that as seed money
to get your dad out of here.
Thanks a lot.
[NADJA] We let them
slip through our fingers.
It was... my fault.
World Destruction...
Why do they
want destruction?
They sure have
piqued my curiousity.
[BOTH heavy exhale]
Later guys. I'm
gonna head out now.
Sorry to get you two
mixed up in all this mess.
[BOTH] Huh...?
Uh... Hey, where
are you going...?!
Is that how it is?
You're just gonna
leave us stranded here?
What? You
wanna come with me?
Uh... That's not
exactly what I meant...
It's just Toppy and I are
fugitives now, and you know...
Well if you want to tag
along I won't stop you.
So... I have an idea.
Why don't we forget
all this world destruction
nonsense and
help people instead...?
I mean that really seems
to be the way it's going.
We end up helping
someone in the end anyway.
Nice idea, but
the way this world is,
we'd be helping people
by destroying it for them.
What are you
gonna do, Toppy?
You guys'll probably
need me, so I guess
I'll stick around
for now, kuma.
[KYRIE] I don't know how this
happened, but we got captured!
Soon enough we found
ourselves behind bars
in a notorious prison
run by a pack of wolves!
Now we have to
find a way to escape
before those two from the World
Salvation Committee show up.
Next time on
Sands of Destruction,
"There are Two
Kinds of Beastmen."
Hey, where's Toppy?
[MORTE] He's
over there... sulking.
[TOPPY] A hero in prison...?
What's the world
coming to... kuma?