[MALE] A clockwork
robot must obey all orders
given to it by beastmen.
A clockwork robot
must always act in
the interest of beastmen.
A clockwork robot
must never comply
with any order given
to it by a human.
I created the robots,
and programmed them
with these one hundred
and eight laws of robotics.
And from the
robots' point of view...
I am none other than the
very God of Creation himself.
But why? Why should I
stop at clockwork robots?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] If I were
to possess the Destruct Code
I could control its power
and become both
the God of Creation
and the God of
Destruction to every
living thing on this planet.
Yes, the Destruct Code...
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] will be mine.
Ha! Hey, guys...
Look over there!
Clock Town's known
for its advancements
in robotics, kuma...
The ones we're
looking at right now
are called
clockwork robots, kuma.
Clockwork robots?
Hey, Morte wait up!
[KYRIE] Did I do
something... to annoy you?
You're walking away
in such a hurry.
We didn't come here to
watch the robots all day,
we came here
for a reason.
The Alligator Master
who's in charge of this town
[MORTE] has vital information
about the Destruct Code,
so we need to speak with him.
Well, yeah I know...
I just thought since we're
wanted criminals that
we'd make a plan first.
It's not like we can
march up to his front door
[KYRIE] and start
firing off questions.
The whole reason I put
these ridiculous bunny ears
back on in the first place
was so we could do just that.
So I suggest we
remain inconspicuous--
[panicked stutter]
[laughing]
Good job staying
inconspicuous, kuma.
Hey lady, you alright?
Clockwork robots are
intelligent, but it's not like
they have eyes in
the back of their heads.
Are you guys travelers?
Tell me, what do you
think about Clock Town
and our clockwork robots?
They seem incredibly
well made, kuma.
That's for sure!
And I can't imagine
what life would be like
if we didn't have these little
guys doing everything we asked!
I wanna try! Mister Robot
bring me the book
that's on the ground over there.
Strange, guess she
must have broken him.
[BEASTMAN WORKER B] Hey!
Clockwork robot over there!
Come give me a hand!
It... hates me.
I guess they don't
respond to humans.
They must be programmed
to respond only to beastmen.
Let's go.
Wait... Does that mean
the two of you are...
humans?!
[beeping]
[ALLIGATOR MASTER chuckles]
Who knew they'd play
into my hands this easily.
[GUARD ROBOT] The humans
have been spotted in town.
What are your orders?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] I want
them captured alive,
but you may injure them.
[GUARD ROBOT]
Yes, sir. Additionally...
two members of the
World Salvation Committee
are requesting
entrance into to the city.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
Delay their entrance
for as long as possible.
Your top priority is to
bring me those humans at once!
[GUARD ROBOT] Affirmative.
[machine cranking]
Welcome travelers
to Clock Town.
I will be your guide
to our remarkable city.
How may I be of service to you?
We appreciate your
assistance and hospitality.
We have come
here today to--
Before we begin,
I must first confirm
your identification.
What is the name
of your organization?
We are Lia and
Nadja, members of
the World
Salvation Committee.
That was...
Curled Vacation Karate?
Uh... No, It's World
Salvation Committee.
Hurled Sensation's a Pity?
No, that's not it...
World. Salvation. Committee.
Girl Devastation
in City?
[LIA growls]
Wrong. Listen close:
World Salvation Committee.
[WELCOME ROBOT]
World Sensation Shmitty?
[NADJA] That's closer...
[sirens]
[KYRIE] Oh no!
I think they found
out that we're
the World
Destruction Committee?
Ahhh!
Be careful, kuma.
These guys aren't your
typical clockwork robots.
They're Clock Town's
fighting robots, kuma!
[sirens]
Not a problem.
We'll just do this the hard way!
Uh...
[heavy breathing]
[BOTH heavy breathing]
[MORTE] Kyrie!
[screaming]
[TOPPY] Kuma!
[KYRIE screaming]
Kuma!
[MORTE grunts]
[sirens]
[sighs]
[TOPPY grunts]
[beeping]
He's calling
for back up...
Stop! Don't
do it, kuma!
That's an affirmative.
[BOTH] Uh...?
Of course! They're programmed
to respond to beastmen!
Toppy, he'll listen
to your every command!
Alright then, I want you
to take us to a safe place
where there's no
one else around, kuma.
Affirmative. Follow me.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] What?!
How could they have escaped?
[GUARD ROBOT] It appears...
that the two humans have
a beastman companion
and now one of the
clockwork robots
is complying with his
commands as a result
of the standard laws
of clockwork robotics.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Impossible!
I foresaw this issue,
so I took specific precautions
to prevent it from happening.
I added an additional law
of robotics stipulating that
no robot shall
listen to any commands
from members of the bear tribe!
It appears their
companion is of the
dwarf bear tribe
and not the bear tribe.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Dwarf bear?!
How can that be unless
the picture upon this
wanted poster is
completely inaccurate?
We've reached a secure
location, Master Bear.
What are your next orders?
Don't call me
a bear, kuma.
That's an affirmative.
Now that our cover's
blown should we leave?
Lead us to where the
Alligator Master is.
[ROBOT] According to the third
law of clockwork robotics,
a robot must never
comply with any order
given to it by a human.
Then you say it.
Not a chance, kuma.
Why don't you ask me later
after you think of a
less suicidal plan, kuma.
Hey, wait a second!
[beeping]
We're in trouble...
Toppy, order
them to stay back!
[TOPPY] All of you...
at ease now, kuma!
I said at ease! That was
a direct order, kuma!
It appears that the
programming for the laws of
clockwork robotics has
been recently updated.
[KYRIE] I don't wanna die here!
[TOPPY] Morte and I will open
up a path to your right, kuma!
After that you
run for it, kuma!
Morte... I'm okay.
I think that I want to
stay and fight this time.
[MORTE] Toppy!
Catch it!
[TOPPY] I'll be back, kuma!
Wait! Why'd you
listen to me?
You know I can't fight!
Follow my lead.
Now they'll take us
to the Alligator Master
just like I wanted.
Why'd I have to
choose this time
to stay and fight?
[MORTE] Baby.
The Pearl
Castration Subcommittee?
No... Listen closely...
It's... World
Sal-va-tion Com-mit-tee!
Hm?
Where's Lia?
[beeping]
We can't do
anything if we
stay hidden in
the shadows, kuma.
Do you know exactly
where those other robots
have taken my
friends, kuma?
Affirmative.
Then tell me, kuma!
The tallest tower
in Clock Town
is the Alligator
Master's Clock Fortress.
The two humans are
currently located within in.
[TOPPY] Take me there, kuma!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Hm...
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
So, the two of you make up
the World
Destruction Committee?
You're the
Alligator Master.
Now that we're
formally introduced,
I have questions for you.
Be mindful of
your position.
I've captured you,
wouldn't that mean
I've earned the right
to ask the questions?
Has prisoner
etiquette changed?
Oh fine.
I'll have some fun
and answer your
little questions.
I'm guessing you simply
want to know how to use
the Destruct Code
or am I mistaken?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER chuckles]
You must take me for a fool!
You have in your
possession an item that could
wreak havoc upon
all of beastmankind
and you think I'll just
tell you how it works?
How amusing.
Do you even know what secret
it is you're fishing for?
The Destruct Code is not the
secret to winning this war!
If you fulfill your threat and
activate the Destruct Code,
it wouldn't be just the beastman
tribes that you annihilate.
Just as the legend states,
the entire world would
return to elemental sand.
That means that you, I,
every person on every
continent, even the memory
of our very existence
would cease to be.
If you activate
the Destruct Code
your World Destruction
Committee will do just that.
That's just fine by me.
[gasp]
I'm Lia of the World
Salvation Committee.
That was "The Curled
Crustacean Drum Kitty"?
[LIA] That's right. I'm from the
Curled Crustacean Drum Kitty.
Now can I please see
the Alligator Master?
Negative. No
affiliations known as
the Curled
Crustacean Drum Kitties
are recorded in our database.
[wind blowing]
Their location
is north.
Wait! No I'm
not ready yet!
Ahhh!
[TOPPY screaming]
What happen, kuma?
I have overheated.
No need to overdo it.
Let's rest here a bit, kuma.
I will rest as
you have ordered.
By the way,
you haven't told me
what your name is yet, kuma.
Robots have no names.
If you wish to distinguish
me from other clockwork
robots, you may refer to me
as number twenty-eight.
Number
twenty-eight, kuma?
Twenty-eight is
my serial number.
I have cooled to a
sufficient temperature.
Resuming forward motion.
What?! Now?!
I'm not ready, kuma!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
You're fine with it,
but have you bothered to
check and see if it's fine
with your companion over there?
He may not be as fond as you
are of becoming a pile of sand.
Yeah... [nervous chuckle]
Now I feel that
I have humored you
for long enough. It's time.
Hand over the Destruct
Code this very instant!
Sorry, don't have it on me.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Don't
even try to lie to me girl.
Gaze upon my
brilliant creation!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] This machine
is my Destruct Code Detector.
Thousands or perhaps even tens
of thousands of years ago,
when the Destruct
Code was activated,
it left behind a
distinctive energy that
I was able to isolate and
now track with my invention.
Due to the high
intensity of the energy,
I cannot construct
a smaller model
but it's fulfilling
its purpose.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Look at how
brilliantly the light glows.
It's indicating that the
Destruct Code is near...
very near.
Now... you can't deny
it any longer; hand it over.
Are you hard of hearing?
I said I don't have it!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] My
detector cannot be wrong,
so you must be hiding it!
Remove this girl's limbs
one by one 'til it's found!
[BOTH shudder]
[chuckles]
[beeping]
Huh?
[TOPPY] Number twenty-eight!
Get my friends
outta here, kuma!
[GUARD ROBOT] Cease at once!
Terminate all violent
behavior immediately!
[LIA] Move it,
you annoying tin cans!
[LIA] I've had enough...
It's time for you to pay!
[ALL gasp]
[NO. 28 panicking]
Huh?
Stop! You fool!
You are hitting the detector!
Agh!
[ALL gasp]
♪
It's starting to resonate.
[MORTE] What in the...?
Dragon Valley...
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] This is
most certainly the landscape
of the Dragon Valley
on the winter continent.
Why would the Destruct
Code want to show us this?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Ahhh...
The Destruct Code,
it wanted us to see...
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Aaauuuhhh...
[NO. 28] Now let us depart.
Stop them!
[MORTE, TOPPY, and
KYRIE breathing heavy]
[stuttering]
[crash]
Danger! You
are in danger.
Please take the item
and resume running away.
Your assistance
is appreciated.
A hero doesn't leave
a friend behind, kuma!
[TOPPY] Even a numbered one.
Sorry I'm late! You
wouldn't believe how much
time it took to
verify our identities.
I think the clockwork robot
at the gate may have a glitch.
[NADJA] What's wrong, Lia?
What? Sorry...
I managed to locate the
World Destruction Committee
members in town,
but unfortunately
I let them slip away again.
They couldn't have
possibly gotten that far
away from here,
though. So let's go.
[NADJA] What did
you do this time?
[LIA] With what happened
before, I'd say the
World Salvation Committee was
never welcome in Clock Town.
Are you alright, kuma?
I sustained only minor
damages. However...
However?
What's wrong, kuma?
You rescue me after I
asked you to run away?
Is there something
programmed in the
Laws of Beastmen to protect
clockwork robots
who are in danger?
No, not exactly, kuma.
Does not compute.
Please explain further.
That's the difference
between clockwork robots
and us living things, kuma.
The decisions we make aren't
programmed into us, kuma.
[TOPPY] We have the freedom
to make our own decisions,
it's called...
having a soul, kuma.
A... soul?
[rumble]
End of the line.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] As
much fun as has it's been,
I'm through playing
your little games.
Retrieve the destruct
code, number twenty-eight.
Number twenty-eight, you
don't have to do it, kuma!
You don't have to listen
to what he says, kuma!
Stay strong, kuma!
[beeping]
You've been programmed
to do as I say.
And I'm granting you
authorization to switch
to firing mode. Kill them.
[TOPPY, KYRIE, and MORTE] Uh...
Ha...
No, kuma!
♪
Optimum escape
route is north.
Impossible!
♪
Hey guys, climb faster.
They're gaining on us!
Come on, kuma!
Please do not approach.
Please continue climbing, for
I have made my own decision.
I won't leave you, kuma!
Repeat. Do not approach.
No, don't do it!
Number twenty-eight!
[crash]
[sigh]
Toppy, the best thing for us
to do is keep moving forward.
Wait a second,
please tell me that
you have the
Destruct Code!
Ah! It was in number
twenty-eight's chest
when he fell!
What?! After all of that?
Morte, you can't go back!
We just barely made
it out of there alive!
Let go of me!
[KYRIE and MORTE arguing]
What seems to be the problem?
Kuma!
[TOPPY] Number twenty-eight?!
[KYRIE and MORTE]
Number twenty-eight?!
I had to return this.
Thanks, but I'm just glad
you made it out safe, kuma!
[NO. 28] Of course I am safe.
Clockwork robotics
law one-oh-seven,
a clockwork robot must protect
it's own existence at all costs.
I am awaiting
your next command.
I have no more
commands to give, kuma.
Master Toppy, please
issue me a command.
Hm...
Right. If you need a command
from me, kuma...
Return to Clock
Town and start living
the way you want, kuma.
Living. It is a difficult
concept, Master Toppy,
but I will comply.
Take it easy, kuma.
[TOPPY] And good luck friend.
[beeping]
Let's get going.
Get going? Please
don't tell me that
we're headed to
Dragon Valley?!
That's right. Now...
c'mon before the
[MORETE] World Salvation
Committee catches up to us.
[KYRIE] Morte, please stop!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] They'll
no doubt will be heading
to the winter continent.
So I'll just have to
meet them in Dragon Valley.
And the Destruct
Code... will be mine!
[MORTE] After making our
escape from Clock Town,
we head to the location
on the winter continent that
the Destruct Code had
mysteriously shown us.
Dragon Valley. But
instead of all the answers
we've been searching
for, we find a very angry
and very familiar descendant
of the dragon tribe.
Next time on
Sands of Destruction,
"There Are Two Kinds of Power."
[KYRIE] T-T-T-Toppy! You
can't just fall asleep here!
You'll f-f-freeze
yourself to d-d-death!
[TOPPY] I'm a bear...
We hibernate in winter, kuma.
[MORTE] So you're
finally admitting
that you're a bear... kuma?
[TOPPY] No.