[TOPPY] There are two
kinds of autumns...
Autumns of harvest...
and autumns spent
lost in one's thoughts.
♪
We can finally see
the town now, kuma!
[KYRIE] You know
of this place, Toppy?
[TOPPY] Well I've
heard about it, kuma.
It's the town of Galoa and
within it resides an academy.
Researchers in every
conceivable field of study
are gathered there
and they devote all hours
of the day to their work, kuma.
Some people say that in Galoa,
you can find out anything
you want to know, kuma.
[KYRIE] Wow.
[KYRIE] What an odd statue.
[TOPPY] "Give me your
beastmen, your humans,
any and all people who
yearn to gain knowledge."
That's what I've
heard it says, kuma.
Oh really? That's
good news for us.
After that little ordeal
we had in the Sand Sea...
[KYRIE] I, for one, am ready
for some rest and relaxation.
This place is
great, kuma!
Yeah. It's way better
than I imagined it to be.
[POTATO VENDOR] Step on up!
[POTATO VENDOR] Fresh
baked sweet potatoes here!
[KYRIE] Hey, that reminds me...
Morte, we haven't eaten
anything all day have we?
Wanna sweet potato?
No, thank you.
Okay, so what's
wrong with her, kuma?
This is stupid.
We're supposed to be
the World
Destruction Committee.
Let's not start
in on that again.
We're already here,
why don't we relax?
Hey I'll go get us
a little bit of food.
[GIRL] Oh come on,
that's crazy!
No way, it's true!
[giggles]
[ELEPHANT] I can't thank you
enough for all the great work
that you and your
friends have been doing.
The children have really
taken a liking to you,
they're having so much fun.
A world where
humans and beastmen
could live in harmony.
It's been my lifelong
dream to make a world
[ELEPHANT] like
that into reality.
[MORTE] It's a
wonderful thought...
But I just cannot
believe a single word
that comes out of your mouth.
Morte! Hey where
are you going, kuma?!
I got us the spuds...
What the heck's
her problem, kuma?
She's been acting like
that since we got here.
Well I think she's...
reminiscing about something.
Reminiscing
about what, kuma?
Let's leave her alone for now.
So what should we do, Toppy?
[TOPPY] I think I'll sit down
and enjoy those sweet potatoes.
It's rare for
us to get a day off,
so we should take
full advantage.
Agreed.
And as for me...
I think I'll walk
around campus a bit.
It seems like there's plenty to
see around here, don't ya think?
[townspeople chatter]
[gasps]
[distant door opens
and bell rings]
[MAN] I'm sorry, ma'am.
Unfortunately, we're closed now.
Can I... help you?
Um, I'm sorry.
It's just...
I've never been
to this town before.
I was curious... so I...
Oh, I understand.
Been a while since
I've had alone time.
It really does feel nice.
Hey look at that
guy. He's so cute!
Him? You think so?
I'm just not that
into blonde men.
[KYRIE] I've been on the
road for way too long.
[SOCCER BOY] Sorry 'bout that
could you kick it back please!
[KYRIE] Everybody's
so happy here!
[grunts]
[SOCCER LION] Thanks!
♪
[snoring]
[MORTE] It's closing down?
[MAN] Yeah. I inherited
this library from my father
who used to work
as an historian.
Between my big sister
and I, the two of us
managed to keep
it going for awhile.
However... I think
the time has come
to move on
with my life.
I see... So you
have an older sister?
Well technically...
I guess... I had one.
[MAN] Several years ago our
father got mixed up in a fight
between beastmen and humans...
and wound up
dying in the melee.
[MAN] Not long after...
my sister left town
and before I knew it,
no one had any idea
what happened to her.
Then just a few days
ago, I got a notice.
Just like my father,
she got involved in a fight
between beastmen and
humans... and was killed.
Is that...
your sister?
Uh huh. Both of
us were orphans.
But luckily our father took us
in and raised us as his own.
'Cause he thought
it would be better
for us to be
raised together.
And he would always say all
tribes were created equal.
[MAN] But since
my father was killed
and my sister disappeared,
I developed
very severe anxiety.
[MAN] I began to doubt
if living in a town where
beastmen and humans live
side by side was best for me.
And now my sister's
been killed under the same
circumstances as my father.
Anyway... That's
when I decided to leave.
Closing out the library's
the last thing I have to do.
So...
[MAN] Um... You don't...
I've got some extra
time on my hands.
[people chatting]
You're late!
[RAM GUY] I'm sorry.
I forgot something at home
and I had to
go back and get it.
[GIRL] That's no excuse!
[RAM GUY] But I needed it.
What was I supposed to do?
Oh well... I guess she
doesn't believe in the idea
that beastmen and
humans should get along.
Poor Morte.
♪
[KYRIE] An historical museum?
Some people say
that in Galoa...
you can find out anything
you want to know, kuma.
They may know about
the Destruct Code.
I mean it is a
museum after all.
[MAN] So... tell me...
What brought you to this town?
[MORTE] No reason.
It's just a stop along the way.
Don't tell me you're
traveling all by yourself.
[EOR] That's my sister's
studio. She painted.
That's what she studied here.
It's another room
I have to clear out.
[MAN] I haven't set foot
in there since she left.
It's kinda hard to describe...
but it feels like
if I go in there,
every memory I
have when she was alive...
will somehow disappear.
And that frightens me.
Yeah, I know.
♪
[TOPPY snoring]
[CURATOR] Well you see, books
that focus on those sort of
topics have no
real academic value.
We like to keep them
together back here
in our storage space.
[CURATOR] We spend
so much time organizing
and still we can't keep up.
Ah... I believe this is it.
[KYRIE] Thank you
for helping me out.
Don't mention it.
Just give me a holler
once you're finished, okay?
[KYRIE] The Destruct Code.
It contains the power
to destroy the world.
For eons, knowledge of
its existence has
remained a mystery,
passed down through
folklore and legend.
You know... I'm not
sure if I even remember
where I first heard
about the Destruct Code.
[KYRIE] Written by...
the Alligator Master.
This book's full of research...
There's so much of it.
[KYRIE] The Destruct Code
was formed by the gods when
the world was in its
first moments of creation.
The annihilation it is
capable of causing may be
carried out by either
beastmen or human beings.
This is some pretty
detailed stuff here.
I wonder if there's any
information on how to use it.
Excuse me, sir!
[CURATOR] I'll
be right there, man!
Would it be alright
if I borrowed
this book for a
little awhile?
Oh yeah, of course.
In fact, I'll even give
it to you if you want.
I mean, it's not
like anyone's
actually going to
read the old thing.
♪
Excuse me...
Uh, yes?
So then... Morte
offered to help you?
And you're sure she knew
you were a beastman?
That's right.
Do you... find something
wrong with that?
Oh no.
Well then... I
suppose it's about time
I put an end to
all of this, huh?
[MAN] Excuse me.
I just wanted to thank
you for all the help
you've given me today.
I think it's about
time we called it quits.
It's already getting dark out.
Yeah. Okay.
[MORTE] On second thought...
Let's keep going
until we're finished.
Since you're leaving, the
sooner you're done the better.
[MAN] Oh... Okay...
Um... I'm gonna go
scrounge up some lanterns.
♪
[crying]
Hey Morte.
[MORTE] What?
[KYRIE] The Destruct Code.
Where'd you find it?
[MORTE] It was with my
brother... when he passed away.
[KYRIE] There's
something written about it
in this book I found.
[KYRIE] It says there are
a number of theories...
but there's no record of anyone
ever seeing the actual device.
I looked through some
other sources as well...
But none of them say
with any certainty that
the item you have is
actually the Destruct Code.
[MORTE] What are you getting at?
That my brother
left behind a fake?
No, that's not
what I'm saying...
Listen... let's say what
you have is the real thing...
if we don't know
how to use it then...
So what? It doesn't
change that fact that
I have to put an end...
to this despicable world.
[TOPPY snoring]
[moams]
Where'd those
two run off to, kuma?
A town like this...
where beastmen and
humans live together...
it seems like the idea of
it doesn't sit well with you.
But what about the three of us?
We seem to do
alright, don't we?
[MORTE] You know, I didn't go
on this journey to make friends.
[KYRIE] So you're
saying this whole time
you haven't had any fun?
Well I know that I'm
having a fantastic time.
I mean really... I've never
done anything like this before.
Of course we did
almost die a few times.
[KYRIE] Before this... I was
nothing more than a loner.
Hey do you remember
the café where we first met?
[KYRIE] I would just hop
around from town to town
before I got that job. I
lived my life in a constant
state of fear just
because I'm a human,
and it didn't take
long for me to find some
comfort in wearing
a beastman disguise.
But even then, I still
don't think I ever got
a decent night's sleep,
you know what I mean?
And this stupid thing.
It almost became
a part of my body.
It was about the only thing I
could really rely on for a time.
You must be helping
out here for a reason.
Is it because that guy
looks like your brother?
I've been meaning to ask
you this for a long time now.
The entire reason
behind why you're so fixated
on destroying the world...
is it because of what happened
to your younger
brother back then?
He was... a member of the
Golden Lions, wasn't he?
That's how... he got caught
up in the struggle, right?
Stop!
[footsteps]
Eor, this must be
hard for you, huh?
Uh yeah. I guess it is.
I think the reason why
my sister decided to leave
is because in some
backwards way she believed
that the town was somehow
to blame for what happened...
to our father.
And you really believe
that that's the truth?
Maybe she felt like
your father did...
that all the tribes were
created to be equal.
If you look at your sister's
motives in that way,
then perhaps she decided to
leave to go spread the word.
I'll open the door.
♪
And there it is.
You know, it's not always
an easy thing to...
forgive and forget.
This room's in
need of a cleaning.
Would you mind staying
and helping out?
Eor, Look.
My sister.
[EOR crying]
[KYRIE] Welcome to Clock Town.
[TOPPY] Why're you
talking like that, kuma?
[KYRIE] You know what
they say, when in Rome?
Come on guys, practice
your robo-voices.
[MORTE] I don't think so.
[KYRIE and TOPPY] Next time
on Sands of Destruction,
[MORTE] "There are
One hundred-eight Laws
of Clockwork Robotics."
[KYRIE] You and me
friends right, Morte?
[TOPPY] Loosen up.
Take a load off, kuma.
[KYRIE and TOPPY]
We are all good friends.
[KYRIE and TOPPY] Kuma.