[MALE] There are
two kinds of heroes...
Those who save the world...
and those who save
single individuals.
[BARTENDER] Word on the
street is those cretins from
the World Destruction
Committee are
hiding somewhere
here in town...
So instead of sitting here
and drinking the day away
like some two-bit
bum, why don't you try
and save the world by
rounding those dirt-bags up?
[MALE] I'm not
that kind of hero.
I leave saving
the world to others...
Know what I mean, kuma?
Hmph.
World Destruction
Committee?
They're the
one's who destroy
everything in
their path, right?
Hey come on
wake up, new kid...!
Go Serve that plate
before the food gets cold.
Eh, right!
Hey, what the heck is this?
I ask for the sand shark eggs
and this is what you give me?!
That's all the sand
shark we got 'cause they
haven't been
catching much lately.
Now stop complaining and eat!
You'd think the world's
coming to an end...
[MAN] The world could
end tomorrow for all I care.
It's not like it has
anything to do with me.
[MAN] Here you are, ma'am.
Stewed sand jellyfish.
You need anything else?
[WOMAN] What's this?
It's the stewed sand jellyfish,
just like you ordered...
[WOMAN] I ordered the whale.
[WOMAN] This
isn't what I ordered.
I wanted whale, not jellyfish.
Ugh...
[WOMAN] That a problem?
No... I'll fix it right away!
You don't see pretty
girls like yourself
in dives like this these days.
I take it you aren't
from around these parts,
are ya, missy?
So where're you from?
Tell me, what brings
you to our fair town?
[CUSTOMER] I'm sure
you're not thinking of
getting aboard
the Jifnil right?
Because if you are you better
not get your hopes up...
With all the rumors
going around about
the World Destruction
Committee being in town,
the Jifnil isn't even
gonna coming to port.
It's not worth
the risk for them.
[MAN] Okay,
here's your sand whale.
Sorry about the wait ma'am.
[CUSTOMER B] Well, anyway,
now that you're in town,
maybe you and
I should go get...
[WOMAN] I don't think so.
I'd like to eat my food now.
And I would prefer
to do it alone.
[WSC SOLDIER A]
Everyone freeze! Don't move!
[WSC SOLDIER B] We're with the
World Salvation Committee...
All we ask for is
your full cooperation.
[WSC SOLDIER A] Hey you...!
What part of don't move
did you not understand...?
Get back here! Now!
[WOMAN] You are so annoying...
I wish you people
would just let things go.
Especially since I spent
all my money on this food!
[WSC SOLDIER B]
It's... it's you!
[MAN] I knew it! She's with
the World Destruction Committee!
[panic]
Careful now...! If
you take one more step...
the beastman'll get
it right in the throat!
Come with me.
Hey, don't be so rough!
You're gonna cut me!
Uh...
[WSC SOLDIER B] Fire!
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[coughing]
Hey...! Wait for me!
[BARTENDER] Hmm. Sounds
like those rumors about
the World Destruction
Committee were true after all.
What do you want...?
Look, I don't
let humans in here
and besides this really
isn't any kinda place
for someone your age, kid.
[BOY] My name's Cain.
I just came over from
the Cat Master's Manor.
And I heard that there's
a Hero's Guild detective
in town who is willing
to work for anyone,
as long as they've
got money he'll work for
beastmen or humans.
Hmmm.
[CAIN] Please sir, help me...!
I beg you! Save my sister!
If no one helps her
she'll be sacrificed to
[CAIN] the God of the Sand Sea!
[MINION A] Sire, we
just received word that
the World Destruction
Committee has been spotted
somewhere in the town below.
They somehow found
a way to evade the
World Salvation Committee
forces and have escaped.
So you mean to tell me that
they're still on the run?!
You don't suppose
they're on their way here
to take down
the castle, do you?!
There's no need to worry, sire.
Our castle's defenses
are impenetrable.
[panicked outcry]
I knew it! Fortune
has forsaken our land!
Fishing in the Sand
Sea has never been worse,
[CAT MASTER] and now the World
Salvation Committee is here...!
It must be punishment
from the God of the Sand Sea
for neglecting him for so long!
[CAT MASTER] Alright...
there's no time to waste.
The only way out of
this predicament is to
offer a sacrifice to
the God of the Sand Sea
as soon as possible!
[CAT MINIONS] Meow, sir!
[heavy breathing]
So what's your story anyway?
Why in the world would a human
work at a beastmen's café...?
Not to mention you almost
turning us into swiss cheese.
You're blaming me for that?
Look, I needed work
so I fooled the beastmen
and got a nice job that
included room and board.
So you infiltrated
the café to carry out
some sort of
clandestine mission?
I just needed a job...
You may find this hard
to believe but most of
us real people need to
work to make a living...
Plus beastmen places are known
to pay a heck of lot more.
What?!
Just for work...?
Do you have any
idea what they would
do to you if they
found out you were human?
Oh yeah, thanks. You
took care of that one for me...
Morte.
How do you know
my name? Tell me.
It was written there on the
wanted poster in the café.
Fugitive wanted for crimes,
Morte Urshela, age seventeen--
[MORTE] I'm sixteen! There's
a big difference between
sixteen and
seventeen, you dope!
[MAN] What the heck's she
so bent out of shape for?
I'd be more worried they know
my name than messing up my age.
[MORTE] You should know better
than to believe everything
the World Salvation
Committee tells you.
You're so naïve.
Anyway, you were...
[MAN] Kyrie!
My name
is Kyrie Illnis.
Actually I wasn't asking
for your name but whatever.
So what is the World
Destruction Committee anyway?
How should I know...?
Those jerks just
stuck that label on me
and have been chasing
me around ever since.
By those
jerks you mean
the World
Salvation Committee?
Right... But to be
honest, at this point
I'm glad they gave
me such a cool title.
It really packs a
punch, don'tcha think...?
The World
Destruction Committee.
[distant rustling]
Oh, hi!
Who are you guys? Humans?
Uh... Um, we
are... we're...
We're just
wanderers. Yeah.
Just passing through.
You didn't happen
to see a young boy
named Cain, did you?
You see, he's my little brother.
[KYRIE] Sorry, we
haven't seen anyone.
[VILLAGE ELDER] Linan.
What are you doing here, Linan?
[LINAN] Oh, hi Elder...
I can't find Cain anywhere,
so I went looking for him.
[VILLAGE ELDER]
Who are these two?
I've never seen
them around the village.
They said they're wanderers.
You're traveling somewhere?
That's right. Uh, but
we're friendly though.
Nothing to be suspicious of.
The sun will be down soon.
You two are more than welcome
to spend the
night in our village.
[heavy exhale] That was good.
I'm starting to
feel kinda sleepy
now that my belly's all full.
So, uh... you
gonna finish that?
In that case I'll take
that sand jellyfish stew
[KYRIE] off your
hands. [chuckles]
So... you got any plans
for the foreseeable future?
No, not really... The
café's in complete shambles
and I've now been
outed as a human so...
now I have no place to go.
Are You gonna eat that
soy-glazed jellyfish?
I can't stand
sand jellyfish.
Oh great!
[KYRIE] I know what I can do...
I should ask that Village Elder
if I can stay here with them...
They seem like
nice enough people...
You know, you should
consider doing the same thing.
[MORTE] As soon as I'm rested
I'm getting out of here.
But where do you plan on going?
Somewhere I can
destroy the world.
You are kidding, right?
No, I'm not.
But if you
destroy the world,
the beastmen wouldn't
be the only one's to die.
Humans would too.
Beastmen, humans,
they're all the same to me...
The only thing I'm
interested in is smashing this
oppressive and hypocritical
world into pieces.
I think you need to
rethink your plan a bit.
I mean, you can't really destroy
the world all by yourself.
Besides the whole
notion of world destruction
is so vague to begin
with it's almost laughable.
With this it only
takes one person.
What is it?
Don't touch it! This is called
the Destruct Code and it has
the power to destroy
the entire world
in the blink of an eye.
It holds secrets that humans
couldn't possibly understand.
It's in your best interests
to not even get involved
with a someone like me.
[MORTE] You'd be better off
putting those fake ears back on
and finding a low-profile
job in another café...
And just wait
for the end to come.
Because... I'll be
the one to end it...
And no one will stand in my--
[VILLAGER] So we'll use
the girl in place of Linan?
Right... No one
will even bat an eye
if a wayward
traveler goes missing.
Wait, Elder. I
have something to say.
Yes. What is it, Linan?
It's just that sacrificing
a complete stranger
in my place sounds wrong.
[VILLAGE ELDER] You don't
need to be concerned with this.
She's a drifter
without a family.
No one will be sad
if she were to disappear.
Besides, sacrificing
her will save your life.
[gasp]
♪
So Elder, where is
the sacrificial girl?
We are preparing
her as we speak, sire...
I beg for your patience.
That it, kuma?
[footsteps]
[VILLAGERS A and B] Huh?
[VILLAGER A] She escaped!
[VILLAGER B] Looks like she
didn't eat the sand jellyfish!
Now what do we do?!
How am I
supposed to know?!
[KYRIE murmuring]
[footsteps]
[MORTE] Don't move!
Oh, it's you.
[MORTE] Sorry to run off
in the middle of the night
without saying thanks.
It's not like I don't
trust you, it's just that
I've been through a
lot lately and well...
if you're looking
for the guy I was with--
[LINAN] That's not it!
Something bad's
about to... happen...
They took your
friend instead of me...
And they're going to make
him a... human sacrifice!
[CAT MINIONS] Meow-go!
Meow-go! Meow! Meow! Meow...!
Meow-go! Meow-go!
Meow! Meow! Meow...!
[CAT MASTER straining]
[CAT MASTER] Meow!
[CAT MINIONS] Meow!
[KYRIE mumbling]
[CAT MINIONS] Sacrifice Meow!
Runny jellyfish... [mumbles]
[cough]
[low growls]
What the--?! Who in
the hellcat are you?!
Never mind that now.
[hissing]
How dare you
interfere with our
human sacrifice
ceremony!
Don't try to play
games with me.
Now tell me what
I want to know...
Where'd you put Kyrie?
Who said our defenses
are impenetrable?!
[ALL meow]
You're worthless!
Just tell me where he is...
or I'll make this one
here... your next sacrifice.
[KYRIE screaming]
He must be
down there... Adios.
[CAT MASTER panics] Oh no!
Uh...
Oh, oh, oh no!
Be-Be-Behind you!
You're not a girl!
[CAT MASTER screaming]
[growl]
[MORTE] Kyrie!
[KYRIE] Morte!
[chuckles]
On your feet!
'Kay.
♪
[WSC SOLDIER B] This time
we're not letting you get away!
Geez...!
Why does everything
have to be so difficult?!
Stay right here, kuma!
[LINAN] Cain!
[CAIN] Sis!
[WSC SOLDIER B] Cease fire!
Hey...! Are you nuts?
Least you could do
is cut my ropes first!
Just hang tight while I
take care of these goons!
Hey, come on!
♪
[power yell]
[BEAR] Hiyaaaah!
Aaahhh!
Ahhh!
[WSC SOLDIER B] That's enough!
[WSC SOLDIER B] Stand down!
[KYRIE chuckles]
[KYRIE] This never
would have happened if
you had just cut
my ropes like I asked.
Aha-ha!
[roar]
[ALL panicking]
No, please. Not again!
Aaahhh!
Linan!
Ahhh!
[KYRIE screaming]
Your brother sent me
to help little girl...
Ahhh...!
[WSC SOLDIER B] Hold it...
Are you a member of
the World
Destruction Committee?!
What? No, I'm not with them!
[WSC SOLDIER C] Just kill
him along with the other two!
Wait, I'm innocent, kuma!
[MORTE] Alright, stop.
That's far enough!
Take another step
and I'll activate this.
[WSC SOLDIER C] She
has the Destruct Code!
[WSC SOLDIER B]
She's bluffing...!
There's no way she
has the nerve to do it.
Mmm.
You're bluffing?!
[WSC SOLDIER B] Now be a
good girl and hand it over!
Uh!
[WSC SOLDIERS gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[KYRIE] What's happening?!
[growling]
[MORTE] Bring that over here!
[KYRIE] Wha--?
[KYRIE] You're crazy!
[BEAR] Don't be chicken, kuma!
[CAT MINIONS screaming]
[roar]
[KYRIE] heavy breathing]
So... will
the world really be
annihilated if
you use this thing?
[MORTE] Yeah, but you have to
know how to use it correctly.
Though I must admit
that's the first time
I've seen it glow like that.
You had to have
done something to it.
[KYRIE] No, I
didn't do anything!
Oh, whatever.
Just give it back.
[LINAN] Hey you guys.
Thank you so much.
No we're part of the
World Destruction Committee...
and we haven't really done
anything to deserve your thanks.
Poor Mister Detective...
[MORTE] See ya later!
[KYRIE] Hey wait,
where're you going?!
[MORTE] I'm
commandeering this boat!
It's almost hard to
believe those two are
actually with the World
Destruction Committee.
[motor running]
Hey, kuma!
You no good
boat thief, kuma!
Who in the
heck is that bear?
Well it, uh... It
looks like he may be
a detective working
with the Hero's Guild.
Off my boat!
I think I
should point out...
those soldiers thought
you were a member of
the World Destruction
Committee too.
That means you
just escaped with us.
[chuckles]
Tough break my man!
That goes for you too.
So what now? You got
any big plans for us?
Didn't I already tell you...?
We're all going
to destroy the world.
[BEAR] It turns out there's
another kindda hero...
The kind that leads the
world to destruction... kuma.
[MORTE] After slipping away
from those annoying jerks
chasinng after us,
we found ourselves on the
pleasure ship Jifnil. In
the chaos of hopes and dreams
that is the Jifnil,
we come across a smuggler
and two people from the
World Salvation Committee.
Though will I be willing to put
the Destruct Code on the line
during a card game?
You better believe it!
Next time on
Sands of Destruction,
"There are Two Kinds of Worlds."
[KYRIE] How come the
two of us have to be
on the wanted list with
all the other fugitives?
[BEAR] Kuma...!