There are two
kinds of men, kuma.
Those who have
a sense of justice
and those who just
create their own, kuma.
[KYRIE] A coliseum?
[MORTE] It's a place where
beastmen pay money to watch
other beastmen attack
humans for sport.
It's completely
senseless if you ask me.
And for some reason
it's the most popular
form of entertainment
around here.
You don't want us
to put our fake ears on
and head down to
watch this do you?
[MORTE] Of course not, idiot...
The smartest move we could make
is to avoid that town entirely.
I heard that when they run out
of fighters from their prison,
thugs from the
coliseum kidnap any humans
they can find to fight
in the remaining battles.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I just heard
something and thought
it might have been
those thugs coming for us.
[KYRIE] Huh?!
Come on out you thugs!
[footsteps]
It's just Toppy!
I knew you were just
trying to scare me
[KYRIE] with that stupid story.
So where are all the fish?
Looks like you--
[gasp]
♪
[cheering and yelling]
[MOLE] Make him feel the pain!
[MOUSE] Woo hoo!
[crowd cheers]
Wait, your story...
It was true!
It seems we've
been kidnapped.
But how did we
get ourselves trapped
inside the coliseum?!
That little bear
and his thugs got us.
I couldn't take all of them.
So it was
another little bear
and not Toppy
that kidnapped us?
Wait, didn't you say
humans battle beastmen here?
[distant cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] And now
the moment that you've
all been waiting for.
Striking fear into the
hearts of all who face him...
give it up for our horse
warrior from the planet Dart!
[cheering]
[neigh]
[MORTE] Hey, Kyrie.
Huh?
You should
put that on.
It might help you
more than the last guy.
[KYRIE worried wimper]
[KYRIE] Ahh-huh.
Hey, settle down.
You're up next, so
give the customers
a good show
before you die.
Wait we're going
out to fight?
Well whadya think
you were gonna do here.
Just don't spoil the
fans fun by dying to soon.
I hate it when that happens.
'Kay. Good to know...
We'll... try our best...
Oh, Morte!
[MORTE] Will you calm down?!
Weren't you listening?
It's just a horse warrior.
We'll fight our
way right outta here.
Listen to yourself.
How can you be so calm?
It's a horse warrior...
Toppy, please come back!
We could really use
your help right about now.
[MAN] Listen mate...
two humans traveling together?
That's not such an uncommon
sight 'round these parts.
Can't say I've
seen those two.
Alright. Thanks
anyway, kuma.
[distant wincing]
No!
A fluffy piece of tail
like you needs a real man.
[wincing]
[chuckle]
Stop it!
[TOPPY] Let go
of her now, kuma!
What?!
Did you say that?
[TOPPY] Down here, kuma.
Did you not
hear the lady, kuma?
Aww, look at the bear?
Ahhh!
Don't worry, miss. You'll
be alright now, kuma.
Oh, how can I ever repay
you for your kindness?
[MAN] You don't seem to
have changed one bit, bear.
[TOPPY] Yappy...?
[crowd cheering]
[HORSE] Ugh...
[cheering]
What an upset to for
the warriors from Dart!
A top fighter taken out!
In their coliseum debut
these fresh meat
humans have displayed
[ANNOUNCER] that they
are here to fight...
Is it over?
It's over.
Well, bear...
When was the last time
we saw each other, bear?
[TOPPY] Been about
twenty years since we
left our village
together, kuma...
Has time treated
you well, kuma?
[YAPPY] As well as
can be expected, bear.
How about you, bear?
[TOPPY] It's actually been
a little rough, lately, kuma.
[BAR OWNER] Here you go
fellas. One jumbo salmon.
Courtesy of the
woman over there.
♪
Rock!
Paper!
[TOPPY] Kuma!
[YAPPY] Bear!
[TOPPY chuckles]
[YAPPY grunts]
[TOPPY] Just Like
old times, kuma.
[YAPPY] Yeah, just
like old times when you
always win and things
go your way, bear.
[TOPPY] You always
pick rock, kuma.
You know that girl reminded
me of that one time...
[DOGS chuckling]
[TOPPY] That day when
you and I first pledged
to become heroes, kuma.
[YAPPY] Well that was
an entire lifetime ago
but what brings you all
the way out here, bear?
Some companions of mine
I've been traveling with
went missing and I
fear that they've gone
and gotten themselves
captured, kuma.
[YAPPY] Captured? Wait...
Do you have human
companions, bear?
[TOPPY] Yep, kuma.
[YAPPY] Why would you be
traveling with humans, bear?
It's kind of a
long story, kuma.
Besides it's not like
either one of us could ever
turn our backs on a person
who's in trouble, kuma.
You haven't seen them, have you?
A short-tempered brunette girl
and a completely
passive blonde guy, kuma.
No.
[distant cheering]
It seems that a
human's been winning.
It's rare that a
human even makes it
past the first round anymore.
[TOPPY] A human?
Yeah. Reports've been
sayin' that an incredibly
strong girl is
taking warriors down
single-handedly while
her male partner just hides.
Sounds like...
[THUG A] Hey, Yappy!
Old friend...
it seems I have some
business to attend to, bear.
Excuse me barkeep, but do
you know what will happen
to those humans after they've
won their battle, kuma?
I'm not sure, but
since the coliseum
doubles as a prison,
as long as they're
not killed in battle,
they'll most likely
[BAR OWNER] be back
to rot in their cells.
Yappy you've really
outdone yourself this time
with such a great find!
Those two humans are
winning all of their matches.
Not only are the
fights exciting...
but look!
[ANNOUNCER] See all the profits
we've made off of them!
Isn't this more rewarding
than that hero junk
you used to go on about?
[ANNOUNCER] Look... Heroes
save peoples' lives while
you kidnap them and since
you've crossed that line,
you can never go back.
Take all of this money
down and put it in the safe.
[THUG A] Yes, sir!
[GUARD] Hey! You're
not allowed down here--
Aughhh...
[footsteps]
Sorry I'm late, kuma.
Toppy!
Is it really you?
Hmph.
A little bear that
looked just like me, kuma?
Yeah. And at first I
thought it was you.
No way...
It can't be him, kuma.
[TOPPY and YAPPY] Ugh!
Uh...
[BOTH gasp]
[distant footsteps]
[GUARD] Hey, did
you guys hear that?
[YAPPY] Down this way, bear!
These humans here are
trying to escape, bear!
Apprehend them, bear!
Wait, I don't get it, kuma.
Imprison that beastman
while you're at it, bear.
He's the one who
let them out, bear!
Yappy, why?!
[KYRIE] Ugh--
[MORTE] Kyrie!
[TOPPY] Augh!
Old friend...
[ANNOUNCER] You want
that other little bear
to fight with the humans?
Do you honestly think
our patrons will wanna see
a beastman fighting
alongside them?
[YAPPY] I think your customers
will appreciate a battle that's
unlike anything
they've ever seen, bear.
You make a good argument.
Besides I hired you
to find me the
fresh meat...
So what's the backstory?
Why exactly are you sending this
friend of yours into battle?
He's no
friend of mine.
He's an excellent
fighter that bookies
will completely
underestimate, bear.
[ANNOUNCER] Allowing us
to pocket a small fortune...
I have just one other question.
I'm glad you
prevented their escape,
but what exactly were
you doing down there?
My whereabouts isn't
any of your business, bear.
Hm...
[THUG A] You heard right
folks! For the first time ever
humans and a beastman
fighting together!
Odds are fifty to one. Step
on up and place your bets!
But with the three of
us fighting together,
isn't someone
gonna notice we're
the World
Destruction Committee?
That's what
you're worried about?
Well if someone does
notice, we won't only
have to defeat a warrior
but an entire coliseum
full of greedy beastmen.
[TOPPY] I still
don't understand, kuma...
Yappy...
[MORTE] What's to understand?
Your old friend wants to kill us
and he's found a
nice legal way to do it.
[TOPPY] You don't know Yappy!
He's a hero... He'd never...
How can you continue to
just sit there and defend him
like this when he's
the one that turned us in?
You saw with your
own eyes that he was
stealing that bag
of money until he
sold out a friend
to save his own tail.
If that's your
idea of a hero,
you really do belong
on a wanted poster.
Why are you being
so mean, Morte?
It's the truth! Toppy
is free to continue
deluding himself into
believing that the one who
[MORTE] ambushed us
with his band of thugs
and had us locked up here
is still an "old friend."
Who am I to stop him?
But I refuse
to listen to it!
[footsteps]
[GUARD A] Hey, you
three! You're up next!
Hrm...
[cheering]
Yappy... Are you sure
this is the opponent
we should be
starting with?
We won't make any
real money if these three
can't make it past
the initial battle.
Oh, I'm most
certain, bear.
Yeah, take 'em all out, girlie!
[SPECTATOR] Do something
besides cry this time, you wimp!
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentleman!
I present to you
a monumental battle
unlike anything you've ever
witnessed in your lives.
Fresh from their
unexpected winning streak,
the two human challengers
are joined by a beastman
to form... The
Gladiator Dream Team!
Let's see how long
they last facing the
warrior-devouring Sand Worm!
Sand Worm?! Where at?
[ALL] Ahhh!
[SAND WORM growl]
[coughing]
[panicking]
[gasp and heavy breathing]
Wow! And the Sand Worm's
assault just keeps coming!
[TOPPY] Uh!
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[YAPPY] Hmph.
Hyaaah!
[SAND WORM growls]
Incredible!
What an upset...!
[ANNOUNCER] Our challengers come
from behind to take the win!
Hm, hm, hm, hm.
Toppy!
You saved us, Toppy!
[MORTE and KYRIE] Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] Do you think our
dream team is warmed up yet?
Up next in our battle series,
a warrior who has taken out
countless gladiators
with his death swing!
It's the Minotaur Holstein!
Wait! We're stuck
in a battle series?!
Yappy, how far will you go to
ensure that we're dead, kuma?
He's coming!
[bellows]
[screaming] I-I don't wanna die!
[grunting]
[screaming]
[KYRIE] Ugh!
[MINOTAUR HOLSTEIN grunts]
[TOPPY struggling]
Toppy!
[MINOTAUR HOLSTEIN
and TOPPY struggling]
♪
[YAPPY chuckles]
Do you remember
me from yesterday?
That little bear's
the one who saved me.
Leave me alone, bear.
Uh. What do you mean?
[WOMAN] Aren't you
going to help him?
[MINOTAUR HOLSTEIN
and TOPPY struggling]
How can you walk away
and not help your friend?
[TOPPY] Kuma...!
I'm begging you, sir. Please,
you just have to save him.
Why should I?
Huh?
What makes that
little bear so much
more special
than me, bear?
[YAPPY] The truth is, before he
stepped in and saved the day,
I had planned on
being your hero.
He's not the
only hero, bear!
[gasps]
So why save him?
Tell me that, bear.
[cheering]
Dumb cow!
Try this!
[TOPPY] Mmm-ughhh!
[crowd cheering]
[YAPPY] Toppy...
Why is it always you, bear?
Are you two okay, kuma?
Yeah, we're fine.
How are you feeling
after taking on
that minotaur?
There's no need to
worry about me, kuma.
What?! Has he lost his mind?!
On the other hand...
this is too good an
opportunity to pass up!
Hey! Go gather up the
bets and bring them to me.
[ANNOUNCER] If you thought
that was all we had,
you're in for a real treat!
Now for your viewing pleasure...
a hate-fueled grudge match
between two fellow baby bears!
So you've decided to
try and kill us yourself?
Just tell me
one thing, Yappy.
When we vowed to become
heroes who stood for justice,
were you lying to me
or just yourself, kuma?!
Yappy!
It's my fight, kuma!
[grunting]
[running breaths]
♪
While I was trying to
be a hero as good as you,
I accidentally
killed someone, bear.
[YAPPY] How could
I go on being a hero
after what I had done, bear?
That bird took me in, so
this is my life now, bear!
That's your excuse
for becoming a kidnapper?
Don't make me laugh, kuma.
[YAPPY grunts]
You don't know
how hard it's been.
Things don't
just come to me...
You have no right
to judge my life!
[YAPPY] Bear!
[TOPPY] Kuma!
Huuuh...
Uggghhh!
[TOPPY] Kuma.
[cheering]
What a fight! And
there you have it folks!
A swift punch and
the bear goes down!
[laughing] So much profit...
Yappy...
heroes make mistakes
but how'd it
get this far, kuma?
[grunts]
I'm no hero!
[THUG B] Boss,
something's wrong!
What now?
It's disappeared! All the
money in the safe is gone!
What?!
Money just doesn't
disappear, so where'd it go?!
I-I'm not certain.
Actually boss...
Tell me!
[THUG A] The night when the
prisoners tried to escape,
I saw someone's shadow
near where the safe is kept.
[ANNOUNCER] Who's was it?!
[THUG A] Well, the person's
shadow looked like it
could've been
from a little bear...
But when could a little bear...
[squaks]
[ANNOUNCER] I'm glad you
prevented their escape,
but what exactly were
you doing down there.
My whereabouts isn't
any of your business, bear.
He wouldn't dare...
[laughing and cheering]
[YAPPY] I can never
again be a hero.
[YAPPY] A murderer...
A kidnapper... A thief...
Those are what I've become
and I will accept
the consequences, bear!
The thief is--
[TOPPY] It was me, kuma!
[squaks]
[TOPPY] You have no idea
who you've messed with,
do you, kuma?
I'm the dreaded
Toppy of the World
Destruction Committee, kuma!
Shut your fat mouth!
And I've already taken all your
beloved gambling money, kuma!
The Toppy?
Wait, those three
down there...
[OX SPECTATOR] are the
World Destruction Committee?
[WOLF SPECTATOR] The ones
from the wanted posters
with the huge reward...
Reward?
Reward!
[OX SPECTATOR] Oh yeah!
We're gonna be rich!
What the--?
[CAT SPECTATOR] Go for the
bird! He's got our money!
Help me!
World Destruction...
Why would you--?
Yappy, no matter what
life throws at you,
you'll always be a
hero by standing up
for what you
know is right, kuma.
We have to leave
right now, Toppy!
Come on!
I'll always fight
to be a hero...
No matter what, kuma.
[whimpering]
[crowd yelling]
♪
[KYRIE] It's so...
incredibly hot...!
We finally arrive on
the summer continent.
Unable to make much ground
in the sweltering heat,
we take shelter in a village
run by a kind, old elephant.
A village where
humans and beastmen
live together in harmony.
A place where children can
run freely to laugh and play.
Have we really
found a desert utopia?
Next time on Sands
of Destruction,
"There Are Two
Kinds of Summers."
[MORTE] Toppy, you're
sweating like crazy!
[TOPPY] Well it's not like
I can take off my coat, kuma!