[NADJA] There are
two kinds of power.
[NADJA] Power
that should be used...
and power that
should be left alone.
Generally I disapprove of
full-on contact with the enemy.
[grunts]
Put down your weapons.
Now that we know the Destruct
Code isn't here anymore,
quarreling with the
World Salvation Committee
serves absolutely no purpose.
[GUARD ROBOT]
Cease all violence at once.
[MALE] I should have known...
Your bots can't
accomplish squat
if it isn't spelled
out in a handbook.
What a pain it
is to see you...
my dear old friend.
So it is you.
Eagle Master?
[nervous exhale]
[EAGLE MASTER] Sure has
been a while, hasn't it?
I believe the last time the
two of us saw each other...
was after the
Elephant Master went soft.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER scoffs]
If the head of the
World Salvation Committee
is making a site appearance,
then the situation
must be serious.
Hunh. I just prefer
not to sit behind a desk
pushing a pencil
all day like you.
Let me guess, you're
here for the Destruct Code.
What else would I be here for?
Although... just a quick
glance around tells me
it slipped through your claws.
[EAGLE MASTER] Where'd those
World Destruction Committee
morons run off to?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] If
I knew that I wouldn't be
standing here
talking to you would I?
[grunts]
Alright, fair enough...
Establish a search
radius around the town.
Those idiots couldn't
have gotten very far.
[WSC SOLDIERS] Yes, sir!
[EAGLE MASTER]
We'll be on our way.
[EAGLE MASTER] Lia.
[EAGLE MASTER] You've been
on this mission for how long,
and yet you still haven't
reached your objective.
I was counting on the
dragon blood in your veins
and the matchless power
of your ancient tribe...
but perhaps that
was foolish of me.
I have no excuse.
[EAGLE MASTER]
Same with you, Nadja.
Uh.
There was a time when
I thought very highly
of that intellect you
carry around in your head.
But perhaps this
is all we can expect
from a human-beastman
half-breed like yourself.
Hm. I'm afraid I
also have no excuse.
I'm ordering you
two to stay put for now.
[EAGLE MASTER] As
for the Destruct Code,
I'll go retrieve it myself.
Hmh.
[LIA] Nadja...
What are we gonna do now?
Should we form a plan?
Ah... we'll see.
But you heard what
that stupid bird
had to say back
there, didn't you?!
I won't take
that lying down!
We've been after the
Destruct Code forever.
The last thing we should do
is listen to the Eagle Master!
[LIA] Why are we just
waiting here like idiots?
We should be going after the
World Destruction Committee
on our own.
[NADJA sighs]
Yeah about that...
Lia...
Tell me...
Do you really
believe those three
can actually
destroy the world?
Hold on... Where
is this coming from?
Of course I believe that!
Well, I have my
share of suspicions.
In all this time we've
been chasing them,
they continue to do things
that typical criminals
bent on
destroying the world
would simply
never think of doing.
Time and time again.
♪
[NADJA] I'm having a hard time
wrapping my head around it.
I mean, why are they doing this?
[LIA] Uh! Nadja are
you getting soft on me?
They're the World Destruction
Committee. End of story.
And what's more...
the one I can't stand more than
anybody else is that woman!
[scoffs]
While you are correct,
there is some evidence
that they have done
some things that don't mesh
with the typical world
destruction attitude.
But there's still...
that evil woman!
She's as good as dead.
I'm gonna capture her if
it's the last thing I do!
Wait up, Nadja!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
What will be my next move?
Despite all the
investments I've made
into the army
of clockwork robots,
they still couldn't
keep up with them.
Those three are turning
out to be a stronger
quarry than I
originally thought.
Dragon Valley.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
What did it mean when the
Destruct Code showed us
that scene of Dragon Valley?
Yes, of course...
It all makes sense.
[NADJA] Actually, isn't
your home not too far away
from where we are now?
Right. That way, on the
other side of the desert.
[LIA] You can just
barely make it out.
That is my homeland...
the winter continent.
Although I haven't been back
there in over a hundred years.
Hundred years?
[NADJA] Lia... I just want to
say that I am very aware this
could be an extremely
rude thing to ask a lady...
Well, what is it?
Just spit it out already.
[NADJA] Um, how... old are you?
It's gotta be over three
hundred years or so by now.
It's not really
something I keep track of.
Uh... Three... hundred?
I know what you're
getting at, Nadja.
You thought I was
older didn't you?
Maybe it's because of my
ultra-feminine physique.
Well, uh...
that's not exactly...
Ah... Just forget it.
[NADJA] Now... you
haven't been with the
World Salvation
Committee for long.
[LIA] That's right.
[NADJA] Okay...
but you've been alive
for over three hundred years.
What made you decide to
suddenly join the committee?
[LIA] They say that if
the Destruct Code were to
unleash its power, everything,
both living and dead,
would be reverted
back to sand...
That means myself and my
homeland would be obliterated.
I can't just sit back and
allow a tragedy like that
to happen right under my nose!
I understand... It's so
simplistic, like you.
Then what about you,
Mister Smartypants?
Oh, I value my
life as well.
But I have another
reason for doing this.
The committee is an organization
where ability is rewarded.
And since I have all
the necessary qualities,
there was simply no
reason for me not to join.
Yours is just as
simplistic as mine.
Yes... the result of
a simple calculation.
However... when it comes to the
World Destruction
Committee, the reasoning
[NADJA] becomes
more complicated.
[NADJA] The question being...
do we chase them or not?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
I've heard that your home
isn't far from
where we stand now.
And exactly what business
is that of yours anyways?
Just listen.
It's been percolating
in my mind for awhile.
Snowy cliffs surround
your home, Dragon Valley.
Terrain that's
classified as inhospitable.
It's said anyone
who's not of the
dragon tribe is turned away.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
But if the visitor is
the Destruct Code itself,
who knows what
could potentially happen?
Just what are you getting at?
You saw it, didn't you?
It's undeniable. The
image the Destruct Code
showed us was
there for a reason.
Think about it for a second.
What other reason would
they have to come here
other than the fact the
Destruct Code has led them here?
Which... only means...
Impossible!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] If I were
you, I'd move quickly on this.
You don't want your precious
homeland destroyed now, do you?
[growls] That freakin' woman!
Heh. She is simple-minded.
Really? Talk about
world travelers.
Now you're heading
to the winter continent?
That's right.
[MORTE] This thing had
a reaction stronger than
any I've ever
felt from it before.
And I have a feeling
we'll be nearing
the end of our
voyage any day now.
[AGAN] Well, you
know how I operate.
As long as I'm
getting paid...
Put these on.
What's this?
Come on, have you
guys forgotten already
all the trouble you got into
on the summer continent?
Do you really think
you could survive
in the clothes
you're wearing?
So... how much extra are
these gonna cost us, kuma?
Ah... I see someone's
grown accustomed
to how I do business.
Excuse me, have
you seen my partner?
She's from the
dragon tribe.
[beeping]
Something wrong?
My system identifies you as
a half-human, half-beastman.
I cannot determine
if I am allowed to
communicate with
you. Please advise.
Is that right?
Then let's do it this way.
[NADJA] I will accept vague
information that only answers
a portion of the question.
That should be enough
to bypass your filters.
[ROBOT JANITOR] Understood.
As... you wish...
Proceed with your query.
Have you seen my
partner recently?
I may have seen her...
and I may have
not seen her.
She may have been
heading somewhere.
Then again...
maybe not.
And where was she heading to?
She may have
been heading somewhere
in the direction of
the winter continent.
Then again... maybe not.
Okay then. Where did
the Alligator Master go?
Our Master may
be chasing after
the World Destruction
Committee and he may have
sent the dragon
lady after them.
Then again...
maybe not.
Thank you. I understand.
That will be all.
[beeping]
Hm...?
Hey, Pengui.
[PENGUIN] Mm?
Walrus...
Hey, what's on your mind?
Who made these
footprints?
Ah... Just some
folks traveling by...
Some humans
and a beastman.
In all my years living
out here I've never seen
such an odd group
passing through.
Hmmm.
[WALRUS] They're not heading
for Dragon Valley, are they?
[PENGUIN] Yeah...
I tried to stop them
but they wouldn't hear it.
They just kept blathering on
and on about them having to.
I hope they get some
sense in them and turn around
and before they run
afoul of dragon tribe.
Euh!
[LIA] About those
travelers you saw...
You're gonna tell me
everything you know about them!
[PENGUIN and WALRUS yell]
[KYRIE] Morte...
Can't we just take...
take a quick break?
Would you quit
whining? If we stop now,
we'll all be ice statues
before the sun goes down.
I know that...
But we don't even know
where we're going.
What about that, huh?
That penguin told us
this was the right way.
Okay, that is true. But
just because one penguin
told us to go this way
doesn't mean we have to
follow his
word to the T...
Come on, aren't you gonna
back me up here, Toppy?
[TOPPY] Ugh!
Uh, uh, uh!
Hey... Toppy,
don't tell me...
you're about to go into
hibernation right now.
What are you
talking about, kuma?
It's not like I'm some bear
that needs to sleep all winter!
I'm losing my mind here!
[TOPPY] Kuma, kuma, ku...
[KYRIE] What's with him?
He's obsessed with
claiming he's not a bear
when he obviously is.
♪
[yawns]
[KYRIE] This place
reminds me of a graveyard.
I've seen one of these before.
Stop where you are!
[gasps]
[LIA] This hallowed
ground is property owned
by the dragon tribe!
[LIA] Who do
you think you are
trespassing on our territory?
I don't know...
Why don't you try
figuring it out yourself?
Whoa, hold on, Morte!
Knock it off already!
The last thing we want
to do is make her mad!
You're annoying me.
And besides, isn't it
a little late for that?
Are you crazy?
You don't want to
[KYRIE] get in a
fight on her home turf!
[LIA] And you...
You filthy woman...
All that world
destruction nonsense!
You obviously don't get it.
If you were to
destroy the world,
you and your friends
wouldn't even be alive!
[MORTE] What about you?
The ridiculous world
salvation you fight for...
Do you really believe
in that nonsense?
[LIA] Ugh! Don't
call it ridiculous.
[MORTE] Saving a world where
the only standard of living
is beastmen ruling over
humans is beyond ridiculous.
It should be a crime!
And if you can't
understand that logic...
then you're more
stupid than I thought.
If you study the
way society works,
you'll see it's a system
that's best for everyone.
Just look back
at the historical--
Morte, what
did you just do?!
Would you shut up already?
I am so sick of this.
Women who try
to push their values
onto everyone
else even when they...
[gasps]
I can see now that it
was just plain stupid of me
to try and reason with you.
Yes, it appears so.
[wimpers]
Go to hell!
♪
[power yell]
Damn you... world
destruction wench!
A snot-nosed little
brat like yourself...
What the hell would you
even know about any of this?
Nice one!
How dare you call me "brat."
[LIA power yell]
Oh no! Toppy, this
isn't looking good.
At this rate we...
Come on! Toppy wake up!
If you keep stuffing
honey down my throat,
I'm gonna get
blimp fat, kuma.
Are you talking in
your sleep again?!
You're not
making any sense!
You're nothing more
than a loose cannon.
Have you considered
the consequences
of destroying the world?
People like you
rely on force alone
to get what you want.
So don't lecture me!
I don't want to hear it.
Step back and listen
to what you're saying
instead of acting so smug!
[KYRIE grunting]
[yawns]
Are you awake? Toppy?
There are two
kind of bears, kuma.
Huh?
[TOPPY] Strong
omnivorous bears...
and strict carnivorous bears.
Bears who live in the arctic
regions typically rely on
seals for their primary
source of sus...
Why are you
telling me this now?
I don't need
to know that!
[LIA growling]
[MORTE] Ughhh...!
[struggling]
Just give up. It's over.
[gasps]
[NADJA] Lia!
You have to get away
from that ledge! Right now!
Nadja! What're you doing here?
[LIA acreams]
[LIA struggling]
What in the world
was that sound, kuma?
♪
Oh, no...
Lia!
[struggling]
What the hell...
is that alligator up to?
Lia!
I've spotted it!
Fan out! And don't
come back without
the Destruct Code, got it?
Oh no! They've found it!
We gotta hurry.
They're trying to
steal the Destruct Code, kuma!
[MORTE] Almost there!
We can get it!
[ALL yell]
♪
Oh no! We're right on the
edge! We're gonna fall!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER chuckles]
I must admit...
you three are about
as lucky as they come.
You see... now I hold the
awe-inspiring power of
the Destruct Code. Too bad.
Looks like your luck's changed.
[chuckles]
[laughing]
[TOPPY] We've been knocked
down to the bottom of a steep,
dark ravine, kuma.
As we try to retrieve
the Destruct Code, we make
our way through a cave.
However, anyone
who steps foot inside
is drawn into a dream world.
For this cave is actually
the Labyrinth
of Memories, kuma!
[KYRIE] I told you, boss.
I'm wiping it down.
[TOPPY] You're wiping
what down, kuma?
Next time on
Sands of Destruction,
"There are Two Kinds of Pasts."
[MORTE] Lotsa
sand... everywhere.
[TOPPY] Lots
of sandy underwear?
What're you
talking about, kuma?