[AGAN] There are two kinds
of smugglers in this world...
Those who transport goods,
and those who smuggle hearts.
Me, I don't much
care what's in the hold.
As long as there's
a little money in it,
I'll smuggle anything at all.
Anything. No matter
how dangerous it is.
[sand whale calls]
[TOPPY] Remind me how we
got in this mess, kuma?!
Why don't you ask
your friend, Morte?
She's the one who wanted
to try sand whale in a can!
Shut up, this isn't my fault!
[sand whale calls]
[ALL scream]
I didn't think I'd
see them again so soon.
Figured they had enough of the
Sand Sea on their last trip.
I guess it's true some
people just never learn.
So... I'm gonna go out on
a limb and say you folks
are headed toward the
autumn continent, too.
And as luck would have
it, I happen to have
a few goods on board that
I'm taking in that direction.
It only makes
sense for me to make sure
you get there, don't you think?
Well, we can't
afford to pay you.
We're broke, kuma.
I guess I'd be willing
to let you work it off.
The deck and the cabins could
really use a thorough cleaning.
Come to think of it,
the kitchen has been
pretty filthy lately.
So how about it? You get
those places cleaned up
before we get to
the autumn continent
and you don't have
to pay me a thing.
Really? It's a lucky
thing we're not afraid
of a little hard work!
Hold on. Since when do
you speak for all of us?
It's the World Salvation
Committee, kuma.
Come on! Shouldn't
you start firing at them?
If this was a warship
I probably would,
but this is
a cargo vessel.
We don't really carry too many
anti-torpedo weapons on board.
[chuckling]
You know you don't
stand a chance against us,
you dirty, smuggling dogs!
[SUB CAPTAIN] Now hand
over the goods quietly
and nobody gets hurt!
They wouldn't be
here if they weren't
looking for something,
kuma, but it sure isn't us.
I've seen that mark.
It's for the Golden Lions.
[SUB CAPTAIN] I'm running out
of patience, so get a move on
with those goods or
we'll put a torpedo square
in the hull of your
pathetic little ship!
[SUB CAPTAIN] Wait a minute...
That's the World
Destruction Committee!
[chuckles] Well, look at that!
I'm killing two sand
whales with one torpedo!
What a great day!
The subarenine crew
has just captured
the World
Destruction Committee.
They happened to
be traveling aboard
an unlucky smuggler's
ship at the time.
They must have been
trying to make their way
to the autumn continent.
I can't help but be
a little disappointed
that you and I didn't
capture them first.
The subarenine received
an anonymous tip that
the Golden Lions would
be trying to smuggle
some goods onto
the autumn continent...
They're they were attempting
to seize those goods
before they reached
their final destination.
Why does any
of that matter?
It could give us a hint as
to who leaked the information.
[NADJA] It's just a hunch.
Anyways, I think it would
be best if we recovered
The Destruct Code
from the suberanine
as quickly as possible.
♪
So, what do the
two three of you
know about the
Golden Lions?
That they're a meaningless
resistance group.
[chuckles] Meaningless, huh?
I guess that's not
completely inaccurate.
Mind telling us
why you were smuggling
such dangerous
goods, kuma?
[TOPPY] Are you a member
of the resistance too, kuma?
No, I don't have anything
to do with those guys.
Like I said before,
I don't care what the
work is as long
as it pays enough.
Even so... once I
take on a job I always
see it through to the very end.
It's the only code I live by.
I've never taken on cargo I
couldn't deliver... until now.
Hope that means you
have a plan, kuma.
[KYRIE] Help!
[WSC SOLDIER A] What's with
all the yelling in there?
C'mon, knock it off!
[KYRIE] Please, please, help me!
We'll try to keep it down!
[alarm ringing]
I'm sorry, sir.
The World Destruction Committee
has escaped from the brig!
Have they? Well, it
isn't like they've
got anywhere
they can run, right?
Captain! There's a
sand ship dead ahead
that's coming
right for us!
Huh?
Trying to steal
my glory, is that it?
We'll see about that! Submerge!
What idiots. Let's go.
We're submerging. We're
gonna be trapped in here!
I'd be careful around
those if I were you.
The fact that you took
those crates on as cargo
[NADJA] tells me you have
no idea what's inside.
[AGAN] What are
you talking about?
[AGAN] I'm a smuggler. We're
not known for being picky
about what goods we move...
if the price is right.
[NADJA] Good, because the
weaponry is only a cover.
Here, look.
[ticking]
Is that a...?
You mean you're
smuggling a bomb, kuma?
Yes. I had assumed they
might try something like this.
You saw this
coming? How?
It's not really surprising.
The Golden Lions are
known for their strategy.
All they had to do was find
a smuggler foolish enough
to accept their cargo,
tip off the beastmen,
then wait for them to
confiscate the goods and then...
Kaboom.
Okay, but was the "foolish"
thing really necessary?
I didn't know that
they were so... evil.
Is there any reason
that we haven't gotten
rid of the
bomb already?
Kyrie's right, we've
got to surface now, kuma!
[SUB CAPTAIN] Not so fast!
You're not going anywhere!
These people are my hostages.
And this is my haul.
So don't think a bunch of
fancy lies will convince
me to hand them over.
[NADJA] Hm. Perish the thought.
Don't just stand there,
what am I paying you for?
Get over there and capture the
World Destruction Committee!
[WSC SOLDIERS grunt]
What do you think
we should do?
Guess we don't
have much choice.
Now it's up to us to
try to diffuse this bomb.
[NADJA] Uhhh...!
Oh no!
I think it's
about to blow!
[TOPPY] Run for
your lives, kuma!
♪
[NADJA] Lia, what are
you doing?! Hurry up!
[SUB CAPTAIN] Hey, let
us in! This isn't funny!
[WSC SOLDIER] Run!
Save yourselves!
[SUB CAPTAIN]
Wait! Don't leave me!
[ALL gasp]
[KYRIE] Uh!
[struggling]
Kyrie!
[gasping]
No good. Get the
hatch off of him!
[MORTE] We don't
have much time!
[struggling]
He doesn't seem
to be breathing.
Does anybody know CPR?
Hey, don't look at me!
I wouldn't even
know where to start!
It's your idea, you do it.
I would try, but I
can't. I don't know how.
What are you all
looking at me for?
I'm not the one who
suggested we save this guy!
Guess it's up to me then, kuma.
[MORTE] Toppy!
[AGAN] The bear.
All right, kid.
Time to save your life.
[heavy inhale]
[heavy exhales]
[KYRIE muffled] Uh.
Toppy! What in the
heck was that for?!
Oh, please!
Don't flatter yourself!
I was just doing CPR!
Kyrie!
Lia!
[TOPPY] Over here! Quick!
We've gotta
get out of here!
I think we'll be safe in
here for the time being.
But what about
Kyrie and the rest?
They managed to get
behind another one of
the hatches
just in time.
They're all
probably okay.
[NADJA] We're here.
Where's that?
She's there...
[NADJA] Lia! Are you all right?
I was a little shaken
up, but I'm okay.
I'm with the World
Destruction Committee kid and--
the bear.
I'm not a stinkin' bear, kuma!
I'm glad to hear it.
Everyone is
fine on our end, too.
[rumble]
[sand whale call]
It would appear that
we've finally reached
the bottom
of the Sand Sea.
Well, let's head to the surface.
Not yet. The engine
still isn't responding.
Any chance at
resurfacing we might have had
was probably lost
during that explosion.
Are you trying to tell me
we're trapped at the bottom
of the Sand Sea
with no way out?
[metal creaking]
If we don't come up
with some kind of plan soon,
the weight of that sand
is going to crush us, kuma!
That's only if we don't use
up all our air before then.
I guess You're going to
have to call for some help.
But if you tell anybody
who we are, you're dead!
I don't have any
means of communication.
And even if I did,
there's no one who could
get to us in time, much
less do anything to help.
What do you mean by that?
The subarenine is a
fairly recent development
created by the
Clock Town engineers.
So recent that
we're aboard the only
subarenine in the
entire world right now.
[KYRIE] Hey, I've got an idea!
Why don't we just swim out?
That's the absolute
dumbest thing I've ever heard!
We're under millions
of tons of sand.
We'd all be crushed the
second we opened the door.
Still... there must
be something we can do.
I think it's safe to assume
that none of us want to
die down here, so why don't
we call a truce alright.
Isn't there any way
to escape, like an
emergency escape vessel?
There isn't anything
that sophisticated.
What was the plan when
something like this happened.
We were supposed
to prevent it before
something like
this ever happened.
I wonder how far away
from the surface we are.
I bet we can make it up to
the top if we hold our breath!
Oh! Toppy, why don't
you hold on to my neck
and breathe into my
mouth like you did before,
and that way I'll have enough
air to get to the surface!
You are not using me
as an oxygen tank, kuma!
Wait! I've got an
even better idea!
We'll grab that toilet bowl
I can use it as a helmet
and there'll be some air
trapped inside so I can
breathe normally all the way
to the top! It's foolproof!
I already told you
you'd be crushed
as soon as you
opened the hatch!
Are you that stupid
or are you deaf?!
Uh. I'm sorry...
I didn't mean it.
[NADJA] The cabin where
the explosion occurred is in
the stern of the ship, but
the bow, where the engine
is located, didn't
sustain any damage at all.
So if the controls
are the only thing
preventing us from
being able to surface...
then our best bet
would be finding the
engine room and
restarting it manually.
Okay, but how
are we supposed to
get there in the first place?
All the passageways are
completely flooded with sand.
[NADJA] If we can reach
this duct, we have a chance.
It might work if that
wasn't a ventilation duct.
No way any of us
are fitting in there.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
They're treating me like
some pathetic regular bear,
[TOPPY] not with the
respect a full-blooded
dwarf bear deserves, kuma!
[KYRIE] Do you think
Toppy will be okay?
♪
[TOPPY struggling]
Now we just have
to pray that the duct
doesn't get
flooded with sand.
It'll be alright. We did
the right thing by putting
our faith in
that little bear.
[TOPPY] I'm not a bear, kuma!
He made it through!
[TOPPY] It was tough, but
I made it to the engine room.
[NADJA] Good. Now follow
the instructions I gave you
and see if you can
restart the engine.
You can count on me, kuma.
This is never gonna work, kuma!
[MORTE] What's
the problem, Toppy?
[TOPPY] The fuel
tank ruptured, kuma!
Looks like all
the fuel leaked out
and now it's
completely empty, kuma!
Well I guess that means
we're out of options.
There's nothing left
to do but sit back
and wait to get
swallowed up by the sand.
Please forgive
my optimism, but if
the World Destruction Committee
were to perish today...
then the World
Salvation Committee would
have no reason
to exist anymore.
Mutual annihilation
would certainly make
for a convenient end.
Don't forget about
the foolish smuggler
who'd be annihilated, too.
Come to think of it...
this voyage will be the
second time in my career
I wasn't able to get my cargo
where it was supposed to go.
The other was a
year ago, but I wasn't
transporting goods;
just a message.
I remember that the
client was a member of
the Golden Lions.
But the kid was far too
young to be a part
of the resistance.
Now that one was tough.
[AGAN] The kid told me
he wanted me to pass along
a very important
message to his sister,
who at the time was living
by herself in their hometown.
"I'm sorry for making
you worry," he said.
"I promise I'll
be back someday.
But right now, I have to
go and change the world.
So until I do,
please wait for me."
Then he ran off with
one of his companions
before I even got to
ask him his sister's name.
[AGAN] He did
say this, though...
"She may be strong-willed,
and she keeps her
true feelings very
guarded... but deep down,
she's an incredibly
gracious person."
I've always wondered what
happened to that poor kid.
I see you haven't
given up, have you?
You promised to
deliver that message
to the boy's sister,
and I won't let you die before
you fulfill that promise!
It's useless. If there's
no fuel left in the tank,
nothing you can
do is going to work.
There may not be
any fuel in the tank,
but there is a small
chance that there's
some fuel in the engine itself,
and it might be just enough
to move us a little bit.
[NADJA] Even if you're right
and we can move "a little bit,"
we're still at the
bottom of the Sand Sea.
Without the ability to
surface, either the sand
or the lack of oxygen is
going to kill us eventually.
♪
Hm.
[distant sand whale calls]
Something of an incredible size
is making contact with our hull.
It couldn't be another
subarenine, could it?
You said this was the
only vessel like it
in the entire world!
No, it's not a subarenine.
I know that sound.
We've got a sand whale!
Uh...
Okay, Toppy. Go ahead
and start up the engine
and we'll see how much
we can get out of it.
It doesn't have to be enough
to make it to the surface,
we just have to move forward!
Right! You got it, kuma!
♪
Here we go!
Sand whales find
their prey by sound,
and they swallow it whole
with the sand around it.
[AGAN] Then once they've
eaten, they expel the sand!
[sand whale call]
♪
[ALL screaming]
[ALL groan]
[AGAN] All right! We made it!
It's the autumn continent!
This is a
miracle, kuma!
Miracles don't have
anything to do with it.
It was simply
another twist of fate.
[laughing]
So what's next, huh?
Do you still plan
on arresting us?
Morte, be quiet!
Not yet. I think for the moment
our truce will remain in effect.
Nadja!
[NADJA] Farewell.
I suppose it's too
much to ask for them
to keep that truce
indefinitely, kuma.
Now that that's all settled,
I guess I should
be heading out.
What? What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
Hm...
Just happy to have
completed another
one of my missions successfully.
[KYRIE] Life on campus is
full of changing leaves,
baked potatoes, and young love.
At Toshigara, the university
on the autumn continent,
humans and beastmen live and
study together, side by side.
But why is Morte
acting so strange?
Find out next time
on Sands of Destruction,
"There Are Two
Kinds of Autumns."
I dunno, Toppy.
What do you think?
[TOPPY] A woman's heart is
like the autumn sky, kuma.
[MORTE] What?
[TOPPY] Or was that's
a man's heart, kuma?
[KYRIE] What?!