[MORTE] Hey, wait for me!
Ahhh!
[KYRIE] Ahhh!
[MORTE yelling]
[KYRIE] Morte!
Wasting your energy
yelling won't help anybody,
so try to cool off, okay?
If we don't keep moving
we'll freeze to death
and you're telling
me to cool off?
[TOPPY] I think I
have an idea, kuma!
Hey, did you see
where Toppy went?
No. He's probably
buried under the snow.
[TOPPY] Kyrie,
you're going to have to
wear your artificial
ears again...
Then go to the human
village and stir up
trouble with the locals, kuma.
After that, Morte will
show up wearing her
artificial ears and
beat you up, kuma.
Trust me. I know beastmen.
This is the only
way we'll be able...
He's talking
in his sleep again?
[MORTE] Okay, Toppy.
Rise and shine!
Kuma?
[KYRIE] So you're
sure this passage leads
to the top of the cliff?
[TOPPY] Even if it doesn't,
it's not as cold in here
as it is outside, kuma.
And I'm not so
sleepy anymore, kuma.
[MORTE] This cave...
It doesn't look like
it was naturally
formed, does it?
It looks like some
kind of ancient ruins.
[KYRIE yells]
Aaahhh!
Mummy!
What's it doing here?
[MORTE] And why
are there so many?
There aren't any
wounds on them, kuma.
It almost looks like all of them
died of natural causes, kuma.
[KYRIE] Great... I guess
that means they all died
after getting trapped in here.
Then we oughta get
moving if we don't wanna
end up the same way. Let's go.
♪
[MORTE] What happened?
Is this...?
[KYRIE] Morte?
[TOPPY] What's wrong, kuma?
♪
[MORTE] It is!
[PRIEST] It's time for
you to say goodbye, my dear.
[PAST MORTE] Reve!
[PAST MORTE crying]
[MORTE] No...
[MORTE] No!
[KYRIE] Wait!
[TOPPY] You okay, kuma?
[KYRIE] Morte!
I know this place.
[TOPPY] Kyrie?
What's wrong with you? Ah!
What's going on?
How'd I end up
back in my home town, kuma?
I knew I recognized this
place. I'd know it anywhere!
It's where I was
working when I met Morte!
I remember seeing this
notice and asking if
I could have a job.
[PAST KYRIE chuckles]
Are you the
owner, sir?
Sorry, kid, but we don't
open for another hour.
Oh, you want the job!
Well, why didn't
you say so?
You have had
experience working in
a restaurant
kitchen, haven't you?
Yes! My specialty
is a sand whale dish
that'll knock your socks off!
I remember this.
It's exactly what happened
the first day I
got to this town!
How is all of this happening?
[EAGLE MASTER] Where did you
go after you left clock town?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Hm?
Have you located
those idiots from the
World Destruction Committee?
My mechanical army has
been in constant pursuit,
but I'm afraid
that they recently
lost track of them
on the winter continent,
somewhere in
the Dragon Valley.
And what about
the Destruct Code?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
It's still missing,
just like our three
fugitives. But...
is this not an ideal outcome?
Both the Destruct Code
and the members of
the World Destruction
Committee are buried under
several tons of snow
on the winter continent.
There is absolutely
no chance they will
escape the Dragon Valley alive.
[EAGLE MASTER] But where
is the meaning in that?
"Meaning"? What difference does
"meaning" make
when your objective
of saving the world is attained?
The Destruct Code is worthless
unless it is in my hands.
While I do not intend
to destroy the world...
others must know that I have
the power to do so if I please.
Only then will
it be meaningful.
How inane...
In that case, go to the Dragon
Valley and find it yourself.
But I suggest you be careful.
You don't want to wander into
the Labyrinth of Memories.
[MORTE] This place...
It's my home... but how?
[WSC SOLDIER] Forgive
me for asking, sir,
but this "Labyrinth of
Memories," what's it like?
Ah. The so-called
"Labyrinth of Memories."
[EAGLE MASTER] Once
someone enters the Labyrinth,
there's no way out but death.
They become lost in a dream
world of their own memories...
where they wander hopelessly
until they wither and die.
[PRIEST] His coffin has been
laid to rest inside the temple.
You should go to see him.
Which reminds me, I found
this among his things.
Can you tell me if
it belonged to him?
[MORTE shaky gasp]
[PRIEST] I see.
Whether or not it was his,
Reve kept it with
him to the very end.
It must have been quite
important to him. Here.
I'm sure he would have
wanted you to have it.
I know this place...
This is where they
brought Reve's coffin.
It's where I first came in
contact with the Destruct Code.
[MORTE gasps]
[MAN] You're Reve's
sister, aren't you?
[MAN] My name is Karna. I'm
a member of the Golden Lions.
[KARNA] Look I'm sorry,
but I have to ask...
Have you ever heard the
stories of the Destruct Code?
I don't even know what that is.
[KARNA] The Destruct Code
is a legendary treasure
that's believed to have the
power to destroy the world.
And they say that
the day before he died,
your brother, Reve, told
some guys in his squad
that he'd found it.
If you find anything...
anything unusual in his
possessions and you're
not sure about what it is,
[KARNA] I'd appreciate if
you'd let me know personally.
[REVE] Let's rest here.
[PAST MORTE] Seriously?
That must be
embarrassing.
You're supposed to
be the big, tough boy.
Listen, sis...
There's something that
I need to talk
to you about.
What's that?
[REVE] It's no big deal, but...
I-I know you're gonna be
against this because you're
my big sister and everything.
But... I just think it's
time for you to know that
I'm going to be joining
the Golden Lions soon.
[gasps]
You don't know what
you're talking about!
Do you have any idea
how dangerous that is?
Well, sometimes
people have to do some
dangerous things if they
want to change the world!
Reve...
But why you?
Because we
can't let things
go on like
this anymore.
I want to help
free all humans
from this beastman
oppression!
[MORTE] No!
Please, Reve, don't!
You don't have to do it!
Please, Reve, stay here!
The world doesn't
have to change!
[MORTE] I'm begging you,
Reve. Stay here with me!
Stop him! You've
gotta keep him from
joining the Golden
Lions. You have to!
If you can keep
Reve here with you,
he'll never have to die!
He can live! He can!
You just have to stop him!
[MORTE] Stop him...
Please, stop him...
[crying]
[MORTE] Huh?
[MAN] Nnghhh... Uh.
Dad...? Is that you?
[TOPPY] There are two
kinds of pasts, kuma.
The kind you want to forget,
and the kind you
won't ever forget.
[YAPPY] Well, look
what we have here, bear!
[TOPPY] Yappy!
We've been waiting
for you, bear.
[YAPPY] Come on,
let's go, bear!
[TOPPY] Uh, alright.
[cawing]
♪
[giggles]
[MORTE'S DAD] Hm.
[YOUNG MORTE giggles]
[CAFÉ OWNER]
I understand. You've been
moving around a lot lately.
That's perfectly natural
for a boy your age.
You've got to get out there
and experience the world
and all it has to offer while
you still have the chance.
[CAFÉ OWNER] I traveled a
bit myself when I was younger.
So, tell me... where were you
before you ended up here?
[PAST KYRIE] Oh! Well, uh...
[CAFÉ OWNER] Oh, nevermind...
Forget I asked.
You don't have to tell
me if you don't want to.
I suppose everybody
has a thing or two
they wouldn't
mind keeping a secret.
What the--?
[KYRIE] Where am I?
♪
[MORTE'S DAD] Aughhh...
Father...! Why do I have
to see all these things again?
[YOUNG MORTE]
Daddy! Please don't go!
Daddy...! Daddy!
[MORTE] Stop this! I don't
want to see any more!
[YOUNG REVE crying]
[BOTH sobbing]
[MORTE] No more... no more...
[MORTE] Make it stop!
[YOUNG REVE] Come on, sis!
Dinner's on the table!
[YOUNG REVE] It's your
favorite... sand jellyfish.
[YOUNG REVE] Hurry up, let's go!
Hold on a second. Not so fast!
[MORTE'S DAD] Look
who finally made it!
It's about time!
Your poor Dad's
starving to death!
This is a special
dinner, we finally got some
fish from the Sand Sea.
[MORTE] Mom! Dad!
[MORTE'S MOM] Go ahead...
There's plenty to eat.
Everything looks
great, huh, sis?
[REVE] Let's dig in!
[MORTE] Right. Dig in.
[YOUNG REVE] Here, sis!
Ahhh...!
Delicious!
Well, you don't have to
act so surprised about it.
Your mom's never made a
bad meal in her whole life!
[MORTE'S DAD, MOM,
and YOUNG REVE laugh]
[ALL laugh]
[GOLDEN LION A] Now that
we've got these explosives,
we can finally give the
beastmen a decent fight!
[GOLDEN LION B] Hey,
you over there! Hurry up!
Yeah, yeah. I'm hurrying.
[REVE] Need some help?
No thanks. I've got it.
It may not be easy,
but it's good work.
You wouldn't believe
how much these guys
are paying me for this.
So you're that smuggler?
I've been known to
smuggle a thing or two
if the price is right.
Oh, that's great.
[REVE] Because there's
something I was hoping I could
get you to transport for me.
[AGAN] Hm? What is it?
Weapons? Food?
Just a message.
A message?
[REVE] Yeah, my sister
is living all by herself
back in our village,
and there's something I
need you to tell her for me.
Say... Say that I'm
sorry for making her worry.
Tell her... I promise
I'll make it home safe...
right after I've
changed the world.
And until then...
tell her... to wait for me.
[KYRIE] So it was
Morte's little brother!
[KARNA] Reve,
come here, will ya?
'Kay! Thanks
a lot, Mister!
Sure.
[TOPPY] So I looked him square
in the eye and I said to him...
"Maybe you ought
to look at what's
on your head
first, kuma!"
That's right. I don't think
I'm gonna forget the look
that stupid bear
had on his face
for as long as
I live, bear!
[ALL laugh]
So loud!
I know.
[laughing]
If you ladies don't
stop looking at me,
you're gonna
make me blush, kuma!
[BOTH] Hmph!
[TOPPY] 'Scuse me, but I
couldn't help noticing you
could use a spoonful
of my sweet honey, kuma.
[GIRL BEAR] Keep
your honey to yourself!
[TOPPY] Kuma!
[TOPPY] Ouch, kuma.
Where am I?
What just happened?
And where did that cute
little dwarf bear girl go?
For a dream, that
sure seemed real, kuma...
Oh, no!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Why is
the reaction energy so weak?
Is it possible that this is
not the true Destruct Code?
That would certainly
explain things.
[GOLDEN LION A] The
beastmen are attacking!
[GOLDEN LION B]
Grab your weapons!
[GOLDEN LIONS yelling]
[GOLDEN LION C] Don't
let them get any closer!
It's him.
Hmmm?
♪
[GOLDEN LION B]
Hurry, put out that fire!
[KYRIE] The fire's
reaching the gunpowder!
Get back! You're
not gonna make it!
[KYRIE] Run away!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER grunts]
♪
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
What is this?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] I see.
[KYRIE] Reve.
[KYRIE'S footsteps]
Ah!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] So
this little runt...
is the Destruct Code?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
Wait. There are two of them?
But... what does this mean?
[TOPPY] Kyrie! Kyrie!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Now what?
[TOPPY] You've
gotta wake up, kuma!
[TOPPY] Kyrie!
[KYRIE] Toppy.
Where's Morte's brother?
You were just
having a dream, kuma.
A dream?
We must have
accidentally walked into
the Labyrinth
of Memories, kuma.
Labyrinth of
Memories. What is that?
I once heard an old legend
about a mysterious cave
hidden somewhere in
Dragon Valley that
can actually make
people see things that
happened to them
in their past.
I think we may have
found that cave, kuma.
It shows you your past?
All those mummies of
beastmen and humans
[TOPPY] we saw lying
around back there...
they were travelers
who got caught up in their
own memories and
couldn't escape, kuma.
So they withered away
and died here, kuma!
[KYRIE] But I've never
been to that place before.
And I've definitely
never met Morte's brother.
Where's Morte?
I haven't seen
her anywhere.
She must be somewhere
else in the cave
reliving her own
memories, kuma!
And if we don't find her
soon, there's gonna be
another mummy
down here, kuma!
[YOUNG MORTE]
And then Reve started
stuffing nuts into his mouth.
I told him to slow down,
but he kept eating!
He could barely move
after that, he ate so many!
Oh yeah? Why don't you tell
Mom and Dad how many you ate?
[KYRIE and TOPPY]
Morte! Morte! Morte!
It sounds like somebody's
calling for you, sis.
[TOPPY] Morte!
Don't you think
you should answer them?
[YOUNG MORTE] No...
I just want to stay here.
I don't want to leave here.
I wanna stay here with you!
[KYRIE] Morte!
Ahhh!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
The Destruct Code.
Those two identical runts...
and the Labyrinth of Memories.
I understand.
So that's what it was.
Found her, kuma!
You've got to pull
yourself together, kuma!
Morte, no!
[TOPPY] Wake up, kuma!
[KYRIE] Morte!
Why won't you leave me alone?
I don't wanna go with you!
It's all right.
You'll be fine.
[rumble]
[MORTE'S DAD] It looks
like it's time for us
to say goodbye, sweetheart.
I won't! I want to
stay here with you!
And my mom and my brother!
Don't make me go.
I think you
may have already
figured out
what's happening.
We only exist in
your memories.
I'm sorry, but
none of this is real.
I know it's not!
But the real world
isn't worth saving!
Nobody cares!
Why can't I stay with my
family if it makes me happy?
Why can't I just
stay here with you?
[KYRIE] Morte!
[TOPPY] Morte!
This is bad!
Whoa, are
you okay, kuma?
Yeah.
Let's get out of here!
There isn't much time, kuma!
Can't you hear
your friends trying
desperately to save
your life, Morte?
[KYRIE and TOPPY
heavy breathing]
[MORTE'S DAD] In your travels
with them, I'm sure you
came across lots
of different people,
some of them struggling
just to stay alive.
The real world
is their world too.
And I don't think
they're the only ones
who think it's worth saving.
We're going to
be crushed before
she even wakes up! Hurry!
[KYRIE and TOPPY scream]
[MORTE'S DAD] The world
is constantly changing.
If things are bad right
now, it just takes time
and work to change
fix them, right?
As long as there
are people like them.
The cave's collapsing.
Don't stop, kuma!
What makes you think
that I'd want to stop?!
[MORTE'S DAD] Or even us.
You could say
your mother and I
have changed the world
in a very important way.
[MORTE'S DAD] The proof
is right in front of me.
Huh?
[BOTH chuckle]
You're the proof, Morte.
I am?
That's right.
[MORTE'S DAD] Now it's your
turn to try to change the world.
And you will.
[MORTE'S MOM] We want you
to live your real life, Morte.
Please, for us.
[MORTE'S DAD] Go create
a new future, sweetheart.
One where everybody
in the world can be happy.
[shaky gasp]
[MORTE] Dad, Mom! Wait!
[REVE] I'm sorry I didn't
keep my promise, sis.
But I feel a whole
lot better knowing
you're not alone anymore.
I'm so happy that
you're doing okay.
Reve, wait! Mom... Dad...
Please, don't leave me!
[TOPPY] Move, kuma!
[grunts]
We're safe, kuma.
[KYRIE and TOPPY] Huh?
[KYRIE] We're outside!
Morte! You're
finally awake, kuma!
I'm glad you made it.
Kyrie... Toppy...
[EAGLE MASTER]
We've found you at last.
You World Destruction
Committee scoundrels.
Now then... give
me the Destruct Code
and I might let you live!
♪
[MORTE] My family
is never coming back.
[TOPPY] That cute
dwarf bear girl isn't
coming back either, kuma.
[KYRIE] The past
doesn't ever come back.
The Destruct Code
will be deciphered.
The world we live
in is falling apart.
What fate awaits us now?
Next time on
Sands of Destruction,
"There Are Two
Kinds of Futures."
[MORTE] Will it be destruction?
[KYRIE] Will it be salvation?
[TOPPY] Will it be a bear?
[MORTE] That would be
three futures, not two.
[TOPPY] Kuma.