[TOPPY] There are
two... kinds of summers...
[MORTE] So friggin' hot...
Oh my gods...
No stupid place...
should be this hot.
Did you expect...
something different...?
We are on...
the summer... continent...
There are, kuma...
are two kinds of
summers, kuma...
[MORTE] Well spit it out then...
What are... the two
kinds of summers...? Huh?
[TOPPY] Uh... I don't
remember... kuma...
Do you know...
If... we're...
Kyrie!
[MORTE] Wake up!
[TOPPY] We need
to get him some water
and out of the sun, kuma!
[AGAN] Are you serious?
You three again?
[MORTE] Agan?
Why're you here? Are
you following us, kuma?
I travel where the jobs
take me, so I'm here
delivering medicine to the
charity hospital in town.
Charity hospital?
[AGAN] If you want,
I'd be happy to
give you guys a
lift into town...
Well... for the
right price I'd be happy.
Where am I?
Ah! Who are you?!
[ELEPHANT] Easy there
son. I don't want you
to get all worked up again.
You're quite safe here.
Don't worry, I'm the
director of this
charity hospital.
[MORTE] I can't imagine a
good reason why a beastman
would set up a
charity hospital.
[AGAN] Are you always
so incredibly negative?
That hospital director
is a kind soul who's
obviously done a lot for
the people of this village.
Sorry to have
kept you waiting.
How's Kyrie?
[TOPPY] Kyrie!
[KYRIE] Toppy...!
Morte...! Agan?
[TOPPY] Are you
feeling better...?
You really gave Morte
and me a scare, kuma!
[ELEPHANT] Your
friend here suffered from
a mild case of heat exhaustion.
It's not all that uncommon with
newcomers to our continent.
After he rehydrates
and gets a full--
[chuckles]
[KYRIE] Morte...
The real problem
with the patient is that
he's a pathetic weakling.
He simply has no
physical endurance.
[KYRIE] What?!
[ELEPHANT chuckles]
Well, I hope that all of
you learn from Kyrie's mistake
and start taking the summer
continent sun seriously.
I've got more deliveries
but remember if you're
gonna travel without water
at least do it at night...
See ya.
Does that guy ever
stop working, kuma?
[ELEPHANT] And what do the
two of you plan on doing?
You're welcome to
stay in this village
while your friend
here recuperates.
Please feel free to
make yourselves at home.
I have to admit that
I was pretty nervous,
with it being my
first solo surgery and all
[HUMAN DOCTOR] but, uh, I think
it went pretty well actually...
[CHILD] Hey you guys...!
It's rare to see a place
where humans and beastman
can live together
in such harmony, kuma.
I've only been here
for a short time,
but I've seen no
place like it...
Everyone that lives in
this village shares in
[MAN] the hospital director's
philosophy of peace and unity.
[CHILD B] Wow...!
It's a little bear!
[CHILD A] It's a bear!
It's a bear!
[CHILD B] I wanna pet him!
[CHILD A] Me first!
[MAN] And here's your room.
There's a bed for each of you.
If you need anything
else, just ask.
[TOPPY] I can't
remember the last time
I slept in a real bed, kuma!
Hey, where did
you just come from?
Sir, what is your job?
Don't call him
sir! He's a bear!
[TOPPY] Don't call
me a bear, kuma!
[KIDS scream]
[MAN] Sorry if
they bothered you.
They were just exicted
to make a new friend
to play with. You
see, they live here
in the hospital and
never get to leave...
Those three are orphans.
[MAN] Their families were
killed in the wars between
humans and beastman
and now live here
out of the hospital
director's kindness...
"When it comes to
the preciousness of life,
human and beastmen
are the same."
That's the hospital
director's philosophy.
Seems he's quite the
noble optimist, kuma.
I wonder if the director
himself truly believes it.
[ELEPHANT] So then...
it's just as I suspected.
[snoring]
[TOPPY] Kuma...
♪
[crying]
[KYRIE] Morte...
You were crying out while you
were sleeping. Are you okay?
Yeah. I guess... I guess
I was having a bad dream.
[KYRIE] It's doing it again.
Why start glowing now?
Come to think of it,
lately, it's almost as if
you've been the
one making it react.
How could I
make it react?
I didn't do anything...
[KYRIE] Maybe it
was that dream...
Is the Destruct
Code giving me that
same dream to
show me something?
[MORTE] What dream?
[KYRIE] I've had this
dream already once before.
There's a guy who died...
but I've never
seen him before...
And Morte you're there crying.
[KYRIE] It's a young man lying
peacefully in a small coffin...
almost asleep...
with a single flower.
Evening.. I'm just
making my final rounds...
Don't keep him up all night.
He needs rest. Hmhmm.
He already does
so much, and still,
he stays up late
to check on everyone.
[TOPPY] There are
two kinds of summers...
Summers to remember...
and summers to forget, kuma.
[BOY] Excuse me, but if
you're a cute little bear...
why don't you have
a cute little voice?
[TOPPY] It's none
of your business, kuma!
[BOY] Aw! He
just said, "kuma!"
[GIRL] That's so
cute! Can I pet you?
[TOPPY] No!
Stop... touching me!
[KIDS laughing]
What part of no,
don't you get, kuma?
It's too hot
for this, kuma!
Get your sweaty
fingers off of me, kuma!
Toppy... I never knew
you were so good with kids!
There are two kinds
of little bears, kuma.
Don't mock me, kuma!
Do you know him?
Are you and Toppy the
very bestest of friends?
Sir, what is your job?
Uh... well in our group...
I guess I'm... the chef?
You know how to cook?
[ALL] How cool!
[NADJA] Ugggh...
This heat is killing me...
[LIA] Are you sure... that the
World Destruction Committee
is on the summer continent?
[NADJA] Yes I'm
completely positive...
My analysis shows
within a shadow of--
[LIA] Nadja!
[MAN] Is everything
alright over there?
I was wondering
when you'd wake up...
It's pretty foolish to be
traveling without any shade.
Oh well. It's
not like foreigners
ever know any better.
Pardon me sir, but
we are members of
the World
Salvation Committee.
[ICE CREAM MAN] I don't
know if that's supposed to
mean something to me...
Ha ha!
But it's you two who
needed the salvation,
which don't say
much of your committee.
I truly appreciate
your assistance
in our time of despair...
[LIA] But shut your beak
or I'll blow it right off!
[NADJA] Forgive her...
We came to your continent
in pursuit of the World
Destruction Committee.
[NADJA] You haven't seen any
of these individuals, perchance?
[ICE CREAM MAN] Well
sure! I've seen those three!
There are enough vegetable
sandwiches for everyone!
I really hope that
you all like them!
[cheering and laughing]
[ELEPHANT] I can't thank you
enough for all the great work
that you and your
friends have been doing.
The children have really
taken a liking to you,
[ELEPHANT] they're
having so much fun.
A world where humans
and beastmen could
live in harmony... It's
been my lifelong dream
[ELEPHANT] to make a world
like that into reality.
[MORTE] It's a
wonderful thought...
But I just cannot
believe a single word
that comes out of your mouth.
[GIRL] Doc Elephant!
[ANNE] You like it?
Aren't the flowers pretty?
Toppy made it for me himself!
Have a sandwich!
They are so delicious.
Kyrie made them
with fresh vegetables.
Come quick doc, before the
sandwiches are all gone!
Yeah. Follow me!
[chuckling] Alright
then. Coming!
[KIDS laughing and talking]
[MAN] Those are
most definitely them,
but they couldn't possibly be...
But they are. They're the
World Destruction Committee.
Sure they look like
them, but I can't imagine
any one of those good
people to be criminals.
Ugh! If you make excuses for
them, you're just a guilty--
Forgive us. We are still
not accustomed to the heat
and it seems to have
gone directly to her head.
Regardless...
we do not wish to cause
any trouble for you...
We're merely asking
you to be a good citizen
and hand over these criminals.
[ELEPHANT] Thank you
for waiting for me.
[MAN] Director...
I can take it
from here, Rigolet.
[ELEPHANT] Thank you for
entertaining our guests.
Uh. It's you...
Rigolet, you may
take leave now.
I truly appreciate you
taking care of them.
[RIGOLET] You're welcome,
director... Take care.
Would you both step
into my office to talk.
Kuma!
[BOY] Catch the ball with
your hands, not your face!
[NADJA] You are
him, aren't you?
[BOY] Rigolet!
Please throw us the ball!
A true legend...
Known only as "The King
of Desert Slaughter."
"The King of
Desert Slaughter."
It's been a very
long time since anyone
has known me
by that name.
[NADJA] So if
you went into hiding,
why open a charity hospital?
[BOY] Catch!
[ELEPHANT] To be honest, I
have a top secret experiment
that is currently underway.
Top secret?
[ELEPHANT] Yes.
[ELEPHANT] And that is why
I cannot consciously hand over
those three criminals to you.
So I need you to give me
a little more time
and then my research
will finally be complete!
Toppy.
[MORTE] Kyrie, wake up!
Toppy's gone missing.
Kyrie!
[MORTE] But why would
the kids be missing too?
[distant scraping]
[MORTE] That awful
sound... I knew it...
I knew that director
was hiding something...
[distant scraping]
[MORTE] The sound's
coming from in there...
[scraping]
Uh, Morte what's wrong?
[gasps]
Looks like the
jig's up you guys.
Jig is up?
What're you doing?
It's the middle of the night.
Well tomorrow is
Doc Elephant's bithday!
We've baked him
a big tasty cake
as a birthday surprise!
You two are adults!
I'd expect this
from kids but not you!
I'm going back to bed!
Wait, Morte. Sorry.
We didn't wake you
'cause we thought
you'd tattle.
Idiots!
[distant thud]
Rigolet!
[MORTE] Shouldn't
the director be untied
for his birthday party?
He can't blow out the candle.
[ELEPHANT] You're still here?!
You were supposed
to get away hours ago!
Get away?
Two agents from the
World Salvation Committee
came to the village
today looking for you.
[MORTE] You
sold us out the WSC?!
I made up a story
to get them to leave
and buy you all
enough time to escape.
That's why I sent word for you
three to get out of here...
You never gave them
the message, did you?
Why should I aide
known criminals?
The World Destruction
Committee deserves to be
locked away or even killed!
It was you!
You've been working
with them all along!
You're wrong! I've only
been working for myself.
Now get out! I need
to make sure that
when he dies he suffers
just like my family!
What are you talking about?
My life...!
This monster will feel
all the agony I've
lived with for years.
One fully sharpened knife
to cut great
big slices of cake!
[KIDS] Hooray!
Morte was pretty angry.
Think she'll go and
tell the director, kuma?
[KYRIE] She's not that spiteful,
but if you want, I'll check!
Be right back!
[RIGOLET] I've dedicated
my life to finding him
and enacting my revenge.
When I heard a beastman
who resembled him
was running a hospital,
I had to come find
out if it was the king.
The king?
At first, his façade
even had me fooled.
[RIGOLET] This beastman
who went out of his way
to do so much
good for people...
he couldn't possibly
be the monster
that I've been searching for.
But then today...
[RIGOLET] I overheard
your friends from the
World Salvation
Committee identify him...
And he confessed!
[RIGOLET] After
spending countless hours
convincing myself otherwise...
it turns out he was right
under my nose the entire time!
I've finally found you,
The King of Desert Slaughter!
What you say is true...
I was The King
of Desert Slaughter,
but I've dedicated the rest of
my life to atone for my sins.
But no amount of
atonement could ever
make up for all of the
suffering I have caused.
Atonement...?
That's why you started
this charity hospital.
Correct. To try and save as
many lives as I had taken away.
Do you honestly think
that your little hospital
can make up for
all that you've done?
You slaughtered
my entire village
then burned it to the ground!
[RIGOLET] You killed
my wife and...!
My little girl! It was you!
Go on... Tell me
the consequences of
my actions and then kill me...
I don't deserve your mercy.
[MORTE laughing]
[TOPPY] What could be
taking Kyrie so long, kuma?
She must've
taken him hostage!
It's midnight, so
it's already his birthday,
let's take him his cake before
she spoils the surprise, kuma.
[MORTE laughing]
[RIGOLET] Why are
you laughing at me?
Are my family's deaths
some sort of sick joke to you?
[laughing]
The opposite actually.
The same thing happened to me.
[MORTE] So feel free
to kill him if you like.
My family was killed
in the fighting between
the beastmen
and humans as well.
Just after that, my brother
joined the Golden Lions
resistance group for
the chance to fight back.
[MORTE] He truly believed
they could defeat the beastmen
and win back
humanity's freedom.
He was just a child,
fueled by anger and revenge...
until he was killed too.
[KYRIE] Could it be
that the boy in my dream...
is Morte's younger brother?
It seems humans and
beastmen will just disregard
the casualties and
keep on fighting forever.
A world like
that shouldn't exist...
I wish... that the entire
world would just die off.
Then let's end it now.
We'll start with him...
then destroy the world.
[MORTE] Kyrie?
[RIGOLET and KYRIE struggling]
Happy birthday, Doc Elephant!
Morte! Stop the kids!
What's going on here, kuma?
[RIGOLET] Let go of me!
[ELEPHANT]
Children, get out now!
[RIGOLET and KYRIE struggling]
Stop it! If I'm the one you
want, leave them alone!
[TOPPY] Everyone get
out of here now, kuma!
Damn you!
Stay away! I'll drop the flame!
[GIRL] No, please don't!
[TOPPY] Ahhh!
[KYRIE] Oh no!
Doc Elephant never
did anything wrong!
Leave him alone!
Anyone who wants to
hurt our Doc Elephant
will first have to
go through me first!
[ELEPHANT] Children...
I love you.
♪
[RIGOLET crying]
[KYRIE] Oh no.
[screams]
[KIDS scream]
Anne! Bel! Seth! Get out!
♪
Doc Elephant's still in there!
I'll go!
No, you can't. The fire
is spreading too rapidly.
[screaming]
[KIDS] Doc Elephant!
[ELEPHANT] Do
not worry children.
It will take more
than a fire to stop me.
[KYRIE] He's alive.
[KYRIE] Hey Morte, wait up!
Where are you going?
[MORTE] If you two were
to remain in this village,
you could both go back
to living normal lives.
You'll be safe here.
It's me the World Salvation
Committee is after anyway.
What's the
matter, Kyrie?
Aren't you going
to follow her, kuma?
You must go
after her.
But I...
I'm not suggesting
that you have to
go and destroy the world with
her, son, on the contrary.
I believe in my
heart that if you
continue with her
on this journey,
[ELEPHANT] perhaps
you will be the one
who is able to
finally heal her pain.
If I can heal my soul,
then she can heal her heart.
[KYRIE] Morte...
A true hero's life should
never be a sedentary one, kuma.
[KYRIE] Hey Morte, wait for us!
[TOPPY] We're coming with, kuma!
[MORTE] I thought I told
you morons to stay there!
[chuckles]
[KYRIE] Don't play cool,
you would've missed us!
[MORTE] I already
miss the quiet.
[TOPPY] She's definitely
trying to play it cool, kuma.
[MORTE] Stop following me!
[KYRIE] Just admit it!
[TOPPY] You totally
need us, kuma!
[TOPPY] We stop
at a town inn where
we hear some strange rumors...
Apparently the World
Destruction Committee is
already in town and causing
all kinds of problems.
Imposters are calling themselves
the World
Destruction Committee?!
How dare they try to tarnish
my hero reputation, kuma!
Next time on
Sands of Destruction,
"There Are Two
Kinds of Companions."
[KYRIE] Morte, do you
want to tell him or should I?
[MORTE] It really
should be you that does it.
[KYRIE] Uh... Toppy. Being in
the World Destruction Committee
already tarnishes
your hero reputation.