[KYRIE] There are
two kinds of humans.
Those who look
good with fake ears on
and those who look
like complete fools.
Hey! Don't you mock me!
And besides you're not
even saying it right, kuma.
No one cares, Toppy...
I just want to know
why I have to wear them.
They're so stupid.
[KYRIE] Because
this is a beastmen town.
[KYRIE] And because
a good disguise
will ensure your safety.
[grunts]
[KYRIE] Actually those fake ears
look pretty good on you, Morte.
In fact, I think
it's such a good look,
you should consider working
it into your everyday wardrobe.
[TOPPY] Oh please.
It's not right for her
to wear those things, kuma.
[LIA] Nadja, are you sure
the spring continent is
the right place for
us to be looking...?
I realize it's the
closest continent to Bonak
but it doesn't seem like
the logical place to go.
[NADJA] Normally a group
would steer clear of
the spring continent
and head straight for
the summer or
fall continent instead.
But that trio is
craftier than most people.
[NADJA] I think they assumed
we'd expect them to do
the opposite of the opposite
of what we'd normally expect,
meaning they did
the opposite of that.
I think you're
over-analyzing this a bit...
If I can speak frankly,
I honestly don't think
[LIA] they're as intelligent
as you make them sound.
Even if they're
not smart enough to
come up with that plan...
[NADJA] there's still...
the will of the Destruct Code.
[chatter]
[TOPPY] Well then,
what's the plan?
Where are we headed, kuma?
And where exactly
do we plan to be
at the end of our journey, kuma?
I already told you...
[MORTE] Everything I know
is within the Destruct Code.
It alone, is the only
thing that can lead us
to the path of
world destruction.
[TOPPY] So what you're saying
is all the trouble we've
been through recently
can be traced back...
to the guidance of
that stupid ball, kuma?
[grunt]
Look at it this way, at
least we made the right call
coming to the
spring continent...
I mean, if you have to travel,
you can't find anywhere
in the world that's as
warm and tranquil as this.
What are you acting
so laid back for...?
Have you forgotten the
fact that we're fugitives?
[TOPPY] And the only
reason that's true
is because of you, kuma!
I was saying...
I've always been told the
spring continent is the place
to go to see cherry trees.
But I... haven't
seen even one yet...
I was hoping the
three of us could
have a nice picnic
under one of them.
Excuse me folks.
Are you traveling beastmen?
[KYRIE] Oh!
Why yes, sir. We are!
[OLD FROG] Unfortunately
all the cherry trees
in this town
have been removed.
Huh?
[OLD FROG] Cherry
trees are known to
suck the lifeblood of beastmen,
and use it to make
their flowers bloom.
It's an old
legend that continues
to live on in this town.
It's just
superstition, kuma...
Back where I'm from
we had a saying that
the ground beneath a
cherry tree in full bloom
was filled with the
bodies of beastmen, kuma.
That's true but it's just
something people say...
And believe me,
no one around here
ever took these legends
to actually be fact.
But then... the Frog Master
became Lord of the town
and started
spreading the word that
cherry trees were
unlucky for society,
so he ordered them
all to be cut down.
Mmm.
[FROG MINION] My Lord!
We have just
received word that
the World Salvation
Committee will be arriving
to port tonight in Vito.
[FROG MINION] They
will be heading here
early tomorrow morning.
The World Salvation
Committee, eh?
[FROG MASTER]
I would rather them not
stir up trouble
in my territory.
[KYRIE] Man, I really
had my hopes up
for a picnic under
the cherry trees.
How many times do
I have to tell you?
We're not here to
gaze at all the flowers.
Hm...?
[MORTE] What the--?
What's wrong with you?
[KYRIE] Look!
Uh...
Cherry blossom!
[TOPPY] Over here, kuma!
[chuckles]
[TOPPY] What's
this one doing here
when all the others
were cut down, kuma?
[KYRIE] Who cares? Besides,
the important thing is that
we can have our picnic now!
[KYRIE] Oh come on, Morte.
Stop making that face, will ya?
Let's try to have
some fun for a change?
[KYRIE] I mean, think
about it for a second.
The only reason we're
on the spring continent
is because the Destruct
Code led us here.
And you never know, the
Destruct Code just might
have a thing for cherry
blossoms like I do.
[MORTE] I seriously doubt that.
So this sucks the lifeblood
from beastmen, kuma?
[TOPPY] That's impossible.
It's just a wives-tale, kuma.
[screams]
[KYRIE laughing]
No way! Did I
actually scare you, Toppy?
I ain't scared
of nothing, kuma...!
Now stop playing
games up there, kuma!
[KYRIE] Ow! Ahhh!
Oh man. I hope
I didn't make it angry!
[TOPPY] Get away
from me with that, kuma.
[gasp]
[FROG CITIZEN]
What have you done?!
Now's when you fess up and
tell him what you did, kuma.
Yeah, I suppose
your right.
[KYRIE] I'm sorry
but I broke this branch!
It was an accident!
Oh... bye.
[gasping]
Heh. Hi...
[KYRIE] I kinda broke this.
Huh... That's
enough truth, kuma.
Something's not quite
right in this town, kuma.
[TOPPY] I say we hurry
up, get what we need,
and bug outta here, kuma.
[KYRIE] Yeah.
[birds cawing]
A human?
Wait... Who're you?
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to frighten you.
But I made a promise
to someone that
I would meet them here
under the cherry tree.
What the heck's
going on here, kuma?
It's just a guess but
maybe everyone actually
believes that tree sucks
away their lifeblood.
Hey, look over there.
It looks like
they're still open.
[KYRIE] Excuse me, do you
have any food for sale?
[FROG CITIZEN]
Ahhh! Stay away from me!
[AGAN] Right this way!
[chuckles]
[AGAN] I've got a wide
selection of rare foods
from around the globe.
[KYRIE] It's you!
[TOPPY] Agan
the smuggler, kuma?!
So we meet again.
Who'da thunk it?
I guess since you're
here you were able to
escape from the pleasure
ship in one piece.
No way! Is that a
branch from the cherry tree?
The last one standing in town?
[KYRIE] It sure is.
[AGAN gasp]
You know something
about it, kuma?
[KYRIE] Yeah what's the big
deal with this thing anyway...?
Everyone runs off all
frantic the minute they see it.
[AGAN] So you're the one
that broke the branch off?
Yeah... I was
climbing the tree...
I mean it was just
an accident, you know.
That tree's got a name.
It's called the
Cursed Cherry Tree,
and every single beastman in
town is scared to death of it.
[TOPPY] The Cursed Cherry Tree?
Right. Apparently anyone
who tries to cut it down
or break off a branch
or harm it in any way
will be cursed with
one unfortunate event
after another
until the end of time.
[AGAN] That's why it
is the only cherry tree
left standing in
the entire village.
No one dares try to cut
it down or even go near it.
Why didn't anyone
tell us about this curse?
Oh don't take it
so seriously, kuma.
It's just one of those silly
local legends, right, kuma?
[chuckles]
Well... Personally I
think it's all a crock.
[AGAN] If it's food
you're looking for
it's right over there.
[KYRIE] Oh, thanks!
But I'm sure you've heard
the saying before yourself.
There's no smoke
without fire...
It wouldn't hurt
to be careful, right?
That's not a bad idea.
As long as we're cautious...
[KYRIE] Ahhh!
[TOPPY grunting]
[KYRIE struggling]
[KYRIE] Help!
Help me! Toppy, please!
[KYRIE] We're in
big trouble, Morte!
We found out this
cherry tree is cursed!
What do you think we should do?
Huh?
I... just... told you...!
The tree is cursed meaning
anyone who breaks off a branch
like I did, will have a
curse set upon them for life!
Oh... kay...
[KYRIE panicking]
[TOPPY shudders]
We're getting sucked in
deeper and deeper, kuma!
You don't have to get
all worked up about it.
[KYRIE] Huh?
Who is this guy?
The name's Jade. And
it's a pleasure to meet you.
I live in the
forest near here.
In case you're wondering
I'm the one who
spread the rumor throughout
town about the curse.
[JADE] It's just a
made up story so you can
rest assured you'll be fine.
Trust me, you're
anything but cursed.
Why would you go
around spreading rumors
and conjecture like that, kuma?
In order to protect this tree...
[JADE] from the
axes of the beastmen.
[LIA] Excuse me, human. We
have some questions for you.
Sorry. Do I know you two?
It's unlikely. We are with
the World Salvation Committee.
Tell me, have you
seen any members of
the World Destruction
Committee lately?
[AGAN] If you want
information from me
you're gonna
have to pay for it...
Or you can buy something.
Doesn't matter to me.
Do you have even
the faintest idea
who it is you are speaking to?
Okay... One dried
sand shark fin.
We'll take it to
go and, of course...
[NADJA] you can keep the change.
Now that you mention it
I did run into them here.
But you may want to think twice
about getting close to them...
See those fools
broke a branch off
the cursed cherry tree.
Cursed cherry tree?
Yup. And if you don't
tread carefully you may
wind up getting some of their
bad luck rubbed off on you.
[gasp]
I'm not too
concerned about it.
Curses, bad luck, and all these
other unscientific theories
are simply cheap fiction
used to scare the ignorant.
[JADE] Well, you see
the truth is I promised to
meet someone under this same
cherry tree some time ago.
[TOPPY] A woman, kuma?
Yes. It was my fiancé.
Many years ago we lived
quietly in a little village
on the outskirts of Bonak.
But then one day
the beastmen came
and set fire to
our whole village.
[JADE] All of the
men from my village
fought bravely to save it,
but we had no hope of
defeating the beastmen.
So just before the final charge,
the two of us made a promise,
that if we both
made it out alive,
we would make our way
to the spring continent
and meet on a hill outside
of a town near water...
underneath a
beautiful cherry tree.
What then...?
Were you able to reunite with
your girlfriend after all?
[JADE] 'Fraid not. And
that is exactly why I can
never allow this
cherry tree to disappear.
[KYRIE crying]
But... today was a new day...
and I will continue
to wait for her.
[TOPPY] Well, I'm glad
that's settled, kuma.
It's a good thing
that curses and bad luck
don't exist in our world, kuma.
[KYRIE] It's not a
good thing at all, Toppy!
And why's that, kuma?
[KYRIE] Because at this
point everyone in town knows
I broke off a branch
from the cherry tree.
And if nothing
bad happens to me,
they're going to figure
out that the curse is a lie.
And then everything Jade
worked for will be for nothing.
[MORTE] I think
it's a little too soon
to say that nothing
bad will happen to you.
[MORTE] You never know
when some unspeakable,
terrifying misfortune
could befall us,
catching us all by surprise.
Wait... What are
you saying, kuma?
Do you really believe in
that sort of thing, Morte?
Hm. I guess I do.
But we know for a fact the curse
of the cherry
tree is just a lie.
And there's nothing
we can do about it, kuma.
Yeah, but Toppy...
now the cherry tree is
in danger of being cut down.
It's just...
[KYRIE] There must be
something we can do.
[TOPPY] Aaah! Gross! Bird
poop has just landed on me...!
Eeek, oww...! Now a big potted
plant just fell on my head!
What the heck
is this, kuma?
Whaddaya mean?
It's a script?
[TOPPY] You spent all
night thinking of ways to
fix things, kuma, and this
is all you came up with?
Yeah... And since the
curse doesn't actually exist
then all we can do is
make it up from scratch.
First, we have to do it
in front of a big crowd.
[KYRIE] Oh, and it'll
be much more effective
if the Frog Master sees it too.
So, our best bet is to
do it along the boulevard
that passes right in front
of the Lord's Mansion.
So once we get there, bird poop
will land on your
head, okay Toppy?
And I'll be the one
dropping it, by the way.
Then at that point
you'll start screaming
your head off and
make a huge scene.
The Frog Master will hear
it and rush outside to see
what the commotion is all
about, which is right when
the potted plant
will fall on your head.
Which again, I will
be dropping myself.
[TOPPY] Now wait
just a second, kuma!
How come I'm the
only one who gets
hurt in this
whole plan, kuma?
'Cause it's the
only way it'll work.
Besides Morte has pretty much
refused to help us at all.
Don't worry.
At the end I'll pretend
to die along with you.
Hm...?
[KYRIE] So you'll start
screaming again and then
make a run towards the canal,
at which point you'll
join up with me and say,
"Let's get out of this
god-forsaken town, kuma!"
Oh, but you won't just
say it, you'll scream it!
Then we'll hop on a boat
we placed there earlier,
but the boat will
have a hole in it...
[TOPPY] I still don't see
why I have to be the one
to go through this
theatrical farce, kuma.
[KYRIE] Geez,
calm down already.
Remember, we're
doing this so Jade can
reunite with the love
of his life someday.
You're not using
real poop, kuma?!
It's got to look realistic or
the people will
never believe it.
Now come on birdie.
Push one out for me.
Hurry up... kuma.
Uh? Uh...!
Something's not right here.
Maybe he doesn't
have to go right now.
[TOPPY] Those two are from the
World Salvation Committee, kuma!
[squaking]
Yes, it worked Toppy!
Now start all the screaming!
Looks like I found them!
[LIA growling]
Now get over here you brat!
Raaahhh!
[TOPPY] Get up and run, kuma!
Ahhh!
Aaahhh!
[LIA screams]
[gasps]
What's this?
Oh my! They're the
ones from yesterday!
Do curses really
exist in our world?
♪
[LIA screams]
[KYRIE] Ahhh!
[growls]
[KYRIE] Toppy! I don't get it!
Why are we running
away from her?!
Because if we
defeated her now...
that script you worked so
hard on will be ruined, kuma!
Woah! Kuma!
[KYRIE] But it's already ruined!
[LIA growls]
This may not be what we
had in mind originally...
[TOPPY] but we can
still make our escape
by pretending to drown, kuma!
Hm?
[KYRIE] Are you sure
this is gonna work?!
[TOPPY] I don't think
she can come after us
in the water, kuma!
Now... find
the perfect spot...
Pretend to drown to death...
[TOPPY] And we'll
be home free, kuma.
[TOPPY] Where'd he
get that boat from, kuma?!
Lia! Get in!
[grunt]
[KYRIE] This isn't good!
Toppy! We need more speed!
We're screwed, kuma!
They're gonna
catch up in no time!
[KYRIE rapid breathing]
[FROG MASTER] What's with all
the commotion?! I want answers!
[snap]
[FROG MASTER] Ribbit...
[FROG MASTER and MINIONS] Ahhh!
[KYRIE] Someone help us!
I should have never
broken off that branch!
Now we're gonna die!
[TOPPY] Throw us
a life line, kuma!
The curse of
the cherry tree is--
[BOTH gasping]
Your plan worked like a charm.
[KYRIE] Yeah I think we
were pretty convincing...
That cherry tree should be safe
from the beastmen from now on.
[JADE] Thank you.
Wow that bridge
collapsing was timed perfectly
but was that just
a coincidence, kuma?
Well it certainly
wasn't the curse
that caused the
bridge to collapse.
[JADE] But I think it is safe to
say a greater force was at work.
[LIA] Are they dead?
[NADJA] No... It looks
like they escaped.
Those two are even slicker
than I made them out to be.
You know... I wonder
how long Jade's been
waiting for his
girlfriend under this tree?
[MORTE] I think...
...it's been decades.
[KYRIE] Decades?
[TOPPY] That's
impossible, kuma.
[MORTE] The war that
Jade told us about...
the one between the beastmen
and the humans in Bonak...
My father told me
about that before he died.
[MORTE] According to my father,
the battle took
place decades ago.
Hm...
While you two were
in town, I decided to
go check out the
story for myself...
I found Jade's house
just on the other side
of that hill over there.
[MORTE] But... I
found Jade's body.
He's been dead for years.
I'm sure he waited day after day
underneath this cherry tree...
in the hopes of seeing his
love again... to no avail.
Then... that means
the Jade we met...
So even after his death,
Jade stood by and protected
this very last cherry
tree while waiting for
his beloved to return, kuma.
I wonder if Jade's
spirit will ever get to
reunite with his
girlfriend one day.
I'm sure that as long as
that cherry tree
continues to bloom...
Then one day the two of
them will be reunited, kuma.
♪
[TOPPY] I get separated
from Kyrie and Morte.
Then end up meeting an
old friend from my past
in a town with a
gigantic coliseum...
It's a reunion between
friends who at one time
vowed we'd become
heroes among heroes.
But as it turns out,
he and I no longer
share the same vision.
Next time on
Sands of Destruction,
"There are Two Kinds of Men."
[MORTE] Why isn't he ending his
sentences with "kuma" anymore?
[KYRIE] Maybe because we're
hearing his inner dialogue.
Kuma.