[YOUNG LIA crying]
Here ya go.
Oh, thank you.
So tell me...
Did you pick it yourself?
[NADJA] Lia... Wake up...
Lia!
[LIA gasps]
Nadja.
Thank goodness...
What a relief that you're
awake. Are you alright?
[LIA wimpers]
[LIA] So... you saved me?
I may be a
half-breed but I'm still
a beastman through and through.
Saving you from
falling to your certain death
was easy enough.
A piece of cake really.
Well thank you.
I guess I owe you one.
[LIA and NADJA chuckle]
[NADJA] I wonder what
the deal is with this cave?
It's very peculiar.
I'm glad we're out of
danger for the time being...
but ever since I got in here
I've been experiencing visions.
I keep seeing distant
memories of people
long gone from my past.
[LIA] That's because this
is the Labyrinth of Memories.
I just saw a vision
of my own past as well.
Something I had
forgotten about years ago.
[SOLDIERS cock guns]
[EAGLE MASTER] I'll be
taking the Destruct Code now
so don't try anything stupid.
Sorry,
we don't have it.
She's telling
the truth, kuma.
The Alligator Master stole
the Destruct Code for himself!
He what?
Looks like the
Alligator Master betrayed
the World Salvation
Committee as well.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Don't listen
to what these peons have to say.
It was you! Damn alligator.
If it's this that you
want it's yours; take it.
[EAGLE MASTER grunts]
In exchange I will
take the three members
of the World Destruction
Committee into custody.
[KYRIE shaky exhales]
[NADJA] Let me get this
straight. You're saying you
met Kyrie over
three-hundred years ago?
[LIA] Right. It was
before I even reached
my hundredth birthday.
I'd been picking
flowers in Dragon Valley
and was heading
home for the day.
I'd been crying
because I fell.
Kyrie had said some nice
things to cheer me up.
But... he looked the
exact same as he does today.
[LIA] Except...
his hair was different.
It was so red it looked
like it was on fire.
So what exactly
does all that mean?
That Kyrie hasn't
aged all these years?
Is it possible he's
a dragon like you?
No way... If he were...
I would have known he
was a dragon right away.
[NADJA] So if he's not, then...
[LIA] He may be a creature
that lives as long as dragons,
but as far as I know,
such a thing doesn't exist.
[NADJA] Hm. Perhaps.
You know what?
We may have been
greatly mistaken about Kyrie.
[distant explosion]
♪
Ahhh!
Huh...?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
Stop this futile resistance
and succumb to me quietly.
Or would you prefer to
not learn about the
secrets of the Destruct Code?
Secrets of the Destruct
Code? What do you know?
A lot. It seems your feeble
minds haven't grasped this yet.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] But
I have unlocked the hidden
constructs that make
up the Destruct Code.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Now...
come with me, human!
Auhhh!
[struggling]
Toppy!
[ALLIGATOR MASTER] Ugh!
Morte! Lets go.
We're out of here, kuma!
We can't leave yet!
I'm not going anywhere
until I have the
Destruct Code back!
Hm-hm!
Huh?
Do not let them get away!
I overheard the
Alligator Master.
What's this about
him knowing secrets
of the Destruct Code, kuma?
I don't know...
But if I had to guess,
I'd say that the Destruct Code
Morte has on her right now
isn't the real
thing, but a decoy!
I hope you're wrong after
all we've been through!
Why else would he come
back with the same device
he had already
stolen from us?
It's the only thing that
makes sense. Think about it.
[MORTE] This is definitely
the real Destruct Code.
I know it is, I can feel it!
Now that we're back inside
the Labyrinth of Memories,
if I can conjure
up that memory again,
I might be able
to figure this out!
What do you mean by
"that memory," kuma?
[KYRIE] The memory I
had of Morte's brother
getting the Destruct Code!
[MORTE] Huh? Wait,
you mean to tell me
that you were there the
day my brother, Reve, died?
Yes, no. Maybe. I don't know.
The thing is I can't
actually remember any of it.
I'm not even sure
if I was really there.
In fact, I'm not sure any of it
actually happened
or not. It's confusing.
Huh?
Eghhh! Gimme that!
[KYRIE] Uh...
[MORTE] Aughhh!
[KYRIE and TOPPY] Ahhh!
[BOTH gasp]
[KYRIE screams]
[GOLDEN LION A] The
beastmen are attacking!
[GOLDEN LION B]
Grab your weapons!
♪
Kyrie!
Reve?
What are you still doing here?
I thought you were supposed
to leave for Tomai by now.
It would have been a
pointless trip anyway.
So I figured, what's
the rush, ya know?
What the heck has
gotten into you, Kyrie?
I just wanted to
find out whether or not
you guys would really
be able to save the world.
I just got curious.
[REVE] Forget all that,
it's dangerous here!
The beastmen found us,
so you better find
a good place to hide!
[KYRIE] Uh...!
Who exactly are you?
[KYRIE RED sighs]
So you still can't remember?
Then in that case...
I'll just tell you.
[KYRIE RED] That black orb
Morte's been carrying around
all this time...
isn't the Destruct Code.
The real Destruct
Code is inside of...
[KYRIE gasping]
[groans]
Morte! Wake up, kuma!
Where are we?
[motorized door opens]
[EAGLE MASTER] It's
about time you woke up.
[TOPPY] Where is Kyrie, kuma?!
[EAGLE MASTER] How should
I know? He's probably buried
under the rubble in that cave.
And if he's still
alive, he's reveling in
the memories of
his happier days.
Now listen...
I need to ask you
something important.
What did he mean by the
secrets of the Destruct Code?
[EAGLE MASTER] What's does
the Alligator Master know?
How are you supposed
to use this thing?
[MORTE] Hmph.
I already told
you, I don't know.
[EAGLE MASTER grunts]
In that case, I'll have
to force it out of you!
[TOPPY] No! Don't do it, kuma!
[KYRIE groaning]
♪
[water drop]
[water dripping]
[water sloshing]
What is it, Lia?
What's wrong?
[LIA] Kyrie...?
I need to ask you...
Is it possible that
you could be the...
[NADJA] Um... I don't
know how to put this...
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
Your hunch is right.
He is the Destruct Code.
[BOTH gasp]
Yes, it took me quite a
while to figure that out.
[KYRIE] What did you
do with Morte and Toppy?
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
They're spending some time
with the Eagle Master.
And right now those
World Salvation Committee
dimwits are trying to
get the girl to confess
all the hidden secrets of
the Destruct Code,
even though the real one
is standing right
in front of me.
Now... time to come with me.
And we will create
a new world together.
Huh?
Not quite. Before
we figure out what to do
with the Destruct Code...
there's the matter of
payback for what
happened to us before.
[ALLIGATOR MASTER]
How dare you stand in my way!
[LIA] If I'm not mistaken,
it was you who betrayed us.
Now get over here, you fool!
[LIA and ALLIGATOR
MASTER screaming]
Good grief...
So, Kyrie...
[LIA and ALLIGATOR
MASTER screaming]
[distant crash]
[WSC SOLDIERS] Huh...?
Kuma?
[EAGLE MASTER] Now... perhaps
this will jog your memory.
[MORTE] Fine then...
But I said before, I don't know!
Heh. Alright,
have it your way.
I prefer it, because
the longer it takes
for you to answer,
the more fun I'll have.
[WSC SOLDIERS] Ahhh!
[EAGLE MASTER] What the...?
[WSC SOLDIER] Ahhh!
What's going on?!
[ALL] Huh?
Huh?
How did you get in here?!
[EAGLE MASTER power yell]
Kyrie.
[KYRIE] Are you two alright?
Kyrie... your hair...
How'd you dye it, kuma?
We'll chat later.
Right now you need to
find a way outta here
as soon as you can.
What? Wait a minute.
[MORTE] The Destruct Code is...
[KYRIE] Morte.
Don't worry about it.
It's not what
you think it is.
What are you
talking about, kuma?
This ball is not
the Destruct Code.
It's really nothing more
than a storage device.
It may be hard to believe...
but I am the Destruct Code.
Huh?
Are you serious, kuma?!
I don't understand.
[KYRIE] During my days
spent traveling the world,
I once visited
the Golden Lions camp.
That is where I
met your brother.
When he told you he had
found the Destruct Code,
he wasn't referring to the orb.
[KYRIE] He was talking
about having met me.
[KYRIE] I got caught
up in the ensuing battle
and ended up losing the orb.
[KYRIE] That is how it
ended up in Reve's coffin...
and eventually found
its way to your hands.
[KYRIE] Having
lost every trace of memory
as to who I was...
I headed for Tomai as
plain ol'... Kyrie Ilnis.
[KYRIE] Shortly thereafter...
I met you, Morte.
[MORTE] That's nuts...
[MORTE] What is this?
[KYRIE] These
are my true memories.
I've walked this planet since
its first day of creation...
tens of thousands of years.
These are the
memories I take with me.
So then... if you're
the Destruct Code...
That means you have the
power to destroy everything?
Destruct should not
be taken literally...
I've been here since the
very beginning of existence,
allowing me the
power to reset the world.
[KYRIE] Whenever someone
comes along who truly believes
in the Destruct Code
and would like nothing more
than to see the world go away,
that's when my power activates.
That man is the Destruct Code.
Take him into custody, alive!
[WSC SOLDIERS grunting]
Kyrie...
[WSC SOLDIERS yell]
[EAGLE MASTER] Aaahhh!
Say goodbye, freak!
[gasps]
[EAGLE MASTER]
Heh, heh, heh... Ahhh...
No wait... Please, don't!
Ahhh!
Amazing...
He is the Destruct Code!
We're finally seeing
Kyrie's true power, kuma!
[KYRIE] When someone hopes
for it strongly enough,
the Destruct Code
becomes active.
Morte believed
in the existence of
the code from the beginning...
and truly wished
for world destruction.
And ever since that day...
the Destruct
Code has been active
and awaiting instructions.
[TOPPY] Wait, not yet, kuma!
[MORTE] Kyrie!
[BOTH gasp]
[NADJA] This must be it...
We are looking upon the
power of the Destruct Code!
[LIA] Watch out! Nadja!
[TOPPY] Kyrie! Stop this, kuma!
Kyrie...
[AGAN] Hey!
[TOPPY] Agan?
I'm trying to deliver some food
and this is what I come across?
What the hell have
you guys done now?!
You again!
[AGAN] If you wanna ride
with me, you've gotta pay up!
[TOPPY] This is not
the time to be haggling.
Now hurry up
and let us on, kuma!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[MORTE] If we don't put a stop
to this soon, the entire world
will be reset into
nothing but a sea of sand!
Isn't that what you've
been wishing for all along?
[MORTE] Is it?
Is this the world I wished for?
♪
[MORTE] Kyrie.
Morte!
[TOPPY] Morte!
[MORTE heavy breathing]
[MORTE] I activated
the Destruct Code.
No, I activated Kyrie.
[MORTE] But is this
the outcome I want?
[MORTE] Do I really
want the world to end?
[MORTE gasps]
[MORTE'S DAD] The world
is constantly changing.
Now it's your turn to
try to change the world.
And you will.
Go create a
new future, sweetheart.
One where everybody
in the world can be happy.
[REVE] But I feel a whole
lot better knowing you're
not alone anymore. I'm so
happy that you're doing okay.
[MORTE crying]
[MORTE] Enough.
The world doesn't have to end.
It's fine just the way it is.
[MORTE] The world is what it is
and I have no
right to destroy it.
[MORTE] So please...
stop this.
[MORTE moans]
Kyrie?
Huh...?
Morte.
♪
[TOPPY] When the gods
created the world...
they also designed
a Destruct Code
capable of bringing
the world to ruin.
They did this so that
if someone believed in
the existence of
the Destruct Code,
and wished to the very
core of their being for
the world to end, the
code would be activated,
resetting time and
space to it's beginnings.
The gods gave both
humans and beastmen alike
this special power,
to do with as they please.
And so... the world was saved.
However, that does not mean
the world had changed at all.
A small yet privileged class
of beastmen still controlled
nearly all the
wealth in the land,
and humanity
was still oppressed.
The Destruct Code
does not possess the power
to change the world.
Instead, we are the ones
who can bring
change to the world.
[TOPPY] There are
two kinds of futures.
A bright, shining
future full of promise,
and a future under
a veil of darkness.
But if a future of
darkness is upon us,
there is nothing to fear, for
hope exists in both futures.
Because the future
continually changes through
the hope of those individuals
brave enough to bring
about that change.
[TOPPY] Kuma.
Hey!
Look at you. A cute little
bear trying to act all cool.
[TOPPY] Don't
call me bear, kuma!
[BOTH laughing]