Okay, good, you're
right on schedule.
Unlike me.
Sorry, I'm running a bit late
because of work.
I'm on my way there now.
My partner's with me.
[NIJO]
Wow. I can't wait!
I've been wanting to meet
your partner for a while!
This is gonna be great.
He said he's looking
forward to meeting you.
What's he wanna meet me for?
It's been a whole year,
he should be focused solely
on his big brother.
Oh, nothing,
Shiori was just saying
he's super excited about it.
[ICHINOSE]
Dude, don't use my first name.
[chuckles]
‐‐[explosion]
‐‐[gasps]
[NIJO screams]
[LUKA]
Hey, what's wrong?!
C'mon, talk to me!
[ICHINOSE]
Luka... look...
[gasps]
The airport!
What do we do?!
[AIRPORT WORKERS giggle]
[ICHINOSE]
That was nine years ago.
It's hard to believe I'm
standing here with the kid
Luka saved that day.
[NANATSUKI whimpers]
[ICHINOSE]
What's wrong, Rookie?
Nothing.
I'm just fine.
Ichinose, Metropolitan Police.
[ICHINOSE] You must be former
Nine officer Taisuke Biwajima.
We'll be transporting
you to headquarters.
Stand up.
I assume you boys
have set me up
with a limousine, then?
I mean, after all,
that's only fair
as I'm an upstanding
citizen risking danger
in service
of society, right?
Oh, an "upstanding
citizen," huh?
You're a sick terrorist bomber.
It'll take at least
a hundred more years
to condition that outta ya!
You should really show me
a little more courtesy.
I'm a very important key
witness in the Warlock trial.
Shut up!
Hey, Ichinose.
‐‐[ICHINOSE growls]
‐‐[BIWAJIMA grunts]
[chuckles]
[BELLEMER] Ichinose's
group has left the airport
and they've gotten on
the Bayshore Route!
[KIRYUIN] It should take
them about 30 minutes
via the Rainbow Bridge.
[BELLEMER]
Some good news there, too.
Traffic restrictions
are in place,
so congestion
shouldn't be an issue.
But do you think
Nanatsuki'll be okay?
I mean, you would think
he'd still have
some baggage about this.
Well, he assured me
that he'd be fine going back.
So I think we should trust him.
To tell you the truth,
I have other concerns.
Hey, are you from
that special unit?
Special Seven?
The thing they organized
just to combat Nine?
And what if we are?
Well, then I
guess I should take
this time to thank you.
[NANATSUKI growls]
[BIWAJIMA]
You see, nine years ago,
there were actually supposed
to be two explosions.
The hope being that
after the first explosion,
police, firefighters,
and reporters
would flock to the scene.
I'm sure you can imagine
how effective a second one
would've been at that point.
I was in charge
of that second bomb,
but I guess Special Seven,
or whatever it's called,
just happened
to stumble upon it!
[chuckles]
I was pretty panicked
at the time, for sure.
[ICHINOSE growls]
But, thanks to that,
I was able to get off with
much lighter charges.
Light enough, in fact,
that there's a good chance
this plea bargain'll
pretty much cancel 'em out.
[ICHINOSE growls]
[FIREMEN murmuring]
Well, thankfully, I think that
should be the last bomb.
I can't believe you went
and found members of Nine
hiding out in the crowd
then actually got them to talk.
Only you, Ichinose.
Glad you're here.
This thing isn't
over yet, though.
There are survivors
being held hostage inside,
but the brass isn't
willing to send in
special forces to help us.
‐‐[phone rings]
‐‐[LUKA] Hmm?
[ICHINOSE]
Your little brother?
[LUKA] Only minor injuries,
he'll be fine.
Let's save the
hostages! Sound good?
Yeah.
[BOY 9A]
Let me go!
[gasps]
Sorry, kid, but I'm
afraid our boss asked me
to bring him one lively brat,
and that brat's gonna be you!
No way! Stop it, let go of me!
Wanna do it the hard way?
‐‐[blow lands]
‐‐[BOY 9A] No...
[BIWAJIMA]
Come on, then!
[BOY 9A]
No!
[NANATSUKI] Um! I'm about
the same age as that kid, there.
Please, I want you to
take me instead, okay?
Looky, here.
I wouldn't expect that
from a kid these days.
You think you're
some kind of hero?
‐‐[NANATSUKI groans]
‐‐You make me sick!
Are you...?
You're that kid from back then.
‐‐Yeah.
‐‐Man, that's crazy!
Is this gonna be okay?
You're not looking for some kind
of long‐game revenge on me
or anything, are you?
[ICHINOSE]
You son of a...
I wouldn't do that.
I'm an officer.
That's the whole
reason I'm here.
So I'll keep you safe.
Because that's my job!
Heh. Well, I guess we'll see.
[chuckles]
That's enough of the chit‐chat.
Looks like we've
got some company.
[NIJO grunts]
Here they come!
[AKANE gasps]
C'mon, you gotta
keep your head down!
[NINE MEMBER 9A] All those
who would harm Master Warlock...
...must die!
Well, damn!
So I guess they are nine!
[gasps]
[groaning]
[AKANE]
What?! Nijo?
Wasn't that our turn?
Yeah, I couldn't take it.
[growls
[ICHINOSE]
Bellemer!
I want you to
check something ASAP.
Up ahead!
Nijo!
What happened to
those traffic restrictions?
Go, Nijo! Floor it!
[NIJO]
Huh?!
[ICHINOSE] Just jam on that
gas pedal as hard as you can!
[AKANE]
Why the gas pedal?!
[ICHINOSE gasps]
[ICHINOSE]
Once you pass the next sign,
turn the wheel hard to the left!
Wait, but left is...
Nijo!
I know!
[BOTH scream]
Look, guys, what's the big idea?
You should really just
be thankful you're still alive.
So, you're telling me
you didn't know
there was an abandoned
factory here?
No, of course I didn't.
But I did get Bellemer
to look it up.
I would really
appreciate more thorough
and courteous
directions next time.
Sure, I'll submit 'em
in writing with Boss's stamp,
will that work better for you?
I'll stand guard
outside till they come for us.
There's no telling
when more Nine members
might decide to show up.
[NANATSUKI]
Oh, I'll go with you.
[BIWAJIMA] Hey. When the hell's
our ride gonna get here?
[BIWAJIMA]
The silent treatment.
‐‐[blow lands]
‐‐[NINE MEMBER 9E groans]
'Kay, the rest of you
can walk on your own, right?
Follow me.
[BOY 9A]
Uh, s'cuse me.
There was a boy here
earlier who stood up for me,
but then, he got taken away.
He did?
[LUKA gasps]
I'm gonna save that kid.
If they wanted
him as a bargaining chip,
they'd have said something.
The fact that
they haven't means...
If there's a chance
I can help, I'm gonna go!
Otherwise... I know
I'll regret it!
All right!
Well, in that case, I'll‐‐
Don't tell me you're offering
to come with me, Shiori.
I mean, you literally
miss every shot you take.
Okay, that's enough‐‐
give it a rest.
Once you've led people
to safety, come back me up.
Is that a deal?
[LUKA]
Partner?
You'd better not die
before I get there, Luka.
Got it?
I won't. That's a promise.
[NANATSUKI groans]
Are you awake now, boy?
Very good. Why don't
we get started, then?
And that‐‐
That man was Warlock?
Yes. I think...
But my memory gets
hazy after that point.
All I can really remember
is that something hurt a lot.
Then... that guy rescued me.
[LUKA]
Oh, good, you're awake.
Some bad guys are on their way.
Don't worry, though,
I'm gonna take care of them.
I want you to get outta here.
Got it?
[ICHINOSE]
Hey, let me go!
Look, we're currently
preparing to storm them.
You'll ruin it if
you go in there now.
I don't care!
Listen to me,
I have to go right now!
[SQUAD MEMBER 9A] Sir!
We've secured the last hostage.
[gasps]
Good. Then, we're going in.
Get to it!
Yes, sir!
Watch it!
[phone buzzes]
Hello?
[BELLEMER (scrambled)]
...that you... nose?
Bellemer, hang on.
The signal's bad here.
Take over for a while?
Sure.
Hold on, I'm moving now.
[NIJO]
Hmph.
Hey, isn't that a jammer?
The kind used for temporarily
blocking phone signals?
[gasps]
What's this about?
Do you happen
to know Luka Mizuma?
Huh?
[NIJO] The officer who
rescued Seiji Nanatsuki,
that boy hostage,
and was then sacrificed.
Oh, him.
I remember. It was
really thanks to him
that I managed to make up for my
major screw‐up with the bomb.
You see, he jumped
out right in front of me!
I shot him, of course.
I mean, it was my job, though,
so whatcha gonna do, right?
You'd have done the same.
[panting]
Heh.
[gunshot]
[BIWAJIMA chuckles]
Did you kill him?
Just tell me that!
[BIWAJIMA] As a matter
of fact, no, I didn't.
Wait, what?
Oh, I filled him full of lead,
he shouldn't have survived.
But somehow or other, he did.
It did have the benefit of
making Warlock happy, though.
Tell you the truth, I really
don't know what happened.
But the next time I saw him, he
was like a different person.
He was Warlock's dog.
[gasps]
[BIWAJIMA]
He killed anyone he was told to,
however he was told to,
without question or remorse.
So, I guess,
at the end of the day,
deep down, that hot‐blooded,
hero cop wasn't actually
all that different from me.
Just a piece of scum,
tryin' to get by!
You lie!
That is not who
my brother is at all!
Your brother, huh?
Well, that does explain a lot.
Can you afford
to kill me, though?
I mean, don't you even care
about convicting Warlock
for all his heinous‐‐
None of that matters to me!
[growls]
What? Hibiya Noblewood Hotel?
[BELLEMER]
Yep, you've got it right.
They said they want you to
bring him there instead of
taking him to headquarters.
[ICHINOSE] He's not exactly
someone you'd want
to put up in a suite.
The orders apparently
come from a big shot
in Public Safety.
Some kind of security issue.
Yeah, fine.
Just hurry it up, okay?
[BELLEMER]
You got it.
[NIJO]
All this time.
The only thing I lived for was
to put a bullet in the brain
of my brother's killer!
These past nine, awful years.
It's all led me to this moment!
Hey, wait, hang on.
I already told you.
I didn't kill your brother!
No, you did!
You killed him!
You murdered
my brother that day!
You killed the strong,
kind man he used to be!
[ICHINOSE]
Hey! What're you doing?!
[gasps]
Lower it, Nijo! Come on, man!
[NIJO growls]
Holy crap, you're Luka's
little brother, aren't you?
I looked and looked, but I
couldn't find you anywhere.
That's because he and I
aren't related by blood.
It was easy enough for me to
hide, just by changing my name.
Stop it!
This man right here... is who
shot and murdered your partner.
Are you still
planning to stop me?
[NIJO]
I guess it makes sense.
In the end, I suppose
that's all Luka Mizuma
really meant to you, right?
You let him go!
Even though he was all alone!
You did that!
And now he's dead!
Look, it doesn't
matter what I did
or didn't do that day.
Luka Mizuma...
...my former partner...
[ICHINOSE]
...he would stop you.
[gasps]
[AKANE growls]
[yells]
[NIJO grunts]
[ICHINOSE]
Hmph!
[police sirens wailing]
[ENDO]
What happened here?
[ICHINOSE]
It's our ride.
Stand up.
[ICHINOSE]
Nijo.
I, uh...
[LUKA]
Yes.
I've just infiltrated the hotel.
[LUKA]
Hmph.
[BIWAJIMA snoring]
He's sleeping?
This guy really must
have nerves of steel.
What do you mean?
Don't you hate him?
[NANATSUKI]
Uh.
Seriously, doesn't
something in you
want to end Biwajima?
[NIJO] After all, he almost got
you killed once before, right?
There are some words
I don't think I'll ever forget.
That he‐‐the detective who
saved my life‐‐said to me.
[LUKA, NANATSUKI] I hope
you find your own justice,
and that you'll live
your life with pride.
[NIJO gasps]
[NANATSUKI]
So, I...
I became an officer
like he was to pursue
the same justice he did.
I don't want to kill this man,
because I want to be an officer
that he'd be proud of.
Besides...
If he testifies at
Warlock's trial,
then we'll learn what really
happened that day.
And that may be some
consolation to the people.
The ones suffering because
of what happened then.
So, that's why...
...I'm gonna get him
there and keep him safe.
All right. The room's all clear.
Man, you're all banged up.
Wow.
Oh. I, uh...
I got caught up
in all the danger.
I acted without thinking.
[BIWAJIMA sighs]
You idiot.
[elevator dings]
[OFFICER 9A]
Good work, officers.
[ICHINOSE gasps]
Heh.
Top floor!
It can't be...!
[NIJO grunts]
[screaming]
[ICHINOSE]
Hey! You all right?
Y‐Yeah. Where did he go?
[NANATSUKI]
Biwajima!
Shit, I figured
he would show up...
Don't talk!
We'll get you to a hospital!
I'm so sorry!
I promised to protect you!
Hey, kid, gimme your hand.
Just take this...
Take it...
Damn it!
[NANATSUKI whimpers]
[NIJO]
Wait!
Stop!
Tell me why, Luka.
[ICHINOSE]
Next time: "The Tenth Dragon."