But how?
How can this be?
[KIRYUIN sighs]
[KIRYUIN] Awfully quiet
with everyone off today.
Good Morning! Sorry I'm late.
Whoops. Oh, well.
What the heck are you
doing here, Nanatsuki?
Hold on, where is everyone?
They're off duty.
Seemed like a good idea
since we cleared up
that terrorist business.
Thought it might be best
for all involved if we
lie low for a while.
Politics. You know how it goes.
Oh, okay, you mean me, too?
[KIRYUIN]
Yep, you, too.
Heh. Now that you mention it,
I think you did say
something like that.
It's not a big deal.
Well, since you're here, if you
don't have anything else to do,
would you mind coming with me?
Oh, uh, no, I guess not.
Great, thank you.
Just think of it as a little
outing or a date or something.
'Kay?
Isn't my superior
demanding a date,
like, workplace harassment?
[KIRYUIN groans]
Right, excuse me.
So, um, would you consider
accompanying me today?
Sure?
[LUKA]
Know what I think?
I think we're both
gonna be good guys!
We'll have the strength
to protect people,
and the strength to fight
for others who can't, too.
We're going to be
men of justice!
Yeah! We will!
I'll be one, too, Luka!
We'll both get
through it together.
After all, we're
brothers, aren't we?
[NIJO]
Yeah!
[laughs
[NIJO]
Luka!
Kujaku!
You look so great!
You've got to come and
hang out with me sometime.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I've just had so much to do
since I joined the police force.
[NIJO]
Listen to you.
I bet you've already ditched
your whole private life!
[laughs]
Honestly, you're just hopeless.
[LUKA]
Enough about me.
What about you, Kujaku?
What? What do you mean?
I mean your future, of course.
What'll you study?
Have you decided?
[NIJO sighs]
That's a secret.
Hey, don't tell me you plan
to follow in my footsteps!
Yes, as a matter of fact.
I'm going to make
a career of it.
No, anything but that.
Having you for a boss would
be an absolute nightmare.
Probably. Still, though.
I've always wanted
to be just like you.
[LUKA chcukles]
Well, I'm flattered.
[KIRYUIN]
We're almost there now.
[NANATSUKI]
Is this it?
[KIRYUIN]
Yes, it is.
Former member of Special Seven?
That's right.
Considered killed
in the line of duty.
So, was he? Or not?
[KIRYUIN]
His body was never found.
He went missing in the
terrorist attack nine years ago.
[NANATSUKI]
Nine years ago.
[KIRYUIN] I want to
believe he's still alive,
but at this point,
I've almost given up hope.
Can you tell me
a little about him?
Like, what was his name?
Luka Mizuma.
Well. He was an
exemplary officer.
He was courageous,
incredibly energetic,
had good judgement,
but most importantly,
he was sincere in his mission.
What do you mean?
[KIRYUIN] I believe sincerity
is the most important quality
a police officer should possess.
If the force is too proud,
people won't be able
to trust them or the law,
and that's a problem.
[NANATSUKI]
That makes sense.
Listen, Rookie.
Humanity invented a system of
law enforcement called "police,"
and when it works correctly,
it can be a truly great thing.
To carry out justice
not for rewards or glory,
but for honor and duty.
It's proof of your wisdom
and personal evolution,
those qualities in you.
Do you really think
it's that big of a deal?
[KIRYUIN] Yes. I believe
it with all my heart.
And if possible, I'd like
you to believe it, as well.
After all, it's a
vital part of your duty
to control that power.
What power?
The one that you
mysteriously seem to have.
One day, the time will finally
come for you to use it properly.
Do you mean that
thing that happened
at the mall, or...?
[KIRYUIN]
Why? Do you have another
mysterious power in mind?
You'll be able to
understand some day.
That's kinda how
fate tends to work.
And when that time comes,
that's when you're going to be
forced to make a hard choice.
I'm, uh...
I'm gonna be honest, here.
I have no clue what
you mean. At all.
I guess not. That makes sense.
Don't worry, it's fine.
Some weather, huh?
I think even God would want to
take a rest on a day like this.
I hope this means
everyone else in Special Seven
is enjoying their
lovely day off.
[sizzling]
[yawns]
[AKANE'S HUSBAND]
You should get some more rest
if you're still feeling sleepy.
Oh, no, I'm okay.
I'll wake up sooner or later.
So, do you want to
hear about work?
[AKANE'S HUSBAND] Hey,
you come home safe and sound.
That's enough for me.
I mean, I'll happily listen if
you feel like venting, though.
Aw, thank you.
[AKANE'S HUSBAND]
How's your hobby going?
My post the other day
got the comments section
all riled up.
[AKANE'S HUSBAND]
What genre is the novel, anyway?
Well, it's...
It's set in this medieval
fantasy‐ish world.
The action opens just as
a certain villainess is about
to come to a bad end.
[AKANE'S HUSBAND]
Oh, wow, that sounds cool.
I've already
lost you, haven't I?
But if it makes you happy,
then I am a huge fan.
[gasps]
Are you almost finished, Dad?
Just another three...
...two... one...
...and done.
[sighs]
Damn. I really am getting old.
I would've recovered
much quicker than this
back in my prime.
[ENDO'S DAUGHTER] Just hurry up
and get changed, will you?
You smell all sweaty.
Yeah, yeah.
One "yeah" is sufficient, Dad.
[ENDO] Guess I've got
about another two years
of active duty in me.
Hope we can find another
sniper to take my place
before it's time for
me to step down.
Stop sitting there looking
so gloomy and hurry up!
Coming.
Mom's gonna get mad again.
We only get to see
each other once a month!
[ENDO]
I know, 'kay. I know!
[sighs]
Why did you get into
an Elf‐Dwarf romance, anyway?
Not exactly
destined for success.
[ENDO]
Your mother fell for me.
Well, that's really interesting
'cause she says
you fell for her.
Damn her! We'll be having words!
What are you, two little kids?
Oh, also, do you
have the present?
[ENDO]
Uh!
You...
No, I‐I bought it!
Just don't know where I put it.
Ugh. Unbelievable.
[blows landing]
‐‐Yes!
‐‐[phone rings]
Ah.
Hello?
[AKANE]
Hey, Belle! It's me.
Sorry, this is Ninja!
Come on, you're not Ninja
now that we're off the clock.
[BELLEMER] No, for real,
I'm Ninja right now.
Oh, you're playing a game?
[BELLEMER]
Ranked best in the world!
Wow! That's cool.
Wanna take a break?
I thought we could grab dinner.
Kinda feel like
eating out tonight.
Sounds good!
I'll just head over to your
place around dinner time,
if that's okay!
[AKANE]
Would you like curry?
Or maybe burgers or steak?
[BELLEMER]
Hmm...
Ah! I want some
fresh spring rolls!
Ooh, nice. I like that idea.
Ah.
‐‐What the...?
‐‐Hey!
What are you doing here?
[KIRYUIN]
He's on a date with me.
[ICHINOSE]
Yikes. My condolences, man.
Ha! I had nothing better to do.
It's fine.
[ICHINOSE]
Whatever.
[NANATSUKI]
Do you come here every month?
[ICHINOSE]
No. I've only come once before.
[KIRYUIN]
How cold‐hearted of you.
Yeah, you said it.
[NANATSUKI] Did you bring
flowers? Or anything?
No, nothing like that.
‐‐I, um...
‐‐Yeah?
Ah‐‐!
Nothing.
It's just, I've been wondering
what Mizuma was like.
[ICHINOSE] He was a cop
who stood for justice. Always.
[NANATSUKI]
Justice.
[ICHINOSE] Well, justice
can mean a lot of things.
I mean, you can have
self‐righteous justice, too.
[KIRYUIN] Yes, That's all
too common these days.
[ICHINOSE] But Mizuma...
He did his best for the victims.
He fearlessly confronted
the people who committed crimes,
and he refused to
give in to pressure.
And that's more than I could do.
Rookie. Give me a minute.
[NANATSUKI]
Huh?
Ugh. I'm asking you to
go so I can speak with Boss.
Oh! Of course. I'm gone!
What's wrong?
So, how much do you
know about this?
About Rookie's power?
Huh? Nijo?
You know, I really
wish you wouldn't
glare like that.
I've got a fair idea of it.
Is he gonna be okay?
You know how it goes‐‐
I think that's for
him to decide.
All I can do at this point is
watch over and support him
as best I can.
[ICHINOSE]
Rookie.
[NANATSUKI] Oh, are you two
finished with your meeting?
Yeah.
You know the trials
for the terrorist attack
nine years ago will be coming
to an end soon, right?
Yes. I know that.
I agree with Public
Safety that we need to be
on alert for an incident.
You mean the kind of
thing that happened at the mall?
That's right.
The time that froze up nine
years ago is about to move.
It honestly scares me
to think what happens
when it does.
Why, what's going to happen?
[ICHINOSE]
The bank robbery,
Hisamichi Goto's
terrorist bombings,
the attack on the mall...
Those weren't Nine devotees
just lashing out on their own.
They've started to act
with a definite purpose.
In which case,
something will happen
at the next trial.
After all...
It's going to decide the fate
and sentence of
Nine's leader, Warlock.
[KIRYUIN] They may make
some sort of desperate attempt
to get him back,
or launch a terrorist attack
and make demands.
[ICHINOSE] Unfortunately,
there's very little
that we can do.
Far too little, really.
Well, Public Safety
has their eyes on this one.
It's a scramble for credit.
[NANATSUKI] I wish we could all
work together to do something.
We're all on the same team!
I think we will, someday.
Oh, yeah? "Someday"?
When is that, Boss?
[KIRYUIN]
Hmm? Well, it's... someday.
[ENDO'S DAUGHTER]
'Kay, I'll see ya, Dad.
I think we're going
to get some dinner now.
Have fun.
Honestly.
How're you this old and
still can't keep neat?
That's... embarrassing
[ENDO'S DAUGHTER giggles]
[ENDO]
Thanks, I guess.
Now, time for me
to grab a bite, myself.
[ENDO] Let's see,
what do I feel like today?
Mm...
'Bye. I'm heading
out to dinner, okay?
[AKANE'S HUSBAND]
Have a good time.
I'll be borrowing Akane now.
[AKANE'S HUSBAND chuckles] Well,
make sure you bring her back,
she means a lot to me.
You!
Didn't expect you
to call so late.
Have I ever told you
why I deal in information?
I can't remember
if I have or not.
You haven't.
As you very well know,
our world's full of deceit.
And none of us are immune.
You see, all of humanity‐‐
including the rarer races
like elves, dwarves,
and vampires‐‐
have come to feel as if
we rule this world.
But that's only a delusion.
I want to know the truth,
and by gathering
information about you,
I will inevitably
reach that truth.
[NIJO]
Well, then.
It's all down in the basement.
Take a look.
[NIJO]
Hmm.
[BLACK PEARL] It's time
to choose, Kujaku Nijo.
Will you succumb to evil,
or submit to good?
[BLACK PEARL] The good news is,
whichever you choose.
It will still be useful to me.
I'm sure it was
right around here.
‐‐[BELLEMER grunts]
‐‐Oh, sorry. Excuse me.
[BELLEMER whimpers]
Ah!
Oh!
‐‐It's the fresh spring rolls!
‐‐Spring rolls!
[laughter]
[ICHINOSE] All right, then,
it's time we got going.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[stomach growls
I'm starving, for one.
Oh, yeah? You're hungry?
All right. I guess it won't
hurt me to act on a whim.
"Act on a whim"?
Do you not usually eat dinner?
[ICHINOSE]
I'm saying it's my treat.
Really?! You sure
you're feeling okay?!
Okay, fine, deal's off.
Oh, no! Come on,
I'm just kidding!
As your junior officer,
I'd be happy to accept!
Thanks! What a
very welcome surprise.
Whoa there, Boss,
you pay for yourself.
I'm afraid I'm only
treating Rookie, here.
Well, I had to try.
Hey, is it cool
if I invite Nijo?
Fine by me.
He won't come, though.
So, where to?
What are you guys
in the mood for?
[ICHINOSE]
Vietnamese, maybe?
I could really go
for some pho today.
"Pho"?
Rice noodle soup?
"Pho"...
It doesn't ring any bells?
How is that possible?
I don't know.
I've only had ramen.
'Kay, Mr. Basic.
All right, let's go!
[KIRYUIN]
Pho! I can hardly wait.
[NIJO growls]
You expect me to believe that?
No, I don't.
[NIJO sighs] The problem is,
I know you never lie.
[BLACK PEARL]
If you doubt me,
why don't you go get
Shiori Ichinose?
Then you can use his
ability to discern the truth.
I feel certain he'd be
able to tell if I was lying.
Then Special Seven's done!
If you're right, then that's it.
Exactly.
Truth be told,
the countdown's already begun.
So, what to do?
[NIJO]
I...
And don't try to claim you were
forced into a decision.
Think it over very carefully.
[phone buzzes]
[gasps]
[BLACK PEARL]
Where're you going?
Goodbye. Kujaku Nijo.
‐‐Uh...
‐‐Eh...
Well, now.
[ENDO, AKANE, BELLEMER]
Uh...
[AKANE] I dunno, I really felt
like fresh spring rolls today.
[ENDO]
Me, too.
[ICHINOSE]
I want pho.
Pho!
All we're missing
is Nijo or we'd have
all of Special Seven
here together!
See? I told ya he wouldn't come.
I told you I invited him, right?
He texted me back
and said that he's coming.
[ICHINOSE]
Do you guys get along now?
No, not at all.
[NIJO] That's right.
We don't get along at all.
What about it?
You just scared
the crap outta me!
Yeah, you guys really
do make a weird combo.
I'll thank you to wipe
the probing look off your face.
Am I the last one here?
This isn't like you at all.
Just call it a whim.
Once won't kill me.
Seems lots of people
are having whims today.
[ICHINOSE] Fresh spring rolls
for everyone before the pho.
Sure, anything for you, hon!
[AKANE, ENDO]
Huh?
[BELLEMER] So, will you
be treating us, Boss?
Sure thing! Happy to!
I'd love to treat every one
of you to mark the occasion.
Lucky us!
Well, then, thanks in advance
for the food, Boss.
You don't miss a beat, do you?
[BELLEMER] Nope! Hey,
give us the most expensive
thing on the menu, please!
Enough for all!
[AKANE] Could I have the shrimp
and avocado banh xeo, please?
[ICHINOSE] A large order
of Mi Quang for me.
[ENDO] Com Ga for four!
Vietnamese curry, mild!
[NANATSUKI]
Steamed whole squid, here!
[NIJO]
I'll have the Bun bo Hue.
Seriously...?
[GROUP]
To the boss!
And to pho!
Look at that! Looks delicious!
‐‐[BELLEMER] So yummy!
‐‐[KIRYUIN] Listen, you guys...
Try to savor it
a little more, huh?
‐‐[NANATSUKI] My cheeks pink?
‐‐[ICHINOSE] Aren't they always?
[ALL] Thank you
for this scrumptious meal!
[laughs]
[LUKA]
So, this is it.
The flames are intense.
My lungs feel scorched.
Well, I hope that young
kid's still safe, at least.
[footsteps]
It's really you!
Congratulations, brave survivor.
I went looking for folks with
struggling vital responses.
[chuckles]
Looks like I've hit the jackpot!
You bastard!
[LUKA gasps]
‐‐[WARLOCK] Heh!
‐‐[LUKA gasps]
Impressive, right?
This is the power of magic.
The blood of the dragons.
The dragons?
I planned to offer
up many sacrifices,
but I got far fewer
than I expected.
Why, you ask?
Because the police took action.
And because
Special Seven did as well.
It's all your fault!
Because you responded
so annoyingly fast,
most of my sacrifices got away!
Guess I can't expect
it all to work in my favor.
Regardless of that, it
couldn't be deemed a total loss.
Not even close.
I gained this, for instance.
[LUKA grunts, gasps]
You don't even know, do you?
The blood of dragons
will grant you immortality.
It what?
[grunts, groans]
You heard right.
The thing is, though,
a single drop like that
will only give you
a few seconds of relief.
At this rate,
you're going to die.
S‐So what do I...
What can I...?
[grunts]
Humans are truly
the most bizarre of creatures,
you know that?
They might easily accept
their impending death
due to their own
personal weakness...
...but when someone
they care about dies
because of something they've
done, their hearts just break.
[gasps, whimpers]
[screams]
[sobs]
Stop, please! I'm begging you!
Please don't do it!
Not my brother!
Not my partner,
please, you can't!
There's nothing to be afraid of!
You just need to do as I say.
Don't worry. I'll use
magic on you right away.
Magic that will erase any
and all pangs of conscience,
my brave survivor!
[BELLEMER] Next time:
"The Eight‐Foot Escape Route."