Just kill me.
[NIJO]
I really will.
I'll do it, Luka.
The detective who saved my life.
He said something
I can't forget.
I hope you find
your own justice.
And, that you'll be sure to live
the rest of your
life with pride.
Yes. I don't see any other way.
[DETECTIVE 11A]
What about that hideout?
[DETECTIVE 11B sighs]
The brass called it off.
Oh, that's right, they did.
[DETECTIVE 11B]
Hmm?
[DETECTIVES coughing]
What the...? What do you
guys think you're doing?
[DETECTIVE 11A groans]
[DETECTIVES groaning]
You know...
I think maybe the two of you
should consider quitting,
since you both have families
that still depend on you.
What about you, though, Belle?
Well, I'm a ninja
and a homunculus.
I don't have a family.
So, Special Seven is really
the closest thing I've got.
[ENDO gasps]
You think we should phone them?
I guess so.
[NANATSUKI whimpers]
I just can't do it...
Yeah, I get it.
[NANATSUKI]
I mean, it's my fault, right?
If not for me,
Mizuma would still be...
It would have
been better for everyone
if I had just died!
[ICHINOSE]
That's not true.
He doesn't regret saving you,
and neither do I,
for that matter.
How can you know that?
[ICHINOSE]
Because I'd do the same thing.
If it'd been me, I would've
chosen to save you, too.
That kind of justice
is the mark of a good officer.
Defending the future of
a total stranger is what we do.
Justice, huh?
[LUKA]
Then you've got to run.
'Cause you still have a future.
I'm a police officer.
A servant of justice.
My job is all about
protecting your future.
[ICHINOSE]
I can promise you this:
If you'd been in
Mizuma's shoes back then,
you would 100% have
gone to save you, too.
There's not a doubt in my mind.
How can you be
so sure about that?
You mean based on my profile?
No, kid.
It's because I have faith.
I don't mean faith in
profiles or experience.
I have faith in you
as an officer.
And I believe in who
Seiji Nanatsuki is, as a person.
[NANATSUKI gasps]
On top of that,
I'm pretty sure
I'll be able to settle things
in this fight, too.
[NANATSUKI]
Settle what?
Ever since that case,
I haven't been able
to fully believe in my own
ability to see justice through.
To me, I was just some blockhead
who couldn't do a thing
to save anyone else.
But now, I've decided
I want to believe in myself
and try to find that
inner pride again.
So, that's what
I'll be fighting for.
I understand.
And, as for you,
recover your sense of justice.
It's something only
you can do, Rookie.
I hope you find
your own justice,
and that you'll live with pride.
I will. I'll fight.
Thank you.
I needed to hear that.
Let's get going, then.
[AKANE'S HUSBAND]
What's wrong?
Are you having
a difficult time at work?
[AKANE] If I told you
that I might decide
to become a criminal,
what would you do?
[AKANE'S HUSBAND]
I'd trust that the values
you've worked so hard for
all this time wouldn't change.
And neither would
my love for you.
[AKANE gasps]
Wouldn't you be embarrassed?
[AKANE'S HUSBAND]
Nope, no chance.
[AKANE] Look, I need you
to take the dog and go stay
with your family for a bit.
If anything happens
to me, I'm sorry.
[AKANE'S HUSBAND]
No, don't apologize.
I'll be waiting.
[AKANE sighs]
[ENDO]
Yeah, that's right.
Go stay with her, okay?
Don't stress about packing,
it'll all be over in a few days.
And, if the worst happens,
I'm leaving the
rest of it to her.
Well, see you.
[ENDO'S DAUGHTER]
"See you" isn't good enough!
Dad! You'd better
come back here alive‐‐
do you hear me right now?
I want nothing
to do with your funeral!
I'm not kidding here!
Do you understand...?
Yeah.
[ENDO'S DAUGHTER]
See you tomorrow, then, okay?
Tomorrow! You got that?
[receiver beeping]
Yeah, I got that.
Loud and clear, kiddo.
[ENDO]
Hmph.
[BOTH]
Hmm.
[KIRYUIN]
This isn't good.
[BELLEMER] What isn't?
What do you mean, Boss?
What's wrong?
[KIRYUIN] Things have taken
a turn for the worse.
[DEPARTMENT CHIEF 1A]
Would you care to
accompany me, Kiryuin?
Sure, I wouldn't mind that,
but where to?
We're going to where he is.
I take that to mean
you're with Nine.
I am! Have been ever
since I was assigned.
Quite a long road,
but I finally got here.
[KIRYUIN]
May I ask exactly what it is
that you're hoping to do?
Oh, you'll know soon enough.
Hey, Boss. Y'okay?
[KIRYUIN]
No, probably not.
Although, it seems they
don't intend to kill me yet,
so that's positive.
‐‐[notification dings]
‐‐Oh!
What is that?
The analysis on
that eye is complete.
So... What's this
I'm looking at?
A picture of Tokyo?
[AKANE]
Is it just an image file?
[BELLEMER] There are
coordinates marked on it,
but yeah, it is, basically.
[ENDO]
What? That's all?
Oh! No, wait, there are
some other image files.
Crime‐scene photos? Maybe?
Uh. And this one?
[ICHINOSE]
A dragon?
[NANATSUKI]
It has nine heads.
[AKANE]
The Nine‐Headed Dragon.
I feel like I've read
about that before.
Doesn't look like the image
contains any kind of code.
Damn it. I have no idea.
Hold on! Look at that.
Right there‐‐isn't that
the same shopping mall?
[ICHINOSE]
And this is the airport.
I remember every
one of these places,
'cause Nine committed
crimes at all of them.
But there must be
a lot of places like that.
Is there something that sets
these specific locations apart?
[ICHINOSE]
Hmm...
Luka. Were you still able
to break the Kasai seal?
Without a hitch.
Maybe seals?
There has to be
something to this.
Do these five points have
anything in common?
[BELLEMER]
Let me see...
Oh! At the mall,
a sacred tree
that had been there since
before it was built was felled.
[ICHINOSE]
It looks like an old torii gate
was also destroyed
at the airport.
Boss, listen, these sacred trees
and torii gates and things‐‐
are they the seals
Warlock was talking about?
[KIRYUIN]
Most likely.
Although, to be honest,
I was never certain
where they were, myself.
So, to break
the seals undetected,
they're committing
terrorist attacks to create a
diversion and
cover their tracks.
[KIRYUIN] Yes, as far as
I can tell from these photos,
they've definitely been
using their crimes as a cover
to break the seals of his power.
[ICHINOSE] And it appears
that Warlock did get stronger
with each one they broke.
[NANATSUKI gasps]
It's a pentagram,
and in the center of it
just happens to be...
[NANATSUKI]
Police headquarters!
[WARLOCK]
Listen up, all you humans!
Fun fact: I am one of
the great, powerful dragons
you worshipped long ago!
I've come back, so,
bow down and praise me!
You'll see!
Once I kill that first dragon,
this will all finally
be over for you!
Isn't that right, Kiryuin?
Wait a minute‐‐
what in the world?
My, my, long time
no see, you old fool.
Yeah, you aren't kidding.
It has been a long time,
you whippersnapper.
[WARLOCK]
Accept it:
all of the dragons' power
now belongs to me.
By the way, why ever
did you forsake your power?
See, I think you've
actually got that backwards.
I should be the one asking
why you would ever want it.
Stop being so ridiculous.
So, you gained
enlightenment like a monk,
then decided vanishing
was the right way
for a dragon to go out?
Seriously, have you not
an ounce of dragon pride?
No, I'm afraid that
I haven't got any at all.
As evidenced by the fact
that I'm the first head
of the Nine‐ Headed Dragon
and I've chosen
to remain in this world.
The truth is, I have
no more need of power.
Well, that's good, because as
the last head of that dragon,
I'm going to take
this whole world.
My, you're a
greedy one, aren't you?
[WARLOCK] You're awfully
complacent, old m‐‐
[gasps]
[KIRYUIN] I confess,
I told you a little lie.
I may be human now, that's true.
But you'll find my dragon power
is still very much intact.
[WARLOCK chuckles]
So!
You're the last boss.
My dragon blood
is seething in my veins!
Why be like that?
I mean, mine certainly isn't.
Maybe grow up?
Hold on. You're not human, Boss?
What the heck?
[KIRYUIN] I'd bet even you
couldn't see that coming‐‐
am I right, Charisma?
There are quite a few surprising
mysteries in this world
He came out and said it!
[KIRYUIN]
Well, because that's how it is.
So I'd really appreciate it if
you would all come rescue me
sooner rather than later, 'kay?
[AKANE] Is there anything
specific we can do to help you?
[KIRYUIN]
Yes, of course there is!
As I'm sure you're all aware, we
dragons tend to grow stronger
the more humans there are
out there who believe in us.
As for the reverse...
It's also true.
Dragons are very frail
creatures, you see.
Even humans can defeat
them if they know how.
[ICHINOSE]
Hmm.
[KIRYUIN] It looks like this
will be my last communication.
Feel free to leave
this drone behind, okay?
I leave the rest
in your capable hands.
No, wait! Come back!
So, let's see, we're going
to fight the Nine members
who're currently
occupying police HQ...
...back up Boss
who's fighting there...
...and finally, arrest Warlock.
Right. Shouldn't be
any sweat at all.
Hang on. We still
haven't heard from Nijo.
I told you before:
Nijo is fine, he'll be there.
Yeah, he will.
Everything's ready to go.
Well, I'm gonna saythis
in Boss's place today:
Special Seven, let's move out!
‐‐Yes, sir!
‐‐You got it!
Tell me why.
[NIJO]
Remember who you are!
You're the best police
officer in the world!
The man who always kept
fighting to see justice done,
no matter what anyone
else might've said!
You could've killed me
twice now, and you haven't!
I think that means
you haven't lost yet!
Look at this!
That's you, right there!
Luka Mizuma,
occupation: police officer!
Until nine years ago,
you were part of Special Seven!
No, this is...
[NIJO] The other man
is Shiori Ichinose.
He was your partner!
[LUKA whimpers]
Yes, that's right.
Back then, I...
But when someone they
care about dies because of
something they've done,
their hearts just break.
[wailing]
[LUKA]
That's right.
I have to protect you.
That's why I...
[LUKA gasps]
[LUKA whimpering]
[sobs]
[whimpering]
[NIJO]
It's all right, Luka.
Listen... I became
a police officer because of you.
We'll stand together.
Fight side by side.
[NIJO]
Please, trust me!
[LUKA]
I am... Luka... Mizuma!
Ah?
State your name and occupation.
I am Luka Mizuma,
ex‐police detective.
But I'm currently
unemployed, Detective Nijo.
[WARLOCK bellows]
[NINE MEMBERS grunting]
You're going to die
if you stay here.
You see, this is
the power that you guys
thought you were looking for.
I'm getting out of here!
This is a whole lot of fun,
wouldn't you agree?
[WARLOCK] They can fly,
they can breathe fire,
and their words ring out
through the night air!
They're more powerful than
any other species on Earth!
And that's what a dragon is!
Much of that is true.
Except for one glaring weakness:
we dragons are omnipotent‐‐
I won't try to deny it.
And that's exactly why
dragons have lost the right
to exist on this planet.
[WARLOCK]
Never fear.
We still have rights
regarding this world,
like the one to devour it!
Our time ended long ago.
Accept that!
[WARLOCK]
Tch.
[KIRYUIN grunts]
Oh, dear,
he's begun to materialize.
That's not good.
[WARLOCK]
I forgot to mention.
I have the trash that worships
me backing me up here today.
What about you, old man?
How many people out
there have faith in you, huh?
Six of them do.
And to be honest,
I think that's enough for me.
[NINE MEMBER 11C] I can't
believe the battle on the roof
is still going on.
[NINE MEMBER 11D]
Look, don't even worry about it.
You really don't wanna know.
[NINE MEMBER 11E]
Yeah, you said it.
We just need to wait so
we can get Master Warlock
to grant us immortality,
and then we'll be all set!
Hey, what are you gonna‐‐
‐‐[gunshots]
‐‐[grunting]
[NINE MEMBER 11D]
Shit! Hostiles!
You son of a...
You really shouldn't relax
when you're on lookout duty.
I'm kinda surprised,
this place isn't even that big.
Hey, Rookie! He's got
a knife at his left hip.
Come on over here and get it.
[NANATSUKI]
Right!
We arrested the five
who were on patrol.
So, you're the last one
for us to snag.
Oh, is that so?
[ICHINOSE] Hmph.
Hey, Belle, there's a sixth
hiding somewhere, go find them.
[BELLEMER]
You got it!
[NINE MEMBER 11F groans]
[BELLEMER]
All taken care of!
[NINE MEMBER 11D grunts]
That's great, good work.
I've already given you
the rundown of the plan, right?
Attacker, Supporter, and Sniper.
You three need to make sure
you're at the top of your game.
You're our ace. Don't slip up.
Right.
We have two objectives:
protecting HQ till the Self‐
Defense Forces get here,
and of course,
arresting Warlock.
But... I don't know
if Rookie and Boss
can beat him, or what Boss
meant about how even humans
could take down dragons.
No clue what that was about.
And if we don't
figure it out soon,
we'll all be killed in
the line of duty.
That doesn't sound ideal.
Don't worry, Belle.
None of us want to die here,
and none of us will.
Speaking of which, dragons draw
most of their power from faith
or something like that, right?
Apparently.
Heh. Well then,
I believe in you, Nanatsuki.
Me, too, with all my heart.
Same with me.
And I do, too, of course!
Thanks!
[KIRYUIN groans]
See, what did
I tell you, old fool?
Little worn out?
This won't do.
It seems I haven't fought
in such a long time
that my body's finally
showing its age.
Plus, nobody's been
worshipping you.
Well, I don't need
worshipping anymore.
And for that matter, humans
no longer need dragons, either.
The fantasy is over, so all they
need now is the conviction
to carry out justice.
Oh, justice, huh?
How lovely for them.
Know what their
"justice" has done?
I'll tell you what:
it's taken over this
entire building for me!
This is the final seal.
I'm going to destroy
every last trace of it!
[KIRYUIN]
Sorry, impossible.
See, here's the thing.
I happen to have
something you don't.
What do you mean?
I simply mean that
it's Special Seven's turn
this time around, Warlock.
Or should I phrase
that differently?
Okay, how about this: the one
with the power you sought
above all else is
finally here for you.
And he has another power.
One that you could never
comprehend in a million years.
I'm afraid that's
my ace in the hole
and the end of you,
young whippersnapper.
[NINE MEMBER 11G]
Rockets at the ready!
Blast them!
Rookie!
[NANATSUKI]
On it!
Here goes nothing!
[NINE MEMBER 11G]
Is he nuts?!
[NANATSUKI]
Hah!
[NINE MEMBER 11G]
What?!
[AKANE yells]
Cool!
All right, let's keep moving.
Rookie and I are gonna head
straight up to the roof.
You three, try and
hold them off, if you can.
Don't die on us, Shiori!
Can you please
not use my first name?!
Your name is Shiori?
Hey, you stay focused!
No. Seriously, Shiori?
I have no comment!
[ICHINOSE] It'll take us ten
minutes just to get up there.
Hang in there, Boss.
[WARLOCK]
What nonsense.
What can only six
people possibly do?
[KIRYUIN] For starters,
unlike your worshippers,
these six believe in more
than just accumulating power.
They believe in me
as a person living among them.
[WARLOCK growls]
[KIRYUIN] The fact is, the
sad rabble you've gathered
wouldn't do anything
to sate my hunger.
A dragon's hunger.
[grunts]
[WARLOCK]
That's fine.
I'll just rip your
blasted head off.
So long, you old fool.
Do it, now.
What's that?
Oh, don't worry,
that wasn't for you.
[NANATSUKI yells]
[WARLOCK grunts]
Are you all right, Boss?
Thanks, I am.
Well, good.
I'm so glad that you're safe!
[KIRYUIN]
Seji Nanatsuki.
Special Seven can
win this fight,
even without an
old fool like me.
So, have confidence.
[WARLOCK laughing]
Your senility has truly reached
new heights, Kiryuin!
You really thought humans
could defeat a dragon?
Hilarious!
That's right‐‐
it's our turn, Warlock.
Get ready.
If you think you can beat us.
[NANATSUKI grunts]
[NANATSUKI]
Warlock.
For murder,
criminal insurrection,
assembling with
dangerous weapons,
and numerous other crimes,
you're under arrest!
[WARLOCK]
Arrest? What?
[ICHINOSE] You have
the right to remain silent,
which would be great.
Heh.
[WARLOCK]
I'll kill you...
I'll kill you!
How dare you treat me
like a lowly human!
‐‐Here he comes!
‐‐Here I go!
[NANATSUKI]
Next time: "From Zero to Seven."