[SUSPECT 2A]
Detective.
I was talking to someone earlier
and they told me you were able
to see through any lie.
[ICHINOSE] I can tell you,
generally speaking,
elves are pretty
accomplished liars.
Whereas, dwarves, on the
other hand, not so much.
Exactly, and I've got dwarvish
blood! I don't lie, I swear!
It's the truth!
Please believe me!
You've got the wrong man.
Don't arrest me, get the
guy who killed my wife!
[ICHINOSE]
Well, that's the goal.
Speaking of which, I need
to ask you about something.
[grunts]
Just a question
about your testimony.
You said you got home
at 5:40PM, discovered the body,
and reported it.
Does that sound about right?
Yes, that's the truth.
Wasn't it... my civic duty?
Oh, it was. Definitely.
Heh.
Normally, when someone finds
a family member's
body in their home,
they're late in reporting it.
They sense danger
and usually freeze,
wondering if there could be
an intruder in the house,
plus, they've got to get
over the initial shock before
they can get their
bearings and call
an ambulance and the police.
And yet, you called and
made a report as soon as
you got home, within
one minute of finding
the body at 5:40PM.
Wonder why that is?
[SUSPECT 2A]
It's just... I knew right away.
I knew she was dead.
Here's the thing.
You have no training,
but somehow,
you just knew she was dead
without even touching her?
It's unusual that you
reported she was dead
and not unconscious.
[SUSPECT 2A]
I was convinced it was suicide.
Things weren't going
well for her at work.
Or at home,
for that matter, right?
[gasps] No, that's not...
That's not true.
Perhaps it's possible
your wife was bringing
her stress from work
home with her.
Was there any domestic violence?
[gasps]
[ICHINOSE]
I'll take that as a yes.
Look, but I
didn't do it, though,
I didn't kill my wife!
Heh. Yeah, but
who'd you hire to do it?
[DETECTIVE 2A growls]
Dammit!
This case is under
our jurisdiction now.
It's been a pleasure, fellas.
Don't get cocky, Ichinose!
[ICHINOSE chuckles]
I'm way too cool to be cocky.
What's with that guy?
Who is he?
Not that it's hard to guess
that it was the husband.
But to get him to confess
that he hired a hitman!
[DETECTIVE 2A] I know, right?
Guy can read minds.
[DETECTIVE 2B]
He psychic or somethin'?
[DETECTIVE 2A]
No idea, man.
He's got credentials in
criminal kinesics or something.
From what I've heard,
he even helped the FBI out,
back when he was in school.
[DETECTIVE 2B]
I don't get it.
What's someone that good doing
in that garbage dump of a unit?
[DETECTIVE 2A]
Good question. I have no clue.
[NEWSCASTER 2A] We now have
an update on the incident
a few days ago in which
several armed men holed up
in a Nihonbashi bank
and made off with...
Sir, I... had a question.
What exactly am I supposed
to be doing here?
Right, right.
Tell me something, Nanatsuki,
do you know anything
about what we do
at Special Seven?
Not a thing!
Definitely no rumors
that it's a bunch of rogues
burning the budget.
Well, that's depressing.
So, listen, what we actually
do is specialize in pursuing
Nine‐related crimes.
The terrorists? I didn't know.
Yeah, that's what we do.
The members of Nine
worship dragons, and yes,
I do mean the mystical beings
that once ruled this world.
Dragons?
[KIRYUIN]
Oh, sure.
Humans have worshiped
and revered dragons
since the dawn of
recorded history.
And some have tried
their best to gain power
from them, as well.
As you know, many
humans turn to crime
in order to gain power.
But these humans have been
designated a terrorist group.
Special Seven was created
with the specific aim
of standing against them.
I thought their
leader was arrested.
In the terror attack,
nine years ago.
[KIRYUIN]
Very good!
Yes, their supposed leader,
Warlock, was arrested that day.
We sacrificed a lot,
but they were
effectively destroyed.
It was a nice, happy ending.
[NANATSUKI]
So, our job is done?
Kind of a problem, right?
I mean, if there are no special
crimes, then we'll all be
out of a job before
we know what hit us!
[NANATSUKI] Should we really
want more crime, though?
So, at the moment,
we just swipe a few cases
here and there from some
of the other sections.
Y'know, to give the brass a
reason for keeping us around.
No wonder they all hate us.
Well, I think that's
all I wanted to cover
about the department.
Follow me, let's re‐introduce
you to your fellow members.
I'll start with myself.
Sakon Zeroemon Kiryuin.
But my code name here is "Boss."
We have code names?
Yes, I've taken the liberty
of assigning one
to each of our members.
First. You see that dwarvish
dandy sitting over there
in the green jacket?
That's Rokusuke Endo.
His code name is "Sniper."
Would you just give it
a rest with the code names?
That crap's embarrassing.
[KIRYUIN]
Oh, come on, it's cool!
So, as you might expect from
the code name "Sniper,"
he's an expert marksman.
Yep, that's clear.
It's great to meet you.
[ENDO]
Hey.
[KIRYUIN] This elvish man,
here, is Kujaku Nijo.
Code name: "Analyzer."
Yeah, I'm gonna need
you to never call me that.
"Nijo" it is, then.
I'm glad to meet you.
If you want
to know anything at all,
you should pretty much ask him.
He's the man with all the
connections around here.
Great. Thank you, sir.
Don't rely on others.
You should get into the habit
of doing things for yourself.
[KIRYUIN]
This is Akane Shikisai,
and her code name is "Samurai."
[AKANE] But, listen, you can
call me whatever you like!
Hey there, new guy.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, yeah.
It's nice to meet you, too.
I know she may not
look it, but she's a vampire.
A real rarity. A vampire
samurai! Pretty cool, huh?
[NANATSUKI]
Vampires suck blood, right?
Heh! Hi there!
My name's Bellemer Cinq!
I have a code name, too.
It's Ninja!
Question: do we
employ minors here?
Oh, age doesn't
matter for homunculi.
We're considered full‐grown
adults the moment we're born.
If we wanna get real,
I'm your senior!
You think you can handle that?
[NANATSUKI]
Sure.
And that goes double because
I'm a really great ninja!
So, what's Ninja's
contribution to the team?
If you ever need to know
about anything mechanical,
she's your girl.
She's highly capable.
[BELLEMER]
That's right!
Wow, really?
But drones are my specialty.
[NANATSUKI gasps, yelps]
I'm really pleased
to meet you, Ninja.
And last but not least,
there's your
old friend, Ichinose.
His code name is "Charisma!"
That's a choice.
[yelps]
Look, don't call me
by that name, though.
Only the boss does that. 'Kay?
And don't ask my first name.
Why, what's your first name?
[ICHINOSE]
Don't. Ask.
[NANATSUKI gasps]
All right, then,
Seiji Nanatsuki!
From now on,
your code name is "Rookie."
Oh, please, sir,
you can't do that to me.
What? You don't like it?
Aw. What's the matter, Rookie?
Oh, right, by the way, Charisma.
[ICHINOSE growls]
Sorry, I mean Ichinose.
It looks like we might have
a shot at a new case,
so, I need you to get on it.
You heard him, Rookie. Let's go.
No, seriously,
I don't want that code name.
Yeah, that's why I'm using it.
[ICHINOSE]
Hey there.
First time at a crime scene?
[NANATSUKI]
'Fraid so.
I've been at the scenes
of crashes when
I was on traffic duty,
but that's it.
Great, Tell me about the victim.
His name's Hyogo Arisawa.
Occupation: politician.
Isn't that right?
[ICHINOSE] He's made
kind of a name for himself
in the ruling party recently.
He lost in the
last election, though.
[NANATSUKI]
So, an ex‐politician, then?
[ICHINOSE] A politician
who loses an election
is just a citizen. But...
Looks like he wanted
to get reelected.
I don't get it,
how can you tell?
A daruma with one eye blank.
Wouldn't need it
if he quit politics.
Oh...
[ICHINOSE]
Still, talk about bad taste.
[NANATSUKI] No kidding.
The cause of death, um...
It's one stab to
the heart with a knife.
[ICHINOSE] Looks like we
can rule out suicide, then.
Listen to this.
His secretary, Yosuke
Kasuga, found the body.
Arisawa didn't show
at a meeting,
so he got the
landlord let him in.
And they discovered
the body here.
[NANATSUKI] There's no one
else who lives on this floor,
isn't that right?
Not with the size of this place.
[NANATSUKI]
So, what now?
Where do we start
our investigation?
Wait, I've got it.
This was done by the secretary.
[NANATSUKI] Cool. Wait, you
really just figured it out?
Nah, but it sure
woulda make our lives easier.
Yes. Yes, it would.
[cell phone buzzing]
Hey, Belle. What's up?
[BELLEMER] You're at
Mr. Arisawa's place, right?
Sure am. Anything wrong?
[BELLEMER]
Well, as a matter of fact,
it's getting kind
of interesting.
We've just received a report.
Looks like there
are three more bodies.
Three more?
Are you ready
for the interesting part?
All politicians.
[ICHINOSE] So, four politicians
were killed in one night, huh?
Belle, you were right.
That does sound interesting.
Victim one. Hyogo Arisawa, 37.
Former member of the Lower
House for the ruling party.
Currently unemployed,
but he was seeking reelection.
Cause of death: single
knife thrust to the heart.
Victim two: Haruka Sakuma, 42.
Member of the Lower House
for the ruling party.
Cause of death
is the same as Arisawa.
Victim three: Kentaro Masuoka.
He's a member of the Lower
House for the opposition.
Same cause of death.
[BELLEMER]
Victim four: Toru Motoyama, 60.
Member of the House of
Councilors for the ruling party.
Wanna guess the cause of death?
Four Identical deaths, huh?
Well, I'm pretty stumped.
They have anything
else in common?
They're all currently
under investigation.
Okay. What's the plan?
Well, let's split up
and figure this thing out.
Belle, stay and handle
communications.
Shikisai, go check in with each
victim's election office.
Sounds good to me!
I'll get on it.
Gramps, you go to
the coroner's and check on
the cause of death
and the murder weapon.
‐‐[ENDO] You got it.
‐‐Then I will go investigate
the four politicians.
Rookie, You're with me.
We're gonna go check
out the crime scenes.
Ah. Yes, sir!
Well then, Special Seven,
all officers, move out!
That's cool, but I'm actually
gonna stay right here.
Ha‐ha. You know what I mean.
[BELLEMER]
Uh...
[sighs]
So, that was
the last crime scene.
It's crazy, we looked
as hard as we could
in there, but we didn't
find a single lead.
Yeah, that's how
investigations go.
[car phone rings]
We got a report from Gramps.
It turns out, all the weapons
match, like we thought.
[ICHINOSE]
The same weapon, huh?
So, our perp really did kill
four people in one night?
Samurai got their schedules from
their election offices and
I've listed them out for you.
[NANATSUKI]
Wow, look at you go!
Come on, I'm a ninja!
[ICHINOSE] Hmph. Is Shikisai
there with you right now?
[AKANE]
Hello. Yep, I'm here. What's up?
Did you get alibis
for everyone involved?
[AKANE] Yeah. Nothing suspicious
about the families at all.
And their secretaries have
pretty clear alibis, as well.
So, it's not gonna be easy, huh?
That kinda figures.
Did you learn anything
about the victims?
Publicly, they really have
nothing in common at all.
Birthplaces. Districts.
They're all different.
Political viewpoints?
[NIJO] Don't match. They only
agree on tax reduction.
Every politician says that.
If they all want to
lower our taxes so bad,
then how come they
keep on raising them?
[NIJO]
I assume they compartmentalize.
This can't be right,
they have to have
something in common.
[NIJO]
Well, there is one thing.
[ICHINOSE]
What?
[NIJO] They all appear
in an online list titled,
"The Top Politicians
I Wish Would Die."
Wow, that's very
to‐the‐point, isn't it?
Let's see...
Their reasons are:
Hyogo Arisawa was accused of
abusing power at work,
Haruka Sakuma had an affair,
Kentaro Masuoka was
suspected of drunk driving,
and Motoyama helped people
buy their way into schools.
Nah, there has to be something
more serious than that.
What, no murder or anything?
Nothing.
[NIJO] I was told Public Safety
is apparently acting on
the theory that the killer
was influenced by this blog.
That's the latest.
Huh?
Is that information about
the victims even true?
[NIJO] Well, from what
I've found so far
it's just gossip.
Rumors from anonymous
message boards.
[NANATSUKI gasps]
There are no other sources?
It would seem not.
So, we think someone
randomly believed
those vague rumors
and killed all four of them?
That's crazy.
[ICHINOSE] I got a
strong feeling there's more
to it than that.
[NIJO] I could always dig
a little deeper if you like.
Yeah, I was just
thinking that maybe
you and Belle could
investigate the blog itself?
[NIJO]
Roger. Ending communication.
Man, that guy's like a robot.
No, he takes it seriously,
and we should, too!
Come on, Charisma!
I'll give it my best,
kid, don't worry.
But don't call me "Charisma."
Good morning, everyone.
[BELLEMER]
Hey, I got it!
Uhh... You figured it out?
[BELLEMER]
Take a look.
There's no doubt about it, this
entire blog is one big fake!
All of it?
[BELLEMER] Look, it has
a comments section. See?
[ICHINOSE]
Yeah, okay. So what?
[BELLEMER] Well, look, 83 out
of 89 comments were submitted
by the same provider.
So they're sock puppets?
No, it's more like
the whole blog is a sham,
from top to bottom,
every single part.
Even if you submit
a comment, it gets canceled.
Don't you think maybe
it just takes time to show up?
[BELLEMER] Nope. Everything
about this blog is managed
and controlled by
a single person.
I'm sure of it.
Why would anyone do that,
though‐‐it seems pointless.
[NIJO]
To make a threat.
What do you mean,
"make a threat"?
This site's source
of information is solid.
Oddly enough. It looks
like a collection of rumors
at first glance,
but it's a lot more.
The scandals posted
on the list are false,
but they're also actually true.
[ENDO] Okay, I don't get it.
What's that mean?
[NIJO]
The truth is worse.
All these accusations
are written
to sound fairly harmless.
Let's look at Hyogo Arisawa's
abuse of power, for a start.
It's actually a labor
issue involving corporations.
There have also been
some deaths from overwork.
The families tried to sue,
but the suit was dropped
at the last minute.
This love affair is the same.
It was actually
child prostitution.
In other words,
this blog isn't idle gossip.
It's written so the people
accused will realize
someone knows the truth.
[ICHINOSE]
Right, so, who runs this blog?
[NIJO]
Mitsuru Suga. Ex‐Public Safety.
[NANATSUKI]
Could he be the killer?
[ICHINOSE] No one's
stupid enough to cut off
his own source of income.
Besides, even in terms of the
timeline, there's just no way
he could have killed
all four in one night
completely by himself.
Then he's innocent?
No, he's definitely
not innocent.
[ICHINOSE]
I've got it.
Let's go solve
this thing, Rookie!
Seriously?
You've figured
something out this time?
Yeah, believe it or not, I have.
[SUGA]
It wasn't me.
[ICHINOSE]
Right, I know it wasn't.
I'm just gonna
run my mouth for a bit.
If you disagree with
anything I say, speak up.
You used your Public Safety
connections in order
to get ahold of some scandals
involving politicians.
But using that information
to threaten them outright
would be a crime. And you
didn't want to take that risk.
So, you thought the
smart thing would be to leak
the information in the
form of a third party's blog.
Of course, it made no difference
if the people who visited
the site believed it or not.
What mattered was that
the politicians themselves
would be able
to see it out there.
Must have been spooky. I mean.
Just imagine seeing something
that close to the truth.
A blog that looks like
a bunch of baseless rumors,
but the author was hiding the
truth of it all in plain sight?
Look. It is!
That blog is only gossip!
I just got the wrong idea!
[ICHINOSE] Yeah, I suppose
you'd have to claim that.
Right? For Public
Safety's sake, too.
[gasps]
[ICHINOSE] Don't worry,
that has nothing to do with it.
Although, there were
people working for those
four politicians who had
access to you, weren't there?
[ICHINOSE]
It was them.
[gasps]
The four secretaries
knew about you,
and they knew the scandals were
worse than anyone imagined,
so, the group of them
secretly joined forces.
It was apparently
a real group effort.
[gasps]
To put it simply,
it was a relay murder.
They made sure to
use the exact same weapon
so it looked like
the same killer,
and then they arranged
their schedules to
give each of them an alibi,
while also leaving
enough time to kill a politician
they had nothing to do with.
Of course, they needed
someone to take
the fall for it in their place.
Someone who killed
their four bosses
in a fit of righteous
indignation.
A mystery killer who was
concerned for the country.
And who do you
think fit the bill?
You... You mean me?
You're one smart guy.
At this rate, you're gonna
get pegged for the murders.
You okay with that?
But it‐‐ It wasn't me!
I swear to you!
The four of them, those
secretaries came to see me!
And they paid me. I filmed it,
but I didn't tell them.
Get me that footage.
[NANATSUKI] Didn't you
say that it was impossible
for one person to do
in one night, Ichinose?
[ICHINOSE] The end justifies
the means, as they say.
Besides, Suga didn't know that.
That's a good bluff.
Now to arrest those
four simultaneously.
Why all at once?
Well, just think about it.
They're close‐knit enough
to kill for each other,
so they're comrades
in arms, so to speak,
and everything
that that implies.
Good guys aren't
the only ones who will
sacrifice themselves to let
their comrades get away.
[NANATSUKI] So, we arrest them
all at the same time.
[ICHINOSE] That's the idea.
All of 'em in one fell swoop!
[KASUGA gasps]
[ICHINOSE]
Hey! Wait!
Huh? Where's he going?
Damn it! Someone musta
tipped him off.
Rookie! Go get him!
What am I, an attack dog?
This is nuts!
Man, he's fast!
[ICHINOSE] Hey, I mighta
forgot to mention,
that secretary is ex‐military.
Yeah, that would've been great
to know a little earlier!
Also, where are you?
[ICHINOSE]
Sorry, I'm not quick on my feet.
[NANATSUKI]
So, I'm on my own, then! Roger!
‐‐[KASUGA yells]
‐‐[NANATSUKI] Whoa!
[KASUGA huffing]
You're under arrest.
Hey! Stop! Just
turn yourself in, man!
No way‐‐ we're on
a mission, here!
We'll purge the
filthy politicians.
And then we'll create
our own government,
one built on
righteousness and justice.
They assured us that we were
fair and full of wisdom!
And that our desire
to kill was righteous!
Who is "they"?
[grunts]
Argh... Damn.
[KASUGA growls]
[NANATSUKI grunts]
Oh, no!
Die!
[BOTH grunting]
[KASUGA groans]
Like hell I will!
I hate corruption, too!
[KASUGA groans]
But murder's not pure, or just!
[KASUGA snarls]
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[bell jingles]
‐‐[crunch]
‐‐[KASUGA groans]
[KASUGA screams
I can't believe
I made it in time.
You okay, Rookie?
No, and you were
definitely not here in time.
Good work today.
Thanks, you, too.
[ICHINOSE]
How d'you feel?
I'm glad we were
able to solve the case.
[ICHINOSE]
Well, good. Glad to hear it.
Let's take care of one more
job while we're at it, though.
[NANATSUKI]
Another job?
The victims have
families, you know.
We have to report
the arrests to them.
Oh, right.
[ICHINOSE] The people who
were killed may have been evil,
it's true, but sometimes,
people like that only show
their good sides to their
immediate families, you know?
So, then...
Yes, reporting the truth
will make us seem like
the big bad guys in the
eyes of their families.
That must be tough. I bet.
[ICHINOSE] Once you can
do this part with a calm heart,
you graduate from
being of rookie.
Honestly, some people
never manage to.
[gasps]
Well, Let's go, Rookie.
Man, you're really gonna keep
calling me that, aren't you?
[KIRYUIN] Huh? What? The diamond
from that bank robbery case?
Doesn't the bank
have it for safekeeping?
[KIRYUIN]
It was stolen?
Next time: "The Threefold Trap."