[NANATSUKI] I was told
to find my own justice,
but what does that even mean?
Do I unflinchingly reject
evil without hesitation?
Do I fight? Should I win?
I don't know.
What is justice?
I wonder.
Still...
I'm stopping this guy!
[WARLOCK]
It's showtime!
[NANATSUKI grunting]
[ICHINOSE grunting]
Damn! I thought I could
at least hit that thing.
[gasps]
[ENDO]
Hmph.
[AKANE]
What's up, guys?
Sorry we're late!
Shikisai! Follow my lead!
[AKANE]
Right!
[AKANE bellows]
It's tough.
As if you could beat a dragon!
But I'm very much
enjoying watching you try!
Ah?
How about this?
[NANATSUKI grunting]
[NANATSUKI yells]
It worked?
Try taking another guess!
[gasps]
After all, we're different
species, you and I!
Don't forget who I am!
Dragons have always been
the rulers of this world!
You see, every last
one of you is inferior!
We're not done!
If we just keep breaking it over
and over, then we can beat him!
I'll smash as many
of 'em as it takes!
[WARLOCK] Hello, all you pieces
of shit around the world!
Do you see my dragon power?
Man, his voice is seriously
giving me a headache, now.
[ICHINOSE]
Think.
He's a dragon.
The faith of Nine's members
is the source of his power,
so obviously he's hoping
to spread that faith
all over the world.
The answer's clear.
We're gonna have to
take that faith away.
But the big question is how.
[phone rings]
Uh?
[NIJO]
Slacking off, as usual, I see.
[ICHINOSE] Nah, just goofin'
around with a dragon.
[NIJO]
Yes. I can see you from here.
I'm taking a breather.
Listen. There's not much
time, so I'll make this brief.
That park below. Get Warlock
down there, all right?
Ah?
I'll trust you.
Thank you for that.
Well, Boss,
I don't think your life's
in any danger, at least.
Thank you, Bellemer.
Look at that strength.
Which one do you mean?
Both of them.
Huh?
[KIRYUIN] Warlock is
disturbingly powerful.
He's stolen the power
of dragons and now he wants
the faith of humans to
help make him even stronger.
Wow. I didn't know that.
Yet, this team still fights.
Your fearlessness
always amazes me.
I have some very fine comrades.
[yells]
Hey, Belle! Come here!
[BELLEMER]
Yeah, what is it?
[ICHINOSE] I want you to use
your drones, if you can.
Evacuate residents
around the park.
Can you do it?
I sure can!
[BELLEMER]
This is the police.
Looks like there are some,
uh, well, bombs or something.
and they've been planted
all over this area!
So, all civilians,
please evacuate at once, okay?
[BELLEMER] I hacked into the
traffic light control system,
and I set all the lights
around the area to red.
[ICHINOSE]
Excellent work.
But, um, how's
this gonna help us?
[ICHINOSE]
Hm. Rookie!
[NANATSUKI groans]
[ICHINOSE] Try to force
Warlock to move to the park!
How do I do that?
Use your dragon
power and figure it out!
[NANATSUKI] There are things
I can do and things I can't!
[ICHINOSE]
Just make it happen!
Keh. Fine. Okay.
Well, then, here goes nothing!
Huh?
[bellows]
You really don't
know when to quit!
You can try all you like,
but it won't‐‐
[grunts]
[NANATSUKI grunting]
[WARLOCK chuckles]
You're a funny one.
Trying to shield your
friends, aren't you?
But you know, kid,
it's really only
a matter of time.
And, look!
It's the beginning of round two.
So why not now?
I'll say it again.
Warlock, you're under arrest!
[ICHINOSE]
All right, looks like he did it.
[AKANE] Okay, but,
what do we do now, then?
[ICHINOSE]
We've got to get down there.
Can't believe I'm saying
this, but let's run.
[BELLEMER]
Wait, you guys!
Check this out!
You two can both ride on these!
[BOTH]
Seriously?
Seriously!
So, uh, how sure
are we that this is
actually gonna work?
[BELLEMER] My calculations
say that it will!
Wait! Belle, listen!
It's just that recently,
I've put on a little‐‐
Waugh!
[shrieks]
[ICHINOSE screams]
That was really
something else, Belle.
Ninja, after all!
In that case...
I'll live up to my code name
and give 'em a little back up.
Have some of this.
[NANATSUKI]
I'm not beaten yet!
[WARLOCK] For someone
who hasn't got a chance,
you sure are persistent.
I do! Boss told me so!
And you believe that old fool?
Yes, of course I do!
In him. In my comrades.
Most of all, in justice!
[WARLOCK]
Justice is on my side!
After all, might makes right.
So, for as long
as I'm still a dragon,
I am justice!
[NANATSUKI groans]
[chuckles]
[NANATSUKI]
Maybe so...
Huh?
[NANATSUKI] Your justice
might make sense to you.
We all have our own paths.
Peh.
But I refuse to accept it.
See?
Then, evil is just as good.
But none of this changes
the fact that I'm a ruler here
and you're nothing but a slave.
[NANATSUKI]
What're you saying?
That you can control
the entire world?
[WARLOCK]
Yes. Yes, I certainly can!
Because this world is all mine!
This whole thing belongs to me!
We're different species.
Most humans don't see
things so black and white.
Fortunately, it's harder
for us to come to
that kind of conclusion.
I'm still deciding where I land
on a lot of things in this life.
But...
...I have no doubt
about stopping you!
Not one!
[ICHINOSE]
You got that right.
Ah. [gasps]
Hey, there!
Warlock. Tell me‐‐
Didn't you just say that
you controlled this world,
or something dumb like that?
I did. It happens
to be the truth.
No, you're wrong.
The real truth is that there's
not a single thing in this world
that's actually
under your control.
[WARLOCK] You really are quite
the comedian, aren't you?
Well? Enlighten me, then.
What don't I control?
[ICHINOSE]
The humans.
You have this idea that you
rule the human world,
and I hate to be the
one to break it to you,
but you're gravely mistaken.
What do you mean by that?
That you're wrong.
Sorry.
[WARLOCK]
What?
Hey!
Wait, is that...?
[LUKA]
I came to keep my promise.
Glad you could make it.
I don't get it, you're...
Super dead?
I'm sure you thought so.
Even if he wasn't,
he wouldn't defy you, would he?
Just unthinkable.
So, maybe I was wrong.
I mean, what difference
does it make?
A single, lowly human!
[ICHINOSE] I get that
you're big stuff, okay?
Literally. I get that you're
a superior species or whatever.
But the truth is,
you're a massive
failure as a dragon.
[WARLOCK]
What did you say?
[ICHINOSE] You can't exist
without human faith.
You wouldn't be
here without them.
Yet, you consistently
kill humans,
use them however you like,
and look down on them.
See the contradiction?
[WARLOCK]
What contradiction?
[ICHINOSE] Could it be that
deep down you're actually
jealous of humans?
[gasps]
You brainwashed this man
standing here in front of you.
It must've been great having
a person with a strong sense
of justice on your side.
But there's no doubt about it,
that pleasure was
born out of jealousy.
It was just your vengeful,
jealous desire to make him
fall as low as you.
I'm jealous?
What, me?
What a bunch of nonsense!
[gasps]
[ICHINOSE]
Look at that.
You're just a sad,
tiny creature who's frightened
and envious of humans.
Kind of a pathetic
sight, really.
[WARLOCK]
I will kill you.
I will.
You see? There it is, that anger
actually grows out of fear.
Ha, ha. Yep!
You're almost as
easy to read as a human!
Fun, right?
You go to hell!
[WARLOCK yells]
Is everybody ready?
[grunting]
Good to go, Ichinose!
[roars]
[AKANE yells]
[WARLOCK yelps]
Got a hit!
I'm coming for you!
Little pest!
[NANATSUKI grunts]
[AKANE gasps]
Nice work, Belle!
This ninja is joining the fight!
[BELLEMER humming]
Looks like your precious
dragon is crumbling!
[gasps] Who do these
humans think they are?
They should know better than
to piss me off by now!
[NANATSUKI]
Secured!
What? Just get off of me!
No, I'll never let you escape!
Please. As if I'd try!
Get the hell off!
[NANATSUKI yelps]
Hey, Mizuma!
I want you to kill all of them!
And that's a direct order!
I refuse.
No, I crushed your spirit.
So you can't refuse me.
Even if they're broken,
people can still
get back on their feet.
You're talking
complete nonsense!
Impossible!
It's not, no!
It's being human!
Hey, follow my lead.
[NANATSUKI]
Right!
[WARLOCK grunts]
Now, aim...
...and fire!
[roars]
It hit!
That's one shot
I couldn't afford to miss.
It's impossible...
This can't really
be happening to me...
Why...? Why is my power
vanishing now...?
[WARLOCK]
What is going on?!
Looks like you lost.
[WARLOCK gasps]
What...? What is happening...?
I don't understand...
I don't understand!
It's all over, Warlock.
Just give up.
'Cause, regardless
of what you may become,
we'll never submit to you again.
Don't you remember
what I told you?
You really can't beat humans,
no matter what.
I've lost to mere humans...
How can this be?
Hey, tell me, Warlock.
What was it that
finally made you fear
a lowly human being, huh?
That he broke free
of your brainwashing?
Or was it because he
managed to stand up to you?
[WARLOCK]
Damn you all!
Give me power!
Put your faith in me!
Come on, I have
the power you want!
I mean, I'm a freaking dragon!
[sobs]
I'm... superior to humans...
So... why...?
[KIRYUIN] Human beings
learned to live without us
a very long time ago.
[WARLOCK]
That's just nonsense!
Tell me what his
power is, then! Huh?!
Without a dragon's power,
there's no way he could even
have fought me like he did!
That may well be.
But, now, if you really
have lost all of your power,
then I don't need mine, either.
[gasps]
[NANATSUKI]
One day soon,
this power will
cease to be just.
A human's power
is enough for me.
[gasps]
You're a fool!
What the...? Hold on.
Why won't it activate?
The problem is that
no one believes in you anymore.
On top of the fact
that you can't believe in
yourself anymore, either.
[WARLOCK grunts]
No, that's...
That's ridiculous!
[screams]
Rookie.
[WARLOCK]
Kill me...
Kill me...!
[ICHINOSE]
Nope. We won't kill you.
I'm afraid you're going
to be arrested as a human,
and you'll be sentenced
as a human, too.
The time is 5:14 PM.
You are under arrest.
Why, you...
Take 'em off me!
Come on, I won't stand
for this‐‐ I can't!
Get 'em off!
Damn! Damn!
Damn it all!
Now, come with us.
I wanna thank you
for saving my life.
I, um...
[KIRYUIN sighs]
It's over.
[ICHINOSE]
Hey, it's been nine years.
Don't you want to catch up
with old friends?
[LUKA] Well, sadly,
I really haven't got the time.
If you're back
to being yourself,
atone for your crimes.
They'll probably go light,
all things considered.
I may be me again, but I can't
make my crimes go away.
I've done unforgivable things.
You're wrong!
That wasn't you!
[LUKA]
I'm not wrong, Ichinose.
It's the honest truth.
I'll carry the burden
of my crimes.
I don't expect anyone else
to take the weight on for me.
[ICHINOSE]
Not even your partner?
[LUKA]
My ex‐partner.
You've got one, and he's
almost too good for you.
Listen, Luka,
I know how you are.
This is for Nijo.
You think if you're arrested,
it'll cause trouble for him.
I'm only doing this for myself.
[ICHINOSE] You'll be crushed
under the weight of it.
That isn't true, Ichinose.
All of you were here for me.
Wanting me to find my justice.
Knowing that is enough
to keep me alive.
[ICHINOSE] You're talking about
a life of never‐ending sorrow
and pain and regret!
You'll get nothing,
and that is not okay!
Not now! You finally,
finally made it back!
[LUKA]
No. I was rewarded.
With him.
One great officer was born.
That's good enough for me.
I'm grateful.
[ICHINOSE] Have you decided
on your next job?
[LUKA]
No idea.
But I'll find my own cause,
and I'll stick to it.
That much, I do know.
[ICHINOSE] How will that
compare to a cop's justice?
[LUKA] Oh, it's similar,
but it's not quite the same.
All I know is, it's what's
right for me right now.
Ah.
See you 'round.
[LUKA]
Hm. Yeah, sure, see ya.
Oh, that's right.
You can see through any lie.
[ICHINOSE]
I wish I couldn't sometimes.
You never were any good
at lying, you know.
[LUKA chuckles]
You were a wonderful officer,
Detective Mizuma.
Goodbye.
It was a great honor to work
with you, Detective.
[NIJO panting]
Ichinose!
Where is my brother?
Or‐‐Mizuma?
[ICHINOSE] He's gone.
Vanished into thin air.
[ICHINOSE]
He did it for you.
Yes, I realize that, okay?
Of course I do, but I just....
[ICHINOSE] I get it, but you'd
do the same in his place.
You two brothers
are the real deal.
Let's go.
[ICHINOSE sighs]
Yeah, sure thing.
[NANATSUKI] It's hard
to believe that Tokyo‐‐
no, the entire world‐‐
may have been on
the brink of ruin.
Or that a man called
Warlock was a real dragon,
like the ones from times
past, and he had the
power to grant wishes.
It wasn't that we beat him.
It was that humanity,
as a whole, overcame him.
That's what Ichinose said.
Warlock refuses to speak now.
And, he'll probably
stay that way forever.
[NANATSUKI]
No one remembered his words
that supposedly resounded
throughout Tokyo.
Probably because
Warlock's power is gone.
Well, if it keeps things
simpler, that's for the best.
I mean, it was only
a drone to start with,
so if we swap out some parts...
[KIRYUIN]
Will it be all right?
I have to admit, I'm quite
fond of the little guy.
It's gonna be just fine.
Also... I'm gonna upgrade it
to fly three times as fast!
[KIRYUIN] Don't paint it
red or anything, all right?
[ENDO]
Huh? What'd you say?
[ENDO'S DAUGHTER]
I said I'm going to a movie
with a friend tonight.
So, you'll have to
eat dinner on your own!
[ENDO]
What? Hey!
Is that "friend" a boyfriend?
[groans]
[NANATSUKI] We're still here,
just the same as ever.
You'll be leaving
Japan for a while.
Can you speak
English or Chinese?
[LUKA]
Well enough, I'd say.
[BLACK PEARL]
So, that's your name.
It was kind of an odd request.
A name with a "seven"
in it, I mean.
[LUKA]
As long as I have this number,
I'm pretty sure
I can live anywhere.
[chuckles]
[NANATSUKI sighs]
Not good. It's too peaceful.
[ICHINOSE]
'Cause we took care of things.
[NANATSUKI] I wonder if we'll
be busy again before long.
[ICHINOSE]
We won't.
Which works great, since I'm
planning to take it easy
from now on.
You've got a long time
before retirement.
[ICHINOSE] My current motto
is "less, and for longer."
[NANATSUKI]
News to me!
And here I thought it
was "less and less."
[ICHINOSE]
So I'm just gonna waste away?
Nanatsuki,
please stop slacking off
and get back to work.
You don't want to be
a failure of an adult
like Ichinose, do you?
Dude. He's talking
trash about you.
[notification dings]
Oh! Hey, we've got a murder!
[ICHINOSE]
If Nine's not involved,
then it's gonna be
out of our jurisdiction.
[BELLEMER]
Hmm... Yeah, about that...
[KIRYUIN]
She's right.
It would appear that
this is one of ours.
[ICHINOSE grunts]
[KIRYUIN] Warlock may be gone,
but the terrorism he perpetrated
to regain his dragon
power is alive and well.
And there are humans who
don't know when to quit.
We all know how
frightening human beings can be
when they get greedy.
There's nothing
new under the sun.
We've got this.
Special Seven, let's move out!
Thank goodness
we've got work to do!
It's about time!
I can't say I like it,
but I am a little relieved.
It means it's
too soon to retire.
Belle, you'll gather
intelligence as usual.
You bet!
Shikisai and Gramps!
Go find out what the
victim's family has to say.
[BOTH]
Understood.
I'll do witnesses.
Gather accounts of the crime!
And we'll investigate the scene.
[NANATSUKI]
Right!
[ICHINOSE]
All right, let's go...
...partner.
[chuckling]
[KIRYUIN]
Hm.
[BELLEMER giggles]
Ah. Yes, sir!
Partner. Proud to serve...
...Special Seven!