[NANATSUKI]
Ichinose.
Stop slacking and help me
sort these papers, man.
Have you seen
how many there are?
Sorry, I'm on break right now.
Hey, Belle, you don't
have to lug around
all that heavy stuff.
I'm sure Endo would be
happy to help if you asked.
[ENDO]
Who, me?
Nah, my hips have really
been acting up lately.
Sorry.
[BELLEMER] I'll be fine!
I am a ninja, after all!
You know what,
I've never understood
that whole ninja thing.
Nanatsuki. Less talk
and more work, please.
Are you kidding me?
[KIRYUIN] Warlock has
been arrested and Nine
has totally collapsed.
We've had to deal with
a couple of copycat crimes,
but no major
incidents, thankfully.
We're at peace.
In other words,
we're pretty much
obsolete these days.
[KIRYUIN laughs] I have some
mixed feelings about it,
but yes, work is hard to find.
[laughs]
[NANATSUKI]
At least we've still got jobs.
Ah! Is that... Nijo?
Oh, wow, that sure
does take me back.
What?
Why does it look like
Nijo is being questioned
in this picture?
Uh‐oh, guys.
I guess we're in for it.
[ENDO]
He saw the photo?
Right, Belle, tell him.
Okay.
We've solved the case
and the criminal is...
...Nijo!
What?
She's joking.
[NANATSUKI]
Ah?
[NIJO]
Who took this?
I've never seen it.
I thought it might
come in handy one day,
so I snapped a quick pic.
And I thought it was
freakin' hilarious,
so I left it in
the official report.
That's a clear abuse of power.
Okay, what?
That's enough.
Rookie's confused.
Cut the crap and
tell him the whole story.
Unless you wanna
upset the poor kid.
Yeah! Please tell me.
What's the deal with that photo?
Already bored.
I'm begging you, please!
This'll take a while,
you better get comfy.
[AKANE] Hmm... How do we even
start a story like this?
[BELLEMER] Well, guess we
should put the kettle on!
[NIJO] That was before I had
any clue that my brother,
‐‐Luka, was still alive.
‐‐[NANATSUKI] Man, just tell me!
[ENDO] Hey, hold on.
Where's that new sweetener?
[NANATSUKI]
Hey!
[NIJO]
Gimlet, please.
I see your convictions
are still as strong as ever.
Just like they were
the day we first met.
And? As for my request?
[BLACK PEARL]
Here's what you asked for.
Addresses and personal details
of all Nine members involved
in the airport attack.
[BLACK PEARL]
And the profiles of every member
of Special Seven.
You'll find it all in there.
[BLACK PEARL]
As for Kiryuin Sakon...
Unfortunately, I can't
corroborate the intel.
No one knows if
it's accurate or not.
Much obliged.
[BLACK PEARL]
A word of warning, if I may.
Information can be both
a weapon and a bright light
in the darkness.
One must shed light carefully,
or else the lurking darkness
will be his downfall.
Take care, friend.
I understand.
Special Seven, huh?
Cheers to that.
[KIRYUIN]
I'll introduce you.
Everyone, I'd like you to meet
Special Seven's newest member.
His name is Kujako Nijo.
Yes, indeed. It's a great honor.
This guy‐‐He was
on the career track,
but for some
incomprehensible reason,
he's cast that aside
and asked to be transferred
to our little unit.
So you had all better
be nice to him, or else.
[AKANE]
Of course we will.
Welcome aboard.
And kiss your dreams
of promotion goodbye.
Sorry.
[ICHINOSE] Pft. So, why'd you
want to be in Special Seven?
What do you mean?
We're a specialized
unit that deals
with Nine‐related crimes
and nothing else.
No one in their right mind would
ask to be transferred here
unless they were obsessed with
justice, or they harbored some
burning grudge against Nine.
[NIJO grunts]
That's dualistic thinking.
You see.
I have come to you as someone
who feels a certain duty
to look after notorious misfits.
I get it.
You're gonna make
things easy for us?
That is so nice of you.
[NIJO grunts]
Well, then, we humbly
accept your offer.
Take good care of him, okay?
[NIJO]
Huh?
[groans]
Seriously?
[BELLEMER] Ichinose, I collected
the data we swiped
from Section One earlier.
You wanna come
check it out with me? Uh?
Where is Ichinose?
He was just here,
wasn't he?
"Patrolling convenience stores."
[BELLEMER growls] Slacking off
right under a ninja's nose?
Impressive.
[NIJO clears throat]
If you give me
the data, I'll look over it.
Thank you!
You should make
Ichinose treat you later.
[NIJO]
There's no need.
[NIJO sighs]
‐‐[applause]
‐‐Ah?
Excellent work.
Yeah, you're pretty damn good.
We have to be, we're
fighting vicious criminals.
Combat skill is
the bare minimum.
Hear that?
I sure did.
Okay.
But we're supposed
to subdue the criminals,
not blow their brains out, so
you may want to work on that.
This yields better
evaluations in training, though.
Hot damn.
All right.
Magnificent.
What the‐‐?
Aw, jeez.
[NIJO grunts]
[ICHINOSE] But we're supposed
to subdue the criminals,
not blow their brains out, so
you may want to work on that.
Tch. Of course not.
"Subdue"?
Why should I let them live?
They killed my brother.
And you let them do it.
[ICHINOSE]
Hmm.
[KIRYUIN groans]
Well.
Things have been quieter than
usual around here lately.
I think that has a lot to do
with Nijo being a part
of the team now.
Yeah, he even picks up
some of Ichinose's slack,
which helps.
Not living up to
your name, Charisma.
I never thought it fit.
‐‐[BELLEMER, AKANE giggle]
‐‐[phone ringing]
[KIRYUIN]
Hello?
Yes. He's right here. Why?
Something up?
Oh, I see.
Last night?
You think we've got a case?
[KIRYUIN]
Listen up!
It seems that there's
been a murder.
Three former members
of Nine were all killed.
Just last night.
[gasping]
[KIRYUIN] And, as it happens,
all three of the victims
were involved in
the airport attack.
They were part of the team
handling airport security
when the attack occurred.
They were sentenced to do time
in prison for leading Warlock
and the actual perpetrators into
the airport, but they were all
released about a year ago.
[KIRYUIN] Their estimated time
of death was somewhere between
11 o'clock last night and
3 o'clock this morning.
And whoever shot them knew
which vital organs to hit.
[ICHINOSE]
Sounds like infighting.
[ENDO] They were former members,
maybe they were silenced?
[AKANE] And that means Nine
was probably behind it.
Yeah, about that...
The rifling marks on
the bullets recovered from
the scenes of the crimes.
They're a match for a very
specific police firearm.
This one hits
pretty close to home.
It's the firearm issued to Nijo.
[gasping]
[ICHINOSE]
Hmm...
[ENDO]
So, is he gonna be arrested?
We shouldn't jump to
conclusions and assume
he's the killer just yet.
For one thing, he flat‐out
denies involvement.
[ICHINOSE] Yeah, but bullets
from his gun were recovered
from all three scenes.
So far, all the
facts point to Nijo.
And it looks like
the case against him
keeps getting stronger.
[BELLEMER] Section One recovered
security camera footage
that puts Nijo near the crime
scenes a few minutes
before the murders.
Gives 'em some good
circumstantial evidence, right?
Yeah, maybe
a little too solid, though.
[AKANE]
What about a motive?
Got me there.
[GROUP sighs]
Well, in any case,
Section One and Public Safety
will be watching him like
hawks for a little while.
So, until the real perpetrator
turns up somehow, I think
we should all prepare ourselves
for Nijo's imminent arrest.
I see.
It sounds to me like
you're convinced Nijo
didn't kill those guys.
[KIRYUIN] I've been observing
people for a very long time.
I'm confident in my judgement.
[police siren wails]
I've worked out
a deal with Section One.
Nijo, you'll have to surrender
your weapon to them until
you're cleared of the crimes,
but you can continue
to work with us here
for the time being.
Wow, Boss!
Way to go!
[KIRYUIN] The fact that Nijo
has a spotless track record
helped a lot.
There's no way
I could have gotten
the same deal for Ichinose.
Yeah, rub it in.
[KIRYUIN]
So, Nijo.
You'll be under
surveillance for a while,
but try not to
let it get to you.
Right.
[ICHINOSE] Tell me,
what did you talk about
with those three low‐lifes?
I'll tell you the same thing
I told the detectives,
because it's the truth.
I've never met those three men.
Heh. You expect
anyone to believe that?
[NIJO sighs]
Where are you going?
Are you okay?
I am innocent.
If I have to prove it, I will.
[ICHINOSE]
Hmm...
[BLACK PEARL]
Been framed, have you?
[NIJO]
Most likely.
[BLACK PEARL]
What did I say?
To shed light carefully or the
darkness might take you down.
[BLACK PEARL] You're either up
against Nine or someone else.
Someone who would prefer
this case not be
investigated too thoroughly.
It doesn't matter which.
They've finally
given themselves away.
All I have left to do
is corner them.
What about Nijo?
He's not coming, huh?
He's filed an official report.
Okay. What do you think?
About what?
Do you think it's even possible?
For a cop's piece to get
pinched without his knowledge.
If it is, I'm not sure
he should be a cop.
But, based on what I
know of Nijo's character,
carelessness... seems unlikely.
But, then, that would
mean Nijo had to fire
the shots himself.
Hey, Belle.
[BELLEMER]
Yeah? What?
Can you check
on something for me?
Figure out how far away
these security cameras are
from each of the crime scenes.
And while you're at it, how
many of them are installed
in that general area.
Quickly.
I'm on it!
[NIJO] I'm impressed
by your aim, Nagase.
[NAGASE]
Nijo.
You're highly skilled.
Certainly enough to kill your
targets with a single shot.
Just like what you
did to those three.
[NIJO] There are reports on the
bullets from the crime scenes.
I'd like you to get them for me.
[BLACK PEARL] You mean your
bullets that were recovered
near the bodies?
Wouldn't it be faster to
ask Section One for them?
I can't.
The police might
be involved with this.
[BLACK PEARL] You think the
real killer is a police officer?
[NIJO] The bullets were
most likely identified before
the victims were even shot.
It all happened too efficiently.
[BLACK PEARL]
Hmm.
It's too neat and clean
to be a normal criminal.
[NIJO] First, there's the
security camera footage.
Counting convenience stores and
traffic intersections alone,
there are at least ten
cameras in the vicinity.
But in the ten hours
after the murders,
which happened in the dead
of night, they were able to
comb through all that tape
and positively identify me.
And second,
almost simultaneously,
they were able to
analyze and ID the bullets
found at the scenes.
[BLACK PEARL] But, still,
those bullets were yours,
were they not?
[NIJO] Indeed, those bullets
were technically fired from
the weapon I was issued‐‐
I don't dispute that,
but they didn't
kill those men.
[NIJO] The only people
present for my training
were Ichinose, Endo...
...and you, Nagase.
[NIJO] And when the three
of us left that day,
you recovered the
bullets I had fired.
After shooting those three men,
you left my bullets at the
crime scenes, near the bodies,
in place of your own.
You should have been
a bit more careful when
you selected the
bullets, though.
I was only trying to
buy myself a little time.
Enough to carry out the plan.
Which was for you to
off yourself with this.
Ah, my gun.
I'm glad to see it.
So why'd you kill them?
Because all three of them
were worthless cowards
and they betrayed him.
Ah! You mean you're with...
They turned away from worship
toward the banal and profane.
Death to all traitors!
I will offer Him their blood
and souls as sacrifice!
[NIJO grunts]
Your snooping gave
me the perfect cover
to carry it out!
And now, I offer your blood
and soul to Him as well!
[NAGASE groans]
[NIJO]
So you're a member of Nine?
That's perfect.
You can answer the questions
I was gonna ask those three.
What happened
in the airport attack?
I might let you live...
...if you tell me why
Luka Mizuma had to die!
Tell me everything you know!
What happened to him?!
Luka... Mizuma...?
[NIJO]
Answer me!
I have no idea who that is.
I didn't even infiltrate
the police force
till after the attack.
No...
[wheezes]
So then, are you satisfied?
Huh, Nijo?!
[ICHINOSE] Lower your weapon
or I'll shoot to kill!
Ichinose?
But why?
Oh, I just arrived at
the same conclusion you did.
I was there for
practice, too, after all.
Me, too, and I saw
how bad your aim was!
[gasps]
[ICHINOSE grunts]
Looks like you
wasted a trip, buddy.
I'm not your buddy, guy.
[gasps]
You better be glad you're
such an important witness.
[groans]
Man, I'm too tired
for this crap.
Did you drop your
gun like that intentionally?
What, now?
Oh, yeah‐‐I have bad aim,
so I knew I couldn't hit him,
and, like he said,
Nagase knew it, too.
Made more sense to
pass the gun to a sure shot,
so I did.
Even though you would
be risking your life?
I just figured
I should take a chance.
[sighs]
[KIRYUIN] Nijo has been
cleared of all wrong‐doing,
and the real killer is
safely in police custody.
All's well that ends well!
I don't think it ended
all that well, though, Boss.
The higher‐ups took the killer,
and Ichinose got injured.
Actually, it could have
ended a lot better for him.
My arm hurts,
and I'm too tired to
do any work today...
[laughs]
Plus, a scandal
happened in the force.
Covering up a whopper
like that is gonna take
some doing, you know?
Who would have thought
that Nine even had adherents
in the police ranks?
They're going to make
another grand sweep
of the entire organization
because of all this.
We'll probably be getting a
summons from Public Safety
before too long, so be ready.
Ah, welcome back!
I've caused you more
trouble than I'm worth.
[AKANE]
And worry.
But, no, not any more
than you're worth.
[chuckles]
I was able to figure out
what was going on.
But only because Shikisai and
the others put in the long hours
and leg work gathering intel.
That's right.
You made these old bones
do a lot of walking.
You should delegate
more to your resident ninja!
I apologize.
[ENDO]
Hmph.
[BOTH giggle]
In any case, we're glad
you're on the team, Nijo.
So welcome aboard.
Things may have gotten off
to bit of a rough start,
but I think you're gonna like
it here in Special Seven.
Well. Now that Nijo's
been reinstated,
how about we knock off work
for the rest of the day
and have a little
welcome‐slash‐welcome‐back
party in his honor?
All right! Anyone else
craving Chinese?
Sure, just gotta let
the sweetheart know.
I'm in the mood
for some Shaoxing wine.
Yeah, let's get drunk.
Your treat, right, Boss?
[KIRYUIN]
You know it, baby!
[NIJO]
So, this must be Ichinose.
[LUKA]
Yeah. He's my partner.
[NIJO]
Your partner?
What's his story, then?
[LUKA]
Hmm? Hmm... Good question.
And, to sum it up,
I think he's somebody you
could trust with your life.
That's some high praise.
I really mean it.
He's trustworthy.
[NIJO]
Shiori Ichinose, the partner
Luka trusted more than anyone.
Why did he save me?
If he could do that,
why couldn't he save Luka?
[KIRYUIN]
Hey, Nijo. We're leaving.
Attendance is mandatory.
[NIJO]
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, Luka.
I can't let myself
trust him yet.
Are you guys telling me
all that actually happened?
[KIRYUIN]
It's crazy to think about.
The fact that Nine already
infiltrated the police force
that long ago...
[NANATSUKI]
Wow...
I was already
impressed by Nijo's ability
to gather and analyze
info back then!
But I'm even more impressed now.
He's like a ninja!
His audacity struck me,
more than Ichinose's.
Oh, no doubt, man.
I used to think he was
so unapproachable.
He may be more
aloof now, though.
Really?
I was just about to say
that he's softened up
a lot since then.
[NANATSUKI]
Well...
Don't say it!
[grunts]
You see?
Nothing soft about that.
Ah. That reminds me:
we owe someone else
a welcome party.
You didn't get one, huh, Rookie?
[GROUP]
Hmm?
Hey, no fair!
Why did Nijo get a party,
but I didn't?
No, we had pho a while back‐‐
that counts as your party.
I mean, we were pretty busy,
with Warlock on the
loose and all that stuff.
All this reminiscing
put me in the mood for
Chinese food again!
It's settled, then.
Time to call it quits and throw
Rookie a belated welcome party!
Good call.
Huh? What about
all this paperwork?
[ICHINOSE] You can finish it
up tomorrow, right, Rookie?
‐‐[NANATSUKI groans]
‐‐[overlapping talking]
Come on, man,
you gotta help me out!
[KIRYUIN] Please don't order
anything too expensive.
I'm trying to save.
[ICHINOSE]
Come on, Nijo, we're leaving!
[NANATSUKI]
Nijo!
Relax, you two‐‐
I'm right behind you.