[WARLOCK] Gentlemen, let me
tell you a little about magic.
[WARLOCK]
Magic is the last miracle
we have left in this world.
It can turn battlefields into
wastelands, restore the vibrancy
of youth to
the old and infirm,
and create the kind of
beauty that captivates
all living things.
[WARLOCK sighs]
Sad, though.
The way it was sealed away
from the unwashed masses.
It's been placed under
the control of the government,
so now, rather than
citizens being able
to utilize that magic,
you are left powerless
and pitifully without hope.
So, what do you do?
‐‐[BOY crying]
‐‐[WARLOCK] You know the answer.
If you can't get your hands
on miracles honestly,
you'll just have to steal them.
Isn't that right, my friends?
[WARLOCK]
We need sacrifices and a ritual.
[WARLOCK] Let's drop
our books, take up arms,
and bathe in blood!
[WARLOCK]
Flock to Nine!
Become Nine!
That is our destination!
You really think it'll work?
What are you? Some kind of fool?
Yes. Of course
it's going to work.
I am a terrorism consultant.
Yes, that may be,
but you do realize they're
a bunch of amateurs, right?
Hey, don't worry.
I made sure to mix
some in with them.
[WARLOCK]
Pros, I mean.
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
I see.
Besides.
However it ends up playing out,
I know I'll enjoy it!
The whole world's in need
of some amusement.
Well, here it is!
How many are going to die?
Shooting for a record!
Now, hip, hip, hooray!
Heh. You're not getting
into the spirit.
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
That's just how I am.
So what you're telling me is,
there was a magical
response detected similar to
the bombing case
from the other day?
[ICHINOSE]
Yeah, Belle picked it up,
since magic is banned outside of
government‐controlled locations
and all that.
That makes sense.
Tell me, what do
you know about magic?
That it's mysterious, I guess?
[sighs]
Magic is actually
dragon technology.
But there've always been a few
people around who could use it.
They've made all kinds of
unbelievable things possible.
Widespread destruction,
reviving the dead,
restoring youth, et cetera.
It can do anything.
So, the rumor is, the
government always jumps in
and locks it down
as soon as it's found.
Hold on.
Are people who can use magic
taken by the government, then?
[ICHINOSE] Well, they're
precious human resources
who can do things
regular people can't.
What's up? You have
someone in mind, or what?
Oh, no! Definitely not!
Hey, wait. How come
Belle isn't locked up?
That's different.
Boss is her legal guardian.
Even the government
can't touch her.
‐‐[NANATSUKI] Wow.
‐‐[phone buzzing]
You talking about
a ninja behind her back?
[BOTH]
No, ma'am!
That's right, boys,
better watch your step.
'Cause I'm a ninja!
Well, anyway,
we need to start looking
for traces of magic.
Yes, Sir!
So, how do we do that?
Y'know, that's
a good question, Rookie.
[ICHINOSE]
I have no idea.
What's the point, then?!
[ICHINOSE chuckles]
Just think of it as a break
and take it easy.
I'm gonna go take a look at
the map of this building.
What do you mean, a break?
You shouldn't be
slacking off again.
[NIJO]
Why don't you make him stop?
Holy crap! You scared me!
‐‐[phone vibrates]
‐‐[ICHINOSE] Mm?
[gasps]
[muffled] Ichinose here,
definitely investigating.
Working very hard.
[AKANE]
Of course.
Tell me, how are
those beautiful, greasy
food court burgers today?
Uh... No, it's actually a part
of the investigation, so...
[AKANE]
I'm on standby, so I'm stuck
with instant noodles again.
[BELLEMER] Hey, I wanted
to order ice cream earlier!
[AKANE]
No way.
Too bad.
[ENDO] You've got some
real nerve, there, Ichinose.
How 'bout if you lower
your head a bit?
That way I can line up
a good shot.
I'd like some gelato, myself‐‐
a double with apricot
seed and chocolate.
[ICHINOSE sighs] So, what,
you're taking it out on me?
[ENDO] Sure am! You got
a problem with that?
[NIJO] You're going to be on
your feet for another half day.
You'd better get
something to eat.
Okay, but where are you going?
[NIJO] It appears Public Safety
is operating in the basement.
I'm going to check it out.
The basement?
There's been information
about an arms deal.
It seems to have
them pretty worked up.
They'd have your head if
you were to get in their way.
Ah! I'm happy to stay out of it.
[NIJO]
Later, then.
But, um...
About Ichinose.
Are you referring to the fact
that I don't trust the man?
I am.
Don't you find that pretty sad?
That you don't trust him?
One of your fellow officers?
Same boat. Heh.
Wait, you really
just figured it out?
Nah, but it sure woulda
made our lives easier.
[panting]
Gonna leave this to you.
I'll stop you if you screw up.
Right!
[NANATSUKI]
I know he's stand‐offish.
I mean, I get that.
But I don't know,
I have a very hard time
believing he would just
let his partner die.
[NIJO]
Nevertheless. The fact remains,
Detective Ichinose
is callous enough
to sacrifice his comrades.
It's just... so weird.
Well, you're free
to believe what you want.
I simply don't trust him,
and I never will.
[NANATSUKI sighs]
[PUBLIC SAFETY 5A]
Freeze! On your knees!
Hands in the air!
You mean like this?
[gasping]
[gunshots]
Rock and roll.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
I'm afraid you haven't
paid for that yet.
[gasps]
[NANATSUKI]
I was just wondering...
About what?
You, actually.
What's your first
name, Ichinose?
[sighs]
Don't ask.
Hey, c'mon, you can tell me!
It can't be that bad.
Don't wanna.
Why not? What's it matter?
No way, not a chance!
[BELLEMER] Would you
please get back to work?
Now. I'm being really serious.
I picked up something
magical in that area!
Uh, could you
possibly give us
more specifics on where?
[BELLEMER]
Are you kidding me?
You mean you guys can't
search a building of this size
on your own?
[ICHINOSE] I mean, we did check
out every conspicuous place
we could find on
the first four floors.
[BELLEMER]
What about the basement?
It's just that
Public Safety is still
working down there.
We can go check it
out whenever they get done.
Oh, right! By the way!
Can I eat the‐‐
‐‐Huh?
‐‐What the...?
[MAN 5A]
Weird, the call dropped.
[MAN 5B]
What's happening?
[WOMAN 5A]
Hey, why can't I get through?
[ICHINOSE]
A jamming signal.
[gasps]
[SHOPPERS yelling]
[NANATSUKI]
What do we do?!
We gotta move!
[gunshot]
I want silence!
Do you understand?
We are the children of Nine.
I repeat. We are the
children of Nine!
[TERRORIST 5A] Here,
in this shopping mall, today.
We will perform a sacred ritual!
As long as you do what we say,
you won't be harmed!
It's Nine!
[TERRORIST 5A] I repeat,
if you do as we say,
you will not be harmed!
A panic would only
make things worse.
We don't know how
many of them there are.
Yeah, but‐‐!
[ICHINOSE]
Don't worry.
Sounds like they don't plan
to kill the hostages yet.
Although, it's only
a matter of time.
Oh, great, of course
they've blocked all the exits.
Damn.
[gasps]
Right. It's time to go!
Ah...!
[NANATSUKI]
What do we do?
We have guns,
but there are too many of them,
and they have hostages,
so our hands are kinda tied.
[NANATSUKI] I guess so. And with
our phones not working, either.
Yeah, it looks like
they're being jammed.
[NANATSUKI]
Why would they do that?
[ICHINOSE] There's something
they don't want getting out.
No clue what that
might be, though.
Come on. Let's do something!
"Something"?
It's more dangerous to act
recklessly than to do nothing
when lives are on the line.
But, sir. These guys
seem really unhinged!
Didn't you see it?
I feel like they're gonna
kill the hostages!
[NANATSUKI grunts]
Hush...
Huh...?
‐‐[knocking]
‐‐[TERRORIST 5B] Hey, open up!
[knocking]
‐‐[thudding]
‐‐[TERRORIST 5B grunting]
Huh...?
‐‐Ah!
‐‐[NANATSUKI] Take this!
Oh, yeah. Get 'im, tiger.
[NANATSUKI]
I'm trying to!
[ICHINOSE] Now. He's some
kind of lousy terrorist.
Look, he left
the fingerprint ID on.
[NANATSUKI] Maybe he didn't
think he'd be found out?
[ICHINOSE]
Nah, prob'ly just an amateur.
Looks like they're all
communicating via group chat.
This guy's "Wyvern."
Nice name, dude.
[NANATSUKI] Is that really
a good idea, though?
Well, it's a whole lot smarter
than getting together
in one place.
Just gathering
increases their chance
of being arrested, after all.
[NANATSUKI]
But it's still a risk.
If someone checked those logs,
it'd expose all of 'em.
[ICHINOSE] Assuming anyone
could take the time to search
through all the logs.
[ICHINOSE] So, Rookie.
You much of an actor?
Are you kidding me?
No, do I look like I have
that kind of talent?
I'm already so sorry I asked.
Bathrooms are clear.
Staying on alert, though.
[TERRORIST 5C]
Roger. Come on back.
[ICHINOSE] Just give me
a minute. Nature calls.
[TERRORIST 5C sighs]
Okay, I bought us some time.
So, what do we do now?
Let's simplify our objectives:.
Don't let them kill
any hostages,
and squash their plans,
whatever they are.
Got it.
[ICHINOSE] Now, not to
change the subject, but...
Doesn't this guy
look a bit like you?
Huh?
[ICHINOSE]
I mean, your general build.
Huh...?
[ICHINOSE]
It's about the same, right?
[NANATSUKI]
Huuuh...?!
Do you really think
this is going to work?
Look, You saw that
chat screen, didn't you?
It's clear that these guys
have only talked online.
You'll be all good.
I think. Probably.
[NANATSUKI]
Not reassuring!
[ICHINOSE chuckles]
You don't need to do much.
You're just a Nine
terrorist, okay?
Do you remember Goto?
All you need to do is pretend
you're exactly like him.
[NANATSUKI]
That's easy for you to say.
[ICHINOSE] And hey,
don't forget your chat handle.
"Wyvern."
Wyvern. What's up?
What? Sorry.
Uh...
Did you hear?
There are passages connecting
this building to next door.
Floors two and three are secure,
but we only have
two guys on four.
[NANATSUKI]
So, should I go up there?
That'd be great.
If we hold this place all day,
that means we win.
Understood. On my way.
So. I'm going
to the fourth floor.
[ICHINOSE]
Cool, take me with you.
[NANATSUKI]
How?
All you have to do
is follow my lead.
[footsteps]
[ICHINOSE sobs]
[TERRORISTS]
Hmm?
[TERRORIST 5E]
Hey, what's the matter with him?
Please, help!
All I wanted was to go to
the bathroom, don't kill me!
I found him in the bathroom.
Taking him to the first floor
is a pain, so he's staying.
[TERRORIST 5E sighs]
Keep an eye on him.
‐‐[NANATSUKI] Yeah, sure thing.
‐‐[ICHINOSE wails]
Stay put and do as I say!
[ICHINOSE]
I‐I will!
I guess we'll go check out
that bathroom, too,
just to be safe. Damn it.
[sighs]
[ICHINOSE growls]
[NANATSUKI]
Listen, you told me to do it!
Yeah, I realize that!
It still pisses me off!
So, all that's left is Nijo.
[NIJO] They're more
skilled than I expected.
Definitely professionals.
But they're not moving.
What are they guarding?
[NIJO]
I can't expect any backup.
Not this time. It's all on me.
[car alarm blares
[TERRORISTS gasping]
[NIJO]
Got you!
[TERRORISTS grunting]
[NIJO gasps]
[gunshot]
Anything?
Nope, no dice.
I can't even control my drones
due to the jamming signal.
It's a big mess.
I'd hoped I could modify them.
But it looks like it'll take
way too much time, so...
So, we don't even
know if they're safe or not.
I guess sniping won't help.
The problem is,
we don't even know
how many there are.
Public Safety's in a
total panic since losing contact
with the team they
sent in earlier.
Plus, they can't seem to agree
on anything with the police
who are surrounding the mall,
so we can't count on them.
The terrorists claim their
organization is called Nine.
I'd say that's sufficient
grounds for us to act.
Okay, but act how?
[KIRYUIN] Well, first,
we'll have to make contact
with the three inside the mall.
I see no other way, and I feel
very sure that Charisma
will want to base
his plan on that.
Yeah, but we can't
use drones though!
[KIRYUIN]
Right. In that case...
We're going to send in
all of Special Seven.
Sending us in?
‐‐Through where?
‐‐But through where?
[TERRORIST 5E] Fourth floor
here, nothing to report.
This is a piece of cake.
[ICHINOSE] So, there are
eight on the first floor.
[TERRORIST 5E]
Hey! What's going on?
Ah. I'm, uh, kinda
scared of heights.
[TERRORIST 5E]
Keep your eyes up here.
Don't relax just 'cause
it's the fourth floor.
Right, I know that.
I just wish we at least
had some better weapons.
[TERRORIST 5E]
Them's the breaks.
'Fraid only the first floor
gets rocket launchers.
[ICHINOSE]
Rocket launchers, huh?
Too bad!
But if push comes to shove,
you know we've got that plan
to blow it all away, so...
[ICHINOSE] They're prepared
to kill themselves?
This sounds more and more
like the Airport Attack
nine years ago.
That's pretty scary, though.
What is?
You must be nervous, too.
You look scared.
Like hell I'm scared.
You know what I'd really like?
To take care of some
business before I die.
So, hey, what time is that?
[TERRORIST 5E] I'd say you've
got about eight hours or so.
[ICHINOSE] Okay. Sounds
like we should assume
the ritual starts
at midnight, then.
[meowing]
[ICHINOSE]
Hmm...
I'm pretty sure
someone on the chat app
used a cat icon.
Guess that's the guy.
[ICHINOSE]
Let's do it.
[NANATSUKI]
Right.
[ICHINOSE sobs] Damn it! I only
came here to buy cat food.
Why'd I end up in this mess?
If I die, my cat will starve!
Please, won't you spare me?!
Like I care!
[NANATSUKI]
Pipe down, you!
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[ICHINOSE whimpers]
Did you just say you had a cat?
Yeah, I have
a very rare calico tomcat.
‐‐[TERRORIST 5E] Really?
‐‐I know, it's weird.
There's not supposed
to be boy calicos.
I just found him by chance, and
I've been told by several people
he'd sell for ten million easy,
but that doesn't even matter
to me 'cause he's family!
Whoa, ten million?!
[TERRORIST 5F]
Hey, don't get distracted.
[ICHINOSE]
Do you have a cat, too?
You bet I do.
I have an F2 savannah cat.
Oh, another rare breed!
That's so cool.
Yeah, I guess.
She's the last treasure I've
got left in the whole world.
I overheard some of the stuff
you were saying earlier.
If... If I die in
eight hours, please...
I beg you...
[TERRORIST 5E sighs]
...take care of my cat!
Here, I'll give you my address.
Please, take it.
‐‐Huh?
‐‐[yells]
[grunts]
[TERRORIST 5F]
Bastards!
[TERRORIST 5F groans]
Hey, don't worry‐‐
I used the back of my sword.
[BOTH gasp]
[ENDO]
Heh!
Shikisai!
[AKANE]
Sorry to keep you boys waiting.
So? What's the plan?
[ICHINOSE]
Any backup?
[AKANE]
Mm‐hmm.
[NANATSUKI grunts]
[BELLEMER]
Hmm!
‐‐[NANATSUKI] Bellemer?!
‐‐Hah! I am a ninja, you know!
We just brought our usual team.
Seriously?
[ICHINOSE] All right. For now,
we need to work out a plan.
[AKANE] Wait, aren't we
missing Nijo, though?
Oh, he's in the basement.
[NIJO groaning weakly]
[NIJO]
Brother...?
[MYSTERIOUS MAN] Next time: "The
Six‐Minute Battle to the Death."