[BLACK PEARL] I had no idea you
were interested in psychology.
[NIJO]
That's because I'm not.
Just trying to pick up
enough to get by.
[BLACK PEARL] A makeshift
weapon can be dangerous.
[NIJO] Maybe, but it's
better than nothing.
Thank you for the "B" case.
Yeah, well, Public Safety
wouldn't believe me.
Whereas you did, and
then you paid me, to boot.
It's as simple as that.
Any news?
[BLACK PEARL] If you mean Seiji
Nanatsuki's history, it's clean.
He lost his parents
at a young age,
so he was raised
by his grandparents.
After the Airport Attack,
his goal was to become
a police officer. His record's
been spotless ever since.
[NIJO]
And the other matter?
[BLACK PEARL]
Yes.
For the past few days,
the dark web arms market
has been buzzing like crazy.
They seem to be buying up
illegal firearms and weapons,
dividing them up, and smuggling
them into the country.
[NIJO]
How many?
[BLACK PEARL]
Enough to start a war in Tokyo.
[BELLEMER]
So, here's the gist of the case:
Shintaro Eguchi's car
suddenly caught fire
while he was driving it.
Shintaro only
suffered light burns.
His son, Shunsuke,
who was riding with him,
was severely burned, though.
He's still in
critical condition.
[NANATSUKI growls]
If you let it
get to you emotionally,
you'll miss the important stuff.
I know that.
All right, so what makes you
think it wasn't an accident?
Three days before the drive,
the son's life was insured
for a hundred million yen,
and 30 mill for
severe bodily injury.
And the recipient...
is his father?
Exactly. As it happens,
Shintaro Eguchi also
lost two children
in an accident two years ago.
And accidents
that keep on happening
may not be accidents.
[ICHINOSE] That's what you're
going to find out, Rookie.
[NANATSUKI]
What, on my own?
I've got a stupid physical.
You're with him today.
Happy to work with you!
[NIJO] Listen, why don't you
go home, Nanatsuki?
Um... I'd like to carry
my own weight around here.
Yeah, I thought you'd say that.
Fine. Follow me.
Why again?
Boss's orders.
It's an experiment to see if
those two can get along.
Wonder if he'll be all right.
Nijo's got a notoriously
sharp tongue.
Nanatsuki puts duty first.
I think he'll be okay.
Nothing to worry about.
That rookie's tougher
than he looks. He'll be fine.
Don't you think you should
praise him like that
to his face once in a while?
[AKANE, ENDO]
Mm‐hmm.
Hell, no. Not a chance.
So, what's the plan?
Are we interviewing witnesses?
First, to the dealership.
I want to find out what
I can about our suspect,
Shintaro Eguchi.
It's hard not to
feel bad about
investigating the guy like this.
He's lost so much.
Yes, but if he
murdered three children,
I won't let him
get away with it.
We don't know
whether he did it yet!
[GOTO] Yeah, it caused quite
a bit of trouble for me as well.
How many times have you met him?
Mr. Eguchi?
We met on three occasions.
When he first came here,
when I visited his house
with the insurance
saleswoman, and then,
when I delivered his car.
And when you
met with Mr. Eguchi,
did anything
strike you as odd?
Matter of fact...
[SASAKI] I understand how you
must be feeling after losing
your children, but taking
out such a large amount
of insurance...
I don't care.
I have my sons' insurance money.
Don't you think you should
use that to improve
the lives of you and your son?
How I use
that insurance money
is totally up to me!
See, I just can't
relax. 'Cause...
'Cause someone's after my
family, do you understand?
Daddy?
[EGUCHI] Don't worry.
I'm gonna keep you safe!
That sounds... unsettling.
I'd say so.
[chuckles]
[SASAKI] Yes. Everything
Mr. Goto told you is correct.
[NIJO]
Does the insurance policy apply?
Yes. Though an
investigation is required.
I'm told the car that caused
the accident is being examined
at the factory.
If you don't mind,
please send us that
data when it's done.
Certainly, sir.
[NANATSUKI]
A persecution complex?
Well, if he's
suffering from paranoia,
insuring his kids
doesn't seem weird.
Maybe, but
something's still off.
Look, do you
always talk this much?
I'm thinking here,
and trying to drive.
Right. I'm sorry, sir.
[doorbell rings]
[NANATSUKI]
We'd like a word, please.
Go away!
Ow, that hurts!
‐‐You're seriously squishing
‐‐Yeah, I just told you
‐‐my foot, here!
‐‐to go away!
Please listen, sir.
We wanna talk.
It's just talk, that's all.
[NIJO sighs] Look, sir,
all this attitude does
is invite suspicion.
If I were you,
I'd speak up, now.
[EGUCHI grunts]
You both know.
I lost two children in
a car accident and I was
awarded insurance money.
Yes?
Of course, it did
nothing to lessen the pain.
Money is no consolation.
They were my precious children.
And can you tell us why
you insured Shunsuke?
[EGUCHI]
Because he's important to me.
Wh‐Why else does anyone do it?
I felt that if I were to insure
him using their money,
in a sense, they'd be saved.
Has his condition
improved at all?
[EGUCHI]
Still unconscious.
He may wake up, or he might
stay like that forever.
May I ask about your wife?
She ran out on me ages ago.
I should say "us."
She left three kids behind.
Have you already claimed
the insurance money?
No. Ms. Sasaki strongly
encouraged me to wait on that.
Did she? Why, because
you're under suspicion?
She said it was inevitable.
That it was hard to believe.
[NIJO] Three kids having
accidents within two years?
I'd agree.
[NANATSUKI] He didn't
look much like a killer.
I don't know. What do you think?
[NIJO]
I couldn't say yet.
I can't see inside people's
minds the way Ichinose can.
[NANATSUKI] I wish we
could have had him there
for the interviews.
[NIJO] Exactly how long do you
plan to depend on Ichinose?
Aren't you a full‐fledged
detective yourself?
Hey, it isn't like that.
Though, of course, I do
feel the same way sometimes.
Like, he manages to grasp
something I can't.
It's infuriating.
Kinda crazy, right?
Although, he can't escape
being called incompetent
at everything else.
That can't be true!
He misses every
time he fires a gun.
He also has a weak constitution
and is slow on his feet.
He's hardly cut out
to be a police officer.
Oh, so when he makes me
chase after a suspect
on my own, it's because
he can't keep up,
not 'cause he's slacking off.
That man will slack off
every chance he gets.
That's good to know.
[NIJO]
Nanastsuki.
You shouldn't put too much
faith in Detective Ichinose.
Huh?
[NIJO] He's quite capable
of sacrificing a partner
if it saves his
own skin, anyway.
Um, why do you say that?
[NIJO grunts, sighs]
Forget I mentioned it.
Next up, the hospital where
Shunsuke is being treated.
Come on.
Right. Coming.
[BELLEMER]
Hmm... I think something is off.
What's the matter?
Well, it looks like there are
two weird parts in the car.
Let me see.
[BELLEMER] It's like the
battery has burned up,
starting from this part
right here. Which means...
...that thing's
an incendiary device.
And that means this is
definitely a criminal case.
Just our luck.
[NANATSUKI] Are we going
to check on Shunsuke?
[NIJO] There's no need to.
First things first.
We're going to ask his doctors
if he shows any signs of abuse.
Do you really think...?
If he does, it will establish
Mr. Eguchi's motive.
Some parents really do despise
their children, you know.
He didn't seem like
that kind of person to me.
[NIJO sighs] And would you
decide he was the culprit
if he did?
It was just
an impression, that's all.
[NIJO] I want you to listen
and never forget this:
The culprit could be anyone.
Regardless of race, sex,
class, or any other factor,
crimes are committed
and criminals emerge
in every corner of society.
So the only sure way
to identify a criminal
is to gather evidence.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Changed my mind,
go check on Shunsuke.
Go ahead.
I'll speak with the doctors.
Okay.
[NIJO]
This won't do.
[knocking]
[NANATSUKI]
This looks like the right room.
Don't worry. We'll arrest
whoever did this to you.
I swear they won't
hurt anybody else.
I mean... I'm just a rookie,
but there are
people helping me.
[heart monitor beeping]
[NANATSUKI]
Hey, that's strange.
Where are the doctors?
[monitor beeping continues]
[separate beeping]
[gasps]
[beep]
[NANATSUKI gasps]
‐‐[bomb beeping]
‐‐[NANATSUKI] Ah!
[NANATSUKI]
I gotcha! [yells]
[yells]
[DOCTOR 4A] It appears
you sprained your ankle
when you landed.
Yes!
[DOCTOR 4A]
That's all, though.
Thanks for all your help!
Well, I'm glad you're all right.
Fortunately, I don't break easy.
Thankfully, the explosion
was confined to that room.
That being the case. Shunsuke's
been moved to another one.
According to Bellemer,
whoever made this device,
made the other one, too.
But how could she tell that?
The parts they used
conformed to the same standards.
See. Engineers of
this type tend to use
the same basic components
whenever they work.
Right, like back
in the "B" case.
[phone buzzing
Excuse me.
[gasps
What's wrong?
Those two children who died.
They weren't
Shintaro Eguchi's children.
What?
Why didn't you tell us?
The children who died
in the accident weren't
related to you by blood?
[grunts]
I didn't want to believe it.
I found out after they died.
[NIJO]
That's a lie.
[EGUCHI]
Ah...
Take a look at this.
Anything seem weird?
Why such an obvious
distance between yourself
and the two older children?
Because they weren't yours.
No, I... I didn't know!
I didn't mean for any
of this to happen.
You didn't kill them, did you?
[EGUCHI]
I didn't!
I believe you.
For now, at least.
Ah...
[NIJO] However, given that
the car you were driving
wasn't defective but
had been fitted with
an incendiary device, no one
but you could be the culprit.
At the very least,
I think we'd better take you
in for questioning.
It wasn't me!
That battery just
suddenly caught fire!
That's the truth!
[NIJO] So, you had
nothing to do with it?
That's right!
And your son?
Shunsuke, your
one surviving child.
Are you two related by blood?
[stammers]
[KIRYUIN] So? Tell me,
how do things stand, now?
Just heard. They're
finished with their inspection.
Now that they've confirmed the
car was fitted with a device,
they'll announce it.
Yeah, and you know,
once they do,
we'll have no choice
but to make an arrest.
I just don't think he did it.
Do you think that's
your instinct talking?
Or just wishful thinking?
[NANATSUKI sighs]
I feel like we're
overlooking something here.
The first accident
with the two kids?
Nah, that's not it.
Do you think there's
any chance Mr. Eguchi
has gotten
reckless with money?
Does he gamble?
[keyboard clacking
Nope, nothing that stands out!
His only major purchase
has been that car.
I wonder, though. That device...
Go on?
Well, think about his record.
There's nothing in it that's
remotely related to explosives.
That's true.
His record's squeaky clean.
[ICHINOSE] Come on, we all know
a little digging on the dark web
is all it takes to find reliable
instructions for how
to make a bomb.
Well, yeah,
I know, but even so...
Uh... I ran an analysis
on the incendiary device.
This thing wasn't made
by an amateur.
It's pretty intricate.
Like, whoever built
it had experience.
A pro. You mean like "B"?
That's right! Just like "B"!
[EVERYONE gasping]
[phone buzzing]
‐‐Hold it!
‐‐[DOCTOR gasps]
You're under arrest!
Attempted murder and
illegal use of explosives...
[NIJO]
...Hisamichi Goto.
I was able to confirm
Shintaro Eguchi's alibi.
He was at his work
during the case's timeline.
His coworkers
all corroborated it.
Huh. Then, I guess
we'll have to shelve our case
against Eguchi for now, anyway.
In that case, who did do it?
If it wasn't him, then who else
would have been able to plant
the device in his car?
The car's manufacturer, maybe?
[ICHINOSE]
Hmph. No, that doesn't work.
It wouldn't be easy to install
something like that while
the car was on
the assembly line.
I contacted the
manufacturer and got
the assembly data
from the car that was
involved in the accident.
Great! Thanks!
Oh, looks like there were no
problems during assembly.
It was identical to
all the other cars.
So, the incendiary device
was added after it was sold.
[ENDO]
Interesting.
That car was definitely
brand new, right?
[NIJO] Hold on. Couldn't
the dealer have installed
the device just before
delivering the car?
[ICHINOSE]
Belle.
Can you tell me how long it took
the dealer to deliver the car?
Did he take his time, or what?
Let's see...
I should be able to use security
camera footage to confirm
its departure time.
Oh! There are also
security cameras
near Shintaro
Eguchi's apartment.
So, I can check to see
when the car got there.
Delivery took roughly
three hours.
It shoulda been closer
to 20 minutes.
Like "vroomy‐vroom"!
Like what now?
"Vroomy‐vroom."
I've thoroughly
investigated this dealer.
Hisamichi Goto.
Let's see. Became
a car dealer ten years ago.
He'd been a guard
at a chemical plant.
Before that... he was
an assistant professor.
When I checked
in with the school,
it seemed like a scandal
was covered up.
What kind of scandal?
A student was seriously
hurt on an experiment
he was supervising.
And there was nothing
academic about it.
He was having them
mix liquid explosives.
What a great teacher.
Well, yep, that'll
tend to get you fired.
Then he was a security
guard after that?
Yeah, and he quit
almost right away.
Is it possible that could
mean he only took the job
in order to
manufacture explosives?
Hey, Belle, see if you can check
Goto's attendance
records at his jobs.
See if he's accounted for on
the dates of the bombings
we think "B" committed‐‐
can you do that?
[BELLEMER] He was regularly
absent from work on days
when a bombing occurred.
Last thing:
check the bomb used in this
case against the ones used
in "B's" terrorist attacks
and see what similarities
you can find.
Sure, let's see here...
They match!
Hold on.
I don't understand this‐‐
why would he go after
that child again?
Isn't that too risky?
He probably couldn't stand it.
The fact that
the child survived?
[ICHINOSE] No, the fact
that he miscalculated.
Because, after all,
it was "B" who made that bomb.
Perfectionism.
He couldn't tolerate the fact
that someone he believed
he'd killed had the
gall to survive.
[KIRYUIN]
Well then, everyone.
Sounds like we're up against
a terrorist who tries
to murder children.
I'd say, don't hold back.
Special 7, move out.
[NIJO]
Don't move!
[GOTO growls]
[grunts]
NIJO gasps]
[snarls]
Hear me now, mighty dragons!
I offer you a life!
Grant me your power!
[NIJO gasps]
[NIJO growls]
[GOTO yelps]
[yells]
[gasps]
Listen to me! There are
no more dragons around!
You lie!
Even if there were,
do you think they would
ever help you?
No, you don't get it,
they are helping me!
You're just a fanatic‐‐
A man compensating for a life
of failure and sick delusions.
You're nothing but a terrorist!
[NANATSUKI]
Nijo! Put it down! Don't shoot!
Given that he's "B,"
It's safe to assume he'll
get capital punishment
for terrorism.
Shooting him here would be
nothing more than dispensing
with the formalities, really.
That's not how the system works!
[NIJO] You were caught up
in the attack nine years ago,
‐‐weren't you?
‐‐[gasps]
Don't you hate them?
I don't know...
Yes, they're monsters.
But still...
Judging people's
crimes isn't our job.
This isn't justice, Nijo!
"Justice," huh?
Heh.
Now, please, lower your gun.
Come on.
[NIJO sighs]
Ah...
[GOTO gasps, cackles]
A sacrifice!
[gasps]
A detonator?
When did he‐‐?
[yells]
[grunts]
[groans, grunts]
I, um, had to subdue
the suspect is all.
[NIJO]
Hmph.
Oh, Shunsuke...
I'm so thankful that
you're all right!
I really am, my boy!
Oh, Daddy! [sobs]
I love you so much!
[EGUCHI]
I love you, son...
[BLACK PEARL] That was pretty
showy by your standards.
Was it?
[BLACK PEARL] Well, it's not
a bad idea to get the tutorial
out of the way now.
What does that mean?
Sometimes,
doing things that way
is just... called for.
You fed Hisamichi Goto
false information through
an informant to manipulate him.
I have that right, don't I?
It worked well.
Information's
a weapon. A pricey one.
In the sense that it can
also hurt the one who has it?
Deceit can be a weapon,
just as powerful as truth.
It's up to you whether
that weapon becomes
a peashooter or a missile.
[NIJO]
Yes. I realize that.
I know it's sudden,
but I'm about to
hand you a weapon.
[NIJO]
Location?
[BLACK PEARL]
Unknown.
The soldiers haven't been told
where they're going to hit.
It's likely only
the leader knows.
Okay, then. Here's where
we're going to strike.
Spread the word.
[NIJO] Even so,
an attack on this scale?
It'll be just
like nine years ago.
[BLACK PEARL]
Exactly.
Nine is planning to do
something big very soon.
What do you think?
Can you stop them?
[ENDO]
Next time: "The Fifth Seal."