[ICHINOSE] Rookie, carry
these guys into the bathroom.
[NANATSUKI] Yeah, sure.
Wait, can't you give me a hand?
[ICHINOSE] Ooh, 'fraid we've
got some important things
we need to think through here.
[NANATSUKI grunts, groans]
I'm proud of him.
He's come a long way, hasn't he?
Still a rookie, though.
[AKANE] That doesn't mean
you should keep treating him
like a child,
that's all I'm saying.
[ICHINOSE]
Yeah, yeah.
So, we can't get
in touch with Nijo
because of the signal
jamming, is that it?
Right, and he's in the basement.
We'll have to think of
a solution without him.
But hey, we've got
Boss here, too!
[KIRYUIN]
Hello, all! Yep, it's me!
Boss, what're you doing here?
[KIRYUIN]
Cheering you on!
Any chance you
could not, though?
[SECTION CHIEF 1A]
So? What should we do?
[DEPARTMENT CHIEF 1A]
Isn't this perfect, really?
I mean, whatever the
outcome of the attack,
it won't affect the plan at all.
Special Seven?
[DEPARTMENT CHIEF 1A]
You think they can beat
the terrorists with their
numbers? It's impossible!
Even if by some miracle
they do clear things up,
it won't matter.
[DEPARTMENT CHIEF 1A] This gets
us closer to our dearest wish.
I say we just sit back and
observe for the time being.
Here's the deal: the five of us
will have to make this work.
Poor Nijo. Do you
think he's okay?
Hey, it's not like
he's an amateur.
He'll be fine.
[ICHINOSE] There's no point
worrying about someone
who's not here, anyway.
[NIJO] Nevertheless. The fact
remains, Detective Ichinose
is callous enough
to sacrifice his comrades.
Right. Guess so.
[ICHINOSE] The only thing
that really matters right now
is how we're going to stop them.
[ENDO]
Any news on that?
Yeah, just one thing.
The terrorists we're dealing
with are mostly amateurs.
Their posture, the way
they handle their weapons,
their poor teamwork.
Everything about them
pretty much screams
"we don't know
what we're doing."
Amateurs can still
fire guns, though.
Oh, yeah, without
a doubt, they can,
but I think they'll
have some trouble
returning fire reflexively.
Hold on.
I thought these were the guys
who called themselves "Nine."
They can't be total novices.
Nah, they're rookie
terrorists‐‐there's no question.
Or else, disposable pawns.
I dunno, they said something
about performing
a ritual earlier.
Well, in my mind,
that all but confirms that Nine
is behind this entire thing.
[KIRYUIN] So strange. It's
hard for me to believe
they'd go to such lengths
for some absurd ritual.
[ICHINOSE] There are eight
on the first floor.
Then five on the second.
And five on the third.
It's the eight on
the first that matter.
[ENDO] Even if we take
out all the terrorists
on Floor One first, we'll be
done for if the buggers
on the other two
floors open fire.
[BELLEMER] I guess that just
means we'll need to take out
all 18 of 'em across three
floors, simultaneously.
Like, wham!
It'll take amateurs
about ten seconds
at the very least to notice
and physically react
to a disturbance
down on the first floor.
The game is knowing how
to spend those ten seconds.
"Game"? How 'bout
a more respectful word?
Have you ever seen him
show proper respect
for anyone or anything?
Words do matter.
If they didn't, we'd go ahead
and call you "Charisma."
[AKANE, BELLEMER]
Right?
[ICHINOSE]
Mind your own business. Now.
I've got it.
Belle and Shikisai,
attack the five on floor three.
You can enter
through the atrium.
Five men.
Well, if Belle's with me.
I think together we can manage.
I am a Ninja, after all!
[ICHINOSE] Gramps,
take the five on floor two.
You know I'll try,
but I can't take out five chumps
at once with this thing.
I'll pick up the slack.
I suck at this,
but if it's just backup...
That, I can do.
[KIRYUIN]
And what about me?
[ICHINOSE] Get in Belle's
backpack, would ya?
[KIRYUIN]
Fine...
And me? Where am I?
[ICHINOSE] You take out
the guys on the first floor.
[NANATSUKI whimpers]
‐‐[ICHINOSE growls]
‐‐Ow, jeez!
What're you doing?!
What the heck was that for?
I noticed some signs of stress.
Listen up.
Here are three cold, hard facts
about our current situation:
Number one.
At this rate, the hostages
will definitely be killed.
[NANATSUKI grunts]
[ICHINOSE] Two: right now,
we're the only ones here
who can stop it.
[ICHINOSE]
Three: as police officers,
we have a duty
to protect people.
[NANATSUKI]
I understand that.
[ICHINOSE] Good, because
protecting the hostages
is what we're doing.
End of story.
[ICHINOSE] We're not setting
out to kill the terrorists.
[NANATSUKI]
So, don't aim at vital spots?
No need. All we have
to do is stop them.
Just remember: we're cops.
We're not hitmen who
get paid to kill people.
Nor are we psycho killers
who do this stuff for fun.
[NANATSUKI whimpers]
[ICHINOSE]
Shoot only to protect.
That's what we're called to do.
[NANATSUKI]
Yes, sir!
So, then. How do I take down the
terrorists on the first floor?
A‐ha, as for that...
[NANATSUKI]
I've got a bad feeling...
Hey, Belle! Ya got one on ya?
Seeing as how you're
a ninja and all that?
A ninja's always prepared!
Oh, wait. Got one of what?
Did you mean this?
You're seriously
gonna use this thing?
Yeah. Rookie
will give it his all
and use it to take out
the first‐floor terrorists.
That's the whole plan.
[NANATSUKI]
Ichinose, to be blunt,
are you really this stupid?
You are, aren't you?
How have you even
survived this long?
Will you be okay?
I mean, I'm sure they'll
be thrown off at first,
but then they'll
target you like crazy.
I think you'll be all right.
The element of surprise
will help you manage.
I'll handle your final affairs.
[NANATSUKI]
Not comforting!
You wanna back out, then?
Though for what it's worth,
I really do think
you can pull it off.
Yes, understood.
Okay? I get it and
I'm gonna do it!
[ICHINOSE]
Good. It's 3:55 now.
We'll get this thing going
at 4 o' clock sharp.
Go!
[AKANE]
On my way.
[ENDO]
I'm off!
[TERRORIST 6A grunts]
Cowabunga!
[TERRORIST 6B gasps]
‐‐[BELLEMER] Hah!
‐‐[TERRORIST 6C groans]
[AKANE grunts]
[ICHINOSE grunting]
[TERRORISTS grunting, groaning]
You can hit things when
you fire at random?
That's weird.
Would you leave me alone?
But it really is
the dumbest thing.
[deep breath, exhales]
Begging your pardon, everyone!
[yells
[TERRORISTS grunting]
[groaning]
[FEMALE TERRORIST yelps]
[NANATSUKI gasps]
It can't be! No way!
It's impossible!
[WARLOCK]
You have been chosen.
[TERRORIST 6I whimpers]
[TERRORIST 6I panting]
[WARLOCK] You really
shouldn't be wasting your life
in a place like this.
[TERRORIST 6I gasps]
You are...
...a descendant of dragons!
[TERRORIST 6I]
I... You can't do this!
I was chosen! We were chosen!
[ICHINOSE gasps]
He chose all of us!
[TERRORIST 6I yelps]
[ENDO]
Damn!
Come on! What're you
waiting for?! Fire, now!
Yeah, I'm about to! Calm down.
[TERRORIST 6J growling]
[yells]
Seriously, though,
why are you so terrible at this?
I ask myself that a lot.
[FEMALE TERRORIST 6C gasps]
[AKANE grunts]
Evening's such an
in‐between time for me.
I'm not at my best yet.
[AKANE chuckles]
[TERRORIST 6K growls]
[AKANE grunts]
[gasps]
[AKANE yells]
[TERRORIST 6K groans]
[BELLEMER]
Smartphone Shuriken!
[yelps]
[AKANE, BELLEMER]
Yay!
[TERRORISTS groaning]
Ugh. I've been upside
down too long, my head hurts!
[NANATSUKI gasps]
[TERRORIST 6M yells]
[grunts]
Tell me! Tell me!
Why are you getting in our way?!
[TERRORIST 6M] Argh! Don't stand
between us and eternal life!
Give it a rest,
you! Gettin' old!
[TERRORIST 6M grunts]
Ichinose!
That was the last one!
You did real good.
Thanks, but it
felt pretty awful.
[AKANE] Ichinose! Is
everybody down here okay?
‐‐Oh.
‐‐[ICHINOSE] Huh?
[NANATSUKI]
Hey, is anyone injured?
Nope! We're all okay!
[chuckles]
[ICHINOSE] Shikisai,
Belle. You two go ahead
and lead the hostages to
the exit at the other end.
The officers on the
outside should be able
to take it from there.
[AKANE, BELLEMER]
You got it!
All right. Now.
Guess we'd better get to work
taking down that barricade.
[ICHINOSE gasps]
You've gotta be kidding me.
[TERRORIST 6N screams]
[gasps]
[ICHINOSE]
What the‐‐?
[TERRORISTS groaning, rasping]
[moaning, groaning]
[TERRORIST 6N yells]
I was, wasn't I...?
I was chosen...
Why is this happening... to me?
Why? Why? Why this?
"Why," you ask?
Because you were chosen
as sacrifices, obviously.
[barks]
[WARLOCK]
Oh, did I not explain that part?
Sorry, my bad.
[WARLOCK]
All those hostages survived.
The only people who died are
the ones in the basement
and the sacrifices,
whom I chose.
Will they be enough?
[WARLOCK] At best, we might get
some nameless miniature dragon.
What are they called for short?
Oh, yes, a "mini‐gon."
[ICHINOSE grunts]
What is that thing?
Maybe we're dreaming. You think?
Unfortunately, being a cop
means you've got to
give up believing in your
dreams and face reality fast.
No good! Not a dent!
[ICHINOSE]
Just keep firing, okay?!
Oh, crap.
[KIRYUIN]
Breath! Everyone take cover!
[ICHINOSE]
Breath?
Whatever it is,
we gotta get back!
[BOTH panting]
[ICHINOSE groans]
What in the hell was that?
[KIRYUIN]
Don't worry.
After using its breath, it'll
need some time to recharge.
And how do you know that?
[KIRYUIN]
Because I'm the boss.
[groans]
You win.
But, if you know about it, does
it have any weaknesses?
[KIRYUIN grunts]
[KIRYUIN]
Its weakness is shiny things.
Okay, will hitting it
with them damage it?
[KIRYUIN]
No, it just likes 'em.
That's not a weak point, okay?
I don't care about
its personal taste.
[KIRYUIN]
I guess you're right.
[ICHINOSE] Well, it might
make for a good decoy.
[KIRYUIN] If you look carefully,
there should be one spot on
its throat that's
a different color.
If you target that,
you might be able to defeat it.
[ICHINOSE]
"Might," huh?
Heh. Sounds like we're about
to gamble with our lives.
Up for it?
Sir!
[ICHINOSE] All right!
Boss, I'm gonna trust you!
Here we go!
[NANATSUKI grunts]
Yo, Gramps!
Got it.
[roars]
[ICHINOSE grunts]
Behind you!
[gasps]
[BOY 6A whimpers]
[ICHINOSE]
I've got you!
[ICHINOSE gasps]
It's working!
‐‐[gun clicks]
‐‐[gasps]
[ENDO] Watch out!
It's that thing from before!
Nanatsuki, catch!
[gasping]
[KIRYUIN]
By blood,
I beg thee to
fulfill thy contract.
Thy name is...
[ICHINOSE]
Rookie!
[KIRYUIN]
Seiji‐‐Nanatsuki!
[ICHINOSE gasps]
[NANATSUKI grunting]
I'm alive!
Do it!
[NANATSUKI grunts]
[yells]
[roars]
[NANATSUKI grunts]
Still not enough?
[ICHINOSE grunts]
I don't care. Hit it or don't!
[roars]
[sighs]
[sighing]
[KIRYUIN] Whew! That was
something, wasn't it?
Guess we should be
thankful it was so weak.
That was a weak one?
[KIRYUIN] Believe me,
if a real one turns up,
the whole country is done for.
[sighs]
[ICHINOSE]
I guess that's it.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
We'd have been in
a real jam without you.
I didn't do much.
Listen, what did you do?
Would you believe me if I said
I'm not even sure
about it, myself?
[ICHINOSE] Hmph.
Well, the case was cleared up,
so that's what really matters...
Detective Nanatsuki.
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[ENDO] Hey, what's up?
You look like a
peashooter or somethin'.
Is it possible that
you mean a pigeon?
Well, this ninja
thinks that wouldn't be
very fair to the pigeon.
Why're you all gathering up?
Did I miss the memo?
Come on. Because
we're special 7, stupid.
It's hard for us to shoulder
this kind of attention.
Don't worry about that!
I think your brave
shoulders are broad enough
to bear it for all of us!
[AKANE]
What? Hold on. No way.
You mean it? You're
kidding, right, Bellemer?
[BELLEMER] I'm sure Nanatsuki
agrees, am I right?
[AKANE]
Huh?!
[NANATSUKI] I respectfully
decline to comment!
Come on, Belle!
Don't do this to me!
Please! You have to
tell me you're kidding!
Come on!
[NIJO]
Why was my brother...?
[NIJO] Does that slacker
know the answer?
Guys, check it out.
What's up, mister?
Hey! You got a sec?
[DOG growls]
[YOUTH 6C]
Heh. Cute dog you've got there.
Be quiet.
[YOUTH 6C]
Huh?
[WARLOCK] I've just been
deeply moved by a reunion
that was nine years
in the making.
If I had tear glands,
I might even be moved to cry.
Rejoice! I'll put you
out of your misery now.
[YOUTHS scream]
[WARLOCK]
Oh! You're back.
Were you able
to destroy the seal?
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
Without a hitch.
Only one seal left.
What's our destination?
[WARLOCK]
Always in such a rush.
This is no place
for that kind of talk.
Let's discuss it over a drink.
Come on, follow me.
[barks]
[AKANE] Next time: "The Seventh
Day is for Idleness."