[SUPERIOR 03A]
Ichinose!
Why did you abandon Mizuma?
[NIJO growls]
[NIJO gasps]
[sighs]
[NIJO] One day, I've got
to discover the truth.
[NIJO] The truth of
how my brother died.
‐‐[phone vibrates]
‐‐[NIJO grunts]
Wait, a bomb?
[NIJO] We've received reliable
information that "B"
has planted bombs in a couple of
office buildings in Shinagawa.
[NANATSUKI]
Um, who's "B"?
They're called
"B," as in, "bomb."
An infamous bomber
who Public Safety
‐‐has been after for years.
‐‐Huh...
[NIJO] He or she has
perpetrated four bombings
that we're sure of.
But, according to other tips,
"B" has actually been
behind several more,
totaling at least 11.
In addition, their statements
strongly suggest links to Nine.
Public Safety?
No help. They got
a different tip.
A different location
from another informant.
They claim it's genuine
and that ours is a hoax.
Wow, they really
do hate us, don't they?
Kinda makes you wonder
what we ever did to them, huh?
One more thing.
Understand, this part
isn't verified yet,
but B's bombs aren't normal,
according to rumors.
They employ technology
called "magic."
"Magic" as in magic‐magic?
Yeah, one of
the legacies of the dragons.
Otherworldly power
that can brush
the laws of physics
aside with ease.
Right, like flying,
turning invisible,
levitating rocks, healing
injuries, halting aging.
So, it can be a lot.
Magic. It's a real thing.
Hey!
If you want to know more
about magic, just ask me.
After all. That stuff is
what was used to create me.
[AKANE giggles]
As it is now, only
certain government agencies
are even allowed to use it.
If an ordinary human being
using magic has the power
to bring down an airplane,
imagine what could happen
if it ends up in
the wrong hands.
Although,
bringing down an airplane
isn't that impressive.
I mean, if that's what
you're aiming to do,
all you really
need is a missile.
Anyway, if there's going
to be magic involved,
Nine is probably involved, too,
since they seek
the miracles of the dragons.
The bright side, at least
it means we don't have to worry
about Public Safety
complaining after the fact.
[NANATSUKI]
We should hurry.
All right, we are
officially gonna handle
this case ourselves.
Special 7, let's move out!
[ICHINOSE]
According to our info,
there are four bombs
set in the Shinagawa
office building
district, downtown.
[NANATSUKI]
Do you think it's really true?
Basically, if Nijo says so,
then I'm just gonna
assume it is.
[NANATSUKI]
So, why is everyone in disguise?
If there's a threat,
we need to evacuate people!
[ICHINOSE]
No evidence yet.
All we've got to go on is
a tip from an informant.
What happens if we order an
evacuation, cause a huge panic,
and then it turns out there were
never any bombs to begin with?
[NANATSUKI]
Disciplinary dismissal?
[ICHINOSE] Heh. That'd be
the least of our worries.
There it is!
‐‐[ENDO] Found one.
‐‐[NIJO] Bomb detected.
Same here.
[NANATSUKI]
What's that thing?
[KIRYUIN]
Hi, everyone! How's it going?
[NANATSUKI]
It talks?!
Oh, this is just
boss's chatty drone.
It moves! It speaks!
It even breathes fire!
As for why it's a lizard,
I really can't help you there,
so maybe just don't ask.
[KIRYUIN] This form has a
tradition behind it, that's why.
I don't know anything
about tradition or whatever,
but just try not to get in
our way if you possibly can.
[KIRYUIN]
Don't worry, I won't.
Now, Rookie, how 'bout you
give me a brief rundown
of the situation?
[NANATSUKI] Well, we've
confirmed that four bombs
have been placed in
these three buildings.
One each in the Number
One Common Building
and the Iyasaka Center Building,
and two in Nakagawa City Plaza:
one on a high floor and
one in the basement.
We've already contacted
the Bomb Disposal Squad.
We've mobilized
the local police,
and evacuation is proceeding
according to schedule.
We have everyone else
except for Belle keeping
an eye on the bombs.
I see.
So, as of now, it seems accurate
to say that we have nothing left
to do but leave it to
the Bomb Disposal Squad.
[ICHINOSE] Isn't Public Safety
doing anything, Boss?
Yeah, they don't like us
very much, remember?
They won't tell me anything.
Just how it is.
Wait, are you saying
they might overlook bombs
just because we aren't
their favorite people?
[phone rings]
[NIJO]
Got some bad news.
Tell me.
[NIJO] Public Safety received
a proclamation from
a terrorist group
that claims to have
planted bombs
in Nishi‐Shinjuku.
So, most of the Bomb Squad
has been sent there instead.
What? Not cool!
I mean, we've obviously
got bombs here, too!
[KIRYUIN] Yeah, that's true,
but sending a proclamation
to Public Safety basically
amounts to a written challenge.
I don't think they're
gonna leave us with nothing.
How many teams did they
say they were sending us?
[NIJO] One Bomb Disposal team
has been dispatched here.
They're supposed to
arrive in five minutes.
Requesting emergency backup...
There's no way we'll
make it to Shinagawa...
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
It's done.
[WARLOCK]
Great job!
Well? What do you think?
Did it work?
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
No issues at all.
How do you want me
to handle Special Seven?
[WARLOCK]
Well... Want to kill them?
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
If that's what you wish.
[WARLOCK]
Doesn't really matter.
Now is the time
for careful preparation.
Oh!
But do make sure to set those
bombs off at the proper time!
Understood, sir.
[WARLOCK] Okay! Well, it's
time for Johnny's walk now.
The rest is up to you.
[receiver beeps]
[NANATSUKI] The Bomb
Disposal Squad is delayed?
How delayed?
[NIJO] According to
Public Safety's theory,
these bombs are just decoys.
But we know
that our intel is legit.
[NIJO] They say the worst‐case
scenario with bombs
of this class is that
they'll cause a small fire.
Is that true?
[NIJO]
Bellemer, please confirm.
[BELLEMER]
Hm...
It looks like S Squad might
have actually gotten that right.
From everything I'm reading,
the most those bombs
could do is blow up a car.
[ICHINOSE]
Doesn't make sense.
Something's bugging me.
[NANATSUKI] Think we should
head to the scene, too?
[ICHINOSE]
Yeah, it kinda looks that way.
[NIJO]
Here it is.
[ICHINOSE]
What's wrong?
Not sure. Doesn't
something feel weird to you?
[ICHINOSE, NIJO grunt]
[NIJO]
This is... a magic spell!
[ICHINOSE]
Be careful.
I don't know what it does,
but it looks like it's active.
Bellemer, analyze!
[AKANE]
It happened here, too!
‐‐Spell's activated!
‐‐[ENDO] Same here.
[BELLEMER]
Data analysis complete!
The spells amplify power.
Looks like they're meant to
increase the bombs' strength!
[ICHINOSE] By how much?
Do you have any idea?
[BELLEMER]
Let's see...
Well, by enough to collapse
all three office buildings,
‐‐that's for sure!
‐‐[gasping]
[gasps]
Wait, what's happening now?
The timer says... 30 minutes?
[AKANE]
This is Shikisai.
The countdown on my
bomb has just dropped
from six hours to 30 minutes.
[ICHINOSE] The Bomb Disposal
Squad won't make it in time.
Old Man Endo, head back
to where Belle is.
[ENDO]
What for?
You'll need to guard us.
Keep watch for any kind of
interference from the outside.
[ENDO]
Roger.
You've gotta take Gramps' place.
Go on.
Right.
Well, Rookie,
we're short‐staffed.
You handle things here and
I'll go disarm the last one,
that sound okay?
You want me
to disarm this on my own?!
[ICHINOSE]
Hmph. No, of course not.
You just stay here and
keep an eye on the bomb.
Got it?
[BELLEMER]
Let me see...
Okay, guys, who here has
experience dismantling bombs?
I've done it
in a VR simulation,
but I'm not sure if
that actually counts.
I was present when
one was being done.
I'm kind of a veteran.
[BELLEMER] You know,
you're really supposed to be
wearing protective
suits for this,
but to be honest,
they're totally useless.
Go!
I just sent you bomb dismantling
tools by drone, okay?
What you wanna do first
is use the liquid nitrogen
and start freezing
the detonators.
Which one is the detonator?
[BELLEMER] The things sticking
out the side are fuses.
See that thing that
looks like a metal tube
right there next to it?
Spray the nitrogen around
that, but not too fast!
There we go.
Now, at least I'm pretty
sure they won't go "boom"
the moment you touch them.
[sighs]
Gotta check out the wiring.
Use the screwdrivers
to open the lids.
'Kay, I'm moving
the camera closer.
[BELLEMER gasps]
What's wrong?
Belle, c'mon, what is it?
Generally speaking,
bombers are very particular
about how they
make their bombs.
They tend to stick
to the same materials
and detonation methods.
Yeah, once they find
something that works,
they don't deviate much.
Especially since making bombs
is such insanely delicate work.
Hold on, shouldn't that
be to our advantage?
If they're all made
the same way,
they should also be
the same to disarm.
That's right. Shouldn't it
really make our job easier?
[BELLEMER]
Yes, it's true, those four bombs
can all be disarmed identically.
The catch is, it has to
be done in a specific order.
[ICHINOSE]
What do you mean?
[BELLEMER] They're set
so that if you disarm them
in the wrong order, they'll
all immediately explode
in a chain reaction.
So, if I tried
to disarm mine first
and that ended up being wrong,
then we're all basically done?
Yep! We die!
[gaspin]
But you know
the correct order, right?
[BELLEMER]
One sec, I'm working on it!
[laughs] Yeah, you know.
I think you're absolutely right!
I mean, dismantling
bombs without waiting
for the Bomb Disposal Squad?
What in the world
were we thinking?
Crazytown!
[PUBLIC SAFETY CHIEF 03A]
This is no laughing matter!
On your own initiative?
[KIRYUIN] Well, that's 'cause
the bomb squad wouldn't come.
You brought this on by
ignoring our information.
You preferred to chase the prize
right in front of you, correct?
[PUBLIC SAFETY CHIEF 03A]
Ah! That's...
[KIRYUIN]
I'll tell ya, I certainly
don't mind withdrawing.
Though, you realize
that means responsibility
will assuredly fall to you.
[PUBLIC SAFETY CHIEF 03A]
So... But...
I‐If they explode, then...
[KIRYUIN] Don't fret,
I'll assume all responsibility.
You won't mind, right?
[PUBLIC SAFETY CHIEF 03A]
Do as you please!
[recieve clicks, beeps]
[sighs] The human world
is so full of dumb obstacles.
It's exhausting. Honestly.
'Kay, time to think.
Not gonna run?
[ICHINOSE] Oh, believe me,
Rookie, I considered it.
If we do, then
those three buildings
will go up in smoke.
Hmph.
Also, we'd all be
out of a job pretty quickly,
I would think.
[NANATSUKI]
Hard pass on unemployment
and blown‐up buildings!
Hey, Belle.
Have you not found any clues
to the detonation order yet?
[BELLEMER]
It doesn't look like the bombs
can be differentiated
by appearance.
They don't even have I.D.
numbers or anything.
If it's psychological,
then it's probably
a job for Ichinose.
Hah! I think you might be
overestimating me, Shikisai.
Although, I still feel like
something's not quite right.
I have no intention of
placing a wager on long odds.
[ICHINOSE]
What, you wouldn't want to die?
No, I would not.
[ICHINOSE] You'll prob'ly
lose your job, you know.
You okay with that?
[NIJO grunts]
Yes. I don't mind.
[ICHINOSE]
Hmph.
[NANATSUKI whimpers]
[ICHINOSE]
What about you, Rookie?
[gasps]
What? Me?
[ICHINOSE] If we fail to disarm
these bombs, we're gonna die.
Doesn't running away sound
like a better option to you?
[NANATSUKI] Well, I guess
that's true, but...
[ICHINOSE]
"But"?
[NANATSUKI]
Protecting the future
is a police officer's job!
So... I'm not leaving
till it's done!
[AKANE] That was a nice
little speech, Nanatsuki.
Just look at you go! So proud.
[NANATSUKI] Please stop
treating me like I'm a kid!
[ICHINOSE clears throat]
It's time to think about "B."
If you were our bomber, people,
how would you pick the order?
And there are
no wrong answers, here.
[AKANE] Happy to help,
but I don't know how
a crazy bomber thinks.
I'd only be guessing.
Well, to begin with,
all bombers have at least
a little vanity driving them.
That's their thing.
[NIJO]
They're intellectual.
The bombs that
had been planted by "B."
Those were all
painstakingly designed
to achieve maximum effect.
Right. "Achieve
Maximum Effect."
Their bombs must
not have hiccups,
impurities, or
irregularities of any kind.
Which means there
are requirements
attached to the order.
Such as what?
Here are Nine's objectives:
mass destruction, mass murder,
and offering as much blood
to the dragons as they can.
Need a calculation!
Belle, there are bombs
in three buildings.
What order would you set
them off if your goal was
to cause the most damage?
Okay, I've got it!
[NANATSUKI]
That was so fast!
Well, I am a ninja!
It would almost
completely destroy
the whole area?
So it's me, Nijo, Shikisai,
and finally, Rookie, yeah?
Let's just pray
we got this is right.
Belle, I need directions.
[BELLEMER]
That wire right there.
Yes, that's it!
You wanna cut that one.
[sighs]
[AKANE] It looks like
we got the order right.
Well, I'm up next.
Cool. I'll head upstairs.
[BELLEMER]
The elevator isn't working.
Will you be okay
taking the stairs?
[ICHINOSE]
Won't pretend it doesn't suck,
but I've got no choice.
Don't touch anything until I get
there, do you hear me, Rookie?!
Right!
What the‐‐?
Oh, no! The countdown
is speeding up!
Hurry!
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
Pitfalls are often found
right where you least
anticipate them.
Our schedule's a little
tighter than expected.
I know it's
your greatest masterpiece,
but I've taken the liberty
of speeding things up
just a little bit.
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
Now.
Annihilation? Or devastation?
[BELLEMER]
Yeah, okay, cut that wire!
[sighs]
[ICHINOSE panting]
Rookie, get out of here now!
[NANATSUKI] No! I'm helping
you disarm the bomb!
This is all their fault!
Stupid Public Safety and
their stupid decision not
to send the stupid Bomb Squad!
I won't run!
[ICHINOSE growls]
I don't know why,
but I've got the feeling
I can't leave now.
We just‐‐ We need to disarm this
bomb as soon as we possibly can.
You think?
[ICHINOSE] Yeah, I've got
a weird feeling, too.
There's some other factor
we don't know about yet.
I don't know what it is.
But that's gotta be why
the countdown sped up.
[NANATSUKI] Police are
the last line of defense!
The key to
protecting the future!
[ICHINOSE panting]
That's why I won't run away!
Listen, Belle, start talking
the Rookie through it!
‐‐Now!
‐‐Got it! Right away!
[ICHINOSE pantin]
Belle! What's the next step?
[BELLEMER] But, there's
only three minutes left!
Hurry!
[BELLEMER] Yes, okay!
So, there are ten wires!
You need to cut five of
them in a specific order!
First! Yellow!
[NANATSUKI]
I saw this three times.
I remember!
Heh.
[BELLEMER]
Stop‐‐no! You have to slow down!
You can't rush ahead!
Some of them are the same color!
I know!
Yellow, blue, red, green, black,
isn't that the right sequence?!
[BELLEMER]
Stop! No, that's wrong!
You've got the wrong order!
Just wait for‐‐
[beeping]
[ALL sigh]
[ENDO] All that promise
you were showing
went right out the window, kid.
[AKANE] You need
to calm down, Nanatsuki.
Seriously!
Forgive me. I guess
I just got too worked up.
Gimme the order again!
[ICHINOSE]
Next is green.
[gasps]
[ICHINOSE panting]
Gonna leave this to you.
I'll stop you if you screw up.
Right!
[NANATSUKI]
The next one is the last.
It's not the kind of thing where
it's an impossible choice,
like, "either red
or blue," is it?
No, of course not.
Real police work is
never quite that dramatic.
Maybe not,
but it's been plenty dramatic
this time, hasn't it?
[beeping stops]
Guys, that was a success!
[MYSTERIOUS MAN] The bombs you
were so proud of were disarmed.
Don't be mad.
It's not your fault.
This was simply the best you
could do with your technology.
But not to worry, I'll be using
Nine's power for the rest.
[MYSTERIOUS MAN] Nine's power
is derived from dragons' magic.
Its uses are nearly limitless.
One is to amplify
the force of explosives
to an impressive degree.
And by making the spell
run out of control,
it can achieve
the same effect as a bomb.
[ICHINOSE]
What the‐‐?
[NANATSUKI]
What's going on?
This is bad.
I don't understand
what's happening,
but it's definitely not okay!
[NANATSUKI grunts]
[gasps]
Rookie, we gotta go!
[LUKA] I hope you
find your own justice,
and that you'll live with pride.
[NANATSUKI] Nine years ago,
something changed my destiny.
Maybe this is why!
For this moment, right here!
[NANATSUKI screams]
Rookie!
[NANATSUKI groans, yells
[ICHINOSE]
Magic.
[ICHINOSE] I've got it!
Surely, at this distance...
[ICHINOSE]
I still can't hit a thing!
Damn it, why?
[gasps]
Hey! Hang in there, kid!
[ICHINOSE]
You hurt?
[NANATSUKI groans]
Talk to me.
Oh, yeah. I think
I'm gonna be all right.
But, did I... Did I mess up
disarming the bomb?
Heh! Well, if you had,
we'd be ash and dust by now,
so, no, that's not what you did.
Dummy.
‐‐We made it!
‐‐Yay!
[AKANE giggles]
[KIRYUIN] My goodness,
that was a close one.
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
I've failed.
It would appear that they
knew enough to be able
to interfere with the spell.
Which surprises me.
However, now we've shown
them what magic can do.
So I was thinking
I'd try that spell next.
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
Yes.
I'm aware it requires
a considerable number
of sacrifices.
I've already identified
several potential facilities.
I'll email them to you later.
Goodbye.
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
It's too late... Special Seven.
The era of human beings
is coming to an end.
[NANATSUKI]
Man, I'm beat.
But, all's well that ends well‐‐
or so they say, right?
Excellent work, Rookie.
Thank you.
I guess that means
I've grown a little bit, huh?
Heh. It's good
you can joke about it.
What do you mean?
I'm being serious.
Oh, you are?
Well, in that case, I'll just
stand here awkwardly
and try to avoid the
question, like I do.
[NANATSUKI]
What does that mean?
[ICHINOSE laughs]
[NANATSUKI]
Don't just laugh!
[laughing continues]
[NANATSUKI]
You're infuriating.
[NIJO] Next time:
"The Four's Families."