[ISSEI] In here?
[ASIA] That's where
the other Bishop is?
[RIAS] Last night,
my brother insisted
for me to release the seal,
and allow the Bishop
to leave this area.
I'm not sure why, but the
Bishop refused the offer.
So this one's
literally a shut-in.
Such a shame really,
considering the child used to
be the largest earner we had.
No way!
You can't be serious!
With special contracts.
The Bishop used a
computer to make them.
Which means the
power this Bishop had
must have been
fairly dangerous
if it needed to
be locked away.
And the seal
has been broken.
All right, let's see
how this goes.
[high-pitched scream]
[ISSEI] What the hell?
[RIAS] Hello.
I'm glad to see
you're looking well.
[GASPER] I don't
understand what's going on!
[RIAS] The seal has been broken.
So you're free to come
home with us now, okay?
[GASPER] No, I don't
want to ever leave here!
The outside is too scary!
[ISSEI] What?
She's just a little girl!
And look!
She looks a lot like Asia.
Does that mean all Bishops
have to be pretty
blondes or something?
[ISSEI] Hey! What's so funny?
[RIAS] The child is a boy.
[ISSEI] Eh?
[ISSEI] Uh, wait.
What did you say?
[RIAS] I realize he
may look like a girl.
But he is most
definitely a little boy.
[AKENO] As you've noticed,
he does like to dress
up like a girl, though.
[RIAS] Everyone say
hello to Gasper Bloody.
The other Bishop
in my household.
He's a first year student, here.
And before I had the honor
of turning him into a devil,
this little guy was actually
half human-half vampire.
[ASIA] What?
He's a real vampire?
[ISSEI] As in a bloodsucker?
You're kidding?
[ISSEI] He's not a girl?
What the hell?
Oh, God, why have
you forsaken me?
[ASIA] Technically, I think
you're the one who forsake.
[ISSEI] You look way too hot
in chick's clothes, dude.
And plus, if you
don't go anywhere,
who are you dressing for?
Um. I-- For me, I guess.
I just think these clothes
are cuter, that's all.
Don't pull that
adorable bullshit on me!
[ISSEI] When I first saw you,
it was like a dream
of two beautiful blond bombshell
Bishops had come true.
He's all those things,
too, you know;
he's just a boy.
Hey, Gasper.
Why don't you come with
us outside, now? Okay?
I don't wanna;
please don't make me!
Come on, dude, let's go;
you heard the lady.
[ISSEI] What?
[GASPER] I'm sorry,
I made you mad, didn't I?
Please don't hit me;
oh please; I didn't mean it!
Was that just me,
or did you guys feel
something weird, too?
I did, and I'm pretty
sure he's behind it.
It looks like the
Forbidden Balor View to me.
[AKENO] Also known as The Evil
Eye that Stops the World.
It's Gasper's Sacred Gear.
[KONEKO] When he
gets too excited,
he can stop whatever
he happens to be looking
at in that moment for
a certain amount of time.
[AKENO] Unfortunately, Gasper
couldn't control his power,
so Sir Zechs decided
that he should be
sealed away here as
a precautionary measure.
[RIAS] On top of that,
his ability seems to grow
stronger unconsciously,
so there's a distinct
possibility it could
become a Balance Breaker.
What? Isn't that good?
[GASPER] I don't
like it when you guys
talk about me like I'm not here.
Why can't you just ignore
that I'm alive like normal!
[ASIA] How'd he get there?
Wow man, you are
not very good at hiding.
Come out!
[GASPER] Leave me alone!
I'm not hiding;
I'd just rather be
a Gasper-in-a-box
than be around you all!
So I take it he's shy.
Um, Rias.
I think it's about
time for us to go.
Yes, you're right.
If you'll excuse us,
Akeno and I must
leave to go to a meeting
about getting ready
for the leaders' summit.
Kiba?
Yes, how can I help?
[RIAS] My brother said he wants
to know more about
your Balance Breaker.
I'd like for you to join us,
as long as you're free, that is.
Yes, I'm free.
Wonderful, thank you.
Now, everyone else, I'd like you
to take over Gasper's
training until we get back.
How are we
supposed to do that?
[GASPER] No!
[XENOVIA] Do you
call this running?
If you don't move
those legs faster,
you'll wind up
Durandal's next victim.
[ISSEI] It just looks like
she's a vampire hunter.
I don't understand
why you have to
be so mean to me.
[XENOVIA] A healthy mind
lives in a healthy body.
Trust me, you won't think
I'm so mean when
you're stronger.
[ISSEI] Well, at least
Xenovia looks like
she's having a good time.
[ASIA] Yeah, that's true.
It seems like she really
enjoys yelling at people.
I can't do this anymore!
What you say doesn't matter
if my legs won't work!
[KONEKO] Gasper.
You'll feel better
immediately if you eat this.
No way!
You trying to kill me?
[KONEKO] This is
no time to be picky.
Come on, you can wash
it down with Holy Water.
[ASIA] Koneko seems to be
having fun training, too.
[ISSEI] Who knew she'd ever
care enough to tease someone?
Oh. Hey guys. Having fun?
Saji. What's up?
Heard Rias finally
released her dangerous Bishop,
so I wanted to check things out.
[SAJI] Another pretty blond?
Pretty but still
a dude, man.
[SAJI] A dude? Oh, why?
Why have I been forsaken so?
Yeah, right?
Believe me.
I know exactly
how you feel, Saji.
[AZAZEL] Well.
Don't tell me the
households of the Devil Kings
have all come out
to play together
because that would
be just too sweet.
Do you know
who he is, Issei?
Ah! Hello
there, Devil Boy.
Oh, sorry. I mean
Red Dragon Emperor.
You're looking well.
Hi, Azazel!
[SAJI] Whoa,
wait a minute, Issei.
That's Azazel?
Yeah, that's him.
I should know; I've met the
douche nozzle plenty of times.
You could come
at me all at once,
but that would
still end in failure.
Even low-ranking devils
such as yourselves
realize that much.
[ISSEI]
What do you want?
I figured I should
stop by to pay a visit.
Is that Holy
Devil Sword guy here?
[ISSEI] No,
Kiba's not here.
Word to the wise; you better
leave him the hell alone!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[AZAZEL] Always the
feisty one, aren't you?
So, no Holy Sword
Devil guy, huh?
Boring! Hey, you,
adorable vampire!
[AZAZEL] Forbidden
Balor View, huh?
You know, this type of
Sacred Gear can wind up
extremely dangerous if the
user's capacity is too low.
And let me guess,
you've got the Black Dragon
Pulse, Absorption Line, right?
[AZAZEL] During practice,
you should get that one
to connect with the
vampire so he can take away
all that extra power
no one can control.
You're welcome in advance.
Take away power?
You mean, I can do that?
[AZAZEL] Don't tell
me you didn't know!
Your Sacred Gear has the power
of the Evil Black Dragon King.
Otherwise known
as Prison Dragon,
it scatters the power
of whatever it comes
into contact with.
Of course, attaching
itself to something else
for a short period of
time is another perk.
This thing is more
badass than I thought.
Although, actually,
there is a faster
and simpler way to go about it.
He can drink the
Red Dragon Emperor's blood.
Hope you don't mean me,
because I don't
do vampire bites.
[AZAZEL] Don't get mad at me.
He's the vampire.
The blood thing is best,
but I'm sure you
guys can figure it out.
Hold on a sec!
I wanna know why you
hid your real identity
when you first contacted me.
[AZAZEL] Oh, right.
That's just
kind of my thing.
[XENOVIA] So he's
the Governor-General
of the fallen angels?
I do not understand him.
Here we go!
'Kay. I'm ready.
All right,
then have at it!
[SAJI] Whoa, did
he just disappear?
[ISSEI] That's not how
this was supposed to work;
his goal was just
to stop the ball,
but he stopped us, too.
[KONEKO] Guess who was
about to run away again.
[GASPER] I'm sorry;
I didn't mean to.
This training would be
fairly difficult for anyone.
And his power isn't
helping much, either.
It's too strong
for his own good.
Poor guy.
Saji, do you think
you could take away
a little more from him?
Absolutely.
Awesome.
Thanks for helping us out, man.
Don't worry about it.
I mean, hey,
I'm the one who's got
to learn how to use
a new power, right?
True.
But I wonder why
Azazel helped us.
And what about that blood thing.
Ugh, the whole idea of
it just freaks me out.
Me too!
I hate blood so much!
[ISSEI] You what?
How does that work?
You're a vampire.
[GASPER] I can't help it!
The smell of blood
makes me wanna puke.
I hate that stuff!
You're like the
worst vampire ever.
Why are you so
mean to me, Koneko?
Wow, that whine
is killing my brain.
[RIAS] Gasper, please come out.
I want you to know
I never wanted you in here.
Hey, I'm sorry about this.
The last thing I wanted
to do was bug you
in the middle of
your big meeting.
No, don't worry.
It means a lot to me
that you're all working
so hard and want
the best for him.
[GASPER] I can't leave.
It's too scary out there!
I feel like we're just
making things worse, though.
Well, to be honest,
knowing Gasper's background,
there's only so much we can do.
How come?
Gasper's father
is a vampire
from a well-known and
distinguished family.
However, his mother
is a mere human.
Vampires are even more concerned
with pedigree than devils.
As a result,
Gasper was discriminated
against by everyone,
including his own family.
And sadly, when it
came to the human world,
he was treated like a monster.
Of course, that's all on
top of his power to stop time.
A power he didn't have
the ability to control.
He wasn't just feared;
he was loathed.
A person can't know
what happens to them
when they've been frozen.
Naturally, nobody wants
to be near someone
with that kind of power.
I get it, now.
Sounds like Gasper and Asia have
a lot in common, don't they?
[RIAS] Yes, they do.
And like her, we know
he would never use
that power to do anything bad.
[GASPER] I wish
I couldn't do it.
I wish everyone wouldn't stop.
Then, they wouldn't
be so scared of me.
I hate it as much
as everyone else.
My friends freeze right
in front of my face,
and there's nothing
I can do about
what I'm making happen.
[RIAS] What kind
of king am I to him?
Don't say that!
Listen Rias, I can
take care of this.
You can count on me!
Thank you, Issei.
This is so huge!
Finally, there's someone around
younger than me who's a guy!
And I gotta keep it that way!
I guess that's true.
All right, I'll let
you take care of it.
I got this in the bag!
[ISSEI] All right,
Gasper. It's on.
I'm not moving from this spot
until you get your
ass out of there.
Oh yes, I understand.
Of course, of course.
I'll be one hundred
percent fine; I promise.
All right, well then
I wish you good luck! Bye.
That was Issei.
He said he won't be
able to come home tonight.
So it's a test
of endurance
until Gasper finally
comes out, huh?
I know this is
the way he wants it,
but I still feel bad
leaving Issei to deal
with Gasper all by himself.
Really? 'Cause
I don't at all.
Well, our options
are limited;
what could we possibly
do to help him?
[XENOVIA] Sorry.
I'm even borrowing
your bathroom.
[KONEKO] I apologize for
having to be included, too.
[ASIA] It's better than just
talking for a long time outside.
[XENOVIA] But why did you want
to discuss this in the bathroom?
[ASIA] I heard someone
talking once about
what they called a
"bare-all relationship."
[XENOVIA] Oh?
I've never heard of that before.
[KONEKO] It's a little off,
but I suppose it's
not technically wrong.
[XENOVIA] I see.
So we can deepen our friendship
while discussing what
to do about Gasper.
We'd kill two birds
with one stone.
[ASIA] That's right!
[XENOVIA] I sweat a
lot chasing after Gasper,
so I'm glad we have
the chance to take a bath.
Xenovia and
Koneko, I have to say
I'm impressed with how
hard you both worked.
[XENOVIA] No, that's nothing
compared to Issei's enthusiasm.
What's really
impressive to me
is that he's still working hard
all by himself
for Gasper's sake.
[KONEKO] I guess
no one can ever say
hat Issei doesn't care
a lot about his friends.
[XENOVIA] I'm beginning
to understand that.
Especially because
the only reason I'm able
to be with you guys
in the first place is due
to Issei wanting to
save his friend Kiba.
[KONEKO] He really
is a good person,
except for that
whole pervert thing.
[ASIA] Speaking of Gasper,
I'm confused
because I thought vampires
could only be active at night,
but Gasper seemed perfectly
fine to me, you know?
[KONEKO] It seems
Gaspie has the blood
of the Daywalker
vampires in him,
so that conveniently
explains that.
[XENOVIA] As I thought.
I had actually figured
as much already myself.
What's a Daywalker vampire?
[XENOVIA] A special
type of vampire,
one who's resistant to the sun.
Yeah.
He doesn't necessarily
like the sun,
but it doesn't seem to
impede his movements, either.
[ASIA] Oh yeah,
I guess that makes sense.
So I've been thinking about
what we could do for Gasper.
[XENOVIA] Me too.
And, the biggest problem right
now is his extreme misanthropy.
Having him run
from place to place
isn't technically training.
[KONEKO] That's true.
That is the first thing.
[ASIA] Um...
[XENOVIA] What is it?
Did you think of
something, Asia?
No.
That's not what I was
just thinking about.
I kinda realized I'm not very
good around people at first,
either, so I think
I understand how he must feel.
[ASIA] I'm okay on
the phone in general,
but when it comes
to face to face,
and I can't tell you why,
I still get completely nervous.
Face to face, huh?
[ISSEI] Hey. Are you scared?
I mean of your Sacred Gear,
and us for that matter.
I've got a dragon in me.
He's supposed to be the
strongest one in the world, too.
It can be frightening.
And every time
I use that power.
I feel like, well,
like a part of me
is turning into something else.
It's scary as hell.
But I refuse to
let fear stop me.
[GASPER] But don't you worry
about the things
you care about most?
You might lose them
all because of your power.
I don't understand how you can
keep going without
any doubts like that.
Well, I'm kinda stupid,
so I might not get
the whole picture.
It's just--
[GASPER] Just what?
I've seen Rias cry.
I never want to again.
[ISSEI] My friends had
been defeated one by one,
and in the end,
I was the only one left.
But I wasn't in great shape.
[ISSEI] I honestly
don't remember much of it,
except for Rias's tears.
I think they've been burned
into my heart forever.
That was the hardest thing
I've ever had to watch.
[GASPER] Oh. I've heard
about that fight.
I'm sorry.
I was locked in
here when it happened.
[ISSEI] I don't blame you, man,
but things'll be different
from now on, right?
[GASPER] Maybe.
If I'm there, though,
I'll only bother
everyone anyway.
[ISSEI] You don't bother me.
Not even a little.
[GASPER] Huh?
[ISSEI] You're like
my little brother,
even though you've
been a devil longer.
But what's most important
is that you're my friend.
You mean it?
You bet I do.
Help me out.
Lend me your power
so we can support Rias,
and I promise,
if anything scares you,
I'll blow that sucker away!
I dunno.
What about
drinking my blood?
You wanna see if that works?
What if he's right?
If it works, you might be
able to control your power more.
No, it's too scary!
I don't like drinking
blood from living things.
It takes everything
I've got just to drink blood
from transfusions
every once in a while.
Besides, I'm already
terrified of this stupid power.
If it somehow got worse,
I don't think I could handle it.
It's too much.
[ISSEI] Wow,
is it really that bad?
Weird, right?
Because I'm totally
jealous of what you can do.
What?
You're really jealous of me?
Being able to stop time
would be amazing as hell!
Oh yeah. Yeah.
Imagine all the girls' skirts
I'd be able to peek under!
So much panty time!
On top of that,
I could freeze Rias
and play big ol' boobie
bonanza whenever I wanted!
And don't forget about Akeno;
I'd have a full-on
nipple-palooza with her!
Imagination blue balls!
Sorry. I'm a perv.
[GASPER] That's true.
But you're a nice perv.
No one's said they were
jealous of me before.
You even have a
good reason for it.
I don't know why,
but it makes me feel better.
Yeah, well, uh--
It's funny.
You're jealous of
something I've believed
for my entire life
that I needed to hate.
[ISSEI] You fool!
You and I are the
bearers of Sacred Gears,
Gasper, and we will
never escape this fate!
It's time for you to
learn to accept your path.
That is, unless
you want to be afraid
for the rest of your life!
Believe it or not.
I have a goal with the
Red Dragon Emperor's power.
There has to be
a way I can use it
to boost Rias's boobs!
Her meat loaves will be
like nothing ever seen before!
Oh, I think
you're amazing, Issei!
You bear this
legendary power,
but instead of being afraid
of that responsibility,
you're ignorantly positive! Wow.
I wish I could be more
blinded to reality like that!
It's like your
depraved carnal desires
somehow give you this
unbelievable courage!
Oh, stop, you.
You're making me blush, man.
Y'know, I'm not sure why,
but finding out you can be brave
makes me feel
kinda courageous, too!
Thanks, that's
cool of you to say.
If you like that, then get this.
In an epic twist of fate,
my right hand
has actually groped
both of Rias's breasts!
What? Both of them, really?
That's amazing.
So did she hit you,
or like, did she
ask you to do it?
You wanna know
something completely insane.
The idea of boosting her
boobs came from Sir Zechs.
[GASPER] I bet his
power could even twist
the possibilities of Longinus,
a man who stabbed God himself!
He really does care
about the greater good;
our Devil King is the best!
I know.
He's a pimp, and I
plan on following him
for the rest of my life.
[KIBA] Look at you two.
Nice work, Issei.
[ISSEI] Hey! Welcome back.
And Gasper,
you seem to be
quite a bit more
comfortable now.
Dude, perfect timing!
While talking to
Gasper, I've come up
with a kick-ass
team-play by the boys
of the House of Gremory
that you are gonna love!
Oh yeah?
Sounds like a good
time to me; I'm in.
[ISSEI] Get this:
I'll transfer my stored power
to Gasper, and then,
Gasper will stop time!
All right, cool!
And after that?
This is the best part.
After the girls get frozen,
I'm gonna grope them like crazy!
Okay, if that's the case,
then you're not technically
going to need me, are you?
[ISSEI] Are you serious?
Of course I will.
While I'm pervving out,
we might get attacked.
You're gonna have to use
your Balance Breaker
to protect me!
eah.
This is the perfect team-play.
Now, listen, Issei.
Normally, you know I would do
practically anything for you.
But you might want to think
about how this would
affect us in the long run.
[ISSEI] You shut up, Kiba!
And don't look at me
like I'm some freak!
It's easy for you!
No one's ever told you
that just making eye contact
with them was creepy!
And you!
You're back inside the box.
How come? What's that about!
Oh. I'm sorry.
If I'm talking to people,
I just feel better in here.
But hey, don't
take it personally.
I didn't close the top, right?
No, but that doesn't
really make it not weird.
Gasper, you know
that it's time
to get over these fears.
You're not sealed away any more.
Yeah. I know.
[XENOVIA] How nice.
You all seem to
be getting along.
[KIBA] Hey.
[ISSEI] What's going on?
Why are you three here?
And why all together?
Well, after leaving, and
after talking about it,
we decided to do what we could
to help take care
of Gasper, as well.
And then,
we brainstormed
several different ideas
that might help him
deal with his life better.
You all want to help me?
Of course, you're our
precious companion, too.
Thank you, Koneko!
[KONEKO] These are for you.
Aaaaaaah!!!
No! It's garlic!
You like that?
[GASPER] Maybe. I feel calmer.
I think I do like it.
[KIBA] Uh, what
just happened here?
[KONEKO] It was Asia's idea,
and it was a good one.
Yeah? You really
came up with that?
Well, not exactly.
I know I'm not especially good
at talking to people
face to face, either.
But on the phone,
I seem to handle things okay.
I just mentioned to
them that as long as
my face wasn't seen,
other people seemed
to be a lot easier to deal with.
[XENOVIA] That's when
I remembered I had these.
Then I thought,
"What if we put
something over his head?"
Why are you still
carrying these around?
[GASPER] How is it?
Does it make me look cool?
[KIBA] It has an
indescribable impact, Gasper.
[XENOVIA] Yeah, he's right.
Indescribable impact
like the fear one has
when walking down an alley.
In the dark and alone.
[GASPER] This is fun.
I like it a lot!
]]You know.
You seem to be pretty
amazing yourself right now.
[GASPER] You think?
Oh, I wonder if wearing this
will help me get a better
reputation as a vampire!
[ISSEI thinking]
Somehow, I doubt that.
[GASPER] Thank you
so much, guys.
You're the best!
[ISSEI] Would've been cool if
Gasper could've come to class.
But I guess he can't
wearing a paper bag.
[ASIA] I think it's just
gonna take him a little time.
Hey, guys.
Hi, ladies;
what's going on?
It's good to see you.
[RIAS] Perfect timing, as usual.
So Issei.
I've been looking for you to see
if you might possibly come
with me somewhere
after school today.
You want me?
[ISSEI] Isn't a
shrine like going
to an away game for a devil?
[AKENO] Hello, Issei.
Thanks for coming.
[ISSEI] Hey, Akeno!
Please forgive me.
I apologize for the
sudden invitation.
[ISSEI] Oh, no problem.
Where's the President?
[AKENO] Right now,
she's finishing up
her last meeting with Sir Zechs.
She'll be here
right after that's over.
[ISSEI] So, does that mean you
didn't have to be there, too?
No, I did not;
I had another job
with a certain someone.
Yeah? Like who?
[ISSEI] I think
I have to stop here.
[AKENO] Don't worry;
we'll be fine
in this place even
if we are devils.
After all, we have a bit
of a special agreement
behind the scenes.
[ISSEI] Go figure there'd be
such a cool shrine
in a place like this.
After its
previous god left,
it remained
unoccupied for a while.
Then, Rias managed to find a way
to get a hold of
this place for me.
[VOICE] So this is
the Red Dragon Emperor?
[ISSEI] Hey! Who's there?
[VOICE] Issei Hyodo.
It's nice to meet you.
[ISSEI] That dude
totally has gold wings.
[MICHAEL] I am Michael.
Otherwise known as
the Chief of the Angels.
[ISSEI] Yo, Issei here!
The leaders of the three-way
deadlock are gathering?
During that time, I found
out about Akeno's past,
and there seem to be a lot of
different ups and downs!
Next time,
"Various three-way deadlocks!"
Bend it like Breasthams!