[VALI] I am Vali,
White Dragon Emperor,
but you can call me
the Vanishing Dragon.
Holy crap.
[thinking] My left hand
is freaking out again.
Sure picked a
crappy time to do it.
How vulnerable you are.
It wouldn't take much to
defeat you with my magic.
Almost too easy.
Boosted--!
Don't you think this joke
has gone on long enough?
It wouldn't be smart for us
to allow you to start a fight
with the Red Dragon Emperor
here, now would it?
[ASIA] What's going on?
Asia, get back.
Is this really the best move?
If all of you fighting still
couldn't bring Kokabiel down,
you'll never beat me.
But don't take
my word for it.
Keep going if you don't
care about causing a scene.
[VALI] Tell me, Issei.
How do you think you compare
to those with the
power in this world?
What do you mean?
I'm talking about
your Balance Breaker.
It looks quite incomplete,
if you ask me,
but still a four digit ranking.
On a scale of strongest
to weakest, that is.
I'd say between
one thousandth
and fifteen hundredth or lower.
That's great.
So what's your point?
[VALI] My point is that
you're a valuable player.
You should be taken care
of and properly nurtured.
Don't you agree, Rias?
What the hell?
I don't need your advice.
[RIAS] Mind telling me
what this is all about?
If you've come here on
behalf of the fallen angels,
I can assure you it's
a huge waste of time.
[VALI] Were you aware
that the Welsh Dragon
and the Vanishing Dragon called
upon the Twin Sky Dragons?
People involved with
the Red and White Dragons
have never had the best of luck.
I'm fascinated.
Makes me wonder
how your life will turn out.
[VALI] Calm down.
I didn't come here
to fight with you.
[VALI] I've much more
important things to do today.
Are you okay?
[ISSEI thinking]
Her hands are sweating.
She must be freaking out.
At least it's
calming down a bit.
Good thing.
I didn't want Akeno to suck the
power out of me during class.
So Vali's the
White Dragon Emperor?
Goddamn.
I gotta admit his
fighting style's impressive.
It's almost like
Riser's except his--
[DDRAIG] His is
the complete form.
[DDRAIG] Yours couldn't
even begin to compare.
[ISSEI] Thanks, Ddraig.
So what's going on
between the White Dragon
and the Red Dragon, exactly?
[DDRAIG] When all
the great powers--
God, the Angels,
the Fallen Angels,
and the Devils--were at war,
the other creatures and
humans were suddenly forced
to choose sides to
ensure their survival.
[DDRAIG] The only ones who
refused were the Dragons.
[ISSEI] Why?
[DDRAIG] The majority
didn't think the war
had anything to do with them.
They ignored it and
lived how they pleased.
However, in the
midst of the war,
two foolish dragons decided
to start a massive fight.
Are you saying
what I think you are?
[DDRAIG] Not caring
about the great war
that had taken over the world,
they fought wildly
on the battlefield.
I don't get it.
Why were they
fighting like that?
[DDRAIG sighs] Hell if I know.
They probably don't remember
the reason themselves.
Okay I'm
already over this story.
[DDRAIG] It gets better.
Unless something was
done about those two,
the war wouldn't
be able to continue.
The three great powers
called a temporary truce
in order to deal
with the rebel dragons.
That makes it sound like
it was more than just a fight.
What happened after
they were stopped?
[DDRAIG] Fury.
Their anger became
wild beyond imagination.
They lashed
out at the leaders
of the angels, devils,
and fallen angels.
They didn't like
anyone--not even God
or the Devil King--interfering
with their battle.
It was payback,
plain and simple.
[ISSEI] I wouldn't
want to mess with them.
Dragons are nuts!
[DDRAIG] Our story
doesn't end there.
The Dragons ended up getting
diced into thousands of pieces,
and their wicked
souls were sealed
within humans as Sacred Gears.
[DDRAIG] From that day on,
those same Dragons
have used humans
as intermediaries
to meet and fight,
over and over again.
Let me take a wild guess.
Those two dragons are
called Ddraig and Albion.
[DDRAIG]
I've been wondering
when we would
finally meet again.
[ALBION] As have I.
We are still fated to fight.
It is inevitable.
I think I know where
you're going with this now.
[DDRAIG] There have been
times where the human host
has died before the two
have had a chance to meet.
[ISSEI] And since I'm alive
and I've met the other Dragon,
I have no choice but
to help you fight him!
Well, even if it is my fate,
I'm a low-rent
devil and a loser.
There's no way I'd be able
to take on someone like him.
Damn.
[thinking]
Screw this fate shit, man.
I'm not going to
let that stop me!
I said I'd be Harem King
someday and damn it, I will!
Issei, you bastard!
[MATSUDA] Everyone knows
what you did, punk.
[MOTOHAMA] Somehow you
got that Xenovia chick
to join the Occult
Research Club!
I'm tired of cool stuff
happening to you all the time!
Remember that
time you hit me?
What was that about?
You asked for it.
Look at all these
super-hot girls
who get all excited
whenever you're around.
Yeah, you're supposed
to have my back, Bro!
Why you gotta
play me like that?
Like what?
Don't even.
Both of you shut up.
I just want to
know about Xenovia.
You haven't hooked up
with her yet, have you?
Of course not,
have at it.
[XENOVIA] At what?
[ISSEI] Oh hey! What's up?
I'm sorry about
the other day.
I didn't mean to spring that on
you when you weren't prepared.
[ISSEI] Oh, right. It's cool.
But let's not
talk about this here.
I brought you something.
Keep these with you
for the next time.
[ISSEI] Are you crazy?
[MATSUDA and MOTOHAMA] Damn it!
Hi guys. Oh,
those are pretty.
Here, you should
probably take one, too.
Oh thanks.
[ASIA] But what are you
supposed to do with it?
Looks like Issei's
throwing a party later.
Where's it at?
This has nothing
to do with me.
Hey, do you have any
idea what these are for?
[KIRYUU] You use it when
you're doing The Naughty
and you don't want
to have random babies.
[ISSEI]
All right, that's enough!
Asia isn't interested!
[KIRYUU] Uh, are you sure?
[ISSEI] Huh?
Nice retort.
I think she'd be
very interested to know
what you're planning
to do with Xenovia.
No, it's okay!
If he doesn't want to tell me,
I don't want to know!
You dick!
Oh no, please
don't hurt him!
No one's hurt.
[ASIA] Please don't hurt Issei.
He's a good guy.
I promise he means well.
Thanks for
being there for me.
I think you're
the only one who is.
Of course I am,
I always will be.
I'm here for you no matter what.
[ISSEI] Wow. Thanks.
Hey, Issei.
[ISSEI] Wha--?
You ready?
Let's go make intercourse.
No, I'm not!
What the hell has
gotten into Xenovia?
Someone ate a
Crazy Sandwich today.
[RIAS] Hello, Issei.
[ISSEI] Oh, hey ladies.
What's up?
How's your arm feeling?
[ISSEI] Awesome!
It went back to normal
after I rested a bit.
I hear you met the
White Dragon Emperor.
Yeah. I guess he just
wanted to come here
and check out the
sights or something?
[SONA] Seriously?
I doubt he has
time for sight-seeing.
He seems to be working
for the Fallen Angels
so I don't think
we have to worry
about him making rash decisions.
Regardless of
his intentions,
I don't want him on
the school grounds.
Me either.
Especially since we'll have
a much bigger problem
to deal with soon.
Good. We agree.
Talk to you later.
[RIAS] All right.
Take care of yourself.
Those two seem
a little depressed.
Did something happen or--?
No, nothing specifically.
They're just a little
stressed out about Open House.
Open House? But why?
I mean, I totally get
why Rias is freaked,
but why Sona?
Looks like you're
feeling better.
I'd say your arm healed up
quite nicely now, didn't it?
Uh, yeah.
I guess it wasn't really
that big of a deal.
Aw, that's unfortunate.
I was hoping there
was still energy left in it.
Sucking those juices out
of you was good for me, too.
[RIAS] Akeno!
You startled me.
[RIAS] Obviously you
two can't be left alone.
[AKENO] I was just
checking on Issei
to see if he needed anything.
[RIAS] Sure you were.
[thinking] Azazel and the
White Dragon Emperor, Vali, huh?
Just great,
it's like all the guys
I don't want hanging around me.
Crap, I'm sorry!
Oh, Issei?
[RIAS] Oh, Issei.
Rias, it's you!
Were you
gonna take a bath?
[ISSEI] Uh, no.
[RIAS] Asia's in here, too?
Oh, hi.
I don't want to have
to wait for both of you.
Why don't we just
take a bath together?
[RIAS] Asia, you
have beautiful skin.
[ASIA] Really, you think so?
I always thought
your skin was whiter
and smoother than practically
anyone I've ever met.
[RIAS] Well, that's
nice of you to say.
[ISSEI thinking] What kind
of world am I living in?
Not that I'm complaining!
Damnit, I want
to look straight on
and save it in my brain,
but if I look straight on
at such a provocative scene,
I'll dirty the bathroom
with my nosebleed,
and that won't be good either!
Whaddaya want?
Nothing it's just
that I've always wanted
to take a bath in
here like this with you.
Are you like
being for real?
[thinking] This is so fucking
intense, my brain can't keep up!
What's wrong, Issei?
Don't you like taking
a hot bath with me?
[ISSEI] Oh no! I do!
It's the best thing ever,
like ever ever.
[RIAS] Good.
Just hearing that
makes me so happy.
I want to take a bath
with you like this every day,
but I don't think
your body can take it,
so how about once
every three days?
Or maybe once every five days?
Once a week just
isn't enough, though;
I want you more than that.
Whoa, too hot!
[thinking] Damnit, we
can't do anything dirty
because Asia's here.
If only I had
more courage,
I could take her on,
here and now.
Wanna piece of me?
I wonder if you would've
come after me already
if Asia wasn't around.
It should be just us two.
[ASIA] No way!
I don't want to be left out!
It's not fair;
I think I should be able
to take a bath with you, too!
Listen, Asia!
Since I have the chance,
let me be clear.
Issei belongs to me.
The child is part of my
household as well as my servant.
He's my Issei!
Do you understand?
[ASIA] What you
say might be true,
but that doesn't mean
he's not my Issei, too!
[RIAS] Asia.
Issei dotes on you every day.
You should be more giving
of him during times like this.
[ASIA] But I don't want to!
Trust me, as it is,
I'm already holding back
a lot on how much
I want him to dote on me.
[RIAS] Come on Asia,
like you could do this?
[ASIA] Yeah,
I can do that all day!
[ISSEI] Wait! You too, Asia?
I have a question.
Do you like me or Rias better?
Now, tell the truth, Issei!
I know I might be smaller in
size, especially in the bust,
but I won't lose
at anything else!
I promise!
Oh dear.
Issei's favorite thing
ever is big bosoms.
In fact, he never
stops telling me
how much he loves my huge chest.
Isn't that right, Issei?
[ASIA] No! That's
not true, is it, Issei?
[RIAS] Issei?
[ASIA] Issei?
[RIAS] Hey, Issei!
[ASIA]
Issei, what's wrong?
Get a hold of yourself!
[MALE TEACHER 8A] On your
desks you'll see a lump of clay.
Your assignment is to
create something original.
It can be whatever you want
as long as it's
meaningful to you.
We all see life and
situations differently.
It's the same with every day
conversations we may have.
We use the same words;
but it's our personal expression
that defines the thought.
[ISSEI] Something
meaningful to me, huh?
[MOTHER] We're so
proud of you, Asia!
Look over here and
smile for the camera!
What the hell are
they doing here?
Man, this is awkward.
Rice balls.
Oh great.
I'm the only one
who hasn't started yet.
[ISSEI thinking] I don't
know what to make.
Something meaningful to me.
Hm. It can be real as
long as I think it's special.
[ISSEI] What could that be?
[RIAS] Hello, Issei.
[ISSEI thinking]
Rias's body!
Those perfect
lumps of sexy time,
that nearly microscopic waist,
'dat ass, 'dem thighs!
I could sculpt it all in vanilla
pudding with my eyes closed!
Pudding.
[MALE TEACHER 8A] Ahem! Issei!
[ISSEI] I'm here!
[KATASE] Holy crap;
it's a gray Rias.
[MURAYAMA] Amazing.
It looks just like her.
[MALE TEACHER 8A]
You've been holding out on us!
I didn't realize we had
a sculptor in the class!
[ISSEI] Oh we don't,
really-- I just, um--
It was an accident!
[KIRYUU] You must
be feeling her up
so much that you have
her body memorized!
I don't believe
anyone was talking to you!
[MATSUDA] I knew he
was creepin' with her!
[MOTOHAMA]
What do they feel like?
You're such a pervert!
I don't know why Rias
would mess around
with a freak like you!
Check it out, man.
That thing is obviously
stressin' ya big time.
Let's trade.
Don't do it, Issea!
I'll give you half
my allowance for a week!
my allowance for a month!
Rias's body isn't property
to be sold, you guys!
Look how
talented our son is!
And to think,
I always thought of him
as a total loser whose
only skill was coming up
with unique and creative ways
to describe women's breasts!
I can't believe how wrong
I was about everything.
Huh?
I mean about Open House.
I never imagined it would
actually be this entertaining.
Yeah, I guess if you're
into people arguing.
I hate it here.
[RIAS] It is very well made.
[AKENO] Oh my!
Well I guess I shouldn't be
surprised considering the fact
that you're groping on
Rias's body every day, right?
[ISSEI] Believe me,
it's not every day!
And because of that,
I've been forced to carve
the image deep into my mind!
In that case, I'd love it
if you'd make one of me, too!
What?
You mean while you're naked?
Without any clothes on?
I want it to be
extremely accurate.
You may have to touch
to learn my curves.
You mean with my hands?
[AKENO echo] You may
have to touch me.
You may have to touch me.
[ISSEI] I may have to touch her!
I didn't know there
was a magic phrase
that would make
me feel so creative!
When do we start?
[RIAS and ASIA] You don't.
[ISSEI] Just kidding. I can't.
[MOTOHAMA] Aw, no way!
A MagiGirl photo shoot?
[MATSUDA] Come on!
As former photography
club members,
we gotta represent
and record this thing!
[ISSEI] MagiGirl?
It can't be!
Or can it?
[MOTOHAMA] You can do it!
Just put your back into it!
[MATSUDA] Ooh girl,
watch yourself!
Show me what
you're workin' with!
[ISSEI] What the what?
[ISSEI] Am I awake?
Is that a Magical
Girl Milky Spiral Seven,
Alternative cosplay?
[ASIA] Issei, how do you
know about that costume?
Because I watched the
whole show in one sitting.
A friend of mine was obsessed
with it and insisted
we do a marathon.
Sounds fun. Which friend?
[SAJI] Knock it off!
We are still on
school property!
You've seen enough of this!
[MOTOHAMA] Dude!
You're blocking my shot!
[MATSUDA] It's just
a frikkin' photo shoot!
[MALE STUDENTS]
Move out of the way!
[SAJI] We don't need this kind
of commotion on the
day of Open House!
Get out of here!
[MALE STUDENT 8A]
That's not right!
[MALE STUDENT 8B]
See you later, Milky!
All right.
Are you related to
someone at this school?
Okay, well,
they should've told you
that this sort of outfit
is unacceptable here.
[LEVIATHAN] Sparkle,
shine, your command is mine!
You have to stop that.
[ISSEI] Well, well.
Hard at work as usual, huh?
[SAJI] I don't have
time for you.
[SONA] Saji!
What's going on here?
Oh hey, Sona.
This girl says--
I finally found you, Sona!
[ISSEI] Who's that?
[SAJI thinking] Sona knows her?
I'm so happy to see you!
What's the matter? You look sad?
Your face is all red.
Aren't you excited to finally
be seeing your big sister again?
I'm gonna require a lot
more happiness from you!
Come on!
You should run into my arms
and tell me how
much you missed me!
And then I'll say,
"oh Sona, I've missed you too!"
And I'll give you a big fat kiss
and then you'd kiss me back
and that would lead
to girl on girl action
and wouldn't that be hot?
She has a sister?
That is the
Lady Serafall Leviathan.
"The Lady" who?
She's currently one
of the four Devil Kings.
I'd always heard things
about Sona's sister.
But I didn't recognize her
since this is the
first time we've met.
Your line's next.
This is the part where
you say how long it's been
and how excited
you are to see me.
It's been quite a long
time, Lady Leviathan.
Oh, yes it has. Rias.
How excited are you to see me?
Very. Thank you for asking.
Did you come here to
visit Sona for Open House?
Yeah!
But I had to find out
about it on my own!
Sona's a meanie
and didn't tell me!
I was so mad when
I found out the truth.
I almost attacked
Heaven out of frustration!
What am I missing?
Is she still talking
about Open House?
Hey look!
Is he the guy who's
supposed to be the Dragon?
He is. Issei!
I want you to meet someone.
Uh, sure.
I'm Issei.
It's nice to meet you!
I'm a pawn in the
service of Rias Gremory!
I can see that!
And I'm the Devil King,
Serafall Leviathan!
But you can call
me Little Levia!
[ISSEI] Uh. Cool.
[SONA] Listen to me.
I am responsible for the
entire student council here.
Even if you are family,
this is inappropriate
school attire.
You're going to have to change!
[LEVIATHAN] Why do you
have to be like that?
Can you hear the tone
of your voice right now?
You're borderline violent!
You know that I've never
asked for anything!
All I want is to
be a Magical Girl!
You know, I feel like
I've heard this
line somewhere before.
With my sparkling staff,
I will do my duty
and obliterate all the
angels and fallen angels!
Do you have
any respect at all?
If you start sparkling,
you could annihilate a
small country in minutes.
I just had a thought.
Why didn't Sona mention
her to us earlier?
Like when Kokabiel attacked,
you think she would've,
like, needed her help.
Is it because they
don't get along?
[AKENO] No, it's the opposite.
[AKENO] The problem is actually
that Lady Serafall loves
her sister a little too much.
Some would say she's obsessed.
Sona could've
asked for help.
But it would've
gotten out of control.
[SAJI] Also, if she found
out her baby sister had been
violated by a fallen angel,
she would've started
a war right then.
Ahh! I can't take it anymore!
[LEVIATHAN] Sona, wait!
Don't leave!
[SONA] Stay away from me!
Looks like Sona's
going to need my help.
I'll talk to you later.
I hear ya.
Check ya later!
Saji's headed for
a rough time, isn't he?
It's not really
my place to say, Asia.
But yes, he is.
All the devil kings
are like this.
He's got his work
cut out for him.
[ISSEI] What do
you mean 'like this?'
[RIAS] High strung
and excitable.
It can be exhausting.
[FATHER] Ahoy there, Issei!
Hey Dad.
[LORD GREMORY] There you are!
I've been looking for you, Rias.
Hello, Father.
What? Rias has a dad?
But he's so young!
[LORD GREMORY]
You must be Issei.
I'm Rias's father.
Thank you for taking
care of my daughter.
[ISSEI] Hi. Nice to meet you.
What's going on?
[FATHER] Your mom and
I ran into him in the hallway.
And here we are,
still talking to
each other in a hallway.
Why don't we go
back to the house
where there's room to sit?
That sounds like
a wonderful idea!
[gasps]
[FATHER] Great!
Then it's settled!
We'll head on over!
Should I stop by the store
and grab us some whiskey?
[LORD GREMORY] Please!
Whiskey?
So dad's gonna get faced
with Rias's dad, huh?
He doesn't realize
who he actually is.
[SIR ZECHS laughs]
That's brilliant.
Why are you laughing?
It looks
like we're having
a family slumber party
with Father tonight.
[sighs]
[LORD GREMORY] This is splendid!
[SIR ZECHS]
Everything looks delicious.
[MOTHER] It's like I told Rei:
if you can't cook big,
then go home!
[FATHER] Let's raise a
glass to our new friend!
Cheers!
[MOTHER] Watch her face
when she notices the camera!
[ASIA] I'm so embarrassed.
Issei, why do you
always look like
you ate a sour lemon
when we film you?
After this, I'd love
to show you Rias's.
You got video, too?
Let's see it!
[ISSEI] It's Rias in class!
[LORD GREMORY] The way I see it,
it's part of a father's duty
to embarrass his
daughter at school.
I feel like I'm in the
lowest level of Hell right now.
[SIR ZECHS] Isn't that sweet?
Our little Ri-Ri is answering
the teacher's question!
Oh and she got it right!
I've had about
enough of this!
I'll be in my room. Stupid jerk!
Rias!
[laughter]
[MOTHER] It's too true!
[MOTHER] Here you go.
[LORD GREMORY] Oh, thank you.
[ISSEI] Um. Rias?
[ISSEI] Do you want to
come hang out in my room?
[ISSEI] So uh--
I know it's awkward
with the videos and stuff;
and your brother's being
kind of a douche-canoe,
but I don't think it's
necessarily a bad thing
that our parents met and
are getting along, ya know?
[RIAS] No, I know it's not.
[RIAS] Can I ask you something?
[ISSEI] Of course.
[RIAS] Be honest.
Are you glad that you met me?
[RIAS] I'm very happy here.
[ISSEI] It's been an honor!
[ISSEI] I mean, yeah!
I'm glad that I met you!
And I'm glad that you're here!
[ISSEI] But--
[RIAS] But what?
[ISSEI] Nothing. Never mind.
[ISSEI] She's gonna
end up with someone else.
I don't think
I can deal with that.
I knew it! It's not fair!
You're always with her!
I made the first move,
and the first strike starts the
war--that's what Akeno says.
[ASIA] Well I say the
second strike starts the war!
What do you
mean by that?
[SIR ZECHS] It's a bad idea.
Fights are never good.
How long have
you been there?
[SIR ZECHS] Long enough.
There's something I've been
meaning to discuss with you.
[RIAS] Go ahead.
All right.
I was thinking that it might be
about time to release
the other Bishop.
What is he
talking about, Rias?
Hard to imagine Asia's
powers could be matched.
[RIAS] The Bishop's
gifts were dangerous.
So they were sealed away
because I wasn't strong
enough to handle them.
Dangerous how?
What does that mean?
You're the one who organized
all this; aren't you?
Guilty as charged.
Rest assured,
after observing the fight
with Phoenix and Kokabiel,
I've reconsidered.
Then why?
There are a lot more
pieces to work with,
and you're stronger now
than you've ever been.
I am more than confident
that the time is right.
Release the
Bishop, Rias.
[RIAS] If you-- I mean, yes,
if the Great Devil
Lucifer orders it done.
[ISSEI] Yo, Issei here!
I'm about to get
another underclassman.
And she's a cute little
girl who's a shut-in!
Wha--? Girl? Huh?
Wa--? Seriously?
Next time,
"I Have a Junior!"
Dude, I don't have nips!