[AZAZEL] My name is Azazel.
And I'm the head
of the Fallen Angels.
[ISSEI] Oh, that's right!
This has to be the same guy!
What do you want?
[AZAZEL] After what
happened with Kokabiel,
I just thought I'd drop by.
[AZAZEL] That and
one other thing.
I also happen to have
a special interest
in that Boosted Gear of yours.
It looks like Albion did
some good work, didn't he?
[ISSEI] What do you mean?
The White Dragon?
Unfortunately, I wasn't
able to be as present
as I'd liked so
I had someone else
take care of it in my stead.
I must say, I was
impressed with how well
he followed
directions this time.
[ISSEI] Oh, I see.
So it's your fault.
You're the reason I wasn't
able to suck Rias's boobs.
You destroyed my dreams!
[AZAZEL ] Did I really?
I'm so sorry.
[ISSEI] You have no idea how
close I was to a boobsickle.
I hope someone
drops a house on you.
[AZAZEL] Okay, I get it.
You'll never be able
to defeat someone like Kokabiel
with the amount
of power you have.
It really doesn't
matter how hard you try.
And another thing.
Because of the recent events,
the leaders of the Fallen
Angels, Angels, and Devils
have decided to hold a summit.
[ISSEI] No way! When?
I'm absolutely livid.
The Governor-General
of the Fallen Angels
has infiltrated my territory
and interfered with my business.
And on top of that,
he's attempting to make advances
towards my prized servant.
He deserves to
die a thousand deaths!
That bad, huh?
So, uh, are there really going
to be a bunch of
leaders meeting here?
There are.
It's absolutely true.
I received confirmation earlier.
We're going to
need to make a plan
and discuss what will
happen in the future.
Any thoughts on the matter?
I still can't
believe this happened.
All relationships
have been changed.
Nothing's the same
between anyone.
Devils, angels,
or fallen angels.
[RIAS] That's why a meeting
of this sort happening
so suddenly could quite frankly
make things more complicated.
I honestly can't help but
wonder what's really going on.
I do have a theory, however.
Has to do with Azazel.
Let me guess.
You think he could be after
my Boosted Gear, don't you?
[RIAS] No matter what,
it's going to be okay.
[RIAS] I will do everything
in my power to protect you.
[XENOVIA] Good morning.
[ASIA] Hi! How are
you doing today?
[RIAS] Good morning, Xenovia.
[ISSEI] Hey what's up?
From the look of things,
I'd say you're getting
used to living out here.
[XENOVIA] Yeah.
The place Rias prepared
for me is quite comfortable.
I'm adjusting well.
[RIAS] This whole area is
supported by the devils,
so it's going to be a
very safe environment.
[ISSEI] Gross!
What is that crap?
[AKENO] It hasn't been
used since last year.
[ISSEI] We have
to clean all of this?
[XENOVIA] How does
it make sense for our club
to have to clean
the swimming pool?
[RIAS] It's actually the
student council's job,
but we've taken it over.
We thought taking
on this responsibility
would be a great way
to thank them for all the help
they gave us with Kokabiel.
On the plus side,
after we finish cleaning it,
the pool will be ours to use
as often as we like for
a least a little while.
No way! We have a pool?
[thinking] Pools mean swimsuits.
If Rias and the
others want to swim,
they will be wearing
teeny tiny swimsuits!
Yes! I love cleaning pools!
I live for it!
Raise your hand
if you can't wait!
Raise two hands
if you're just trying
to be a pervert.
What do you say
we blow their minds
with how clean the
Occult Research Club
can make the school pool!
[GROUP] Yeah!
[ISSEI] G-strings
and Tittie Slings!
[KIBA] Hey Issei.
[KIBA] So, listen.
I want you to know that if
anyone tries to hurt you,
I will destroy them.
Okay, that's random.
[KIBA] I know it seems that way,
but I was waiting to find a time
when we were alone to tell you.
You definitely did
a good job just now.
[thinking] Isn't that
something you should be saying
to some helpless hot
chick who can't fight?
Not to like, another dude?
You saved
my life, remember?
If I can't return the service,
then I can't call myself
a Knight of the
House of Gremory.
[ISSEI thinking] We're in a
locker room and I'm shirtless.
Just sayin'.
[ISSEI] Cool. Well, good talk.
I gotta go!
[KIBA] Wait! Issei!
[ISSEI] What the hell?
I thought Akeno sucked
all that crap out?
[DDRAIG] Remember
that time I told you
to be careful of strong power?
[ISSEI] What?
[DDRAIG] If you keep
coming into contact
with someone of a higher class,
like the Governor-General of the
Fallen Angels for instance,
it'll happen even if
you don't consent to it.
Power cancels out power.
I didn't realize you
meant that kind of power.
I promise to be more
careful from now on.
Hey Asia,
were you able
to finish the
homework for forth hour?
Sure did.
So how do you
think you did on it?
I don't know.
There were a lot of phrases
I couldn't identify.
Well, it was a tough
one so don't feel bad.
I'm better with numbers.
Word problems are
too complicated.
No big deal.
I'll just stay up late tonight
and go over all of it again.
I know God will be
right there beside you
to offer strength
and knowledge.
Thanks.
You're right. Amen.
Amen.
You two better hurry
up and get changed.
[ASIA] Yes, miss. I'm sorry!
[KIBA] Rias! Come quick!
We need help! It's Issei!
[RIAS] Why? What's
the matter with him?
[RIAS] Not much we can
do about it, I'm afraid.
Akeno will have to suck the
energy from your arm again.
[ISSEI] You really don't mind?
[AKENO] I'm making an exception
for such an adorable
underclassman.
[ISSEI] Thank you very much!
[RIAS thinking]
Why is this upsetting me?
[moaning and sucking noises]
You look so hot when
you're being pleasured.
I'm just dying to know
what you'd look
like writhing in pain.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
[AKENO] Nothing.
Don't you want to
get naked with me?
Say what?
What do you say
we just keep this
between you and me?
Asia and Rias don't need
to know our secrets, right?
Doesn't it turn
you on to know
that no matter what we do
in here, no one will see?
I wonder what it
would feel like
to have my body devoured
by a hot younger guy.
I bet we could learn
a lot from each other.
Yeah. Maybe we could.
I dunno.
I know.
You want me to
be in control.
[ISSEI thinking]
What am I doing?
Is this even allowed? Shit.
I'd probably lose my man
card if I ran away.
Maybe it's fine.
I'm a goddamn man, aren't I?
Which one of you
would like to explain?
[ISSEI] Wasn't me!
[chuckles] I wanted
to make sure
the dragon energy
was evenly distributed.
Yet, somehow
I don't believe you.
Issei, tell me the truth.
Uh. What do you
mean by that?
I mean, did you
get the chance to know
your big sister in the
way you always wanted to?
All I know is my face
hurts right now.
Well, it's none
of my business.
[ISSEI] No no no! Rias, wait!
Was that not the
sweetest thing?
She got jealous!
You okay, Issei?
Huh?
I'm so glad
our relationship
is starting to go in
a better direction.
[ISSEI] Whoa! That's so awesome!
All right,
feel free to swim
until your heart's
content! Ready, Issei?
Yeah?
[RIAS] What do you
think of my new swimsuit?
[ISSEI] It's the most
epic suit I've ever seen!
[AKENO] Oh my, this is really
getting to you, isn't it Rias?
It's adorable how bad
you want to impress
Issei with that outfit.
And I suppose
you're only wearing yours
to show off for yourself?
Sure.
Jiminy!
Those are two of the
hottest bods I've ever seen!
[ASIA] Hi, Issei!
I decided to change
into my swimsuit, too!
[ISSEI] Sweet!
Aw, Asia, you look great!
I'm so proud! Damn.
[ASIA] You have no idea
how happy that makes me!
[ISSEI] Koneko, you look
even more like the
mascot than usual!
Gotta say, it's definitely
working for you!
I honestly have no
response to that.
Better to have the perv's
approval than not, I guess.
By the way,
where's Xenovia?
She was having a little
trouble putting on
her swimsuit and told
me to go on without her.
Oh?
Issei.
Would you mind doing me a favor?
Kay.
Okay, ready?
Kick, kick, kick, kick, kick.
[ASIA] You can do it, Koneko!
[ISSEI thinking]
Weird.
I never expected Koneko
to not be able to swim.
Man, if this were Rias or Akeno.
[RIAS] Kick, kick, kick, kick!
[AKENO] Kick, kick, kick, kick!
[ISSEI thinking] I could
so get behind that shit!
[KONEKO] Hey, um, Issei?
[ISSEI]
Uh, yeah?
I'm, uh, sorry that you had
to help me learn how to swim.
Don't worry about it.
Helping a little girl learn
to swim is super fun, too.
[ISSEI thinking] Crap,
she's gonna punch me!
[KONEKO] You are
unexpectedly kind, Issei.
Especially for a pervert.
Yeah.
I can't tell if you're giving me
a compliment or just hating.
I mean, I want to help out
some of the underclassmen, too.
I'm a nice guy.
[ISSEI] All the
problems I end up
causing are honestly accidental.
[ISSEI] Whoa!
[RIAS] To put it simply, a
strong rival has appeared.
[AKENO] There's no
stopping a heart in love.
[RIAS] Even if
we're best friends,
I refuse to ever
lose to you, Akeno.
[AKENO] Let's do this
fair and square, Rias.
[ISSEI] Whoa, the
big sisters are at it!
All right, time
for a closer look!
Boosted Gear!
[DDRAIG] Transfer!
[ISSEI thinknig] If I transfer
power to both my eyes,
my vision will be powered up!
Now this is exactly what
my Boosted Gear
should be used for.
I gotta save this
to the Gentleman
Folder inside my brain.
Hey, out the way, Kiba!
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but weren't you
supposed to help Asia
with her swimming next?
[ISSEI] Here we go; kick,
kick, kick, kick, kick, kick...
[KONEKO] You can do it, Asia.
Hey wai--
I hope I didn't piss
those guys off too much.
[RIAS] Issei?
Would you help me
rub lotion on my back?
Omigod yes
please thank you!
[ISSEI thinking]
This is the best day ever.
[RIAS] That feels great.
[RIAS] Would you like to
rub some on my chest, too?
[echoing] Would you like to
On my chest.
[ISSEI thinking] "Rub lotion
on my chest" are officially
the most beautiful words I've
ever heard in my entire life!
[RIAS] Is that a no?
[ISSEI] No! I want to!
It's cool?
[RIAS] Of course it is!
I know how passionate you are
about touching women's breasts.
[ISSEI] They're only my most
favorite things in the world!
[RIAS] Then make sure you
do a thorough job on mine.
[ISSEI] It's weird but
kinda cool how bossy
she's been about me
touching her lately.
[AKENO] Whatcha doin?
Is she the only
one who gets a back rub?
[ISSEI] You scared
the crap out of me.
Akeno, that was
highly inappropriate!
He hasn't finished with me yet!
[ISSEI] Rias! You're out!
They're out!
I have a good idea.
Why don't you hand Issei
over to me for a while?
[RIAS] Ridiculous!
I will never
give him away
and I'm asking you one
more time to back off!
[AKENO] Tell me
something, Issei.
[ISSEI] Okay?
Were you able to suck
on Rias's breasts?
No, I couldn't.
I never got the chance.
Oh dear,
that's just too bad.
Tell you what,
you can suck mine instead
as long as you want.
[ISSEI thinking] I'm in trouble.
Akeno, I don't know
what's gotten into you,
but you are out of control.
[AKENO] I am not.
But if you're refusing
to back down
then I'm fighting to win.
I'm not giving
Issei to you!
You won't even let me
play with him a little?
I don't know why
you would want to,
considering the fact
that you hate men.
You're one to talk.
You said all men looked the same
and you couldn't
possibly be interested.
What the hell's
going on today?
The way a devil family
shows affection
is just a little too much
for me to handle.
[XENOVIA]
What are you doing here?
[ISSEI] Xenovia?
Where have you been?
We thought we lost you.
It's the first
swimsuit I've ever had,
so it took some
time to figure it out.
Do you think it looks okay?
You've never been
swimming before?
Is it because you
were born in a church?
[XENOVIA] No, I've just
never been interested
in recreational activities.
[ISSEI] Still. It's
just two pieces of fabric.
You're right-- I did
figure it out a while ago.
Truth is I was
doing some thinking.
[ISSEI] This can't be good.
Just hear me out, okay?
I have an important matter
I'd like to discuss.
Okay? But first.
What's with the dramatic tone?
[XENOVIA]
That's just my voice. Listen.
I would like you to
make a baby with me.
You never
gave me an answer.
I want to make a baby with you.
[ISSEI] Why?
[XENOVIA] It used
to be that serving God
was my only dream--
my every reason for living.
But now things have changed
and that dream is dead.
I've already approached Rias
for her thoughts on the matter.
Devils have desires,
grant desires,
give desires, and hope for
desires without obligation.
We get to live
the life that we want.
[XENOVIA] So...
[ISSEI thinking] Shit.
[XENOVIA] I decided the
life I want right now
is the womanly life
I never thought I would have.
To create life inside of me.
[ISSEI] Yeah. Life. Great.
[XENOVIA] As I was watching
you fight Kokabiel,
I noticed your latent powers.
I decided they
are worth looking at.
Also, you have taken
on the aura of a dragon.
I want my child to have that.
They should have unique,
strong, and powerful genes.
But I'm not the only one
who can give that to you!
So it must be fate
that we are here alone together.
It has to be God's will.
Okay, let's hurry.
These things take
a few months to grow.
I apologize that I don't
have any experience with men.
I will need to follow your
lead while we intercourse.
[ISSEI] Wait!
[XENOVIA] Touch me, please.
[ISSEI] Huh?
You can do
anything you want
as long as I end up with
your seed inside of me.
Issei! What is
going on in here?
[ISSEI screams]
[AKENO] Uh oh. Sorry, Xenovia.
That's not going to work.
I already claimed Issei's
virginity so I get to go first.
Issei, you're so mean!
Why didn't you tell me
that's what you wanted?
I would've done it!
Looks like you're
in for a bumpy night.
It's time to make a baby.
Let's go. We don't have all day.
Do you even understand
what you're saying?
You want to make a baby?
That's insane!
You can't just force
your eggs on someone!
[ISSEI screams]
[RIAS] Seriously.
I swear I will never understand
your perversion, Issei.
It's not perverted.
He was just trying
to make a baby with me.
It's a beautiful thing.
I was not!
You were forcing eggs!
[SIR ZECHS]
This looks like a good time.
Is there some sort
of event going on?
[RIAS] What are you doing here?
Whoa! It's The Devil King.
[ASIA thinknig]
This is the Devil King?
Mister Sir Zechs?
Lucifer? Rias's brother?
[SIR ZECHS]
You must be Asia Argento.
[ASIA] Yes, sir.
I've been told that you
are an excellent Bishop,
and that you're taking
very good care of our Rias.
[ASIA] Really? Wow!
Don't look so nervous, my dear.
I'm merely here to conduct
some private business matters.
[ASIA] Right.
What private business?
It's very good to meet you.
I've heard so much.
I'm Xenovia.
Pleasure to meet you,
Miss Xenovia.
I didn't believe
my ears at first
when I heard the Durandal
user had joined my sister.
What a beautiful and intelligent
decision you've made.
[XENOVIA] I do wonder
if I didn't think over
my decision to become
a devil long enough.
I still sometimes
regret what I did.
I mean, what was
it that made me
want to change
in the first place?
Was I just desperate?
Did I even have a choice, or--?
It's nice that there are those
in my sister's family
that make her laugh.
Xenovia.
I'd like to ask you to support
the House of Gremory
as part of Rias' family.
I guess I have no choice
if the Devil King
commands it so.
I promise to do
my very best, sir.
It will be an honor
and a pleasure.
[SIR ZECHS] Thank you.
And you have yet to tell me
what you're doing here exactly.
[SIR ZECHS]
You honestly don't know?
Isn't it almost
time for Open House?
What? No way! You can't!
If you mean that I can't wait
to see my little sister
in action at school,
then you're absolutely right.
Was it you, Grayfia?
Did you tell him? Be honest.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Father will be here, too.
You can't just leave like that.
You have work to do.
You're the Devil King.
You have responsibilities.
[SIR ZECHS] No, actually
this counts as work, too.
[gasps]
[SIR ZECHS] Your school seems
like it would be a lovely place.
We were thinking we might want
to hold the leaders'
summit there.
Of all the places.
Are you serious?
[SIR ZECHS] I'm glad to
hear that my little sister
hasn't inconvenienced you.
[MOTHER] Oh no,
Rias is such a lovely girl.
Clean. Eats her veggies. Lovely.
[FATHER] Oh yes, she's
a wonderful young lady
but I have no idea what's
she's doing with Issei.
All right, come on
and have another drink!
[SIR ZECHS] If you insist.
[FATHER] Hahaha!
You're a good drinker!
It's whatever, Dad.
Hang out with the Devil King.
It's okay.
He doesn't even know
he's talking to Lucifer.
Issei.
What were you thinking?
Why did you say he
could stay at your house?
[ISSEI] I was being polite.
Besides, he said he'd
find a hotel tomorrow.
Ugh... So humiliating.
[ISSEI thinking]
Rias gets humiliated?
[RIAS] What?
You can't be serious!
Are you trying to tell me
I can't sleep with Issei?
[SIR ZECHS]
Sorry, but I'd like to talk
with him as we
fall asleep tonight.
Surely I can borrow
him for just one evening.
[ISSEI thinking]
So her very own brother
doesn't care that
we sleep together?
Rias!
Tell me you'll be okay.
Do you think you can even
fall sleep all by yourself?
Can you ever survive
without me by your side
because I don't think
I'll get a wink of sleep
without you there.
[GRAYFIA] Come now, my lady.
It's time for us to go.
Yes, I'm coming.
Thank you, Grayfia.
Rest well, gentlemen.
Yeah, uh,
good night, ladies.
Good night, Issei.
And sweet dreams.
Yeah, sweet dreams
to you, too, Rias.
[ASIA] Issei.
Unfortunately,
I will also be sleeping
in my own room tonight.
[ISSEI] Oh, right.
Good night, Asia.
And good night
to you, Issei!
[ISSEI thinking] Weird.
What do I feel so guilty for?
[ISSEI] Man.
I'm so sorry.
[SIR ZECHS]
For what?
[ISSEI] For making the Devil
King sleep in a place like this.
[SIR ZECHS chuckles]
Actually, I'd like to thank you.
In our world,
it's unthinkable to be treated
as a normal guest in a home.
I'm enjoying the change.
Thank you.
You've been a wonderful host.
I actually feel
more comfortable here
than I would at a hotel.
[ISSEI thinking]
How is this real life?
[SIR ZECHS] Also,
I don't think I've ever seen
Rias have so much fun,
even in Hades.
It's all thanks to you.
Nah. It's not like
I've done anything.
[SIR ZECHS] Issei?
Yeah?
I'm counting on you to
take care of Rias for me.
[ISSEI]
Of course, sir!
I mean, I have to.
I'm her pawn. It's my job.
Unless she doesn't need me
then I stay out of her way.
I appreciate it.
Also, I never asked, but is
it okay that I call you Issei?
Yeah!
It would be weird to
be called anything else.
All right then, Issei,
it's only fair that I ask you
to call me by my name, too.
You're also welcome
to call me "Big Brother."
[ISSEI] Wow. Yeah.
I don't know about all that.
Honestly, I've gotten so used
to calling you Sir Zechs
that I might forget.
[SIR ZECHS]
Let's go with that, then.
Oh, and by the way,
my sources tell me that you've
met our mysterious Azazel.
[ISSEI] Yeah.
I'm guessing he's
probably trying
to get in on some
Boosted Gear action.
[SIR ZECHS]
You might be right.
He does seem to
be very interested
in the Sacred Gears as of late.
But he's not a
war-lover like Kokabiel.
Besides, in the previous war,
the fallen angels were
the first side to withdraw.
[SIR ZECHS] It has
been said that Azazel
punished Kokabiel
by freezing him solid.
So what does he
want with me?
You don't think he wants me
to be his servant, do you?
What's gonna happen
if he brainwashes me?
What am I supposed to do?
He won't do that.
I promise you have
nothing to worry about.
Wow. Thanks for looking
out for me, man.
Sure.
It's not every day
that a legendary dragon
joins the ranks of the devils,
and there's something
else I wanted to ask you.
It seems that
you have a strong
appreciation for large
breasts on a woman?
Huh?
Oh yes, sir, I love
them more than air!
Well, even though
I'm her brother,
I can acknowledge that Rias
has a very attractive set.
Agreed!
I think Rias, I mean,
my Master's boobs
are the best there is!
Nothing else can compare!
[SIR ZECHS] Might I speak
hypothetically for a moment?
[ISSEI] Yes, sir!
Have you ever wondered
what might happen
if you were to
transfer your power.
What if somehow
the Boosted Gear
found its way to
Rias' breasts?
Just something
to think about.
I'm mostly joking.
Don't read too much into it.
Sleep well.
[ISSEI thinking] Using my
Boosted Gear on Rias's knockers.
Why didn't I didn't
think of that before?
So much valuable
time has been wasted!
[thinking] Would they
get even bigger?
Could those beautiful
mounds become rounder?
Will the firmness or shine
become even brighter?
I can't think about this!
It's too much!
It's not gonna happen!
I can't even deal!
Thinking of those things makes
at least one of my
heads want to explode!
[ISSEI] No more. I'll go insane.
[ISSEI thinking] So much
for not thinking about it.
I hardly slept at all.
Dude, though,
transferring the Gift
to her breasts is a killer idea.
That Devil King knows what's up.
Why didn't I think of
it in the first place?
I'm showing my
brother around today,
so I will likely
be late for school.
I'll see you two again
at the Open House.
Take care, and
good luck in class.
Thank you. Goodbye!
[SIR ZECHS]
Grayfia, what do you say
we be proper tourists today?
[GRAYFIA]
After we complete our tasks.
[RIAS] This is the worst.
[ISSEI] Xenovia's late, I guess?
[ASIA] She said she was
going to stay up studying.
Poor thing.
I bet it was a long night.
I'll see if she's feeling okay.
You go ahead, Issei.
[ISSEI] Okay.
[thinking]
I'm glad Asia and Xenovia
are getting along so well.
Makes my life easier.
[FEMALE STUDENT 7-1]
Good morning!
[STUDENTS] Morning!
[ISSEI thinking] Damn.
It's been so long since
I've come to school by myself.
[thinking] When I first got
here I was an unpopular nobody.
But now I come to school
every day surrounded by hotties.
Talk about climbing
the social ladder.
Shit! What's going on?
[ISSEI] Who's that?
[VALI] You don't remember?
This is the second
time we've met here.
[ISSEI] It is?
[VALI] You're Issei Hyodo,
the Welsh Dragon.
Red Dragon Emperor.
[VALI] I am Vali.
White Dragon Emperor,
but you can call me
the Vanishing Dragon.
[ISSEI] Yo, Issei here!
It's time for our school's
Open House!
Rias's older brother,
and even
the student council president's
older sister are coming.
And there's a huge
commotion while we're there!
Hope it's all right!
Next time, "Open House Begins!"
I'll cherish those
pretty pillows!