[DDRAIG] Boost!
[ISSEI thinking]
It's not enough.
[DDRAIG] Boost!
I'm ready now.
Are you?
[RIAS] Absolutely.
Boosted Gear,
Gift! Transfer!
[DDRAIG] Transfer!
Holy shit!
She's amazing!
I can feel the waves of
power, even from over here.
[KOKABIEL] Now things
are getting interesting.
Yes, what you've
got there is
a devil's power to
the highest degree.
You've been blessed
with strength on par
with that of your big,
bad brother, little girl.
In that case, be gone!
So much better, and
far more interesting.
Almost as good as Sir Zechs!
Rias! No!
Go! Akeno!
Now ring out, Thunder!
[KOKABIEL] Could it
be she who possesses
the power of Barkiel
is trying to fight?
[AKENO] Don't speak his name.
I am nothing like that creature!
What's a Barkiel?
One of the fallen
angel leaders.
He can use
lightning and thunder.
So basically,
Akeno's power.
Well, that's a
strange coincidence.
[KOKABIEL] Oh dear,
say it isn't so.
Why choose to fall
so far as to be a devil?
What an amusing house, Rias.
The Red Dragon Emperor.
A ruined Holy Sword
Project subject.
And Barkiel's daughter!
What?
No, it can't be!
For real, Akeno?
You're the daughter
of a fallen angel?
How terribly amusing.
A propensity for inferior
products must run in the family.
[RIAS] Your insulting comments
about my brother will
not be tolerated!
But for insulting
my servants,
you will pay the
ultimate price, and die!
By all means,
go ahead and try.
Possessor of the Welsh Dragon,
Crimson Haired Ruin Princess,
and the Devil King's
baby sister!
Please tell me you realize
you're confronting
the archenemy of devils.
Might as well take advantage
of this opportunity.
You may never get it again.
[ISSEI]
Hey, fallen angel douche nozzle!
Issei!
If you say one more rude
thing to Rias or Akeno,
I am going to beat
the shit out of you!
Don't test me, either,
you bird man freak!
Really?
You must be an idiot.
[ISSEI] I am what I am, asshole!
Stay right there
if you want some!
Now Boosted Gear, go!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
Don't, Issei! No!
We've got your back.
I think we can buy you
a little more time!
Just focus on
powering up for now!
Right. Totally focusing!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
Oh!
What's more fun than Holy Sword
and Holy Devil Sword
attacks at the same time?
[KONEKO] This.
[ISSEI] Koneko!
Hyodo. Come on.
I'm about to hit my limit here.
Saji, do what you
can to keep focus!
Yes, ma'am!
[SONA thinking]
Other than Tsubaki and me,
everyone else is
running out of power.
[SONA thinking]
Hurry, Rias.
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[ISSEI] Damn.
I hate this jerk.
Are you okay, Asia?
[ASIA] I'm fine.
But what about those two?
[XENOVIA] We're not done yet!
[KOKABIEL]
Still wanting more, huh?
Well, hop to it already!
Sword Birth!
Cute, but is that
all you've got?
[KOKABIEL] Give up, yet?
[KIBA] Never!
[KOKABIEL] You cut me!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
A little bit more.
Almost there.
[KOKABIEL] Why fight so
hard for a group of losers
who don't even know
they've lost their master?
[XENOVIA] What?
Mind clarifying?
[XENOVIA] Kokabiel, tell
me what "lost their master"
is supposed to mean!
[KOKABIEL] Whoops.
That just slipped right out.
[XENOVIA]
Answer my question now!
I guess I am trying
to start a war.
There's no point in
hiding it any longer;
I might as well tell
you the brutal truth.
In the previous
three-way war,
God was actually killed along
with the four great Devil Kings.
No way. God's dead?
He's what?
God has been dead?
How is that possible?
You're lying; I've never
heard anything about that!
[KOKABIEL] Back then,
the devils lost all their kings
and most of their
high-level devils.
The angels and
fallen angels lost
almost everyone except
for their leaders.
Pure angels could
not increase their numbers,
and purebred devils are
just as rare, aren't they?
It's not true.
It can't be.
[KOKABIEL] All sides have
been ruined to the point
where they have to
rely on humans to survive.
Angels, fallen angels, devils.
The leaders of the
three factions had
to seal away this information.
That way the God-fearing
humans would keep on fearing.
[XENOVIA] Lies. They're lies.
It's not true.
[KOKABIEL] Now, try to remember
I couldn't care less
about any of that.
What drives me crazy is the fact
that after God and
those devil kings died--
It was decided
to stop the war!
Why would they do
something like that
in the middle of winning?
How dare they try to keep me
from squashing my enemies
just when it was getting fun!
We would have won!
Even that bastard
Azazel declared
there would never
be another war.
What the fuck?
[ASIA] God doesn't
exist anymore?
hen where is the love
that has been given
to us coming from?
Heh! Michael has been
holding his own so far.
He's the one who's been keeping
the angels and humans
together in God's stead.
The archangel Michael
is acting as God's agent?
That means all our prayers?
[KOKABIEL] As long
as the system works,
prayer and exorcisms will
endure to a certain extent.
I'm sure someone
has been listening.
[ISSEI] Asia!
It's a natural--
a natural reaction.
I'm surprised I can
still think right now.
[KOKABIEL] Well,
I suppose knowing the number
of believers in God
has drastically dropped
probably doesn't
help anything, does it?
But without anyone
to manage the balance
between good and evil,
it's no wonder that
something contradictory
like the Holy Devil Sword
would appear.
Which means the
war must continue!
And I'll keep it going by
taking your heads if I have to!
Are you okay?
Again. I let my
pride get in the way.
It's my fault.
[ISSEI] Don't fuck with me!
Issei!
[ISSEI] I'm not gonna let you
destroy this town or my friends.
And I don't really care what
bullshit reasons you've got!
Besides, I don't
think you understand!
[ISSEI] I'm going
to be Harem King!
And some cliché
wing flappin' fallen angel
is not gettin' in
the way of my glory!
A Harem King?
You mean, that's all the
infamous Red Dragon
Emperor wants?
Then, join me.
You'll be Harem King
in no time.
Beautiful girls falling
at your feet wherever you go.
You just point at the
ones you like and take them.
I won't fall for your sweet,
sweet, awesome words,
even though that totally
sounds like the shit!
Issei?
Yes, ma'am?
Sorry; you know how
I get with the word harem;
this guy ain't
playin' fair at all.
If you really like girls
that much, listen up.
After we get back home,
I will let you do
whatever you want to me.
[echo] I will let you do
[ISSEI] Like, for real?
So, uh, not just basic groping,
but like, I can
suck on dem tittays?
You can.
If that's what it takes,
it's a small price to pay.
No way!
I know that light.
I swear I've
seen it before!
It's a Sacred Gear
releasing power after being
perfectly aligned
with its master's wishes.
Yes. Bring that
shit on, Kokabiel.
You're going down.
And I'm going to suck
on a pair of jumbos!
Man, I can almost feel
them in my mouth already!
Oh yeah!
I feel like I could
kick God's ass right now!
Lucky for him,
he's already dead.
No offense!
Wow.
[DDRAIG] Explosion!
[KOKABIEL] All the
Red Dragon Emperor had to do
to release this
much power was think
about sucking on some breasts?
Unbelievable.
What in the world are you?
[ISSEI] Remember me, Kokabiel!
My name is Issei Hyodo!
I possess a Boosted Gear
powered on sex and passion.
I am also
Rias Gremory's pawn!
This is
embarrassing.
I bet he thinks
that sounds cool.
Being a twisted pervert
will never be cool.
Well, I suppose that's
Issei for ya, right?
I'm sorry, Rias.
I'm starting to like him, too.
He's right;
what's important now
is we haven't lost yet.
You can only lose
when you give up.
Let's take Issei's lead, guys!
You got it, Rias!
For such a low-ranking devil
to reach my face is
damn near impossible.
This is interesting, boy!
I find it very interesting!
[VALI] Haha! Him? Really?
Who's there?
[TSUBAKI] What is that light?
[ISSEI] My body is
starting to shake.
What is that thing?
[KOKABIEL] Why is the
Vanishing Dragon here?
The Vanishing Dragon?
What the hell's going on here?
Come on.
Surely the White Dragon must be
captivated by the Red as well--
What is he doing to him?
I don't know.
I couldn't see.
[VALI] Your wings
remind me of a filthy crow.
Azazel's wings are deeper,
like everlasting darkness.
You bastard!
What are you trying to do?
[VALI] Someone who's
fallen lower than
the ground hardly needs
wings, don't you agree?
[ALBION] Divide!
[KOKABIEL] What've you done?
[VALI] His name is Albion.
One of the powers of my
Sacred Gear is Divine Dividing.
Every ten seconds,
it cuts in half the power
of whatever it's
touching, sustaining me
with that power instead.
Cuts power in half?
[VALI] Better hurry,
or you won't even be
able to defeat a human.
[RIAS] The Red Dragon
Emperor multiplies
its owner's power and
transfers it to something,
while the White
Dragon Emperor halves
the enemy's power, using
that gain for its owner.
[RIAS] So the
legends were right.
[VALI] Are you still "bored"?
Here, let me make this a
little more "fun" for you.
[VALI] I've been told
you're getting out of hand.
Azazel asked me
to bring you back,
even if it took all my power.
[KOKABIEL] Azazel!
The waves from the
magic square are disappearing!
Then Rias must have won.
But if so, what was
that light from earlier?
[VALI] Oh, good.
There are a few things I need
to ask our stray priest as well.
We'll take care of
the rest afterwards.
[DDRAIG] Are you going
to ignore me, White One?
[RIAS] The dragon hand talked?
[ALBION] You are
still alive, Red One?
[DDRAIG] I've been wondering
when we would
finally meet again.
[ALBION] As have I.
We are still fated to fight.
[ALBION] It is inevitable.
[RIAS] I can't imagine a
battle between those two.
[ALBION] Let's meet
again soon, Ddraig.
[DDRAIG] Yes, let's. Albion.
[ISSEI] Hey!
What the hell is going on?
I don't even know who you are!
[ISSEI] More importantly,
you just ruined everything!
I was gonna win!
Now I won't get to
suck on Rias's boobs,
and it's all your fault!
[VALI] Before you
can understand,
you will need more power.
Become stronger, my archrival.
We will fight someday.
[SONA] Rias.
[RIAS] Sona!
[SONA] I wonder why
the White Dragon Emperor
showed up out of
the blue like that.
I wonder if he realized
he saved our town.
Oh, I certainly doubt it.
Now, Tsubaki.
Time to repair the damage
done to our school.
[TSUBAKI] We should be able
to manage before classes start.
[RIAS] We can help.
[SONA] No, taking
care of the school
is the job of the
student council.
Is it over then?
No.
There are people who
took over Valper's research.
My fight is not finished, yet.
[ISSEI] You did it, pretty boy!
Thank you, Issei.
Hey, is that the
Holy Devil Sword?
It's totally bad-ass, man!
Look, I wanted
to say something.
No. Dude, don't say
another word, okay?
It's over now,
isn't that good enough?
For the Holy Swords,
and your friends?
Besides, there's been way
too much drama going on,
so whatever you were gonna
say is too much for my brain.
UUm, Kiba?
We can do club activities
together again, right?
Hey there, Asia.
[ISSEI thinking] I can't
imagine how she must be
feeling after
learning the truth.
But still.
What's important
is everyone is safe.
The town is safe.
That's enough for now.
[RIAS] Kiba.
[KIBA] Rias.
I'm glad you decided
to come back to us.
And for you to be
a Balance Breaker,
as your master, I can't tell you
how proud of you that makes me.
[KIBA] Still though.
I betrayed the club members.
And more importantly,
I betrayed the one person
who saved my life
such a long time ago.
I can't make up
for what I've done.
But you came back.
That's enough for me, Kiba.
That's enough for all of us.
Next time, don't let everyone's
feelings go to waste.
President.
I'll make my vow
to you once more.
I, Kiba Yuto,
promise to protect you
and your companions as a
Knight of the House of Gremory
for the rest of my life.
[RIAS] Thank you.
And welcome home.
[ISSEI] Hey!
Get your face off there,
that's my spot!
[KIBA] Whoa, calm down, man.
[ISSEI] Instead of
being a stupid Pawn,
I wish I could have
protected everyone
as a Knight like you did.
But I guess you're it.
You're the only guy I know
who's good enough
to be her Knight.
So no more flaking out.
Oh... I don't know
if I'm ever gonna get over
missing the chance
for that sweet meat
nipple fun time suck-a-thon.
The prodigal
pervert returns.
[RIAS] Now, then, Kiba.
[KIBA] Yes?
[ISSEI] Oh shit, don't tell me!
It's time to
accept your punishment.
Here's one
thousand spankings.
[KIBA] What?
[ISSEI] This is awesome!
Good luck taking it, pretty boy!
[KIBA] Shut up, Issei!
[XENOVIA]
Hey, Red Dragon Emperor.
[ISSEI] Uh, why are you here?
[RIAS] Oh good, you found us.
[ISSEI] Rias? Why is she here?
She's the newly-made
Knight of the House of Gremory.
Welcome home, Xenovia.
[AKENO] Now it's important
you get along with her, Issei.
[ISSEI]
Wait, she's your new Knight?
This has to be a joke.
[ASIA] You've been
transformed into a devil?
Well, that's a rather
unexpected development,
to say the very least.
After I found out that
God had actually died.
I was desperate, so I
begged her to take me in.
Wait, you begged for this?
Seriously?
[RIAS] It'll be nice
to have the Durandal user
added to our ranks.
With this, you and Kiba
will be the swordfighters
covering our right
and left flanks.
That's so cool. Yay.
And I transferred
to this school
as a second-year
student earlier today.
It looks like we get
to work together!
Don't try to sound cute
while making that face!
My goal was
to mimic Irina,
but I guess I just
didn't quite get it right.
So like, are you for sure
this is what you wanted?
Without God,
I have no meaning.
I honestly don't
know if becoming
my old enemy is
the best thing.
But for the little
sister of the Devil King,
she's been shockingly kind.
Oh, I hope I made
the right choice.
I feel like I have,
but there's so much doubt.
Please help me, O Lord!
[KONEKO] Anyone else
getting' déjà vu?
That girl's a
genuine crazy person.
Oh, speaking of,
what happened to Irina?
[XENOVIA] She returned
to our headquarters.
You have all four of the
destroyed Excalibur's cores.
There should be no problem
re-forging those cores
into holy swords.
At this point, they only
have to get the alchemists
to take care of that for them.
Irina, you should be very proud;
you've accomplished
your mission.
Oh yes, I know.
I just wish you
did it with me.
Yeah, I feel
that way, too.
Tell me why!
Why did you let yourself
be reborn as a devil?
And I can't understand
why the church
would simply accept
it like they did, too!
You know what you are?
You're a traitor.
[XENOVIA thinking] The next time
we meet, we may be enemies.
[XENOVIA] Irina's faith
is deeper than mine.
I didn't tell her
because I didn't know
if she'd be able
to handle the truth.
And, as for me, I'm now
a dangerous person
who found out the truth about
something I shouldn't have,
so the Church has
declared me a heretic.
They kicked you out.
That's why you
became a devil.
Yes, and Asia,
I owe you an apology.
If there is no God,
then there is no hope
of salvation or love,
so I am very sorry.
The things I said to you
were wrong and hurtful.
You may hit me if it
will make you feel better.
[ASIA] Um, no thank you.
[XENOVIA] For a Holy Sword user
who should be respected
to be cast out
for knowing the truth.
It's changed the way
I look at everything.
I can't get their treatment
of me out of my head.
I must have made you
feel the same way.
[ASIA] Xenovia.
Don't feel bad.
In case you couldn't tell,
I'm incredibly satisfied here.
Even though I'm
technically a devil now,
I've never
felt more blessed.
I've met so many people
who mean so much to me.
I've never been this happy
before in my whole life.
I see.
Oh, and I had a favor
I wanted to ask of you.
What do you want?
I would really
appreciate it
if you would show me
around the school sometime.
I'd love to!
Also, if it isn't
too big of a deal,
I think it would be fun to
try out my Holy Sword Durandal
against your Holy
Devil Sword again.
I was thinking
the same thing.
[ISSEI thinking]
I don't really get her,
but that doesn't mean
she's a bad person.
Now, we've
got a new member,
so let's go ahead and get
the Occult Research Club
back open for business!
[EVERYONE] Yes, ma'am!
[RIAS] I wonder which one
Issei would like the most.
Hey, so, what do
you think, Akeno?
[AKENO] I wonder.
Oh well, that's like a
pretty vague answer,
don't you think?
[AKENO] Fine then,
I think Issei
will like this kind
of bathing suit best.
What's going on
with you, lady?
You've been acting kind of
strange ever since that battle.
No, I think your
imagination is running wild.
I should send a selfie!
[AKENO thinknig]
I think I will, too.
[MATSUDA and MOTHAMA]
♪ Now is the time. ♪
♪ Now, more than ever. ♪
Asia, you should
sing along with us!
[cellphone ringing]
[MATSUDA and MOTHAMA singing]
Is everything okay?
Yep; everything
is perfect.
Pull yourself
together, Issei;
your nose is bleeding.
Is there an abnormal
protuberance betwixt your legs?
Hey, my eyes are
up here, ya perv!
Uh, excuse me for a sec.
[ISSEI] Hello? Yes.
Okay, I'll just go now then.
No, not at all, it's fine.
So, I'll see you
in a little bit.
Got a client?
Yeah, it's that
same old rich dude
who always calls me.
[KIBA] Calling
on a day off, too.
That sucks.
[ISSEI] What am I gonna do?
He's like the
only regular I have.
[ISSEI] Man.
What was I thinking;
I should've gotten
something carbonated.
[KIBA] Hey, um Issei.
I wanted to thank you,
but I haven't gotten
the chance to, yet.
So, thanks.
No biggie.
And don't worry;
all of us, including Rias;
we've already forgiven you.
Besides. You don't
need to thank me.
I know!
We totally have
to do a kick ass Pawn
and Knight of the
Occult Research Club duet
right now before
I gotta leave, okay?
Yeah, okay.
[ISSEI] No! I lost again!
[ISSEI'S CLIENT] I had a
lot of time to practice
in order to play against you.
After all, it
has been a while
since you've come by to visit.
[ISSEI] Yeah, I'm sorry.
I've just been
kinda busy recently.
Meanwhile, you've been
busy buying a ton of stuff!
[ISSEI'S CLIENT] Yeah,
well, I got kind of obsessed
with games after you
took me to that arcade.
[ISSEI] Really? That's awesome.
Geez, how many gaming
systems do you have?
All of them?
Like that have ever been made?
[ISSEI'S CLIENT] What can I say?
I can't stop once I've
started collecting something.
I've often been
told I get completely
immersed in
whatever I'm collecting.
Weird.
I feel like I've heard
that somewhere before.
Well, then,
shall we have
another match, devil boy?
Or should I say the
Red Dragon Emperor?
[ISSEI'S CLIENT]
I am Azazel.
Otherwise known as the
head of the fallen angels.
[ISSEI] Yo, Issei here!
The pool's open, ladies!
Let the push-up swimsuits rise!
And don't worry,
Imma take all dem good parts!
Next time, a new series!
"Summer, Bathing Suits,
I'm in Trouble!"
Do your thang, jigglies!