Koneko?
Don't move a
muscle, Gaspie.
[KONEKO] Humans?
[MAGICIAN 11A]
Yes, that's right.
We are indeed human,
but we're somewhat different
in that we utilize magic
by rebuilding the
structure of devil magic.
We're known as magicians.
[MAGICIAN 11D] If it helps
you understand a bit better,
we're on the same level
as what you devils
call mid-ranking devils.
It would be best if you
did what you were told.
[MAGICIAN 11C] Hand the
half-vampire over to us.
[MAGICIAN 11C] We've already
confirmed that he's here.
[GASPER]
What's going on out there?
[MAGICIAN 11A] There's
nowhere for you to run.
Nowhere at all.
[MAGICIAN 11B]
There's magic on the door.
[MAGICIAN 11A] I did think
there was something strange
about this room when
we first infiltrated.
I was right.
[MAGICIAN 11C] I'm assuming they
must be hiding in there, now.
[KONEKO] We should
be able to stall here
for at least a little while.
Don't worry.
I'm sure Rias and the
others will come to save you.
Yeah. I'm sure
they will.
Koneko!
[MAGICIAN 11F]
I've been waiting for you.
[MAGICIAN 11C]
That magic square will render
all physical powers
one possesses useless.
There's no use struggling.
[GASPER]
Please, you have to stop!
What are you even trying to do!
[KONEKO] Gaspie. I'm sorry.
Gaspie.
Our perpetual
three-way stalemate
is getting rather old and hardly
doing this world any favors.
I assume we're
all in agreement on that?
God and the
Devil King are gone.
Both of our war generals
have been annihilated.
[XENOVIA thinking] Irina.
I suppose she must have
heard the truth by now.
We have a complication.
Once again it's not
even our three powers.
But these forces are equally,
if not more, destructive.
They are the Red,
and White Dragon Emperors.
So, I'd like to
hear their thoughts.
What I want is to fight
someone who's as strong as me.
Heh. Yes, but
you can still find
a lot of powerful opponents
without having a war.
I suppose.
[AZAZEL] And you,
Red Dragon Emperor?
Thoughts?
I uh-- um, wow.
Yeah, I'm not good at coming up
with stuff on the spot, so, uh--
I see.
Well, then why don't I make it
a little easier for you, Issei.
Try to focus here.
If we start fighting again,
you'll never be able to have
your way with Rias Gremory.
[ISSEI] Uh?
[gasp]
But, if we make peace, instead,
then prosperity and propagation
become far more important.
You mean, like,
baby making?
That's right.
Imagine those training sessions.
And you could practice
every single day.
Hey, I'm right here!
[sighs]
Peace means a daily
dose of Rias lovin'.
War means no sexy time.
You understand?
Is that simple enough for you?
[ISSEI thinking]
If there's peace between us,
then I could actually get
my dirty-dirty freak-freak
on with Rias?
Can my dreams really come true?
Wait. Am I in the position
to make that happen?
Even if I'm not,
at least with no fighting,
there'd be a chance.
Peace is number one!
Yeah. Peace for me, please!
I'm gonna do it
with Rias so hard!
Hey, Issei, you might want
to notice her brother
is still present.
[snickers]
[sighs]
Both of you
are nightmares.
She likes it.
[ISSEI thinking]
Maybe I should
stop talking out
loud altogether.
So, anyway,
bottom line is, dude.
I'm not gonna use
my power unless
I'm helping Rias and my friends.
That's just the way it is.
Red Dragon Emperor.
Did you still have a
question you wanted to ask me?
I do.
Although I didn't figure
you'd remember that.
[MICHAEL] I made a promise.
All right.
You weren't fair to Asia.
I want to
know why you guys
kicked her out of the church.
She loves God more than anyone.
Issei, stop.
[MICHAEL]
After God was destroyed.
Only the system remained.
The only thing we
had to keep the faith
was our power to administer
divine protection,
mercy, and miracles.
Even with me as the center,
the church is barely
functioning right now.
Consequently,
there was a need
to avoid anything that could
negatively affect our system.
So, you had to.
I mean, Asia could heal devils
and fallen angels
on top of humans.
[MICHAEL] Indeed.
The faith of
believers is the reason
those of us in Heaven exist.
A threat to the system is
a threat to our survival.
Therefore, anything that
could negatively affect it
had to be removed.
Of course, that's why
I suffered Asia's fate, too.
Along with others
who found out the truth.
Exactly. It was unfair.
You were hardly heretics.
We should have
discovered another way.
I ask your forgiveness.
[IRINA thinking]
Then she didn't betray us?
Apology accepted,
Chief Michael.
It's interesting.
I grew up in the church,
so I must admit,
I do have a few regrets.
But to be perfectly honest,
I am more than satisfied
with my life as a devil.
I am sad, though.
For the other believers.
[ASIA] As am I.
And I'm so much
happier as a devil, too.
I've met people I cherish
who also care about me.
Both of you have
forgiving spirits.
And I am grateful for that.
Oh, right.
I've heard of her.
Wasn't one of my underlings
responsible for killing you?
[ISSEI] Yeah, and you
should be apologizing!
You wanna know why that
fallen angel bitch killed her?
Because she wanted to be like
you, you stupid asshole!
[AZAZEL] Naturally,
I take full responsibility.
So to atone, I will satisfy
you in a way that only I can.
How?
Calm down, Issei.
What in the hell?
They're frozen.
[ISSEI] Is it just me,
or did time stop?
[AZAZEL] It appears so.
Fortunately, those of us
with superior powers
weren't affected.
Thank our dragons.
They protected us.
The heavenly bunch over there
were shielded by
their Holy Swords.
What?
I don't understand.
I'm okay thanks to you, Issei.
You did it again.
[loud crashing sound]
[ISSEI] Who are those freaks?
[LEVIATHAN] They're magicians.
[ISSEI] Magicians?
[LEVIATHAN] They're so rude!
I'm a real life MagiGirl, and
they're flat out ignoring me!
But what is this power?
[AZAZEL]
It's the half-vampire boy.
He must have been coerced
into creating Balance Breaker
conditions for them.
You mean Gasper?
He has the power to stop time.
I think it's safe
to say yes, it is him.
Gasper has fallen
into enemy hands.
Oh no.
Terrorist magicians dared
to kidnap a member
of my household?
They will pay
for this disrespect.
Our guards are disappearing.
[MICHAEL] Teleportation magic.
That can only mean someone
is connected to the
Gate within this barrier.
[GRAYFIA] And, unfortunately,
our magical transport troops
are completely
sealed off from us.
[AZAZEL] So we've been cornered.
[MICHAEL] Yes.
Their timing along
with their use
of Lady Gremory's Bishop could
not have been more perfect.
We've been betrayed.
[SIR ZECHS] I recommend
we take action soon.
If they've somehow
found a way
to make Gasper even stronger,
none of us will survive.
No one is strong
enough to beat him?
How could Gasper
have that much power?
Because he is
a Mutation Piece.
What's a
Mutation Piece?
It's something that causes
many strange phenomena.
The Bishop I used
to turn Gasper into a devil
should have required
several of my chess pieces,
however, only one
ended up being used.
It was a Mutation Piece.
[ISSEI] I guess that
means he's pretty awesome?
Awesome in that his potential
is utterly incalculable.
That's the reason
he was sealed away.
If we don't do something
about this half-vampire kid now,
it'll be far too
dangerous to fight back.
Sir Zechs. I have an
unused Rook in storage
where my household
usually holds meetings.
[SIR ZECHS] A Rook?
Castling could work.
What's castling?
It's a special rule in chess
where you can switch
the places of the King
and the Rook in one move.
[SIR ZECHS] But I'd rather
not send you in alone.
Gasper is a member
of my household.
I take responsibility for him.
I'll steal him back.
I'd recommend using
some of Sir Zech's power,
then another person will
be able to escape with you.
[ISSEI] Then I wanna
be that person!
I promise to protect her!
[SIR ZECHS] You can go with her.
Thanks!
[VALI] Wouldn't it
be easier to go ahead
and take out the half-vampire
with the terrorists?
If you'd like.
I can just do it for you.
You're such a dick!
Vali, try to be a little
more considerate, okay?
After all, we're trying
to make peace here.
Sorry; it's hard for me
to do nothing like this.
Hmph. Fair enough.
Then why don't you go
welcome those magicians.
Upset their ranks some.
Seeing the White Dragon
Emperor should help.
Of course.
Here we go!
Balance Break!
[ALBION] Vanishing Dragon.
[ALBION] Balance Breaker!
He pulled that off fast!
If I tried it,
it would cost me my left arm,
and even then, I could
only hold it ten seconds.
[ISSEI] He's strong.
I mean, like stupid strong!
[XENOVIA] True.
But his power also
feels dangerous to me.
Don't worry.
We're gonna get Gasper
back safe-- I swear it!
[AZAZEL] Uh, first things first.
[SIR ZECHS] I'm leaving
Rias in your hands.
Understood?
[ISSEI] Yes, sir!
Gasper? Koneko?
Let's try looking
in a different room.
Right.
[AZAZEL] Take these with you.
You should be able
to use that bracelet
as compensation
instead of your arm.
Are you serious? Thanks.
That means I can become
a Balance Breaker!
Only as a last resort.
It can't regulate how
fast your strength is used.
Which would suck.
I don't wanna go
through that again.
[AZAZEL] Put the other
one on the half-vampire.
It can bring him
back under control.
Now, pay attention
to what I'm about to say.
Luck is the only
reason you've survived.
You're barely a devil,
and that's a compliment
to your strength.
Keep refusing
to accept others' help,
and you will be dead.
[AZAZEL] You, yourself,
are the weakest point
of the Sacred Gear.
[ISSEI thinking] Like I don't
already know that.
[SIR ZECHS]
It won't be long, now.
As soon as Gasper is
rescued by Rias and Issei,
we can begin our counterattack.
[GRAYFIA] We have a visitor.
I know this
magic. But how?
[CATTLEYA]
Well, if it isn't
the unworthy Devil
Kings Mister Zechs
and Little Miss Serafall.
Explain yourself;
what are you doing here?
[SIR ZECHS]
Cattleya Leviathan,
descendant of the
first Leviathan.
I'm here to bring
destruction and chaos.
[explosion]
That's where
everyone's trapped!
[RIAS] My brother.
[CATTLEYA] Adorable;
the Three Great Powers
put up a defensive
barrier together.
Adorable and pathetic!
[SIR ZECHS] What are
you thinking, Cattleya?
[CATTLEYA] What I'm thinking
is the complete opposite
of everyone at this
disgusting meeting.
If God and the Devil King
aren't around anymore,
then there should be a
revolution in this world!
[LEVIATHAN] Cattleya,
stop this right now!
Why are you trying to do?
Serafall, you stole
my Leviathan title
and now question me.
How dare you?
Cattleya.
[CATTLEYA]
Oh, don't worry, darling.
Once I kill you today,
I'll simply take back the name
of the Devil King
Leviathan for myself.
[AZAZEL] Of course.
I suppose it's too much to hope
we're just caught up
in a devil's coup d'état.
I think it's more than that.
Her plan is most likely
to take over the whole world.
Oh, Michael nailed it.
No one wants a world where God
and the Devil King's
death are covered up.
So, since you
have clearly failed,
we will take this decaying realm
and reform it for
ourselves instead.
[AZAZEL laughs]
Azazel, what do
you find so amusing?
[AZAZEL] Decaying? Reform?
How cliché.
Come on, you have to
know the first villains
to die always
say crap like that.
I'll teach you to mock me.
Oh, you will, will you?
Sounds like fun.
[SIR ZECHS] Cattleya, you have
no intention of backing down?
Not at all, Sir Zechs.
Don't get me wrong,
you were a good Devil King,
but you won't have that
or any other title much
longer, unfortunately.
Doubtful. Shall we, then?
[AZAZEL] A descendant of the
former Devil King Leviathan.
A desperate monster
nearing her end.
Not a bad opponent.
I think I'll treat myself
to some Armageddon.
Surprise.
You don't scare me.
[RIAS] Who's that?
Look, with Azazel!
What's she doing here?
Who is she?
Cattleya Leviathan.
You know when the four devil
kings were killed in the war,
they were replaced
by devils that earned
instead of inherited
those titles, right?
[ISSEI] Yeah, that's
how your older brother
and Sona's older sister
became Devil Kings.
[RIAS] Through the
long years of fighting,
the devils were almost
completely decimated.
If the new Devil Kings
hadn't ended the war
when they did, we probably
wouldn't be here right now.
But the direct
descendants
of the former Devil Kings
still retaliated.
They declared themselves to
be the rightful successors,
so they were chased to
the farthest ends of Hell.
For real?
[RIAS] Cattleya was
a part of the resistance.
She is a descendant
of the Leviathan family.
[RIAS] Come with me.
Hold on. What
about everyone else?
We can't worry
about them right now.
There are other things
to take care of first.
I want you to promote
yourself to Queen.
You got it.
What's going on?
[MAGICIAN 11B] A devil?
We disabled
their ability to teleport.
How did they get here?
[RIAS] Don't worry, we're here.
Rias, I'm so sorry.
This whole thing
is all my fault!
[MICHAEL] We are outnumbered.
But a war of attrition
must still be avoided.
[SIR ZECHS] Grayfia is
currently analyzing the gate.
Which means we need to
buy her some extra time.
[KIBA] You can let us
ward off any attacks.
[SIR ZECHS]
Can you work together?
[IRINA] Yes, Xenovia
and I became friends
when we were
Chief Michael's guards,
and all three of us
have teamed up before.
In the meantime,
let's hope Azazel has
the power to defeat her.
There's no need
to worry, Chief Michael.
Remember, he's not
alone out there.
Right. He's got
Rias and Issei.
[IRINA] Xenovia!
[XENOVIA] Irina!
Thank you.
[IRINA] Why?
Why didn't you tell
me the truth, Xenovia?
That you weren't a traitor,
but had just been exiled.
In order to
tell you that,
I would've also had to tell
you that God didn't exist.
I couldn't
do that to you.
And I didn't have the
strength to tell you.
Irina?
Well, come on.
We can't let these
talks be thwarted, right?
Because if peace
gets established,
then devils won't
be my enemy anymore.
And neither will
believers in God.
Then, let's do this!
We can fight for
our friendship's sake.
All right!
[KONEKO]
Please forgive me, Rias.
[RIAS] It's all right.
I'm just glad we
found you. You're okay?
[MAGICIAN 11E] I don't know what
tricks you used to get here,
but don't take one more step.
Please Rias.
Just kill me now
and get it over with.
Don't say stuff like that!
[GASPER] It would be better
for everyone if I was dead!
I'm a useless coward, and not
only that-- look what happened.
My stupid power caused it, so I
don't deserve to live anymore!
[RIAS] Don't be so dramatic.
Remember what I told you
when I made you one of us?
[RIAS] Live for me, little one.
At the same time, find a way of
being that will make you happy.
[RIAS] You are my servant
and a part of my household.
I made a solemn vow.
I will not abandon you.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Are you as excited
about your final
moments as I am?
[AZAZEL] A snake?
[AZAZEL] We should
clear something up
before moving forward.
You've got a lot of aura.
Seems to be more than
a Devil King's descendant
should possess.
Where'd you get this power?
I would love to
answer that question,
but why waste so much breath
when you are just going to die?
[MAGICIAN 11D] How stupid.
You should have taken
the time to brainwash
such a dangerous creature
so that you could
then use him as your own,
personal weapon.
[RIAS] I know
this is most likely
beyond your understanding,
but my servants are
actually cared for.
Disrespectful bitch.
I'll turn that pretty face into
one deserving the name Devil!
Listen to me.
Now would be the right time
to cause major problems.
I promise if you do,
I'll scold you over and over
for being so naughty, Gasper.
Then I will hold
you and never let go.
You will? Okay. I can try!
[ISSEI thinking]
Look at her. Rias Gremory.
She's so awesome!
[ISSEI] Hey, Gasper!
You can do this!
Don't be afraid!
And stop crying!
You've got us,
and that's not all!
Akeno, Asia, Kiba,
Koneko, Xenovia.
We're all your friends!
And we believe in you!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
Go! Ascalon!
[DDRAIG] Blade!
[MAGICIAN 11D] Are you
going to fight back?
What are you doing?
Issei, stop.
[ISSEI] You know what, Gasper?
Nothing will happen
if you don't move.
Damn it, dude,
you are a member of
the House of Gremory!
Show them what kind
of man you are!
Do it, Gasper!
[MAGICIAN 11E] He's gone!
[MAGICIAN 11D]
No, he stopped time.
[MAGICIAN 11F]
I don't understand;
the Sacred Gear was suppressed.
[MAGICIAN 11E] And he
managed to transform, too!
[MAGICIAN 11D] Take this!
Attack him! Attack!
He's drinking my blood!
But not only our blood;
he's absorbing all of
our power along with it!
[ISSEI] Awesome.
This is just a small dose
of Gasper's power.
No way, are you shitting me?
No, I'm not shitting you;
his power was released
when he tasted your blood.
But Issei.
How'd you ever
come up with that idea?
Oh, uh--
because I might've...
...had some help.
[KONEKO] You guys, look out!
[MAGICIAN 11E]
Wait, what happened!
The magic's been stopped!
[GASPER] It's no use.
I can see every move
all of you are making.
Issei, now! You're up!
You got it!
Hell fuckin' yeah!
Dress Break.
Oh, hot damn, this is like
a festival of naked ladies!
Gasper!
Look at what we can accomplish
when we're working together!
[GASPER] Yeah!
We can do anything!
Look at them all.
Naked. Gropin' time!
Down boy.
[ISSEI] Right. I'm down.
[KONEKO] You're the worst.
This should keep
you more in control.
Wow, thank you!
All right.
Let's get out of here.
[ISSEI] You got it, Rias!
[ISSEI] Yo, Issei here!
As the fighting
grows more intense,
I finally battle Vali,
the White Dragon Emperor.
I definitely can't lose for the
sake of the world,
for the sake of the breasts!
Last episode!
"Clash of the Twin Sky Dragons!"
Defend the dairy pillows!