[SONA] We've covered
the entire school
with a protective barrier.
If nothing drastic happens,
it should be able
to keep anything within
it from getting damaged.
Thank you, Sona.
This means so much.
Understand that
this will only work
if conditions remain the same.
[RIAS] Got it.
[ISSEI] Tsubaki. How's Irina?
Her condition is
not life threatening.
She can thank Asia for that.
What a relief.
Where's Xenovia?
I wonder if she'll
even come now.
Have you heard
from Kiba, either?
No, we haven't
seen him at all.
We know he'll be here, though.
Right.
[SONA] I'll keep the barrier up,
but I might not be able to keep
the school from collapsing.
As much as I'd
prefer to avoid it.
I'm not going to
let that happen.
[SONA] Rias, it's not too late.
You can still
contact your brother.
You know what I don't see?
You trying to contact
your big sister.
With good reason, too.
Sir Zechs loves you.
You know he would
want to assist us.
There's no doubt
that he'd come here
as soon as you
called him. So call him.
[AKENO] There's no reason.
I've already
contacted Sir Zechs.
How could you do that
without asking me first?
Look, Rias.
I understand you don't want
to bother your brother
unless we absolutely must.
Our enemy is a
leader-class fallen angel.
He's not someone you
can take on your own.
I think that qualifies
this to be a "must."
Fine.
I thank you for your
consideration, President.
Sir Zech's is on his way.
I believe that his
forces should arrive here
in just about an hour.
Good grief, girl.
I cannot win
against you, can I?
Should be a fun hour.
[RIAS] Issei. I need you
to be on support this time.
[ISSEI] Support?
[RIAS] I want you
to use your ability
to transfer your
power to the rest of us
to increase our strength.
No problem.
I'm all over it!
In the meantime,
I think we can stall
until Issei can transfer his
power to everyone, don't you?
Yeah, I bet we
can manage that.
Absolutely.
[RIAS] Issei?
I'm still here!
Yes, and we're
counting on you.
Sure thing!
[RIAS]
Let's concentrate on being
on the offensive
for this battle.
We have to get into the school
and prevent Kokabiel
from releasing his power,
whatever that may be.
Unlike the fight with Riser.
Our lives will be
at risk this time.
But believe me,
I will not allow us
to die today.
We will survive,
my dear servants.
We'll survive this fight
so we can come back here
and go to school once more!
[GROUP] Yes, ma'am!
[ISSEI] Promotion to Queen!
[ASIA] What in
the world is that?
[KOKABIEL] It seems
like the four Excaliburs
have been made into one.
That is just so
Valper, you know?
[RIAS] Kokabiel!
So, is big brother
on his way, yet?
Or is it Serafall instead?
Right now, we're the
ones here ready to fight.
That's all that matters.
[ISSEI] Be careful!
[ISSEI] The gym!
[KOKABIEL] This is so boring.
I need a diversion.
No freakin' way.
[DDRAIG] What's wrong, kid?
You skeered?
I've never seen
that big of a lance
made of light before, dude.
It's like from
another dimension!
[DDRAIG] Of course it's
from another
dimension; look at it.
We're talking about a man
who survived fighting
with God and the Devil King.
You really think we
can still beat him?
[DDRAIG] When it
comes down to it,
I'll beat him even if I have
to turn most of your
body into a dragon.
Most of my body, huh?
Well, as long as you leave
me the important parts.
Since you came all
this way to see me,
I might as well let you
play with my favorite pet!
[RIAS] Cerberus?
[AKENO] Living at the
gates of the underworld,
it's the Watchdog of Hades.
So he's real?
What are we gonna do?
Bringing him to this
world is forbidden.
Let's send him back!
Akeno! Koneko!
[BOTH] Yes, ma'am!
[RIAS] Issei, use the Sacred
Gear to enhance our power!
Right! Boosted Gear!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[ISSEI] Asia, get back!
[ASIA] Okay.
[ISSEI] We'll be fine.
Trust me; our girls
will have no problem
taking care of that puppy.
[DDRAIG] Boost!
I think he wants more!
[ISSEI] Jeez, how
tough is this bitch?
[DDRAIG] Boost!
Not yet.
I don't have enough
power built up to transfer.
[ISSEI thinking] Damn it,
if only I were stronger,
I could enhance
everyone in a split second!
[ISSEI] What the hell?
There're more than one?
[DDRAIG]
Boost!
If I get attacked or
attack something else,
the multiplier is reset on me.
Run, Asia!
I'll get its attention!
Issei!
Look out, Koneko!
You look out.
I'll take care of this.
[ISSEI] But you
can't take him alone!
[KONEKO] At the least,
I can stall for time.
Or you could die.
[DDRAIG] Boost!
All right, Koneko,
but be careful!
Are you all right?
For the most part.
[ISSEI] Okay, I'll take
it from here!
Asia, help Koneko out for me!
Hey, you piece
of shit dog!
What's wrong; can't tell your
opponent's standing right here?
I think I pissed him off!
Now all I've gotta do
is lure this thing over in time!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
So, you think this
is gonna end up okay?
We have no choice
but to trust them.
I think we'll be fine.
Besides, I believe in Rias
Gremory and her household.
Issei, please be careful!
[ISSEI] I'm doing my
best here; trust me!
You need
a little help, here?
[ISSEI] Xenovia!
And that is
exactly the damage
you can expect a Holy
Sword to have on evil.
I'd rather we didn't
need the help,
but I am glad you're here.
She's amazing!
What is that?
[DDRAIG] It's the signal.
We've reached an appropriate
multiplier for fighting.
Seems kinda convenient
to have that built in.
[DDRAIG]
Let's chalk it up to you
and the sacred
treasure maturing.
What you want can be
a reality and all that.
[ISSEI] Cool! Heads up, ladies!
Good boy!
Oh. Fun!
[ISSEI] Boosted Gear!
Gift!
[DDRAIG] Transfer!
Nice work.
I didn't realize you were
strong enough to do that, Issei.
We're ready now!
Oh, yeah.
Akeno?
Of course. Now,
ring out thunder!
No! Asia!
[ASIA screams]
Kiba made it.
Kiba, you're here!
More!
I would love to!
Awesome!
That was so cool, Kiba!
[KOKABIEL] Awesome
is a bit of a stretch.
[RIAS] Take this!
[ISSEI] That's huge!
Impressive.
Look how much stronger
you've become
now that you've had a little
Red Dragon Emperor inside you.
Sexy. And fascinating,
as well!
[VALPER] It is complete.
[KIBA] Oh no.
[VALPER] Finally, it is done!
[KOKABIEL] Now, I get
to have the massive power
that results from the
combination of the swords.
That's our trade off.
Sweet deal, huh?
[RIAS] So that
power is what you used
to make the ground collapse?
[ISSEI] Seriously?
So then, what?
Does that
mean you guys're
gonna use it to make
our town disappear?
[VALPER] I suggest
you leave quickly.
This whole area is
going to be destroyed
in less than twenty minutes.
[KOKABIEL] If you
want to save it,
you'll have to defeat me. Oh no.
Ready, Rias Gremory?
I'm ready!
[KOKABIEL] Fool!
[AKENO] Rias!
[ISSEI] Akeno!
[AKENO] Issei?
Are you okay?
You feel awesome!
I'm sorry, Issei.
You wasted all that power on me.
[ISSEI] I'm not worried
about it right now.
Hey, asshole, how could
you do that to her?
Now, you're gonna
have to pay big time!
And there he goes; the
passionate hero as always.
It doesn't look like
we'll be able to hold out.
What's taking Sir Zechs so long?
We have to find
a way to win. Kiba?
Kiba!
[KIBA] Valper Galilei.
I'm a survivor of the
Holy Sword Project,
or more accurately, of
those you tried to murder.
[KIBA] I was able to live
because I was reborn as a devil.
I refused to die
because I knew one day
I would avenge the
deaths of my comrades!
Kiba! No!
Kiba!
[KOKABIEL] You were able
to avoid a direct attack?
What a quick little rat.
[KOKABIEL] Freed.
You called? I'm here!
[ISSEI] Not you again!
[KOKABIEL] This is our
last piece of entertainment.
Use the Excalibur with
the power of four swords
to get rid of all this debris.
[FREED] I would love to!
You know that
fancy Excalibur
with those ridiculous specs?
Surprise! I just
got one as a gift!
Now, who wants the pointy
end of this bad boy first?
Well, I'll just go
ahead and chop up
that devil and bitch
believer a little, then.
That sound okay?
[ISSEI] Xenovia!
[FREED] Too slow!
[FREED] Have you met?
Say hello to the
Chopper Rapidly!
So fresh!
Such an amazing Excalibur!
This bad boy can
make anything happen!
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
My face! You scum bitch!
Who kicks a beautiful
creation like this;
I'm going to tear
you apart for that!
I'll turn you into a
slip-n-slide, you hear me?
Prepare for your
final reckoning.
It's not just mimicry,
you know! Yahoo!
It's a nightmare.
[FREED] This is the power
of the Excalibur Nightmare!
Ba-dum, dum-dum dum!
How do you like it, princess?
[XENOVIA] An illusion?
[FREED] Now, Transparency!
[XENOVIA] He can
use all their abilities;
all the swords
that were combined.
[FREED] All righty,
brace yourselves, dears!
Y'mean Xenovia can't even
do anything to this creep?
[XENOVIA] I can't defeat
this guy on my own.
[ISSEI] Don't forget
we're here too, asshole!
[VALPER] I'd heard about you.
They said one of the
subjects had escaped.
[VALPER] How tragic
to survive only
to live as a lowly devil.
I am grateful to
you and the others.
You taught me what
I needed to know
to complete the project.
[KIBA] Complete it?
The subjects we
used didn't individually
have enough of a
particular gene required
to use the Holy Swords.
After I realized that fact,
I came to a conclusion.
So... All I did
was take out the gene
from the kids who
carried any of it.
Then, I found a
way to combine
and crystallize their genes!
This crystal contains the
correct quantity of the gene.
It's the last one made
from those pathetic
little brats.
[FREED] The other guys
they tested the crystals
on died halfway in
because they were too weak
to take all the gene goodness.
If you think
about it that way,
you're lucky to be
fighting one of a kind!
[ISSEI] Bastard!
[XENOVIA] The crystal.
Holy Sword users
receive a blessing.
Something like that is
put into their bodies.
A gene deficiency.
That must be what they've
been using them for.
[VALPER] Those hypocrites!
After excommunicating
me as a pagan,
they shamelessly
use my research?
Typical church behavior.
Of course, we're
talking about Michael.
So even if he took
genes from his subjects,
I bet he didn't take
the time to kill them.
[KIBA] There was no
need to kill us either.
[KIBA] How could you?
You were nothing more
than materials used
in a top-secret project.
We had what we needed.
What were we supposed to do?
[KIBA] We believed what
we were doing was for God.
We bore everything
because of that faith.
And then--You--
You just threw
us away, like trash.
No.
Here, why don't
you take this?
I no longer need it;
we've gotten to the point
where we can mass-produce
higher quality crystals,
no martyrs required.
Run away!
Hurry; save yourself!
Gone.
[ISSEI] Valper Gaililei.
You'll pay for this!
[KIBA] How many.
How many lives did your
blessed research cost?
How many deaths did it take?
[ASIA] What is that?
[KONEKO] Look.
[ISSEI] It kinda
seems like people.
[AKENO] It's probably
the different powers
from the battlefield combining.
And Kiba.
Our powers on
top of the trembling
of his heart must have freed
the souls from the crystal.
I prayed, and wondered.
Why was I the only one? Why me?
It wasn't fair for
me to have survived.
[KIBA] There were kids who
had bigger dreams than I did.
Kids who wanted to
live more than I did.
It was a mistake.
Someone better
than me should have
made it out of that nightmare!
It's okay.
Let's all gather together.
[BOY 3B] Take us in. It's time.
[GIRL 3A] You don't
have to be scared,
even if there is no God.
[GIRL 5B] Though God may
not be watching over us.
[BOY 3C ] Our hearts
will forever be one.
Yes.
[KONEKO] Aw, that's sweet.
I can't stop crying!
Damn it, Kiba.
You're breaking my heart.
[DDRAIG] The Knight has Peaked.
It happens when the thoughts
and wishes of the
user oppose nature.
When they go against
the natural course
of things in this world.
The Sacred Treasure Peaks,
or as it is also known:
The Balance Breaker.
[KOKABIEL] Oh?
My comrades,
they never wanted
me to wish for revenge.
They wanted me free.
But I'm not.
First, I need to destroy
the evil in front of me.
Then no one else
will have to suffer.
No one but you!
Help me! Freed!
Yes? I'm here!
You are such a little fool.
You should have let yourself
be killed with the rest of them.
[ISSEI] Kiba!
Go on and kick that
Freed bastard's ass
along with those Excaliburs!
No point in wasting
your friends feelings now,
or their souls!
[KIBA] Issei.
You can do it, Kiba.
Fight like a member
of the House of Gremory;
take them down.
Besides, no true Knight of mine
would ever lose to
such a pathetic foe.
Come on, Kiba!
We all believe in you.
I wanna see blood.
Kiba!
Thank you.
[FREED] Gross.
Another "moving scene"
from the House
of Gag Me Gremory!
Now my skin is
starting to crawl
and is creeping me out!
I can't take it!
I need to hurry
up and kill you.
Yes. That should make
me feel much better!
Time for a new sword.
Dear comrades whose souls
have merged with mine.
We shall overcome this together.
All our dreams that were
stifled can now come true.
I'll create a sword for Rias
and for all of
my fallen friends.
Sword Birth, go!
It's the Sword of Betrayer,
a sword vested
with both Holy and Devil powers.
Try and stop it.
[RIAS] Holy and Devil
powers fused together?
[ISSEI] Now it makes sense!
I get what Ddraig
was talking about!
He said Kiba had Peaked.
So that must be Kiba's
prohibited technique.
That sword is his
Balance Breaker!
[VALPER] A Holy Devil Sword?
It's impossible.
Two opposing elements
cannot mix together.
Something like
that is an aberration!
Talk to me, Knight
of Rias Gremory.
Are the two of us still
fighting on the same side?
I'd like to
think we are.
I have a
thought, then;
why don't we destroy
that Excalibur together.
Are you sure?
I understand
that technically
we're looking at a Holy Sword.
But there's nothing
holy about that.
Agreed.
Oh, Peter.
Oh, Basilius and Dionysius,
and the Blessed Virgin Mary.
I ask you to please
hear my prayers!
[XENOVIA] In the
name of the saint
living within this blade...
I hereby set you free!
This is called Durandal.
Durandal?
It's a Holy Sword!
[AKENO] A sword on
par with Excalibur,
said to cut everything
in this world.
[VALPER] That's impossible.
My research didn't go
into how to use Durandal;
no one should be able
to wield that thing.
You're wrong.
Unlike Kiba or Irina.
I'm one of the
rarely found naturals.
[VALPER] One who
is perfectly suitable,
also known as a
true Holy Sword user!
[XENOVIA] This kiddo cuts
anything he touches to pieces.
He doesn't always
listen to me, either.
Besides that, he's
infinitely dangerous
if not stored in
another dimension.
[FREED] I don't believe you!
Damn, I love a
good plot twist!
[XENOVIA] What you have is
simply a broken Holy Sword.
It's no match for my Durandal!
Kiss my ass!
[FREED] I have decided
that I don't like you!
[KIBA] The feeling's mutual!
[KIBA] It wasn't enough
to sever our hopes!
[FREED] My sword broke!
Are you fucking kidding me?
How could I be taken
out by lame devil scum?
No!
Yes! Did you see?
Our powers overcame Excalibur!
[VALPER] How is this possible?
In theory, the fusion of
holy and devil powers is--
Prepare yourself,
Valper Galilei!
Yes.
I understand now;
if the balance between holy
and devil powers is disrupted,
it could be possible!
Which means, not
only the Devil King,
but also God!
[KOKABIEL] Oh Valper,
you really were very talented.
Unfortunately,
you weren't supposed
to figure that part out.
[RIAS] Okay, Kokabiel, what
are you trying to do here?
[KOKABIEL] I'm destroying
everything I find tedious.
Now, I'm even more
bored than before.
Hey there, little boy!
[ISSEI] Yeah, what do you want?
[KOKABIEL] Raise the
Dragon's power as much as
you can and transfer
it to one of them.
Why would you
want me to do that?
[RIAS] So what?
Are you offering
to give us a chance?
Don't bother; we don't need it!
[KOKABIEL] You're being
ridiculous, Rias, my dear!
You're gonna need more
than a little power up.
Rias.
We're out of time.
Let's go. We can do it.
Issei.
[DDRAIG] Boost!
Really?
[ISSEI] Yo, Issei here!
Kokabiel's power
isn't letting up at all!
But don't discount
Kiba just yet.
Or, for that matter,
the rest of us!
Next time:
"Go, Occult Research Club!"
Never underestimate a man
who's still got titties to lick!