[FREED chuckling]
Time to die!
Hasn't anyone told you
to heed the
faces you make?
We wouldn't want our
pretty little prince
getting stuck that way.
Luckily Excalibur
isn't picky.
It's simply hungry
for your blood.
[KIBA] That's
enough, Freak!
[FREED] Now there's
a tone of voice
I never thought I'd
hear come out of you.
Good job!
Holy Eraser!
That was cute.
You win some,
you lose some.
Nice try, kid.
[KIBA] Whatever.
It was just a test.
I wanted to see if
that sword was real.
Thanks for
giving me the license
to destroy you,
and your sword!
[FREED]
That's the spirit!
Get 'em Tiger!
[FREED] Aw, someone
forgot to warn you.
This Holy Sword
absolutely despises devils.
Phooey.
Shut up!
I'm not done yet!
That's cheating!
[KIBA] That's
what devils do!
[FREED]
Nice move, Kiddo.
Oh shit.
[FREED] I hate
to cut this short,
but someone more
important is calling!
It's been fun.
That's all, folks!
It's time to get wet!
So go out there and
make a big splash!
Good morning! It's going
to be a beautiful day!
I feel like hell!
[ISSEI secreams]
[RIAS]
Good morning, Issei.
Did you sleep okay?
[ISSEI]
Why are you here?
You didn't tell
us what to do
before you fell asleep last
night so we just stayed here.
[ISSEI] What?
We made the best of
our sleeping arrangements
and each used one of
your arms as a pillow.
It was quite comfortable.
Very.
[ISSEI thinking] Something's
totally wrong here.
ASIA] We should go
get breakfast started!
It's already late!
[RIAS] Oh right!
Thanks again.
We'll talk to you later.
I hope we didn't keep you
from something important.
Now that she's
hanging out with Rias,
Asia's sex appeal has
gone through the roof.
Not that there's
anything wrong with that!
No, what am I saying?
Asia's pure and I shouldn't
be checking her out,
but I am, which has to mean
that I'm not just into boobs.
Hey! I'm not just into boobs!
No, no, no!
This isn't good!
Best thing to do is
just focus on Rias.
But of course, I can't
because Asia will freak out.
[sniffs deeply]
Why does my
life suck right now?
[ISSEI] In my perfect
fantasy world...
[ISSEI] So who's gonna
be the lucky girl today?
Oh, Issei,
please choose me.
Please have mercy and choose me!
You sure?
Yes! Please choose me!
I'm begging you;
please, have mercy!
All right,
if you say so.
What are you even
talking about, Issei?
Pardon me, ma'am?
Issei, now, listen
to me carefully.
I cannot and
simply will not live
without you in my life,
which means I need you
to satisfy me immediately.
Yeah, okay!
[ASIA] No, please,
you have to do me first!
No, do me first!
[ISSEI] Come on, ladies.
You gotta realize I've
only got one body here!
I know.
Let's decide this with a little
game called rock-paper-scissors.
I won't lose!
Well, neither will I!
Let's do this thing!
I'm not gonna lose!
[RIAS and ASIA]
1, 2, 3! 1, 2, 3! 1, 2, 3!
[ISSEI] I love being
the Harem King!
At least that was what
was supposed to happen.
Reality sucks balls!
It's not fair!
I saw her boobs already!
I touched them!
I can't just act like
everything's normal--
like it didn't happen.
That's torture!
This sucks ass.
[DDRAIG] Yo! Issei!
Sorry to interrupt
your pouting.
Don't act like you've
forgotten my voice.
Oh, Ddraig, hey!
[DDRAIG] Your mind is as
perverse and twisted as ever.
That's refreshing.
I'm in the middle
of a mental breakdown
so I'd appreciate it if you'd
be a little more sensitive!
[DDRAIG] Well,
that's unfortunate.
I came here to
give you a warning.
About what?
[RIAS] Here, try this.
Tell me what you think.
[ASIA] Wow, it's delicious!
Rias, this is the best
miso soup I've ever had.
Mine always ends up too salty.
What did you do?
[DDRAIG] I've felt a
strong spiritual presence
surrounding you lately.
It's made me nervous
and I can't sleep.
Oh yeah.
That's probably Rias.
She's been hanging out
around here a lot more.
If you know what
I mean by "hanging out."
[DDRAIG] Assuming you're
talking about your buddies,
I don't even
notice them anymore.
Are you saying
there's an enemy close by?
[DDRAIG] I'm saying be careful.
You never know
when the White One
will decide to make an
unexpected appearance.
The White One?
That sounds intense.
What does it mean?
[DDRAIG] The Vanishing
Dragon is The White Dragon.
What's a
Vanishing Dragon?
[DDRAIG] We are called
the Twin Sky Dragons,
and we've been fighting
for several years now.
Those with sky dragons living
within them are destined
to fight each other.
What do you mean
"those" with sky dragons?
There's someone else who
has the Sacred Gear like me?
[DDRAIG] There is.
And I'm gonna have
to fight this guy someday
because he's got
your twin inside him?
[DDRAIG] You're my only hope.
This isn't fair.
You're the one who
decided to come live in me.
[DDRAIG] And in
exchange I've given you
the power of the dragon.
It's way fair.
I know.
I haven't forgotten.
You're the only reason
that I was able to save Rias.
And speaking of that,
I've got to say this
one more time, Ddraig.
[DDRAIG] Say it.
Listen close.
I have a dream that
one day I'll rank
so high that
I become the Harem King!
I'll have one
group of hot girls
with huge jugs as servants
and another for my babe army!
Oh yeah. One day all
of this will be mine!
[DDRAIG] It's not
every day I get
to live inside a pervert-tron!
As if I didn't feel
awkward enough. Jeez.
[DDRAIG] Maybe it's
not out of the question.
It's true;
the dragon powers can be
overwhelming to several
of those around you.
Some will want to fight,
but then, many will
find it charming--
especially the female sort.
No way! Really?
[DDRAIG] Definitely.
Every male I've lived in
has been surrounded
by lustful women.
I was there, remember?
Wow!
I had no idea you
were the most amazing
sacred treasure
in the whole world!
[DDRAIG] That's more like it!
Nice switch.
Yes! It's time to
take your powers for a spin!
I am now on a mission
to fully experience
Rias's hot fleshy globes!
[DDRAIG] You want
to squeeze them?
[ISSEI] Suck them. Now.
[DDRAIG sighs]
So this is all about you
having a woman's
breasts in your mouth?
How far we've come.
I suppose the variety of goals
in a partner is good for me.
Just promise you'll
remember what I told you.
I will.
The White Dragon.
Got it.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2-1]
Good morning!
Sona. Look.
The Holy Sword.
Karaoke?
Gotta get my sing on, yo!
We should go to the one
in front of the station.
They get new inserts every week.
They also have contests.
I always love
a good insert.
[BOYS] Kiryuu!
You're having
a contest to see
who gives the best insert?
We were talking
about hittin' up
the K-roke after school!
[KIRYUU] Omigosh
that sounds so fun!
What time are
you guys leaving?
I wanna go!
What do you think, Asia?
You can't
invite yourself!
[ASIA] Karaoke? I'd love to go!
What?
[ASIA] Wow! Look
how shiny the floor is!
[ISSEI] Huh? Oh.
Yeah, that shine is amazing!
[ASIA] What's that?
[ISSEI] Huh? What's what?
[ASIA] That room way
back over there.
See it?
[ISSEI] Oh that.
Yeah that's called
"The Forbidden Room."
It's never been opened.
[RIAS] They did a good job
cleaning the place, didn't they?
Feels like we're
getting a fresh start.
[ISSEI] So, where's Kiba?
[KONEKO] Looks like
somebody decided
to take the entire day off.
Must be nice.
[ASIA] I hope he's okay.
[ISSEI] So do you think
this has anything to do
with what we talked
about yesterday?
Whoa, no frikkin' way.
So what the hell
does Kiba have to do
with the Holy Swords?
Do you remember
me telling you
before about how
he was a survivor
of the Holy Sword Project?
For sure.
What I didn't
tell you was that
there were several
other children involved.
They were all being
raised to use an Excalibur.
[RIAS] As of right now,
there are seven Holy Swords
that are known by
the name Excalibur.
Long ago, pieces of
the original Excalibur
were scattered during a war.
[ISSEI] What? Seven?
[RIAS] That's right.
It was the church
that tracked down
and collected all
of those pieces.
They then used alchemy
to create seven
entirely new swords.
[ISSEI] So does that mean Kiba
is able to use all of them?
Actually, no it does not.
He never adapted to
Excalibur's strength.
In fact, none of those
who were trained ever could.
[RIAS] The entire
project failed.
Completely?
[RIAS] Yes.
So those in charge
of the project decided
to dispose of Kiba and
the other test subjects.
Dispose? Like, kill?
They were already on
the verge of death.
[RIAS] However,
one child was able to escape.
His motivation in staying
alive was a promise
to himself that he
would someday get revenge.
[RIAS] I felt that such
a passion could be used
in a meaningful way
and wanted to help.
There was but a single solution.
[ISSEI] So that's the
reason you made Kiba a devil.
And why he was weird
when he looked at that picture.
We'll just have to wait and
see what happens next.
[AKENO] Fantastic!
It looks like everyone's here.
[RIAS] Akeno.
Why are you so late?
[AKENO]
Well, I brought some guests
and was helping them get here.
[SONA] Thank you for having us.
[ISSEI] The student body
president and vice-president?
Why?
They said they had something
urgent to discuss with you.
Right, Rias.
Would you mind coming with me
to my house right away, please?
This isn't something
you're going
to want to discuss in
front of a lot of people.
Trust me.
You make it sound like
a complicated situation.
It is.
Very complicated.
[ISSEI] What in the
world happened?
Was it just me,
or did you think Sona
was acting weird, too?
[ASIA] Yeah, maybe.
What do you think
about it, Koneko?
Don't know.
It's not like there's
anything wrong
with Rias talking to someone.
However.
I guess I'm more
worried right now
about what's going on with Kiba.
Yeah, actually,
I am, too.
I know what Rias
told us, but still.
I feel like maybe I should try
and help out somehow,
you know what I mean?
Not because I feel obligated,
but because we're friends.
[KONEKO] Yeah.
Well, see you tomorrow.
[ISSEI] See ya, Koneko.
Bye!
See you tomorrow!
Koneko and Akeno
chose this, as well.
What?
Oh.
I was just wondering
why they decided
to become devils, too.
Surely they had reasons
like the rest of us.
Haven't been
here in a long time.
[AKENO] Really; did
you used to come a lot?
[SONA] In the past,
Rias and I came here together
all the time so we could
tell each other secrets.
[SONA] This sauna was
installed for my personal use.
[TSUBAKI] The space is directly
connected to Sona's stronghold,
which means if it's closed,
no one else will be able enter.
[AKENO] Well, that explains
how you could tell
your secrets here.
[RIAS] All I did was complain
about getting in trouble
with my mom.
Silly stuff like that.
And I think Sona
only ever complained
about her sister.
[AKENO] Oh my.
I didn't realize the two
of you were so close.
[SONA] That's all
in the past, now.
True.
So then, what are we
here to discuss this time?
Something tells me
this secret's a good one.
[TSUBAKI] It was this morning.
Two people from the
church contacted me.
Contacted how?
[RIAS] It's been a while
since they came to this town.
Did they tell you
want they wanted?
They did.
Rias, they said they
wanted to speak with you
and that it was urgent.
[RIAS] Members of the church
want to speak with a devil?
What are they up to?
There's no
other reason for them
to be here except
to stir up trouble.
All right, then.
What did you say?
I accepted
their request.
I told them where
they could find you
so after school tomorrow
they'll be paying you a visit.
[RIAS] What?
[SONA] There is one other
thing you need to be aware of.
Not only were these
two members of the church,
but they were also
carrying Holy Swords.
Wow, really?
Well that is certainly
something to consider then.
Why would they
come to this town?
Maybe members of the
church are from this area?
No way!
[ASIA] I just got the
chills for some reason.
[ISSEI] Yeah,
I know what you mean.
Actually, now that
I think about it,
I recognize this
feeling from before.
[ASIA] How?
It was when I met you,
and you were showing
me around the church.
And also...
My mom!
I'm very sorry, Sona.
I have to get back home soon.
Issei and Asia are in danger!
[ISSEI] Mom!
[MOTHER] That's my boy!
And then there was the time
when he ripped his swimming
trunks at the pool for grins.
What's happening?
Hey! There he is!
Welcome home, Issei!
Now what's that sour face for?
[ISSEI thinking] So these guys
are the reason we got chills?
[IRINA] It's been a
while, hasn't it, Issei?
How could you
forget this face?
It's me!
[ISSEI] Uh, right.
[MOTHER] Irina Shido!
Don't you remember this photo?
[ISSEI] Whoa!
That's her? How the hell?
[MOTHER] I know!
She looks so different!
I mean you'd mistake her
for a boy if you
didn't know any better!
And look at her now!
She's positively
gorgeous, isn't she?
[ISSEI] What?
This is so freaking weird!
I always thought she was a boy!
[MOTHER] That's not
very nice! Apologize!
[ISSEI] Huh? For what?
[IRINA] No, he can't help it.
I really did act
like a boy back then!
Yeah. That made
it pretty confusing.
It's okay.
But we should catch up.
A lot has happened to both of us
in the time we've been apart.
Also? I love reunions!
You never know
what's going to happen!
I'm so glad
you're home safe!
I'm so sorry.
I should have paid more
attention to both of you.
I was terrified of
what I might find
when I came back here today.
I'm thankful
I worried for nothing.
I promise to keep a better eye
on each of your
whereabouts from now on.
[ISSEI] Uh, Rias?
What is it?
[ISSEI] Your breasts.
[RIAS] Of course, I understand.
Oh, Issei, do you have any
idea how much I spoil you?
You can't do that!
[ISSEI] Yeah,
I can't do that.
[RIAS] Why were they in
there talking to your mother?
No clue.
Maybe Irina actually
wanted to catch up
and show me she's a chick now.
They never said
why they were there.
But it didn't matter.
All they cared about when they
left was that we were devils.
[RIAS] That's fine.
I honestly don't know
what they're planning,
but perhaps we can
ask them tomorrow.
[ISSEI] Tomorrow?
That's what
I've been told.
They'll be visiting the
clubroom tomorrow after school.
[ISSEI] Can't believe
someone I've known
since I was a kid is now a
follower of the church.
I'm not looking
forward to tomorrow.
[ISSEI'S CLIENT]
What's the matter, Devil Boy?
Hey. I'm sorry.
I've just got a lot
on my mind right now.
It's a bit unusual
to see a devil looking
so worried, isn't it?
Things in this
world usually turn out
the way you want them to.
Stress about the
future is a waste of time.
Just wait it out a bit.
Things'll change.
Oh. Looks like you've
got a bite on that hook!
Pull him in!
[XENOVIA] Thank you for
agreeing to speak with us today.
My name is Xenovia.
And I'm Irina Shido.
[RIAS] It's fascinating
to me why followers of God
would want to meet with a devil.
[IRINA] It does seem random.
Here's the thing.
There are six swords
we can account for.
Three of them are
still with the church.
But we happen to know
that the other three
were stolen by fallen angels.
You sure about that?
These are from the
ones we have left.
They're made from Excalibur.
This weapon is mine.
It's called the
Sword of Destruction.
[IRINA] And then there's
the one I have here.
It's known as the
Holy Sword of Mimicry.
It's an Excalibur Mimic!
Well.
What is it you would
like us to do for you today?
Stay completely out of it.
This is between us
and the fallen angels.
Let's keep it simple, shall we?
We don't need the devils
in this town to intervene.
[RIAS] That sounds
like an accusation.
Are you
afraid that we'll side
with the fallen angels
and keep you
from obtaining
the Holy Swords?
[XENOVIA] We know
that for devils,
a Holy Sword is
a detestable thing.
Wouldn't it make more sense
for you to support
the fallen angels?
[ISSEI thinking] Oh, man.
Rias is getting pissed!
And if that's true,
we will have no choice but
to completely annihilate you.
Even though you are
the Great Devil's sister.
[RIAS] If you already
have me figured out
then let me share
something with you:
There is no way
I'd ever even think
of joining the fallen angels.
I would never do anything
to besmirch the name
of the House of Gremory
or my dear brother.
It's enough for me just
to be able to hear that.
I was only relaying the
thoughts of headquarters.
I honestly didn't think
the little sister of Lucifer
would really be that stupid.
[RIAS] Good to know.
Then I hope you also understand
that I will not provide
aid to your side, either.
Of course.
I trust that we will
prevail if you promise
not to intervene in anything
we may do in this town.
[RIAS] You have my word on that.
[XENOVIA] We won't take up
any more of your time.
[RIAS] Would you like
some tea before you go?
[XENOVIA] No, thanks.
I'm not here to make
friends with devils.
We'll let ourselves out.
I was wondering
if visiting the home
of Issei Hyodo
would lead us to you.
[XENOVIA]
Aren't you Asia Argento?
Um, yes.
It makes sense
that I would run
into a witch in
a place like this.
Oh my goodness!
It is you!
You're the former saint
who became a witch!
I had heard that
you were banished
because you had the power to
heal fallen angels and devils,
and that one time
you actually used it!
You must be pretty strong!
I didn't know you'd actually
become a devil yourself.
[ASIA] Well, I um-- I guess so.
[ISSEI ] You okay?
[XENOVIA]
Of course she's not okay.
She went from being
a saint to being a devil.
That's about as
far as one can fall.
[ISSEI] That's enough!
Why don't you take that
crap and get out of here!
[KONEKO] Dude,
you're not helping.
[ISSEI thinking] She's right.
Even I know it
would be a dick move
to pick a fight with
these jerks right now.
Ball sack!
[XENOVIA] Do you still
believe in our God, Asia?
Don't be silly.
She's like, a
devil, and stuff.
She's over us.
No.
That doesn't always mean
what you think it does.
There are those whose hearts
continue to remain pious
in the midst of their
own selfish betrayal.
She seems like she
might be one of them.
[IRINA] Really?
Is it true, Asia?
Do you still believe in God?
I mean, I know you're
like a devil, but do you?
Yes. I've never
been able to let go.
I've believed in God
this whole time.
Then you should allow us
to execute you this instant.
Though you have sinned
in the worst way possible;
if you sacrifice your soul
to Him, He will forgive you.
Let yourself be
convicted by my hand.
God will work through
me to save you.
[RIAS] Do you mind
stopping there, please?
There is no need
for you to be
shaming my servant
here in that way.
I wasn't shaming
her senselessly.
As one of God's servants,
I feel it is my duty
to rescue her soul.
Issei, no!
Stop! Don't do it!
Everything's okay.
You have no right
to call Asia a witch!
Believe me;
that's one of the
nicest descriptions
I have for someone who
has done what she has.
[ISSEI] I don't want to hear it!
You pricks are the ones
who decided she
was a saint, not Asia!
That wasn't her choice!
She was happier
without any of this!
I'm okay.
[XENOVIA] A genuine
saint can survive
on the love of God alone.
If Asia makes sacrifices for
the love of anyone besides God,
then she was never a true saint.
[ISSEI] What does
that even mean?
Saint or not, Asia is one of the
kindest souls you'll ever know!
If you can't see that,
then you're an idiot!
And who exactly
are you to Asia Argento?
[ISSEI] I'm her family!
We all are! And her friends!
If you so much as raise
a hand against her,
I will spend every last breath
I have making
sure you regret it!
[XENOVIA] Is that so?
Then are you prepared to
take on the entire church?
That's pretty big talk
for a little devil,
like yourself.
[RIAS] Issei, that's enough!
[KIBA] This is perfect.
I'll take all of you on.
[XENOVIA] Who are you?
Your superior.
Nice to meet you.
Kiba?
[XENOVIA] Alright then,
let's begin.
[AKENO] Are you
sure this is okay?
Should we be fighting people
from the church
without permission?
[RIAS] It's just
an informal bout--
not an actual official battle.
'Cause if the
higher-ups found out,
then we'd all be in trouble!
[XENOVIA] Consider it a drill.
No killing.
Why are you laughing?
[KIBA] Because the one
thing I always wanted
to destroy more than
anything has appeared
willingly before my very eyes.
Sword Birth, is it?
I remember now.
During the Holy Sword
Project there was
one subject facing disposal
but managed to escape.
Issei, it's totally you!
Yeah? So what?
[IRINA] I feel like fate is
making fun of me right now.
A friend I grew up
with has become a devil?
Why is this happening?
[IRINA] My one goal in
this world was to learn
how to use a Holy Sword,
move far away,
and help everyone around me!
God must be
testing my will
to overcome this
traumatic heartbreak.
If I can prove
I'm strong enough,
I will be that
much closer to Him!
Yeah, I'm pretty sure none
of this has to do with you.
But whatever.
I'm so sorry, Issei.
This hurts me much
more than it hurts you,
but your sins will now face
the wrath of my Excalibur!
Fine. You wanna
go there?
Boosted Gear!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[ISSEI] Yo, Issei here!
It's finally time
for the showdown
with the pair of
hottie church girls
with holy swords!
If it comes down to it,
I'll have no choice but to
let that special move explode!
Next time:
"I'll Destroy the Holy Sword!"
Come to me, boobies!