Here, have a gift!
[ISSEI] Dragon Shot!
Thanks, Issei!
No prob. Everyone okay?
[RIAS] This is too dangerous.
Which is why I need you
to please take care
of Gasper for me.
[SIR ZECHS] All right.
Can we kill them, now?
We're supposed to
protect this area
until the gate closes,
so let's focus on that first!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[SIR ZECHS] The only one
who can use strong
protection magic is Rias.
This whole thing's all my fault.
[ISSEI] Rias!
[GASPER] I should
help them. I wanna help.
Rias! Issei!
Please listen.
I can fight, too.
I want to be a
man just like Issei is.
I want to make
you all proud of me,
and I want to be worthy of you.
I will fight. I just have to.
I'm gonna do whatever it
takes to protect my friends!
You can't, Gasper!
Please, Zechs,
you have to stop him!
Do something!
[GASPER] I can do this.
Watch me! I can be a man, too!
[RIAS] Gasper!
Oh?
What was that?
Any idea what
just happened?
I don't have a clue.
Welcome back, Sona!
Will you get off of me?
Gasper did it.
I'm not sure how, but he
made time go back to normal.
[GRAYFIA] He stopped
the enemy gate, too.
One less thing to
worry about, so hooray!
Oh, hell yeah!
You owned them, Gasper!
I don't understand.
We'll tell you
the details later.
For now. I need everyone's help.
[AKENO] You got it, Rias!
Ring out, Thunder!
Tsubaki!
I'm on it, Sona.
[AZAZEL] Well then, why don't
we start getting serious here?
I'm so bored right now, are you?
What're you holding?
[AZAZEL] Something much
more interesting than war.
Call it my hobby.
This is the Downfall
Dragon Spear.
It's an artificial Sacred Gear
developed by yours truly.
[AZAZEL] Balance Break.
What's he doing?
[AZAZEL] Armor of
the Fallen Dragon.
Downfall Dragon Another Armor.
[ISSEI] A dragon's armor.
He can do a
Balance Breaker, too?
[AZAZEL] Now, come here.
I'll kill you!
[CATTLEYA screams]
[AZAZEL]
Ha ha!
[CATTLEYA] I am not
necessarily needed
for the creation
of our new world!
[CATTLEYA] If I can take out
one of the Three Great Powers,
then I welcome death.
[CATTLEYA] I'll destroy
myself for glory!
[AZAZEL] Destroy yourself?
Ha!
I don't want to mock
your hopes and dreams,
but it doesn't seem worth it.
[AZAZEL] You'll still die.
[high-pitched wail]
[AZAZEL] But I'm only willing
to give up an arm for you.
And yet again
there's still plenty
of room for improvement.
But I guess you can stay
with me a little while longer.
My Dragon King Fafnir.
That dude is hard.
He lost his arm!
We're not done.
There are still a
few stragglers left.
Right, yeah.
Ascalon!
[DDRAIG] Blade!
Nice, they've
annihilated everyone.
What the hell?
Y'got me.
Must be losing
my edge. Bad, Vali.
[VALI] Sorry, Azazel.
Things looked more
interesting on this side.
[ISSEI] Vali!
You're the one who betrayed us!
I can understand,
but there is something
I'd like to ask you.
[VALI]
Hmm?
[AZAZEL] You know Shemhaza,
my Vice Governor-General.
Well, he's recently
informed me of a faction
that has been gathering
the dangerous elements
and members of the
Three Great Powers.
What were they called?
Oh, yes, the Chaos Brigade.
Chaos sounds accurate.
Whoever's in charge
must be strong.
But why would
anyone gather
such dangerous
people together?
So. I bet I can guess
who's leading you.
Has to be Orphis,
the Ouroboros Dragon, right?
Orphis! It can't be!
Is that another dragon?
The Infinite Dragon God,
a dragon so strong,
even God was afraid of him.
[VALI] Yes, it is true
I have sided with Orphis.
But believe me,
neither one of us
has the slightest interest
in world domination.
[VALI] We're just
a group who formed
in order to use our power.
And that's all.
Well, that makes more sense.
Conspiring with Cattleya seemed
a little beneath you,
but even so.
Both of you had
Devil Titles stolen,
so I wasn't sure.
He's a Devil King
descendant, too?
What are you saying?
[VALI] My name is Vali Lucifer.
[SIR ZECHS] What?
[ISSEI] Lucifer?
[RIAS] No!
[VALI] I am a direct descendant
of one of the dead Devil Kings.
My mother was a human,
so I'm a half-blood.
My father was
the grandson
of the former
Great Devil King Lucifer.
[RIAS] No. It can't be true.
[SIR ZECHS]
Of course. Half-human.
There's no way we
could have known.
[AZAZEL] While you have the
blood of a real Devil King,
since you are also a
human, you just happened
to be able to be possessed
by the Vanishing Dragon.
[AZAZEL] So basically,
your very existence is a joke.
I would go with
"miracle" personally,
but to each their own.
[ASIA] Look at his wings!
[MICHAEL] Dear God.
[AZAZEL] I have a
feeling this one will be
the best White Dragon Emperor
the world has ever known.
Past, present, and future.
The best dragon ever.
[VALI] Issei Hyodo, fate can
be cruel, wouldn't you agree?
Yeah. Maybe.
[VALI] I am the
strongest dragon,
and I carry with me the
blood of the Devil King.
But you are just a lowly human.
Before becoming a devil,
you weren't even an impressive
student in high school.
That is to say,
aside from the Boosted Gear,
you are nothing.
It's disappointing.
It's so disappointing
it's funny.
Even though we are
rival Sacred Gears--
You and I are as far
apart as the sky to the earth.
No, more than that.
You got a point there, Vali?
[VALI] I do; I think
you should try harder.
Maybe you should
try being an avenger.
I could kill your parents
if that would help.
[ISSEI] Eh?
[VALI] If I take something,
as precious to you as
your mother and father, away,
surely you would be able
to act on that tragic fate.
Your parents would most likely
be grateful to me
for their murder.
Any death I would
grant them would be
far more exciting than
their current boring life.
Yes, let's do that.
No. How can
he be so cruel?
Oh, Issei.
I'm so gonna
kill this asshole.
[RIAS] Issei!
Why should my
parents have to die
for his damn convenience?
Like I would just sit idly by
and let him take
anything from me!
[DDRAIG]
Welsh Dragon Over Booster!
[ISSEI] No one hurts
the people I care about.
I don't care who they are!
It's his Balance Breaker!
[VALI] Look, Albion.
The boy's power has
gone up exponentially.
[ALBION] The Sacred Gear
uses strong feelings
to sustain its power.
You're facing pure
rage from him right now.
Well done.
That is one of the
most appropriate ways
of drawing out the dragon.
[VALI] So what you're saying is,
I'm even better at
drawing out his dragon
than he is at being one.
[ISSEI] Yeah, keep
talking, douchebag!
Ascalon!
[DDRAIG] Blade!
[ALBION] The Dragon Slayer?
I won't be able to deflect
even one cut from this.
[VALI] All right, then
I won't let him cut me.
Issei!
Let me go; he needs me!
At this point,
both of their auras
have passed their limits.
If you get too close to either
of them, you'll burn and die.
But I-- I can't just
sit here and watch this!
[VALI] Weak. You're too weak!
[splutters]
[ALBION] Divide!
[ISSEI] Damn it.
How could I have forgotten?
He absorbs the power
of whatever comes
into contact with his sword.
I'm so stupid.
[RIAS] Are you all right?
[ISSEI] A-okay! You don't
have to worry about me!
[GASPER] Issei, don't lose!
You have to beat him!
[ISSEI] I will.
Especially since
Rias is watching!
[ISSEI] I won't
lose in front of her!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[VALI] Adorable.
What did he do?
[DDRAIG] He sent
the extra energy he got
from you out through his wings.
By doing that,
he can maintain his power
at the upper limits
of his capacity.
[ISSEI] Okay, so no matter
how amazing he might be,
there's still a limit
to what he can handle?
[VALI] Exactly.
[VALI] During the
fight with Kokabiel,
you were fighting for the sake
of your friends, weren't you?
Does this mean
I should kill your friends,
before I kill your family?
[ISSEI] Asia!
[VALI] What about her?
[ISSEI] You bastard!
Stop fucking around,
you piece of shit!
[VALI] Hate me more!
Get angrier!
Get stronger and
stronger for me.
[VALI] Let's have some real fun.
Issei, no!
[ISSEI] Ddraig!
Transfer power to Ascalon!
[DDRAIG] Transfer!
[ISSEI] Do it again!
[RIAS] He's transferring
power to Vali?
[ISSEI] I'm going to
boost the power you absorb
along with whatever you're
releasing at the same time!
Eventually, your
precious wings won't be
able to take any more!
[ALBION] The mechanisms
are going into overdrive.
We must restart the system.
[ISSEI] Feel the power
of The Dragon Slayer!
That was amazing.
You completely blew
away my Sacred Gear.
I knew you could hold
your own if you just tried.
That's what I expect
from my rival.
What's going on now?
[ISSEI] Son of a bitch!
[DDRAIG] It won't be over
until the other person
is unable to fight any longer.
This is how dragons battle.
[ISSEI] What's wrong?
[DDRAIG] The armband is reaching
the limit of its effectiveness.
This is happening
because I'm too damn weak again.
[DDRAIG] There's no way we
can win against a time limit.
Run away, or you'll die.
[ISSEI] I can't
abandon everyone!
[ISSEI] Ddraig, the Sacred Gear
evolves in response
to what I'm feeling, right?
[DDRAIG] Yes, but before
you do anything rash,
are you really ready to die?
[ISSEI] I can't die yet.
Come on, I still have
to get it on with Rias.
Trust me, for that, I can
take on the whole world!
[DDRAIG] I like your resolve.
Now, let me show you
my determination!
I am the mass of power
known as the Red Dragon Emperor.
We will survive this
together as true partners!
Issei Hyodo, are you ready?
[ISSEI] Yeah!
[VALI] What can you
do so late in the game?
Listen, you
Vanishing Dragon Dickhead!
This is where I take your power!
Issei, no!
Um. What happened?
Is he okay?
Damn it, this fucking hurts!
The light spear
was nothing compared
to what I'm going through, now!
[VALI] Are you trying
to take in my power?
Kiba managed it.
He fused them.
Holy and Devil powers together.
I can, too.
I'm gonna take your
vanishing power.
Combine it with my Sacred Gear
and then kick your ass!
[ALBION] Rather reckless.
We are conflicting existences.
To do that would be suicide.
[DDRAIG] So you know, Albion,
possessing this
particular master
has taught me
something important.
Even a fool can make
the impossible possible
as long as he never gives up.
[ISSEI] I'm that fool.
I'm proud of it.
If my abilities can't win,
then I'll stick with being
the idiot till the end!
Respond to what I'm
feeling and do your worst!
[DDRAIG] Vanishing Dragon,
Power is Taken!
[ISSEI] Bam, Dividing
Gear in your face!
[ALBION] Impossible.
This is impossible.
[DDRAIG] You've definitely
taken years off your life.
Most devils live almost forever,
but you will not be one of them.
[ISSEI] Didn't plan to
live that long, anyway.
I still got shit
I want to do, though!
Vali, I have taken
away your power!
Surrender to me or--
[VALI] This is fun.
My turn to play seriously.
[ALBION] Half Dimension!
[ISSEI] What's he doing?
Vali is warping
the dimensions.
It's a very dangerous action.
Wait, how is that fair?
[AZAZEL] It isn't fair at all.
Oh, what are we going to do
with our two fighting
dragon lovebirds?
He'll have to want
it more to win.
Let's try adding another element
that isn't fair of our own.
Hey, Red Dragon Emperor. Issei!
[ISSEI] What do you want?
Let me make sure this is
simple, so you'll understand.
That power he has divides
things around it in half.
[ISSEI] Divides it?
[AZAZEL] Meaning
Rias Gremory's bust line
will also become half
its original size.
Huh?
[ISSEI gasps]
[ISSEI thinking] Her boobs?
Half their size?
I don't want to live in a world
where Rias has a normal rack.
They're such wonderful
tits, and I love them.
I've never loved
anything more. Boobies!
[ISSEI] Don't fuck with me!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[ISSEI] Rias's boobs
are perfect,
and I won't let you reduce them!
[VALI] Wait, what?
[ISSEI] You monster!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[ISSEI] You're pure evil!
[ISSEI] I will never
forgive you for this!
[DDRAIG] Boost! Boost!
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
[AZAZEL]
Hahahaha!
This fight is hilarious!
His power increases
this much just
to keep his master's
chest from getting smaller.
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[VALI] Today has
been full of surprises,
but at least it's not boring.
[ISSEI] Try laying a
finger on Rias Gremory!
I dare you!
I'll destroy
you so completely,
you'll never be able to be
reborn again, you hear me, Vali!
[VALI] Where did
that speed come from?
[ISSEI] So what.
If you had your way,
would it just be Rias,
or would you make
everyone's boobs smaller?
[ISSEI] This is for Rias
and her mammoth love melons!
[DDRAIG] Divide!
[ISSEI] And this is
for Akeno's huge honkers!
[ISSEI] This is to make sure
Asia gets to keep on growing!
[ISSEI] For Xenovia's
killer kazongas!
[ISSEI] And this is for Koneko's
poor itty bitty titties.
You can't divide them.
The only things left would
be very lonely nipples!
[VALI] Interesting!
This is fascinating!
How can he
still stand up?
[VALI] All right.
Think you can handle
something stronger?
It's the Juggernaut.
[ALBION] Forget it, Vali.
That is not the best
choice for this situation.
[VALI] I, one who awakens,
to the supremacy...
[ISSEI] C'mon!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[ALBION] Vali!
Are you asking me
to adapt to this power?
[VALI]
...and join with me.
[VALI] Bikou, what
are you doing here?
[BIKOU] We're finally
going to fight
with the Northern earth gods,
so I was sent to find you
and bring you back.
[VALI] I see. It's about time.
[ISSEI] Who are you?
Where the hell
did you come from?
[AZAZEL] That's Bikou.
A descendant of the
Victorious Fighting Buddha.
[ISSEI] What?
Oh, come on,
surely you've heard
of the trickster monkey
from the Saiyuki legends.
You know, Son Goku?
Huh?
He's related to Goku?
I have to say, Bikou,
I never expected you
to become a member
of the Chaos Brigade.
Hell must have frozen over.
On the other hand,
the White Dragon
and Son Goku do
look good together.
Hahaha!
Well, charm and beauty
do run in my family,
so I look good with
just about anybody.
Until next time,
Red Dragon Emperor.
[VALI] When our
battle continues,
we should make this
fight more intense.
Make sure
you're ready, Issei.
Wait, are you
running away?
Even if it was
only for a short moment,
he released an
explosive amount of power.
He's out of steam.
Issei! Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
But more importantly, I did it.
And your boobs get
to stay perfect.
Oh, Issei.
[RIAS] Finally a joint effort
between all of us.
It looks like
we really have
achieved peace
this time, doesn't it?
Apologies, Azazel;
Cattleya was one of
our internal issues.
Vali from our side
caused problems, as well.
And, it was my mistake
not to nip that in
the bud a long time ago.
Everything truly
is starting anew.
Excuse me, um, Chief Michael?
[ISSEI] I uh-- I just
wanted to ask a favor.
As long as it's within
my power, anything.
Do you think you could maybe
allow Asia and Xenovia
to start praying again?
I know it would mean
so much to them.
Well ladies,
is that the truth?
Yes.
[MICHAEL] Then let
me ask you this.
Would you still pray
even though you know
God isn't here anymore?
Yes.
Even if there is no God,
I'd love to be able to pray;
it brings me comfort.
Same for me.
I'd appreciate the
chance to give thanks
to God as well as
to you, Chief Michael.
I'll ask the same
on their behalf;
please let them pray.
Irina.
I didn't know
the entire story,
and I was so devastated when
I thought you had betrayed us.
I'm so sorry.
Well don't be;
there's nothing
to apologize for.
[IRINA] Asia,
what I said to you
was mean-spirited
and just plain cruel.
Oh, not at all.
I'm used to it anyway.
I hope you
can forgive me.
No, please.
I-- I wasn't really even
all that upset, believe me.
[LEVIATHAN] How cute;
a friendship between the
believers of the Devil and God!
Michael, can you do it?
Perhaps granting them their wish
will be a symbol of our peace?
Yes.
And besides, I seriously
doubt two devils
that don't receive damage
when they pray will
be the end of the world.
How merciful, Chief Michael!
Yes, thank you!
Thank you so much!
Dear God.
Give it time, ladies;
I have to return to headquarters
and change the system first.
I think I'll stay
here for a while.
I can't believe how much
I like this place.
Surprised?
I told you I'd do something
for you only I could do, right?
[ISSEI] Yeah, so what's
that supposed to mean?
[AZAZEL] I'm tired now.
I'm going home.
[GASPER] Koneko,
please tell me it's over.
[KONEKO] Don't worry.
I promise nothing scary
will happen to you anymore.
[GASPER] Finally, huh?
[RIAS] Hey, Gasper.
Oh. I'm sorry, Rias!
This is-- this
was all my fault
because the bad
guys wanted me.
No, this was my fault
because I failed to
protect you, Gaspie.
You're wrong;
that's not true!
Yes, it is true.
[RIAS] You did
a good job, Koneko.
You both did a good job.
Gasper, I'm so proud of you.
You were very brave just
so you could help
the rest of us.
And that makes me happy.
I haven't been this
happy in such a long time.
Yeah, me too.
You made me really
happy, too, Gaspie.
Oh, President Rias, and Koneko.
[LEVIATHAN]
Sona. Confession time!
I've taken a fancy to this
town and this high school.
Oh, is that right?
So, I'll come back soon!
[SONA] No. Please don't do that.
Please don't? Why?
Um-- because
I uh-- said so.
Hey Tsubaki,
you won't mind
if I decide to come back
here again, will you?
Uh-- I-- course not.
[SONA] Tsubaki.
But that's me.
The president should be the
final judge of that, after all.
[LEVIATHAN] No fair!
[ISSEI] Chief Michael.
Thank you very much
for granting my request.
Let me know how I can repay you.
But you already have.
You performed a
distinguished service.
Granting your request
doesn't even begin
to compensate for what you did.
[ISSEI] No sir,
that's not true at all.
[XENOVIA thinking] I see.
It's not because he has
the power of a Dragon.
It's because he's a good man,
the kind that attracts
people like Rias and Asia.
And so, I must
return to Heaven
to report on the
peace agreement.
Next, we will work on measures
against the Chaos Brigade.
Farewell.
[ASIA] Issei.
[ISSEI]
Isn't everything great, Asia?
[ASIA] Oh, Issei. I love you!
What did you
just say? Hey, Asia!
Oh my goodness.
Asia, I like how bold
you're getting to be.
[SIR ZECHS] Well.
I guess it was an important
factor after all, wasn't it?
[GRAYFIA] What do you mean?
[SIR ZECHS] Issei Hyodo.
The true source of his power.
[ISSEI] Xenovia!
Now you can pray all you want!
Isn't that awesome?
Oh. Yeah. But um--
No. I-- I
mean thank you.
Now. Club
activities start tomorrow!
[CLUB] You got it, Rias!
[AZAZEL] And so, starting
from this day forward,
I have become the advisor
for the Occult Research Club.
Wait... you can't be serious.
Oh, but I am; I asked
Sir Zechs and everything.
He told me I should talk
to Serafall's little
sister about it.
[ISSEI] You did this, Sona?
Look, I didn't
have much of a choice;
if I didn't agree with it
my sister threatened the worst.
She said she'd come instead.
So basically, what you
mean is you sold us out.
Anyway. I'll leave you to it.
[RIAS] Hey, Sona!
[ISSEI] Dude.
How'd you get that arm?
Oh, my new friend here
is the omnipotent arm
I made during all
my Sacred Gear research.
I've always wanted to
equip something like this,
and I'm so glad I did.
Now, understand, Sir Zechs
had one condition for me.
I cannot stay here unless
I provide a gift to you.
[GASPER] Yeah?
What kind of gift?
As long as I'm around,
I will help you properly develop
your immature Sacred Gears.
[chuckles]
The mysterious Boosted Gear
with unpredictable evolution.
The Holy Devil Sword.
And Forbidden Balor View.
[AZAZEL] I can use the research
I've done to evolve them
on an individual level,
understand?
So, then, from now on you can
call me Mister Azazel, okay?
Uh, "Mister Azazel"? Dude.
Nothing personal, but that
feels weird in my mouth.
I'm looking forward
to working with you all.
Hold it; I never
agreed to this;
how can we even trust you?
[AZAZEL] Oh, yeah.
Sir Zechs gave me another
message for you, as well.
Another message?
It seems when he stayed
at Issei's house previously,
he learned the importance
of a good skinship
between household members.
Notably for you.
Apparently that's what
the Red Dragon Emperor
needs to charge his power.
Okay.
I don't get what
you're saying at all.
[AZAZEL] All right, then.
This is an official order
in the name of the
great Devil King Lucifer.
All of the
current female members
of the Occult Research Club
are hereby directed
to move in with
Issei immediately.
There ya go.
Move in?
[AKENO] Issei.
I'm here, and I swear
no matter what,
I'll never leave your side!
[ISSEI] Hey, cool, thanks!
[XENOVIA] Should I just stay
in the same room as Asia then?
Issei. I need to say something.
Yeah?
If you peek in my room,
and steal or sniff my panties.
I will make you suffer.
This isn't fair.
Yeah.
I know, but my big
brother ordered it,
so what can we do?
I've got it!
I'm going to demand
that my brother
to remodel this
house completely!
[ISSEI] You what?
The White One is after power.
And the Red is after women.
Well, at least their
motives are pure,
in their own way.
[ISSEI] Hey!
[AZAZEL] Even without God.
The world keeps
right on turning.