Mr. Tasman. Where do these
mountains of ice come from?
A continent known
as Magallánica.
A mysterious land located
somewhere on the southern seas,
yet to be discovered.
It's said to be completely
covered with snow.
Ruled by strange creatures with
pouches on their stomachs.
[KOMA] A place not even the
explorers of Europe have seen.
That is my destination.
It's too dangerous!
I thank you for taking me this
far, Mr. Tasman. Goodbye.
[EXPLORER A]
It's not unheard of.
An explorer goes missing,
then years later, the ice will
melt and we'll find their body.
Hm?
[EXPLORER A] I don't know
which base she's from,
but I guess we have
to dig her out.
[EMI]
That expression on her face.
[MAGOTAKE] Looks like she's
smiling, doesn't it?
[EMI]
Is she a superhuman?
[MAGOTAKE]
She'd have to be to survive.
Frozen in place for
over 300 years.
[EMI] But her outfit,
it's definitely Japanese.
How did she end
up in Antarctica?
[MAGOTAKE]
Good question.
Could she be related
to your kind?
That's too far back for
me to have knowledge of.
She doesn't smell
like a yokai though.
[SATOMI]
Sold!
[MAGOTAKE]
Why am I not surprised?
Imperial Ads has
purchased this decoration
from the Environmental Agency.
We'll handle the investigation.
The Superhuman Bureau
will be reimbursed
for maintenance and
transportation costs.
It will be invoiced as a
"reference material fee."
What's your scheme
this time, Mr. Satomi?
My scheme? A rather
bizarre choice of words.
The Superhuman Bureau,
the Public Security Force,
and Imperial Ads?
We all work together now.
Public and private, creating
better policies for superhumans.
[MICHIKO] And now we
have one frozen in ice.
Think of the publicity.
It's really a shame they're
going to wake her up.
Seems like she's
having a good dream.
Hey, guys. Has the
ice block arrived yet?
[HYOUMA] Are you sure you
can take him down, Koma?
[KOMA] I destroy evil
and bring peace.
That is my purpose.
It's all I know.
Imperial Ads said they're
gonna use it for publicity.
Maybe they're shooting
a film about Antarctica.
Mr. Jaguar?
[TACHIBANA]
Why do you think I'm spending
so much money on you?
Stop them from
printing this trash!
[SATOMI] The tall nail
does get the hammer.
And you, Mr Tachibana,
are a telephone pole.
Japan has seen
unparalleled advances
thanks to me and my continued
role as its Prime Minister!
That will never change!
No one denies that, sir.
We met you before the war,
and we've helped your
career get this far.
Imperial Ads is still your
friend, I assure you.
[MICHIKO]
She's ready to meet you.
[TACHIBANA]
Oh.
[TACHIBANA] It is an extreme
honor and privilege
to welcome you to
my estate today.
Iron Mask Fencer!
Um, all right.
Can't believe it's
been over 300 years.
Wow, these drawings
are really something.
What does this mean?
All of these little circles?
Oh, that's the starting
bid for the auction.
Twenty-five hundre--
[clears throat]
[TACHIBANA] These modern
songs must not suit you.
This might be of interest.
[REPORTER A] Tonight,
we look at superhuman crime,
including the violence
in Shinjuku.
And recently, a daring
prison escape.
Unease is spreading
among the populace.
There are new sightings.
Reports of giant bug-like
invaders similar to the ones
that attacked...
This is a nightmare!
The nation will fall
into chaos again.
[KOMA]
As told in the legends,
I must sacrifice myself, as the
daughter of the village elder.
Please, protect my village,
and stop those villains.
Sister! No!
Tachibana. You're the
ruler of this land?
Yes.
[KOMA] Then I'll repay you
for saving me from the ice.
I'll put a stop to this.
These superhuman bandits,
tell me where I can
find their leader.
Everything you need is here.
One of your clients?
No! I've never seen her before!
I can't think why anyone
would attack me.
Followers of Zeth Satan,
you villains have grown weaker
over the last 300 years.
I'm no villain.
I'm the Iron Detective!
You haven't heard of me?
[KOMA] Then where is he?
Dragongod Asahi?
What are you talking ab--?
Don't protect him!
He betrayed you, the Zeth
Satan Clan, and my--
[gasps]
[KIKKO]
How cool! He has his own office!
[HYOUMA]
Keep it down, wouldja?
[KIKKO]
Shiba Detective Agency.
Don't know why a wanted criminal
would put up a
sign up like that.
He's askin' for it.
You're distracting me, Kikko.
I can't treat it
if you won't let me.
[ULLR] Just use your healing
spell. It's more effective.
You know a healing spell?
Oh. Right. I forgot.
You weren't kidding.
You have grown up.
So, I wonder what
Fuurouta is up to.
He hasn't shown up in a while.
Have you seen him lately?
Are you okay?
Hey, Mr. Jaguar! Is it true?
That girl's the legendary
Iron Mask Fencer?
[RAITO] The Iron Mask
Fencer is just fairy tale.
A character in storybooks.
Fighting evil in
the Sengoku period.
There's a chance the characters
from ancient folklore
were really superhumans.
What?
I wonder if Mr. Jaguar's seen
any of 'em in real life.
What do you mean?
Hoshino!
[KIKKO] Sorry! Was that
supposed to be a secret?
Wait a sec.
Are you try'nta say
this jaguar-man
has the power to
travel back in time?
Of course not.
That's impossible.
I didn't realize
he could hear me!
Seriously?
A time traveler.
[KIKKO]
Mr. Jaguar's been to the past
and met the Iron
Mask Fencer before.
That's how he was
able to identify her.
What I don't understand is
why she would attack Jiro.
But I may know
where she's going.
Last year, after they dug up
the Takamatsuzuka Tomb,
several excavations
were made nearby.
She must be headed there.
[WORKERS yelling]
Please! Don't destroy it!
It's a national treasure!
[KOMA]
Asahi's blood.
Looks like we beat her to it.
The wall painting from the tomb.
Over there! That's the
girl from the ice!
[HYOUMA]
Jiro! Hoshino! Stop her!
Or this won't end well!
Don't you have missiles
or weapons of any kind
on this thing?
Hey, hands off!
And no, I designed this
plane to support Equus,
not act as a combat jet.
Then stop time or something!
Great idea!
Just one problem.
Your friend took my watch!
[CHINATSU]
Listen to this!
The Iron Mask Fencer joined
forces with Dragongod Asahi
to defeat Zesuzusaata.
Zeth Satan!
The legendary rulers of
Azuchi-Momoyama period Japan!
It all makes sense.
[CHINATSU]
Zeth Satan?
The name sounds awfully Western.
Likely.
There were European missionaries
in Japan during that period.
I spoke to some of my kind who
knew the history better than me.
That area has a strong
spiritual force,
and centuries ago was used
to seal away an ogre-god.
Then Emi won't be
able to go near it.
Yes, yes, it all makes sense!
Everything makes sense
for the second time today!
Nobody knows who was buried
in the Takamatsuzuka Tomb,
or why it was built
in the first place.
But if this other tomb
is similar in shape
it must have been used
by the Iron Mask Fencer
to seal evil with help
from the local spirits.
It's imprisoning Zeth Satan?
[ULLR]
Very strange.
It seems that girl just
dug up her old nemesis
she worked so hard to seal away.
I think I know why.
I'll bet she's going to
resurrect a 300-year-old spirit.
[KIKKO]
Jiro! Listen to me!
What do I do?
[ULLR] You don't need my
permission to transform anymore.
Adults set their
own power channels.
Right.
Witch power channel
set! Meteortail!
[ULLR] Star Child has lost
touch with her essence.
She's no longer a
candidate for queen.
She will simply age
like a normal human.
I've been told you're
the Iron Mask Fencer.
I only know you
from picture books.
A lone warrior, battling
evil to save the people.
A hero of justice.
So why are you trying to
bring back Zeth Satan?
Don't interrupt me!
Fencer Beam!
[JIRO]
She can fire beams?
Kikko! A weapon!
[KIKKO]
If you want my help,
you have to promise
me something!
[JIRO] I'm not going
back to the Bureau!
In that case...
It's obvious you don't
understand women.
You can't handle this!
[JIRO] What is this smell?
It's like strawberries.
What do you want
here, sorceress?
To help. You're alone and
looking for a familiar face.
But you woke up in a world
that no longer remembers you,
so you're seeking out
the one who does.
Your archenemy who was
frozen along with you!
Perhaps.
After all, I fought
countless bloody battles
against the Zeth Satan Clan.
And I was determined to kill
every last one of them!
Every last one? Isn't
that just a bit extreme?
Back then, it was
considered normal.
Neither side stopped fighting
until the other was
totally eliminated.
Maybe that's how things
worked back then,
but these are modern times,
you have other choices!
After all, you're pretty cute.
[ULLR] Do you want her to
work in a department store
or something?
War is the only thing I know.
But you're just like
that dumb bandit.
You don't understand
women either!
[KIKKO]
Wha--? Excuse me?
Arise! Iron Mask!
Whoa! The Iron Mask
Fencer is real?
Great detecting.
Kiko, get clear!
I can't run! Zeth Satan
is almost finished.
[KOMA]
Fencer Rocket!
[KIKKO]
Meteorta--!
You saved me.
Change of plans: I need
you to take the stick!
Oh, now I'm allowed? I thought
I didn't know how to fly it!
You've piloted Arcus
before, right?
It's pretty much the same thing!
[KOMA]
Spirit. Awaken.
Come on, need to find something
tall. Something tall.
Meteortail!
[KIKKO screams]
A ninja trick!
[HYOUMA]
Koma Kage! Stop the ritual!
It'll revive Zeth Satan, but it
won't bring back your friend.
The one who sacrificed his
life to make the seal,
Dragongod Asahi!
[KOMA]
Fencer Beam!
Well, what are you
waiting for? Finish it!
Answer me first.
Why did you betray Zeth
Satan and go on the run?
So that I could bring
closure to our struggle.
And you've bested me.
Then it's over. There's
no reason to fight.
There is a reason. People
will know you spared me.
If you let me go, you'll
be seen as a villain.
How many innocents have I hurt?
I cannot be forgiven.
No! You've changed!
If you let me live, you
cannot stand for justice.
I will defeat Zeth Satan!
Then I shall take his power,
and with it, I will kill you.
[KOMA]
Asahi!
[ZETH SATAN]
Zeth.
Koma! Do it!
[yells]
[KOMA]
Asahi.
That's right.
I'll bring Dragongod Asahi
back into this world!
Raito! Now!
[RAITO]
Huh?
Meteortail!
[FLOWERS]
No! No! No...
It was a different time.
Neither you nor
Asahi could admit
you had feelings for each other.
I know you.
Jaganosuke!
Are you sure you can
take him dow, Koma?
[KOMA]
I destroy evil. And bring peace.
That is my purpose,
it's all I know.
[HYOUMA] Even if Asahi
lives in your heart?
They were close friends. Wow.
Just listen!
[KOMA]
I thought if I kept fighting
and didn't stop until I killed
every last one them,
it would lead to an era
of peace and happiness.
But... the fighting never ended.
All I accomplished was losing
the one person I cared about.
I understand what
you're feeling,
but this won't bring Asahi back.
That seal is all that's
left of him now.
[KOMA] Then I'll break
apart every last piece!
For Dragongod Asahi.
So no one makes my mistake,
I'll make sure evil
never gets revived!
Why did you--?
It's in rough shape,
but I think the seal can
hold its power for a while.
We'll put it back more
securely this time.
I know a couple of specialists.
Get out of the way and
let me destroy it!
[JIRO] Asahi rests here!
Isn't that what you said?
A superhuman of evil that has
since woke up to justice.
I think that's cool.
This guy's determined to
protect all superhumans,
living or dead.
That's not what I heard.
I was told he's the leader
of the forces of evil.
Who said that?
[TACHIBANA]
Huh.
After today, these rumors
will vanish forever!
No! No! My lady!
You're mistaken!
But Hitoyoshi is leading
a band of evil superhumans.
But only because you've
labeled all superhumans evil
so you can torture them.
Prime Minister Tachibana!
It's you I'm after!
Defend yourself!
Please, my lady, I beg you!
Look at my family tree!
Stop this nonsense!
[KOMA]
Shinnoshin!
[TACHIBANA]
Lord Shinnoshin Kage.
Your brother. My ancestor!
We share the same blood!
So your plan was revive
the Iron Mask Fencer,
make her do some "hero" stuff,
then reveal you're related.
A publicity stunt that would
blow away those pesky scandals.
I'm almost impressed.
[TACHIBANA] I can prove it.
I have superhuman powers.
They're limited,
but I have the ability to
control the minds of animals.
I'll show you!
Is that how you
influence politicians?
Yes. It's not that hard.
Their brains are on
a par with reptiles.
I refuse to believe
we're related.
My family wouldn't torment
superhumans for greed.
[TACHIBANA]
Superhumans are tools for war.
Their abilities have to
be managed carefully.
War? Is that all you seek?
Not me, I'm trying
to put a stop to them!
I destroyed all my enemies,
but the world is still fighting.
These new models
are quite small,
but the quality is remarkable.
Satomi?
We can integrate my
pocketwatch into Earth- chan
and give her time
travel capabilities.
She'll be able to carry you back
to your original timeline.
I'd do it, but I can
only transport myself.
Earth- chan 's already
agreed to help you.
Since you know right from wrong.
It must be difficult, figuring
out good from evil in this era.
The Prime Minister
might be corrupt,
but killing him won't
change anything.
You'll get lost, like Fuurouta.
[KIKKO]
Huh?
Koma. You belong in a time
where there's clear sides.
I don't think so.
Why not?
Iron Mask Fencer,
defender of justice,
cutting down evil in swaths.
You should be in a--
A different era?
What's so great about mine?
I killed every single
agent of evil,
but the present doesn't seem
any better than the past.
[KIKKO]
Then where will you go?
I remember now.
Before I was frozen,
I wanted to explore the world.
I don't need a destination.
I was on a journey.
And that journey's not over!
[REPORTER A] A secret audio
recording has surfaced
of Prime Minister Tachibana
confessing that he is
in fact a superhuman
able to control the
minds of the weak.
A shock to not only politicians,
but the entire nation.
Late last night,
copies of the tape
were delivered to all
major news outlets
by a man calling
himself Renderer Brace.
The tape contains a conversation
between Prime Minister Tachibana
and an unknown person.
In it, the Prime Minister
refers to himself
as the descendant
of a superhuman.
It's often said that
the Prime Minister's
long-lasting time in office,
beginning right after the war,
was brought about by his
extraordinary ability
to understand the
minds of others.
If, however, this ability
is a superhuman power,
the implications are disturbing.
[CAROLCO] Comrades! We are the
Jungle Operation Enforcers.
J.O.E. for short.
Welcome our newest
member, G.I Jonathan!
Transform and set
your cyborg arm!
Even the enemy's machines
are no match for him!