Now go!
And show those government
fools what a mistake it was
to create a Reserve
Police Force!
Nothing will protect
them from you, Jiro!
[screams]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[MONSTER A roars]
That's what I saw. It attacked
my home when I was little.
Huh? But, Mom, you always
said you couldn't see anything.
I didn't, but I know
it had to be a kaiju .
[MAN A]
Down in front!
[EMI hisses]
[MAN A yelps]
[MOVIE MAGOTAKE]
My secret weapon!
I'll use his blood
to revive GaGon,
the giganta-pithecus giganteus!
Its cells rejuvenated, I'll
unleash the beast on Tokyo!
Like a 2,000-year-old
lotus blooming,
GaGon shall return
from the dead!
Oh, such a delicious flavor.
A delicacy even to
a monster like me.
[MOVIE MAGOTAKE]
With this,
we'll create an army of
unstoppable kaiju ,
and bring Japan to its knees!
Movie's terrible. Why
don't we get out of here?
It's not that bad.
Some of it's true.
He did use my blood.
Jiro. How did...? There's
no way you remember.
I'm not sure it is a memory.
It's like... More like a dream.
It would appear
Jiro is dreaming.
[SATOMI] Master Ultima
has expressed an interest
in the case.
[MAGOTAKE] You mean he wants
us to hand over Jiro.
Technically, he is
an American weapon,
and by extension,
their property.
[MAGOTAKE] I'm afraid I don't
share your theory, Satomi.
It makes more sense the bomb
failed when it dropped,
and a baby happened to be
left in a nearby crater.
End of story.
I was there, Magotake.
I saw everything.
[MAGOTAKE]
Saw what?
If the atomic bomb
had been a success,
it wouldn't be used
merely as a weapon.
The human race
would've found a way
to harness its energy and create
an advanced civilization.
That boy is our second chance.
This is the Type Ga beast
we tested during the war!
All the reports indicated
it was destroyed!
I revitalized heart cells we
recovered from the carcass,
using the boy's blood.
Master Ultima can't have Jiro.
He'll have to accept this.
[roars]
Who are those guys with?
I'm guessing some
international cabal.
[grunts]
[MAGOTAKE]
Jiro!
Destroy! Destroy it all!
Show no mercy!
Giganto Gon! More fire!
More destruction!
I know Father created
kaiju using my blood.
Ikuta never closed,
the lab just moved
beneath the film studio.
And where did you
learn all of this?
From Claude.
But how? Claude is dead.
[CLAUDE]
I knew we'd meet again, Jiro.
[FUUROUTA, EARTH-CHAN gasp]
[JIRO]
Jin is dead!
[CLAUDE]
My name is Claude.
Impossible. You're just
a mask Jin wore.
Wait, what if your
alter ego took over
and actually became
a real person?
[CLAUDE] The man you knew as
Jin Nagakawa fused with metal.
Imagine.
At that moment the
Claude personality
became electronic information,
burnt onto the semiconductor
processors in the helmet.
And Imperial Ads mass-produces
them with no idea.
Your psyche, they're
creating copies of it.
[CLAUDE] But can you honestly
even call me Claude?
Jin never wanted to admit
that he was created as
a replacement for Jiro.
Yet he couldn't deny
that he admired you.
You know the superhuman
behind this illusion.
[gasps]
[JIRO] And now, I'll show
you everything I know.
[CLAUDE]
I did it? I killed him?
No. I don't believe it.
Not me! It's not me!
Don't show me this!
[MICHIKO] Look how sweaty
he is. Now it's gonna stink.
Was it Claude? What'd he say?
It's too dangerous.
That helmet, Claude's
put a curse on it.
You're kidding me. I know I'm
a ghost and all, but cursed?
C'mon.
It's imprinted with his beliefs.
Convinces you superhumans have
the power to change the world.
It's addicting.
I used to hate superhumans.
Shinka Year 34. That's when
the kaiju attacked Tokyo.
My relative's house collapsed
and killed my parents.
Your hero, Rainbow Knight, took
the beast down, saved the day.
But that's it.
There was nothing else
he could've done.
No. I totally get it.
Superhumans aren't
perfect either.
I just thought,
with all that power,
they'd be more
impressive than me.
Taller than a building!
Space travel!
Transforming into any shape!
Whatever you can imagine.
Shouldn't folks like that
been able to stop war?
Feed all the starving children?
Find homes for strays?
[FUUROUTA]
You're being unreasonable.
Unreasonable? Then at least
show me what justice looks like.
I'm talkin' real,
absolute justice.
Not just some phrase like,
"every person has
their own definition."
Heard it all before.
I'm drunk.
I'm not a superhuman, and I
don't ever wanna become one.
I'm just ordinary.
But if I had power...
actual power...
[EARTH- CHAN ]
It's too dangerous.
Um. Right.
The exhibition is near Tokyo
station. We'll provide security.
The castle is right
down the street,
so you know what that means.
Yeah, in the event
things get outta hand,
there will be
innocent causalities.
If so, the public will never
view superhumans as heroes.
So is Jiro going to be arrested?
I would never let that happen.
[rattling]
Um, are you showing
off the new helmet?
[MICHIKO] Blocking the
flashes. I am so hung over.
[FUUROUTA] There they go.
Planning to attack NUTS.
The fuel's too big
a threat to use.
And you've seen what
the helmets do.
Then don't just watch them.
Do your own fighting.
You've been acting weird since
yesterday. What's going on?
[JIRO] Maybe I don't deserve to
fight for what I believe in.
[JIRO]
Daitetsu?
Everyone, please
stand back. Beware!
These two are
superhuman supremacists!
All pilots, to NUTS!
[SATOMI]
Don't fight back.
The media will hear that
the Tries corporation
made a design error.
Whatever you do,
don't damage the fuel pipe.
[CLAUDE]
Jacky! Let's sing.
My friends. I welcome
you all back.
[CLAUDE]
Nana. IQ go!
If evil escapes the law,
we'll eliminate it ourselves.
To save the world!
Huh? What's happening?
[YUMIHIKO] Watch out, Rainbow
Knight! I'll protect you!
[FUUROUTA]
Claude?
Yumihiko, listen!
The helmet's evil!
We have to get it off!
You control metals!
Give me a hand!
You saved me.
There's that adorable
boyish voice I love.
What's with the
modifications to the Ahra?
Miss Emi. The NUTS
are on the move!
[gasps]
[CLAUDE]
This is your power.
I have power?
[CLAUDE]
You can control the world.
Become a god. Fight for justice.
[MICHIKO]
You'll pay for your crimes!
Michiko!
[EARTH- CHAN ]
Falling glass! Heads up!
I'll protect everyone!
I have got to stop them!
But I thought you
were on their side!
That's why I have to stop 'em!
Jiro! Their blood
is on your hands!
It wasn't me! It was Claude!
He's delusional.
[MICHIKO]
This is my power!
[JIRO]
Don't listen to him!
You're stronger
than this, Michiko!
[MICHIKO] Superhumans
were supposed to be
stronger than this.
But I've been
disappointed every time.
You let me down.
[JIRO]
Since when could it fly?
I can't fight back or
the fuel will leak.
Did you discover any
universal truths
travelling around
the world, Reiichi.
Kikko! Let's give
him some backup!
On it!
Meteortail!
[CLAUDE]
Jiro Hitoyoshi!
If you're a superhuman,
then change the world!
You know the superhuman
behind this illusion...
...is you.
She hit him!
Jiro! Damn you!
[RAITO]
What the hell are you doing?
[FUUROUTA]
Seriously!
Even if it is the girl
from the ad agency,
you have to defeat her!
[JIRO]
Is that the right thing to do?
Ask yourself that, Fuurouta.
You might think it's just,
then regret it later.
You of all people
should understand that.
I won't have any regrets
kicking her ass!
Claude's gotta be
controlling her, right?
He's inside the helmet.
[JIRO]
Not Claude. Not Jin either.
It's me.
What's you?
[JIRO] The "Claude" persona
inside the helmet
is looking for a hero.
Someone who fights for
justice, peace, and freedom.
For the powerless.
I believed there had to be
someone out there like that.
But I never found one.
So I'm calling out for help.
Like a stupid child.
That's the reason
you won't fight?
That urge driving Michiko,
the need to be a
superhuman of justice,
it's driving me, too.
All this power... and no
idea what to do with it.
Not sure if justice even exists.
I remember everything now!
I want to protect
all superhumans!
If I can't do that, I'm useless!
I couldn't even... I couldn't...
Jiro. You can't give up.
You swore an oath.
You said you'd fight anyone
who threatened kids.
Doesn't really matter
to me what you are.
Come on!
For every child you made cry.
[FUUROUTA] Well, there's a
crying kid right over there!
[JIRO]
But that's...
What does it matter? It could
be you, could be anyone!
It's still a crying child
who needs your help!
Hey, Jiro.
Did you forget what you said
when Fuurouta first joined?
I'll help you out.
See, you need him
around to remind you
of the things that matter
to you the most.
Your words, not mine.
Jaguar.
[HYOUMA] I just never thought
it'd actually happen.
Now get up.
Your job as an adult is to help
get a child back on his feet.
Think you can do that?
Or are you still
a child yourself?
How is he supposed to fight?
You know how to pilot
the Ahra, right?
[HYOUMA] Use the code
phrase I taught you.
Oh, the one you just
made up on the spot?
Ready! Fuurouta!
[RAITO]
Ah! Fine! Ignore me!
Bombs away!
[JIRO, RAITO]
Ahra Union!
Equus?
Right! Fire!
[KIKKO screaming]
Kikko!
If I give this back,
I could save her.
Equus? He's flying?
No more crying.
I know...
We want a rampage.
We feel powerless.
We wanted to be a superhuman
of justice so badly.
But we can't 'cause
adults aren't like that.
We don't always get
to do the right thing.
But still, I can't give up!
[SATOMI]
Eight confirmed dead.
More than 300 injured.
The worst terrorist attack
in Japan's history.
Now superhumans and beasts
are both considered dangers.
Until the repairs are
completed, then we'll have...
Humans weren't meant
to be gods. Shame.
[MOVIE MAGOTAKE]
That troublesome Rainbow Knight
has meddled with our
plans for the last time.
He must be killed.
The more power he has,
the less control we have over
superhumans and kaiju .
Dig it, man.
We'll frame him for kidnapping
and ruin his name!
Ugh. Enough of this
propaganda trash.
I need to watch
and see what I did.
You and Emi knew. You must have.
You protected me long enough.
It's true. You do remember.
So that was the reason.
Why you hesitated when
you fought the NUTS.
[MOVIE MAGOTAKE]
We were responsible for him
at our laboratory.
It's my fault.
[JIRO]
Daitetsu. Jin.
Rainbow Knight kidnapped
them. I saw it happen.
Shut up!
It's fact! He's not the
hero you thought he was.
[JIRO] I refuse to believe
he's a kidnapper!
[EMI sighs]
I'll help you, but you
owe me a favor.
What is it?
You have to love me
till the day you die.
Rainbow Knight. Time to
reveal your true identity.
Don't look!
Claude showed me this.
But I wanna confirm
what I saw was the truth.
I need to know how it ends.
[JIN]
Jiro!
You did it! They're right.
Jiro, no! He saved us!
All lies! It's all lies!
[RAINBOW KNIGHT]
No!
[JIRO]
Stop lying to me!
[WOMAN A yelps]
[JIRO]
You fought for justice.
How could you do this?
[RAINBOW KNIGHT]
I am not justice.
Perhaps there's no such thing.
[JIRO]
No!
What have I done?
I'm sorry.
[RAINBOW KNIGHT]
I... I understand.
[JIRO]
It was me?
I killed him?
No. I couldn't.
[EMI]
Jiro!
[gasps]
Not me! It's a lie!
Don't show me this!
[SATOMI] The truth is
Rainbow Knight was killed.
Not by a police conspiracy.
Not by a fire he started.
This superhuman of justice
was murdered by a beast
that is still running free.
Jiro Hitoyoshi.
And now, he's trying
to destroy Japan.
I knew the truth. All along.
[EMI]
Long before humans existed,
monsters, spirits, and demons
called this planet home.
In modern times,
we've lived in fear.
Hiding from you until now.
My name is Emi Kino.
A woman born from a
human and a monster.