[REPORTER A]
Early this morning,
a train accident and
fire broke out
in the Hokuriku Tunnel.
Over 700 were injured
and 30 are confirmed dead.
After receiving reports from
the on-site investigators,
the government has concluded
it's extremely likely
superhumans were involved
in this accident...
Ugh!
I'm sick of 'em
blaming superhumans
for every little thing!
[KIKKO]
They already know the fire
came from the smoking room.
[FUUROUTA] How does switching
the blame to superhumans
help change anything?
Don't get all worked up.
Won't make those poor
folks any less dead.
It helps control
the public's opinion.
Makes people demand
their government
take greater control
over superhumans.
You're right. The
media's helping us.
Thanks.
I'm reporting to you from the
Tsuruga side of the tunnel.
Are we working to make life
more difficult for superhumans?
Professor?
You don't have to be such
a square all the time.
Ugh! C'mon, Miss Emi!
We gotta speak up
against these old men!
Uh. Wait. Where'd she go?
She stepped out. I imagine
she's quite worried.
About what?
The princess has
several underlings.
A couple of whom
reside underground.
They're obviously going
to be the prime suspects.
[REPORTER A]
In other news,
after successfully
placing men on the moon
for the longest duration yet,
Apollo 17 is now on
its way back to Earth.
Open up.
[UP-DOWN]
Oh, exalted ogre princess,
thank you visiting me.
Your beauty is as
magnificent as ever.
I, Up-Down, your humble
elevator attendant,
tremble with joy to have
you ride alongside me.
I want to see Miss Devila.
[UP-DOWN]
Eh?
[EMI] Do you know
where she is right now?
[UP-DOWN]
No.
But just give me the
order, my princess.
And I'll travel to the bottom of
the Earth to find her for you.
[EMI]
Hm.
The way I hear it,
you say terrible things about
me when I'm not around.
[UP-DOWN]
What? I'd never!
[FUUROUTA yells]
[UP-DOWN yelps]
[UP-DOWN] You freeloader!
Stop stealing rides!
Stealing? I'm incorporeal!
I can go wherever I want to!
[UP-DOWN] Ha! Ghosts
are such lowly beings.
Born from over-imaginative
human minds.
[FUUROUTA growls]
Enough of this!
Take me to see Devila!
Wait a minute. Who's Devila?
[UP-DOWN]
You aren't worthy of knowing
the answer to that,
lowly ghost boy!
[EMI]
And what about me?
[UP-DOWN] Oh, of course
you are, my ogre princess.
After all, you're--
"Barely her equal"? Your words.
[UP-DOWN yelps]
Just take me to her!
Now! We're in a hurry!
Cool.
[UP-DOWN]
The last time I saw her,
she was swimming
through a magma pool.
Not that I was watching
her or anything! How crass!
I don't know where Her Grace--
I mean, that idiot
disappeared to afterwards.
And that's what
I'm worried about.
She can appear
anywhere she chooses.
If she starts trouble,
it won't end well.
Was the tunnel accident
this Devila person's fault?
It's hard to imagine
her acting so reckless.
But she and I are different.
Unlike me, she has no intention
of being friendly with humans.
[KIKKO]
The Great Depth Construction?
[MAGOTAKE] It's exactly
what it sounds like.
The underground's
almost untouched.
The plan is to develop
it like the surface.
Expanding human
infrastructure downward
the same way we've built it up.
You're talking about more than
just subways and sewer systems.
The metro system is only
scratching the surface,
so to speak.
The idea is to go much deeper
using a process called
"shield tunneling."
Sounds dangerous.
And what'll happen to Miss Emi's
kind who live down there?
Actually, there's an old clan
that even Emi doesn't
have jurisdiction over.
They go by many names,
but are commonly referred
to as demons.
Are they superhuman?
Technically speaking, yes.
There are no legal distinctions
separating monsters from demons.
[HYOUMA]
Meaning they fall under
the Superhuman
Bureau's protection.
Superhuman laws
have weight up here,
but would demons
even listen to us?
In truth, I highly doubt it.
Devila's relationship with
humans is tenuous at best.
[FUUROUTA]
Besides being fireproof,
what are Devila's powers?
Ah! Ouch!
[UP-DOWN] How dare you
call her by her name!
You'll refer to her
as "Her Grace"!
Oh, princess, you can call her
whatever you want, of course.
[sighs]
How far down are we going again?
[UP-DOWN]
Here we are.
We've reached the First Mantle
level, your eminence.
About time. I'm ready
for this to stop.
We're going sideways?
What kind of elevator is this?
[FUUROUTA]
Oh! Oo! Ah! Eeee!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Are you coming down?
Is this a monster?
[KOMORIN]
My name: Komorin.
My power: Waterproof
and pressure proof.
Full speed ahead!
[KOMORIN]
My task: Searching for Devila.
Searching.
Uh, Komorin. Devila has a
younger sibling, doesn't she?
[KOMORIN]
A younger brother. Devilo.
If we find him first,
he might able to help us.
Is Devilo like his sister?
Yes, but he hasn't reached
his mature form yet.
So he's ridiculously cute.
And much easier to talk to.
There is Tokyo and
there is Shinjuku.
There is Shinjuku
and also the East Exit.
Is he an actor? A model?
Is he talking to us?
What an amazing voice!
There is a park.
If there is a park,
then people will gather.
Atttention.
You're not permitted to loiter
here. Disperse immediately.
This isn't a park!
It's a passage!
A passage is meant
for traveling.
A passage allows all kinds of
people to meet one another.
Different people. Me. You.
He's right!
There is the sky
and the earth.
There is up and there is down!
There is right
and there is left.
If there was no right,
the earth would splinter.
If there was no left,
the sky would shatter.
We have both right and left.
[FUUROUTA]
His power is speaking?
Can he cast spells or something?
Not really. He just says
ordinary, everyday things.
But they say it has the
power to move people.
Some days, the sun will shine.
Some days, the rain will fall.
On other days,
the wind will caress.
Some days, a storm will rage.
"On some days,
the wind will caress."
"Some days, storms rage."
It's "some days, a
storm will rage."
Oh! My mistake.
[GIRLS giggle]
This is the building with the
deepest underground structure.
The Shield Tower.
Yeah, built with the
Great Depth method
the professor told us about.
This must be where
Miss Emi went.
I don't see why.
It's under construction.
Hm?
What's going on?
[DEVILO]
Some people are strong.
Some people are weak.
Some people are serious.
And some people are cheerful.
There're so many different
people in the city.
Like birds. All different
types in the sky.
Or flowers. Different types
growing on the earth.
You are here. I am here.
We are all here.
No two people are the same.
That's why the city
is so much fun!
[KIKKO]
What's happening?
No one mentioned anything
about a demonstration.
[DEVILO]
You and I are different!
Different people
gather together.
Gather to make a city. Our home!
[CROWD] Different people
gather together.
Gather to make a city. Our home!
An unregistered protest!
They're blocking traffic!
I have to call for backup!
A superhuman's doin' this.
[KIKKO gasps]
How can we find
them in this crowd?
Right there. He must be
the one responsible!
Different people gather
together. To make a city...
What is this? It sounds more
like a cult than a protest.
Right?
[DEVILO]
...make a country.
Different countries
come together...
Did you see that?
The eye blinked!
Yeah. I saw it.
What's going on?
[gasps]
A monster? Is Emi nearby?
[SHAKKOU] Superhumans that
dwell beneath the earth.
The ones that caused
the tunnel accident.
The tunnel accident?
You think that boy did it?
So they finally
reveal themselves.
The Public Security Force
will take it from here!
[POLICE OFFICER A] So many.
Where were they all hiding?
[KOMORIN] My status:
Continuing search. Searching.
Uh! Is there any other
way we can find her?
[KOMORIN] My recommendation:
Find Devilo.
Ninety percent chance
of finding Devila.
Okay, so where is he?
[KOMORIN]
My status: Search complete.
Devilo at Shinjuku West Exit.
[EMI gasps]
The Shinjuku West Exit?
What's he thinking?
Security Forces will spot
him! Is he there alone?
[UP-DOWN]
No, no. Lady Devila-- Uh!
I mean, that repulsive witch
ordered Zumanan
to accompany him.
It's getting hard
remembering all these names.
[UP-DOWN]
Zumanan. Don't forget it.
He's a super-highly-concentrated
super-super-high-density
underground organism.
A simple ghost like you
wouldn't understand.
Of course I do! Super-duper-
highly-underground-dense--
Uh! I bit my tongue!
Zumanan. If shakes his
whiskers, it'll be chaos.
[DEVILO]
Together, we make the city.
The city does not
make the people.
The people make the nation.
The nation does not
make the people.
[CROWD]
The people make the nation.
The nation does not
make the people.
[SHAKKOU]
Stop chanting! All of you!
Snap out of it!
Look down at your feet!
[CROWD gasps]
[SHAKKOU] It's a creature that
prowls beneath the ground.
That's what caused
the tunnel disaster!
[CROWD screams]
[SHAKKOU]
Over there! Go!
[SECURITY FORCES]
Yes, sir!
Huh. They left. Now
I'm talking to myself.
Jiro? You're here?
Leave him and his friend alone.
They haven't done anything.
His friend happens to be a
monster no one can control!
Now stop getting in our way!
When did the Bureau become
enemies with superhumans?
Superhuman? You mean me?
Technically, yes.
What's your name?
Devilo. What's yours, old man?
Old man?
Where I come from, it's polite
to introduce yourself.
Is it different for humans?
Hyouma Yoshimura,
Superhuman Bureau.
And I'm not old.
If you say so.
Now please, follow me.
What for?
We're placing you under
the Bureau's protection.
Devilo, you don't have to go.
They only wanna exploit you.
That's not true!
You just want him for leverage
against the Public
Security Force!
You're wrong!
[MAGOTAKE]
His voice clearly has
a wide-range hypnosis
effect on humans.
Like an underworld Pied-Piper.
Imagine if he fell
into the wrong hands.
A power that strips
people of free thought
and turns them into lemmings.
We can't allow him
to stay in public.
Kikko. You saw what
he's capable of.
People followed him,
but it's not like he was talking
about anything dangerous.
[DEVILO]
Isn't your name Star Child?
I like you. You're cute.
[ULLR] Watch out,
he's a real smooth talker.
[DEVILO]
Hey! You're cute, too!
[ULLR yelps]
Come with us.
We can't let you wander
around with that power.
Don't listen. Go back home!
Stay away from humans
and you'll be safe.
I think I'll follow
you, Star Child,
since you're the cutest
person I've met.
Um. Thanks.
[HYOUMA]
We don't have time for this!
I don't think you
should worry about me.
See?
[BOTH gasp]
[HYOUMA]
Dammit.
Careful. You don't
wanna make him angry.
Come on, Zumanan!
[SHAKKOU]
Attack!
Direct hit!
[SECURITY FORCES yell]
He's not the aggressor here!
[HYOUMA]
The Bureau will save him!
Is that you, old man?
Impressive! I just ask that
you don't let go of me.
That son of a--
[ULLR] He's quick for
not being in a hurry.
Meteortail!
Get ahead of him!
Keep it from the Juniso shrine!
[DEVILO]
You should stop this, old man.
If you keep bothering him,
he'll show his real power,
and there's nothing
I can do to help you.
[SHAKKOU]
This is your monster?
Yes. He's my friend.
My sister gave him orders
to protect me from harm.
[SHAKKOU]
Sister?
Devila, Queen of
the Underground?
So it's true. She really
is invading the surface.
Devilo! It's vital we
meet with your sister.
We'll get Emi to
serve as mediator.
The conflict between humans
and your kind must stop!
I've had just about
enough of you.
There'll be no peace.
Our orders are clear!
The monsters below caused
the tunnel accident.
And they have to pay for it.
In exchange, Japan
demands that they forfeit
the underground as a new colony.
We can't allow dangerous
superhumans
to live underneath our feet.
Look. Underneath all your feet.
Zumanan lives.
Ready yourselves!
Aim for the whiskers!
[SECURITY FORCES]
Yes, sir!
Meteortail!
[SHAKKOU]
Damn you!
[JIRO]
Give up!
Meteor-- Ah!
Continue the attack!
[SECURITY FORCES]
Yes, sir!
Zumanan hasn't done anything!
You're obstructing justice.
What the--?
I thought only ghosts
were able to do that.
Because it is a ghost.
That's Fuurouta!
Do it!
[SECURITY FORCES]
Yes, sir!
[FUUROUTA] I've had
enough fire for one day!
[yells]
Damn you, Superhuman Bureau!
You'll pay for your treachery!
Where did he go?
[SOLDIER A]
Captain!
Our forces are engaged in
combat near the park bridge!
[SHAKKOU]
Got it! Let's move!
We have to stop them!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
Those who dwell below are
not enemies to humans.
[SHAKKOU]
Silence!
They caused the train wreck
and attacked the city.
Enough lies!
I'm returning them
to their home.
[DEVILO] Why do we have
to go back under ground?
We are everywhere.
Below the earth. On its surface.
Everywhere!
Eliminate them! All of th--!
Stand down! You're outta line!
Hey, look's who's talking.
Are you sure you
wanna get in trouble
with the guys from
Public Security?
Good show, old man!
[SHAKKOU] You're going back
underground. Six feet under!
Meteortail!
Oh, right!
[thud]
Oh, man. Now what's wrong?
The Shield Building! It's
sinking into the ground!
Earthquake, maybe? Then why
can't we feel it over here?
Zumanan did his best
to control himself.
But he must have done
something under the building.
So then...
Huh. It'll think twice
before it messes with
the Public Security Forces.
It ran in fear of us!
We are victorious!
[SECURITY FORCES cheering]
What are you talking about?
If he stopped going easy on you,
it would've been total chaos!
You got off easy.
That so?
Well, if that creature is
as dangerous as you say,
it's even more reason for us
conquer the underground.
[EMI sighs]
Yeah. Good luck with that.
[SHAKKOU]
And we'll start with that boy!
You're under arrest!
Over my dead body!
And what'll you do if
his sister shows up?
[SHAKKOU] Well, that's simple.
We'll arrest her, too!
No, you won't!
The Superhuman Bureau
has jurisdiction here.
Not anymore. You're nothing
but a fringe group.
Arrest them!
[SECURITY FORCES]
Yes, sir!
[SHAKKOU]
What? Can't see!
Hey there, Devila!
[SHAKKOU]
Get back, you freak!
[laughing]
[FUUROUTA]
Look over there!
[DEVILA laughing]
[SOLDIER A]
Sir, water is being sucked up
in multiple cities
around the world!
[ALL yelp]
[REPORTER A]
The details are still sparse
but what we do know
is that Apollo 17
is clearly experiencing
some sort of trouble!
Once again, Apollo 17
is experiencing--
[DEVILA laughs]
Sister!
[FUUROUTA]
Huh? A tail?
A tail? Oh, look.
It will grow and then
my legs will go away.
Then I will be just
like my sister.
[DEVILO chuckles]
Goodbye, Devilo.
They're leaving. So that's why
he came up to the surface.
He wanted to visit the
city before he changed,
while he still looked human.
[FUUROUTA]
Sort of like a graduation trip.
I wonder what happens
next for them.
[DEVILO] If you don't
want us underground,
we'll live in space.
We'll create an ocean in space.
We'll go anywhere.
There are no rules.
It's true for everyone.
[DEVILO]
You and I are different.
But one day, we
can live together.
We'll wait for you. In space.
[DEVILO] The city is there.
The people are there.
He is there. She is there.
And then, the
flowers will bloom.
Humans cannot become birds.
Humans cannot become flowers.
They'll always remain human.
But they love the
flowers, the birds,
and most important,
they love each other.
And love is what the
planet is all about!
Wow! How cute!
[WAKAMURA]
Ichiu Wakamura.
Born in Year 20 of
the Shinkah Era.
I work for the
Imperial Ad Agency.
I live with my
three-year-old daughter, Yuko.
Commute time from my house,
50 minutes, one-way.
But when I'm not at work
or at home, I'm Human-Man!