[REPORTER A]
Three months have passed
since the grand opening of
the Okinawa Superhuman Expo
and the festivities
continue to this day.
Superhumans have gathered
from all around the globe
to attend this event,
the first of its kind.
Many conflicts have
arisen around their kind
in recent decades.
But now, thanks to
Master Ultima's efforts,
superhumans have promised
to work together
for the benefit of humanity.
So you gonna tell
me who you are?
Or why you came to this country?
[ULTIMA]
Of course.
I am Master Ultima, and I've
come for the creatures.
[KOMA laughs]
[KOMA] Sorry but if you were
trying to not be offensive,
you failed. So why not
call us what we are?
[ULTIMA sighs]
Fine, in your terminology,
i'm here to eliminate
the kaiju , yokai ,
and devils once and for all.
That's crazy.
[EMI]
And the truth finally comes out.
Well, if it isn't
the Yokai Princess.
Reports say superhumans
are disappearing
once they arrive for the expo.
But when you look closer,
only the types you just
listed have gone missing.
This is your doing.
Haven't we met before?
You know Jiro somehow, right?
[EMI] I'm actually supposed
to be his fiancée.
I'm sorry they threw you in
the "freak" category, too.
[gasps] What is wrong
with you, my friends?
[EMI]
You don't get to call them that.
Especially now that your
power to subdue kaiju
has been nullified.
They don't seem too happy
now that I've filled them in
on what you've been doing here.
I guess you can say that
I opened their eyes.
[ULTIMA]
So I see.
Initiate: Freeze Mode!
[FIRE MONSTER] Princess.
He is quite formidable.
Yes.
[ULTIMA] Have you not realized
no superhuman can defeat me?
[EMI] You truly think
I find your silly
Bio Destroyer intimidating?
[EMI]
It's us against them now.
It's time we showed the world
we're the real superhumans.
[FUTAGAMI] The Superhuman
Bureau this Emi Kino used to
work for has been dormant since
the Great Prophecy of Japan
film was released
in theaters last year.
In light of these recent events,
it has officially
been shut down.
With that, our first
order of business
is arresting its former members.
[REPORTER A] Following its
transfer from the cabinet
to the office of the
Ministry of Defense,
the Public Safety
Force has united
with the police department's
Superhuman Violence
Regulation Headquarters.
Together, they have
been reestablished
as the Super Soldier
Warrior Squad.
Today marks the start
of their first mission:
A mass search of radical
superhuman hideouts.
They're looking for
a terrorist group,
with ties to the recent
murder of Master Ultima,
calling themselves "Monsters."
Many potential suspects,
including kaiju and devils,
have since occupied
Ultimapolis, eluding arrest.
Along with the
proactive approach
of the Super Soldier
Warrior Squad,
the government is attempting to
negotiate with the Monsters.
All of this in hopes of
preventing incidents
like last year's Maru-nochi
bombings from happening again.
[ALL gasp]
Good choice going with
the tear gas, guys.
But it won't work on me!
[SHAKKOU]
That's why I'm here.
To destroy you
with my own hands!
[SHAKKOU]
Megasshin! Get him!
[MIEKO]
It's all right.
[HANTA]
We have bigger concerns.
[MAGOTAKE]
I'm telling you,
I haven't seen the other former
bureau members in months.
They all left after that movie.
I guess they didn't
want to work for
an "evil organization that
harbored a violent beast."
We can barely go
out in public now.
[HYOUMA] "A violent beast."
So where is Jiro?
I couldn't tell you if I wanted.
I haven't seen him
since New Year's.
[JIRO gasps]
[CHINATSU]
Mr. Jiro! It's really you!
Uh, sorry.
[JIRO]
It's okay. Are you leaving us?
[gasps]
I have to.
[JIRO] I get it. Thank you
for everything you've done.
I'm engaged now. He's nice.
He has a child already,
but I don't mind.
[REPORTER A]
Needless to say,
the film that came out
earlier this month,
Great Prophecy of Japan ,
took us by surprise.
Is it true there was a kaiju
within the Superhuman Bureau?
[REPORTER B]
Afraid so.
Twenty years ago,
there was a mysterious fire
that damaged Shinbashi, Ginza,
as well as the
National Diet Building.
That same beast is said
to have been responsible
for these events.
It was just a movie.
Another of Satomi's products.
It's not "just a movie."
The people who
saw it believe it.
Besides, I know it's true.
[gasps]
I want to know.
Where did I come from?
I told him.
About the hypothesis you
proposed to me so long ago.
Really? I don't imagine
Jiro liked hearing
he could be the connection
between two worlds.
[MAGOTAKE]
In our world, 30 years ago,
during the summer in Hiroshima,
it seemed as if the new
bomb had been a failure.
However, what if instead
of vaporizing the city,
the bomb's destructive energies
took on the form of baby boy?
[HYOUMA] While, in a different
overlapping world,
those same energies successfully
wrought devastation.
There wouldn't be
anything left standing
after a blast like that.
But it would mean
they've harnessed
the power of nuclear fission,
freeing them from the strife
surrounding fossil fuels.
A world like that will
have obtained peace.
Nice theory, but it doesn't
explain why Jiro exists.
Because someone
wished for him to.
Whoever that was,
they wanted to save us.
They didn't want us to
experience the same death,
destruction, and tragedy
that had happened
in the other world.
[MAGOTAKE] When a person
cries out for help,
someone has to swoop in
and save the day.
So that's what I did,
the day I heard you crying.
[JIRO]
Then the Bureau's purpose...
[MAGOTAKE] Wasn't to
protect all superhumans.
It was to protect
one superhuman.
You, Jiro. We were
defending you.
Satomi, the Americans,
they were all after you.
That's why we had to organize:
To keep you safe.
[JIRO]
I don't deserve to be saved.
[MAGOTAKE]
Jiro.
I've killed people,
like Rainbow Knight.
Then there's Shinbashi,
the kaiju made from my blood.
I'm responsible for
those murders, too.
That's why you should let
the Bureau protect you!
[JIRO]
I won't go back!
You don't care about me!
You just care
about your "science"!
So fine, take my blood!
That's all I've ever been
useful for anyway!
How can you say
something like that?
Don't you still want to
be an ally of justice?
Tell me you do.
You have to believe
in your dream.
Because as long as you believe,
this world will continue to be.
[HYOUMA] And that was the
last time you saw him?
It was.
[[FUUROUTA sneezing]
[MAGOTAKE]
Hm?
[NO-NAME] What do we
do with the professor?
There's no point
in arresting him
just because of his research.
He didn't have anything
to do with Okinawa.
[KIKKO]
I hope we're not intruding.
[MAGOTAKE]
No, it's okay.
It's been too long since
we were all together.
Well, almost all of us.
But as I'm sure you
must've heard...
Yeah, you haven't seen
Mr. Jiro in a long time.
[ULLR] I really must inquire
about your theory.
You truly believe that Jiro
is an otherworldly destructive
force given human form?
It seems mildly farfetched.
I dunno, but Satomi sure did.
More than that. He also wanted
to destroy Jiro's body.
He thought by doing so, he could
open a path to the other world.
[ULLR]
That's a bit extreme.
Y'know. I actually
saw Jiro the other day.
[gasps]
What do you mean you
saw him the other day?
Why didn't you say
something to me sooner?
[FUUROUTA]
'Cause this was the first chance
you've let me get
a word in edgewise!
[MICHIKO] Yes, actually,
the wanted man did stop by.
[FUUROUTA]
But why did he come see you?
Oh! You must be his third
pick after Emi and Kikko!
He just asked me some questions
about Ultimapolis, then left.
You mean that place
Miss Emi took over?
Of course!
He came to you because
Imperial Ads ran that expo!
But unfortunately,
I ended my involvement
with anything related to
superhumans last year.
So to keep me out of the way,
they put me in charge of
songs for a children's show.
[AUDIO MIXER] 'Kay, let's jump
back one section
and try to sound sadder.
♪
♪ Day after day. ♪
♪ Tossed on hot plates. ♪
♪ Stuffed with
filling and cooked. ♪
♪ Then one day I decided... ♪
"Really Getting Tired
Of Getting Cooked."
I let Hitoyoshi listen to it
while he was here, too.
[MICHIKO] Have you ever
thought of this possibility?
That the superhumans
aren't real.
Maybe some child
just imagined them.
And one day,
all of them are going
to completely disappear
from this world.
Because the child wakes up
and realizes his dream
could never happen.
She said that when Jiro heard
the song, he just stormed out.
He must've realized something.
From a song about fish?
[RAITO]
I can't believe you two went to
a known affiliate
of Imperial Ads.
The Super Soldier Warrior
Squad has eyes everywhere.
That's how we knew where to find
you to place you under arrest.
So we don't have much time.
That's impressive.
I'm surprised you knew I
was looking for you guys.
[UP-DOWN]
I didn't.
The princess ordered
me to pick you up.
[JIRO]
"The princess"?
I thought you underground types
only did Devila's bidding.
[UP-DOWN] You mean "Her
Highness Devila," you fool!
[JIRO]
I thought Emi was in Okinawa.
[UP-DOWN] Ha-ha. You don't
understand where you are.
Even if you're thousands of
miles apart on the surface,
in our world you're only
a short drive away.
[MIEKO] Miss Emi asked us to
find these for her last month.
In case you're lost,
they're Ultimapolis's
engine schematics.
[[FUUROUTA]
Man, I'm glad you said that.
I thought they were molds to
cook snacks shaped like fish.
[KIKKO]
Wait a sec.
[HANTA] Ultimapolis is the
first ocean-based city.
It can travel above
or below sea-level
to anywhere in the world.
Master Ultima designed
the engine himself.
As of now, no one
knows how it works.
[ULLR]
Hm. According to the newspapers,
it was being hailed as some new,
state-of-the-art system.
It's supposed to launch
a "superhuman-driven
energy revolution,"
making fossil fuels obsolete.
Which would have been explained
at the end of the expo.
Could something related to that
have driven Miss Emi to
assassinate Master Ultima?
Fish shaped, cooking?
[gasps]
[EMI]
It's been a while, Jiro.
[JIRO]
You're normally so levelheaded,
I couldn't figure out why
you did what you did.
But I finally put it together.
The Ultimapolis engine.
It's not hydro, or gas, or even
solar that powers it, is it?
[EMI] Right, it's powered
by superhumans.
[JIRO] This place is filled
with Bio Destroyer.
[EMI]
It has a lot of applications.
Apparently, every
superhuman's genes
resemble Sanae's and
the immortal family's.
Which sounds surprising
until you realize
it's probably because
we all evolved
from their cells to begin with.
When the Bio
Destroyer is diluted,
it can't completely dissolve us.
We melt, regenerate,
and then melt again.
And in the process of
decomposing and recomposing,
we generate a huge
amount of energy.
[JIRO]
Which the system then harnesses.
[EMI]
Master Ultima was campaigning
to establish human rights
for people with powers,
by claiming they would be the
solution to the oil crisis
and bring an end to all wars.
[KOMA]
But those rights only apply
to those of a human origin.
As for Monsters
and other lifeforms,
for them, they're sacrificed
to make energy.
The only rights we'd
receive would be in death.
[JIRO]
Koma. Campe. All of you.
So now? What do you
plan to do next?
[EMI] We're going to become
our own nation--right here.
I'm already negotiating with
the world's governments
to grant us independence.
Tell me, Jiro. Do you
remember what Claude said?
Whether it's for justice,
freedom, or peace.
We superhumans will always
find a reason to fight.
But are those the only things
that drive us to action?
What about friendship?
Our families?
Huh? What about love?
If you ask me, I'd say,
we're at our strongest
when we're fighting
for those sorts of things.
I get what you're saying,
Emi, I really do.
But still, I'm afraid.
You made me a promise, Jiro.
[JIRO] That I would love you
for the rest of my life.
So somehow they're
powering their machines
by making fish snacks
out of superhumans?
That is absolutely ridiculous.
It know it sounds crazy,
but Miss Michiko...
Well, she clearly knew something
she couldn't tell us outright,
so she played that
song as a hint!
But why? That can't be
the way superhumans
are meant to help people.
[MAN A]
That's Earth- chan !
[KIKKO]
Earth- chan !
[EARTH- CHAN ]
Witch Girl. I need your magic.
Will you help me?
[KIKKO]
Of course! What happened?
[EARTH- CHAN ] I'm not sure.
Something's wrong with me.
I'm so confused. All I want
now is to dream in peace.
[HYOUMA]
She's reached her limit.
[KIKKO]
Mr. Jaguar!
Earth- chan gets her power
from receiving distress
calls from people in need.
Which means she requires
their suffering to survive.
But since she couldn't bring
herself to make others suffer,
even in self-defense,
she ran out of juice.
Like you knew she would!
But you pursued her anyway,
leaving her no choice!
[SHAKKOU]
Of course we did!
Given her influence, we couldn't
risk her joining the monsters.
Extract her!
Super Soldiers Three and Four,
what exactly do you
think you're doing?
There's no doubt what
you're doing is wrong!
Our programming
tells us so! Cross...!
[HANTA gasps]
Mieko!
[YUMIHIKO] You must've forgotten
I can manipulate metals.
Yumihiko!
[YUMIHIKO]
Up next.
You're too slow!
[HYOUMA]
These are my ultimate creations.
Based on Megasshin's data.
The Red Jaguars.
And I should warn you,
not even Earth- chan
could escape them!
[BOTH gasp]
[KIKKO]
Raito, no!
Detective?
[RAITO]
Jiro... Jiro...
I can't find you.
It's time to fight... together.
[KAEDE]
S Planetarian inbound!
[EMI]
Run away with us, Jiro.
We can build our
new nation together.
[JIRO] We don't need
to run. Bring us up.
Bring us up!
[BOTH gasp]
You're here. But why?
This place is full of
monsters and kaiju .
You do know that they're
the bad guys now, right?
I know they've chosen
to fight humans
'cause it's the only
way they'll survive.
[BOTH gasp]
But these superhumans
have been protecting
the Human race this whole time!
This doesn't make sense!
Then I'll speak slowly
so you can follow.
Kaiju and humans are enemies!
[JIRO]
Equus!
[SHIROTA grunts] Stop it!
This won't solve anything!
As superhumans,
we have a responsibility
to protect the humans!
[JIRO] See, that's where
you've got it wrong!
I'm not a superhuman at all!
[JUDAS]
Jiro!
[JIRO]
Judas! What are you doing here?
Sadly, the Iron Detective's
been destroyed.
I've come to deliver his
final message to you.
[RAITO]
Jiro. I can't find you.
It's time to fight... together.
For justice!
[JIRO]
Let's go!
Ahra Union!
[SHIROTA gasps]
[EMI] That's it. Now we
have no other choice.
Fighting's all we have left.
Just because someone
has superpowers,
it doesn't mean that
they are superhuman.
There's no way they could
have ever been our saviors.
So instead, they're our enemies.
I hafta put a stop to this!
Oh, no, you don't!
You can't possibly defeat
them in your current state!
[KIKKO gasps] Okay. Then I'll
just use my Devil Realm powers!
You can't! Miss Emi took
those away years ago!
What happened to our agreement
to never tell her that?
She had to do it, otherwise
we couldn't keep you safe!
She even made Jiro promise
to never see you again
so you wouldn't lose control.
You mean, the reason Mr. Jiro
left the Superhuman Bureau...
...was because of me?
[HYOUMA]
It's over, Hoshino.
There's no point in
us fighting anymore.
[KIKKO]
There's not?
We've found them.
The Ultimapolis surfaced
near Okinawa.
Jiro defeated the S Planetarian,
then declared war
against all superhumans.
[KIKKO]
Moments later,
Miss Emi appeared before the
world to release a statement.
The superhuman city built
as the home of the Expo
would now be a safe
haven for y okai , kaiju ,
and other demi-humans.
On that land, they would
be eternally free.
According to our
latest research,
these inhuman
creatures can be used
to create a completely
new form of energy.
[KIKKO]
Soon thereafter,
Satomi revealed the truth
he'd hidden away for so long.
However, we've been
fighting over this resource
for many years now.
So mother nature decided to
provide us with something else.
The way he talks about them
makes me sympathize
with the monsters.
[SATOMI] Has there ever
been a more appropriate time
for superhumans
to band together?
[KIKKO]
The people made their choice.
As did the superhumans.
After all, in this era where
the line between right and wrong
is so hard to see,
they finally had what
they'd wanted all along.
An enemy to overcome.
And so the fighting began.
Both the Self Defense Force
and the American military
kept their distance,
fearing a Bio Destroyer leak.
This had become our fight,
and we had to do it alone.
[JIRO] It's time to wake up
and face the music.
Justice is here. But has this
really been a child's dream?
Either way, I will keep singing.
What about you?
Concrete Revolutio ,
final episode:
"Can you still sing?"