[REPORTER A] One of our
nation's projected gold medals
is the 200-meter ski jump.
Following the grand
opening on January 6th,
the competition will be held
here at the
Hikarinomori Schanze.
And representing
Japan in the jump
will be none other than
the "Three Birdmen."
[SHIN chuckles]
[SHIN]
Great jump! As always.
Thanks a lot, Zenda.
Or rather "Birdman Shin."
Oh, come on. You don't
have to call me that.
[AMATO]
Actually, I do.
You guys are representing Japan,
and that demands
all of our respect.
That's right, it does.
So why don't you practice what
you preach and call us "sir"?
[AMATO]
I guess I should.
You "guess"?
So much for respect.
I'll work on it. Sorry, sir.
Knock it off, Gamba.
You can't talk to him like that
just because we got the
superhuman surgery.
[GAMBA]
Sure I can.
After all, if he'd gone
through with it, too,
maybe he'd be more than
just a test jumper
checkin' the hill
for the real pros.
Why didn't you accept
the procedure?
If you'd done it like we did,
taking home the gold
would be a snap.
What does that mean?
Don't tell me.
You "sirs" still aren't
good enough
after everything
you've been through?
Oh, that's it!
Stop it!
You wouldn't want the paparazzi
getting a shot of this.
I bet you'd like it, huh?
[SHIN]
That's enough!
[laughing]
[COBRA]
What's that?
[SHIN, COBRA scream]
Finally. That flight
made me queasy.
I didn't realize ghosts
could get airsick.
Well, the high altitude does
distance him from nature.
It has that much of
an effect on him?
It might!
You still can't tell when
she's makin' stuff up?
[KONPARU]
Please, call me Konparu.
I'm sorry if this
ruined your holiday.
You feel the excitement
in the air?
That's because of the Sapporo
International Sports Grand Prix.
It represents peace, and
reminds people they're safe.
Nothing may cause
its cancellation.
[HYOUMA] People seem really
excited about the ski jump.
It's not surprising when
you think about it.
The Birdmen are popular.
[HYOUMA] Coming out of
the "post-war" phase,
port Grand
the Tokyo Inter
Prix in '39 was the "hop."
The Osaka Expo in
'45 was the "skip."
And finally this year's "jump"
will mark the completion
of Japan's reconstruction.
[KONPARU]
That's right.
So of course, upper management
have it in their heads
that we need to sweep all
three medals in the event.
Which is where we come in
to help you with
your little problem.
[HYOUMA]
So they got hit by lightning
and then flowers grew
out of their heads?
[GAMBA]
It was him. He did this to us.
[HYOUMA]
Him who?
[GAMBA] Slope's test
jumper, Koichi Amato.
He was there when it happened.
You know Mr. Amato's
not behind this.
He isn't a superhuman.
Are you sure?
How do we know he didn't get
a weird power all of a sudden?
It's not like it'd be the first
time that's happened.
Right, Superhuman Bureau?
Would it kill you to be
polite for a minute?
These people came all the
way out here to help us.
Then why haven't they
done anything yet?
We can't compete
in this condition!
It's that serious?
Not in the sense
that it's detrimental
to their health or
anything, but uh...
[COBRA]
Stupid thing won't bend.
We can't put our
helmets on over 'em.
Well, uh, you boys
could wear this helmet
with a hole we worked out.
[SHIN chuckles]
Idiot.
We'd be the laughing
stock of Inter-Sport
if we went out
looking like this.
It is not gonna happen.
[KONPARU] Unfortunately,
we're running out of time.
The opening ceremony is
the day after tomorrow.
To make matters worse,
the Three Birdmen are
supposed to perform
an exhibition jump
on the new hill.
There's no postponing it.
So you see, we must have this
issue resolved by tomorrow.
[EMI]
While you have my sympathy,
our job is to protect
superhumans,
not solve paranormal problems.
Despite that, we can't let
the Sapporo Inter-Sport fail.
Our nation is counting on us,
so that means we're
gonna have to work
outside our comfort zones.
What's up?
[EMI]
Well...
[GAMBA]
Aw, man!
Those look just like the
clouds that zapped us!
[KIKKO] I'll go check
it out! Meteortail!
Everyone! Clear this area!
Look up there!
A real witch girl!
Meteortail!
Come on! Why are they so fast?
Typical Kikko discretion.
Between that and
her uselessness,
at least she's consistent.
[KIKKO screams]
[ULLR]
Stay with me, Star Child!
[KIKKO yelps]
Nice catch.
Oh, wow, Miss Kikko!
You're heavier than I thought!
Oh! Wait!
[ULLR] You're all right.
No flower sprouted.
Fuurouta!
Yeesh. Spinny. Dizzy. Hehh.
Looks like you two are okay.
But the attack didn't
even phase them.
Kikko, conjure me a
lightning rod, now!
[KIKKO]
Huh?
Hurry!
[KIKKO]
Right! Meteortail!
[HYOUMA]
That's a first.
It's not like you
to put yourself
in harm's way like that.
No choice.
Okay, so we managed
to handle one problem,
but we still don't
know the cause,
and Sapporo's turning
into a flower garden!
We'll get there.
[AMATO]
Huh? What the--?
[GAMBA]
What did you do?
Is that you, Iwashita?
[GAMBA]
No, not Iwashita. Gamba.
Now tell me how you
did this flower thing.
I didn't do anything!
[GAMBA] Like I'm gonna
believe you didn't go
outta your way to shut us down.
After all, if we can't compete,
they'll have no choice
but to let you jump!
I told you. I didn't!
Don't lie to me!
I heard you mumblin'
something under your breath!
What, 'd'you think
I was unconscious?
You know what's
causin' all this.
Tell me. Or pay the price!
[GAMBA]
Whatcha think?
That was just a
small demonstration
of what I'm capable of as a
Bio-Enhanced Super-Athlete.
[AMATO]
Stop it, Iwashita!
[GAMBA]
I told you, my name is Gamba!
I threw away that identity
when I was modified.
And because of those
modifications,
you think you're better than me.
No, that isn't true at all!
Oh, I'm pretty sure it is.
There's no reason you'd
attend as a normal person.
You want everyone to think
you're just a test jumper,
but you're listed
as a competitor!
The office made that
choice without asking me!
How convenient!
Stay away!
It's ridiculous.
To think that a flower could
ruin so many years of sacrifice.
But that's what you
wanted, right?
[AMATO]
You're wrong!
I don't know why
this is happening.
[GAMBA] How long can you
keep up this charade?
And what are you willing
to give up for it?
Because the only thing I have
left is this childish name.
But now that I won't
be able to compete,
I'll gladly take it.
If I don't, nothing I went
through will have any meaning!
Listen! I admire
what you've done!
See, that's how I
know you're lying.
'Cause if you did,
you'd call me "sir."
[JIRO]
Put him down!
Hold it!
[AMATO] Let him go! There's
no point in chasing him.
[JIRO]
But he--
It's fine. Unless
you're with the police.
I'm not. But I am here
for you, Koichi Amato.
How'd you get your own place?
This is where I grew up.
So what's going on
really isn't your doing, is it?
But everyone thinks it is.
So the Superhuman Bureau
will be coming after you.
Their entire purpose is to
register unknown superhumans
and make them work for
the nation's government.
That's wrong. So I'm
here to protect you.
[AMATO] The only athletes that
are supposed to participate
in the Inter-Sport are those
with biological enhancements.
Mechanical enhancements
aren't allowed,
so the competition is still
determined by a person's talent.
That's why they wanted
me to become enhanced.
But I declined the procedure,
and became a disgrace
to our country.
So they removed me
from the roster
to make an example of me.
Oh, man.
I was just too afraid.
I kept thinking,
"What if I do this, but I
don't win any medals?"
It would've been a waste.
I couldn't bring myself
to sign the papers.
[AMATO] And if I couldn't
do that, there was no way
I could compete with our
people counting on me.
So you don't have to worry about
this Bureau coming after me,
'cause I can't do anything
"for the nation" now.
Looks like I made a
terrible mistake. I'm sorry.
What? You're giving up?
With that weird power of yours,
you could help get to
the bottom of this.
[JIRO] I'd like to, but you
were the only lead I had.
[AMATO]
Well, your lead's not cold yet.
[AMATO chuckles]
[AMATO] Man, look at
that big ol' dumb grin.
I feel embarrassed
just looking at it.
[JIRO]
Aw, it's not bad.
[AMATO] This was taken back
when I was in middle school.
There used to be a shrine around
where the Hikarinomori
Schanze is now,
but it doesn't exist anymore.
Every New Year,
there was a tradition
to hang a target in the forest.
Hitting it was said
to please the gods,
who would then deliver
a good harvest.
This had happened since
before anyone could remember.
A 15-year-old boy was always
chosen to take the shot.
And that year, they chose me.
[SPIRITS laughing]
[AMATO]
You see, the Hikarinomori Forest
used to be the home of
a god called Pirikappi.
Pirikappi.
[ULLR gasps]
[ULLR] I'm starting to get cold.
How much farther?
You'd have to ask Miss Emi.
[FUUROUTA]
Yeah, but it feels so good!
Man, I love places like this!
Are you sure the cause of
this human flower phenomenon
is really out here?
[EMI]
Absolutely.
And honestly, I feel like
we're partly to blame
for how out of hand it's gotten.
The only ones who sprout the
flower are normal humans.
If we'd realized that earlier,
we could've saved a lot
of people back in the city.
[HYOUMA]
But the Three Birdmen got 'em,
and they're superhuman.
[EMI]
Yes, artificially.
Despite that, though, they're
still fundamentally normal.
How do you know that?
You'll have to wait and see.
We're here.
[HYOUMA]
This is it?
[EMI] Yes. It's the symbol
of the god of this forest.
Jiro, hey!
Great, it's you.
[KONPARU]
Mr. Amato.
The test jump for
today is cancelled.
[AMATO]
That doesn't make sense,
the opening ceremony
is tomorrow.
Well, given the Three
Birdmen's current condition--
Regardless of that,
I have a responsibility
to check the hill.
It's my job as the test jumper.
[KONPARU] I'm afraid I can't
allow you to approach the slope.
Mr. Gamba's orders.
I'm sorry? He has that
kind of authority?
A top competitor speaks,
the brass listens.
Sadly, this is
out of my control.
[AMATO]
Konparu.
Please try to
understand, Mr. Amato.
[HYOUMA]
Spill, Jiro. Why are you here?
So! Are you responsible
for all this?
[JIRO] No. But trust me,
you're outclassed on this one.
Mr. Jaguar! What's Emi doing?
Oh, no.
Uh, guys, this situation just
got a whole lot more dangerous!
What?
[FUUROUTA]
'Cause that's a god.
[JIRO]
She's been possessed.
That's the god of the forest.
[HYOUMA]
What are you saying?
[JIRO] The Hikarinomori
Ski Jump was built on top
of this god's home.
Its name, Pirikappi,
was given to it by the people
who used to live here.
In their language,
it meant "Beautiful Seed."
They chose it because
Pirikappi would spread seeds
that grew into
flowers and trees.
Which would explain the
human flower phenomenon
we've been dealing with!
[FUUROUTA]
Look out!
[SHIN]
You attacked Mr. Amato?
As payback for
causing this mess.
[SHIN] No one who loves
skiing as much as he does
would ever do such a thing.
But he's been reduced to a test
jumper! The motivation's--!
[COBRA]
Will you two shut up?
Yelling at each other
won't help us find a way
to get rid of these
stupid things.
[giggles]
[COBRA]
Seriously.
You're right.
[HYOUMA]
Emi!
After her, Kikko!
'Kay!
Meteortail!
Wait for me!
What's this?
[KONPARU]
You can't be here!
These grounds are off limits!
Men! Secure the area!
[GUARD A] We're trying,
but they won't stop!
[KONPARU]
They're here, too?
What is going on?
[AMATO]
This is bizarre.
[HYOUMA] The god is using Emi's
power to bolster its own.
We have to find some
way to bring them down.
[FUUROUTA]
Impossible.
You're talking about
fighting a force of nature.
Even working together,
we'd never stand a chance.
But still.
Now, let the ceremony begin!
This can't be!
[FUUROUTA] No way!
They all turned into trees!
Turn those people
back to normal!
[giggles]
[HYOUMA]
What're you doing?
What I have to!
I never thought
you'd attack Emi!
If it's the only way to save
her, of course I would!
I guess he still
cares about her.
port!
Our priority is making sure
nothing cancels the Inter
Our nation's pride
depends on it!
[JIRO] So you'd rather get
rid of a problem than fix it?
"Business as usual."
You only care about what
superhumans can do for you!
[HYOUMA] Stop acting like
a child and grow up!
You don't even try
to understand!
[AMATO]
That is enough!
None of the things you're
bickering about matter.
Not even in the slightest.
All that's important now
are the competitors.
They've given
everything they had
just so they could
participate in this event.
Meanwhile, you've lived your
whole lives with powers.
But you would rather use
them to fight each other
than do anything to help!
I'm begging you to
please restore the hill.
I don't want the athletes' hard
work to have been in vain.
[HYOUMA]
Wha--?
[gasps]
[AMATO] The opening
ceremony is tomorrow.
Every New Year,
there was a tradition
to hang a target in the forest.
Yes, I see.
Hold on.
[AMATO]
Just go.
Mr. Amato.
[AMATO] I know what it wants:
The tradition must be fulfilled.
Wait, you don't mean
you're gonna try and jump
with the hill like this.
I am.
[HYOUMA]
You can't!
I will. And you can't stop me.
[JIRO]
Mr. Amato.
[AMATO]
I understand.
We humans have become
so self-absorbed,
the gods must have
gotten lonely.
[FUUROUTA]
He's not seriously gonna try
and jump into that gap, is he?
[KIKKO]
That's impossible.
As a normal human, he'll
never make it that far!
[AMATO]
Draw. Draw.
Loose!
[HYOUMA]
Kikko! Move those trees!
If we do nothing, he's gonna
crash right into them!
--Right!
--[JIRO] No!
[HYOUMA]
No good. He's falling short.
[JIRO]
Don't! He has to finish this!
Look!
Bullseye!
How'd ya like that, Pirikappi?
Just like when I was a kid!
[SPIRITS laughing]
[KIKKO] This must be
Pirikappi's blessing.
[HYOUMA] Mr. Konparu,
you feeling all right?
Yes. How's everyone else?
[HYOUMA]
Emi. You okay?
Yes. Where's Jiro?
He disappeared again.
[GAMBA]
So, Amato...
I'm sorry!
What I did to you was
terrible and wrong.
They told us what you did.
How you risked your life
to save everybody.
Thank you so much!
You really are the best!
It's fine. Don't thank me.
Sir, I was just--
[GAMBA] Aw, man! You don't
hafta call us that anymore!
I wasn't brave enough
to do what was necessary
to represent the nation.
Unlike you.
The only way I could be
useful was as a test jumper.
So that's what I am.
Go get those medals.
It doesn't matter if you're
superhuman or not.
You guys are heroes.
[EMI]
Thanks again, everyone.
I'm sorry I caused
so much trouble.
[HYOUMA] We all know
it wasn't really you.
[EMI] Monsters like me
are very similar
to the forgotten elder gods.
We were a little too in
tune with each other.
We got the medals, though,
so it turned out great!
Maybe. Although...
[KIKKO]
Huh?
What if they hold an Inter
Sport event here in Tokyo?
I don't know what we would do.
The elder god beneath this city
is a troublesome one indeed.
[DEVILO]
Rarirero rareriro rororon pa.
I'm Devilo, my sister's Devila!
Deroron deroron dededeno de.
Gods may be ugly,
but devils are pretty!
That's a fact that
none shallala know.
Tears come up and falololow!