[grunts]
[NANA] Why'd they choose to
show up now of all times?
Well whaddaya know? The
rumors were true after all.
There actually is
a secret hideout
for superhumans on the run.
Well, well. Nana Maria.
Formerly of IQ.
Later hired by Imperial Ads
to instigate the Shinjuku riots.
You people are why we're hiding.
We're public enemy number one!
Thanks to you, we
can't find any jobs
and we live in constant fear!
Ha! You think we
caused all of this?
I bet you weren't even there
to know what happened!
It was a party, man!
"We superhumans could
change the world.
All we had to do
was work together."
That was the line they sold us.
It was Imperial Ads who told
us that, who you worked for.
Stop trying to act
like you're innocent.
Well, excuse me for wanting
to make a difference!
[FUUROUTA] That's enough!
There's no need to fight.
Fuurouta the ghost.
[FUUROUTA] When you're in here,
there's no good or evil.
Everyone is welcome regardless
of where they came from.
As if we can tell who's good
or evil these days anyway.
Exactly.
So there isn't any reason
for us to do anything
except throw back
a couple of drinks
and enjoy each other's company.
Playin' nicey-nice
today, are ya?
Heh. I'm always nice
to pretty girls.
I stopped takin' favors
from the Superhuman Bureau
after they killed my friends.
Come on! I said none of
that stuff matters here!
[NANA]
Uh! What the--?
Let me go!
[CLAUDE] You are a
superhuman of justice.
Now. It is time we
returned to battle!
[REPORTER A] Eyewitnesses
described the event as...
Where is he?
[JIRO groans]
Prime Minister...
[HANTA]
You see this?
[REPORTER A] ...revealed
his plans to establish
a new police force
after meeting with Master
Ultima earlier today.
This new organization will
specialize in superhuman crimes,
replacing the public
Security Force...
[HANTA] The Prime Minister's
getting desperate.
Not surprising, he's
lucky to still have a job.
If it weren't for
the oil crisis,
he'd've been removed from office
when he was impeached.
The real question is where
he got these new weapons.
All of them were excavated
from a legendary ruin
at the bottom of
the Pacific Ocean.
They've been refurbished
with today's hardware.
The salvage op was
run by Imperial Ads.
Them again?
[gasps]
[REPORTER B] What is the
intention of these "NUTS"
and how are they being used?
There is no way this ends
well for the people like us.
Perhaps not.
But we can't take matters
into our own hands
and attack the government.
That's terrorism.
I know what you're saying,
but still, I couldn't stop him.
[INTERVIEWEE A]
No, not at all...
Where would he be now?
[MICHIKO] Ugh! Am I ever going
to find a good candidate?
[HYOUMA] Sorry, but when
we screened these guys,
finding NUTS pilots
wasn't our priority.
Yeah, well it is now
seeing as our weapons
are being beaten by ancient
monsters in the Middle East.
Which, don't tell the news,
is the real reason
behind the oil crisis.
[KIKKO] Y'know, to some people,
they're superhumans of legend.
[MICHIKO]
Yeah, so?
There are other people that
wanna call them gods.
But this is Japan, so they're
" yokai ." That right?
As you are aware, our country
hasn't overcomplicated
our definition of what we
consider to be "superhuman."
It includes humans who were born
with extraordinary abilities,
or developed them later
on in life, and that's it.
Plain and simple.
In other words, non-humans like
Miss Emi and I don't qualify.
I think you're forgetting
the Bureau you work for
was founded off one
simple principal.
That every superhuman of justice
has an evil counterpart.
You ask me, we're only just
starting to understand
what evil really is.
[MAGOTAKE]
Now I get it.
Doesn't matter how many
"evil" superhumans you catch.
To the masses,
there's no good or bad.
Just two people
going at it in public.
But if you call every
powered non-human evil,
suddenly there's a clear enemy.
One that can be smashed
with your giant robots.
Sound about right?
Well, we certainly
can't let superhumans
have a bad image when
we've been saying
they'll make the world a better
place for the last five years.
[EMI, KIKKO]
You stole that line from Jiro.
Maybe. But happens once
all your enemies are gone?
I'm sorry that this
evening isn't turning out
to be more romantic for you.
I'll worry about romance once
it's over and we're free.
Good plan.
One of these days, we're
gonna find a way out of this.
Just give it time.
[tires screech]
[RAITO] It would be nice
if he were here to join us,
but we know that's not the case.
This doesn't need to get
out of hand, Raito Shiba!
Heh.
[SATOMI] The Superhuman
Bureau is finally obsolete.
Aren't you worried that we
may be rushing things a bit?
After all, we're not sure how
the NUTS will perform.
[HANTA, MIEKO]
Cross Megasshin!
I'm shocked you took time
outta your schedule
fighting evil labs to come here.
Android Megasshin.
[MEGASSHIN] You contain both
good and evil within you.
This is confusing to me.
However, your actions
tonight... are evil!
Fair enough!
Aki! Is that you?
[gasps]
[SATOMI] It sounds to me like
they want a demonstration.
Yeah, but, uhh...
I don't know why
you're so worried.
You are a capable pilot.
They have to be used by
superhumans. I can--
That's a cover story.
Something we said to make
the public feel safe.
But once official
service starts,
the pilots are going to be
normal people like you.
The NUTS robots are going
to give us the power
to rival the gods themselves.
Are you saying if all
of this works out,
we won't need
superhumans at all?
I'm saying you will
become a superhuman.
In the riots six years ago,
they used large robots
to oppress us.
Those were nothing
compared to the NUTS.
I must crush them.
So you think fighting the
government is an act of justice?
[AKI]
"Justice"?
C'mon, Jiro, how
old are you now?
Pushin' 30, right?
[MICHIKO]
I learned this in the simulator,
but this is ridiculous!
[MICHIKO] Why aren't
the monitors turning on?
[SATOMI]
Is something wrong?
[MICHIKO] No, I've got it under
control. Action lever, in!
[yells]
Arachne, stop!
Or should I call you
the Hikari Knight?
I can't win. Please stop.
I'm only human. I can't--!
[CLAUDE]
Justice. Freedom. Peace.
Why is it that you fight?
[MICHIKO] Peace. I fight
to protect the peace.
[SATOMI] The power to rival
the gods themselves.
[gasps]
[CLAUDE] I may never be a god,
but I can be a superhuman!
That's Claude's voice!
[MICHIKO]
What? I'm out of fuel!
[AKI screams]
Aki! Get out of there!
[SATOMI]
Tries Corporation.
Just had to give me one
more headache, didn't you?
[EMI]
Jiro! How could you do this?
[KIKKO] Tell me it's not
what it looks like!
Well?
Do you want me to
turn back time?
Even if I did, I wouldn't
be able to stop them.
For now, you should investigate
the fuel. There's something--
For the record,
I'm not mad that you
couldn't stop their attack.
And we're all upset
about Imperial Ads
and their giant new toys.
I'm mad... 'cause
you stood there!
You didn't do a damn thing
to try to beat their robot
or the Iron Detective!
Instead, you just watched
from the sidelines!
Don't treat me like a criminal!
When are you going to grow up?
[KIKKO screams]
[MAGOTAKE]
No doubt about it.
Yeah, it's the Bio Destroyer.
You mean... it's that stuff
from the incident with Sanae?
[MAGOTAKE] Yeah, the chemical
the Americans created
in hopes of destroying
the immortal family.
Now they've found some way
to turn it into a fuel source.
Breaking down molecular
bonds for power.
That sounds awfully familiar.
Like the nuclear fission
research done in the past.
[JUDAS]
This is...
[HANTA] I warned you many
times before, but this time
will be the last!
Your violence and destruction
don't accomplish anything!
And you fighting Yatsuka
Heavy Industries robots does?
Or how Shirota battles
against aliens?
It's your actions that don't
accomplish anything.
Still better than your methods,
which only make
superhumans look bad!
Why can't you set aside your
differences and work together?
We're supposed to be friends!
[RAITO]
Oh, that's rich.
[HANTA]
It's simple, Jiro.
Because whether you want
to admit it or not,
your organization is evil.
[MIEKO]
Earth- chan !
[RAITO] With so many
machines showing up,
you'd think we were
a science fair.
Whose side are you taking?
[HANTA] More importantly,
why are you here?
Someone was crying
for help, so I came.
Jiro! The doctor needs you!
[JIRO] Are you sure we're
the same blood type?
[JUDAS]
Honestly, it doesn't matter.
I'll explain once
I've got her stable.
[AKI screaming]
What's the matter?
[JUDAS] Don't worry about it.
This is how it always is.
How it always--?
[JUDAS] For some reason,
your blood vitalizes cells
and makes them grow.
I'm surprised you
didn't know that
considering it was a well-known
rumor in the circles I ran in.
You mean amongst the evildoers.
You may recall, I took
some of your blood
as part of a health
exam a while back,
then ran some experiments.
Aki Haruka was part of them.
Why would you do that?
Growing larger really
isn't all that useful.
It was just a side
effect of my tests.
That's how his blood works.
It produces varying
results in superhumans.
But as for its true
nature, well,
I'd have to ask Professor
Hitoyoshi about that.
Why would you ask my father?
[JUDAS] Because he's the leading
researcher of your blood.
Take the GigantoGon
incident for example.
They said your blood
created a giant kaiju
out of a peaceful
animal from the south.
How do you think that happened?
It's also the explanation behind
Beastly Radio Wave Japan.
Enough!
[MIEKO] That must be the reason
Aki went berserk as well.
If it weren't for Jiro,
she wouldn't've lost control
and attacked NUTS.
Aki wished for this!
He had nothing to do with it!
Oh, really?
Come on. You must've
thought it, too.
"Another varying side
effect of Jiro's blood
is doing things he wants to do."
[gasps]
He couldn't be sure.
True. But we always are.
We don't struggle with a choice.
We make the right one.
But humans aren't like that.
Sometimes, they make
the wrong choice.
Wow. Did you come up
with that yourself?
That's why Jiro called me.
[JIRO]
But I didn't--
[EARTH- CHAN ] You did. Your
heart is crying out for help.
But I don't know what
I can do to save you.
And I don't think you do either.
[RAITO]
Where are you going?
We were built for one reason,
to fuse so we can preserve
peace in this nation.
We can't stay.
[HANTA, MIEKO]
Cross! Megasshin!
So I guess we're
enemies of peace?
[TACHIBANA] Why do we even
care about a small fuel leak?
Just tell 'em it's experimental!
We care because the fishery
in the Arakawa River
and its outlets were
heavily damaged.
It will likely affect
the entire Tokyo Bay.
I'm not worried about that.
All I want is results!
In that case, NUTS-One more
than proved itself in combat
against a superhuman.
Yes, it performed better
than we had hoped.
What a shame it's been
nothing but a waste,
considering that the
media is now aware
of your secret dealings
with Master Ultima.
The people now suspect Tries
Corporation paid you off
to accept NUTS.
[gasps]
[SATOMI]
Let's review:
Our company is
completely unaffiliated
with the NUTS fiasco,
Tachibana will be
forced to leave office,
and Master Ultima will now
face countless lawsuits.
That stone killed a lot
of birds. Not too shabby.
Maybe, but will the NUTS
project really be cancelled?
Yes. And it's quite
the costly loss.
illion per robot.
About 13
But what else can you
do when the things
are too dangerous to employ?
Sir. How can you be
so calm about all this?
Because even without NUTS,
we still have Okinawa.
And that movie is coming out
at the end of the year.
See? The end result
will be the same.
[MICHIKO]
And what result is that?
A world without superhumans.
[gasps]
[SATOMI] Leave them on
display here for the night
and then get them back
to the facility tomorrow.
[MICHIKO]
But you and I are the only ones
who know this program
has been cancelled.
What if superhumans decide
to launch another attack?
All the better, really!
An act like that would
only serve to further
the public's hatred of
"violent superhumans."
[YUMIHIKO] "Don't fight
if something happens"?
You want me to just stand there
and watch them attack the NUTS?
No, I would also
like you to make sure
the fuel doesn't get everywhere
as they're being destroyed.
Don't worry, Rex FE's armor
shouldn't be affected by it.
Doesn't matter who it
is? Not even Jiro?
[MICHIKO] All this time and
you still worry about him?
[YUMIHIKO]
I read the film script.
So, this is all true, isn't it?
"Not everything is
black and white.
There's a lot of grey, too."
That was profound
when I was a kid.
But I realize now
it means nothing.
Running red lights, urinating
in public, skimming change,
things like that are
so trivial, and yet,
we make such a big
deal out of them.
Even the Prime Minister
is wrapped up in scandals.
Jiro didn't say anything new.
He just stated the obvious.
I see. You're upset.
[YUMIHIKO] I think true
justice requires more
than seeing the problems.
It also needs a strong will to
denounce evildoers like him.
[sighs]
[knocking]
[MICHIKO] Hey, I'm dry
over here! Hurry up!
Yeah, I'm coming!
This is water!
[FUUROUTA]
'Cause I'm cutting you off!
[door opens]
[FUUROUTA]
About time you got here.
For real!
Case you forgot, you called me!
And then made me wait!
What's wrong with
you? Typical man.
[JIRO]
Almost surprised you showed.
Guess you really are concerned.
Just so you know, she was
already pretty hammered
before she came here with me.
It's not her most
endearing side.
Can't believe I drank
the whole thing.
Anyways, this is what
you want, right?
When you were inside the robot,
explain why your voice
sounded like Claude's.
It's 'cause these superhuman
power ampfification helmets
are based on the one he wore
that had the voice changer
built into it, jeez.
But the voice changer
was only added
in order to hide Jin's identity.
So why keep a useless function?
It wasn't like "Claude"
was another personality.
How should I know
why they kept it?
What're you doing?
That one's for girls!
I'll clean off my cooties.
[MICHIKO] Fine, just don't
let it touch your mouth!
[door opens]
Jiro. Let's play!
[JIRO]
Oh, wow!
The sky's so huge!
[EMI]
Wait up! Don't go so far!
[JIRO] No! I wanna play
outside some more!
[PEOPLE screaming]
There's a kaiju inside me?
But why?
[JIRO] Twenty-first year
of the Shinka era.
A year after the war ended.
[SATOMI]
I'm sure you've figured it out.
About the child you
found in Hiroshima.
Jiro? He's just an
ordinary baby.
Tell me. Have you heard
of the atomic bomb?
Of course, the one the Germans
were hypothesizing about.
But it was ultimately a failure.
Last year, the U.S. military
tried to drop one on Hiroshima.
They'd hoped it would
vaporize the entire city.
However, it appeared the
bomb had no effect at all.
Instead, only a small child
was found at the site.
But what if that wasn't
supposed to happen?
What if the bomb actually
did what it was supposed to
and caused horrible destruction?
What if that was the right path?
"The right path"?
What are you saying?
[SATOMI] In a world where
our humble happiness
is threatened by
violent superhumans,
a new motion picture
vows to showcase
their terrible nature
in stunning detail.
Tokusatsu Movie
Corporation presents:
The Great Prophecy of Japan .
Coming soon.