[TAKI] The Strange Power
Risk Management Office
was commissioned by the police.
To investigate
Sword Phantom Claude
and the incidents surrounding
his recent activities.
[MALE REPORTER A]
This is new.
[MICHIKO] What can you tell us
about the superhuman remains?
Most of the corpses
were Japanese.
And most were in their teens.
Some of them no more
than seven years old.
Total, there were
over 100 bodies.
[REPORTERS murmur]
Those that were
discovered in Hokkaido
were carried there
from the Ogasawara labs.
[REPORTERS]
We suspect a government agency
called the Superhuman Bureau
to be involved.
Hey! Publish one word of this
and you're all under arrest!
This is a human
rights violation!
[sighs]
[MALE POLICE A] Raito!
Stop those two from talking!
We're the ones who hired
them to reveal the truth.
That's what they're doing.
[JIRO]
Claude. Jin Nagakawa.
This is what he was
trying to show to us.
[HYOUMA] How many times
do I have to tell you?
We didn't know anything
about the labs
and experiments at Ogasawara.
[EMI sighs] How about the
fact the chief was actually
a puff of
extraterrestrial smoke?
[HYOUMA] So he was a spaceman.
It never caused a problem.
[JIRO]
The point is he hid it from us.
And the truth about
Rainbow Knight.
[HYOUMA] You let Claude
and Hoshino go
because you believed
what he said?
[JIRO]
I didn't let them go!
Claude and Kikko. I'll find
them both. I promise.
Finish the job. We have
two months 'til the
Revised Superhuman Law
passes the House.
Everything else can wait.
Kill Claude and
avenge the chief.
[MICHIKO] Last year, in August,
near Shinjuku Station,
a tanker train derailed.
It was carrying
U.S military fuel.
And was being transported
through the center of the city.
Then, there was
October last year.
[SATOMI] You'll remember
rioters clashed against police
in Haneda. There was
a student casualty.
[SATOMI] This summer, secret
experiments on superhumans
were revealed to have taken
place in Ogasawara.
This was the final push.
The youth are raising
their voices in anger.
[JIN] October 21st.
Year 43 of the Shinka Era.
This will be remembered
in history as the day
your generation shouted
"Enough is enough!"
Anti-war movements in the U.S.
Student uprisings
in Paris and Berlin.
And not only there.
Milan. Rome. Athens.
Istanbul. Belgrade. London.
Mexico City. Barcelona.
Amsterdam. Tel Aviv.
Warsaw. And Prague.
Young adults are rising
up at the same time
to face off against
the ruling powers.
Fighting for justice
all over the world.
Including this country. A huge
protest is planned in Tokyo.
And appropriately today
on World Peace Day.
What's the point?
The students claim that they'll
stop the American fuel tanker
at Shinjuku station. But how
will it change anything?
[MALE STUDENT3A] It's all
a fantasy. Changing the world.
[SATOMI] The students
won't stop at the station.
They'll march on to
government buildings.
You should prepare
for the possibility
of violent revolution today.
The government won in the
end in Prague and Paris.
Those countries didn't have
to worry about Claude.
I see, so that's the reason
you don't want me to vote
"Yes" for the revised
secrecy laws. Unbelievable.
Your only concern is
making some quick cash
with a superhuman star.
Under the revisions,
all superhumans will be
put under government control.
Civilians like you wouldn't
be able to do your jobs.
You business types
are all the same.
You only start to worry when you
feel your profits are at stake.
I'm sure you want to
control dangerous individuals
as much as I do.
Read the law before you form
an opinion! Don't you see?
The new measures breaks
people into two categories.
Humans and everything else.
Once somebody's classified
as superhuman,
human laws no longer
apply to them!
Potential criminals.
Dangerous thinkers.
Different races. By defining
them as superhuman,
you can create any
segregation law you wish.
[gasps]
A paranoid fantasy. I assure
you, it'll never happen.
[MITSUYA] You still don't
know where Claude is?
It's been two whole months!
What do I pay you for? Find him!
Claude and that witch die!
Tonight! Understand?
[tires screech]
[MITSUYA gasps]
[AKITA]
I was mistaken to trust you.
Akita? It can't be! You're dead!
[screams]
[MALE ANNOUNCER A] Earlier this
month, several student groups
organized street protests in
opposition of the government.
Their demands included
discarding the revised
Superhuman Law and halting
US military tankers.
On World Peace Day,
the 21st of this month,
an even larger turnout is
expected at Shinjuku station.
I didn't expect you to
come out of hiding
without your queen.
[ULLR]
We're not enemies, you and I.
Unlike Hitoyoshi and Star Child.
Really? But you teamed up
with the Phantom Sword.
[ULLR]
If Claude and Star Child elope,
this world will achieve balance.
So that's the deal.
[ULLR]
To tell you the truth,
I have been searching for a
partner myself for a long time.
And I find normal
humans so boring.
But you... You're different.
[ULLR grunts]
[ULLR]
We were just chatting.
[ULLR screams]
So, tell us about the
Queen of the Devil Realm.
[ULLR]
Fine. I'll talk.
She sees humans
only as a resource
and feeds on their happiness.
Kikko was a mask.
Hidden beneath is a
cold-hearted, merciless ruler.
The medicine prepared
by Jin Nagakawa.
The powerful hypnosis by Claude.
And finally, her disappointment
in you brought out the
second personality.
Is there a way that we
can bring Kikko back?
[ULLR]
No. She's lost forever.
What you saw is
Star Child's true form.
[EMI] So you're still going
to fight Claude. For Kikko?
[EMI grunts]
What is it?
Do you know what a Jinko is?
A Human Tiger?
What does that matter?
They aren't uncommon.
At least in Japanese folklore.
There are several stories of
greedy or lonely humans
turning into tigers.
It's a type of monster.
So what?
I can turn Kikko into one.
[gasps]
[EMI]
If it works,
it should only affect her
"Devil Queen" half.
It's only active right now
because the medicine
brought it out. And the
other Kikko you know?
[JIRO]
She'll survive?
[EMI] Yes. If that is
really her true face.
But you have to
promise me, Jiro.
After this, you'll never
see her again.
[EMI]
Whenever you're with her,
you act like someone
completely different.
Like you think you can
save every superhuman.
[MALE OFFICER A]
They're here!
[SHAKKOU] Claude is hiding
amongst the students!
Anyone who resembles him,
arrest on sight!
[POLICE shouting]
[SATOMI] After he conquers
the Shinjuku station,
Claude will become
a household name.
Then, all superhumans
will join the revolution
and change this nation.
Hey! It's time.
[MAN A]
Yeah! Everyone, helmets on!
[SHAKKOU gasps]
[MAN A]
I am Claude!
[CROWD]
We are all Claude!
[FEMALE REPORTER A]
Even before protestors arrived,
the Shinjuku East Entrance
Gate Square area
was flooded with onlookers.
Based on reports...
It looks like they just
want to cause trouble.
I don't understand why
they're getting so worked up.
It's simple, really.
The protestors are students
who were born after the war.
They never experienced it.
Or want to.
They grew up listening to
their parents make promises.
"We'll never go to war.
We hate Fascism."
And now it's happening again.
I see. Adults make promises and
then forget about them later.
But to the students, it's an
important legacy handed down
from their parents.
[FEMALE REPORTER A]
Oh! It's the Angel Stars!
They're performing
alongside the students!
♪ My lips trembling
on the rim of my glass ♪
♪ Tension is growing fast ♪
♪ Drink a little more,
get out on the floor.. ♪
[MASTER ULTIMA]
The Americans relented.
The fuel tanker was
officially cancelled.
Then explain to me
why do they continue
gathering to this place?
We leaked some information.
They think it's still coming
through the Shinjuku station.
[MASTER ULTIMA] You're amassing
them on purpose.
The East Station
entrance is a mess!
[NO-NAME]That so?
[MALE ELEPHANT]
You're going out there?
[NO-NAME] The students are
putting themselves on the line
for us superhumans!
[MALE ELEPHANT] But the police
have superhumans on their side.
Superhumans fighting each other?
Isn't that sort of...
Earth- chan ... Which side
are you really on?
All right. This isn't funny
You really want to go
to Shinjuku station?
The security forces
will be waiting!
Claude will be there. I know it.
Right! This is our stop!
[FUUROUTA]
This isn't Shinjuku!
[MALE POLICE B]
Detective!
[RAITO] Did they break past
the East ticket gates?
[MALE POLICE B]
No, sir.
They're moving from
Yoyogi station!
Ugh. Perfect. An infinite
supply of ammo.
[CROWD, POLICE shouting]
[EARTH- CHAN ]
All of you, stop!
[MAN A] Earth- Chan !
Whose side are you on?
[EARTH- CHAN ] If you keep
fighting each other like this,
I'll have to punish everyone!
I won't let people get hurt!
I don't want another Haneda!
[YUMIHIKO]
Earth- Chan !
The students who resort to
violence need to be punished.
Yumihiko? Whose side
are you on?! The police?
Yeah. That's my choice!
You should always know
what's right and wrong.
You told me that once!
I had a dream.
And now I don't know.
Things aren't always
black and white!
[REIICHI]
Out of our way.
The kid gloves are coming off.
Turn back around.
Don't make me do this!
[REIICHI]
We'll take the station.
[RAITO] The only thing
you're going to do
is inconvenience commuters!
[REIICHI]
The point of being a Superhuman
isn't defeating criminals!
We're supposed to work together!
To change the world for peace,
justice, and freedom!
[RAITO] You're quoting
a criminal. Claude's evil!
[REIICHI] The United States
and our government
experimented on superhumans!
Someone has to speak up!
They can't be forgiven!
[gasps]
[FUUROUTA]
Psy-Kicker! Hurry!
[REIICHI] Fuurouta!
Thank you! Now follow me!
Fuurouta! You're with
the Superhuman Bureau!
Yeah. I know that. But I'm
also every kid's friend.
[RAITO sighs] I was supposed
to be that way too.
The other groups
aren't here yet.
We're the first to arrive!
[ALL gasp]
[HYOUMA]
The jig is up.
This is where the real
war begins. Aranea, go!
[ALL gasp]
[CROWD shouting, coughing]
[SHAKKOU laughs] Your next
lesson is learning just how
powerless you truly are!
[gasps]
[EARTH- CHAN shouts]
The world can change.
I won't stop believing that.
[HYOUMA]
Hey! What are you--?
[HYOUMA gasps]
Claude!
[CLAUDE]
I went along with your plans.
Now everyone is watching.
If we defeat you here,
everyone will know
that superhumans are stronger.
We're this planet's saviors!
[HYOUMA]
He discarded the battery pack?
How can the Aranea operate
with no power supply!
[gasps]
He's the same as Jiro?
Its power is equal to Equus?
[MAGOTAKE] I read the
Ogasawara reports on Claude.
He always emitted a
mysterious energy source
and was able to transform metal.
But that wasn't good enough
for you. You needed more.
[MASTER ULTIMA]
Your son was the one we wanted.
Yes. But Jiro's a product of
coincidence and can't be copied.
He's truly unique.
[MASTER ULTIMA]
His origin is inconsequential.
We want his power.
So you sacrificed
countless superhumans
to create a proxy and
ended up with Claude.
No. The only thing you
invented was that helmet.
A weapon that allows him to
amplify his powers temporarily.
[JIRO] I'm sorry for what
happened to you in Ogasawara.
But this? Starting riots?
Putting students in harm's way?
Was it necessary?
[CLAUDE grunts]
Of course it is!
We're in the middle
of a war, Jiro!
Between humans and superhumans!
[JIRO] Superhumans aren't
enemies with humans!
They're allies.
They protect people!
[CLAUDE] And who looks
out for superhumans?
The Superhuman Bureau?
When did you ever
protect us, Jiro? Never!
[JIRO grunts]
Kikko!
[KIKKO]
You may call me queen, peasant.
[JIRO]
You want war too, is that it?
All I seek is to
protect my Jiro!
The weapons are gone?
[EMI] Of course not. We decided
to relocate the armory.
[KIKKO grunts]
I wish I could kill you right
here, but I made a promise.
[JIRO] You were like me.
You admired superhumans!
Those who chose to
do the right thing.
Not for themselves or because
their country ordered them to!
For a different reason!
[CLAUDE] And what
reason is that, Jiro?
Peace? Justice? Freedom?
He's strong.
[CLAUDE] Defending my
freedom disturbs the peace!
Your justice violates
my freedom!
There is no simple answer!
The only way to change
the world is through force.
If you insist on
defending the humans,
you have to combat them.
Simply to create a place where
superhumans can live in peace.
You should feel better now.
[CLAUDE]
Superhumans protect humans.
And the humans accept
them with open arms?
You're living a fantasy, Jiro.
[JIRO] It's possible,
but I have to believe.
There has to be someone out
there like the superhumans
I looked up to.
Heroes of my youth.
I want to be able to protect
them, or at the very least...
...be an ally of justice.
Jiro. There you are.
Jiro, don't...
[CLAUDE] I'll admit. Your words
are sweet on the ears.
But it's all an illusion.
Dreams and ideals that can
never be made into reality.
I was told to be a second Jiro.
And I'll become that...
...by finally erasing you!
Unlock one.
[CLAUDE] I'm not your
replacement. I'm superior!
Unlock two!
Stop it!
[CLAUDE] That's why I
deny all you stand for!
Freedom! Peace!
Justice! Everything!
[JIRO]
Unlock three!
[CLAUDE grunts]
Is that... Is that what's
behind your mask? Jiro!
[JIRO yells]
Out of my way.
What? No, I can't stop.
With my helmet broken
I can't stop absorbing, metal!
[MASTER ULTIMA] The rest is
a domestic matter for Japan.
[MAGOTAKE] Jiro. Do you hate
me for what I've done?
Emi's the only one
who can stop him.
But not when he's in Equus.
Save him. Someone
please save Jiro!
[JUDAS]
Jiro?
Why should we help the
Superhuman Bureau?
[gasps]
[JACKY (SONG)] ♪ Someone's
knocking on my door ♪
[MAGOTAKE]
"S" Planetarian?
The same one who
fought Grosse Augen?
[S PLANETARIAN]
Not long ago, you saved me.
I wasn't the only one.
Come on, everyone!
I mean, we're all government
officials now, aren't we?
[SONG]
♪ I've got walls inside me ♪
♪ Where my heart
lies in hiding ♪
♪ But the
season's changing... ♪
Should I stop time? Dammit.
[REIICHI]
You're with the Bureau, right?
What should we do?
Equus is taking too much
power away from Jiro.
We need to pull him
out of there but...
Will you help me?
[shouts]
Aim for the target!
[SONG] ♪Someone's
knocking on my door ♪
[SONG] ♪ Feel it
deep down in my heart ♪
[SONG]
♪ Now's the time for love ♪
[EMI grunts]
[CROWD chattering]
[MALE GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL A]
Due to a majority vote,
the Revised Secrecy Laws
Governing Superhumans,
has been rejected!
[MALE REPORTER A]
Mr. Mitsuya.
The bill's failure is
said to be largely due
to your change of heart.
Did the Shinjuku incident scare
you away from the revised laws?
[MALE REPORTER C]
Mr. Mitsuya! Explain!
[MALE REPORTER D]
We want answers!
[MALE REPORTER G]
Secretary General!
The chief. Chief Akita would
have never forgiven you.
[UCHIHATA]
Mr. Mitsuya!
You promised us your support.
To guide and protect superhumans
with our own powers.
That may have been
too arrogant on our part.
I've learned from
my mistake. Have you?
Akita. Is that you?
You killed Mitsuya?
Took his body?
If our brothers in space ever
found out about this...
[FEMALE REPORTER A] The revised
secrecy laws that were expected
to pass today were
instead rejected
in the House
of Representatives...
[KIKKO] Um, Emi. So, Jiro
really didn't leave a note?
Or tell you where
he might be going?
[KIKKO sighs]
[FEMALE REPORTER A]
...whose sudden reversal on
the issue surprised even
the most senior members
of the House.
When asked by reporters for
the reason behind his vote...
[ULLR] Looks like he
kept his promise to you
and won't ever speak
to Star Child again.
I was hoping he'd chase her
out of this dimension for good.
[BABY cries]
[MAGOTOKE pants]
[MAGOTOKE gasps]
{ULLR] November, 46th year
of the Shinka Era.
Superhuman freedoms
are being taken away.
Jiro Hitoyoshi chooses
the path of the wanted man
to protect superhumans.
Is justice just an illusion?
Concrete Revolutio,
Superhuman Phantasmagoria.