[ding]
All right. Time to go.
[grumbles]
[YUKO]
I'll see you later, mommy!
[YUKO giggling]
Yuko!
[YUKO] ♪ Here we go round
the mulberry bush. ♪
♪ The mulberry bush,
♪ Here we go round
the mulberry bush. ♪
♪ So early in the morning. ♪
[WAKAMURA]
Damn these stupid plants!
Sweetheart?
[WAKAMURA]
This thing again.
You shouldn't touch
it. It's dirty.
No, it isn't.
[KIKKO]
Around this time,
a plant known as
the Canada Goldenrod
started growing in Japan.
It's not indigenous
to the region,
yet large numbers of them
sprouted up all over,
and quickly became
a social problem.
[FUUROUTA] A bunch of
superhuman convicts escaped?
[EMI] After the Sugamo
Prison closed last year,
a bunch of them
were put in Fuchu.
It happened when they were being
transferred between facilities.
Jiro wouldn't be behind
something like this,
so it's not worth
getting involved.
True, but we're getting so
many requests to handle it!
[EMI] Yeah, but that's what
the ninja guys are for.
Besides, we're
understaffed this week.
Personally, I say we let
everything go to hell.
[FUUROUTA]
Ugh! It already feels like hell!
[YUKO] ♪ Wash our face!
Wash our face! ♪
♪ This is the way
we wash our face! ♪
♪ So early in-- ♪
Quiet, dear.
You can't make me!
[OLD LADY A]
Hm.
[BOTH giggle]
[PASSENGERS scream]
[PASSENGERS gasp]
[PASSENGER A]
A superhuman?
[PASSENGER A] Look at that mask!
He's from the prison!
Let's go!
Why are you going so slow?
Daddy! That man's not a
real superhuman, is he?
Superhumans are supposed
to be good guys
who come out of hiding to save
us when we're in trouble,
not break our bus and act scary!
[ATTENDANT A]
Attention!
Do any of you have powers who
may be able to offer protection?
Why can't these monsters
just leave us alone?
All superhumans ever
do is kill each other.
You're wrong!
Superhumans are people who
fight for justice like heroes!
--Come out, heroes! Save us!
--Y-Yuko, don't do that!
[gasps]
Hey. You keep talkin' like that,
'n' you'll hurt my feelings.
[SHAKKOU]
The target is Jack Flash,
a vile fusion between a human
and one of Devila's race!
The Security Force
labeled me a villain
and locked me away in prison.
But I'm just a superhuman!
How 'bout we sing a song?
It'll help everyone
feel more at ease.
I said sing!
[YUKO] ♪ This is the way
we comb our hair. ♪
[JACK]
They can't hear you!
Let her go!
Shaddap!
Daddy!
[NINJA A]
A civilian fell out!
[SHAKKOU]
Where is he?
[gasps]
[WAKAMURA] No. What the
hell is happening to me?
What are you?
[WAKAMURA] Just a man.
A normal human man!
No! Please! Put me down!
The two of us can work together!
[WAKAMURA]
Never!
[YUKO]
Human-Man?
That's your name, isn't it?
That was awesome!
[WAKAMURA]
Uh. Sure!
Well, if you'll excuse me.
Thank you! Human-Man!
[sighs]
It's me! I'm back to normal.
You've become quite
the man, Daitetsu.
Meanwhile, you've become
nothing but garbage.
If you're the great "ally
of justice," am I evil? No.
Because good and
bad don't change
whenever it suits your
selfish desires.
Here I come!
[gasps]
Okay. So it's big.
Meet the successor to the Arcus.
Once it gets mass produced,
we'll have no trouble
dealing with Equus.
Jiro Hitoyoshi! What
are you trying to do?
[gasps]
[YUMIHIKO] It's not like
you can make a difference
by getting in our way.
You're wasting our time!
[JIRO] And all you accomplish
is keeping superhumans
from living in peace!
We do that?
I was there in Shinjuku.
[CROWD]
We are Claude!
That was war.
It's been four years.
It won't happen again.
Pretty sure that was my line.
Rex FE! Take him down!
Chicken!
[YUMIHIKO]
Rex! What's wrong?
[HYOUMA] Looks like
we're done for the day.
Hey, Hoshino!
Can you give us a hand?
[YUMIHIKO] I never had a problem
like that with Gigander Seven!
Because your power wasn't being
used to generate electricity.
Altering metal at the
molecular level's hot.
It makes the Rex FE
way more powerful.
Trouble is...
It still needs to cool off.
Then why didn't we just
make it like Equus?
Because Equus is one of a kind.
You're heavy!
Well, that was mean!
Sorry all my upgrades are
such a burden on you!
Kikko! What is the Bureau doing?
Those helmets,
they look like Jin's!
It's an experimental design
that stimulates the brain
and amplifies a
superhuman's abilities.
Imperial Ads picked up
where Claude left off.
Even though you
know that's wrong,
you still work for the Bureau?
[KIKKO] Imperial Ads only
cares about superhumans
who can be made
into celebrities.
The security forces want
them to be soldiers.
That's exactly why we need
the Superhuman Bureau--
in order to keep them
from being exploited!
I mean, that's what
Mr. Jaguar says.
Then?
I don't care about that,
but if I keep this job,
I get to see you.
[JIRO]
But only as enemies!
[KIKKO]
If that's all we can ever be,
then I'll gladly take it!
Kikko.
[EARTH- CHAN yells]
You said humans make mistakes,
that sometimes they aren't
going to do the right thing!
Guess that applies
to witches, too!
Yeah, but there's a difference.
I'm not supposed to do the right
thing because I'm a witch.
[JUDAS] The "Iron
Detective" is responsible.
I assume you chose them because
you knew we'd be outta town.
Of course he did.
Some of them were arrested
because their powers
were deemed dangerous.
Others because they
were sympathetic
towards the revolution.
They didn't do anything wrong.
[EARTH- CHAN ] You think that
makes what you did okay?
Just being superhuman
shouldn't be illegal.
Yet, I arrested many in
the past for that reason.
That's why--
Yeah, then one of
them hijacked a bus.
Damn it. Were any of
the civilians hurt?
[JUDAS] Nope.
The unexpected happened
when some superhuman
decided to show himself
in public and save everyone.
"Human-Man."
I've never heard of him.
Can you focus for one minute?
None of that
excuses his actions.
[JIRO] What if he's trying to
atone for some sin of the past?
Judas. He could be like you.
And you're like the
Superhuman Disease.
It's an illness
caused by pollution
that's giving people powers.
I don't think I follow.
Course not.
'Cause you're so obsessed
with protection,
you don't consider
who deserves it.
Like the disease,
it's a problem.
[FUUROUTA] "Human-Man
appears at the Ueno Zoo
to help kids see the pandas."
"Human-Man assists in rush
hour train pervert's arrest."
"Human-Man exposes conspiracy
behind popular personal
calculator counterfeiting"?
Spreading the word about the
good things superhumans do
is also a part of our job,
it's not all negative.
I don't get why he
doesn't understand that.
What? Who do you mean?
The real question
is why's this guy
pulling all these heroic
stunts in this day and age.
That was No-Name and Saburai.
[WAKAMURA]
I don't mean to be rude,
but I need to pick
up my daughter.
Don't worry, we're
not gonna keep you
for too long, Humid-Man.
That's Huma--
[SABURAI]
You're among friends, comrade.
I know you. You were in
a bunch of magazines!
Yeah, back when we
were "good guys"
who would bust up evil
organizations and stuff.
Does that mean
you don't anymore?
Doesn't matter what we do
'cause the people resent us for
what happened in Shinjuku.
Today, all our powers are
good for is personal gain.
We're about to hit
that bank up ahead,
but we're also lookin'
for new allies.
You in?
[crash]
[gasps]
[WAKAMURA]
Don't come any closer to me!
There's no way I'm gonna help
you do anything like that!
All I want is to be helpful!
You're Human-Man, right?
Saburai, No-Name.
I hope you realize I won't be
able to protect you after this.
[SABURAI]
Like it matters.
You're not even with
the Bureau anymore.
[NO-NAME] So if you
ain't gonna turn us in,
there's nothing you can do!
[POLICE OFFICER A]
Attention pedestrians!
This is a pathway,
not a park....
You had a spare suit?
How many do you own?
A bunch.
But I was lucky enough
to buy them in bulk,
so I got a good discount.
Do you mind if I ask you
something personal?
I can't figure out
why you would decide
to come out as a hero
at a time like this.
I guess it is uncommon.
Especially with how
things are now.
Few years ago, this
place was like a park
where people would
gather and sing.
But that's not allowed today.
They want everyone
to keep moving.
Loitering is prohibited.
Plus, if they find more than
five superhumans together,
they're all arrested
on the spot.
[JIRO]
That can't be helped, though.
Not after the riots in Shinjuku.
They're wary of us
and of young people.
[WAKAMURA] I was there.
In the crowd that day.
It was terrifying.
I still don't know what
they were hoping to do.
And it didn't seem like
stopping the American trains
accomplished much either.
Despite that, the
reason I revealed myself
is really quite simple.
Someone I love
loves superhumans.
So I'm happy to be one.
Now that's something
I can relate to.
But in my case,
that someone believed I was
an ideal ally of justice.
When that person was around me,
I felt like I had to do
the right thing.
If something needed to
get done, I had to do it.
No matter what.
Where is that person now?
All grown up and doesn't
need me anymore.
"Happy to be one." Huh.
[EMPLOYEE A]
Excuse me, Mr. Wakamura?
[WAKAMURA]
Yes?
Superhuman Security
is here to see you.
Huh?
Superhuman disease?
Yes, you tested positive for it
in your recent
medical examination.
See?
[WAKAMURA]
Okay.
So there's an illness going
around giving people powers.
Is there a cure?
[MICHIKO]
Nainorin. You heard of it?
Yeah, that's supposed to be
a power suppressant, right?
I thought it hadn't been
approved for public use yet.
Don't worry about that.
We've been testing it in
elementary schools
by mixing it with
the kids' flu shots.
It's safe.
Oh, good.
But I was thinking,
our company contracts
superhumans for various jobs,
like entertainment gigs, or
security guard work, doesn't it?
It does. If that's something
you're interested in.
I'll look at your file.
Wait, you're a widower?
Uh, yeah?
I'm sorry, but that
doesn't work for us.
Our heroes have
a positive image.
We could hire you as a
villain to be taken down,
but what would your
daughter think?
[MICHIKO]
Did you take it?
I-- Yes.
[MICHIKO]
Good.
So let's talk Canada Goldenrods.
Have you noticed any
growing around your house?
Uh.
Yeah, I have. A whole
bunch, actually.
We tried pulling them out,
but they just kept
growing back in.
I see.
That's consistent with what I've
heard in other cases as well.
The Canada Goldenrod performs
a process called "Allelopathy."
This means it emits chemicals
that inhibit the growth
of other nearby plants.
However, these seem to be
mutated so that the chemicals
are stimulating dormant
superhuman genes.
Which explains my
health exam results.
It does seem to be
the most likely cause
as far as we can tell.
So we're burning the colonies
whenever we come across them.
How does three days
from now sound?
[WAKAMURA]
Sorry?
For the burning.
Don't worry, I'll handle
all of the legal work.
Oh, look! That's Christmas Day!
I guess you'll be
giving your daughter
the gift of good health
this year, won't you?
And then I really won't be
a superhuman anymore.
[MICHIKO]
That's the idea.
We believe this
mutant strand...
Dad, look! I drew Human-Man!
Tell me, sweetie, who's cooler:
Him or your old man?
Human-Man!
Sorry, Daddy, but since
Mommy went to heaven,
all you ever do is cry.
[SHAKKOU] Local residents, may
I please have your attention?
We are about to begin
the incineration process
of these dangerous plants.
They are believed to
be the cause behind
a widespread
pollution-based disease
currently affecting the nation.
We posted several newspaper ads
to notify you of
today's procedure.
Your safety is of the
utmost importance.
Human-Man?
What are you doing?
[WAKAMURA]
You can't destroy these plants.
I won't let you!
That's just great.
[FUUROUTA]
I don't get it.
I thought Human-Man was
one of the good guys!
He probably has the
superhuman disease.
That would explain why
he showed up outta nowhere.
[EMI]
He must realize that if
the mutated plants
are destroyed,
he'll lose the source
of his powers.
But he isn't aware
of how widespread
this issue is becoming.
Most of those who've developed
powers have no idea
how to control them.
The worst cases wind
up in the hospital,
while others just have trouble
adapting to their
daily routines.
Are you saying we
shouldn't protect them?
That disease victims aren't
the same as other superhumans?
[MAGOTAKE] If having
powers becomes the norm,
there will inevitably
be more riots.
So, no, we should
get more samples,
but this is the Security
Force's problem.
Sounds like we're settling
for their leftovers.
Jiro would never go
along with this.
What, Kikko?
Sorry. Excuse me.
[ULLR]
Wait, Star Child!
Oh, good. Now I have
to return that.
Human-Man! Why are you
hurting those people?
[SHAKKOU]
Cease your attack immediately!
These plants are ruining
lives across the country!
By defending them,
you're making people suffer.
And I won't allow it!
He's here!
Jiro Hitoyoshi!
Why are you doing
this, Mr. Wakamura?
You said you were happy
to be a superhuman.
You refused to use your
powers for personal gain.
So what's making you lash out?
Ullr, wha--?
[ULLR] I have a message. This
man has the superhuman disease.
I've heard of it.
[ULLR] Those flowers are
the cause of his condition.
Without them, he will become
a normal human again.
That's why he's protecting them.
Aw, crap!
[SHAKKOU]
Listen, Hitoyoshi!
If that villain refuses to move,
we'll have no choice
but to attack!
[WAKAMURA] I'm a villain?
I guess that's true.
These plants are hurting
people simply by existing.
And as long as I fight to keep
them from being destroyed,
I'm no better than a
criminal who would try
to poison the
city's water supply.
You can't be serious.
Don't think that way!
[ULLR] This man is knowingly
risking the lives of others
just so that he may
remain powerful.
There is no reason for
you to protect him.
End of message!
[WAKAMURA] Please leave.
I have to do this.
[JIRO] Why is this such
an obsession for you?
[EARTH- CHAN ]
Because he's a bad guy!
[yells]
[JIRO]
Earth- Chan . Not you, too!
There's no denying the truth.
That man didn't
become a superhuman
for the sake of world peace
or vanquishing evil,
and therefore, he has
no heart of justice.
[JIRO]
You don't know that!
[YUKO]
Daddy, where are you?
Those people wanna
hurt Human-Man!
You need to help save him!
[WAKAMURA]
That's my daughter.
She's the one who
loves superhumans.
So when I became one,
I thought she would be happy.
That's why I wanna
stay this way.
For her!
That reasoning doesn't make
up for all of the trouble
your actions are causing for
countless innocent lives.
It's wrong.
[WAKAMURA]
Yeah, you're right.
But honestly,
I've never concerned myself
with the welfare of others.
Ever since her mother
passed away,
I haven't been there
for my daughter.
But when I'm like
this, I can be!
[EARTH- CHAN ] Jiro Hitoyoshi!
Get away from him!
This can't go on any longer!
[screams]
[SHAKKOU]
I don't believe it!
Jiro! You can't be
siding with that villain!
Not when he's spreading
the superhuman disease.
Because I'm just like him.
My obsession is my disease.
What this man is doing may not
truly be the "right" thing,
but still, I will protect him.
[WAKAMURA]
Why?
Heroes fight for many
reasons. Even for children!
[gasps]
Well, if that's how
you really feel,
I'm afraid you've left
me with no choice.
Yumihiko!
How sad. Guess you
really did turn evil.
Mommy?
[YUKO]
Mommy! Mommy!
You have to save
Human-Man! Please!
Mommy, please!
Well, I wasn't
expecting to see that.
What is it, a rock?
[ULLR]
No.
[YUMIHIKO]
Rex FE! Attack!
[ULLR]
That's a chrysalis!
[gasps]
[MICHIKO]
The pollen. Do something, quick!
If it continues to spread,
so will the disease!
What is that?
[ULLR] Do you remember
the Black Fog incident?
A Tartaros Bugman?
[ULLR]
She survived somehow.
You're not Mommy, are you?
You must be the one
who called out to me.
It's because of you that
I was able to grow.
As a thank you, I will take the
cause of this conflict away.
[KIKKO] After that,
there was no stopping
the mutant Canada Goldenrods
from growing all over Japan.
And so, many
superhumans were born.
Because of this, the 48th
year of the Shinka Era
was later referred to as the
"Superhuman Explosion."
Yuko! Let's go!
Okay!
[KIKKO]
As for Human-Man,
he was never again
seen after that day.
[KOMA]
During the Waring States era,
a heroic youngster sped
through the turmoil,
living and dying
to protect Japan
from the Evil Zeth Satan Clan.
Let us join our hearts together.
The time to transform is now!
Come, Jaganosuke!
Arise, Iron Mask!