Here. This is the last
of the uncontaminated stuff.
Thanks.
Briareos. How long are we
gonna have to live like this?
Until we find our paradise.
Oh yeah. Wonder what
I'll do when we find it.
I could work at a fancy
restaurant or better yet,
a bar so I can drink.
Heck, maybe even
settle down and get hitched!
If Karl could only hear you now.
Well, the truth is
I'm way better with this
than with a kitchen
knife anyway.
Olympus. A utopian city
structured around the comfort
and prosperity of its human
inhabitants and maintained by
the artificially created,
genetically-engineered bioroids.
Briareos. Briareos! Briareos!
Awesome. The
forecast got it wrong.
Couldn't ask for
better weather than that!
Hey, Deunan. You ready yet?
Calm down, just another minute.
Okay, all set.
Great.
Well?
Uh. Yeah...
Looks nice. Let's go.
What? That's all
you have to say?
You're sure worked up
over a one-night vacation.
Come in Poseidon Air
M727, this is OAS Control.
Do you copy, Poseidon?
You're off course.
Please adjust to your
flight plan right away.
This is an urgent request.
Do you read me,
Poseidon? Come in.
What's wrong?
M727's veering off course.
They keep getting further
and further off track.
Lance here. Your
request for vacation leave
has been rescinded. Sorry.
What? We put this in months ago!
We need you back at base now.
This is urgent. Understand?
Aw, man. This sucks.
We've just received information
that an ultra-high capacity
passenger plane
flying from Poseidon to
Paris has been hijacked.
As of 13 minutes ago, the
plane dropped communication and
altered its course,
and appears to
be headed straight
for Olympus.
Who's behind it?
From what we've gathered,
it's a group of Human
Liberation Front sympathizers.
They've actively claimed
responsibility for the act
and they're demanding
the immediate release
of their captive allies.
That's just crazy. No country's
gonna offer them asylum.
As for the hostages, they come
to a total of three thousand.
We don't have much intel,
so I need a Hekaton in charge.
I'm leaving it up to
you and Deunan. That's all.
We could've had a nice trip but
you've just gotta be a Hekaton.
I don't want to hear
any whining, Deunan.
Get your asses back here!
So what's the story on
this Human Liberation Front?
Even for human supremacists
they do seem a little extreme,
what with this
"opposing all robotics,
even cyborgs
and bioroids" thing.
Calling them extremists
is putting it lightly.
The life of a
bioroid means about
as much to them as
batteries in a flashlight.
Damn. They're
just modified humans.
I mean sure, they've got
an inhibitor on their emotions
and lifespan, but that's
their only real difference.
Well, that's true.
Bioroids and humans are
essentially the same, but still.
Some people will only
see the differences,
and convince themselves
that these distinctions
make them superior somehow.
So stupid.
Pure-blooded humans are an
endangered species these days.
They commit these acts out of a
desperate fear for preservation.
Not everyone can be a
roll-with-the-punches,
ballsy hellcat like you.
You said the plane
left from Poseidon?
Yes.
Funny how this coincides with
the advance of the Ark Project.
We must not allow anything to
interfere with its completion.
Monitor all
activity from Poseidon.
Right.
They've been rather vocal about
their displeasure
with this project.
The Ark Project
was Gaia's decision.
It's anyone's guess
how it's going to
affect Olympus in the long run.
There's always
the likelihood that
we bioroids may cease to
exist depending on how it fares.
Don't say that.
I know. Regardless
of the project's results,
we must put our faith in
the wisdom of Gaia's guidance.
All we can do is hope that
it will lead to a
prosperous future for mankind.
Briareos!
I'm fine. Just focus
on finding the enemy.
Okay.
A flying pillbox.
Your camouflage is
worthless. I found 'em.
Briareos! You bastards!
Relax, Deunan. Did you forget?
A Hekaton can
plug in and operate
an entire aircraft carrier.
Even with the engines out,
I think I can handle a
passenger plane just fine.
You're sure?
The passengers'
lives take priority.
Don't think about me,
just focus on taking them down.
It's a miracle. He landed it
like it was a walk in the park.
Even with three engines out.
I take it you've
never met a Hekaton before.
If you'll excuse me.
Briareos!
I'm so glad you're okay!
Should you be here?
It's okay, we're from
the Tartaros Center.
My name is Deia Cides,
a Bioroid analyst.
Oh and allow me to
introduce the head of
the next-gen bioroid
project: Mr. Eurys.
Thank you for your
help in retrieving the
3000 frozen embryos.
You're telling me that
the hostages were these?
Once a bioroid ovum
has been fertilized
it's considered
a living organism.
All it needs is to
correctly incubate for growth.
Sounds a bit murky
to me, but okay.
You saved the future
of the next-gen bioroids.
And Olympus as well.
These embryos are
this city's great hope.
Someday they'll help
watch over your paradise here.
The very heart of the
Ark Project is diseased.
Left in the hands of what they
call an "unprocessed" bioroid.
Despite the claim
that these creatures are
no different from
humans, it's not true.
As natural creatures, humans
deserve divinity, not bioroids.
Understand?
No matter what it costs us,
the Ark Project
must not be fulfilled.
We cannot allow
Olympus to see it through.
Bioroids can't grasp
the concept of paradise.
So they couldn't
possibly create one.
Not twenty years
ago, and not now.
I can't take that.
It's important to
me that you have it.
But are you sure?
It means so much to you.
A compass always points north,
regardless of who
holds it in their hand.
Be it man, or bioroid,
cyborg, or even robot.
It will always guide its user
to the same objective truth.
It's something to
have faith in, and to know
it'll always guide us,
on any path we choose.
I'll always look to the
future, and walk toward it,
but only with you by my side.
Alcides.
Let's get married.
You okay?
Yes.
Whoa, nice save, Briareos!
Be aware of your surroundings!
Hey, it worked out, right?
Partners are supposed to
clean up each other's messes!
I'll begin with
the analysis results.
The case likely contained
Argonaut-made parts for
a Damysos device.
The Argonaut, huh?
It's still populated? Last
I heard, Poseidon had bombed
and immobilized the
Argonaut 20 years ago.
It's become somewhat
of a breeding ground for
terrorist cells
since its destruction.
But it's still a
valuable source of intel.
We believe Poseidon has ulterior
motives for keeping it around.
So this is the work of
the Argonauts. If that's true,
this might've been carried
out by someone following in
the footsteps of
their hero, Alcides.
Briareos, look!
Water birds!
Earth to Briareos.
What? What's wrong?
Are you still
thinking about work?
About this morning's
mission, yes.
Oh goody, a lecture.
You should pay more attention
to what's going on around you.
The regular police's
perimeter was full of holes!
It's their fault a civilian
was in the mission zone.
Calm down.
It could've gone badly.
We're on a new team
now, so you need to--
To what? Lose a target
because of those jerks?
Forget it. I don't
need 'em anyway.
Knock it off. Most of them
do have more experience than us.
You need to trust them more!
You can forget about that.
I mean I have faith
in each person's skills...
But you are the only
one I can ever really trust.
If that's your attitude,
you should quit ES.W.A.T. now.
You just don't get it.
For someone with eight eyes,
how are you so
blind when it comes to me?
Deunan is partly
of African descent.
She was only ten when
her mother was killed.
Gunned down while
crossing a street
designated for white people.
After that day, her father,
Karl, drilled all the fighting
and survival skills
into her he could.
You took a real beating.
Briareos.
Here. Try this healing balm.
Thanks.
I wish I could be
somewhere other than here.
Not cut out for this hard life?
Day in and day out,
all I learn is how to
wield a knife,
how to fire a gun.
It was never like this
when I lived with my mom.
Hey. Let's just go
somewhere far away from here.
Somewhere peaceful,
like a paradise.
Do you think such
a place still exists?
If it's there, then
we can find it together.
I know we can. We have to.
Ugh, he's such a jerk!
I ain't goin' home na-night!
Hitomi! I'm gonna
crash here, okay?
Hitomi?
Oh! Hey there, Deunan!
Right, introductions.
This is a bioroid researcher
sent here from Poseidon.
Meet Deia!
It's nice to see you.
Wait a-- Don't I know you?
Shut the hell up! Not goin'!
Why do human
beings get this way?
You wouldn' unnerstand,
you're a bioroid.
It's about
Briareos again, isn't it?
And that's who?
Deunan's man. He's a
Hekatoncheires cyborg!
More like a Heka-don't-care-
about-a-woman's-feelings
cyborg, if ya ask me.
So she's a member of ES.W.A.T?
The explosion caused severe
damage to his entire body.
Briareos. Briareos! Briareos!
Sorry for the trouble.
No trouble.
Happens all the time.
Hitomi seems quite nice.
Well, bioroids are designed
to "serve humans" and all that.
So, how many humans
are there in Olympus?
We're only about twenty
percent of the population.
Even the Olympus administration
is run by Bioroids.
You mentioned you're
from Poseidon, right?
Yes. Please don't jump
to conclusions, though.
I know there's a lot of bad
blood, but I promise you that
not everyone in
Poseidon hates Olympus.
No, no. That's
not what I meant.
You know, it's funny.
Who would've thought we'd
run into each other again.
I never properly thanked
you for saving me earlier.
Ah, forget it. Just doin'
my job. Take care now.
Thanks. You too.
Briareos.
You're nice and warm.
Just talking in her sleep.
I hear the Argonauts have
announced a terrorist attack.
What sort of response
has Poseidon issued?
A man claiming to be the son
of Alcides has taken control of
the group,
expanded its influence,
and now insists on
Argonaut independence.
If armed guerillas
are confirmed to be
hiding among the
Argonauts, I am told that
Poseidon will have no choice but
to exercise the use of force.
Independence, huh? This is
twenty years ago all over again.
I thought the bombardments had
crippled the Argonauts'
technical capabilities, but if
this current threat of theirs
is anything more than mere talk,
then perhaps
they've found a way for
the Bronze Bird
to finally take flight.
The Stymphalean.
A Landmate capable of
leaving the Earth's atmosphere!
We'll be breaking up
a human-smuggling deal.
Our orders are to apprehend
everyone on that list alive.
The dead can't talk.
Do not deviate from
the operation as briefed.
I'm goin' ahead.
Stay on your toes out there!
Ten-Nine, drop!
Ten-Nine! Copy!
Four-Five, we're in!
ES.W.A.T., hands up!
Whaddaya know? This little
rabbit hutch is actually
the Poseidon
ambassador's powder room.
This is an international port!
Technically speaking,
this is sovereign ground.
And you people are in distinct
violation of border statutes!
Chief of Staff approved it.
Yes, well, sadly, your
homeland informed us that,
as of two seconds ago,
your diplomatic privileges
have been suspended.
Poseidon cut me out? What
did the Foreign Minister say?
We can discuss all that
back at our reception room.
Now, if your bodyguard
would kindly stand down--
ES.W.A.T. will
see to your safety.
Magus. Pretty sure
we got somethin' here.
Professor Leon.
International Most Wanted list.
Terrorist engineer with
known ties to the Argonauts.
Vengeance belongeth unto me.
To build a paradise where
people can live as people.
The Argonauts hereby declare
independence from Poseidon!
A Hekatoncheires!
Briareos!
Are you okay?
Deunan. Go.
Go.
If it's there, then
we can find it together.
Guy's no slouch!
What kind of armor is this?
Don't beat yourself up.
Is this really it?
Our paradise?
Yo!
Hey! What's up?
How's it going?
Okay, I guess. You?
I'm back, Yoshitsune!
And early, too!
Welcome home!
Hi Briareos, how're you?
Hitomi. I thought you were
going shopping with Deunan.
No. I've been
gone for three days.
I did a stint at
the Legislative Bureau.
Listen up, Deunan! When you
move left, watch the right.
When you move up, watch below.
Take in all your surroundings!
Damn it.
Don't look at the target,
just pull the trigger!
Eliminate anyone
who looks suspicious!
Keep your eyes open!
If this were real,
you'd be dead two times over!
Karl, would you let
her take a break already?
How many times do I have
to tell you? Watch your back!
No one else will do it for you!
That's enough, Karl!
What the hell are you doing?
The poor girl can't
take much more of this!
Is something wrong? Briareos!
Deunan.
Earlier, you--
I what?
Uh, never mind.
You can be such a weirdo.
She's probably just
getting it overhauled.
If she was in the
Ladon River district,
I bet she took it to Ceryneia.
Ceryneia?
Yeah, it's a gun shop.
The police buy their
weapons there wholesale.
You never heard of it?
Supposedly they're
the best around
when it comes to
firearm maintenance.
The owner is a
bioroid named Lark
and from what I hear he's
pretty popular with the ladies.
This is a rare piece, even
for a custom Government model.
It's got the original slide and
frame, but it looks as though
everything else
has been replaced.
I take it you prefer
rubber grips, Deunan?
No, that was my dad's gun.
I keep it as a memento.
I'll be careful with it.
Karl.
I don't understand why
you keep pushing her so hard!
Karl? Are you
even listening to me?
Is that...?
She's my daughter and the
only family that I have left.
She may think I'm a monster
now but what kind of father
would I be if I didn't teach
her how to protect herself?
Deunan's not ready
to handle life on her own.
So if anything
ever happens to me,
she's in your hands, Briareos.
All of the bioroids
in Olympus are bred
and managed right
here at the Tartaros Center.
They're essentially clones
created from human genes that
have been altered to
promote specific physical
and character traits.
Basically, their
hardware is human
but their internal
software is not.
I would liken them to
sophisticated precision robots
but then I suppose
I'm a little biased,
since I am a bioroid myself.
Here we are.
And what would
you want with him?
Sorry. Lark Ceryne. Ah.
He's a bioroid created with
Karl Knute and Alcide's genes.
That's quite an
impressive combination.
Bioroids crafted from superior
human genes, such as this one,
are widely considered
the ideal citizens for
the utopian city of Olympus.
Yeah, sure. Because, unlike
humans, they're perfect, right?
I assure you,
they're far from perfect.
After all, if they were,
they wouldn't commit
suicide, would they?
Bioroids don't
consider life a gift.
Instead, they
see it as their duty.
Self-abandonment
is the only way
they can avoid
that responsibility.
It's the only way
they can truly be free.
Would you call that perfect?
You were out late.
Uh, yeah. I'm sorry.
So, where's your
Government model?
I decided to get
it overhauled. Why?
You have a problem with that?
Maybe I do.
C'mon, Briareos.
Karl's gun. It's the only
memento you have of your father
and you left it
with that Lark guy.
How did you know that?
What, have you
been spying on me?
I can't believe this!
Don't you trust me?
What's wrong with
caring about your partner?
Ugh, nothing! Except when
"caring" means snooping around
and prying into my life!
You're my boyfriend,
not my parent, okay?
I'm just looking out for you!
Give me a break.
You're just pissed
because, for once,
I want to do things my way!
I swear, you're no
different than my shitty dad!
You don't mean that.
Whatever! I'm outta here!
A fixed rate of bioroid
suicides is to be expected.
But, the number of
cases over the past year
has exceeded
Gaia's projections.
The administration's
starting to get concerned that
this might be a
terrorist plot in action.
So they called ES.W.A.T.
in to investigate.
And?
It took a while but we finally
put all the pieces together.
What's crazy is Deunan's
right smack dab in
the middle of the puzzle.
Thanks again for dinner.
But you didn't have to
take me out, you know?
I was just doing my job.
Well, I appreciate it and
this is my way of saying thanks.
That gun. It was a memento
from your father, right?
Yeah. But honestly,
he was a shitty dad.
Hey, now.
It's true! When I
was a kid he had me
taking apart rifles instead
of playing with blocks.
I had to go through
close-quarters combat with
elite soldiers if I
wanted to play "house".
I mean, can you imagine?
But if it weren't for all
that combat training he put me
through, I never would've
made it this far in life.
If I could, I'd thank him,
but he left for the war
and he never made it back.
I've heard stories about
him. The hero, Karl Knute.
Briareos was in the same unit.
In fact, he's the one who
brought my dad's
gun back for me.
I'm honored that you trusted
me with it. Thanks, Deunan.
Thanks for joining me.
I had a great time tonight.
I did, too. I'm sorry
I can't take you home.
I gotta get back to work.
I'll see ya.
'Night.
So, who's the next target?
It's me.
The cops showed up at
Tartaros just as I was leaving.
Unfortunately, if they're on
to me, it won't be long 'til
they come for you.
I'm afraid the jig is up.
They've linked me to
the bioroid suicide cases.
They know the victims
were under my supervision.
It's over.
You saw right through me
from the beginning, didn't you?
Assisted bioroid suicide?
Does it really come
as a surprise to you?
He's unprocessed, just like me.
I'm amazed he's
even made it this far.
I've been told that the humans
consider Olympus a paradise.
But let me assure you,
that wouldn't be the case if
it weren't for the
bioroids slaving away
to carry out Gaia's intentions.
In this utopian city,
not everything is perfect;
there are those of
us who are anomalies;
bioroids with deadly impulses.
They realize they're defective
and that this place would be
better off without them,
but their "programming"
keeps them from
committing suicide.
And you think that gives
you the right to kill them?
Don't act like I'm some
kind of deranged murderer.
These flawed bioroids are simply
acquiescing to their genetics,
and in turn, I'm
optimizing our society by
granting their wishes. I
don't see what the problem is.
I'm genetically driven to
maintain this place for you.
You could say I did
this for the sake of
you humans and your paradise.
Know what I'd say?
You should have
optimized society by
offing yourself first.
Maybe you're right, but think
how many unstable bioroids
there'd be, and how much
damage they might cause.
I like to think this impulse
of mine comes from your father.
Briareos!
You all right?
So you were out to
catch this guy all along?
I couldn't
have a bioroid with
my dad's genes
murdering innocent people.
Karl may not have
been the best dad,
but he wasn't a
cold-blooded killer.
Why did you
have to get involved?
I didn't need your help. I
could've handled it on my own.
I was just trying to keep you
safe. I have to protect you.
Oh, really? For how long?
You're not going to be
able to protect me forever.
Partners are supposed to see
each other as equals, Briareos.
I'm sorry but there's nothing
you can say to change my mind.
I've always been
there watching over you.
Well, you can stop now.
I've had enough.
Come on.
I don't need you to protect me.
I'm a big girl. I
can take care of myself.
Deunan. Whether you like it or
not, I have to look out for you.
I'm home!
Who does the baby belong to?
Me and Yoshitsune!
Surprised, aren't you?
You can't, though!
No, a member of
the Legislative Bureau
asked me to babysit today.
Wait a minute, so,
it's a bioroid, like you?
Mhmmm. I know, it's
rather unusual, isn't it?
You don't see
many baby bioroids.
10-9. Emergency mission.
This is similar to the tracking
implants we sometimes use to
chip bioroids, except that
this one is biodegradable.
Two weeks from now, it'll
have completely dissolved.
It takes two hours to calibrate,
so try to relax 'til then.
Thanks, Deia.
Not that it'll matter to
me, but if I turn up dead,
at least ES.W.A.T. will know
it sooner rather than later.
A dangerous job,
in other words?
What is that?
The compass on
your desk. Looks old.
Ah.
It belonged to my late husband.
Something of his
I kept as a memento.
Oh. I'm sorry.
It happened a
long time ago. I'm okay.
By the way, I ran
into your partner.
He seemed pretty worried.
You know, one
day you might wake up
and it'll too
late to clear the air.
So, uh? How did you lose him?
What?
I've been meaning to ask you.
Whenever I've needed
to vent about my dad,
or 'bout Briareos, you've
always been there for me.
I'd like to return the favor.
A compass always points north,
regardless of who holds it.
Be it man, or bioroid,
cyborg, or even robot.
It will always guide its user
to the same objective truth.
You lost me. Sorry.
Sorry. It's just
something he used to say.
And whenever I see
Hitomi, and Briareos,
and you getting
along, it rings true.
Now be a good girl
and patch things up with him.
Briareos.
That solo mission to
infiltrate the Argonauts.
You're turning it down, right?
I'm not turning it down.
Lance chose me for this.
What're you so worried about?
If that giant Landmate
turns out to be more than talk,
you're going to be outgunned.
Lance gave me the thumbs-up.
If you want to tell
him he's wrong, go ahead.
Look, I'm just gonna say it.
You can't handle this one alone.
And that's why I have to go.
As long as you see me this
way, we can never be together.
Since when have I been helpless?
When did things change?
Back when I was
living with my mom,
even when I was
being forced to train with
knives and guns every damn day,
you never treated me like this.
I just want to keep
you safe. Like Karl.
Karl was an awful
dad and you know it!
Deunan. I know you think--
If we can't be equals,
then we're through.
Damn it.
I, Hyllus, ask my fellow
Argonauts to heed these words!
As the son of our
great founder, Alcides,
and the inheritor of his will,
I implore you on
behalf of my father!
See that your talents
and soul carry on!
Dummy. I told ya
that was too many.
Uh-uh. I can handle it.
You're gonna drop 'em.
Here.
Uh, thank you.
Go on. Thank her.
Thanks a lot.
Pollux!
You need to
work out those arms.
Yeah, right. Thanks, Briareos.
Eleven-three here.
Moving from Point C to F.
Copy that, Eleven-three.
Four-five en route
to Point F, as well.
You might wanna get your head
in the game. I'm just sayin'.
Yeah. Sorry.
Still got Deunan
on the brain, huh, man?
A cyborg?
Not half bad, for a girl.
Guess I was good enough
to get the drop on you!
Is that what you
think just happened?
Huh?
Isn't that the big-shot
Poseidon doctor over there?
Wonder what that car
inspection's all about.
Peekaboo! You like that?
So, what's with the luggage?
Officer. It's good to see you.
Briareos, please!
You have to help me!
Huh?
I really need a babysitter!
It's just for one day!
I'm on duty. No can do.
Deia's going back to Poseidon
and I-- I can't take
care of it by myself!
Heading home to Poseidon, eh?
I am. My time here was short
but I've really enjoyed
all the people that I've met.
Not again! It's okay, you're
fine! So no crying, okay?
Seriously, no more crying.
I can't handle this.
Thanks.
Thank you!
Forget her.
Problem?
You shouldn't make those
boys do your dirty work.
Don't give me that look.
Those boys were defending
their home, that's all.
I gotta say, you know how
to make a girl feel welcome.
A Colt Government.
You're packing
quite the antique, miss.
I keep it for good
luck. It was my dad's.
Really? I knew a man
named Karl Knute who used to
carry that very same model.
Wait, so you knew my dad?
You're Karl's daughter?
I guess it's been twenty
years now, if it's been a day,
but our hero Alcides and your
father were as thick as thieves.
Why would my father
befriend a terrorist?
Alcides was no
terrorist, little girl.
All around the world, bioroids
are the slaves of industry--
and nowhere is this
more true than in Olympus.
Alcides founded the
Argonauts in the hopes of
carving out a paradise where
people could live like people,
no matter how
they were created.
Where technological
advancement was won by
the sweat of our
brows, side by side.
That was the challenge
we'd taken up if
we wanted to change our future.
There could be
failures along the way,
but the resulting success
would be a triumph of humanity.
We were all ablaze with
Alcides' vision of paradise.
If anything, our
technology grew grander by
leaps and bounds as
we grasped for that ideal.
This culminated in our
magnum opus, the Stymphalean.
An enormous
Landmate designed for
the rigors of
deployment in outer space.
The Stymphalean was
such an accomplishment
it eclipsed anything Poseidon
had made, and suddenly,
we Argonauts were on the map.
No surprise what happened next.
In order to safeguard the tech
and those who made
it from outside forces.
Alcides declared the
Argonaut an independent state.
Obviously, Posiedon
was having none of that.
Soon we were
besieged by pirates
looking to claim
the Stymphalean.
Operatives from
the major nations,
and soldiers-of-fortune
of every stripe.
As a result,
Alcides brought in
your old man as a
defense consultant.
Tell me something. The
entire world is gunning for
the Argonauts.
Is this voyage of yours
really going to better mankind?
It's hard to say. Still.
I think it's too late
for peace at this point.
It is my destiny to
remain with my people.
I must live out my life
as the hero they deserve.
Karl. Say that you'll join me.
It's tempting, but
I have to return home.
The situation there's
only getting worse.
So what is it you
hope to accomplish?
Gotta look out for my own.
Your wife?
I have a little girl on the way.
The world's a hell of a place,
so I'm gonna toughen her up.
That way, she'll
live through anything.
With those words,
Karl left the Argonauts.
All that time, was he
just trying to keep me safe?
I just want to keep
you safe. Like Karl.
Around that same time,
a bioroid took to
calling the Argonaut home.
Along with a
woman from Poseidon.
A Poseidon woman, really?
It wasn't too long before
Alcides fell in love with her,
and she became pregnant.
Hyllus, I assume?
No. Hyllus is
nothing more than
a bioroid created
from Alcides's genes.
Huh?
Poseidon attacked us one night.
Alcides shielded the mother
of his unborn child with
his own body, and met his end.
Humanity may very well be the
god who created the bioroids...
but this does not mean
that humanity is their ruler.
But nothing can stop the
god of jealousy's scheming.
So the hero murdered the ruler.
Thus, the voyage of the
Argonauts came to an end.
Plate tectonics stole the
waves out from underneath us,
leaving the ship to
rust in a sea of sand.
But Alcides left
his people with more than
just memories to
show for his leadership.
So, you're telling
me that it's real?
Your outer-space Landmate?
Isn't that what
you came here to find?
Suppose there's
no harm in showing you.
Huh?
There she sits.
That's the Stymphalean?
But it's just a pile of junk!
That thing can't even stand up,
much less fly into outer space.
What you demean as junk--
I consider our hope.
In the words of Alcides:
"Protect not the
things you cherish
but the means to make them."
Our people wield
the knowledge to
repair that broken
Landmate, and they shall!
That's enough, Hyllus.
Your pride will bring
calamity raining down on us.
I didn't lengthen my life
with this contraption just to
watch some cocksure upstart
jeopardize the Argonauts.
I am the son of Alcides
and the inheritor of his will!
I don't know if you were sent
here from Olympus or Poseidon,
miss, but either way, if Hyllus
were created by your people
and sent here
to stir up trouble,
I wouldn't be a bit surprised.
If you declare independence,
you know that Poseidon
will try to destroy you.
That's a price I'm glad to pay.
A hero must glorify the name
of his people the world over.
A hero looks out for the people
they're supposed to protect!
What do you know of heroism?
"Vengeance belongeth unto me."
Who's there?
Alcides?
Hyllus!
No!
How can you be so blind?
Poseidon's plans
to attack the Argonauts
have just been called off.
Turns out they got some intel,
that confirms the terrorist
ringleader's been killed.
Aw, we're all dressed
up and nowhere to go?
What's going on?
An accident?
Oh man!
No way!
Magus, Liesse and Baxter!
I want you three
suited up in the Guges Ds
and in the air, A-SAP!
Gina, Grigg and Briareos,
put your heads together
and focus on getting
that coded signal deciphered!
You got two hours
to figure it out.
Lance. I want you to send
me up with the strike force.
I've given you your orders.
The others know what
they're doing up there.
You need to trust 'em more!
You need to trust them more!
You can forget about that.
I mean, I have faith
in each person's skills.
But you are the only
one I can ever really trust.
If that's your attitude,
you should quit ES.W.A.T. now.
You just don't get it.
For someone with eight eyes,
how are you so blind
when it comes to me?
After we're done with this, take
me out for a fancy dinner, okay?
This might not be our idea of
paradise, but we can at least
have a nice meal
every once in a while.
I'm guessing you
have someplace in mind?
This place Hitomi told me about.
She says it has this
totally incredible view
of the city at night.
S'fine with me, but I
don't think a place like that
is gonna serve the burgers
and fries you call a nice meal.
Quit making me out to sound
like some kind of savage!
Where ever would
I get that idea?
"Sometime early this morning,
the Human Liberation Front
will mount an
assault on Tartaros."
"If our demands are
not met within six hours,
the Stymphalean will
utterly annihilate Olympus."
"Know that the Stymphalean
will be armed with
a 20-kiloton nuclear
warhead. It's your move."
What do they want?
For Tartaros to shut off their
cryo equipment for a full day.
If the cryo goes down,
Poseidon is prime to
lose decades of progress.
Our options?
The Stymphalean is being
maneuvered by remote control.
ES.W.A.T. is trying to subvert
its communication system.
I'll want to
get Urban Planning's
take on the situation.
Convene the Legislative
Bureau and the Senate.
I'll need to consult with Gaia.
They've measured the intercept
capabilities of Olympus
and determined that an external
foray would be impossible.
So I guess that hijack incident
was just a practice run, huh?
It still takes some balls to
aim straight for
the urban area like this.
How'd they even
get that thing this far?
All right, Gina,
why don't you tell me
what you've got
on this damn thing.
Its comms link randomly switches
between transmission modes.
Back and forth between radio,
optical and acoustic
every billionth of a second.
There's only one way to stop it.
Kill the power to
every one of those systems
and leave it dead in the air.
Damn it, this is crazy.
Bad news, guys. That Landmate
topside is a Hekatoncheires.
What's the deal
with this signal, huh?
It sounds like a
fixed rhythm at first blush,
but it keeps
changing ever so slightly.
Y'know, it reminds
me of something.
A heartbeat?
No, this isn't real! We were
going to find paradise together.
You promised me!
I'm going to need you to sign
this, ma'am. Cyborg consent.
Huh?
Without the hardware,
I'm afraid he has no chance of
surviving these
injuries. I'm sorry.
You're telling
me he's gonna die?
I'm not going to
let that happen. Never!
Deunan.
That pulse is
Deunan's heartbeat!
They're using her heartbeat
to encode their comm signal.
It matches up perfectly
with my data cache.
Briareos.
Olympus!
The city is--
Not Olympus, it's our
only chance at paradise!
There is no
such thing as paradise.
Huh?
In their heart of hearts,
people don't trust one another.
Mankind almost destroyed
itself over it once already,
and absolutely
nothing has changed.
How could paradise possibly
exist in such a faithless place?
Our primary objective now is
to cut that Landmate's strings.
But what about Deunan?
When forced to weigh the life
of a single special unit member
against the tens of thousands
of Olympus citizens, I'm sorry,
but I think the
choice is pretty clear.
Even he understands that.
I need you on sniper duty.
Where are you going?
To do what has to
be done. Where else?
There is no
such thing as paradise.
Fifteen minutes until Tartaros
is within bombing range--
Hurry it up out there.
"Vengeance belongeth unto me."
Alcides shielded the mother
of his unborn child with
his own body, and met his end.
Briareos!
What're you doing?
My heart.
See how the good people of
Olympus reward
you for your service?
I assume they've
discovered the unique role
your heartbeat plays
in our current drama.
See how they turn on you?
They'd just as soon put
a bullet in you as save you.
He wouldn't.
Deunan.
I never realized it,
but at some point I took on
Karl's mindset as my own.
And that's not what you
need from me. I know that now.
If I'm going to protect you,
I have to protect all of you.
Watch your ass
out there, eleven-three!
Don't get so hung
up on the sniping that
you forget to dodge
that bastard's attacks!
Deunan, whether you like it or
not, I have to look out for you.
It'll kill you if
you get any closer.
So, for once,
I'm gonna protect you!
Briareos. How long are we
gonna have to live like this?
Until we find our
paradise, same as always.
He did it.
I'm not reading a heartbeat.
The encryption is
gone. And we're in.
We've gained access to the
Stymphalean's command functions.
ES.W.A.T. control
at 60% and rising.
Steer it to the intercept
point within Olympus.
Coordinates 45-25-29. Let's
take that warhead out of play.
Roger that.
It's over. Step out of the
Landmate with your hands up.
Deia!
You could have
saved the woman you loved,
but you blew her
heart out instead?
You've become quite the
obedient machine, haven't you?
But how? Your heart,
it stopped beating-- I saw it!
I mean, even if a Hekatonchieres
can snipe accurately enough to
stop your heart, how on Earth
did you come back from that?
If there's one
thing in this world
my old man taught
me how to do, it's live!
Defending the place
we worked so hard to reach.
And giving this
life everything we've got.
No bullet is going
to cut that short.
So you gambled on
Deunan's will to survive,
that she inherited
her father's instincts.
Genes aren't what saved me.
He took the shot for
the same reason I jumped,
to protect what needs
protecting! Our paradise!
Paradise.
I can't take that.
It's important to
me that you to have it.
But are you sure?
It means so much to you.
A compass always points north,
regardless of who
holds it in their hand.
Be it man, or bioroid,
cyborg, or even robot.
It will always guide its user
to the same objective truth.
It's something
to have faith in,
and to know it'll always guide
us, on any path we choose.
He always spoke of
paradise, too. Of a dream.
You mean you were Alcides'--?
The inheritor of Alcides'
will could never be a bioroid.
Are you trying to
tell me that that's why?
That you're doing this for him?
That this is what he wanted?
Alcides no longer exists.
These bioroids carrying the same
genes as him, they're puppets.
I refuse to let
his genes be used to
create these
unnatural abominations.
I won't let him
be exploited like that.
I refuse to let him be defiled.
Paradise is a fairy tale.
No, stop!
You can't
counter-hack the system!
You'll burn out your cortex!
We lost control
of the Stymphalean
but I'm not sure how!
Stop this, Deia!
They stole my
paradise and my beloved.
And I will pay them
back a thousandfold!
Stand down, Deia! The
next one goes in your head!
How I envy you!
Your man is still alive.
Deia!
Briareos! Move! Get
outta that thing's airspace!
We're taking it down!
Bioroids have never
experienced paradise,
so they couldn't
possibly create one.
Not twenty years
ago, and not now.
In that moment, were you
afraid you were going to die?
Were you afraid?
I felt like I
did it to protect you.
I know you did.
You said you'd
protect me no matter what.
That includes what I love.
I know that now.
Honestly.
I'm just thankful
you're still alive.
One day it'll be too
late to clear the air.
Poor Deia.
She told us she lost her family.
She lied about a lot, but
I think that part was true.
Long before we ever
knew her, Deia had someone who
made her life worth living.
Sounds familiar.
Want to hit the road again?
Of course. We haven't found
what we're looking for yet.
A goodwill ambassador
from Poseidon has traveled to
Olympus to profess
friendly relations between
her people and ours.
That looks like!
Deia.
A hero once attempted to
steal the treasure of a ruler.
But instead fell
in love with the ruler,
and the two had a child.
However, the god of jealousy
doesn't give up that easily.
And the scheme festered until
the hero murdered the ruler.
And fled with the treasure.
You've fought valiantly
to claim your treasure,
but you're not finished.
Deia.