♪ opening song ♪
Look at that cute face.
He has your eyes.
How impatient do you have to be
to run a predictive simulation?
People have always dreamed
of creating paradise.
But I've found it.
Spending my life with you.
And raising our child together.
That's it.
Deia.
A goodwill ambassador from
Poseidon, Deia Cides,
has traveled to Olympus
to profess friendly
relations between her
people and ours.
Deia.
It's okay.
Don't you cry, Mommy's here.
See, it's all better now.
Yeah, there's
nothing to cry about.
You're pretty good
at all this mom stuff.
Deia gave me some pointers.
Deia?
Just before she
left for Poseidon.
Deia's got a way with babies.
It's kind of incredible.
I was always led to
believe that bioroids
don't have maternal
instincts programming.
Turns out we do.
Well, it's not much different
than the childcare
guidelines given to us.
But it's all so new to me.
I wasn't raised by a mother,
so it's not like I
have much experience.
Oh, I wanted to ask you.
What exactly is a real
mother like, anyway?
Sorry, that came out weird.
What was your mom like?
As of yesterday at O-800
hours, Deia Cides
has traveled from
Poseidon to Olympus.
The administration
plans to cordially
welcome her as an ambassador.
Can't we just arrest her?
It couldn't be more
obvious that she
masterminded the
terrorist attack.
Deunan and Briareos saw it.
Poseidon's covered her ass.
They claim that
the terrorist is dead.
Which means we're powerless
to do anything unless we can
present 100% irrefutable
evidence Deia Cides
was behind the attack.
Makes me sick to my
stomach to think that
a terrorist is acting
as an ambassador.
They're labeling this as a
goodwill visit, but her main
objective is to help warm her
country's reception to the
"Ark project" that
Olympus is developing,
and maybe get
Poseidon on board.
The deep space project?
Aren't they trying to create a
spaceship capable of long-term
self sufficiency, in
order to explore the
outer reaches of the
cosmos or something?
And unsurprisingly, you need
the most capable leader
possible in charge of
such an enormous craft.
Gaia's currently
narrowed the selection
down to ten candidates.
In other news, the Tartaros
Center is reporting that
three thousand frozen
embryos stored
at its facilities
were destroyed.
Assassinated during
an armored transport.
A lack of immuno-processing
resulting in death.
Of these ten candidates,
seven of them have perished from
transparently suspicious causes.
Only three remain.
So we think the
"goodwill ambassador"
is secretly offing the
candidates, do we?
At the orders of Poseidon?
The Chief of Staff has
assigned us to protect
one of the three
remaining candidates.
Councilman Theseus of
the New Poseidon Party.
He also happens to
bear Alcides' Genes.
He's traveling with
his wife and daughter.
They're scheduled to
meet with Deia Cides
at a hotel in the
city tomorrow.
The moment the councilman
is under our authority,
you're to take the K2s and
provide 24-hour security
for him and his family.
Thank you for inviting
me to Olympus.
It's no exaggeration when
people say it's the
most beautiful place
in the world.
As an ambassador of goodwill,
I offer my gratitude.
And we extend to you
our warmest welcome.
We're pleased to have you.
I hope you can
overlook the construction.
It's only been two
months since the attack.
And yet you've already
managed to rebuild so much.
Bioroids are extraordinary.
To say the least.
We're nothing but tools to
assist the needs of humanity.
You say that, and
yet Gaia requires a
bioroid for the Ark
Project, isn't that so?
A completely unprocessed
bioroid, to be specific.
They're physically
identical to humans.
Which makes it even worse.
They want a perfect bioroid.
Not an unstable human.
Tell me, ambassador.
What is it that's brought
you to where you are today?
The well being
of our two nations.
You misunderstand.
What is it that you want?
What's brought you
to this point in your life?
The treasure of the
queen's girdle, I suppose.
What?
There's a tale of a man
who plotted to steal
a queen's treasure, but he fell
in love with her instead.
And they had a child together.
However, the goddess of
jealousy manipulated the man.
Not only did she trick him
into stealing the treasure,
but also into
murdering the queen.
The man was grief-stricken
with remorse
when he realized
what he had done.
And this relates, how?
Nevermind.
It's just an old story.
Papa, look!
Beautiful.
Subject is clear.
Line of sight?
Clear.
No obstructions.
Mechanical sweep?
Clear.
There's no sign of
acoustics, thermals,
or any type of jamming.
Are we prepared
for a Hekaton attack?
Prepared enough to hold
them off, assuming they
don't have any other
tricks up their sleeves.
Each member of the security
team is a full-blooded human.
So the only chance of
bioroid interference would
come from beyond the
secure perimeter.
Personnel confirmation.
All hotel employees
were properly screened?
Yes, sir.
Just to be safe,
we screened Theseus' wife
and daughter as well.
As expected, they were a
perfect match with the
bioroid genes in
cryo-storage at Tartaros.
I hope you have no
objection to a security check.
Of course not.
Go right ahead.
We appreciate your cooperation.
I appreciate your thoroughness.
Now I can rest easy.
Hey, Briareos.
Is this something
we should use a
coded communication
channel to discuss?
Y'know, Deia.
She's apparently really
good with children.
Don't let your personal feelings
cloud your judgment on this.
That won't happen.
She's coming.
No sign of jamming.
She's not connected
to the outside.
Don't let your guard down.
Her left arm's functional.
Subject has entered
the meeting room.
The goddess of jealousy
manipulated the man.
Not only did she trick him
into stealing the treasure,
but also into
murdering the queen.
Following the schedule,
the meeting is
due to end any minute now.
Status update.
Hotel employees clear.
Maintaining surveillance for
detection of unplanned contact.
All terminals clear.
Situation normal.
Surroundings clear.
Clear.
Activity normal.
If she's gonna make a move.
This is her
last chance to do it.
Keep your eyes on her.
Subject is now clear.
She didn't try anything.
Her role as ambassador
must have taken priority.
All terminals clear.
Proximity clear.
Downgrading to security level B.
They've reduced
the threat level.
Why don't you take a break?
Go get some fresh air?
We've still got a
long night ahead of us.
Yeah, thanks.
That sounds good.
I heard you like kids.
That you're good with them.
Hitomi told me.
She asked me to help
out and give her
a hand when my
assignment's over.
These bioroids raising children.
It's unnatural.
They're not human.
They're basically objects.
Or perhaps like
these butterflies.
A species with no purpose.
They have no business existing.
And yet here they are.
It's perverse,
and I refuse to accept it.
I assume that includes Hitomi?
You really feel that way?
You honestly believe
that bioroids don't
even deserve the
right to exist?
All I see are normal people
with families they love.
How are they different from us?
They're only capable of
mimicking emotion, like puppets.
It's hollow.
There's no worry or fear
behind their placid smiles.
It doesn't even matter
if they lose their families.
They can simply collect
a replacement with
the same characteristics
as the last one.
Bioroids are an abomination of
everything it means to be human.
You told me that
you lost your family.
I lost my mother too,
when I was just a child.
We were walking down a street.
And somebody shot
her in the back.
Gunned her down because
her skin was a different color.
Don't compare what we've lost.
Your sadness
doesn't interest me.
It's dishonest.
The genuine sadness
of losing someone you love.
It produces hate.
Sadness devoid of hatred,
is just a plea for pity.
You're saying the
pain I felt wasn't real?
Tell me this.
Imagine, you lost
the man you loved.
If it was your fault,
would you be unchanged?
Do you think you're the only
one who understands loss?
And the feelings of everyone
else are somehow beneath yours?
What's wrong with you?
Do you think you're
some kind of a god?
Nothing you can say
is ever going to
convince me that I'm wrong.
But you can try to stop me.
Just stay right there.
That's it.
You're gonna be just fine.
There.
Hold on.
Your sadness
doesn't interest me.
It's dishonest.
Bioroids are an abomination of
everything it means to be human.
Deia.
Deia!
I'm sorry.
But this is technically
considered Poseidon soil.
Deia.
I don't care how much
pain you've been through.
I won't let you
turn our paradise
into a stage for your revenge.
♪ closing song ♪