Olympus. A utopian city
structured around the comfort
and prosperity of its human
inhabitants, and maintained by
the artificially created,
genetically-engineered bioroids.
An Argonaut-created
Landmate designed for
outer space deployment.
It's beautiful.
Oh! Hey there, Deunan!
Right, introductions.
This is a bioroid researcher
sent here from Poseidon.
Meet Deia!
Nice to meet you,
Deunan. I'm Deia Cides.
Shut the hell up! Not goin'!
Why do human
beings get this way?
You wouldn' unnerstand,
you're a bioroid.
It's about Briareos
again, isn't it?
And that's who?
Deunan's man. He's a
Hekatoncheires cyborg!
More like a Heka-don't-care-
about-a-woman's-feelings
cyborg, if ya ask me.
Sorry for the trouble.
No trouble.
Happens all the time.
Hitomi seems quite nice.
Well, bioroids are designed
to "serve humans" and all that.
So, how many humans
are there in Olympus?
We're only about twenty
percent of the population.
Even the Olympus administration
is run by Bioroids.
You know, it's funny,
who would've thought
we'd run into each other again?
I never properly thanked
you for saving me earlier.
Ah, forget it. Just
doin' my job. Take care now.
Thanks. You too.
Briareos.
You're nice and warm.
Just talking in her sleep.
Bioroids can't grasp
the concept of paradise,
so they couldn't
possibly create one.
Not twenty years
ago, and not now.
I'll begin with
the analysis results.
The case likely contained
Argonaut-made parts
for a Damysos device.
The Argonaut, huh?
It's still populated? Last
I heard, Poseidon had bombed
and immobilized the
Argonaut 20 years ago.
Yes, but it's become somewhat
of a breeding ground for
terrorist cells
since it was destroyed
and is still a
valuable source of intel.
A double-edged sword.
It's hard to believe that old
derelict is all that remains of
this once mighty
"Mobile Corporate City".
Alcides founded the Argonauts
in the hopes of carving out
a paradise where people
could live like people,
no matter how
they were created.
Where technological
advancement was won by
the sweat of our
brows, side by side.
That was the challenge
we'd taken up if we wanted to
change our future. There could
be failures along the way,
but the resulting success
would be a triumph of humanity.
We were all ablaze with
Alcides' vision of paradise.
If anything, our
technology grew grander by
leaps and bounds as
we grasped for that ideal.
This culminated in our
magnum opus, the Stymphalean.
An enormous Landmate
designed for the rigors of
deployment in outer space.
The Stymphalean was
such an accomplishment,
it eclipsed anything Poseidon
had made, and suddenly,
we Argonauts were on the map.
No surprise what happened next.
In order to
safeguard the tech
and those who made
it from outside forces,
Alcides declared the
Argonaut an independent state.
Obviously, Posiedon
was having none of that.
Soon we were besieged by
pirates looking to
claim the Stymphalean.
Operatives from
the major nations,
and soldiers-of-fortune
of every stripe.
Bad news, guys. That Landmate
topside is a Hekatoncheires.
"Vengeance belongeth unto me."
Please tell me you have a plan.
Even if we give
in to their demands,
the Ark Project will
not survive a thawing-out.
Go, Eurys. Keep Tartaros's
gene banks operational.
You know what
we'll lose if they fail.
Decide what to prioritize
in the event of disaster.
Meanwhile, I'm
placing the future of
this city in
ES.W.A.T.'s hands.
You can't
counter-hack the system!
You'll burn out your cortex!
Stand down, Deia! The
next one goes in your head!
How I envy you!
Your man is still alive!
Deia!
Briareos! Move! Get
outta that thing's airspace!
We're taking it down!
It's like she dropped into
our lives from out of nowhere.
Just who exactly are you, Deia?
Being here with you
two, it reminds me of
a time when I
used to be happy.
You're not happy now?
I ran into your partner.
He seemed pretty worried.
You know, one
day you might wake up
and it'll be too
late to clear the air.
It's okay. Don't
you cry. Mommy's here.
See, it's all better now. Yeah,
there's nothing to cry about.
You're pretty good
at all this mom stuff.
Deia gave me some pointers.
Deia?
Just before she
left for Poseidon.
Deia's got a way with babies.
It's kind of incredible. I
was always led to believe that
bioroids don't have
maternal instincts programming.
Turns out we do.
Well, it's not much different
than the childcare guidelines
given to us. But
it's all so new to me.
I wasn't raised by a mother,
so it's not like I
have much experience.
Oh, I wanted to ask you.
What exactly is a
real mother like, anyway?
Sorry, that came out weird.
What was your mom like?
As of yesterday at O-800 hours,
Deia Cides has traveled
from Poseidon to Olympus.
The administration plans to
cordially welcome
her as an ambassador.
Can't we just arrest her?
It couldn't be
more obvious that
she masterminded
the terrorist attack.
Deunan and Briareos saw it.
Poseidon's covered her ass.
They claim that
the terrorist is dead.
Which means we're powerless
to do anything unless
we can present 100%
irrefutable evidence
Deia Cides was
behind the attack.
Makes me sick to
my stomach to think that
a terrorist is
acting as an ambassador.
Thank you for
inviting me to Olympus.
It's no exaggeration
when people say it's
the most beautiful
place in the world.
As an ambassador of
goodwill, I offer my gratitude.
And we extend to
you our warmest welcome.
We're pleased to have you.
I hope you can
overlook the construction.
It's only been two
months since the attack.
And yet you've already
managed to rebuild so much.
Bioroids are extraordinary,
to say the least.
We're nothing but tools to
assist the needs of humanity.
You say that, and yet
Gaia requires a Bioroid for
the Ark Project, isn't that so?
A completely unprocessed
bioroid, to be specific.
They're physically
identical to humans.
Which makes it even worse.
They want a perfect bioroid,
not an unstable human.
Tell me, ambassador.
What is it that's brought
you to where you are today?
The wellbeing
of our two nations.
You misunderstand.
What is it that you want?
What's brought you to
this point in your life?
The treasure of the
queen's girdle, I suppose.
What?
There's a tale of
a man who plotted to
steal a queen's treasure, but he
fell in love with her instead.
And they had a child together.
However, the goddess of
jealousy manipulated the man.
Not only did she trick him
into stealing the treasure,
but also into murdering
the queen. The man was
grief-stricken with remorse when
he realized what he had done.
And this relates, how?
Nevermind. It's
just an old story.
They're labeling
this as a goodwill visit,
but her main objective is
to help warm her country's
reception to the "Ark Project"
that Olympus is developing,
and maybe get
Poseidon on board.
The deep space project?
Aren't they trying to create a
spaceship capable of long-term
self-sufficiency, in order to
explore the outer reaches
of the cosmos or something?
And unsurprisingly, you need
the most capable leader possible
in charge of such
an enormous craft.
Gaia's currently narrowed the
selection down
to ten candidates.
In other news, the Tartaros
Center is reporting that
three thousand
frozen embryos stored at
its facilities were destroyed.
A lack of immuno-processing
resulting in death.
Assassinated during
an armored transport.
Of these ten candidates,
seven of them have
perished from transparently
suspicious causes.
Only three remain.
So we think the
"goodwill ambassador" is
secretly offing
the candidates, do we?
At the orders of Poseidon?
The Chief of Staff has
assigned us to protect one of
the three remaining candidates.
Councilman Theseus of
the New Poseidon Party.
He also happens to
bear Alcides' Genes.
He's traveling with
his wife and daughter.
They're scheduled
to meet with Deia Cides
at a hotel in
the city tomorrow.
The moment the councilman
is under our authority,
you're to take the K2s
and provide 24-hour security
for him and his family.
Alcides shielded the mother
of his unborn child with
his own body, and met his end.
Papa, look!
Beautiful.
Subject is clear.
Line of sight?
Clear. No obstructions.
Mechanical sweep?
Clear. There's no sign
of acoustics, thermals,
or any type of jamming.
Are we prepared
for a Hekaton attack?
Prepared enough to hold them
off, assuming they don't have
any other tricks
up their sleeves.
Each member of the security
team is a full-blooded human.
So the only chance
of bioroid interference
would come from beyond
the secure perimeter.
Personnel confirmation.
All hotel employees
were properly screened?
Yes, sir. Just to be safe,
we screened Theseus' wife
and daughter as well. As
expected, they were a perfect
match with the bioroid genes
in cryo-storage at Tartaros.
I hope you have no
objection to a security check.
Of course not. Go right ahead.
We appreciate your cooperation.
I appreciate your thoroughness.
Now I can rest easy.
Hey, Briareos.
Is this something we should
use a coded communication
channel to discuss?
Y'know, Deia. She's apparently
really good with children.
Don't let your personal feelings
cloud your judgment on this.
That won't happen.
She's coming.
No sign of jamming. She's
not connected to the outside.
Don't let your guard down.
Her left arm is functional.
Subject has entered
the meeting room.
The goddess of jealousy
manipulated the man.
Not only did she trick
him into stealing the treasure,
but also into
murdering the queen.
Following the schedule,
the meeting is due
to end any minute
now. Status update?
Hotel employees clear.
Maintaining surveillance for
detection of unplanned contact.
All terminals clear.
Situation normal.
Surroundings clear.
Clear. Activity normal.
If she's gonna make a move. This
is her last chance to do it.
Keep your eyes on her.
Subject is now clear.
She didn't try anything.
Her role as ambassador
must have taken priority.
All terminals clear.
Proximity clear.
Downgrading to security level B.
They've reduced
the threat level.
Why don't you take a break?
Go get some fresh air?
We've still got a
long night ahead of us.
Yeah, thanks. That sounds good.
I heard you like kids.
That you're good with them.
Hitomi told me.
She asked me to help out
and give her a hand
when my assignment's over.
These bioroids raising
children. It's unnatural.
They're not human.
They're basically objects.
Or perhaps like
these butterflies.
A species with no purpose.
They have no business existing.
And yet, here they are.
It's perverse, and
I refuse to accept it.
I assume that includes Hitomi?
You really feel that way?
You honestly believe that
bioroids don't even
deserve the right to exist?
All I see are normal people
with families they love.
How are they different from us?
They're only capable of
mimicking emotion, like puppets.
It's hollow. There's no worry or
fear behind their placid smiles.
It doesn't even matter
if they lose their families.
They can simply
collect a replacement with
the same characteristics
as the last one.
Bioroids are an abomination of
everything it means to be human.
You told me that
you lost your family.
I lost my mother, too,
when I was just a child.
We were walking down a street,
and somebody
shot her in the back.
Gunned her down because her
skin was a different color.
Don't compare what we've lost.
Your sadness doesn't
interest me. It's dishonest.
The genuine sadness of
losing someone you love,
it produces hate.
Sadness devoid of hatred
is just a plea for pity.
You're saying the
pain I felt wasn't real?
Tell me this. Imagine
you lost the man you loved.
If it was your fault,
would you be unchanged?
Do you think you're the
only one who understands loss?
And the feelings of everyone
else are somehow beneath yours?
What's wrong with you? Do you
think you're some kind of a god?
Nothing you can say is
ever going to convince me that
I'm wrong, but you
can try to stop me.
Just stay right there.
There. Hold on.
It is my destiny to
return with the treasure.
I won't be stopped.
Deia.
Deia!
I'm sorry. But
this is technically
considered Poseidon soil.
Deia.
A sculptor named Poeas.
He's one of the few remaining
unprocessed bioroids.
And our latest
assignment. We're on a
24-7 security
watch starting tomorrow.
Daddy? Daddy!
Oh, honey. I know.
The thing that I don't get
is why did Deia come back
to Olympus, especially as
ambassador of Poseidon?
I wish I knew.
Although, I get the feeling
we'll start to see
why soon enough.
Let's just worry about
what needs to be done.
Wow. Wait. I know these.
What's with the bandage?
It's a technique
elderly sculptors employ.
The tightened bandage
helps to strengthen their
grip enough to
continue with their work.
And that's apparently how
he's lived his life here for
the past three years straight.
Hey, Deunan!
Good work out there.
Hitomi. I didn't
know you were here.
Mhm. I thought you might
like something to change into.
Thanks so much, Hitomi. But--
You really didn't have
to go to the trouble of
bringing me extra clothes.
You should be with your baby.
Oh it's fine. Yoshitsune
offered to babysit.
Besides, it's nice to have
a little break from the baby
every once in a while.
This is like a short vacation.
It's so weird how
delicate our society is.
Gaia carefully determines the
very balance of our existence,
even mine. Some of us are
given the gift of motherhood,
while others dedicate
their lives to a craft.
Yeah, right.
It's milk time! I'm gonna
have a cranky baby. See ya!
That's not what I
would call a vacation.
Seemed more like a power
lunch. I guess that's her job.
I get the feeling she
was just checking up on you.
Why?
I think she's a little
worried this stuff with
Deia's got you down.
And that concludes my report.
Although, this whole business
of you sending ES.W.A.T
to guard me at my
home, it's not exactly
the peace and
quiet that I'm used to.
I know you're worried,
but it seems like overkill.
You think that I'm bad?
Well the Judicial
Bureau's worse.
From what I understand,
they intend to
use both FBI and
ES.W.A.T surveillance.
Don't get me wrong,
I understand the rationale.
I'd imagine that
you are concerned with
giving off the impression that
you have things under control.
And I get the feeling
you're telling me that
my cautious approach
makes me look weak.
Not at all. I'm simply
admiring your perspicacity.
Well then, I should get going.
The Ark Project essentially
places the future of humanity in
the hands of an
unprocessed bioroid.
Do you really think it's wise to
make such a big
gamble, Prime Minister?
I was unaware
that you harbored
such ambivalent
feelings about it.
Considering that Gaia proposed
it, I'm sure there are sound,
logical reasons behind
the decision. But even so,
you feel that it's
a precarious decision.
I've heard every argument that
can be made
against this project.
Poseidon has done
everything in their power
to hamper its progress.
But to abandon the project now,
we would be surrendering to
their demands, and sacrificing
our own convictions as well.
I readily admit that it is a
gamble to use Mars as a foothold
to push deeper into space,
but I won't lose faith in it,
which is why I've
left it entirely in
the hands of Eurys,
the project's architect.
And precisely because he
is an unprocessed bioroid.
Although they're bioroids
by design, they are in fact
more human in nature and possess
the same aptitude for free will.
Bioroids are an
abomination of humanity.
There's nothing human about
them. They're basically objects.
Hey. I'm sorry to interrupt.
But you've got me curious.
What are you sculpting?
Oh, I'm sorry! Maybe I
shouldn't have bothered you.
I'm sculpting the
twelve labors of Hercules.
Hercules, huh?
The hero Hercules was
cursed by the goddess Hera,
which caused him
to uncontrollably slay
his own sons. As atonement
for committing this atrocity,
he performed 12
incredible labors.
The Nemean Lion. The Ceryneian
Hind. The Erymanthian Boar.
The Augean Stables.
The Stymphalian Birds.
The Cretan Bull.
The Mares of Diomedes.
The girdle of the
Queen of the Amazons.
The Cattle of Geryon. The
golden apples of the Hesperides.
The guard dog of
the Underworld, Cerberus.
And this creature before
you, the Lernaean Hydra.
So once you complete that
one, they'll all be finished?
No. To be honest...
I sincerely doubt that
this final sculpture
will ever be finished.
Why not? You're so
close to being done.
There's no point.
It's not a sculpture,
it's the work of a bioroid.
I'm incapable of
creating anything genuine.
These are imitations. My work
is inferior by its very nature.
It'll never match the purity
of art created by humans.
This sculpture, its very essence
is modeled after someone I knew.
It is?
That's right.
His name was Ercole.
He was a fellow sculptor,
a peer of mine.
Aside from the obvious,
we shared many
similarities in our lives.
Except for the major
distinction that I'm a bioroid,
and he was a human.
We had joined the same workshop
and shared a passion for honing
our craft, even to the point
of competing with one another.
But there our
experiences diverged.
Even though our sculptures
were of matching quality,
his work drew a constant parade
of admirers. While my creations?
They were, without fail,
critically ignored.
He was the only one
who gave me any support,
who appreciated my
work. Always there to
calm me with a gentle smile.
Inevitably, he realized the
truth behind that disparity.
Neither his talent nor the
beauty of his sculptures were
reason enough for his supporters
to so outnumber my own.
The truth was that Gaia had
produced bioroids whose sole
purpose was to support
the human artists of Olympus,
regardless of their ability
or the quality of their art.
Ashamed of his vanity in
accepting this for so long,
and of his very need for such
praise, he took his own life.
There hasn't been a
human artist in Olympus
since that tragic
day. In light of
these unfortunate events,
Gaia simply won't allow it.
Her fear of human
self-destruction has
trumped their
need to create art.
But I couldn't forget the
artwork that he labored over.
I needed to know if his art was
worthy of the
praise Gaia created.
Ever since his death,
I've made it my life's work to
follow in his footsteps.
To create the
works Ercole strived for.
This compulsion. Do
you think you feel that way
because you're an
unprocessed bioroid?
Look at what you've done.
You devoted almost your entire
life to your friend's memory.
This isn't about being
a bioroid or a cyborg,
or a robot, or even a human.
You made these,
and only you could've.
You might have chosen to
follow in Ercole's footsteps,
but you've traveled
down this path on your own.
But I have traveled it with
the memory of my lost friend.
Deia!
No!
How the hell did
she even get in here?
She simultaneously
hacked and ambushed us.
She has incredible
processing power.
Why can't she understand?
Just because they're bioroids,
it doesn't mean that they're
incapable of
emotion or feelings.
His feelings for his friend.
They weren't any
less than the feelings...
that a mother
has for her child.
I've got the Landmates perfectly
synced with one another,
and we're now hacked into
the insects as you requested.
Perfect.
We've pushed your
neural load to its limit.
Taking it to a higher level?
I simply can't
guarantee your safety.
There's only one left now.
It won't be
much longer, Alcides.
I can't take that.
It's important to
me that you to have it.
But are you sure?
It means so much to you.
A compass always
points north, regardless of
who holds it in their hand.
Be it man, or bioroid,
cyborg, or even robot.
It will always guide its user
to the same objective truth.
It's something to have faith in,
and to know it'll always guide
us. On any path we choose.
I'll always look to the future,
and walk toward it,
but only with you by my side.
Alcides.
Let's get married.
The purpose of the
Olympian Ark Project is to
conduct an ultra-long
term exploration of
deep space,
overseen by bioroids.
The passengers for
tomorrow's journey are
scheduled to arrive
at the spaceport shortly.
The current goodwill ambassador
for Poseidon, Deia Cides,
was reached for
comment earlier today,
stating that she has
great hope this project will
usher in a new
future for all bioroids.
Providing an alternative
to Earth's natural resources
is a key aspiration
of the Project.
Deia. Were you ever really the
person that I called "friend"?
Or were you always driven by the
vile desire to destroy paradise?
But you can try to stop me.
Deia.
I will stop you.
150 multipede turrets
have been deployed to
patrol the grounds
of the Argonaut.
Multipede turrets?
New model Auto Insectors.
Rollin' out the big
guns for this one, huh?
ES.W.A.T. will provide
any needed air support
while the
turrets cover the ground.
You're doin' pretty good.
Pollux.
Hey, Castor.
Happy birthday, little brother.
Cool! I thought
that you forgot,
but you know what'd be even
cooler? If you let me have that.
I bet. Maybe on your
eighteenth birthday.
Not fair, you're
still a kid, too.
Not to you.
Those were close! Right?
Given its location between
Olympus and the spaceport,
The Argonaut will
serve as a base of
operation for
Eurys' security detail.
Last I heard that place was
suspected to be a terrorist den.
If we locate the base there
aren't we
begging to be ambushed?
S'possible. That's
why we need to secure it.
And what'll Minister
Cides be doing?
Poseidon's keeping that quiet.
They've demanded that
they handle her security.
Yeah, that's not shady.
Right, and that's it? What?
We're not gonna
keep an eye on her?
Calm down, we've got an
FBI agent on board her plane.
How're you feeling, Ambassador?
Fine, thank you.
Everything is
progressing exactly as
you've hoped and planned.
You'll soon be
recognized as a hero.
I imagine you must be excited.
You'll be known as
the champion of Olympus.
And Poseidon will
finally gain the trust
and beneficial alliance
of the old superpowers.
Not a bad deal, is it?
Deia.
Stop obsessing.
This is no longer
just about Deia.
Poseidon is
pulling the strings.
The bronze bird incident
was all the proof we need.
Still, though.
If it's true and she
really was Alcides' wife,
there's no way she's done yet.
You're right.
And she probably does
have a grudge against Olympus.
We simply don't know who she
is or the things she's done.
But there is one thing that we
know for certain about her now.
That she is our enemy.
The envoy's plane is
scheduled to depart shortly.
Surrounding area?
Clear.
Alright. Deploy
the Guges Ds. Commence.
10-9. 11-3. Initiate.
10-9, copy. 11-3, copy.
The ambassador's shown
no suspicious activity.
As of now,
looks like we're still
right on course for Poseidon.
Continue to watch her.
Yes, sir.
Even if I have
to destroy myself,
I will wipe out the bioroids.
Something wrong, Ambassador?
The Poseidon plane? And Deia?
There's a naval search
underway for her, ma'am.
To directly attack one
of their own airplanes.
It just doesn't make sense.
Maybe Poseidon
isn't responsible.
Who else would it be? Deia?
That makes even less sense.
Unless her goal
in this is obliteration.
Destroying Alcides'
remaining genes.
What about the candidates'
genes, are any of them
still backed up somewhere
in the Tartaros Center?
No. They were damaged
from the skyjacking.
Some cryogenic issues arose,
and they were all disposed of.
It's down to Eurys. His
genes are all that remain.
So she's willing to
create a global conflict
just to murder a single man.
What is it?
Gaia's requested
a meeting with you.
This can't be good.
The Poseidon aircraft
has been shot down.
And Deia?
Whereabouts currently unknown.
They're searching
the surrounding waters.
Stay on the envoy's plane
and keep your guard up!
What is this? The Poseidon
plane was taken out?
We've conducted our business.
You are correct, our
business has been finalized.
All that's left is the
business between you and her.
She's the one that
you'll want to beg for mercy.
What do you mean?
Found you.
Somebody is hacking into
the security control network!
What now?
The Auto Insectors!
They're destroying it all.
Hey! Let's get out of here!
Yeah.
It's no use.
They're too deep into the
network to lock them out now.
We can't even program around it.
It's got the processing
power of a Hekaton.
A Hekatoncheires?
Deia's nearby!
11-3! 10-9! Find the
enemy Hekaton and take it out!
Roger!
And good luck.
Briareos, you see her yet?
But you can try to stop me.
C'mon. Where are you, Deia?
Me too! Me too!
Higher! Come on, giddy up!
Even if it turns out
Poseidon is devil, not god,
my purpose is clear. I must
exterminate every last bioroid.
Found her! Enemy
spotted dead ahead.
T-minus ten estimated
time of contact.
Just don't get hasty
and leave yourself open.
You go ahead and take the lead.
I'll cover your blind spots.
I'm practically made of eyes.
That doesn't mean you're
able to see everything.
There!
Deia!
It should be safe here.
Promise me that you'll stay put.
Where're you going?
I wanna take a look outside.
Don't worry though.
I'll be fine. I've got
this. Stay right here.
'Kay.
Bastards.
Nothing you
can do will stop me.
So, no blind spots, huh?
Good thing I've got your back.
I won't let you get in my way!
Castor...
What happened to Alcides?
Everything went according to
plan, Deia. You've done well.
The envoy's aircraft. It's
way out of your reach, now.
Disarm immediately,
Deia! It's all over.
Do you hear what I'm saying?
You can't chase him any further!
You're right. It's over.
Oh, crap!
That was the envoy's plane!
It was shot down. It's gone.
The second Landmate.
The cockpit's empty.
You're able to control
that Landmate remotely?
It's finally over, now, Alcides.
It's your fault. None of
this would have even happened.
He'd still be alive,
if it weren't for you!
None of you have
any right to be here!
This is supposed to be our
world! Our hero left it for us!
The hero...
and the heroine.
Deia!
It passed through clean. I
think her brain is over-heating.
The neural load was too much.
I'll try to stabilize her.
Deia.
The heroine. She fell
in love with the king
and they had a child together.
But, nothing can stop the
god of jealousy's scheming.
So the heroine
murdered the king,
and absconded
with the treasure.
It's said that she
was overcome with remorse,
What is she talking about?
after she realized
what she had done.
Briareos?
Bioroids are not human.
They're nothing more
than tools for humans.
Although, as long
as bioroids exist,
they will be dragged
into human conflicts.
Just like the
Great Flood of long ago,
pain and turmoil will wash over
everything, engulfing us all.
Humans and bioroids, both.
Finally put these bugs to bed.
Lock 'em down before
they can start twitchin'.
Yes, sir.
Something's approaching.
Yeah, I see it.
You in the vehicle! Halt!
Is she okay?
The heroine wanted more.
10-9. 11-3. We've
taken a surprise visitor
into protective custody.
Deunan!
She claims that she's
transporting a baby with
Alcides' genes to the spaceport
at the direct request of Gaia.
Alcides.
Deunan! Will you
back me up down here?
Sh, it's okay, don't cry.
Gaia was mindful enough to store
one last double up her sleeve.
So full of surprises. Oh well.
Can't say that I'm too worried.
Just giving me a reason to
crank up the juice, aren't you?
Her neural load's increasing!
Deia!
They will all
share in my suffering.
She's getting away!
"Vengeance belongeth unto me."
The second Landmate's
intercepting!
It's kinda sad we
already have to say goodbye.
You sound like you're attached.
I don't get it, it's not
like you're genetically related.
You only take care of
him 'cuz Gaia asked you to.
Yeah. It's not
quite that easy, though.
I am blown away by how
good you are with babies, Deia.
I might be wrong but
I think that this is what
human happiness
might feel like.
There's a red
Landmate headed your way.
Do not let it get
anywhere near that baby!
We'll take care
of the second one.
Roger that.
The last living unprocessed
bioroid is at the Argonaut?
Correct.
Will it make it here?
We just have to
have faith in ES.W.A.T.
Gaia wants us to trust humans.
You must admit.
They possess a force of
will we're incapable of.
The fate of humanity hinges on
the success of the Ark Project.
And if Gaia has
chosen to place everything
in the hands of humans,
our very future...
...then we must
have faith in them.
Damn you!
Briareos!
You alright?
Yeah.
You find someplace safe. We'll
protect this place for you.
Bioroids must suffer.
I'm not seeing the red one.
The Argonaut's
internal sensors are jammed.
We're not picking up anything.
Stay on your toes and
keep your eyes peeled then.
Here it comes!
She's found him!
Get the hell outta here!
Where do we take him?
Anywhere, just go!
Found you!
It's pretty obvious
she went this way.
Deunan. I managed to
hack into Deia's memory
when I was linked to her.
So what the
hell's wrong with her?
It was just before
the Argonaut was bombed,
that's when it happened.
You ordered a bioroid of me?
That's right.
He's at your command,
so you'll finally
have some time off work.
Please, you need to
leave those types of things for
the bioroid to deal with.
The only reason it was created
was to be your servant.
To lose our ability
to empathize is to
lose the very
essence of our humanity.
We all want the same thing.
Bioroids, cyborgs, humans,
as long as they're all
striving for the same goal
I consider them all
to be a part of my family.
People have always
dreamed of creating paradise.
But I've found it,
spending my life with you,
and raising our
child together. That's it.
Deia.
The bioroid Deia gave to him,
Poseidon had marked it with
a geo-tracker, making
it a walking target.
Alcides and their unborn
child died in the attack.
But Deia miraculously survived.
From that point on,
Deia was considered
a heroine by all of Poseidon.
It just doesn't make sense,
working with the government
that killed her husband?
She was using them.
To enact her vengeance.
Her grief hardened her heart.
Don't compare what we've lost.
Your sadness doesn't
interest me. It's dishonest.
The genuine sadness of
losing someone you love,
it produces hate.
Bioroids are an abomination of
everything it means to be human.
They're only capable of
mimicking emotion, like puppets.
You know, one
day you might wake up
and it'll be too
late to clear the air.
Hey, Briareos.
Yeah?
You wanna get married?
What? You do realize that we're
in the middle of a mission here?
I realize, but the fact that
Deia's forgotten her family,
the family that she loved, makes
me want to start one of my own.
Because I know what it's
like to lose your whole world.
And I don't want to
be afraid of that anymore.
Do you mind if I give you
my answer after the mission?
Sure.
Then let's stop Deia.
Right!
Dammit!
Deia!
Section E5!
Deia! Surrender!
Deia!
Watch out!
Even if it costs me my life,
I can never give up
my search for paradise.
Deia!
Deia. I love you.
What kind of person am I?
I've betrayed my husband, and
brought ruin to the Argonauts.
Briareos. What is this?
Humans are all
that matter there.
That world puts them above all
else, and I could no longer live
in a world so blind to others.
One that's so
quick to persecute.
Even if it costs me my life,
I can never give up
my search for paradise.
I didn't ask for this. I
never wanted to be their puppet.
All I ever wanted was to
live in paradise by your side.
Just to be with you.
It's yours, Deunan. Take it. I
leave the future in your hands.
Deia!
As their creators,
we are the bioroids' gods.
And just as we read
in the texts of mythology,
those who choose to defy their
gods are bound to live a life of
ceaseless suffering as
punishment for their sins.
They belong to us.
Bioroids exist for
the sole purpose of serving us.
An apostate, who betrays the
gods, doesn't deserve mercy.
And so I chose--
I chose the path of
the gods over my husband.
And betrayed him to Poseidon.
Deia.
Here. You don't
wanna forget this.
It always points north,
regardless of who holds it.
Be it man, bioroid,
cyborg, or robot.
No matter what. It'll
always guide you to the truth.
I remember. You told
me that seeing all of us
together gave you some peace.
Me, and Briareos, and Hitomi,
it reminded you of when you were
happy. I hope you feel that now.
For Deia, her paradise,
it was here on the Argonaut.
And it was so pure
and beautiful to her.
She couldn't bear the
idea of a new paradise.
Despite earlier delays, the
deep space exploration vehicle
has now been fully prepped
and will launch shortly.
The Ark Project
launch was delayed,
so I would say we were
quite successful. Of course.
There's no need to worry.
I've destroyed all
implicative evidence that
could lead
back to the incident.
No one will ever
suspect Poseidon of anything.
We couldn't
have a better patsy.
Everyone thinks she
was working on her own.
Sure. One thing though.
About my new position
as the institutions director.
Do you think there's
any way we could
push the inaugural
ceremony back a week?
No, no. I just thought I might
take in a short vacation first.
Deia.
This paradise
humanity's built...
Maybe it really isn't
the kind of place we were
all meant to live in.
But I think,
if we keep looking, someday
we'll find the real thing.
We have to try. For Deia's sake.
Let's find a place where people
can finally live as people,
regardless of
how they were created.
Together.
Hey, Briareos.
Yeah?
Mission's over.
Gonna give me your answer?
Answer? To what?
You did not forget!
Don't you try and pull that!
Pull what?
Man up and give me an answer!
Well, let's get back to work.
No, you don't!