♪ opening song ♪
Don't just stand there; come on!
You just keep scanning.
Watch it!
What the hell's with you?
I know it's just a drill but
that's no reason to be lazy!
So you don't like
the idea of adding
Kottos robots to ES.W.A.T.
You gotta be kidding me!
After what I saw today,
I don't know why the force
decided to take on
those buckets of bolts!
You sure they aren't defective?
It's been statistically
proven that the deployment
of robotic police is
a crime deterrent.
But you may be onto something.
Just because it works
for the police doesn't
necessarily mean
it'll work for us.
I think it's a shame, really.
We could've benefitted
from their thick armor.
Well, I'd rather run
the risk of dying
than get stuck with
those duds, okay?
Sure, you can always stay here.
Is something going on
with you and Briareos?
As your new landlady,
I think it's only
fair that I know my
tenant's situation.
Just another fight; nothing new.
I'm home!
Who does the baby belong to?
Me and Yoshitsune;
surprised, aren't you?
You can't though!
No, a member of the
Legislative Bureau
asked me to babysit today.
Wait a minute.
So it's a bioroid, like you?
I know, it's rather
unusual, isn't it?
You don't see
many baby bioroids.
10-9.
Emergency mission.
I've sent 11-3 to pick you up.
We're investigating the
kidnapping of a little girl.
We have reason to believe a
Hekatoncheires may be involved.
How long are you
going to stay at Hitomi's?
I was just trying
to keep you safe.
I have to protect you.
You're not going to be
able to protect me forever.
Partners are supposed to see
each other as equals, Briareos.
I'm sorry but there's nothing
you can say to change my mind.
I've always been there.
Watching over you.
Well, you can stop now.
I've had enough.
Come on.
I don't need you to protect me.
I'm a big girl.
I can take care of myself.
I want you to treat me like your
equal, not some helpless girl.
Until then, I'm not coming home.
Got it?
This is all my fault.
Don't cry, dear.
She'll turn up safe and sound.
I'm sure she will.
The police are doing everything
in their power to find her.
Given her parents' status,
this could be a
summit-related terrorist act.
4-5, anything to report?
Apparently, they hacked
the hospital's system, sir.
They were able to look up the
girl's records, and they nabbed
her when her mother brought
her in for a regular checkup.
In the surveillance
footage they appear
to be dressed as doctors;
lab coats and all.
Anything from the
scene of the crime?
Eyewitnesses report
seeing a nondescript,
gray van leaving the hospital
right after the incident.
I'm searching the tapes for
a positive ID as we speak.
Good work, men.
When you're finished
there, join Zero-2.
Use our jurisdictional authority
to set up vehicle checkpoints.
Got it, sir.
Damn!
I hate sittin' on my ass
waiting for them to screw up.
It's just not my style, at all.
We got the case, man.
Now what do we do?
Go to the designated point.
You'll get further
instructions there.
Yeah, yeah.
You just better make
this worth our while.
If you're successful, I will.
Talk about horrible parents!
Kids should never be
left alone in a parked car.
Especially not one
in her condition.
Give 'em a piece of my
mind when you find 'em.
Guess that's it, Kottos.
If you'll take care of the
girl, I'll take the van
over to the impound lot.
Kottos.
Where are we?
Where's mommy and daddy?
Are they waiting for
me at the hospital?
"Ady.
I have taken you
into my custody.
I'm taking you to the police,
they've been looking for you."
They're looking for me?
But why?
I haven't done anything wrong!
I swear!
"Don't worry,
you're not in any trouble.
We will call your parents
from the police station,
so that they can come and
get you. "Sounds good to me!
I'll go, but that's not the
first place I'm headed, okay?
Hey!
Where's the van?
What'll we do now?
If we don't deliver the
"package" we're screwed.
We might as well kiss
our bonus goodbye!
She couldn't have
gotten far in that chair.
Let's find her!
"You're going the wrong way.
The station's in
the other direction."
I wanna go this way!
Don't worry!
I'll go to the station
with you but there's
somewhere I really
wanna go first.
I promise it won't take long.
Okay?
Not even for a little while?
You really mean it?
Fine, then.
I've got no choice.
I'll have to go by myself!
The child's name is Ady.
She's a bioroid who suffers
from severe bronchitis.
She's unprocessed; she hasn't
had any genetic modification.
She's as close to
human as you can get.
In other words, it would be
virtually impossible for
an AI to distinguish whether
she's human or bioroid.
You can't see 'em, but there are
dandelions on top of that hill!
I can't get up there by myself.
Kottos, will you take me?
Please, just for a little while?
Wanna know something?
My mommy and daddy
aren't really my parents.
I'm special because
I'm a bioroid.
Mommy and Daddy always
wanted to have a baby but they
weren't able to, so
they made one instead!
They asked the Tartaros Center
to make me especially for them.
So, you see.
I get sick a lot 'cause
I never had modifications.
At least that's what
the doctors tell me.
I'm always at home or else,
I'm in the hospital.
I've never had the
chance to play outside.
The doctors said I have to
stay away from windy
places and stuff.
Whenever I think about it,
I get sad, 'cause it means
I might never get to go
anywhere, you know?
It may be a lot to ask,
but just this once.
I wanna visit the hill I can
see from my hospital room.
Kottos!
We've located the girl.
A tow truck driver left her
with a Kottos robotic officer.
I'm sending their
coordinates now.
Retrieve her before
the kidnappers
attempt to make contact again.
Roger!
I appreciate the intel.
You've been a big help.
I've already ruled
out a few possible
motives for the kidnapping.
You have?
And those are?
Well, if this were only
about ransom money,
they'd already be
negotiating with the police.
And those goons are
too amateurish for
this to be a political scandal.
If they were just out
looking to kill someone,
that little girl would've
been dead a long time ago.
We don't have a clear
motive yet but at
least we've narrowed
the playing field.
Well, you've certainly
thought this through.
Ma'am, there is
one more question
that I'd like to ask you.
With Tartaros' technological
abilities, I would think the
company would be
able to produce
bioroids based on
personal preference.
So why would her guardians
keep her unprocessed?
It makes no sense to me.
I can't speak for them,
but because we live in
a world where everything can
be modified and controlled.
Some people are drawn
to leaving things to chance.
I don't quite follow you.
Bioroids who aren't genetically
processed suffer from greater
health problems than their
processed counterparts do.
But even in our utopian
society, there are
those who prefer these
"flawed" beings.
Their frailty is considered
a unique quality.
This is especially true
of couples who are
unable to have human
children of their own.
Like her parents.
Oh, wow!
Look at Olympus.
It's such a
beautiful city, isn't it?
Thank you, Kottos.
Here, you should have this one.
Pretty.
Fly away; you can go
wherever you want now.
There she is!
On top of that building!
Thanks for keeping an
eye on her for us, officer.
But we can take over from here.
We've been looking for you.
We're her doctors, you see.
No, they're not.
The poor girl's just confused.
And I don't blame her;
she's been though a lot today.
She's had enough excitement.
We need to get her
back to the hospital now.
We have to hurry!
Are you okay?
Go after him!
Worthless piece 'a tin.
He's goin' down!
Doesn't matter if
she blows up with him.
Stupid bastard's seen too much.
Kottos.
Damn robot.
You just had to go
and ruin everything.
ES.W.A.T.!
Throw down your weapons
and surrender at once!
This will be your only warning!
No, Kottos.
Please don't die!
Kottos.
Please!
Eat this!
Changed your mind about
Kottos robots in ES.W.A.T.
have you?
I didn't think they were
worthy of joining us.
But now that I've seen
them in action, I do.
I see.
What happened to that Kottos?
Oh.
It's fine.
It was recovered by a
specialized lab and serviced.
Apparently, they had
to reinitialize its AI.
Kind of unfortunate it won't
remember its heroic deeds.
Yeah.
Ady?
Kottos?
It's really you!
Do you remember?
Ady!
I thought you died saving me.
But you're really okay.
And that makes me so happy.
Oh, yeah!
I kept picking these
just in case I saw you.
Here you go!
Ady!
Bye-bye, Kottos!
♪ closing song ♪