♪ opening song ♪
Authorities have concluded the
cause of death in the case of
the bioroid found in the
early morning hours
on the seventh was,
in fact, suicide.
Investigators are scrambling
to identify a possible
connection in the city's recent
string of bioroid suicides.
In other news, the Tartaruss
Center is reporting that three
thousand frozen
embryos stored at
its facilities were destroyed.
More details on that to come.
But authorities say the cause is
currently under investigation.
Deunan.
Want to go for a ride?
I'm sorry.
I told Hitomi I'd
go shopping with her.
Great.
Guess I'm on my own, then.
Why take time off together if
we're going to spend it apart?
Yo!
Hey!
What's up?
How's it going?
Okay, I guess.
You?
I'm back, Yoshitsune!
And early, too!
Welcome home!
Hi Briareos, how're you?
Hitomi.
I thought you were going
shopping with Deunan.
No.
I've been gone for three days.
I did a stint at the
Legislative Bureau.
Briareos?
You're something else, coming
in to train on your day off.
Aren't you doing the same?
Nah, we're on duty.
We're holding down the
fort while the others
are on some "secret
investigation."
Isn't Deunan off, too?
What's she doin' right now?
I would take her on
the town, but that's just me.
Oh.
She dumped ya, huh?
Who, Deunan?
I saw her earlier today.
You did?
Yes.
There was another
bioroid suicide
in the Ladon River district.
I was asked to visit the scene
as a Tartaros Center observer.
That's where I saw her.
Another suicide.
It seems so out of
character for bioroids.
They're designed to take joy
in serving humans and
maintaining society.
What would drive them
to take their own lives?
The deeper I dig,
the less sense it makes.
What do you think, Briareos?
Briareos?
If it's bothering
you that much,
why don't you try
asking her about it?
You can't just
let it eat at you.
Listen up, Deunan!
When you move left,
watch the right.
When you move up, watch below.
Take in all your surroundings!
Damn it.
Don't look at the target,
just pull the trigger!
Eliminate anyone
who looks suspicious!
Keep your eyes open!
If this were real, you'd be
dead two times over!
Karl, would you let her
take a break already?
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Watch your back!
No one else will do it for you!
That's enough Karl!
What the hell are you doing?
The poor girl can't
take much more of this!
Is something wrong?
Briareos!
Deunan.
Earlier you--
I what?
Uh, never mind.
You can be such a weirdo.
She's probably just
getting it overhauled.
If she was in the
Ladon River district,
I bet she took it to Ceryneia.
Ceryneia?
Yeah, it's a gun shop.
The police buy their
weapons there wholesale.
You never heard of it?
Supposedly they're
the best around when
it comes to firearm
maintenance.
The owner is a bioroid
named Lark and from what
I hear he's pretty
popular with the ladies.
This is a rare piece, even for
a custom Government model.
It's got the original
slide and frame, but it
looks as though everything
else has been replaced.
I take it you prefer
rubber grips, Deunan?
No, that was my dad's gun.
I keep it as a memento.
I'll be careful with it.
Karl.
I don't understand why you
keep pushing her so hard!
Karl?
Are you even listening to me?
Is that?
She's my daughter and the
only family that I have left.
She may think I'm a monster now
but what kind of father would
I be if I didn't teach her
how to protect herself?
Deunan's not ready
to handle life on her own.
So if anything ever
happens to me,
she's in your hands, Briareos.
All of the bioroids in
Olympus are bred and
managed right here at
the Tartaros Center.
They're essentially clones
created from human genes
that have been
altered to promote
specific physical and
character traits.
Basically, their
hardware is human
but their internal
software is not.
I would liken them to
sophisticated precision robots
but then I suppose
I'm a little biased,
since I am a bioroid myself.
Here we are.
And what would
you want with him?
Sorry.
Lark Ceryne.
Ah.
He's a bioroid created with
Karl Knute and Alcide's genes.
That's quite an
impressive combination.
Bioroids crafted from superior
human genes, such as this one,
are widely considered
the ideal citizens for
the utopian city of Olympus.
Yeah, sure.
Because, unlike humans,
they're perfect. Right?
I assure you,
they're far from perfect.
After all, if they were,
they wouldn't commit
suicide, would they?
Bioroids don't
consider life a gift.
Instead, they see
it as their duty.
Self-abandonment is
the only way they
can avoid that responsibility.
It's the only way
they can truly be free.
Would you call that perfect?
You were out late.
Uh.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
So where's your
Government model?
I decided to get it overhauled.
Why?
You have a problem with that?
Maybe I do.
C'mon Briareos.
Karl's gun.
It's the only memento
you have of your father
and you left it
with that Lark guy.
How did you know that?
What, have you
been spying on me?
I can't believe this!
Don't you trust me?
What's wrong with
caring about your partner?
Ugh, nothing!
Except when "caring"
means snooping around
and prying into my life!
You're my boyfriend,
not my parent, okay?
I'm just looking out for you!
Give me a break.
You're just pissed
because, for once,
I want to do things my way!
I swear you're no different
than my shitty dad!
You don't mean that.
Whatever!
I'm outta here!
Why're you so angry?
Briareos is your man!
Of course he's gonna
worry about you!
If anything, you
should be happy
he feels that
strongly about you.
Aw, don't give me that crap!
He's just like my old man!
Ah!
If I ever caught
Yoshitsune spying on me.
I'd be one happy lady!
Hello?
Are you even listening to me?
Hey, Deunan?
Why don't you tell us about
this other man of yours?
Yes!
Spill it!
I want details!
You wanted advice and that's
what we're gonna give you!
But first, you've gotta
tell us about this guy!
To be honest, it's kind of weird
'cause he looks like my dad.
I'm guessing he
must have his genes.
Well, they do say it's
common for human women
to be attracted to men
who resemble their father.
They look similar but
he's a better person
than my dad ever was.
Oh really?
I could use another drink.
How about you ladies?
I'll be right back.
You know it's funny.
Humans are attracted by
a fatherly resemblance,
but bioroids don't feel that.
Even though we
share the same genes.
We're so different!
Ugh!
If that's the case,
what was the
point in coming to
you for advice?
Hey, I'm still your friend!
The body in the vacant
building is a male bioroid.
Identity is being determined.
It appears to be a
suicide by firearm.
Forensics is en route.
I repeat, body is
that of a male bioroid.
Identity is being determined.
Here you go.
It's as good as new.
You test fire it?
200 shots from 50 yards.
The grouping rate is off,
but less than a decimal.
Want to try it?
No thanks.
Are you sure?
It's not like I'm ever going
to use it in combat.
I'd like to thank you
for all your help.
How about dinner?
Sure, that sounds good to me.
Y'ready?
Hold on!
Before we go.
We're just in time!
Why? What'ja want
to show me up here?
Turn around.
Why won't you just tell me?
And ruin the fun?
C'mon.
Now stay right there.
Isn't it beautiful?
You can only catch it for
a few seconds each day.
Wow.
You know.
I'm not like the other bioroids.
No longevity processing.
I don't have
much longer to live.
An "unprocessed" bioroid?
Knowing that my death is
imminent, helps me appreciate
fleeting moments, such as the
one we're sharing right now.
That's how it is
for humans, right?
Yeah, I guess.
A fixed rate of bioroid
suicides is to be expected.
But, the number of
cases over the
past year has exceeded
Gaia's projections.
The administration's starting
to get concerned that
this might be a terrorist
plot in action.
So they called ES.W.A.T.
in to investigate.
And?
It took a while but we finally
put all the pieces together.
What's crazy is, Deunan's
right smack dab
in the middle of the puzzle.
Thanks again for dinner.
But you didn't have to
take me out, you know.
I was just doing my job.
Well, I appreciate it and this
is my way of saying thanks.
That gun.
It was a memento
from your father, right?
Yeah.
But honestly,
he was a shitty dad.
Hey, now.
It's true!
When I was a kid he had
me taking apart rifles
instead of playing with blocks.
I had to go through
close-quarters combat
with elite soldiers if I
wanted to play "house."
I mean... can you imagine?
But if it weren't for all
that combat training he put
me through, I never would've
made it this far in life.
If I could, I'd thank him,
but he left for the war and
he never made it back.
I've heard stories about him.
The hero.
Karl Knute.
Briareos was in the same unit.
In fact, he's the
one who brought
my dad's gun back for me.
I'm honored that
you trusted me with it.
Thanks, Deunan.
Hold up!
Just where do you
think you're going?
We need to sit tight.
Why's that?
There's more to
this than meets the eye.
And we're talking about 80
percent of Olympus's population.
We can't mess around.
Don't worry, we'll strike
when the time's right.
Until then we wait.
Thanks for joining me.
I had a great time tonight.
I did, too.
I'm sorry I can't take you home.
I've got to get back to work.
I'll see ya.
'Night.
Deunan.
It's Magus.
We got our proof,
but we lost the guy.
I'm attempting
to locate him now.
Tell me when you do!
So who's the next target?
It's me.
The cops showed up at
Tartaros just as I was leaving.
Unfortunately, if
they're on to me,
it won't be long 'til
they come for you.
I'm afraid the jig is up.
They've linked me to
the bioroid suicide cases.
They know the victims
were under my supervision.
It's over.
You saw right through me from
the beginning, didn't you?
Assisted bioroid suicide?
Does it really come
as a surprise to you?
He's unprocessed, just like me.
I'm amazed he's
even made it this far.
I've been told that the humans
consider Olympus a paradise.
But let me assure you...
...that wouldn't be the case
if it weren't for the
bioroids slaving away to
carry out Gaia's intentions.
In this utopian city, not
everything is perfect;
there are those of us
who are anomalies;
bioroids with deadly impulses.
They realize they're defective
and that this place would be
better off without them,
but their "programming"
keeps them from
committing suicide.
And you think that gives
you the right to kill them?
Don't act like I'm some kind
of deranged murderer.
These flawed bioroids are simply
acquiescing to their genetics,
and in turn, I'm
optimizing our society
by granting their wishes.
I don't see what the problem is.
I'm genetically driven to
maintain this place for you.
You could say I
did this for the
sake of you humans
and your paradise.
Know what I'd say?
You should have
optimized society
by offing yourself first.
Maybe you're right.
But think how many
unstable bioroids there'd be,
and how much damage
they might cause.
I like to think this impulse of
mine comes from your father.
Briareos!
You all right?
So you were out to
catch this guy all along?
I couldn't have a bioroid
with my dad's genes
murdering innocent people.
Karl may not have
been the best dad,
but he wasn't a
cold-blooded killer.
Once the administrator realized
he and Lark shared the same
point of view, he gladly
handed him a list of bioroids
that had been deemed
suicidal during
their regular
counseling visits.
For whatever reason,
he eventually decided
to add his own name
to Lark's hit list.
Be honest with me,
you weren't attracted
to him in the slightest?
After all this time,
you still don't get me.
Why did you have
to get involved?
I didn't need your help.
I could've handled it on my own.
I was just trying
to keep you safe.
I have to protect you.
Oh, really?
For how long?
You're not going to be
able to protect me forever.
Partners are supposed to see
each other as equals, Briareos.
I'm sorry but there's nothing
you can say to change my mind.
I've always been
there watching over you.
Well, you can stop now.
I've had enough.
Come on.
I don't need you to protect me.
I'm a big girl.
I can take care of myself.
Deunan.
Whether you like it or not,
I have to look out for you.
♪ closing song ♪