♪ opening song ♪
It belonged to my late husband.
Something of his
I kept as a memento.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
It happened a long time ago.
I'm okay.
By the way, I ran
into your partner.
He seemed pretty worried.
You know.
One day, you might
wake up and it'll be too
late to clear the air.
So uh.
How did you lose him?
What?
I've been meaning to ask you.
Whenever I've needed
to vent about my dad,
or 'bout Briareos, you've
always been there for me.
I'd like to return the favor.
A compass always points north,
regardless of who holds it.
Be it man, or bioroid,
cyborg, or even robot.
It will always guide its user
to the same objective truth.
You lost me.
Sorry.
It's just something
he used to say.
And whenever I see
Hitomi and Briareos
and you getting along,
it rings true.
Now be a good girl and
patch things up with him.
I still can't believe that--
that Deia was a
terrorist, you know?
Yeah, me neither.
But that line between friend and
enemy can get blurred sometimes.
That's just the reality of the
world we're living in I guess.
Lance still runnin' you ragged?
Some vacation
this has been, huh?
See ya later!
So the word from on
high is that Poseidon
is sending a goodwill
ambassador to Olympus.
Guess who's gonna
provide 'em with security?
The ambassador will be
arriving on one of our
subs along with a security
detail from Poseidon.
What gives?
That submarine's,
like, a museum piece.
The ambassador asked for it.
Seems like a weird request.
Must be a pretty heavy hitter.
All this fuss, y'know?
You're gonna rendezvous
with the submarine.
Provide it with
some air support.
Deunan's going
aboard for guard detail.
Really?
Why me?
You were requested.
Hero of the
"Bronze Bird crisis,"
that's what they called you.
That's what they'll get.
Meet 'em at the coordinates
an' bring 'em in.
That's all.
Way to go, Deunan.
Try not to upstage us too
bad out there, would ya?
Don't you worry about Briareos.
We'll make sure he's okay.
I just wanna take my vacation!
Twenty years of service
and you're finally down
to your last voyage.
Level with me.
How's it feel, Captain Diomedes?
The same as always.
I've done my duty, that's all.
Eight people aboard this sub,
and six of them are bodyguards.
Still, for an ambassador,
that's not a ton of security.
Man, this ship has really
been around the block.
I'm afraid I can't
let you in here.
Guarding the ambassador's
what I'm on this sub to do.
And you're telling
me I can't say hello?
Look, I'm sorry but
it's not my call.
I had a hunch you might try
to finagle your way
through that door.
Who might you be?
I'm the head of security, Iris.
Are you gonna let
me do my job, Iris?
You should leave the
ambassador's well-being to us.
Come on, I'm not trying
to step on your toes!
Here, take a look.
The ambassador
is resting comfortably.
As you can see,
vital signs are normal.
Huh.
In the event of an emergency,
the ambassador's pod is
designed to disengage from
the rest of the submarine.
So if all the rest of us
are crushed or drowned,
at least the ambassador
gets to survive?
You hit the nail on the head.
Now, if you would be so
kind, remain in your
quarters for the
rest of the trip.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I'm not suggesting that you're
not up to the task at hand.
ES.W.A.T.'s exploits are quite
well known to us in Poseidon,
believe you me.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to confirm our
course with the captain.
If you need anything
brought to your quarters,
don't hesitate to let me know.
The sub carrying the ambassador
is on course as scheduled.
ES.W.A.T. is playing
an active role in its security.
It needs to arrive safely.
Because of the Ark Project,
I assume?
If any harm should
befall that sub,
it will leave us vulnerable.
We can't afford that before
the plan reaches completion.
What's that guy's problem?
The engine's stopped!
Do you know
what's going on, Sir?
No.
Did something happen?
Whatever it is, we'll fix it!
Kagaya!
What the hell's going on?
Captain!
Oh no.
Damn it, we're locked out.
So unlock it!
It won't accept my commands.
What about?
Right!
Safe in the pod.
Thank goodness.
Hold on.
Shouldn't that pod
eject if anything goes
way wrong aboard the submarine?
What the hell?
It's been tampered with!
Chief.
I found Thomas!
He's--
Damn it.
What happened?
I don't know.
If somebody murdered your
guy, we have to assume
that that same person has
hijacked this vessel.
You don't think that it's--
Where's the other bodyguard?
We're being jammed.
Anything?
Still nothing.
It's just as bad here.
Bow section is all-clear.
Good.
Move to Section C4.
Yessir.
Dmitri!
Dmitri, come in!
Say something!
Can you hear me?
What's wrong?
I just lost Dmitri.
Where did he go?
The bow. I think.
Glenn.
There's an enemy on board.
The submarine carrying
the ambassador
isn't showing up on the
agreed upon course.
Wherever it is, we're not even
picking up its beacon signal.
Where're you
positioned right now?
We're standing by at the
edge of Olympus waters.
Worst-case,
we're ready to engage.
Dmitri.
Another murder.
High-pressure steam.
That's what killed him.
Could be an accident.
Everybody's dead except
for us and the ambassador!
You need to wake
up to the facts!
I'm just saying we don't know--
Save it.
What are you doing?
I'm keeping your
ambassador alive.
Hands in the air.
We do this my way from now on.
Make any trouble,
and I will take you out.
In that case, you're the boss.
The only way we can eject the
ambassador's pod is to regain
control of the submarine
and do it manually.
Why don't we just surface?
Well.
I'm not qualified to
navigate a capsized sub,
and neither are you.
S.O.S.?
No, we're too far down.
We can't transmit
anything unless
we're up at periscope depth.
Damn.
Still not working.
ES.W.A.T.
come in!
This is Ten-Nine!
I repeat, this is Ten-Nine!
No luck.
Looks like we're trapped
on this infernal thing.
And you're absolutely
sure there's no
other way we can gain control?
It's possible some kind of
emergency aboard the sub
would cause basic control
to be restored to us.
One emergency, coming up.
RDX explosives.
Indeed.
And one detonator.
Why is that even aboard?
The Balanced Military Arms
Treaty demanded we render
this sub inoperable after
delivering the ambassador.
Explosives seemed
like the surest bet.
You're telling me if
we set those off,
it might be enough to
reset the controls.
Iris!
Diomedes you let me out of here!
"Diomedes?"
The only vital signs left are
from me and the ambassador.
If there's no outside
intervention, then the main
controls are the only
way to pilot this sub.
Okay, then fine.
We're gonna have us a
little talk, just you and me!
Open this door!
Do it, or I blow
us both to hell!
Would you like some coffee?
That's a first.
The ship itself
committing mutiny.
"Mutiny," eh?
One could make the argument
that they betrayed me first.
My purpose as a
bioroid was so simple.
Guide this vessel
through the waters,
and live in harmony
with the sea.
They would put me in drydock
in some new body ashore,
but I reject such a fate.
The ocean is vast.
Far deeper than you fathom.
It is the one place
where I can live
out my existence as intended.
In its embrace
I find my destiny.
That's nice and all,
but I'm destined for dry land.
What are you doing?
Shaking things up.
I don't know what happened,
but the sub's back on the radar.
Sir!
Requesting permission to
cross Olympus's border
and approach the submarine
in extraterritorial waters.
Granted.
The ambassador's pod
is ready to be ejected!
What the?
The oxygen supply!
I gotta get that pod
out of the submarine!
Where am I?
Who's there?
The ocean is vast.
Far deeper--
--than you fathom.
I had to lay around in
a decompression tank
for two whole days afterwards!
It was a drag!
Not exactly a pleasure cruise.
What about the ambassador?
Make it out okay?
So they said.
Guess we'll see them at
the press conference later.
That looks like!
Thank you for
coming all this way.
A fitting entrance for the
start of our little show.
A goodwill ambassador from
Poseidon, Deia Cides,
has traveled to Olympus
to profess friendly
relations between her
people and ours.
Deia.
♪ closing song ♪