♪ opening song ♪
Briareos.
That solo mission to
infiltrate the Argonauts.
You're turning it down, right?
I'm not turning it down.
Lance chose me for this.
What're you so worried about?
If that giant Landmate turns
out to be more than talk,
you're going to be outgunned.
Lance gave me the thumbs-up.
If you want to tell him
he's wrong, go ahead.
Look, I'm just gonna say it.
You can't handle this one alone.
And that's why I have to go.
Huh?
As long as you see me this way,
we can never be together.
Since when have I been helpless?
When did things change?
Back when I was
living with my mom,
even when I was being forced
to train with knives and
guns every damn day,
you never treated me like this.
I just want to keep you safe.
Like Karl.
Karl was an awful dad
and you know it!
Deunan.
I know you think--
If we can't be equals,
then we're through.
Damn it.
This is similar to the tracking
implants we sometimes use
to chip bioroids, except that
this one is biodegradable.
Two weeks from now,
it'll have completely dissolved.
It takes two hours
to calibrate,
so try to relax 'til then.
Thanks, Deia.
Not that it'll matter to me, but
if I turn up dead, at least
ES.W.A.T. will know it
sooner rather than later.
A dangerous job,
in other words?
What is that?
Huh?
The compass on your desk.
Looks old.
Ah.
It belonged to my late husband.
Something of his
I kept as a memento.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
It happened a long time ago.
I'm okay.
By the way,
I ran into your partner.
He seemed pretty worried.
You know, one day you
might wake up and
it'll too late to
clear the air.
So, uh?
How did you lose him?
What?
I've been meaning to ask you.
Whenever I've needed
to vent about my dad,
or 'bout Briareos, you've
always been there for me.
I'd like to return the favor.
A compass always points north,
regardless of who holds it.
Be it man, or bioroid,
cyborg, or even robot.
It will always guide its user
to the same objective truth.
You lost me.
Sorry.
It's just something
he used to say.
And whenever I see
Hitomi and Briareos
and you getting along,
it rings true.
Now be a good girl and
patch things up with him.
I hear the Argonauts have
announced a terrorist attack.
What sort of response
has Poseidon issued?
A man claiming to be the son
of Alcides has taken control
of the group,
expanded its influence,
and now insists on
Argonaut independence.
If armed guerillas are
confirmed to be hiding
among the Argonauts, I am
told that Poseidon will have
no choice but to
exercise the use of force.
Independence, huh?
This is twenty years
ago all over again.
I thought the
bombardments had crippled
the Argonauts'
technical capabilities.
But if this current threat of
theirs is anything more than
mere talk, then perhaps
they've found a way
for the Bronze Bird to
finally take flight.
The Stymphalean.
A Landmate capable of
leaving the Earth's atmosphere.
I, Hyllus, ask my fellow
Argonauts to heed these words!
As the son of our
great founder Alcides
and the inheritor of his will.
I implore you on
behalf of my father!
See that your talents
and soul carry on!
So this is the Argonaut.
Dummy.
I told ya that was too many.
Uh-uh.
I can handle it.
You're gonna drop 'em.
Here.
Uh, thank you.
Go on.
Thank her.
Thanks a lot.
Pollux!
You need to work out those arms.
Yeah, right.
Thanks, Briareos.
Eleven-three here.
Moving from Point C to F.
Copy that, Eleven-three.
Four-five en route
to Point F, as well.
You might wanna get
your head in the game.
I'm just sayin'.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Still got Deunan on
the brain, huh man?
As long as you see me this way,
we can never be together.
Since when have I been helpless?
When did things change?
American Imperial FBI.
EU intelligence agents.
And their equivalents from
a bunch of other countries, too.
Feels like I'm at
a spy convention.
Found him.
A cyborg?
Not half bad for a girl.
Guess I was good enough
to get the drop on you!
Is that what you
think just happened?
Huh?
Isn't that the big-shot
Poseidon doctor over there?
Wonder what that car
inspection's all about.
Peekaboo!
You like that?
So, what's with the luggage?
Officer.
It's good to see you.
Briareos, please!
You have to help me!
Huh?
I really need a babysitter!
It's just for one day!
I'm on duty.
No can do.
Deia's going back
to Poseidon and I,
I can't take care
of it by myself!
Heading home to Poseidon, eh?
I am.
My time here was
short, but I've really
enjoyed all the
people that I've met.
Aw not again!
It's okay.
You're fine!
So no crying, okay?
Seriously, no more crying.
I can't handle this.
--Thanks.
--Thank you!
Forget her.
Problem?
You shouldn't make those
boys do your dirty work.
Don't give me that look.
Those boys were defending
their home, that's all.
I gotta say, you know how
to make a girl feel welcome.
A Colt Government.
You're packing quite
the antique, miss.
I keep it for good luck.
It was my dad's.
Really?
I knew a man named Karl Knute
who used to carry that
very same model.
Wait, so you knew my dad?
You're Karl's daughter?
I guess it's been twenty years
now if it's been a day, but our
hero Alcides and your father
were as thick as thieves.
Why would my father
befriend a terrorist?
Alcides was
no terrorist, little girl.
All around the world, bioroids
are the slaves of industry--
and nowhere is this more
true than in Olympus.
Alcides founded the Argonauts
in the hopes of carving out a
paradise where people
could live like people,
no matter how they
were created.
Where technological
advancement was
won by the sweat of our brows.
Side by side.
That was the challenge
we'd taken up if we
wanted to change our future.
There could be failures
along the way, but the
resulting success would be
a triumph of humanity.
We were all ablaze with
Alcides's vision of paradise.
If anything, our technology
grew grander by
leaps and bounds as we
grasped for that ideal.
This culminated in
our magnum opus,
the Stymphalean.
An enormous Landmate
designed for the rigors
of deployment in outer space.
The Stymphalean was
such an accomplishment,
it eclipsed anything Poseidon
had made, and suddenly,
we Argonauts were on the map.
No surprise what happened next.
In order to safeguard
the tech and those
who made it from
outside forces.
Alcides declared the Argonaut
an independent state.
Obviously, Posiedon
was having none of that.
Soon we were besieged by
pirates looking to claim
the Stymphalean, operatives
from the major nations,
and soldiers-of-fortune
of every stripe.
As a result, Alcides
brought in your
old man as a
defense consultant.
Tell me something.
The entire world is
gunning for the Argonauts.
Is this voyage of yours really
gonna to better mankind?
It's hard to say.
Still.
I think it's too late
for peace at this point.
It is my destiny to
remain with my people.
I must live out my life
as the hero they deserve.
Karl.
Say that you'll join me.
It's tempting,
but I have to return home.
The situation there's
only getting worse.
So what is it you
hope to accomplish?
Gotta look out for my own.
Your wife?
I have a little girl on the way.
The world's a hell of a place,
so I'm gonna toughen her up.
That way, she'll live
through anything.
With those words,
Karl left the Argonauts.
All that time, was he just
trying to keep me safe?
I just want to keep you safe.
Like Karl.
As fate would have it,
Alcides was about to
become a father, too.
Hyllus, I assume?
No.
Hyllus is nothing more than
a bioroid created from
Alcides's genes.
Huh?
Poseidon attacked us one night.
Alcides shielded the
mother of his unborn child
with his own body,
and met his end.
Thus the voyage of the
Argonauts came to an end.
Plate tectonics stole the
waves out from underneath us,
leaving the ship to
rust in a sea of sand.
But...
Alcides left his people with
more than just memories
to show for his leadership.
So you're telling
me that it's real.
Your outer-space Landmate.
Isn't that what you
came here to find?
Suppose there's no
harm in showing you.
Huh?
A paradise where people
can live like people.
There she sits.
That's the Stymphalean?
But it's just a pile of junk!
That thing can't even stand up
much less fly into outer space.
What you demean as junk,
I consider our hope.
In the words of Alcides.
"Protect not the
things you cherish,
but the means to make them."
Our people wield the knowledge
to repair that broken Landmate.
And they shall!
That's enough, Hyllus.
Your pride will bring
calamity raining down on us.
I didn't lengthen my life
with this contraption just
to watch some cocksure upstart
jeopardize the Argonauts.
I am the son of Alcides
and the inheritor of his will!
I don't know if you
were sent here from
Olympus or Poseidon,
miss, but either way.
If Hyllus were created
by your people
and sent here to
stir up trouble,
I wouldn't be a bit surprised.
If you declare independence,
you know that
Poseidon will try
to destroy you.
That's a price I'm glad to pay.
A hero must glorify the name
of his people the world over.
A hero looks out for the people
they're supposed to protect!
What do you know of heroism?
"Vengeance belongeth unto me."
Who's there?
Alcides?
Hyllus!
No!
How can you be so blind?
"Vengeance belongeth unto me.
I will recompense."
So sayeth the Lord
to His faithful.
Poseidon's plans to attack
the Argonauts've just
been called off.
Turns out they got
some intel that
confirms the terrorist
ringleader's been killed.
Aw, we're all dressed up
and nowhere to go?
What about Deunan?
Lance?
The Poseidon recon team
has been looking for a signal.
The implant in her
chest is off line.
There're no signs of life.
What's going on?
An accident?
Oh man!
No way!
♪ closing song ♪