♪ opening song ♪
A Hekatoncheires!
Briareos?
Is this really it?
Our paradise?
Awesome.
The forecast got it wrong.
Couldn't ask for better
weather than that!
Hey, Deunan.
You ready yet?
Calm down, just another minute.
Okay, all set.
Great.
Well?
Uh.
Yeah.
Looks nice.
Let's go.
What?
That's all you have to say?
You're sure worked up over
a one-night vacation.
How often do we
get time off work?
I say that we try to
enjoy it to its fullest.
As soon as we get there?
I'm gonna change clothes,
hit the beach and then order
a pina colada the
size of my head.
Something wrong?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
Come in Poseidon Air M727,
this is OAS Control.
Do you copy, Poseidon?
You're off course.
Please adjust to your
flight plan right away.
This is an urgent request.
Do you read me
Poseidon; come in.
What's wrong?
M727's veering off course.
They keep getting further
and further off track.
Keep at it.
Reach them.
Control tower calling.
What's going on, M727?
Course correct immediately!
I repeat.
This is OAS Control.
Lance here.
Your request for vacation
leave has been rescinded.
Sorry.
What?
We put this in months ago!
We need you back at base now.
This is urgent.
Understand?
Aw, man.
This, sucks.
We've just received information
that an ultra-high capacity
passenger plane flying from
Poseidon to Paris
has been hijacked.
As of thirteen minutes ago, the
plane dropped communication
and altered its course,
and appears to
be headed straight for Olympus.
Who's behind it?
From what we've gathered.
it's a group of Human
Liberation Front sympathizers.
They've actively claimed
responsibility for the act.
And they're demanding
the immediate release
of their captive allies.
That's just crazy.
No country's gonna
offer them asylum.
As for the hostages, they come
to a total of three thousand.
We don't have much intel, so I
need a Hekaton in charge.
I'm leaving it up
to you and Deunan.
That's all.
We could've had a nice trip but
you've just gotta be a Hekaton.
I don't want to hear
any whining, Deunan.
Get your asses back here!
So what's the story on this
Human Liberation Front?
Even for human supremacists
they do seem a little extreme,
with this "opposing
all robotics,
even cyborgs and
bioroids" thing.
Calling them extremists
is putting it lightly.
The life of a bioroid
means about as much
to them as batteries
in a flashlight.
Damn.
They're just modified humans.
I mean sure, they've got an
inhibitor on their emotions
and lifespan, but that's
their only real difference.
Well that's true.
Bioroids and humans are
essentially the same, but still.
Some people will only
see the differences,
and convince
themselves that these
distinctions make them
superior somehow.
So stupid.
Pure-blooded humans are an
endangered species these days.
They commit these acts out of a
desperate fear for preservation.
Not everyone can be a
roll-with-the-punches,
ballsy hellcat like you.
It's somewhat sad, isn't it?
So many of these humans agreed
to relocate to our paradise.
Only to find themselves becoming
completely reliant on us.
Incapable of managing crises.
Just as the Legislative
Bureau assumed.
I suppose it is
a natural response.
Fundamentalists rallying
for a strictly human society.
It's an inevitable
course of action.
So you're willing to
dismiss their grossly
simple-minded methods?
The fact that their reactions
are base and instinctual
makes it all the more
comforting to them.
Maybe it's our paradise.
Perhaps Olympus is too
utopian for their lifestyle.
Stress and anxiety
have always been
a factor in the
lives of humans.
Expunging it might cause
them to lose self-control.
Yes, except.
It's what humans
have always wanted.
The world they say they've
always dreamed of,
and now it's come true.
We've been chosen
to watch after it.
Bioroids are the
caretakers of this world.
Which does raise a single
important question.
How do we as bioroids truly help
the humans to live a human life?
I'm certain this group
must realize that their
demands are beyond the
realm of attainability.
We won't release a bunch
of dangerous convicts.
Then what would be the
purpose of their demand?
Unless it's a distraction
to throw us off their
true intentions.
Which leads to the next concern.
What if they're planning
to use the plane
to commit an act of terrorism?
Our intelligence has
compiled a partial list.
And every suspected passenger?
They're all bioroids.
Not a single human on the plane.
Terrorism sounds
the most likely.
Do you think Tartaros
is their target?
Yes.
It's the point of
origin for all bioroids.
The genes used to create
them are cryogenically
preserved there.
I would imagine that they see
some perverse significance in
using the lives of the
bioroids on the plane,
to wipe out the
epicenter of their species.
Better safe than sorry.
We'll deploy
our intercept system.
Good idea, sir.
What's wrong?
Don't try to tell
me you're nervous.
Maybe I am.
Hey, Briareos.
After we're done with this, take
me out for a fancy dinner, okay?
This might not be
our idea of paradise.
but we can at least have a
nice meal every once in a while.
I'm guessing you
have someplace in mind?
This place Hitomi told me about.
She says it has this
totally incredible
view of the city at night.
S'fine with me, but I don't
think a place like that
is gonna serve the burgers and
fries you call a nice meal.
Quit making me out to sound
like some kind of savage.
Where ever would
I get that idea.
It's time.
Let's get this wrapped up
so we can salvage what's
left of our vacation.
Sounds like a plan!
We'll attach
ourselves to the belly.
Then we can get in through the
emergency exits under the wings.
Let's do it.
No sign of a single
passenger anywhere.
It's a genuine ghost plane.
It's definitely odd
to say the least.
There some secret compartment in
this thing we don't know about?
Any bio-signs?
Yeah.
I'm still picking up
a strong reading
for all 3,000
supposed passengers.
Well, that's a relief.
At least we know the
hostages are still alive.
For the moment, at least.
And now?
What's next, should we
try and secure the cockpit?
I'm concerned
about the hostages.
Let's do a thorough
search of the plane.
Just remember.
Don't start a firefight
without you backing me up.
Is that it?
Exactly.
What the hell?!
You can't do this!
This is an official office of
the Human Liberation Front!
Yes, we're aware of that.
It's a very low-level office,
though, wouldn't you say?
Who the hell are you guys?
Oh, we're just an
excitable hooligan
and a combat cyborg
from ES.W.A.T.
But why should you
be worried about that?
ES.W.A.T?
Please!
Don't kill me!
I'll do anything!
Sheesh.
I just wanted to ask
you some questions.
I'm not gonna kill a fellow
cyborg, even a petty one.
Find anything?
Just the jackpot.
Our lucky day!
What's on it?
You know how Gina couldn't
stop griping about
her visit to the
Poseidon office earlier?
S'cause they're sticking close
to the privacy protection laws.
Refusing to share the
full passenger manifest
for some reason.
Bet I could have
gotten it outta them.
She always does have
to play by the rules.
I take it it's on there?
You got it.
So why does the HLF have this
classified Poseidon information?
Mighty bit suspicious
don't ya think?
That's an easy one.
There's gotta be an
unknown 3rd party
secretly in the mix somehow.
Mmm hmm.
My thoughts exactly.
So you're thinking the
HLF got it's hands on
the manifest from
some sort of mole?
And then they used the info
to plan out this hijacking?
Everywhere I checked was empty.
Same here.
But I'm still picking up
bio-readings loud and clear.
This is starting to
get downright creepy.
It really is a ghost plane.
Only one place we
haven't checked yet.
Cockpit it is.
It's on auto-pilot.
Lance's guess was right.
The plane is heading straight
for Tartaros in Olympus.
Not only that, but they've
locked the auto-pilot
to prevent anyone else
from overwriting it.
What is this?
Don't!
It's a bomb?
That's right...
...an older model
set off by vibration.
It's a simple design,
but they're tough to disarm.
What now?
I'm willing to bet
that whoever's behind
this is watching how things
unfold from nearby airspace.
So.
What's our play?
Repay the favor for
snaring us in this trap.
Here's the plan.
Suit up in your Guges.
Hunt them down
and settle the score.
Wait.
You mean without you?
There are hostages on board
even though we can't find them.
We gotta play this safe.
We can't risk them
remotely triggering
the bomb when we catch them.
All of our bases have
to be covered here.
So I'm gonna stay behind and
work on disarming the bomb.
Get a move on.
Briareos!
Don't worry.
I successfully managed to
disarm the bomb in the cockpit.
They must've wired it to
alert them when it was
deactivated so they launched
a missle on the plane.
Guess they covered
all their bases, too.
They're close.
Be careful out there.
Don't you worry.
I've got this.
A flying pillbox.
Your camouflage is worthless.
I found 'em.
Time to call off the plan.
I don't really feel
like dying today.
Briareos!
You bastards!
Relax, Deunan.
Did you forget?
A Hekaton can plug
in and operate
an entire aircraft carrier.
Even with the engines
out, I think I can
handle a passenger
plane just fine.
You're sure?
The passengers'
lives take priority.
Don't think about me,
just focus on taking them down.
It's charging for us!
Calm down, alright?
Only reason it
moves that fast is
cause its armor is paper thin.
We only need one
hit to take it down.
Why the hell would you
throw your weapon away?
You are so dead!
That would be checkmate.
I demand a lawyer.
And a lawful interrogation.
I know all my rights, dammit.
Save your routine for
the team on the ground.
Of course, to tell the truth,
those guys aren't nearly
as friendly as I am, so.
It's a miracle.
He landed it like was
a walk in the park.
Even with three engines out.
I take it you've never
met a Hekaton before.
If you'll excuse me.
Briareos!
I'm so glad you're okay!
And thanks to you.
all the hostages
are safe as well.
Deia... what are you doing here?
On behalf of the
Tartaros Center,
I extend to you my gratitude.
Meet the head of the
next-gen bioroid project.
Mr. Eurys.
Thank you for your
help in retrieving
the 3000 frozen embryos.
You're telling me
that the hostages.
were these?
Once a bioroid ovum
has been fertilized
it's considered a
living organism.
All it needs is to correctly
incubate for growth.
Sounds a bit murky
to me, but okay.
You've saved the future
of the next-gen bioroids.
And Olympus as well.
These embryos are
this city's great hope.
Someday they'll help watch
over your paradise here.
Paradise, huh?
About time!
Let's enjoy our vacation!
The beach is a lost cause,
but at least we can
check out the restaurant
with the great view!
You're excited.
Well take a look at that.
Seems like the forecast managed
to finally catch up to us.
There goes your view.
You wanna do burgers and fries?
This sucks!
♪ closing song ♪