♪ opening song ♪
A sculptor named Poeas.
He's one of the few remaining
unprocessed bioroids.
And our latest assignment.
We're on a 24-7 security
watch starting tomorrow.
Daddy! Daddy!
Oh honey, I know.
Do you think you're the only
person who understands loss?
And the feelings of everyone
else are somehow beneath yours?
They're not human.
They're basically objects.
Wow.
Wait. I know these.
What's with the bandage?
It's a technique elderly
sculptors employ.
The tightened bandage
helps to strengthen their
grip enough to continue
with their work.
He wakes up every morning
before sunrise, and then
he works for precisely fifteen
hours, to the very second.
And that's apparently
how he's lived his life
here for the past
three years straight.
Three whole years?
Hey, Deunan!
Good work out there.
Hitomi. I didn't know
you were here.
Any updates?
Just that he has a
bland appetite.
He ate some bread, drank
some water and went to bed.
His existence really does
revolve around his work, huh?
I'm guessing he's lived
his whole life this way.
They're not human.
They're basically objects.
Thirsty?
Thanks so much, Hitomi.
But you really didn't have to
go to the trouble of
bringing me extra clothes.
You should be with your baby.
Oh it's fine, Yoshitsune
offered to babysit.
Besides, it's nice to have
a little break from the
baby every once in a while.
This is like a short vacation.
It doesn't even matter if
they lose their families.
They can simply
collect a replacement.
It's so weird how delicate our
society is. Gaia carefully
determines the very balance
of our existence, even mine.
Some of us are given
the gift of motherhood,
while others dedicate
their lives to a craft.
Yeah, right.
It's milk time! I'm gonna
have a cranky baby. See ya!
That's not what I
would call a vacation.
Seemed more like a power lunch.
I guess that's her job.
I get the feeling she was
just checking up on you.
Why?
I think she's a little
worried this stuff
with Deia's got you down.
And that concludes my report.
Although. This whole business
of you sending ES.W.A.T to
guard me at my home. It's not
exactly the peace and quiet
that I'm used to.
I know you're worried,
but it seems like overkill.
You think that I'm bad? Well
the Judicial Bureau's worse.
From what I understand,
they intend to use
both FBI and
ES.W.A.T surveillance.
Don't get me wrong,
I understand the rationale.
I'd imagine that you are
concerned with giving off
the impression that you
have things under control.
And I get the feeling
you're telling me my
cautious approach
makes me look weak.
Not at all. I'm simply
admiring your perspicacity.
Well then. I should get going.
This neuro-augmentation.
It should give you a
processing capacity
more advanced than a Hekaton.
However, the neural strain
and heat generation
it'll cause,
I doubt the upgrade
will be worth the pain.
I don't have a choice.
There's no time for hesitation.
I'm your business partner
so I'll do what you're asking,
but I have my reservations.
Tell me this. Imagine
you lost the man you loved.
If it was your fault,
would you be unchanged?
Such melancholy eyes.
Are you familiar with
the beast I'm sculpting?
It's the Hydra.
The Hydra?
The hero Hercules was
cursed by the goddess Hera,
which caused him
to uncontrollably
slay his own sons. As atonement
for committing this atrocity,
he performed twelve
incredible labors.
The Nemean Lion.
The Ceryneian Hind.
The Erymanthian Boar.
The Augean Stables.
The Stymphalian Birds.
The Cretan Bull.
The Mares of Diomedes.
The girdle of the
Queen of the Amazons.
The Cattle of Geryon.
The golden apples of
the Hesperides.
The guard dog of
the Underworld, Cerberus.
And this creature before you,
the Lernaean Hydra.
So once you complete that
one, they'll all be finished?
Well, that's assuming
that I'm even capable
of completing this one.
It's the last.
Why wouldn't you finish?
As much as I know
it appears to be,
sculpting's not about
reshaping stone.
It's about finding the breath
of life concealed within the
core of the rock, and then
revealing the true appearance
of the stone.
But for some reason.
I just can't seem to discover
the truth within this stone.
No matter how hard I try to
find it, it keeps evading me.
It belonged to my late husband.
Something of his
I kept as a memento.
The sadness of losing someone
you love. It produces hate.
Hercules.
A normal human being. A man
cursed by the powers above
to kill the ones that he loved.
You feel it too, don't you?
This sadness.
It's hard to explain, but
I suddenly get these
overwhelming waves of bleakness.
Well, the future looks dark.
The way you speak, my dear.
Maybe I'm wrong but,
you sound as though
you're ready to give up.
Oh! Sorry. Just ignore me. I'm
pretty sure that came out
sounding a lot stranger
than I meant it to.
No, no. It's alright.
If you don't mind, would
you tell me your name.
Oh, of course.
It's Deunan Knute.
Not to state the obvious,
but I'm with ES.W.A.T.
I'm here to protect you.
My personal bodyguard, huh?
Well I do hope you're
good at your job.
Naturally.
The Hydra is a mythical
serpentiform beast
with nine heads. Severing one
of the heads is pointless
as two will sprout from
the wound to replace it.
To prevent this,
Hercules requested the help
of his friend Iolaus to
defeat the monster.
The two men burned the
creature's multiple heads
with torches, cauterizing them
before they could grow back.
In that story we
find a universal truth.
A single thoughtless act can
beget more and more hatred.
Until it spawns a terrifying
beast, damning all in its path.
Sadness devoid of hatred,
is just a plea for pity.
It is true.
I actually know someone.
She was so filled with sorrow
that she was overcome
with a burning hatred.
Maybe the Hydra's rage
was born from sadness.
The same way her hatred was.
But what made Hercules
continue to fight?
Was it just a sense
of responsibility?
Or was it redemption?
Atonement, as you said.
This sculpture...
Its very essence is modeled
after someone I knew.
It is?
That's right.
His name was Ercole.
He was a fellow sculptor,
a peer of mine.
Aside from the obvious,
we shared many similarities
in our lives. Except for
the major distinction that
I'm a bioroid, and
he was a human.
We had joined the same
workshop and shared a passion
for honing our craft,
even to the
point of competing
with one another.
But there our
experiences diverged.
Even though our sculptures
were of matching quality,
his work drew a constant
parade of admirers.
While my creations?
They were, without fail,
critically ignored.
He was the only one
who gave me any support.
Who appreciated my work.
Always there to calm
me with a gentle smile.
Inevitably, he realized the
truth behind that disparity.
Neither his talent nor the
beauty of his sculptures were
reason enough for his supporters
to so outnumber my own.
The truth was that Gaia had
produced bioroids whose sole
purpose was to support the
human artists of Olympus,
regardless of their ability
or the quality of their art.
Ashamed of his vanity in
accepting this for so long,
and of his very need for such
praise, he took his own life.
There hasn't been a single
human artist working in
Olympus since that day.
Gaia simply will not allow it.
The concern over humans
self-destructing has trumped
their intrinsic
need to create art.
However, this ban did
not apply to bioroids.
Not only was my genetic
structure engineered to
enhance my craftsmanship,
it was also carefully designed
to withstand the
crushing disappointments
of being an artist.
Ever since his death. It's been
my responsibility to assume the
workload that should've
been shared by my friend.
After some time. Gaia asked
me to create a monument
to commemorate the ideals
behind the Ark Project.
I was immediately
reminded of a dream Ercole
once shared with me. A vision in
which he and I worked together
to create a series of sculptures
depicting a hero overcoming
tremendous obstacles as he
moved toward the future.
It was meant to provide hope for
the world as it marched onward.
Creating the twelve labors of
Hercules was my way of sharing
Ercole's dream with the world. A
way to inspire anyone who comes
to Olympus in
search of paradise,
regardless of how their
biology might classify them.
Human, bioroid,
robot or cyborg.
I wanted to share his aspiration
with each and every one.
But no matter how hard I try,
I just can't seem to complete
this final sculpture of
Hercules battling the Hydra.
I guess it makes sense.
I was unable to do anything to
help Ercole in my youth.
Perhaps the task is even
further beyond me now.
I'm certain that Ercole
could've finished this piece.
There isn't a doubt in my mind
about it. He was always capable
of bolstering my spirits.
I know he could've
created a masterpiece that would
embolden the people of Olympus.
You aren't alone, you know?
You may have felt that
you've been sculpting
by yourself all this time.
All to achieve his dream.
But really, the memory of
Ercole has been with you.
I know you can finish this.
Because your art has given
me the same hope that
Ercole gave to you.
Trust me on this. I mean
you might as well.
You trusted me with your life.
Perhaps I'm not alone.
She's attacking Eurys' mansion.
She's after Eurys?
Requesting backup!
Just a little more.
Ercole, my friend.
We're almost there.
Stop her!
That's your plan? Funny, I was
about to say the same to you.
Me too.
I'm not picking up any vital
signs. The cockpit's empty!
Eleven-Three! This one's
a decoy! Turn back now!
But that's. She can't control
the Landmate remotely!
Deia!
It's finished.
We all want the same thing.
Bioroids, cyborgs, humans.
As long as they're all
striving for the same goal,
I consider them all to
be a part of my family.
Deia!
No!
I never even heard of
that kinda thing before.
I feel like I shoulda seen it.
Don't blame yourself. Not even a
Hekaton could've simultaneously
controlled two Landmates
with the ease that she did.
I think it's quite possible
that Deia is no longer human.
♪ closing song ♪