[ominous music]
[rumbling]
[music continues]
[man] The land of the samurai.
There was a time, long ago,
when our country was called by that name.
[music continues]
[laser blasts]
[rumbling]
[man] Those dream -filled blue skies
upon which the samurai once gazed
are now filled with ships from strange worlds.
The streets where the samurai once proudly walked
are now filled with swaggering, arrogant aliens.
- [guns firing] - [people screaming]
- [alien] One more! Now! - [glass shattering]
[man] But a select few rose up to face the crisis,
one unprecedented in the Edo of old.
They were the samurai.
[ominous music]
No, wait.
They were the Z Warriors!
[roars]
[upbeat music]
[man] Part One: The Super Long Story So Far!
So, planets out there in the universe
have a thing called Altana,
a sort of energy that's like that world's life force, right?
On Earth, it's known as ley lines.
That energy led to the birth of the immortal fiend, Utsuro.
As a result of living life after life,
an existence of never -ending suffering,
Utsuro ended up with a whole bunch of personalities.
One of these was my teacher,
the founder of the Shoka Sonjuku school, Shoyo Yoshida.
With the goal of destroying the entire planet,
himself included, Utsuro waged war
against the whole dang universe.
Of course, the people of Edo resisted with all their might,
and at the end of a long, fierce battle,
the Odd Jobs and their allies showed some real strength,
and forced Utsuro to fall into the ley lines.
It was then, after using up
all his energy to contain the ley lines,
the dog deity called Sadaharu fell into a long coma.
Later, the members of the Odd Jobs
discovered their respective goals
and set off on their own personal paths.
And so, two years have gone by.
[dramatic music]
I'm gonna do it! I shall become the Pirate King!
[man] Huh? No, wait.
Not that \"two years later.\"
We've done so many two and five year little time jumps.
It's hard to keep everything straight at this point.
Ah, here! This is it!
[clears throat] Let's see. Uh...
Kagura looked to find a way to return Sadaharu back to wakey -wakey town,
while Shinpachi, he remained in Edo.
Meanwhile, Gintoki, having foreseen Utsuro's return,
made the rounds of the gates,
the openings in various scattered areas
from which the ley lines' power erupts.
You see, Utsuro's genes continued to survive
deep underground within the ley lines.
And over the two years, they rebuilt his physical form,
and he was reborn at one of the most remote ley lines.
Gintoki wandered the lands with Utsuro in tow,
who grew very rapidly.
One day, it became clear that the body housed
a personality that could actually be Shoyo.
However, Utsuro was captured by the Death Star Sect,
led by the remnants of the Tendoshu.
To prevent them from gaining a perfect immortal,
he left his heart alone with Gintoki.
In order to complete Utsuro's recovery,
and by extension, their own immortality,
the Sect then sets its sights on what?
Earth's Altana.
At the ruins of the Shoka Sonjuku,
Gintoki is reunited with Takasugi,
who has used the bones of senior student Oboro,
to become partially immortal.
In order to thwart the Sect's plans,
Gintoki and Takasugi head for Edo.
[upbeat music]
Gintoki spots the older Shinpachi and Kagura,
but doesn't make contact.
Meanwhile, Katsura, the first Prime Minister,
uses his office to investigate the Sect's actions.
- [explosion rumbling] - In order to draw out the Sect,
Takasugi blows up the Terminal
and attempts to assassinate Katsura.
- [explosion rumbling] - Katsura uses the attempt
to relinquish his position as Prime Minister.
The pupils of the Shoka Sonjuku school
once again come together.
- [siren wailing] - Even the Shinsengumi,
who were pretending to have disbanded, regroup.
Also, meanwhile, the gorilla was holding a wedding ceremony. Aw!
And after much ado, the ship carrying Kondo
attacks the Sect's Mobile Cathedral, Kuyo,
causing the wreckage to fall on top of the Terminal.
Kondo reunites with the Shinsengumi.
However, the Sect occupies the Terminal,
and the city is plunged into dangerous danger.
Edo is once again in harm's way.
This is when Shinpachi, Kagura,
and the residents of Kabuki District,
gather in front of Odd Jobs and set off to battle.
[upbeat music]
To fulfill the wishes and save their teacher,
Gintoki, Takasugi, and Katsura, decide to rescue Utsuro,
with the Terminal as the battlefield.
[dramatic music]
Will the Z Warriors be able to reclaim the future?
I don't know. You'll have to watch to find out.
Nobody is gonna pay attention
to a recap with those crappy visuals!
[both grunting]
[wolf howls]
Wolf Fang Fist!
[Gintoki groans]
Not only was the recap way too long,
the art style made it look like it was for a different show!
It looked like some damn fan -made \"Dragon Ball\" nonsense!
What? \"Dragon Ball\"?
What are you talking about, Katsurass?
[Katsura] It's not \"Katsurass,\" asshole! It's Katsura!
So the anime staff have finally gotten serious, have they?
Free from the shackles of TV production,
they've finally started putting some effort in the actual animation.
[man screams]
This is what the animation staff is truly capable of.
[Katsura] They're just drawing while holding
\"Dragon Ball\" merch in their hands!
And why do I have to be Yamcha,
while this meat head gets to be Vegeta?
That makes me look like a total freaking loser!
Give me a break. You are a loser.
[Katsura] It pains me to say it, but you're virtually identical,
and when did you become a master at growing a widow's peak?
You morons just don't get it, do you?
We've gone beyond the final TV episode,
beyond the manga's annoying cliffhangers.
and finally reached this point right here.
This is a new world, called the movie theater!
- [upbeat music] - [Gintoki screams]
It's up to us to show the fine folks in attendance
our power, and the power of Akira Toriyama!
See that Shoyo, it all worked out somehow.
Yeah. It all did work out somehow.
No matter what anybody out there says.
Got that right!
[music continues]
[Gintoki] And thus marks the end
of the cinematic exploits of Gintoki and his companions.
Their path ahead is sure to be rife
with trials and tribulations.
But they will no doubt be able to overcome them.
They will be fine, for they have the Silver Balls.
- [electricity crackling] - What in the hell are Silver Balls?
[shouts]
[man] Galick Gun!
[speaks indistinctly, groans]
Are they the type of balls that can grant wishes?
Or are they the tiny little balls
rolling around in your head you call a brain?
If balls that wonderful really existed,
none of us would be here, stuck in this position right now.
[ominous music]
[door clanking]
[footsteps thumping]
[Takasugi] But well, I guess I do feel grateful.
We managed to get this far,
and on top of that, we're still alive.
[doors creaking]
[music continues]
[Takasugi] With our own power,
and with our very own hands,
we will take back all we lost,
because that's how we,
the students of Shoyo, get things done.
[ominous music]
[soft music]
[no audio]
[music continues]
[clanking]
- [beeping] - [bomb explodes]
- [men screaming] - Fire!
[guns firing]
[men screaming]
[ominous music]
[guns firing]
Eliminate them!
Bring the hammer down upon those heretics
who would interfere with our divine summon-- [groans]
Divine summoning?
That's rich, coming from a bunch of fools
looking for immortality on the cheap!
- Catch! - [bomb beeping]
- [bomb explodes] - [men screaming]
[ominous music]
Look there, their ship is down,
but it's still drawing Altana
from the Earth through the Terminal's core.
[Takasugi] Does that mean the Star-drain gate
is still operating?
[Gintoki] Okay, question, and with that Altana,
can even an incomplete god without a heart
be brought back to life?
[ominous music]
[guns firing]
- [bomb beeping] - [bomb explodes]
[Katsura] I'm more surprised that so many people
want to live forever in this awful world.
My life has put me through
more than enough joys and sorrows.
If I can overcome that last final trial with you guys,
then guess what fellas?
[man groaning]
I won't mind, if my life were to end right here and now!
- [men groaning] - [bomb beeping]
- [bomb explodes] - [men screaming]
[scoffs]
Would our meeting be one of the joys?
- [bomb beeping] - [bomb explodes]
Or is it one of the sorrows?
[Takasugi] There's really no telling at this point.
But one thing is for sure, without a doubt.
[glass shattering]
[Gintoki screams]
[both screaming]
We hated each other and we tried to kill each other,
but still our ties could not be broken.
[ominous music]
I'm so sick of saving you idiots.
I'm sick of the runaround. I'm sick of your dumb faces.
I only hope this is the last life you ruin for me!
- [both shouting] - [all thudding]
[Gintoki groans]
That so?
Got some bad news then.
You guys can't die just yet.
I will not let you die.
I understand how they feel.
I don't wanna die. I mean, I wanna keep on living.
[bell dinging]
[footsteps thumping]
Because there's this damn fool of a teacher
who's put me through a lot, and this other idiot
who just threw me like a stone,
and I'm not done kicking their sorry asses yet.
I also have a few things I'd like to say to Sensei.
- [soft music] - I have some things to say too.
How long will you need to beat him up to feel better?
[footsteps pattering]
[Gintoki laughs]
[music continues]
[all] An eternity of beatings would not be long enough!
- [gasps] - [gun firing]
[Katsura grunts]
[bomb explodes]
Zura!
- [Katsura groaning] - [footsteps thumping]
[ray gun zapping]
[man over speaker] To those occupying the Terminal,
you are completely surrounded.
Resistance is futile.
Give yourselves up now!
If you refuse--
Shoot them all down!
[explosion rumbling]
[ray guns zapping]
[man over speaker] Uh, if you refuse,
let me express my gratitude.
It is thanks to you all
that our country has become so damn strong!
[upbeat music]
[men shouting]
Those freaky guys.
Let's go!
It has been many long decades
since you last came to Earth, Amanto.
We've lived! Lived full of doubt and agony!
But now we can say this,
those days have not been in vain!
- [grunts] - [man groans]
[shouts]
Amidst all that we have lost,
we have found which is important,
that which we must protect!
[music continues]
Our shadows on the ground
have shown us the way to the light and here to you!
You don't scare us, not anymore.
We are going to take you all head on! Face to ugly face!
[music continues]
[all grunting]
[both] Huh! Welcome to the land of samurai.
[music continues]
Huh?
A land whose people have minds of steel.
And a land whose people possess souls of silver.
[both] We're glad you could pop by!
[men groaning]
[music continues]
[gun firing]
[ray gun zapping]
[bell dinging]
Gintoki!
[footsteps thumping]
[guns firing]
- Gintoki! - Huh?
[bomb explodes]
[gun firing]
[Kondo] Hey Pops! Little help down here!
We need to split up the enemy's defenses
surrounding the Terminal!
Yeah that sounds like some tedious crap to me.
We'll just attack the mother -scratchin' mothership up top!
[Kondo over radio] Um, right now, that ship contains all the Altana
it has already taken from the Terminal!
If we launch an attack it now,
no telling what will happen.
So ix-nay on the help.
[man grunts]
[upbeat music]
Yo. You took you your sweet ass time.
You took so long, I thought you guys [grunts]
got scared and run away.
You can't have a party without the guests of honor.
[grunts] Know what I mean?
Well, well, so you finally admit
the Odd Jobs are better than you, huh?
The hell are you talking about?
I'm just saying, if we're gonna raise a little hell,
it's more fun to do it with the nastiest devils around.
And you guys are nasty.
So I guess that would mean we're out, then, huh?
[music continues]
Let's get going. Let's go see our guests of honor.
And raise hell one last time!
[ominous music]
[alien] This is shaping up to be a long, drawn-out battle.
We should fall back and regroup.
Even if we're able to revive Utsuro,
it would be for naught if we lost the Sect in the process.
We would lose the ability to produce the elixir
and thus our chance to return to power.
There is no need to worry. Everything is going as planned.
It truly does appear as though Utsuro
can only be fueled by the Altana of Earth.
Just look! Our god is truly pleased!
He's absorbing Altana.
I'm not sure I understand.
Is it actually reconstructing his heart?
Time is nigh.
Soon my friends,
our god will awaken.
Is it not enough by now?
Prolonging any further will make it
more difficult for us to leave.
Prepare to withdraw!
[both groaning]
You have no control of your bodies.
It happened to me as well.
We Tendoshu self-destructed by stealing Utsuro's blood,
but that very same blood also brought us back.
We were being kept alive, we were being used.
[ominous music]
We were controlled by his genes.
Taken from the very moment that we took them in.
[both groaning]
We've always been a part of Utsuro,
and now it falls upon us to execute his will.
[soft music]
[music continues]
[Takasugi] Give up the heart.
Such treasures do not belong in your hands.
They are meant to hold better things.
[soft music]
[Gintoki] Since we had the same teacher,
we were fated to cross swords.
If I could do it all over again, I...
I would have loved to be one of you.
[Takasugi] I have my own things,
and you have your own things to take back, yes?
[metal clanking]
Takasugi, listen I...
[explosion rumbles]
[elevator dinging]
[guns firing]
[door creaking]
[blood dipping]
[door banging]
[bomb beeping]
[bomb explodes]
Let's get a move on.
Takasugi.
Yeah?
There's nothing left for me to take back anymore.
Everything is done.
Whatever I have lost, somehow, it has come back to me.
It's all right here and I'm here to make sure
that I don't lose any of it ever again.
- [explosion rumbles] - [both grunting]
Gintoki! Takasugi!
- [Katsura groans] - [Gintoki] Zura!
Hang on, okay!
Now!
[explosion rumbles]
- [Gintoki] You're stepping on me. - Huh?
[Gintoki] Now we're even.
You're the last person I wanna owe anything.
What a coincidence, I could say the sa-- [groans]
[dramatic music]
[Gintoki] Takasugi.
[Takasugi groans]
- [Gintoki growls] - It's over.
You people cannot defeat me.
[music continues]
Did you see it, the Utsuro that lives within me?
[Gintoki groans]
Utsuro rules over and decides for all.
His designs are inescapable. He is our fate.
[swords clanking]
[music continues]
[Takasugi] Is that so?
Then what you're telling me,
is that the only reason I'm standing here in front of you
and totally not dead, is because it is the will of Utsuro?
I don't think so. Oh, no.
We weren't led here by anyone.
We are here of our own free will.
[music continues]
[bombs explode]
[swords clanking]
[men panting]
Go! Now!
[music continues]
[swords clanking]
I am taking this back.
[ray gun zapping]
[Katsura grunts]
[metal clanking]
You are Hitsugi, isn't that correct?
One of the three crows in the Tenshoin Naraku.
Why would you go this far?
Why do you want the heart of your former chief, Utsuro, so badly?
- [shouts] - [ray gun zapping]
[upbeat music]
[Katsura grunts]
[ray gun zapping]
[explosion rumbles]
[music continues]
[grunting]
[Katsura groans]
[music continues]
[Hitsugi] Give me the heart.
[Katsura groans]
[grunting]
[shouts]
[swords clanking]
[music continues]
[building rumbling]
[grunting]
[Hitsugi groans]
[building rumbling]
Kagura! No!
- [Kagura groans] - I'm coming.
Never mind me Shinpachi. Go on ahead! [groans]
[music continues]
[rocks thudding]
[Hitsugi groans]
Give me...
the heart!
What's it for?
Naraku has already fallen apart. It is over.
[swords clanking]
And yet you still want to bring Utsuro back,
even if you have to reduce Edo to rubble in the process.
[swords clanking]
[Katsura grunts]
[explosion rumbling]
The only one...
The only one who can save him is me!
- [metal clanking] - [grunts]
[electricity crackling]
Wait, are you...
Don't tell me.
[electricity crackling]
- [dramatic music] - [Takasugi groans]
[Gintoki grunting]
[Gintoki gasps]
[Gintoki groans]
[ominous music]
- You okay? - Make good use of me.
Huh? What are you saying?
[swords clanking]
[glass shattering]
[both screaming]
[all thudding]
[ominous music]
It is futile.
You will never be able to take us down,
not with your inferior blood.
[Takasugi whimpers]
[ominous music]
[Takasugi] Then let's go ahead and see whose blood, mine or yours,
will end up draining out of our bodies first.
It could go down to the wire.
[ominous music]
Yes. Do it.
[explosion rumbles]
What is going on?
[ominous music]
[screams]
[music continues]
[groaning]
[Takasugi] Gintoki.
[music continues]
Damn it, Gintoki.
[all panting]
Foolish of you!
Unable to watch your friend sacrifice himself,
you lost a golden opportunity to slay your foes.
[Gintoki chuckles]
That sort of miracle will never happen again! [groans]
[both] Gintoki!
[ominous music]
Hey. You don't have to yell at me, you guys.
I can hear you fine.
[groans]
- [gun firing] - Damn you! [screams]
[music continues]
[gasps]
[Kagura groans]
[peaceful music]
Is that Sadaharu?
[gasps] Sadaharu!
Huh?
[both] Sadaharu!
[music continues]
[rumbling]
- [Sadaharu barks] - [triumphant music]
Sadaharu, you've been waiting to meet Gin just like us, haven't you?
Sadaharu?
- [Gintoki groans] - [all gasp]
[Gintoki screams]
Sadaharu!
[thudding]
Ah, Sadaharu. You've finally come back to us.
You've come back to help us and help us help Gintoki.
[whines]
Sadaharu!
I'm pretty sure I just saw an arm.
Hold it! I'm happy Sadaharu's back, but he ate Gintoki!
I mean, did you see that? He just swallowed him whole!
It's understandable.
Sadaharu just recovered, so he needs something to eat, duh.
[Shinpachi] Then he didn't come to help. He just showed up 'cause he was hungry!
Don't you even worry about it. Gin's trash.
He'll probably pass right through, like the turd he is.
- [Shinpachi gasps] Gin! - [Kagura] See!
What kind of nightmare reunion is this?
Come on!
Squeeze him out.
[upbeat music]
What do you want?
Uh, sorry. I was looking for someone else.
[Sadaharu farts]
[ominous music]
Some freaking old dude just came out his ass!
And then went right back in!
[Kagura] A parasite, maybe?
Sad is always eating junk off the ground.
[Shinpachi] What kind of parasite looks like
it needs to pay butt rent?
[Sadaharu farts]
Oh yeah, that felt good.
What the H is going on? There's more!
Wait! What was in there? Were you guys in a bathhouse?
Your skin looks great! Excuse me you guys!
Did you happen to see a young silver-haired fella in there?
So prematurely gray?
Oh, I take it you must mean the new fella.
Ah! That kid said he was taking a different exit.
Saying he didn't wanna be covered in a bunch of filthy filth.
[Shinpachi] Ew! I guess that's kind of better.
[Gintoki coughs]
- Gintoki. - [Gintoki] Remember what I said?
If you ever found something that you really needed
to with your life, I would close up shop.
Does the fact that you're here
mean that you've gone back to having absolutely nothing?
Not at all.
We're here because there's something that we need to do.
Gintoki, we didn't become Odd Jobs
because we had nothing else better to do, you know.
I mean, we were fine with anything.
Anything at all would have done.
As long as we could be here,
with you and everyone else.
[both] That's why we will be Odd Jobs forever!
[soft music]
Well, jeez.
In the time that I was away,
you two've gone and grown up so much.
[music continues]
My back really hurts, do you mind giving me a hand?
[both chuckle]
Come on, you are sounding pretty pathetic.
And you call yourself an Odd Job?
[Gintoki] Surely your list of services includes compassion.
Can I get an employee discount?
Apparently, it's not that we've grown bigger or anything,
but that Gin's gotten smaller.
Even dumber too.
[all laughing]
But, seriously, you shrunk and look pretty stupid.
Hey, you better watch your mouth Shinpachi,
Or my Shun Oguri legs are gonna kick your scrawny, puny ass.
Whatever! More like Short Oguri!
What is going on? I mean, What happened to you?
Maybe a little bit of me got digested inside Sadaharu?
Think so?
Did you happen see anything else come out before I did?
A couple of old-timers fresh from a bath!
[Gintoki] Hey, what do you two farts think you're doing?
Gintoki Sepia! Gintoki Austere!
Sepia? Austere?
You know, you can't just split off from me without asking.
Only when together are we, Ginto-three.
[Shinpachi] Wait, what? Ginto-three?
Okay, lets go! Get back in there! I need my legs back!
Piss off, I'm never going back
to being someone's appendix.
What kind of brainless moron
stuffs his damn feet into boots?
What is wrong with him?
Why is he starting to add to his character profile
in the last freaking movie?
- [explosion rumbles] - [gasps]
[Shinpachi] Oh crap!
- [gun firing] - Hurry up, Gin! We need to go!
[Shinpachi] Great, now we're back to square one again!
Shinpachi, focus, we need to somehow get Gintoki Sakata
reconstructed inside of Sadaharu!
- What in the hey-hey? - [growls]
Okay fine. Whatever happens, happens!
[both] Come back to us, Gintoki Sakata!
- [Sadaharu farts] - [glass shattering]
[upbeat music]
[man] That man had eyes too fierce to be a samurai,
but too focused to just be some thug.
Just like always.
[music continues]
[no audio]
[Takasugi groans]
[panting]
[blood dripping]
Uh, you okay?
- [banging] - [gasps]
[electricity crackling in distance]
Huh?
[Gintoki] Dammit!
I got all the way up there once,
and now I have to do it all over again.
[tires screeching]
[car engine revving]
Uhh...
[tires screeching]
[car window creaking]
- You kids in a hurry? - [all gasp]
I can give you a ride to the final boss for super cheap.
Oh! Look it's you, Madao.
Yeah. I kind of quit being a hero.
I'm gonna starting over from scratch again.
- [glass shattering] - [grunts]
Come on and get in, you stupid Earthlings!
[all shouting]
[car engine revving]
[all screaming]
- Yeah! Get some! - [gun firing]
[Shinpachi] Somebody let me in!
[all screaming]
You people could not have done it.
[sighs]
You finally met your teacher again. [groans]
How could you have put an end to him?
You were trying to prevent Utsuro's return, weren't you?
Now, at long last,
he will finally be able to rest.
[ominous music]
Now that I have this body,
which refuses to die even when rotting away,
I now understood the pain of being eternal.
I caught a glimpse of his deep solitude.
[Hitsugi sighs]
[electricity crackling]
[Hitsugi] I pray that at least in the end,
he may go out humanely.
[dramatic music]
[electricity crackling]
[ominous music]
Ah! Yes!
[glass shattering]
[car engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[Gintoki groans]
- [Kagura grunts] - [Gintoki groans]
Well that hurt.
Get your asses moving!
[panting]
[sighs]
[building rumbling]
[gasps]
Gintoki!
[Gintoki groans]
[electricity crackling]
[man groaning]
[Utsuro] Who brought me back to this world? Was it you?
[man] Utsuro.
I have inherited your blood.
Tell me, what is your desire?
Revenge on mankind? The destruction of the universe?
Whatever it is, I shall follow you and your commands.
There is only one thing that I truly I desire.
[squelching]
[electricity crackling]
But, well, it would seems that there is
something else I need to take care of first.
[ominous music]
[Takasugi] Sensei.
[soft music]
[groans]
You're Sensei,
are you not?
Please, do not look so sad, so down-trodden,
I will protect you, we will protect you
from anything and anyone who means you harm.
So please... [groans]
[groans]
Please come back with us... [coughs]
To the school. [coughs] Come back--back to Shoka Sonjuku.
I have so much to tell you, so very much to tell you.
And it is my sworn duty
to attend to you every need, Sensei.
Sensei...
[Utsuro] I...
I'm not the kind of person you should call Sensei anymore.
That time is over, I cannot go back to being Shoyo Yoshida.
[ominous music]
Forgive me.
You were the ones who I truly wished to protect,
but I could not.
In the end I couldn't help a single one of you.
Please forgive me.
[heart beating]
- [blade thuds] - [grunts]
[electricity crackling]
[Utsuro] There's no need to apologize.
Oh, Shoyo.
I knew all along that you couldn't protect anything.
It is beyond your capabilities.
How I waited for this, this moment to come,
just like you waited, oh, so long ago.
I just needed you to let your guard down,
while hiding away like a coward inside this pupil of yours.
[dramatic music]
[electricity crackling]
[explosion rumbles]
[glass shattering]
[building rumbling]
[Gintoki] Shinpachi! Kagura!
[shouts] Goddammit!
[panting]
[ominous music]
Two years ago, young Gintoki,
as you decided to reject me,
I believe I gave you some advice.
So long as you live,
tragedy and misery will continue.
I can hear his voice very clearly.
It says he wants to put an end,
[chuckles]
to anything and everything.
[Gintoki] Yeah? Well, I couldn't agree more.
Let's end this.
With our swords.
You still carry that little twig? [chuckles]
[Utsuro groans]
[Gintoki groans]
[Utsuro laughs]
[rumbling]
[Utsuro gasps]
[Gintoki] Utsuro, we may have to put several of these twigs
together to do it, but we will take back
what we lost that day.
That's a promise, I swear to you.
- [grunts] - [blade slices]
[ground rumbling]
[swords clanking]
Your little promise was broken along time ago,
by the very man you foolishly call your friend.
[wind whistling]
Utsuro, no matter what number of tragedies
may forever fall on that man,
he is not the type of person
to ever say he wants to end things.
You know what he's more likely to say at times like these?
Oh, he knows, I will simply destroy
this rotten festering world you walk so freely upon.
You know a place where you don't belong.
[Utsuro gasps]
- [gasps] - [ominous music]
[Utsuro groans]
[blood spatters]
[ominous music]
Utsuro, you are not alone. You are not the only one here.
[footsteps thumping]
Where is Shoyo's corpse?
I wanna see his lifeless body before me.
[Gintoki] A corpse?
There was never one here to begin with.
The one body lying flat on the ground was you, Utsuro.
[ominous music]
My Sensei, as much of a problem student I was,
it seems I had some homework left to do.
Go.
Don't worry. You have many more students.
Many more than just us.
[Kagura groans]
- [explosion rumbles] - [Kagura screams]
- [Sadaharu growling] - [Shinpachi gasps]
[Utsuro] I'll leave you to them and them to you.
[all gasp]
[Utsuro groaning]
[Gintoki] You aren't some immortal demon anymore.
The moment you entered his body, you were done for.
I will put an end to you just like you wish, Utsuro.
And also, I'll end your pathetic sob story.
You think you have the ability to kill me?
You wanted to save him, did you not?
Wanted to protect him, I know you did.
I learned that fact all too well
during our travels to get here.
If you kill your master for your friends,
and then kill your friend for your master,
what will that leave you with?
Nothing.
You will be nothing but a hollow void.
Do you have what it takes to survive
through such dark emptiness? [grunts]
Utsuro, I will never be empty inside.
[grunts]
[swords clanking]
[Gintoki] What I wanted to protect is right here with me.
With me in spirit.
[Utsuro gasps]
[Utsuro groans]
[swords clanking]
[shouts]
[Utsuro groans]
[blow thuds]
[Gintoki screams]
[no audio]
- [sword whooshing] - [blow thuds]
[sword whooshing]
[Utsuro groans]
[blow thuds]
[Gintoki shouts]
[Utsuro sighs]
Humans beings are hollow,
but because they know that fact,
they take root in the hearts of others,
never fading, even after death has come for them,
and therefore, continue to live on forever.
[no audio]
[wind blowing]
[sword clanking]
[Takasugi] The score is now 246 to 247,
and you know what?
I wouldn't have it any other way either.
How the mighty have fallen, huh?
In our final duel,
I let someone else fight in my stead and lost.
It was your sword that finally took him down,
and the one who protected Shoyo and me,
was you, it was all you.
[chuckles] Nothing could feel any worse
than a victory given to me out of pity from you.
I couldn't make you, I couldn't force you
to cut down Sensei again.
Because, compared to him,
I was a much easier target, wasn't I?
Damn straight!
There's no other face in the universe
I enjoy punching as much as yours.
- [gentle music] - It was the same when we were kids.
We fought every time we met.
I figured growing up some would fix that,
but we remained competitive little brats the whole time.
And in your case, you didn't even manage
to grow out of being such a jerk.
[Takasugi] Eat it, you asshole.
[Gintoki chuckles]
Maybe this is just how we were fated to end up all along, my friend.
But hey, that's not too bad, is it?
Takasugi, you know what?
As much as we love to fight each other,
that's not all.
[music continues]
We're so much more than that.
I loved to get drunk with you just as much.
[music continues]
[chuckles] Yeah, no. That's not us.
Instead of wasting time on drinks,
I would've used it to beat your face in
as many times as I could.
[Gintoki chuckles]
[music continues]
But now, I guess, I'll have to give it a rest.
You should get going.
You aren't empty, you know.
You still have plenty to protect.
[music continues]
Takasugi.
[Takasugi] Gintoki,
this crushed left eye of mine
it closed forever on that day,
with the last thing it saw etched
into the back of its eyelid.
I've lived my entire life looking at your gloomy
pasty face and I gotta say, I'm sick of it.
So at least when my other eye closes,
don't go looking like a goddamn pouty pants again, all right.
[crying]
The cocky little kid who stood tall
before me when we first met.
The man I always wanted to best,
the man I spent my whole life chasing,
the man,
that prematurely gray man,
is so much better than that.
Do you hear me?
I... [sobs]
Wait for me in hell, Takasugi, my old friend.
You don't get to quit while you're ahead.
I'll beat you for sure next time.
Yeah, you wish.
[music continues]
[Gintoki crying]
[electricity crackling]
[machines beeping]
Oh man! That ship sucked up way too much Altana!
[creaking]
I must say, I don't understand why you're helping me,
I'm the direct cause of all this pain and tragedy.
Whenever you see someone in need, you help them out
and then run off with all their money.
That's what Gintoki Sakata has always taught us over the years.
And besides, I've always wanted to talk to the guy
who made him the person who he is today.
[Shoyo] I'm afraid it's the other way around.
[soft music]
If I had never met them,
I would have remained as empty as Utsuro.
They made... they made me human.
[music continues]
But, my mere existence only served to shackle them down,
and keep them from growing.
I have absolutely no right
to dare call myself their teacher.
Yeah, well, even if everything you just said is true,
it's because of you that we got to meet Gintoki Sakata.
I've always wanted to meet you so I could tell you,
thank you.
Hm.
[Shinpachi] I'm sure Gin and the others feel the same way as me.
[radio static crackles]
[Katsura] Gintoki! Takasugi! It's me.
Can you hear me? Are you all right?
Listen, we've managed to taken over Kuyo, the enemy...
the enemy is in tatters, too,
but the Terminal is still running out of control.
It's only a matter of time before it
collapses along with this ship.
Get out of here at once!
Zura! Running away won't help!
Look, if the Terminal were to go down,
all the Altana inside of it will go completely berserk.
And if worse comes to worst, this entire planet could blow!
Okay, but there must be something we can do.
- [static crackles] - Uh--
I ask that you allow me to handle this situation.
Who the hell are you? [gasps]
I'll use the weapons on-board this ship.
I will fire all of the Altana and it's mine
back down via the Terminal.
And I'll do so by using the Altana within me.
But, even if that manages to quell its rage,
the Terminal will not be left standing.
My school's biggest prodigy,
can I ask you to handle the evacuations?
I have complete confidence in you.
I want you all to live on to the next adventure.
[static crackles]
All hands should evacuate!
We need to get out of the Terminal as soon as we can!
[man] Zura! Feel free to use our ships!
Well, there you have it.
You should probably hurry up
and begin your escape as well. [groans]
Shoyo, are you okay?
It's ironic, isn't it?
I've been full of hate for all my eternal life,
but now time is not on my side.
That boy...that boy granted me what little life I have left.
A path has been paved to the future.
[energy whooshing]
You are that future, and it's my job to protect you.
[rumbling]
[door shuts]
I must last, every second counts.
[Shinpachi] Mere seconds won't be enough.
If we were to add up all our lives,
we could buy you enough time
to see your stupid student's stupid face.
[Sadaharu barks]
You kids...
We're very sorry, but we can't just...
We really can't just leave, you know.
Remember what I said?
Our job isn't over until we leave
with all your money, or something like that.
[Shinpachi] If the future's within our reach,
then we'll grab it and take off.
That is the Odd Jobs way.
Why don't you let us join you, then.
This faction, they'd been collecting Altana
from several planets across the galaxy
to mass-produce their elixirs.
If we fire it all in, then you'll
not only have time to see him,
but also smack your stupid student on his stupid head.
And how exactly would you fire it all in?
Just so you know, I can't operate anything
other than my ancient flip-phone.
What the matter? Is modern tech too much for you to handle?
Asked the with the robot body guy.
It's a good thing I'm a cellphone expert.
Machines are much the same as people.
When they refuse to listen to you, you kick their ass!
[electricity crackling]
[man] Hey, take it easy, you cuckoo crazies!
All this violence won't just get you blocked,
it'll make even Siri snap and start cussing our asses out!
Oh, that's okay.
All our feelings combined are powerful.
Even without a cellphone, they're sure to get through!
[electricity crackling]
[all groaning]
[building rumbling]
[Gintoki grunts]
[Gintoki gasps]
[Gintoki groans]
Hey.
It's you guys.
Back on your feet. We got places to be!
[radio static crackles]
[Katsura] Gintoki, keep going,
[indistinct] and the rest of the Odd Jobs should be down that way.
If there's anything you've left undone,
take care of it at once.
[Gintoki] Oh! Mister Shoka Sonjuku's biggest prodigy.
So good of you to call.
Weren't you tasked with getting everyone to safety?
[Katsura] Everyone has already evacuated.
Well, that is, except for, you losers.
Zura, Takasugi is...
[Katsura] What happened? Sensei was unaware.
[upbeat music]
That back then, whenever you two
got yourselves into some mischief,
there was another little troublemaker out there,
and he was cleaning up all your messes for you.
[thuds]
Isn't that right, Gintoki?
So I'll tell you what, if you two are up for one last act of mischief,
there is no way I can leave this place,
not until I've had the chance to
clean up your messiness all over again.
Zura.
[Katsura] Live or die, the two of us are in this together, right?
[Sakamoto] Then I would say you have to make sure
you come back alive, eh, Gintoki?
So just relax! I'll rescue you.
I'll save you from the depths of hell if I have to.
And with that said, go raise all the hell you want to, okay.
[Sakamoto and Katsura] Including our fallen friendship!
[music continues]
[gun firing]
[building rumbling]
Sogo!
[explosion rumbles]
[pipe clanking]
[Kondo grunts]
[Hijikata grunts]
[Gintoki groans]
[both groaning]
[electricity crackling]
[crystals clattering]
[grunting]
[all screaming]
[grunts]
[explosion rumbles]
[soft music]
Shoyo, I've always wanted to tell you a little something.
A lot has happened since we were together last, a lot.
Nowadays, I run an Odd Jobs business with these guys.
Yeah, I got a good look at that,
Odd Jobs Gintoki Sakata.
[crystals crackling]
You've grown into a fine man.
[energy whooshing]
[music continues]
[glass shattering]
[electricity crackling]
[music continues]
[Shoyo] Gintoki,
the people here must be to you what you once were to me.
Just as long ago on that fateful day,
the eternal beast became human
by meeting you, meeting all you kids.
The little monster, the one with the saddened eyes
he changed too, he has also become human,
has he not?
[music continues]
[ominous music]
[machine beeping]
[woman] Data transfer is now complete.
Good morning, it's good to see you Fuyo Number Zero.
- Where am I? - [machine whirring]
This would be Master Gengai's robot warehouse.
You suffered damaged during the war
and then you fell into a lengthy coma.
I am your clone, and during the time while you've been asleep,
I have been collecting all the data for you.
I am Tamako.
[Tama] I'm very sorry.
It seems my circuitry is still acting a bit glitchy at the moment.
How long did...how long was I asleep?
- [whooshing] - [bright music]
[vehicle engines revving]
[Tama] Is this really Edo?
[Tamako] No, now it is called Tokyo.
In the years following the war, Edo was reborn
and entered into a period of long sustained development.
But Tokyo would be nothing like it is today
without all of the efforts you and your friends put in.
Okay, so then I assume the world has returned to peace.
[music continues]
Although, it no longer resembles the world I once knew,
the place I once lived.
What became of everyone after the war?
[Tamako] I believe you already know the answer to that.
Oh!
[machine beeping]
[whooshing]
[Shinpachi] Tama.
Tama!
Shinpachi!
[Shinpachi] By the time you finally wake up, and obtain this data,
who knows how much time will have passed?
[soft music]
Just what was it we fought against? What did we defeat?
Or were we the ones who were defeated?
There's still no clear answer to that,
but we did make it back, back to Edo,
and back to our lives.
[electricity whooshing]
[music continues]
But when I saw Gin's slightly sad smile,
I started to fully realize
the significance of the things we'd regained
and also, the things we'd lost.
[music continues]
[Shinpachi sighs]
There really was no way he'd be back here, huh?
- [squelching] - [Gintoki snoring]
[Shinpachi screams]
How long have you been sleeping in here?
Ah! I stepped in your puke! [grunts]
I've been worried sick about you,
and you are just out getting sauced again.
Oh! O, quit your nagging! This is my own place.
Free to come home whenever I want
and puke wherever I want. [retches]
No! Don't puke in here anymore!
[retches] Now I puked.
Whoa! Whoa! What do you think you're doing?
What makes you think you can sit on my seat?
What are you talking about?
I've been taking care of things and keeping
Odd Jobs going while you butt-wads were gone!
And now, you're starting over as a lackey!
This was your idea, you know!
[Gintoki] I never said any crap like that.
You were the one who said you'd start over as a glasses frames or some shit.
[Shinpachi] I did not say that!
I think you need to start over from your dad's pair!
Your face could start over from your dad's pair.
You are not even making any freaking sense!
Now go sleep in your bed!
- [both screaming] - You can't just waltz into a lady's room!
How many times do I need to tell you losers?
Since I was the second to came back,
I am the COO, and this is my room now!
You're the COO, huh? You blew away the CEO too, you know.
CEOs everywhere are just figureheads.
All lazy, good-for- nothing leeches.
The real power rests in the hands of strong women,
like me and Beyonc, no matter where we go
we can't help but get stuff done, too bad.
[Shinpachi] Beyonc and you are very different kinds of strong,
and she was never COO!
[Kagura] Put that worthless heap of trash
in the closet where he belongs.
- [door bangs] - [munches]
[Shinpachi] Beyonc Muscles -Carter, the closet was a no-go too.
Oh, damn it! Will you two get it together!
Where the hell do I belong in this place?
Maybe, I'll just have to go ahead and mark all my spots.
[Kagura] No I don't think so!
[Shinpachi] But still, in the end, we remain the same as always.
It must be because the four of us
are finally back together again.
[electricity whooshing]
[soft music]
Oh, good grief.
I was hoping you'd have made a bunch of money
to pay off your rent, but it looks like over two years passed by
while you were just sitting around picking your nose.
Oh, with a matter this critical
we should let the new CEO handle it.
Could you not force me into the role
whenever things go south?
You can leave it to me, your leader.
I'll handle the right nostril,
and Gin can take the left one, Shinpachi can do the rest.
We need to do more that just picking out boogers.
And here I thought Shinpachi and Kagura
had actually grown in some capacity, but here you are,
and dear God, its right back to square one.
[groans]
Well, you know what they say,
one bad apple can spoil the whole barrel of monkeys.
I'd rather be one of those sweet canned apples
than a wormy one in a monkey barrel.
If you're locked up in the can, you can go bad
and it won't affect the whole bunch.
Can we please stop assuming I'm a bad apple?
[laughs]
[Shinpachi] Everyone was quick to bust our balls,
but nobody asked any questions about why we came back here.
[electricity whooshing]
[Umibozu] Because the answer was obvious.
Allow me to ask you a question in return.
Why would I ever travel across
the vastness of space to come see you?
Probably because you're bald.
I'm trying to be serious here!
I'm sorry, maybe because... Because you're bald?
Okay, okay, that's quite enough.
There is no particular reason.
One doesn't need a reason to see their family, do they?
And this is the same.
If you would like to remain here
and be a part of Odd Jobs again,
you don't need to have a reason for that either.
But it is also why that walking
disaster of a brother of yours,
might show up as well without reason.
[Shinpachi] Kagura said Umibozu looked a little sad
and he left with those words, and he also looked bald.
[electricty whooshing]
Well, whatever, I won't pitch a tizzy
as long as you still manage to pay your rent.
They say we've entered a new era and everything.
Surely, there'll be some sort of good news
to kick it off, right?
[Soyo] Have a look at this, everyone.
Can you believe how well the rebuild
of the Terminal is going?
No matter how many obstacles we find in our way,
as long as we never give up, we should be able
to get back up and continue as many times as it takes.
So please, everyone--
Princess Soyo, I hate to interrupt,
but we're all here to ask you about the assassination
of former Prime Minister, Donald Zuramp.
Rumors say that you are the one who actually
masterminded the whole thing, is it true?
[upbeat music]
[Nobume] If you believe the princess to be the kind of person
to kill anyone who gets in her way,
I have to assume you all stand here
before her, ready to die yourselves?
Nobume, please.
It's an assassin!
So then that means all the rumors were true!
Oh, man.
[Shinpachi] The only reason Edo was able to get back on its feet
was thanks to these girls.
Actually, I'm sure they had on their side
the spirits of three great men,
and, well, maybe one more.
[ObaZ laughs]
You pathetic, petulant peons.
These little puny girls could never do in the great Zuramp!
That man continues to watch over this nation
as a heroic spirit!
Never forget, if you stray from the right path,
I shall return to punish the crap out of you!
I am the Heroic Patriot ObaZ!
And so, every year, [indistinct] Katsura died.
Hey, don't take over the narration
and start killing people off!
I mean, we don't even know if that's really Katsura!
Even though it obviously is.
That idiot's already brain-dead.
Why don't you lets the numbskull go?
Oh, and this whole narration thing
you've been doing, when's it gonna end?
Wait a minute, you mean you guys could hear all that stuff?
I just wanted to make something to inform Tama
about everything that happened.
Are you trying to forcefully wrap up
this whole damn story with a sappy narration?
It's too long, who cares?
You're gonna need to keep things more concise.
[ominous music]
[Gintoki] Now, Tama, a lot has happened since then,
but I just want you to know this...
- [bell dinging] - ...everybody died, the end.
[Shinpachi] You cannot just say that!
What's the problem? Everyone out there dies eventually.
It's just lazy! Tama will want more details.
Character arcs and plot development.
Shinpachi's right, you know.
So much has happened while she wasn't around,
and all the emotions we felt.
I want her to know everything we went through.
[soft music]
The egg rolls were super yummy.
[Shinpachi] Nobody gives a solitary shit about that!
- [both laughing] - [ObaZ] I hope you saw all that.
[both] Huh?
[ObaZ] Without proper supervision, people will even stoop
- to falsifying endings. - Who is that?
- Well, it's not me! - [ObaZ] Society needs watchful eyes
that can monitor people and nations across eras.
And the only one capable of that
is the Heroic Spirit ObaZ, and ObaZ alone!
- [Kagura grunts] - [utensils clanking]
We do our best to ignore him,
and he still finds a way to sneak in.
Either way, that takes care of at least one problem.
'Kay, so, who's next?
Quit trying to force an ending where everybody dies!
And that was be the last time he played the straight man.
- [Shinpachi] I'm not dead! - [electricity whooshing]
[Shinpachi] Don't worry folks, I'm not handing over the narration. Okay.
The Zuramp Administration handed things over
to the next generation, and with that,
the Shinsengumi returned to power.
I'd like to say welcome back,
but what you've returned to is a war-zone.
[tense music]
If you are prepared to die,
then drink my friends, and puke!
[all cheering]
[glasses clanking]
[laughter]
[soft music]
[Kondo] There are no breaks in their war.
A life like that can be overwhelming at times,
but they'll be fine, because they have her.
The woman who once rebuffed all the moves
Kondo tried on her, now supports him wholly,
in both his professional and personal life.
I'm a little saddened by that,
but I'll accept it for Sis's happiness.
And perhaps, I've grown from weak little boy to grown ass man.
[Shinpachi screams]
Have a taste of the straight man's return!
Are you the a-hole who's been bullshiting the narration?
[Kondo] The question concealed my own pain,
because in was not a man, but still puny and sad.
You can stop it, I'm standing right here.
And that goes for you too, Sis!
Why are you going along with all this nonsense?
Huh? I did nothing of the sort Shinpachi.
I was just checking in.
[soft music]
[Otae] Yo, Gorilla.
Didn't I say you'd have to pay triple the price
if you were ever to show your face here again?
[Shinpachi] You were saying all kinds of crazy stuff during the narration!
Yes, my very wallet...
No, the government's coffers, they belong to you now.
Take this, it's a B's concert ticket.
Well, Gorilla, you're a naughty one, aren't you?
Not as naughty as you are sweet.
[Shinpachi] This footage has become evidence of official corruption!
You use narration to hide it, huh?
Oh, come one. You ate up all that screen time.
And the punch-line was just that
you're still a bunch of idiots? You need to fix this.
Yes, well, no news is good news, right?
I don't need a fake narration or a spin-off series,
just as long as I have this.
[Gintoki] Oh, you're wrapping things up?
Okay, you get one minute.
[ominous music]
[Sogo] Things went back to how they used to be. Alas!
That only signaled the start of a new battle
for the Shinsengumi.
[music continues]
Forget the ending, we're getting a new damn preview!
[Sogo] What is the Shinsengumi's new battle? You ask.
Who is their new foe?
[Gintoki] He's not new at all! We saw him earlier!
[Sogo] What is the Shinsengumi's new weapon?
[Gintoki] Hey, what happened to blandy?
It ain't easy being Vice Chief, is it my old friend?
But I'll keep the Shinsengumi going,
just like you would have have done yourself.
- Hijikata. - What?
Now, you're falsifying narration too?
Why are you hairy rat farts drinking instead of working?
To atone for your lack of discipline you must kill yourself!
Hijikata, its all over after this movie.
We won't get paid for any extra work.
I mean, just look at Yamazaki.
He's playing mechabaddi with the Mechazakis.
[Hijikata] Yeah, look, I don't know what mechabaddi is,
or even Mechazakis for that matter!
[Gintoki] Vice Chief, Vice Chief!
Look, we totally understand that none of you guys
have any idea how to wrap any of this up.
- So here, just take this. - [Yamazaki] Mechabaddi down.
Now pose.
Ooh, nice! That's the stuff.
[sighs]
[Kagura sighs]
Don't just walk away from me!
Why the hell did you make me dress up in this thing?
[both] I mean, the Shinsengumi have always been a little--
You know what? You two are stupid! Stupid faces!
You need to calm down.
Don't be so on edge, Hijikata.
This is the end, just take it easy.
There is no end to the duty of the police, okay!
- [Kyubei] Is that so? - [ominous music]
Then it must be the police's job to shout
and cause a scene at a private establishment?
In that case I shall also do my job.
Well, Kyubei, go on then. What's your job?
Why don't you show me? Huh?
Care for some fruit. Say, aah!
Aah!
So, you're a cabaret girl?
When I invited her to come visit with everyone,
she insisted on helping out.
I came up with a way where I could
serve men without approaching them.
With this skill I can be ranked number one.
[Gintoki] Why do you make a girl who measures
personal space with her sword serve patrons?
It's a sales tactic.
In Yoshiwara, they often play hard-to-get,
making the customers more obsessed with them!
Huh! So predictable.
That's is. Cleanup's complete.
[Gintoki] Forget hard-to-get, this is down right dangerous.
Gin, you can't...
[Gintoki] What in the name of all that is holy is she doing?
What's up? I came here to hang out like you asked me to
but I'm not really seeing any uggos here.
[utensils clanking]
[Gintoki] Your order is served sir.
Tsuki! Kyubei! Hi.
Kagura.
- I hope you've been well. - Mm-hm.
I didn't know you guys were here.
Yes. All of us.
[laughter]
Oh, now they all decide to show up.
They just wanna be in the spotlight of the big finale.
But now, we can wrap up
- all their stories in the narration. - [shouting]
What do we say about this, exactly?
That everybody got black-out drunk together?
[Otae chuckles]That doesn't sound too bad.
It suits us perfectly, does it not?
[gentle music]
[Shinapchi] Yeah, same as always.
That might just be the perfect description for all of us.
Come on, keep it together, okay.
Whatever man, I'm in perfect control over here.
Want me to list all of the Dragon Ball's
adversaries to prove it, I can do it!
[Shinpachi] Just by saying that, you've only proven
that you're wasted!
- [Gintoki] There's, uh-- - [Shinpachi] No! No! No! [thuds]
[man] Hey, lady, I'll take 10 more of these please.
Come on, now, would you just give it a rest?
We don't have any money,
we don't have any backers to pay for all this.
[man] What? Food on the Earth is so freaking good.
Besides, they say you shouldn't fight on an empty stomach.
Fight, huh? Yeah, we can't afford to do that either.
[man] Then I'll look forward to when we can. There you go lady.
Next time I'll come here to feast on the Earth itself.
[man 2] Those are some tall words
you're spoutin' there, big britches.
[man] Gotta dream big, money or no money.
[man 2 chuckles] Don't be a nincompoop.
Oh! Good job noticing us! [laughs]
- [gun firing] - [ObaZ screams]
[soft music]
[paper rustling]
[Sakamoto] We haven't talked in a while.
Hope this letter finds you well.
How have you been, Peen-toki?
Yeah, I've been flying across the universe as always.
You know, space is pretty bitchin', my friend.
You should join me on a trip sometime, Vagin-toki.
Anyway, the reason I'm writing you
is because I have something
important I'd like to say.
That day, when I promised a brave and heroic
rescue of you and everyone else, well,
once I saw the Terminal crumble down,
I was thinking, \"They dead, lololol.\" [chuckles]
[soft music]
I don't mean this to sound as
some sort of consolation or anything,
Because I truly believe, deep in my heart of hearts
that he saved you back then, so please,
you don't need to beat yourself up over it.
Your teacher's soul lives on everywhere on Earth,
and he continues to watch over you, I'm sure of that.
And I know you can feel it too.
To my beloved friend, Peen-vaginto-fuk-u.
PS, I heard something when I ran into Zura the other day.
It would seem the remnants of the Kiheitai
are making some curious moves.
[Katsura] The gates?
Indeed.
[Katsura] Who do you think you're mimicking?
She probably couldn't stand the fact
that she was so powerless.
[soft music]
But she was thankful
that after he was a prisoner for so long,
she could see him smile, once again.
[music continues]
And she says that now it's her turn.
[Katsura] Well, there is no chance of him
coming back to life like Utsuro did.
That was a miracle which only occurred
because he was born from Altana.
[groans] That's how it is and it's fine.
This is simply how we, the Kiheitai,
atone for the sins we've committed.
Takechi, you too. You're also abandoning me.
[paper rustling]
[Sakamoto] In the end, here's what I believe.
Miracles are not real. Sorry, they're just not.
[panting]
[soft music]
[indistinct chattering]
Whenever a teacher protects their student...
[baby cooing]
[Sakamoto] ...you cannot call that a miracle.
[music continues]
- [water trickling] - [coos]
[Sakamoto] Because that is just what they do.
[crying]
[footsteps approaching]
Oh, look who's here?
It's been a while since we came to see Father together.
- Do you have any news for him? - I don't.
When Father died, he lamented the state of Edo's skies...
[spaceship engine revving]
[birds chirping]
...but whenever I look upon them now,
these same old skies look a bit different.
[soft music]
[Shinpachi] After all, there is one thing we do know,
that the people we care about, they live under these skies.
[electricity whooshing]
Sure, the skies might get cloudy at times,
but in our hearts, beneath our skies
live all the people I love so much.
[music continues]
[Shinpachi] So, Tama, even if you find yourself
beneath unfamiliar skies, please don't cry.
We will always remain in your heart with you.
And if you'll believe in that, then I'm certain,
we will come to you and wipe your tears away.
[soft music]
Let's keep going.
[siren wailing]
[Hasegawa] After that, these lovely ladies
went on to live as citizens of the modern age.
The world was entering a golden age of techno technology.
Machines, and not people,
were to be the new leaders of civilization.
And these girls, well, they were robots,
so they lived happy lives.
Turns out it was the humans who ended up unemployed.
Yeah, that's right, every last one of them.
You see, if nobody has a job,
they can't ridicule anybody else for being unemployed.
The jobless become one and everyone's happy. You dig?
[chuckles]
Every single person can be happy. [laughs]
That's Mister Hasegawa. Why is he here in the future?
[electricity crackling]
Tamako, let me tell you how
this story really ends, all right?
You see, Edo's gonna turn into a... [burps]
Um, hey Number Zero, the data I gave you
might have contained some massive errors!
What kind of massive errors?
[all] You're trying to bullshit the narration too?
[Shinpachi] What in the holy hell did you tell Tamako?
[Hasegawa] I was just saying how hard it was to find work
after I quit being the hero.
I mean, turns out that people like heroes, right? [groans]
My sincere apologies, it seems this world we perceived
has encountered a few glitches,
with the inclusion of Hasegawa's data, it has some problems.
[electricity whooshing]
[upbeat music]
The real world must be something else.
[music continues]
Hey, and good morning to you.
You look like you're half-asleep or something.
Whatever, we've got some extremely
urgent work to take care of.
We'll have to catch up with you later.
[Shinpachi] Huh? Wait, Gin!
Oh, and,
you don't need us to wipe those tears away, right?
Looks like the big guy upstairs feels better.
He stopped his crying, too.
The skies above are all clear.
Let's go.
[music continues]
[Sadaharu barks]
[Kagura] Hey, Gin, where are we going?
What--what is this work we have to do?
[Gintoki] Oh yeah. What was that?
[Shinpachi] You forgot? You said it was extremely urgent!
[Gintoki] You mean, you don't remember?
[Shinpachi] What? No!
[Gintoki] Well, hey, it doesn't matter what, right?
- [Kagura laughs] - [Gintoki] After all,
we're the Odd Jobs!
[music continues]
[upbeat music]
[Ginpachi-Sensei] Attention Class 3-Z.
[class] Teach us, Ginpachi-Sensei.
[Shinpachi] Stand, bow, take your seats.
Listen up, everyone, the manga and movie
have reached the final chapter.
So you guys, who have repeated this class,
year after year, finally get to graduate too.
Now meet transfer student, Hideaki Sorachi.
He says you can ask him
anything you want right now and he'll answer.
Question Sensei!
How are we supposed to communicate with a gorilla?
[Ginpachi-Sensei] What's he saying?
- All I hear is \"Unga-bunga.\" - Unga-bunga.
Sensei, an establishment containing multiple gorillas
would be a zoo, and not a school, may I go home now?
[Ginpachi-Sensei] Kondo, Sorachi, and Otae,
you may go home to your cages.
[groaning] Excuse me.
I can interpret the unga-bunga if you'd like, Sensei.
[Ginpachi-Sensei] You're the Sensei, Shoyo.
As someone who's been repeating all eternity,
I can understand every language.
[Ginpachi-Sensei] A guy who repeats forever is a crazy person, you know.
- This is the question Kondo has. - [ominous music]
Getting kicked off of a jump, two final chapter scams,
and series of multiple delays, why did all that happen?
[Kondo] That is a dangerous question!
He really is crazy, Sensei!
- [grunting] - Uh-huh.
Oh, I see. Is that what happened?
[Kondo] Sensei! You didn't even need an interpreter!
It's a rather delicate matter,
so we'll have to banana-coat it.
[Otae] Could you sugarcoat it instead?
- [ominous music] - [Ginpachi-Sensei] It's like this.
[Kondo] The banana peel isn't working!
The Sekiro is there for all to see!
Okay, forget the banana.
Things got crazy after Isshin
tore his way out of Genichiro's back.
[Otae] Please, stop talking about Sekiro.
It'll just cause online drama.
Anybody else got a questions?
[Kondo] I'm too scared to ask!
I have a question.
We never got any details about Gintoki Sakata's origins.
So I would like to know.
There's a fan theory that says he's half-Amanto
because of the whole silver hair thing.
Does that mean Sacchan with her purple hair
is really half-Osakan hag?
So rude! How can anyone be half an Osakan hag?
Don't worry, Sarutobi. You are not an Osakan hag.
More of a Nagoyan hag.
I'm not a hag!
Does that mean silver -haired guy is--
Half-Sugamo-old-fart-geezer?
- Ooga-booga-booga. - I hate to say it, but you're all wrong.
Keep it between us, but there's a banana-coated
reason for the silver hair.
[ominous music]
[Kondo] Too blunt! The banana-coating is failing!
Are there any other questions out there?
[Kondo] That's enough, Sensei! We'll just dig our own graves!
Okay, then I shall turn everything hollow,
with this one perfect question to end them all.
[Ginpachi-Sensei] Shoyo's other persona, Hollow-Brain's here.
He's gonna say something stupid!
Sorachi, I have a question for you. Riddle me this.
Do you count bananas as snackies?
- [Kondo] That was Shoyo! - Stay out of this, Shoyo!
What I want to ask is, do you consider bananas as royalties?
No, no, bananas count as snackies.
[Ginpachi-Sensei] Looks like both of their questions are trash.
Banana is royalties!
[Ginpachi-Sensei] Somebody stop those two morons or that one moron.
Any other questions?
Sensei! What was that ObaZ stuff all about?
[Ginpachi-Sensei] You need to drop it already.
Sensei, I have a question about
something very important to me.
Am I alive? Or am I dead?
[Kondo] It's Takasugi! He's right.
His survival was kind of left up in the air, wasn't it?
It was obviously left vague
so that the people out there could have a little hope.
Are you prepared to accept reality,
as cruel and unfortunate as it may be?
Sure
[Kondo] No! Too blunt! Banana -coat it! Banana coat-it!
Not that I really care, but we can decide
if Takasugi's alive or dead by vote.
[Kondo] Don't use a poll to decide someone's fate!
Okay, was that bare ass Takasugi's ass
or just some random person's ass?
Pick whatever you like.
[man] Sensei, why are there two votes already?
Um, Sensei, one vote for everybody died.
- [low music] - [indistinct chattering]