[TENCHI]
So you are up here!
[KINOJO]
Mr. Tenchi...
Did you come up
here for a reason?
No need to get freaked out!
Just wanted to
have a little chat!
Is it okay if I sit by you?
[TENCHI sighs]
[TENCHI]
There we go.
What a view. The stars sure do
look beautiful from up here,
don't they?
Too many to count.
You like stars, Kinojo?
Not really.
It just calms me down
to look at 'em.
What do you really want?
I wanna talk about
that thing you're searching for.
[KINOJO gasps]
I suppose those two
opened their big mouths.
I presume that it's
something pretty important.
Don't worry about it;
it's none of your business!
I was wondering
if it's connected
to this treasure everyone--
How do you know about that?!
I'm just here to talk!
Can you put that down, please?
It doesn't encourage
conversation!
[KINOJO] Come to think of it,
I've got something I wanna
ask you, too.
[TENCHI]
Huh?
How 'bout telling me
exactly who you are,
Mr. Tenchi?
I'm just a regular
old student teacher!
Don't lie to me!
Don't forget, I was there!
I saw how you brought
down that big robot!
[TENCHI]
That was just instinct!
The adrenaline
brought that out in me!
[KINOJO]
Do you think I'm stupid?
If you don't wanna tell the
truth, we can play this
--a different way.
--What do you have in mind?
I'll question you, with my club!
I'm not really a
big fan of that plan!
I have no clear memories
of my distant past!
I don't even know
exactly who I am!
But...
There's one thing
I know for sure!
I don't belong here!
I don't fit in, and I'm
not a normal person!
[TENCHI]
What's not normal about you?
[KINOJO] Show me a
normal high-school girl
who can handle a chunk
of metal like this!
Point taken.
[KINOJO] With this power, I
could accidentally hurt someone.
It's all I can think
about anymore.
Since I'm not like anyone else,
It's dangerous for me
to be around people.
[TENCHI] Have you thought about
just putting down the club?
[KINOJO] I thought I was
doomed to total isolation,
but then I found you and
realized I wasn't alone.
I'm right here!
[KINOJO]
Since you won't talk,
I've decided to beat
the truth out of you.
You'd better fight back,
Mr. Tenchi,
or you and this roof
will be smashed
into a million pieces!
[TENCHI]
Do I have a vote in all this?
[KINOJO] You can reveal
yourself or you can bleed.
It's up to you!
What is all the
commotion up here?
What in the--?
[TENCHI]
Look out, Kawanagare!
[MOMO yells]
[coughing]
What happened up there?
You're both okay, right?
[MOMO]
Are we still alive?!
[KINOJO coughs]
Why do you have
your arm around me?!
I'm sorry!
I was just trying to help you.
[KURIHARA]
Well, well.
Here you are in the courtyard,
and with two partners, no less!
I thought I'd made myself clear.
I told you to stop
being so touchy-feely
with the students!
You've got this wrong!
[KURIHARA]
Since you don't seem to listen,
I'll have to use
a more forceful lesson!
[TENCHI]
Somebody help me!
[MOMO]
Beni, your fingers are hurt!
[KINOJO gasps]
[BABY MOMO cooing]
Huh?
Keep your distance!