Space Pirate Ryoko,
surrender or be destroyed!
Your reign of terror
ends right now!
Ha! Big talk!
Go ahead, try to get me!
[MIHOSHI]
You missed!
[YOUNG MOMO gasps]
We've gotta move! Let's beat it!
[RYOKO grunting]
[MIHOSHI yelling]
[RYOKO laughing]
[MIHOSHI] Give up!
You don't stand a chance!
Ha! We'll just see about that!
There's a little girl here!
Don't fire your blasters
over this area!
[MIHOSHI]
Oh, my goodness!
I didn't know anyone was there!
I'm very sorry about that!
Right! I'll show you what real
sorry is for attacking me!
[MIHOSHI yells]
Hold on tight. We're outta here!
[MIHOSHI yelling]
Here's the big finish!
[MIHOSHI yells]
That's for giving me
a hard time.
Huh? What's going on?
[MIHOSHI, RYOKO yelling]
[TENCHI gasps]
They just totally disappeared!
[YOUNG MOMO] I want to thank
you all for trusting us.
We should thank you for
keeping that Space Pirate
from causing us harm.
We're very grateful
for what you did.
It seems strange to be
saved by a little girl.
You're all fine.
And that's really
what matters the most.
Right. I have to agree.
We still don't know anything
about the two of you.
Where you came from,
how you got here.
We have a mountain of questions
and an anthill of answers.
We know one thing.
You came here because
you're looking for someone.
We'd like to help you find
whoever you're looking for
as a way of saying thanks.
You'd really do that?
That's great. Means a lot to us.
It's kind of
difficult to explain.
Momo got stranded here and
we're trying to find her friend,
who was supposed to be
coming along after her.
He's walking this trail
like he has a guide beside him.
Like someone's giving him
directions on where to search.
That thing in his hand
must have something
to do with it.
What's in the little box?
Some kind of divining rod?
No, but it sort of
works that way.
[YOUNG MOMO] Tenchi, if there's
a signal coming from the ship,
I should be able to pick
it up on this thing.
I keep trying,
but it's just not working.
Something burned the trees.
[SARYU]
From the top.
Whatever it was
gave off extreme heat
as it passed through.
--[YOUNG MOMO] This way!
--[TENCHI] Hey!
Where's my ship?
--[YOUNG MOMO yells]
--[TENCHI] Careful!
Something blew up.
It's the only way this hole
could've been created.
[beeping noise]