[GP CHIEF] Honored directors
of the Scientific Academy,
thanks for your patience.
[DIRECTOR A] We did not
come here to wait for you.
This is unacceptable!
I'm terribly sorry for that.
But unfortunately,
it could not be helped.
[DIRECTOR B] We all have other
things that need attending to.
Please get to your report.
[GP CHIEF] I have some
good news and some bad news.
Which one would you
like me to start with?
[DIRECTOR A]
We don't care. Just begin.
Then I'll start off
with the positive.
We've received some solid
intel about who's behind
the space-time warp.
[DIRECTOR A]
Well. That is good news.
[DIRECTOR B]
Great. Who is this criminal?
I'm afraid this is where
the bad news begins.
[DIRECTOR A]
Go on.
The person behind
the space-time warp is...
...Washu. It's Washu Hakubi.
Therefore, I request your
permission to arrest her
and bring her in immediately.
Do you read?
It's the Chief here.
I'm about to dispatch
the special forces team
for this mission.
It's extreme, but I'm
afraid you'll need them.
Listen up!
You have to assume the
worst and act accordingly.
Move out!
[FUEYAMA]
That's good. Very sexy.
All right, now look this way.
That's right, good good.
What in the world
are you two doing here?
What's it look like?
Isn't it obvious?
[SARYU] I wouldn't be
asking if it were obvious!
[MOMO yells]
You're supposed to be
creating campaign material!
I've never seen a campaign
use sexy-time photos
like the ones you're taking.
I mean, seriously?
Hachiko, are you paying
attention to this nonsense?
Listen up!
We only have three days
until the election, people,
and we have competition!
Yuki Fuka is a tough candidate!
Well, based on the
current student polls,
Momo is beating Fuka
by a landslide.
It's hard to believe
she could lose.
Maybe in a normal election.
Unfortunately,
this is the Science Club
we're talking about.
We can't assume that they will
act like honorable people.
Those guys--
They're tougher to get
rid of than a bad case
of food poisoning!
Ugh! We've got to do this right!
[FUKA sneezes]
[AOI]
Oh! Are you all right?
Yep. Check this out!
What is this?
It's the new campaign
poster, of course.
What? Huh?
[SARYU]
Now that looks great!
Don't you think
it's a little stiff?
We should have used
this picture, it's--
Ugh!
[MOMO] I really like this
poster just the way it is.
I mean, everybody helped
with the design of it,
after all.
[FUKA]
Now that is one crappy poster.
[GROUP]
Huh?
There's no need
to be so uptight.
We're just here to hang up
a few posters ourselves.
Let's go, Rui!
Um, 'kay.
[FUKA]
Awesome, huh?
[clears throat]
Mm-hmm!
Hm?
Stop it!
What are you all implying?
Seriously? Well...
You've increased
your boobs 250%.
Cheating the size
of your assets!
[FUKA] This isn't cheating!
It's just politics.
Everyone enhances their photos!
It won't make a difference.
Momo's going to win the race
and continue as
Student Council President.
That's cute. Keep that
thought as long as you can.
Let's go, Rui.
Right.
They have some scheme
up their sleeve,
I just know it.
Girls. We need to get serious!