[SARYU] It's finally time
for the big debate.
[FUEYAMA] Fuka's closed the gap
in the polls with her cheating.
It's now dead even.
[HACHIKO]
We have to stay focused.
[MOMO]
Mm-hmm!
[gasps] Mr. Tenchi!
I think it's about time
to go to our seats, girls.
Momo, you'll be wonderful.
Thanks!
[TENCHI] I can't really
take sides for this,
but, well, you know.
Thank you, Mr. Tenchi.
It means a lot to me
that you feel that way.
I appreciate your support.
Mr. Tenchi.
I have the weirdest feeling.
Like I've known you before.
Like these hands have
been protecting me.
Not just now,
but for a long time.
Now! Time to win a debate!
[TENCHI]
Mmm!
[STUDENT A] The final debate for
the Student Council election
is about to begin!
[STUDENTS cheering, clapping]
When I'm elected as your
Student Council President,
I promise you this. First:
Free school lunches,
and I'll double the budgets
on all student activities!
You're gonna be rolling
in so much money,
you're not gonna believe it!
What?!
Of course, there's no way
to deliver on either
of those promises.
What a lot of hot air!
Well. More politics
as usual, I see.
What? Fuka's poll numbers
are climbing like crazy!
And that's not all, people.
To protect the dignity
of this school,
I promise to stamp out this
kind of scandalous behavior!
It certainly appears that
the student in this photo
is Ms. Momo Kawanagare!
That's correct.
The student who appears
in that photograph is me!
[STUDENTS chattering]
Are you aware of what
you just said to everyone?
The person you're hugging
in that picture is a teacher.
He's a student teacher,
but a teacher nonetheless.
--I'm well aware.
--You are?
There's something I don't
understand about all this.
Ms. Fuka here seems
to be suggesting
that this kind of behavior
should not be allowed.
For what possible reason
should that be prohibited?
It's so obvious!
One of the two is in
a position of authority!
Regardless, it's just
between two people.
Everybody knows that.
It's natural that two people
can develop feelings
for each other;
it's common sense!
Feelings of respect or trust,
friendship, distrust, hatred.
Or even... love!
[STUDENTS chattering]
I just cannot believe that
you would find it wrong
for someone to feel love
for someone else!
Cut the sappy nonsense!
Some relationships are just
completely unacceptable!
Maybe.
But people are
certainly responsible
for the things they say
and do in the name of love.
And yes, they can make
mistakes because of love.
But that's forgivable.
Love is the one true thing
that binds people together!
Love forms societies.
Love forms families.
It nurtures life.
Love is the root of everything!
So I'm not ashamed!
And no one can
make me feel ashamed
for embracing the power of love!
The truth of the matter is,
I do have special feelings
for another person.
And I'm proud of that!
[STUDENTS clapping]
[FUKA]
Huh?!
[clapping continues]
[MOMO gasps]
[TENCHI gasps]
They've arrived.