How pretty!
[TENCHI]
So, uhh, Washu...
Why in the world am I here
strapped to this chair?
Well, Master Tenchi,
it's a long story,
but there's someone
who's in desperate
need of your help.
Someone I've met?
No, I don't believe so.
You see, there was
a bit of an incident
during my recent research.
It seems that
one or two people
accidentally got caught up
in a dimensional warp
that was created during
one of my experiments.
And you have no way
to retrieve them?
[WASHU]
I'm glad you asked!
That's where you come in.
I need you to rescue those
poor castaways for me.
[TENCHI] Why can't you
just go pick them up?
I would, but there
would be complications,
if you know what I'm saying.
The problem is,
I'm such a genius,
and so famous.
My mere presence would
be extremely disrupting.
[TENCHI] So you don't want
to be found out, right?
You're so perceptive!
It's important that this job
be carried out
quickly and quietly.
How do I get back?
[TENCHI yelling]
[WASHU] When you find the two
people you're looking for,
open up the Recovery app,
and leave the rest to me.
[TENCHI]
Got it.
Well, I made it.
But where am I?
And what's with
this weird outfit?
--[YOUNG MOMO screaming]
--[TENCHI] Say what?
[YOUNG MOMO screaming]
[TENCHI yells]
Owwee.
Oh! It's a person!
[TENCHI grunts]
Huh?
Hi.
[TENCHI]
Oh, hello.
I was looking for someone.
Can you help me?
I climbed a tree to see if
she was somewhere nearby,
but I couldn't find anybody.
Have you seen her?
[TENCHI]
Uh, I don't know.
What does she look like?
[YOUNG MOMO] Well, she's
got these really pointy,
kinda grumpy-looking eyes,
and when she stares at you--
You're scaring me
just talking about her!
[YOUNG MOMO gasps]
First things first.
Who are you?
[crying]
What?
Okay, calm down! I'm sorry!
[TENCHI]
Could she be...?
S'cuse me. I have a question.
[YOUNG MOMO]
Huh?
I believe you said
you've been out here
searching for someone?
Yes.
And I have to
find her real soon!
[TENCHI]
What a break.
I'll bet anything this little
girl and her lost friend
are the exact two people
Washu sent me out here to find.
Don't you worry!
[YOUNG MOMO]
Huh?
How about if I help you
search for your friend?
[YOUNG MOMO]
Really?
Sure. I'm happy to help.
Thanks so much!
What do you think?
How 'bout we take
a look in that place?
Oh. Now that I think of it...
[YOUNG MOMO]
What?
I never asked
what your name was.
I'm Tenchi. Tenchi Masaki.
That seems like a nice name.
[TENCHI]
How 'bout you?
What's your name?
They call me Momo.
You know what?
I have a feeling you and I
are going to be best friends!