[TENCHI]
This must be the girls' dorm
'cause it's plastered with
signs warning guys
not to go in.
Lucky me, Mr. new dorm monitor.
Welcome to our dorm!
Mr. Tenchi!
[TENCHI]
Reporting for duty!
[MOMO] Okay, come with me and
I'll show you around the dorm.
Hurry up! This way!
Like a spider leading
him into her web.
Spider?! Don't let it near me!
I was merely using
a figure of speech.
I'm gonna make
a web of my own,
and lure him away from her,
so our Science Club
has that teacher in our pocket,
which will end up
getting us perks!
[MOMO]
This is our cafeteria.
And this is our bathing room.
Most of the dorm
bedrooms are on this floor.
[SARYU]
Thought I heard voices.
Oh, nice to see you, Mr. Tenchi.
Why are you greeting me
in your underwear?
You'll have to get used to it.
This is what I wear
around the dorm.
--Please cover up!
--Black underwear?
I've never seen you
wearing that before!
Look, the color's
not really the problem.
The lack of clothes is
certainly the biggest issue
facing us at the moment!
Looks to me like your
mind is somewhere else,
which is why you're
getting so upset.
[MOMO] If you're saying
Mr. Tenchi's mind
is in the gutter, you're wrong.
He's very proper!
All guys are natural wanderers,
and before you know it,
their hands are
wandering all over you!
Could we change the subject?
This is getting weird!
[SARYU] Afraid to admit
that the way I look
in my underwear
is exciting to you?
Hey! I'm an excitable guy!
Just leave me alone while
I'm in the dorm so I--
You're gonna have
a problem here.
Absolutely not!
Wait up, Kinojo!
Mr. Tenchi. I heard you
were the new monitor.
I'm sure you'll
see plenty of us.
I already have!
Could you put on some clothes?
Well, that would
be kind of silly.
I'm about to step
into the shower.
Could you do it anyway?
Mr. Tenchi's just
trying to do his job,
and he can't if he's
all turned on by you!
--Oh, yeah?
--I never really said that!
[MOMO]
Please, Beni!
There's no dress code here.
You can't tell me what to wear!
[SARYU]
She's right.
What?
Where'd he run off to?
[FUKA] Find the spot.
Oh, that's good!
[TENCHI]
I can't hold it forever!
[AOI] Please, Mr. Tenchi,
don't move like that!
I'm almost there!
Just hold it very still!
Don't panic!
We won't let you fall!
[AOI]
O-Okay.
Thanks for the help.
Sorry to have to
bother you with this
when you're busy just
getting started here.
No bother, although
it might be better if I got up
on the ladder;
we don't want Rui to get hurt.
She loves changing bulbs.
She's extremely
passionate about it.
--How odd.
--Yeah!
She's full of surprises.
[TENCHI]
Huh?
[farts]
[TENCHI gasps]
[AOI whimpering]
Basic rule to know when flirting
with the opposite sex.
It is really not sexy to fart
in the face of a guy
when you're flashing
your panties.
Okay, but I always
fart when I'm nervous.
If it happens,
don't do it twice.
Just stick with the plan
to fall into his arms!
[AOI]
I've gotta hold it in!
You seem a little shaky, Rui.
No, I'm fine!
You look like you could fall!
This ladder's starting
to wobble!
[AOI yells]
[TENCHI yells]
I gotcha.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Yes!
I feel something.
It's small.
[AOI gasps]
It's a spider!
[TENCHI]
Please let go of my head!
--[AOI screaming]
--[TENCHI] Can't... breathe!
You're squashing Mr. Tenchi!
Is the spider gone?
I'm afraid to look!
[TENCHI]
Call 911!
I can't feel anything
below my ears!