--[GIRL A screams]
--[thunder crashes]
--[GIRL B screams]
[TENCHI]
Is someone else in here?
I thought I heard a scream.
Huh! Some fools
must have slipped in.
Now they're probably lost.
Really? Is that possible?
It wouldn't actually
surprise me.
This warehouse is huge.
Equipment from every
Culture and Sports festival
in the school's history
is stored here.
The place is filled with
booby traps, locked doors,
and dead-ends.
You can't get through it without
this Student Council guide book.
Any mis-step you make
in here is guaranteed
to become a one-way
ticket to the afterlife.
[HACHIKO]
Hurry!
[TENCHI yelling]
Are we gonna turn into
blue-haired old ladies,
stuck in this crazy
warehouse forever?
Speak for yourself. My Navigator
App will show us the way
when my phone is charged.
Feel free to help me
do that, by the way!
[KINOJO] Electrical work
isn't really my cup of tea.
What are you reading, Kinojo?
[KINOJO]
This.
Where did you find such a thing?
That manga is older than we are!
[HACHIKO]
We're here.
From sleep eternal,
rouse thyself.
The hour of festival
has arrived.
Unseal the lock of
ancient wisdom's wealth.
O Guardian, open thy eyes!
[TENCHI] Did you need that
incantation just to show me
the key?
It makes the whole experience
a little more mystical,
you know?
It was Mistress Momo's idea.
[TENCHI]
Why doesn't that surprise me...
[AOI grunting]
How bad do you need
Book 9, 'cause it's stuck!
[screams]
A spider!
Now that it's quiet again,
I can keep reading.
I thought it was
gonna eat me alive!
I hope that one missing
book doesn't mess us up.
[KINOJO] I just wish we
knew exactly what it is
we're looking for.
[crash]
[KINOJO, FUKA, AOI]
Huh?
[FUKA, AOI screaming]
Quick, run!
[KINOJO grunts]
[KINOJO yells]
That stuff's very important.
Don't drop it.
Got it.
[FUKA, AOI screaming]
--[TENCHI] Huh?
--[HACHIKO] Hm?
Mr. Masaki!
Run for it!
Ya see what happens
without a guide book?
Hey, Hachiko!
We've got a big problem!
No kidding.
[TENCHI]
Come on!
Why is this thing even in here?!
It's an iron ball that used
to be part of Sports Day!
[TENCHI]
Really? For what event?
Never mind, it's not important!
[HACHIKO]
Oh...!
Hey! What are you--?
[TENCHI]
Ow, ow, ow!
Are you hurt?
[HACHIKO]
No. I'm all right.
[KINOJO grunting]
[TENCHI]
Kinojo!
[HACHIKO gasps]
[KINOJO grunts]
I think she'll be okay.
Damn it!
What?
When we ran, I dropped
the guide book!
[TENCHI]
No!