[GIRLS chattering]
Come on, Mr. Tenchi!
Everything's almost ready!
Thanks a lot, Momo!
I'll be down as soon as
I get this hole patched!
So what's the deal?
Is this ready yet?
Go away!
Go set the table.
Make yourself useful!
I'm not leaving!
I'm keeping an eye on
you girls and these grills!
Stand there as long as you want!
This meal's in honor
of Master Tenchi,
and we're not eating
until he finishes his work!
Hey, thanks for inviting us.
We owe him a lot for
saving our friend here.
You're welcome.
We should thank you.
We couldn't have
done this if you hadn't
gotten permission
to use the courtyard.
[FUEYAMA] Who are these
friends of Mr. Tenchi's?
Normally, only dorm
students and proctors
are allowed in here.
[SASAMI laughing]
[MOMO] Since you were
going to all this trouble
for Mr. Tenchi's sake,
how could we not let
you use the facilities?
Well, that, plus the
delicious barbecue
you brought in!
[stomach growling]
A-ha! Apparently,
we have an eager stomach!
[FUEYAMA] This data confirms
that smiling over your shoulder
has 80 times the seductive force
of smiling straight ahead!
[FUKA yawns]
I'm bored, guys.
Why is the courtyard so busy?
[GROUP gasps]
Why are you here?
We live here.
[AYEKA. SASAMI]
Hm?
[RYOKO]
Huh?
You again!
[FUKA sighs]
We're not here to pick a fight.
Sorry for intruding.
--Come on, ladies.
--[MOMO] Wait!
What's the problem?
I said we were leaving.
Isn't that good enough?
That's not what I meant!
Why don't you stay
and have some food?
I think for these
kind of events,
the more the merrier,
don't you agree?
Sasami, can we handle it?
Sure!
We've got plenty of food.
Why not spread it around?
This is ridiculous! What makes
you think we'd be willing
to take handouts from our--
[stomach growls]
Sure about that?
Good! That settles it!
Let's have a nice,
friendly party together,
what do you say?
[TENCHI sighs]
It's not perfect, but at least
it'll keep out the rain!
[FUEYAMA]
Heat penetration, 74 degrees.
A perfect medium-rare.
[SASAMI laughs]
All right, my
super-secret meat sauce
is ready to go!
[BOTH arguing]
Wow, what service!
[BOTH gasp]
Want me to flip
you some veggies?
No, thanks!
Somebody threw the
party switch around here!
You're finally
down off the roof!
We waited as
long as we could!
Thank you.
[GIRLS chattering]
Everyone's getting along.
I wish it was always like this.
[TENCHI]
Huh?
It's no fun feeling
like you're all alone
in the world.
Yeah.
[MOMO] I know, because
I was alone for so long.
--I never realized.
--Oh!
But now I'm a lot better!
I have all these great
friends around me!
And you know what?
It feels fantastic!
C'mon, guys!
If you don't move your feet,
you're gonna lose your meat!
She's right!
We'd better go join the party!
The guest of honor is here!
Save him some food!