[WASHU]
Come, on you guys!
When are you gonna
find the treasure already?
Sorry, we're doing
the best we can.
But we don't have
enough money or workers
to do it very quickly.
[FUKA]
Even the students who joined
thinking it sounded
interesting got bored
and quit really quickly.
[AOI]
We didn't have any money,
and they didn't like
getting paid in snacks.
[MIHOSHI]
Here, treasure treasure!
Where could you be hiding?
[WASHU]
That's not good enough!
I expect better from you!
[GROUP gasps]
[WASHU] I even gave you
a top-of-the-line robot
to help you with this project.
It's like giving
chopsticks to a pig!
If you don't get results soon,
I'm gonna have
him self-destruct!
Don't say that!
Goriki's our friend!
That's mean, even for you!
Oh, don't worry, Goriki,
we won't let anything
happen to you, I promise!
[WASHU] Then you'd better
find me what I need, and fast!
We're running out of time!
--[AOI] All right.
--[FUKA] Yes, ma'am.
She's right, we're outta time.
So why do you have
to keep on working
when you get home, Tenchi?
I have to complete this job,
and there's no other
time to get it done.
Can't you finish it
when you get back
to the school?
I wish I could.
Is everything all right?
All good, thank you.
[KURIHARA] If there's
anything you don't understand,
I can teach you
one on one, privately.
I won't leave anything out,
even if it takes all night.
[TENCHI]
Thanks, if I need your help,
I'll certainly let you know.
[KURIHARA chuckles]
[laughs] Look, that's funny,
you're misspelling everything.
[TENCHI]
Huh?!
There's one here and here,
and a couple more here.
If you turn it in
looking like this,
you're gonna be in big trouble.
[TENCHI groans]
[SASAMI]
Aww.
[pounding on door]
[TENCHI]
Kinojo?
We need your help
searching for the treasure.
[SASAMI]
Here you go.
Give me one good
reason why Tenchi
should drop everything
to help you out
with your little treasure hunt.
Yeah, Ryoko's right.
Your shenanigans always
end up being trouble,
and a lot of unnecessary
work for Tenchi.
I know that Mr. Tenchi
and the rest of you
are more than
just ordinary people.
We need your special
powers to help us.
[GROUP]
Uh... huh?
I'm begging you.
[door opens, closes]
I'm coming, Mr. Tenchi!
Huh? What're you here for?
The same thing as you.
[KURIHARA growls]
Be quiet, you brats!
Mr. Masaki's in the field
with the Science Club today.
What?!
For what purpose?
I don't know!
He took off with
those little bitches
when today was the day I was
gonna start training him!
[SASAMI]
Wow!
[RYOKO]
Would you look at this place?
[AYEKA] It's way bigger
than I expected.
[MIHOSHI grunts]
Ask her if you want
some more details.
She's knows a lot more
about it than I do.
[MIHOSHI grunting]
Uh, excuse me?
[MIHOSHI]
Yes? [chuckles]
[GROUP]
Huh?
[AYEKA]
Mihoshi?
[RYOKO] The Galaxy Police
sent her to this planet?
Well, hello, everybody!
What a nice surprise!
What brings all of you here?
[laughs]