No matter how much chaos
goes on around here
during the day, everyone
pretty much goes to sleep
on time.
Huh?
What are you doing up?
It's after eleven! Huh?
[FUKA] You discovered
our secret, did you?
[TENCHI gasps]
[FUKA]
You're eating already?
It hasn't even been
three minutes yet!
Sorry, I was so hungry,
I just couldn't wait!
Why did you bother
cooking it at all?
Mr. Masaki.
Since you accepted our
bribe of a bowl of ramen,
you'll keep quiet
about this, right?
The rules say we're not
supposed to be cooking
anything after 10 pm!
[TENCHI]
You two are impossible.
But I guess making
a bowl of ramen
doesn't really
qualify as cooking.
It falls more into
the snack category.
--[robot ringing]
--[TENCHI] Huh? [gasps]
[FUKA] Mm-hmm.
That's the three-minute bell.
Voilà! Time to dig in!
That's a pretty handy
robot you created there.
Tell me something.
What kind of power
source does it use?
Don't know.
Seriously?
[FUKA]
I drafted the basic plans,
but to tell you the truth,
I'm not too clear
on what makes it go.
[TENCHI] You just assembled it,
pushed a button,
and it started moving?
[FUKA]
Pretty much, yeah.
[TENCHI] That's actually
a little alarming.
But you could do so
much with those skills.
Just think, you could use
your talents to help people
instead of causing
chaos and trouble
everywhere you go.
Don't sit there and
accuse us like that!
Our work does help people,
Mr. Know-It-All!
We're in the midst
of reforming society!
I beg your pardon?
That's right! We're about to--
You're spitting food
all over yourself!
[AOI]
Hm? Sorry about that!
[chewing]
It's kind of a crusade,
but we're really
committed to it.
First, we're going to end
the Student Council's tyranny!
[TENCHI]
Tyranny?
[FUKA] They think they
can do whatever they want
because they control the
budgets for all the clubs!
[AOI] But that doesn't
give them the power
to control people's behavior.
Take Kinojo, for instance.
What's so different
about Kinojo?
Aren't you all members
of the Science Club?
You're mistaken, Mr. Tenchi.
Kinojo doesn't belong
to any club.
What? Are you serious?
To tell you the honest truth,
we have no idea what
that girl's even up to
most of the time.
She showed up here one day,
but she doesn't know
much about herself, either.
[TENCHI]
Well, that's very unusual.
I don't get it. How can that be?
[AOI]
She has no memories of her past.
[FUKA] It's not even clear
if Kinojo's her real name.
We give her some time alone,
hoping that she'll
have a breakthrough.
When everyone's in bed,
she's usually up on the roof,
thinking.
So, I'm confused.
Why is it you three
hang out together?
It's not like we're besties
or anything like that.
We've been helping
her search for something.
I wonder what it could
be she's looking for.
Is it possible...?
--[robot beeping]
--[GROUP] Huh?
--Is it...?
--It's close!
Close? What's close?
Don't make a sound!
Where is it?
Where is it? Underneath?
Rui, get ready!
What are we looki--?
[FUKA]
You help, too, Mr. Tenchi!
[TENCHI]
Wha--?
[FUKA]
This is so weird!
There's just nothing here!
Did Goriki get it wrong?
[FUKA]
Ugh!
There's nothing more
we can do tonight.
We'll run some tests
tomorrow to make sure
he's operating properly.
S'cuse me?
See you tomorrow, Mr. Tenchi.
Right.
This is a very
troublesome event.
As far as I know,
Goriki's treasure sensor
has never gone off
in the dorm before.
[FUKA]
Mm-hmm.
Huh... It stopped working.
[TENCHI] What in the world
was that all about, I wonder?