[TENCHI sighs]
Weeding, repairing the roof, now
scrubbing the bathing room.
What a day! I feel like
an overused plow horse!
Huh?
Close to bathing time.
Better finish before
the girls show up!
Huh? A time change note?
The bath is open?!
Nobody's here! Yay!
Hey, Momo, don't forget
to wash up first!
That's right.
Bathers are required to cleanse
before entering the water.
The sole purpose
of soaking in the bath
is to purify you.
[MOMO]
Oh please, I know all that!
[MOMO humming]
[SARYU humming]
[TENCHI] I'm trapped, and
the whole Student Council's
naked in front of me!
Not good!
Oh! I think they got
bigger again, didn't they?
That's right, but it takes
a lot of extra effort
to stand up straight.
Well, that doesn't seem
like a bad trade-off to me.
[MOMO gasps]
Wanna have beauties like mine?
I'll show you my technique.
How's it work?
[SARYU]
You massage them like this,
but you have to hold still
while I demonstrate.
There's no scientific
data proving that massage
will stimulate breast growth.
[SARYU] If you don't have
any facts to say it doesn't,
why not try?
[TENCHI]
More fun than pulling weeds!
How can I get that assignment?
That should be enough for now
'cause you're still growing.
Don't want to stretch
'em too much.
Now get some warm water on you
so you don't catch a cold.
[MOMO laughs]
[MOMO yells]
Huh?
--Why are you in our tub?
--Shh!
I was cleaning and I couldn't
escape before you all came in.
You're in hot water.
And it's gonna get a lot
hotter when I report this!
According to my data,
you already have
a bad reputation.
You're gonna feel the
consequences of ogling us
in our birthday suits, buddy!
[TENCHI] This is bad!
How can I hide?
They won't see you.
I've got you covered!
[SARYU]
Now, we need to talk business.
The Science Club is
getting more and more
out of hand.
We need to keep
a close eye on them.
Just in the last few months,
they've committed more
than fifty infractions.
That includes embezzlement and
Illicit occupation of buildings
on the school grounds.
[SARYU] We're gonna have
to take some kind of action.
Let's not waste our time
thinking about it.
This requires brute force!
No mercy, no listening
to their stupid excuses.
Give 'em a thorough beatdown!
[MOMO] No, using physical
force is not the way
the Student Council
should behave!
[SARYU]
Huh?
Do you have indigestion?
[MOMO]
No, it was just a little burp!
Anyway, let's try to find
a solution that makes
everybody happy!
Are you serious?
What universe are you living in?
[FUEYAMA]
According to the simulations,
the probability of an agreeable
solution is almost zero!
Why should we work
things out with them?
They'll just take
advantage of any kindness.
And right now,
Rui has proof they've been
running around behind our backs
and getting away
with embezzlement!
Worse than that,
I'll bet at this very moment,
they're plotting
to snatch the treasure
before we can even get near it!
[TENCHI]
You know about the treasure?
You've gotta be quiet!
They'll discover you!
Get down!
[TENCHI grunts]
[TENCHI] Momo, let go!
Can't breathe...!
[TENCHI gasps]
[TENCHI]
What should I do?
Momo and the others don't know
what they're getting into.
This is bad.