[TENCHI]
I'm home.
[SASAMI] There you are,
big bro Tenchi!
Welcome back to...
What happened
to you out there?
You're a mess!
[TENCHI chuckling]
[sighs]
Thought I was gonna die!
From teaching a class?
There was some
weird stuff after class.
[SASAMI] Sounds like being
a student teacher is dangerous.
[TENCHI] You have no idea,
but it's just two more weeks.
I'll be here to cheer you on!
[AYEKA] Sasami, Master
Tenchi just got in
and he's probably tired, so
don't bug him with a lot of--
Oh, my goodness!
Did someone steal your pants?!
[AYEKA]
Are you sure you're all right?
Ask me tomorrow.
Apart from that, I'm sorry
I had to leave you two
with all the unpacking.
But you both did a great job.
--[AYEKA] Thanks.
--[SASAMI] Yeah!
We're here to support you.
We wanna help you
accomplish your mission
in any way that we can.
[TENCHI] I hope today was
the exception, not the rule.
[SASAMI] Tenchi, if they're
gonna attack you every time
show up at school, maybe we
should be there to help.
[TENCHI] I appreciate
the offer, I really do.
But I don't think they
allow student teachers
to bring in their
own bodyguards.
[AYEKA]
If you're that determined,
I guess all we can do
is keep offering support
from the sidelines.
Is she right?
Things have to get better.
I mean, after today, I can't
imagine them getting any worse.
I almost forgot to tell you,
a package arrived
today from Washu!
Her note said it's stuff you'll
need for your student teaching!
So what did she send?
Let's see!
[ALL]
Huh?
[TENCHI]
A helmet?
Why would a student teacher
need a helmet?
Huh...
Body armor? She must think
I'm teaching delinquents!
[chuckles]
[SASAMI]
Look at this, Tenchi!
[TENCHI]
A shield?
There's no way I'll need that--
she must have thrown
it in by mistake!
[AYEKA]
Look at these charms!
[TENCHI] Does she think
I'm in the middle of a war?
A student teacher has
no need for all this stuff!
I think she's lost it!
Her school must
have been really tough!
[TENCHI]
"Here lies Tenchi Masaki."
Somebody jumped the gun
on your obituary!
Maybe a hot bath will
bring you back to life!
That sounds pretty good to me!
At least I'll be a clean corpse!
[TENCHI] This situation
may be more complicated
than I thought.
No, no, no,
I can't think that way!
It must be nerves because the
first day was such a disaster.
A bath should perk me back up.
I had no idea this job
was going to be such
a challenge to pull off.
Now where's that shower head?
[RYOKO]
Here.
[TENCHI]
Oh, thanks.
--[TENCHI] Huh?
--[RYOKO chuckles]
What are you doing
in here, Ryoko?!
[RYOKO]
Don't be so shy.
I was lonely while
you were gone today.
Let me do something nice.
I'll wash your back for you!
Forget it!
[RYOKO]
Quit playing coy!
Wait a minute,
you're all beat up!
Who did this to you?
No way am I gonna
let this slide!
Someone's gonna pay for
those cuts and scratches!
If you get mixed up in this
on top of everything else,
it'll just get worse!
And don't you come
snooping around the school!
Aww! You're no fun!
[AYEKA] Master Tenchi,
what's all the commo--[gasps]
I should've known!
Get out, Ryoko!
Oh, shut it, you fussbudget!
It's not a big deal!
Not true! As a matter
of fact, it's a very big deal!
What is happening?
Ryoko, were you hiding
in here, spying on Tenchi?
I think someone's
really jealous.
I see you haven't
changed a bit!
Now please, ladies,
let's be nice.
[overlapping chatter]
[TENCHI]
Get out of here, everybody!
Give me some peace and quiet!