[TENCHI]
Sorry about this, Kawanagare.
I hate to have you use
your precious break time
showing me around the school.
No big deal.
Don't worry about it.
It's all in a day's work for
the Student Council President.
I do appreciate it.
And, uh...
...the rest of you
are okay with this?
Oh, absolutely!
Supporting the President
is one of the jobs
of the Vice-President.
[SARYU] Unless, of course,
you and the President
would rather have this
time all to yourselves.
That's not what I was saying!
[FUEYAMA]
Entering data.
Tenchi Masaki
wants solitary time
with the Council President.
Why are you putting
that in your records?
Gathering data around the campus
is one of my most important
duties as Treasurer.
--I see, but there's been a mi--
--[HACHIKO] You pervert!
Why are you trying to get
Mistress Momo alone?
I won't let you lay
a single finger on her!
That's my duty as auditor!
You're sure this is all
coming from your position
as auditor?
Of course it is! What are you
implying by that remark?
[MOMO laughs]
Hold on.
Could she be the one who lan--?
Goodness, what seems
to have caught your eye?
You've got me all wrong!
[HACHIKO]
Back off, you filthy animal!
Entering data in log:
Tenchi Masaki peeked up
Momo Kawanagare's skirt
on his very first day of work.
[TENCHI] Hey, that's not
what happened at all!
That's right!
Stop implying things!
I'm sure he's a helpless
victim of his own temptation!
Oh, Momo, you're so
kind and understanding.
Wait a minute!
I object to that explanation!
[TENCHI]
Huh?
Is something the matter?
Just a feeling.
I can't quite put
my finger on it.
[MOMO] This is the Student
Council Headquarters.
Don't be shy.
Please, go on in.
[TENCHI]
Uh...
[yelling]
Huh?
[SARYU]
Hachiko.
Ah! What are you doing?!
What is everybody up to?
Just hang on, you'll see.
Tori?
We're going to give you a test.
Why didn't anyone tell me?
A test about what?
About whether or not
this cretin intends
to do harm to you.
[MOMO]
What?
Why would Mr. Tenchi want
to do something like that?
The fact of the matter is,
the school database
has almost no information
on Mr. Tenchi.
We don't even know
where he came from.
So what would be the best way
to get more information?
Hm, I guess ask
Mr. Tenchi directly.
You're right!
What a great idea!
[MOMO laughs]
And in this case,
we'll be asking his body
those questions.
How will his body
be able to answer you?
It depends how
we ask the question.
No matter how much they resist,
their body always
answers honestly.
Hey, Mr. Tenchi,
what's your favorite food?
Hey. It doesn't
seem to be answering.
You're getting a little
bit ahead of yourself.
There's a trick to the
technique, you see.
[FUEYAMA]
Don't worry, Mistress Momo.
The data shows that in
the hands of Hana Saryu,
even the most hardened
spy is going to crack
in an average of 7.2 seconds.
[SARYU chuckles]
This won't take very long.
Before you know it,
it'll all be over.
Will you quit squirming
around! Hachiko!
[TENCHI grunts]
Well, look who's
finally calmed down.
Everybody ready?
Let's continue.
[MOMO laughs]
--[overlapping chatter]
--[TENCHI muffled yelling]