[RYOKO]
This is a Jurai ship?
I can't believe the
thing's still functioning!
It's intact, so it
shouldn't be completely
shut down.
[BOTH gasp]
We'd better get moving!
[WASHU]
Ryoko! Are you there?
Washu?
That's right! The greatest
genius  in the whole galaxy!
And the prettiest, too!
So as we speak, where are you?
About a mile or so
beneath the school.
I'm down here with
that Kinojo girl.
We're staring at
an old Jurai ship.
Excellent!
Does the ship look okay?
There's a big-ass tree
growing out of it,
but the kid says
it'll still work.
That right?
[KINOJO]
Uh, yeah. It should.
Kinojo, you think you
can get it started up?
[KINOJO] If the main systems
grant me access, I can.
Let's hope they do.
I think I know what's going on,
and the answer's in that ship.
[WASHU] Hey, science geeks,
how's your progress?
[FUKA]
Everything's almost done, boss.
We'll get it going soon.
[AOI] You've become such
a team-player, Fuka.
I like it.
[FUKA]
Just connect this, and...
Transmitting!
[TROOPER A]
Hands up!
[FUKA, AOI gasp]
[FUKA, AOI scream]
[FUKA]
You three did this?
Is this revenge 'cause
I ran for President?
I'd never vote
for anyone but Momo!
Is this really the
time to talk politics?
Look sharp! Back-up's here.
[KURIHARA]
Lower your weapons!
We need to evacuate.
That's an order. Now go!
You should all leave, as well.
Run as far as you can.
--[GROUP gasps]
--[FUKA, AOI scream]
Momo. Mr. Tenchi.
[MOMO gasps]
I can't catch him!
But I will!
Every time I find her,
I get sent somewhere else.
Are we stuck
like this... forever?
Can't we at least get
back to where we started?
[WASHU] I've got control
of the oscillator!
Try it now.
Okay.
[WASHU]
Phase stabilizer, activate!
[KINOJO]
Come on!
Get going, Peach Blossom!
[MOMO]
I can get to him!
[WASHU]
So far so good.
The ship's up and running.
Let's hope it has enough
power to get the job done.
Huh?
Yes, finally.
We're together again!