[GIRLS chattering]
So this next event is
called the Chicken Fight?
Hmph. It's a popular
tradition on Sports Day.
Something tells me this
won't be easy to referee.
Bound be a lot of "fowl" plays!
[GIRLS cheering]
Sounds like they're
out for blood,
and it's not chicken blood
I'm talking about!
Hey, we have very simple rules.
If your Captain's ribbon
falls off her head, you lose!
[HACHIKO]
Got a question for you!
Hope I can answer it.
Why is that oversized
tin can competing?
[FUKA] You should apologize
for being so rude!
He's not oversized, just husky!
I'm still bothered that
he's allowed to participate
in the Obstacle Course.
He's not enrolled
here as a student.
[FUEYAMA] According to
this institution's by-laws,
non-students are strictly
forbidden from taking part
in special school events.
[SARYU] Not to mention
the fact that your player's
not even human.
Are you saying that robots
don't have basic rights?
Who made you the judge
of what Goriki can do?
[HACHIKO] As usual,
you're missing the point!
Why don't you
all just calm down?
We should let the referee do
his job and settle this issue.
[GIRLS growl]
Let me see...
It's an obvious answer.
Goriki is going to be
allowed to participate.
You guys lose. Too bad.
At least we tried
to make it fair.
Despite all the odds,
we're gonna go for the win!
Yeah, whatever, bring it on!
--[TENCHI] Let the match begin!
--[horn blowing]
[GIRLS yelling]
Wow! You are so strong!
Leave it to me,
Mistress Momo!
I'll make sure they never
lay a finger on you!
[GIRLS yelling]
[FUKA] What am I doing down
here in the line of fire?
There's a lot more
protection on top of Goriki!
Anyone can see that!
[GIRLS yelling]
You should've let
me handle those girls!
[gasps]
Happy with my work,
or do you still wanna complain?
You're fine.
Please ignore my comments.
[AOI] But that's not
fair fighting, is it?
It is when you're
fighting to win!
[ANNOUNCER] That's three
points for the Red Team!
The White Team pushed ahead
with disastrous results.
All four White Team Units
were wiped out!
Medics, please get the
injured off the field!
[FUKA]
Only one more battle left!
[MOMO] No matter how bad
it seems, keep fighting!
[HACHIKO, KINOJO growl]
Watch out, everyone!
Punch coming from Goriki!
[GORIKI growls]
Smart maneuver!
But we're still in the lead and
we have more power than you
to bring home a win!
Well, power alone isn't
what decides a match
like this and we'll prove it!
We need to make sure that
no matter what they do,
we don't lose.
And I have something in my
pocket that'll seal the deal!
Take a peek! Here!
[AOI]
Huh?
Spider! [screams]
[FUKA]
Go, Rui!
[AOI screaming]
[HACHIKO yells]
[MOMO]
Let me help you!
Don't worry about me!
Protect your ribbon,
Mistress Momo!
It's much more important
that we stay together
than worrying about
any silly ribbon!
[HACHIKO]
But we'll lose!
[AOI screaming]
[TENCHI yells]
Well, I suppose we lost.
It looks like the
winner is the Red Team.
[groans]
All right!