[GIRLS chattering]
[TENCHI]
This sure is a long line.
I wonder what
we'll see in there.
--Hey! What the heck?
--[MOMO] Huh?
Watch out!
[MOMO gasps]
[STUDENT A] Look!
It didn't crack that egg!
[STUDENT B]
Amazing!
[TENCHI laughs]
What's wrong?
Why are you holding
on to me like this?
Oh! Sorry!
There's an arm wrestling
booth over there.
And it seems
to be quite popular.
[STUDENT C grunting]
Okay, next.
I'm so lucky! l held Kinojo's
hand for a long time!
[giggles]
That's weird.
I wonder why she's so popular.
Beni may not look that friendly,
but she's actually very gentle
and won't try to hurt you.
You pointing to me?
--[KINOJO] Mm-hmm.
--[MOMO] Go ahead!
Give it your best, Mr. Tenchi!
I'll try.
[TENCHI yells]
You lay a finger on
my Tenchi's fingers
and I'll crack you like an egg!
[TENCHI yelling]
I've heard what you
can do with that hand!
I don't want it near my man.
I'll wrestle you for him,
and I don't intend to lose!
[RYOKO, KINOJO growl]
[TENCHI yelling]
[RYOKO] Wow! I feel like
my hand is caught in a vise!
[KINOJO] What's her
deal with the teacher?
She's a real nut case!
[RYOKO, KINOJO grunting]
--[GIRLS gasp]
--Don't surrender!
[RYOKO, KINOJO grunting]
[RYOKO]
Is she even human?
I'm afraid I'm about
to lose this!
[RYOKO grunting]
[TENCHI grunting]
C'mon, Mr. Tenchi.
Where did you go?
[RYOKO, KINOJO]
Hmph!
Please hurry, girls.
--There are a lot more of these.
--Thank you.
You're both gonna have
to work twice as fast.
You have a very big
sweets bill to pay off.
My hands are starting
to shrivel up.
We should have brought
Goriki for this.
Oh, gosh!
Now because of this, we're gonna
miss the Drama Club's play!
I really wanted to see
"Beauty and the Prince."
Oh, listen,
my beautiful princess.
I'd bear any suffering to
awaken you from your spell.
And plant a kiss on
your lips one last time
to seal my love for you.
[HACHIKO gasps]
[HACHIKO]
How did he get in there?
I know not what to do!
Improvise!
Go for it!
Yeah, the show must go on!
[kissing noises]
[HACHIKO] This audience is going
to get an award-winning
performance from me!