Are you getting used to
how things work around here?
Oh, yes.
Or as much as I can,
considering all the chaos.
Hm?
What's that thing?
Huh? Oh.
This is sort of a charm
that was passed down to me
from the shrine in the
town where I grew up.
[KURIHARA]
Oh.
So for generations,
the men in your family
have been influenced by
the shape of this artifact?
I think there's a
misunderstanding here.
[KURIHARA]
Oh, please.
Just look at the shape,
the length, the girth.
What else could it be for?
And coincidentally,
this event's going on
at the school.
Maybe we should get
together and explore
a little
extra-curricular activity
since you've brought
along a toy.
I appreciate your
kind offer, but...
What a shame you have
so much restraint.
Those two are at it again!
--[KURIHARA] Huh?
--[TENCHI] S'cuse me!
I'll be back after
I separate them!
[KURIHARA growls]
[HACHIKO, KINOJO grunting]
Just hand over the materials!
Where's your voucher?!
We don't need a damn voucher!
We only want a little
bit of it anyway!
"We only want a little!"
Sure you do.
In the end, all those
resources get wasted!
[KINOJO growls]
All right, you two.
Just cut it out!
Go away!
Now surrender your weapons!
[TENCHI]
Whoa!
We're being discriminated
against by the Student Council!
They refuse to give us
the materials we need!
[TENCHI sighs]
We're all agreed, then?
They get nothing
until they come clean.
The Science Club
has been accused of
deliberately misappropriating
school resources.
Bull!
That's a phony charge!
Absolutely!
We need those tools and
materials for our exhibit!
It's all on the up and up!
We would never use
them to dig for treas--
The bottom line is
if you don't want trouble,
give us what we need!
[FUKA gasps]
If you bother
Mistress Momo anymore,
your head's gonna be
looking for a new body.
[KURIHARA]
That's enough!
If you lack resources,
make up for it
with brains and wit!
Understood?
[thunder rumbles]
[SARYU] Tori, did you
handle the request
from the Drama Club
for extra resources?
Yes, I approved it.
[SARYU]
Mm. Thank you.
Wait a minute.
I don't understand.
We seem to be pretty
flush at the moment.
So why'd you turn down--
[SARYU]
It's a simple system.
We give the money
based on how effectively
they justify their
budget request.
This is the responsibility
of the Student Council.
Teachers aren't
supposed to interfere.
Not ever?
If the Science Club's
determined to set its own
budget and resources,
then it will need to take
over control of the school.
That's the bottom line here.
We need to pick up
some materials
from the warehouse.
It won't take long.
Hachiko, would you
mind handling this?
Whatever you wish,
Mistress Momo.
Very good.
But there's quite
a bit to pick up.
Oh. No problem!
If you need help
carrying stuff, I'll do it!
[thunder rumbles]
This is weird.
[HACHIKO]
All right.
Shall we?