[SARYU]
Hey! Come back here!
[TENCHI yelling]
[GIRLS screaming]
[TENCHI gasps]
Oh, crap!
[TENCHI] There's gotta
be a place to hide!
[yelling]
This is a complete nightmare!
[TENCHI] I just need
to find some place--
Any place without an audience
to put on my clothes!
[yelling]
[TENCHI sighs]
That was awful!
I've never seen this room.
Where am I?
[TENCHI]
Hm?
Huh? Wait a minute.
I thought this
was the bottom floor!
[yelling]
[TENCHI groaning]
Huh?
What's happening? How weird.
[FUKA] Prioritize your digging
in the third quadrant!
[FEMALE OVERSEER A]
Keep it up!
We've still got three feet
of rock to cut through!
[FUKA]
We've gotta find this treasure
before the Student Council does!
[GIRLS]
Right!
If we can just
get hold of it first,
those goody-two-shoes
will be toast.
We're not really gonna
cook them, are we?
--[FUKA] Yeah!
--[AOI] Oh!
We're gonna cook
their collective goose!
Listen, this is war!
War, do you hear me?
They control our
operating budget--
they think they can make us
do whatever they want!
Wake up and smell
the oppression!
[FEMALE OVERSEER B]
We found it!
[FUKA]
That's just a lump of iron ore!
Keep digging!
Is this some kind
of a school project?
[MIHOSHI]
I can't do this anymore!
I'm so hungry
I can't swing my pick!
If you can't work,
you don't get any food!
[MIHOSHI] Does the
principal know about this?
Wait a second! Is that--?
I recognize that voice!
[FUKA]
Who's there?
[AOI gasps]
[TENCHI]
Meow!
[AOI]
It's a kitty! I wanna pet it!
[FUKA]
Are you for real?
[TENCHI yells]
Why don't you
come along quietly?
[TENCHI grunts]
[TENCHI]
Hey, let me go!
What do you think you're doing?
[FUKA]
Great work, Kinojo!
That's why you're
the muscle on this team!
[KINOJO] Well, I did
promise to protect the club.
So, what's next?
He knows about this place.
We don't have much choice.
Hold on,
what are you gonna do?!
I have to think about it.
Yeah, that should work.
[chuckles] Hey, Kinojo.
Let's start by getting
this guy's clothes off!
[TENCHI]
Why is that necessary?
Well, you could be
a Student Council spy.
Who knows what hidden weapons
you might have on you!
[FUKA chuckling]
Oh, my!
[TENCHI grunting]
[fabric ripping]
[FUKA]
Hmm...
He looks clean enough so far.
Just one place left to search.
We have to make sure this dude
doesn't pose a threat
of any kind!
[AOI squealing]
[TENCHI grunting]
[muffled screaming]