[MOMO] Don't you think
we're overreacting?
Not under the circumstances!
This is a dire emergency!
Mr. Tenchi's been kidnapped
by the Science Club.
Who knows what danger he's in?
Kinojo's long, thick, black club
could be dangerously
close to him right now.
Only two people in the world
would be worried about that--
you and Ms. Kurihara.
It appears that the three
accompanying Mr. Tenchi
have been taken captive as well.
[FUEYAMA]
What?!
We have to form a rescue party!
Little Sasami's in danger!
[MOMO whimpering]
[MIHOSHI] It's actually
an interesting story.
I've been sent here on a
kind of infiltration mission.
Really?
I'm trying to prove that
there are criminals here
who have been illegally
manipulating space and time.
[GROUP]
Huh?
Are you saying you have
the proof that such a thing
really exists?
Oh, please don't be silly!
You'd never find something
like that on a planet
as backward as this!
Then why are you
wasting your time?
Well, since I'm
down here anyway,
I thought that
searching for treasure
sounded like it
could be a lot of fun.
I happened to come
across Fuka and the others
and I decided I'd help them out
with their exploration
down here.
But...
This has to stay
just between us,
okay, you guys?
If anyone finds out,
then my infiltration
will be blown,
and we don't want
that to happen, do we?
So, this treasure
you're pursuing...
Does it really exist?
[FUKA]
Yes, it does.
And if you're interested,
we'll show you the proof
we've found.
I'm all set.
I am, as well.
[FUEYAMA]
Madam President.
Allow me to explain our plan.
[FUKA]
Here's the proof.
[TENCHI gasps]
[TENCHI] I dropped that
after I tracked down Momo!
We found it one day
when we were excavating.
It was in a layer of earth
that happens to be
a little over 1,300 years old!
And that makes it...
...an out of place artifact!
[FUKA] I said out of place
artifact, not implant!
So what exactly is
an out of place artifact?
It's an item found
within a time period
when it should've been
technologically impossible
to have been built!
You certainly wouldn't
expect to find
a 1,300-year-old
smartphone, would you?
That, my friends,
is incontrovertible proof that
there's something down there.
Oh, and by the way,
it was found by someone
that you know. Me!
[FUKA] Even after a
millennium underground,
its data is intact.
[AOI] Today, we discovered
the password that unlocks it.
[FUKA] The password is
"carrots are delicious."
Silly, huh?
[TENCHI] Oh, no, the
wallpaper on that phone
is a dead giveaway!
Finally!
[TENCHI gasps]
[FUKA]
Activate!
[AYEKA]
Oh, my!
[MIHOSHI]
How cute! Isn't that sweet?
Mr. Masaki, it appears
for over 1,300 years...
...you've been a cradle-robber!
Pervert.
Tenchi, how did
this picture get--?
You backstabber!
How could you?
It's not what you think!
That's just a picture
from the time we all went
to the beach together.
That was so much fun!
Where's all the rest
of your friends, then?
Come on, guys,
can't you see that Washu's
been messing with
my phone's settings?
--[crash]
--[ALL gasp]
[RYOKO]
What was that?
[AOI]
It's the Student Council!
So they've finally
resorted to force.
[GORIKI roars]
He's sure gotten a lot
stronger since Sports Day!
Tori!
His security systems
have been reinforced.
I can't hack in!
[HACHIKO]
Then that means
we'll just have to
"hack" in ourselves!
[SARYU]
Give us back Mr. Tenchi
[SARYU, FUEYAMA]
and Sasami, right now!
[GORIKI roars]