--[TENCHI] Momo?
--[YOUNG MOMO] Huh?
[TENCHI]
What in the world is going on?
Have I gone back in time?
[YOUNG MOMO]
I'm sorry.
Do I know you?
[TENCHI]
Uh...
[RYOKO]
Does this hole have a bottom?
Hey.
Are you certain there's
really a ship down here?
What if we go straight through
the Earth and pop out
on the other side?
Gee, lady, can't ya
even crack a smile?
Not when she needs me.
You mean Miss Momo?
[KINOJO] When I had no
idea what my purpose was
or how to use my power,
she helped me find my way.
Protecting her
isn't just my job.
It's a sacred duty.
Look. I'm only helping you
out here because of Tenchi.
I don't really need to know
your entire life story.
[CHIEF ENGINEER]
This is awful!
If the rift keeps
expanding like this,
it won't just engulf the Earth,
it'll swallow up every star
and planet in this whole system!
[GP CHIEF growls]
Fine, then shut it down!
We can't, sir!
If you can't,
then tell me who can!
[CHIEF ENGINEER]
Mmm...
[GP CHIEF growls]
Damn.
Huh? What?
Sorry, I couldn't
quite hear you.
We won't be able to stop this
without your help.
Well, I would help,
but there's not much I can do
if I'm stuck behind bars.
Of course, if someone were
able to fix that situation,
I'd gladly lend a hand.
Just what are you implying?
All the stuff that I did
that you arrested me for.
Make it go away.
[GP CHIEF growls]
What are you doing out
here all by yourself?
Because I'm new here,
everyone treats me
like I'm from another planet.
Maybe I just wasn't
meant to have any friends.
[TENCHI]
They'll come around.
[YOUNG MOMO]
Huh?
[TENCHI]
Just give it some time.
Once people know you,
you'll make lots of friends.
[YOUNG MOMO]
You think so?
Yeah.
[TENCHI gasps]
[MOMO screams]
[TENCHI]
Momo!
[TENCHI grunts]
What am I supposed to do?
On behalf of the
Galaxy Police, I hereby...
...pardon Washu Hakubi,
and exonerate her of
all her past offenses.
[WASHU]
Thank you.
Now that I'm free,
you've got a deal.
Congratulations on being
an honest citizen again!
All right, then.
This has gone on long enough.
Time to fix things.
I've gotta hold up
my end of the bargain.
This is one creepy place.
There it is!