[TENCHI sighs]
Glad that's over.
[SARYU]
Hello!
Huh? Who's there?
Hey, what's wrong?
Mr. Masaki, you're not wearing
your dress and make-up!
That's 'cause the
Culture Festival's over.
Do you need something?
Hey. If you're looking
for help with the cleanup,
I'm not available.
Classes are starting.
I know that!
What I wanna know is
may I call you Miss, Mr. Masaki?
Uh, excuse me?
Not all the time. I mean...
Just when we're
alone doing girl talk.
What? I'm confused.
Also, Sports Day is coming up.
You'll need a kick-pleat skirt!
[TENCHI yelling]
[TENCHI] How do you
like these high kicks?
Pretty cool, huh?
[SARYU] I'll need every one
of those kicks in my fight
to retain my
Student Council seat!
Lead the cheers for me!
With you, my B.F.F.,
looking so cute in your
cheerleader outfit, I'll win!
--[SARYU] Hmm?
--[TENCHI] Uh... uh-uh, uh-uh.
I take it that's a no, then?
Yeah.
That was a one-time only
stunt for the Culture Festival.
[SARYU sighs]
Sorry, but I can't.
[SARYU]
Yeah, I get it.
Your beauty as a girl
has burned into my eyes.
I see you in that
dress over and over.
And the memory of your long hair
will be in my mind forever.
Actually, I'd rather
you erase that image
--[SARYU] I can't!
--as soon as possible.
I've already made this adult
erotic comic book of you!
You're kidding me, right?
I have the printing
press working overtime.
Everybody will get one!
They'll be out tomorrow!
[TENCHI]
Great...
[SARYU giggling]
[SARYU] I'll see you manana,
Miss Tenchi Masaki!
Yeah! Manana, I can't wait.
[RYOKO] You're quite the popular
lady these days, Miss Tenchi.
[TENCHI]
How did you all get in here?
[AYEKA] The back door was
open and we tippy-toed in
quietly so as to not
interrupt your conversation.
From what I heard,
somebody has the hots for you.
Right?
I think it's great the
students have an open mind.
They've accepted you
totally as a girl!
You'll need my help again!
For Sports Day, we'll have
to girly you back up!
No, absolutely not!
I can't run around
with long hair in my eyes.
--What a shame.
--I'm the game referee!
--You're cute with long hair.
--[TENCHI] Ayeka!
--[RYOKO] Huh? What's this?
--[TENCHI] Give that back!
What are you hiding?
Huh?
[gasps]
[AYEKA]
Hey, I wanna see, too.
[RYOKO] This certainly leaves
nothing to the imagination!
It takes infatuation with Miss
Tenchi to a whole new level!
Hey! I wanna see the pictures!
[AYEKA]
Absolutely not!
You'll have to wait till
you're much older!
[SASAMI]
You're such a party poop!
[RYOKO] You might as
well doll it up, Tenchi.
When this comes out,
everyone will have
already seen up your skirt!
[TENCHI]
No way!
[FUKA]
Launch mode set!
[KINOJO growling]
We'll win big on Sports Day.
Nobody will defeat us!
[HACHIKO grunts]
[HACHIKO]
Certain victory is ours!
[KURIHARA laughs]
My prey is in my sights!