[wind whistling]
[TENCHI]
Where am I?
What is this place?
[TENCHI gasps]
[chuckles]
Kawanagare!
[MOMO]
Huh?
[TENCHI]
Did they get transported
somewhere else?
[KINOJO]
This is a sign.
It's down here!
Her ship, the Peach Blossom.
It's at the bottom of that hole.
You're sure?
Hey, wait!
[RYOKO grunts]
What the hell
were you thinking?
That's gotta be hundreds
of feet down!
You'd never survive!
I have to get down there, now!
[RYOKO groans]
What if I carry you
the rest of the way?
[KINOJO]
That's fine.
Sorry you're locked up,
but you're difficult to catch!
You have eluded us up to now,
Washu Hakubi, but not anymore.
Justice has finally
caught up with you
and you're going to pay.
Starting with 70,000
years' hard labor.
Whatever.
I did the crime.
I'll do the time.
[GP CHIEF]
How admirable of you.
[GROUP yells]
That is, if you live
long enough to take me in.
[MOMO]
I'm sorry, but who are you?
And how is it that
you know my name?
[TENCHI]
Huh?
Uh...
Oh!
Are you the school
psychologist they just hired?
What is it?
Did my teachers say
I'm acting strange?
You've got it wrong.
I know this place
is kinda far away.
But it's quiet.
And I can be alone
with my thoughts here.
It honestly helps me study.
I swear!
Not that I always
do great on tests,
but I'm working very
hard to get better.
Ah! It's getting late.
I need to go home now.
Goodbye!
--[TENCHI] Momo!
--[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
Huh?
Wait.
Have you and I
met somewhere before?
Well...
[gasps]
[GP CHIEF]
Hey! What's going on?
Why ask?
You're the one in charge.
[OPERATOR A]
Sir! The planet!
[TENCHI gasps]
What is this place?
Am I still in the same
dimension or somewhere else?
[swingset creaks]