[MOMO, KINOJO gasp]
Intruder alert's been activated!
What's happening?
[WASHU]
What are you waiting for?
Now's your chance!
Get moving!
Hurry up and find it!
Wait, I know that voice.
Yeah, there's
no doubt who it is.
You're absolutely right.
It's Washu.
What the hell
is going on here?
[WASHU]
I already told you!
You have the key to
the treasure's location!
Do not keep me waiting!
Oh, we've been
given a mission!
[TENCHI]
Miss Momo, may I?
Of course.
[TENCHI]
It's very close.
In fact, it's buried
right below us!
So all we have to do
is a little digging, then?
--[FUEYAMA] Sasami!
--[SASAMI yells]
I was so worried
about my little Sasami.
Are you okay?
That weirdo Tenchi didn't
do anything awful to you,
did he?
You poor little thing!
[HACHIKO yelling]
Playtime is over!
[RYOKO]
Ha!
Crap!
Victory is mine!
I forgot I lost my sword!
This is not turning out
to be the great day
I thought it would be!
I can't be a hero
without my weapon!
[KINOJO] The treasure's
just below us, right?
[MIHOSHI]
Dig, dig, it's right below.
We'll find it soon, that I know!
So, what did you find there?
Wait, that's a...
...Sword of Jurai!
[MIHOSHI]
Oh, my!
[WASHU]
We finally found it!
The final key!
Hold up! Be careful!
[MOMO, KINOJO]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[AOI]
It's so pretty!
[ALL yell]
The Jurai ship
has started to activate.
It's been buried
here this whole time!
[SASAMI]
What? Really?
[TENCHI] It was Momo,
Kinojo, and the sword.
Apparently, they were the keys
that Washu was looking for!
[ALL scream]
[KINOJO yells]
[yells]
[MOMO]
Kinojo!
Please try and find
it in your heart
to forgive me, Ayeka!
I guess, as long as
you've learned your lesson.
An earthquake?
[RYOKO]
Ayeka!
This is totally messed up!
[AYEKA] What do we do about
Tenchi and the others?
You get these two out of here!
I'll go find everyone and
get them all to safety.
Right. I'm on it.
[KINOJO]
Just... a little bit further.
[MOMO grunting]
[TENCHI]
Kinojo!
Hurry and grab my hand!
I'm not gonna leave
without that sword!
I've almost got it!
It's the only way I can
get my real self back.
[MOMO]
You don't need to!
Don't you see?
I like you just the way
you are right now!
I don't think I can hold on!
Hurry up, please!
Kinojo, come on!
Take your time, I'm good!
[KINOJO]
Almost have it...
[gasps] Oh, no!