[KURIHARA] First up is the
obstacle course competition.
Runners, take your positions!
Hmph! This race belongs to me!
We'll just see about that,
'cause I don't plan
to lose, either.
What are the rules of this game?
I think it's obvious.
They have to overcome obstacles.
I get that, but isn't
it too dangerous for them
to be carrying swords?
Oh, quit your worrying.
According to an
old safety manual,
as long as there
are no steel blades,
swords are allowed.
How old is that safety manual?
[horn blows, starting gun fires]
C'mon, Goriki, where are you?
--[GORIKI roars]
--[GIRLS scream]
Do as I command!
Get over here now!
[GORIKI roars]
[GIRLS yell]
Hold on!
[yells]
[grunts]
Well, I warned you.
Aren't you glad you
have that extra padding?
It's not nearly enough.
Why allow Fuka's team
to have Goriki?
--[KURIHARA] Why not?
--[TENCHI] Huh?
[KURIHARA] There's no mention
in the safety manual about it.
You need a new manual!
I'm catching up with you, Fuka!
[growls]
The game is heating
up quite nicely now.
But this isn't a fair game--
at least not the
way you're running it.
Life's not fair.
It's filled with hurdles.
You have to find a way to
survive and overcome them.
Just as you do in this course.
Your biggest obstacle
is your competitor!
[TENCHI sighs]
[HACHIKO grunting]
I can tap right into her info.
I've found her weak point
and I'm gonna use it to win!
[HACHIKO]
No!
Give... give it back!
Give it back!
Give me back my sword!
[crying]
Hachiko, get up!
Pull yourself together!
[HACHIKO]
I can't! I'm scared!
Something made Hachiko
switch to little girl mode.
If she stays there,
it's no good for our team.
Heh! But it sure is
good for mine!
Let's go!
According to my data,
little-girl Hachiko is impaired.
She has only two percent or less
of her normal physical ability.
Oh, boy.
Hachiko, get it back!
Don't let her keep your sword!
[HACHIKO]
I'm really scared, Momo!
I don't know if I can!
Of course you can! Don't let
your fear stop you from acting!
[HACHIKO]
What do I do?
Trust me, we've got your back!
All you have to do
is focus on your strength!
Looks like I'll be taking
the first-place win!
That's my girl!
Give me back my sword right now!
[crying]
Getting close; almost there.
Got it.
So will you be able
to shut him down?
Hacking complete.
Let's see if this works!
[FUKA]
Take her out, Goriki!
[GORIKI roars]
Hey! What's the problem
with this device?
Come on, why won't it work?
--[SARYU] It's no good!
--[FUKA] Huh?!
You busted him?
--[HACHIKO] Fuka!
--[FUKA] Huh?
How about you and me
finish this fair and square?
All right, now just
give me a moment.
I've got one thing to do
and then I'll be happy
to face off with you!
[HACHIKO chuckles]
[FUKA yelling]
I'm done for without my Goriki!
[GIRLS cheering]
[TENCHI] It's a big win
for the White Team!
You did it! Way to go, Hachiko!
[HACHIKO chuckles]
This really sucks!
[growling]
The next match is mine!
You'd better believe it!