[KINOJO]
This is impossible!
Gravitational anomalies
this huge don't just appear
without warning.
Communications are disrupted.
How could everything
go wrong all at once?
Beni!
Princess!
You need to get outta here!
Do you remember
how the controls work?
Yes, I do!
But I won't go alone!
I'm sorry.
But you have to this time.
I'll follow you soon.
Beni, no!
You have to go with me!
Be well, your royal highness.
[YOUNG MOMO]
Beni!
Oh, dear.
Now I've gone and done it.
I mean, really.
Why now of all times?
[TENCHI]
Excuse me! Is anyone in there?
[HACHIKO] Who are you
and what do you want?
You're both unknown to me!
You could be in
the service of monsters!
Inukai, hold on for a moment.
Tamaomi, have you
seen these two before?
I have no memory of them.
One may assume they are
not humans of our village.
[SARYU]
In that case, why should we not
drive you away from our gates?
We mean you no harm.
Trust me on that.
We're simply
looking for someone.
Oh, really? What is your
true relationship to this girl?
Her father? Her brother?
Or perhaps...
Her kidnapper!
You've got it wrong!
He's not kidnapping me!
He saved me!
When I was falling
to the ground,
he caught my butt with his face!
Excuse me? He did what?
Hey, could you
find some better way
of saying that?
Huh?
Let's try this direction.
Okay!
Why are you all following me?
We have important
business in this direction,
as well.
Reports indicate there have been
several monster
sightings in the area.
Really?
Oh, yes.
People have seen a beast
that rips through the sky,
firing arrows of light.
A creature that lays
waste to whole villages!
What?
[SARYU]
At last, we've found you!
You're the monster, aren't you?
Ryoko? What are you
doing in this place?
You mean you know this girl?
Well, whoever you are,
I've never seen you before.
But if you know my name,
you're after the bounty.
That's fine.
I was getting bored anyway.
I might as well kill some
time with you, sweet-cheeks.
It might be amusing for a while.
It'll beat hangin' with these
huckleberries, that's for sure.
No more of your insults!
[RYOKO]
Oh.
So you've decided
you're strong enough
to play with me?
Here you go!
[SARYU, FUEYAMA scream]
This won't end well.
Her power exceeds
all expectations.
Wanna keep playin'?
Stop it!
[YOUNG MOMO grunts]
[RYOKO yells]
[RYOKO groans]
I admit, that was
surprising, young lady.
Turns out you had some hidden
talents I wasn't aware of.
[YOUNG MOMO gasps]
Ryoko, she's a little girl!
Just stop this!
--[RYOKO laughs]
--[MIHOSHI] Excuse me!
--[RYOKO] Huh?
--Much as I hate to intrude.
--[TENCHI] Huh?
--[GROUP] Huh?
[MIHOSHI]
Don't move, Space Pirate Ryoko!
This is the Galaxy Police!
[MIHOSHI] And I'm Detective
First-Class Mihoshi!
--[RYOKO] Huh?
--[GROUP gasps]
Don't resist! You are
officially under arrest!
[giggles]