[SARYU] Here we are,
back for another year!
By and for school girls!
The Miss Junai Competition!
I'm your host, Hana Saryu!
I'm your show commentator,
Tori Fueyama!
Here's our first contestant!
Our Student Council President,
Momo Kawanagare!
I hope everyone's having fun!
That's the point
of this festival!
Momo's scoring well, showing
us the beauty of having fun!
And she's scoring for wearing
that cute peachy mascot outfit.
--Looking good!
--[SARYU] Right!
Let's see if the
judges agree with you.
[FUKA]
Hmph.
Audience score, five hundred.
What a bunch of jerks!
[SARYU]
10, 12, 15, 8, 11!
Total score, 56!
That's really setting
the bar high
for the rest of
our contestants.
[FUEYAMA]
And the audience is just loving
her whimsical and carefree
display of joy and love!
[MOMO laughing]
Have a peachy-cool
Cultural Festival, everybody!
Our next contestant is the
Student Council's lethal weapon,
Hachiko!
She's here in costume,
straight from her
starring performance in
"Beauty and the Prince"!
--[HACHIKO] Hmph.
--[AUDIENCE cheering]
[FUKA growls]
1,200 points from the audience?
What's so special?
She was super cool in that role!
Quit praising the enemy!
And you, go get changed!
Without her,
the play would've bombed!
Up next, the least
notable threesome,
straight from the Science Club!
Hold on!
Why aren't we being
announced separately?
Sorry 'bout that.
It's a tight schedule.
The girl in the blah
swimsuit is Yuki Fuka.
[FUEYAMA] That suit doesn't
flatter her curves,
if she has any.
[SARYU] The one in the workout
clothes and boots is Rui Aoi.
[FUEYAMA] Boy, it must be quite
a challenge to do a spin-cycle
in those knee-high boots!
[SARYU] And sporting a
stowaway-meets-pirate motif
is Beni Kinojo.
[FUEYAMA]
Terrific outfit for her,
but watch out for that club!
I'm not sure
how to score them.
Their presentation lacks
personality and charm.
That's enough already!
Why don't you just
let the judges decide?
[SARYU]
Their composite score is...
[FUEYAMA]
94, and divided by three is
--31.333333...
--[FUKA] You're crazy!
There's no way
we scored that badly!
My calculations put us
closer to 120 points each!
[KURIHARA] Knock it off,
you sore losers!
Check out this design!
[SARYU] Our school's voluptuous
principal, Ms. Kurihara!
[FUEYAMA] Flaunting a
generous display of skin
in a skimpy and
very revealing look!
This isn't fair!
You're competing against
your own students!
[KURIHARA]
Hmph!
What the...?
She sure doesn't look that good
when she's giving
Master Tenchi a hard time!
He might give her a hard time
when he sees that outfit.
[SARYU]
The judges have decided!
It's a runaway lead!
And now, the final contestant!
Our student teacher,
Mr. Tenchi Masaki!
[gasping]
[KURIHARA]
Huh?
[AUDIENCE whispering]
5,000! 7,000! No, 10,000! Gah!
[KURIHARA] I thought he'd
make a fool of himself,
but instead he pulled it off.
It's been a long time
finding a prey worth breaking!
I'm gonna enjoy this!
--He.. just won.
--Just won.
I call Mr. Tenchi... winner!
Nobody has scored so high in
all the years of this contest!
As a woman, he rocks!
[MOMO]
Congratulations on your victory!
[TENCHI laughs]
You did pretty well
yourself, Momo!
It was a fun contest filled
with so many surprises!
Yeah.
[MOMO]
I'm off to wash up.
You should probably
do that, too!
[SARYU giggles]