Oh, boy, this is amazing!
There's plenty more,
Master Tenchi.
Enough for seconds.
So please dig in, help yourself.
Thanks, I will, Ayeka.
Wow, that just
made my toes wiggle!
Guess being a student
teacher doesn't give you
much time to eat.
Yeah, but at least
I won't get fat!
So who's winning
the sports contest?
[TENCHI] Well, both teams
are running neck and neck
at the moment.
The White Team has
Hachiko as their top scorer
and Kinojo's coming on
strong for the Red Team.
Bat girl loves to
show off her strength!
[RYOKO, KINOJO grunting]
All right, time for me
to get back to refereeing.
Keep up the good work,
big bro, Tenchi!
Thanks! We're about
to begin the finals.
Afterwards I'll be soaking
in a hot tub!
Master Tenchi,
no one seems to know.
What's the final competition?
Well, it's a little different.
Hard to describe.
You'll have to see for yourself.
[AYEKA]
Hm?
[TENCHI] In this corner,
White Team sumo wrestler,
the one and only...
...Momo the Magnificent!
[TENCHI] In the other corner,
for the Red Team,
the brawny Beni Kinojo!
Sumo wrestling?
They aren't fat enough!
How come they're facing off
with their bottoms touching?!
Doesn't that position
seem kind of odd to you?
Not really, not if your butt
is your biggest "asset."
Ryoko, that's so crude!
Don't you think they
should turn around?
Why are you so upset?
You're not a bottom-feeder,
are you?
What? I take offense at that!
Do you think my rear-end
is competitive, Mr. Masaki?
[TENCHI laughs]
Ready! Bottoms up!
Begin!
[RYOKO] Hey, quit ogling
the merchandise!
Ah! I'm doing my job,
that's all!
Yeah, a guy's dream job.
What boy wouldn't
volunteer for this?
Mr. Masaki is an ass man.
I've entered the data.
[TENCHI]
That's wrong!
All I want is to get
this thing behind me!
Wait, I didn't mean that--!
Hey, whose idea was it
for this sumo butt
stand-off, anyway?
Sorry, I can't take credit.
It was Kawanagare's idea
that Sports Day should end
with a keister contest.
Huh?
You're pretty good at this.
So are you, Beni.
Did you think you'd have
a better chance at winning
if I couldn't use my hands?
Winning or losing
wasn't really on my mind.
[KINOJO]
Huh?
I just wanted to have
some quality time with you
so we could talk about stuff.
Talk about what?
[MOMO] To find out how you
were doing and feeling,
girl talk, you know,
stuff like that.
If we looked at each
other face to face,
you would just focus
on beating me to a pulp,
so I thought this was the
best way to have a chit-chat!
Is that like prat-chatter?
[KINOJO]
You know you're kinda weird?
[MOMO]
Yup!
But at least I don't try
to cause pain to anyone
with my words.
[KINOJO] My cheeks are chafed!
That's pain, isn't it?
[MOMO]
Hmm. Right!
Momo, what do you want from me?
I want you to be
my friend, Beni.
Is that so hard?
Yes, it is!
[BOTH yelp]
[TENCHI]
Look out!
Are you both okay?
Oh! Did we lose
points for that?
[TENCHI]
What about you, Kinojo?
Get away from me, you creep!
[TENCHI]
Wha--?
[KINOJO] Don't pretend you
weren't coppin' a feel!
Oh, thank goodness
this final event is over!
I can go home
and soak in the tub.
--[FUKA] Not so fast!
--[TENCHI] Huh?
They both went down
at the same time.
There was no declared winner!
[TENCHI]
S'cuse me?
What numbers do you
have for the final score?
1,050 to 1,050. It's a tie.
Sports Day is not over
until this match is complete.
Neither team can win
until that tie is broken!
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention, students!
Sports Day has been extended
to complete the final match.
Resuming now!
[GIRLS cheering]
[KURIHARA] We're gonna
go as long as it takes,
until one of these
teams collapses!
[TENCHI]
Or I do!