Oh, good! You made it!
Nice work getting away.
Washu! It's you!
What the heck is going on?
Why don't we save
all the details for later?
Get moving!
The Galaxy Police are
on their way over here!
Master Tenchi, Ryoko,
take those two and
head down below.
As for you...
You girls are going
to help me ambush
those alien nitwits.
I know that voice!
You're the one we heard?
[WASHU]
Hm?
[SWAT GUY A]
This is Galaxy Police SWAT!
We've got the building
completely surrounded!
You're sweatin', rookie.
A little nervous?
Yeah. I mean... I'm okay.
You're gonna want to
change out your equipment.
A gun's no good for
what we're up against.
Roger that.
There's no shame
in being scared, kid.
This is Washu Hakubi
we're talkin' about.
Behind the Academy's back,
she did whatever she wanted
and called it "research."
Who knows how many
planets she destroyed?
No one's counted them all.
Yet she's never shown
one shred of remorse.
Her eyes are cold as ice.
She is evil!
Don't you think she
should be stopped?
I do!
[KINOJO]
Are you serious?
[MOMO] You're saying
we're not from Earth?
I don't understand!
[TENCHI]
I know it sounds unbelievable,
but it's the truth.
1,300 years ago,
you and Kinojo were caught
in a dimensional warp
and flung to Earth.
Eventually you wound up
here, in the present day.
But this is the place
where everything started
all those years ago.
So.
It's right that it
end here, as well.
Hey!
I hope it's time for snacks,
'cause I'm hungry.
What? You're still
digging down here?
[MIHOSHI]
Should I not be?
[WASHU] Looks like they
disarmed my booby traps.
Well, good for them.
You're nuts!
You want me to squeeze
down in there?
You have to!
[RYOKO]
Ugh!
[SWAT GUY A]
No barricades or force fields.
This should be a piece of cake!
[SWAT GUY A grunts]
[SWAT GUYS grunting]
[FUKA laughs]
I don't know if you guys
are aliens or what,
but you're not getting past me!
[SWAT GUY B]
Go around her! Huh?
[AOI screaming]
It's a spider!
Get it away! Get it away!
Get it away!
[SWAT GUYS yell]
[KURIHARA]
Call your men back.
I don't want them using
any deadly weapons,
not on the humans.
[SWAT OFFICER]
Their weapons are a joke.
A wooden stick?
Primitive savages!
[yells]
[KURIHARA] Watch your mouth!
They're my students.
You girls!
You both need to stop!
If you resist,
you'll lose all credits
you earned this year,
and be expelled!
[FUKA]
That's not fair! Aww!
[WASHU] Well, at least
they bought us some time.
[chuckles]
It's almost here.
I'd never do this
for anyone but Tenchi.
Huh?
Is that it?