[LLOYD]
Lloyd here.
Last time, my team of S-Rankers
and I tried our best
to protect Mistgun from
a Devil Beetle invasion.
But when a strange
Chimera showed up,
someone else in the city
took the monster down.
I don't know what
happened exactly,
but I'd bet my buddy
Kanata's somehow involved.
[MISORA panting]
[panting continues]
[yells]
[MISORA] Quit moving,
you stupid balloons!
Hey, Rico. Help me out here!
--What're you doing?!
--[RICO hums]
Maybe if you didn't fly
around so erratically
you would have better aim.
You should be able
to handle them.
Rico! Quit gawking at
yourself and cover me!
[RICO] That's no way to
talk to a supreme being.
[LECTY]
Misora... Uh, uh!
I'd help but...
[screams]
[MISORA] I'm the leader and
I'm giving you an order!
[LECTY]
Please don't fight, you two!
We're supposed to be
working together...
[RICO] You need to
get up to my level!
[FREON]
Kanata Age's fireteam
hasn't made any progress
since he took over.
[CHLOE sighs]
I'm afraid that's true.
They still haven't been able
to break their losing streak.
[FREON] The reports indicate
the abnormal Chimera
was not destroyed by your team.
Are you certain that you
had nothing to do with it?
Definitely not, ma'am.
We could see the
resulting explosion,
but none of us were there.
We owe our lives to whoever
killed the beast. So naturally,
Kanata is now claiming that
his fireteam was responsible.
Like I'd believe that.
Uh!
[FREON]
Because of this,
he says his fireteam shouldn't
be held accountable for the
considerable collateral
damage they caused
the day of the attack.
[CHLOE] So, what did you
say about these claims?
[FREON] The only thing I
could do was laugh at him.
He has no evidence or
eyewitnesses to the event.
But one thing's for certain.
They destroyed an entire city
block trying to fight the bugs.
Due to this and their
previous failures,
I've decided it may be best
to disband Fireteam E601.
[LECTY whimpers]
I'm starting to think
we're getting in a little
over our heads here.
Hey, Rico! You gotta cover me!
It's the only way we're gonna
get ourselves outta this mess.
[RICO]
Do you really think
I'm in the position
to snipe anything?
Though I could probably
put you out of your misery
if I tried hard enough.
[MISORA] Don't you even think
about firing that weapon at me!
[LECTY] I can't take any
more of this, you guys.
I'm really getting worried here.
[MISORA]
Butt out, Lecty!
I guess it's about time for
me to end this exercise
so we can move on
to the next one.
[CHLOE] If his fireteam's
disbanded, what'll Kanata do?
Obviously, he'll be
relieved of duty.
Do you have a problem with that?
[YURI] You're making
the right decision.
[FREON]
Mm?
But, Yuri...
A traitor shouldn't be
leading Sky Wizards.
Who knows what lessons he's
actually teaching those girls.
[FREON]
Chloe.
I know this might be hard for
you since you recommended him,
but please bring Kanata to
my office this afternoon.
[CHLOE sighs]
Okay.
So is that it?
You called this meeting
just to talk about Kanata?
Because if I were
a guessing man,
I'd say you've got something
else on your mind.
[FREON] How adept of you.
Let's talk about this.
[MISORA]
Ow! What's goin' on back there?
Man, It hurts!
I'm bruised all over!
Huh? That's because your
movements lack grace.
Look at Lecty's skin.
[LECTY gasping]
Hey, stop. It tickles
when you do that.
[RICO] She doesn't
have a scratch on her.
Well, if you had just
covered me like I asked
this wouldn't be a problem.
But my pain aside,
the real issue is why no one
recognizes that we took down
that weird Chimera and
totally saved Mistgun!
They should be throwing
us a parade!
Misora has a point.
It's high time this city
started celebrating
its most divine citizen.
Huh? Think about it.
Nobody was around
to see you girls
fighting the Devil Beetles.
It's no surprise they
don't believe you.
What?! Who cares who saw it?
You used that weird power that
made you fall out of the sky--
[grumbling]
So, you're saying you
feel unfulfilled?
I guess...
What about you, Kanata?
Don't you want some credit
for what you did?
Nah. I don't care what other
people think about me.
Well, Anyway, check this out.
Doesn't it sound like it's
gonna be a good time?
[RICO]
The Mistgun...
[LECTY]
...Tournament?
[AMIE] All fireteams are
eligible to join the competition
except for those designated
as Special Teams.
Whoa, look at that
prize package!
The winning team moves
up two whole ranks!
And that's not all.
The last team standing
gets cutting-edge gear.
Unique weapons specially made
by the Alchemy division!
Plus a year of free food at all
the restaurants in Mistgun!
Ah! Think of all the desserts we
could eat if we come out on top!
[STUDENTS cheer]
You brought everyone in the
city joy. I'm proud of you.
I'll give my all to
win the tournament.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[GIRL A]
She's so superior!
It's only natural
that I should win.
[STUDENTS cheering]
You're a far better
Sky Wizard than I am.
There's never been a leader
as good as you, Misora!
You've done it.
The student has surpassed
the instructor.
We have to win this
thing no matter what.
[GIRLS laughing]
So you're into it?
[GIRLS]
Huh?
Well, guys?
Um. I don't know if
it's possible for us
to beat all the other
fireteams in the academy.
We still have to try, though!
Yeah, she's right.
We have to at leasts
see how far we get.
Well, then. I suppose I'm in.
Without me watching your backs,
you mortals won't make
it past the first round.
[KANATA] All right, great.
That settles it, then.
I'll start filling out the
application right away.
So... You mean
you're firing me?
It's my only option.
Your fireteam has
shown no improvement,
and this morning's
training was a disaster.
Not only were they sloppy,
but the girls spent
most of the time
fighting amongst themselves.
[KANATA] Hm. Sounds like you've
been watching us closely.
[FREON]
That's my job.
Disbanding fireteam E601
is simply the most
logical thing to do.
They don't seem very motivated
anyway, so what are they losing?
You're wrong.
Say what you want,
but I'm not going.
You see, I've still got
a lot to teach them.
[FREON]
What are you saying?
Exactly what it sounds like.
I signed on to make
them better Sky Wizards.
And so, I'm not giving
up until those girls
are the best fighters
you have at this school.
Oh, don't make me laugh.
You are a traitor.
What on earth could you possibly
have to offer our students?
You may have come with
Chloe's recommendation,
but I still have serious
doubts about your--
You can keep your doubts, Freon.
I don't need your approval.
I only care what three
people think of me.
And those three are
Misora, Lecty, and Rico.
That's nice and all, but
I don't really believe it.
Don't worry. No one really
expected much from any of you.
[KANATA] But if we
win the tournament,
everyone will have
to respect us, right?
That's the deal.
[laughs]
No chance in hell.
The best of the best will
be in this tournament
and your three girls
can't compete.
They're all hopeless. They can't
even beat other E-Rankers.
Care to make a bet, then?
[FREON]
Uh?
[FREON laughs]
[RICO]
Report.
Yeah. What's she saying?
It's kinda hard
to hear. Be quiet.
[FREON] ...though I've decided
to disband your fireteam,
I'll reconsider if...
She wants to
disband our team!
She what?!
No! We can't let that happen!
Well, maybe there's something
we can do to stop this.
Let's keep listening.
[GIRLS gasping]
Hello, ladies.
[GIRLS laugh]
[RICO] Why was she talking
about disbanding our fireteam?
On what grounds?
We deserve to know!
[KANATA]
Listen, girls.
Eavesdropping's a
really annoying habit.
The best thing you can do now
is to forget what you heard.
Wait. Come back!
Yeah, tell us what's
going on, Kanata!
[RICO]
Hmph.
[KANATA] Wow, everyone
looks so depressed today.
[LECTY]
Why aren't you more upset?
[MISORA] Seriously, if
what we heard is true
our team is doomed.
They'll kick us out.
[KANATA] All right, so what
are you gonna do about that?
We can't disband.
I want this fireteam to be
the strongest it can be!
Maybe Freon will reconsider
if we prove ourselves
in the opening match!
Yeah! She'd have to, right?
Being a divine goddess,
I don't really need
this silly fireteam.
But, if you two
insist on fighting,
I suppose I could play
along and help you out.
[KANATA] I'm glad to see we're
on the same page for once.
Try not to let yourselves get
freaked out by the stakes.
All you have to do to
continue your training
is show them you can win.
No pressure.
[MISORA] What do ya
mean no pressure?
You're kidding us, right?
[LECTY]
This is the worst.
I know how this looks.
We don't have any wins yet.
You're the lowest-ranked
team at school.
That's helpful.
You sure do know how to
bring down a room, Kanata.
This tournament is a gift to us.
Previous rankings don't matter
so we start with a clean slate.
This is your chance
to start from scratch
and prove yourselves.
[MISORA]
Sure. I guess.
[KANATA]
That's all for today.
Tomorrow we're starting
a new training regimen
so make sure you get
a good night's sleep.
I'm gonna put you girls
through the ringer.
You're gonna hate me
when I'm through with you.
[MISORA]
You're just leaving?!
[LECTY]
Shouldn't we train more today?
[KANATA]
Oh, by the way. Don't forget.
The opponents for the first
round are being chosen tomorrow.
Make sure you're there
to get matched up.
Later!
[FREON]
This is it.
[FREON] I'm sure you've
heard rumors about the labs
where we study Devil Beetles.
Hopefully this tour will give
you a better understanding of
our efforts to defeat the enemy.
[LLOYD] Is it true they're
dissected down here?
[FREON]
Certainly.
You likely saw the results
of such research
in your Hostile
Organisms classes.
[YURI] Yeah, it was almost
more than I could swallow
when I was a prep student.
[CHLOE] But why are you
showing us all this now?
[FREON] You're still against the
idea of the Mistgun Tournament,
right Chloe?
[CHLOE] Well, yes.
I think it'll only serve
to agitate rivalries
between fireteams.
But what does that have
to do with anything?
[FREON]
Here we are.
[REAL]
Welcome to the lab, everyone!
We've been expecting you.
[REAL]
Ah...
Hosting the Sky Wizards
division lead is an honor.
All of us are thrilled.
Let me introduce the
others. Some of our best.
Oh, I already know who you are!
Special Duty team S-128.
The highest-ranked Sky Wizards
in the entire academy.
The powerful Chloe Sevigny.
Mr. Lloyd Alwyn.
Hello.
It's very nice to meet you.
[REAL]
And of course...
Nice to see you again,
Miss Yuri Flowstruh.
Uh!
Oh, please forgive me for
running into you that day.
I hope I didn't end up
ruining your pants.
Ah! I'm so delighted that you
remember talking to me!
Seriously! Ah. I have
something... uh... for you!
Uh. Please.
Just show us the sample.
Of course! Right this way.
[LLOYD]
What is that?
[CHLOE]
A Chimera shard?
[FREON] I'm still not sure
who took this monster down.
It appears to be larger than
a normal Chimera Deneb.
We don't know much about it.
But we've given the species the
codename "Chimera Antares."
[FREON] It's not just bigger
than the typical Chimera.
Watch what happens when
trauma is inflicted on it.
[CHLOE, YURI, LLOYD gasp]
[REAL chuckles]
--[YURI, CHLOE] Mm?
--[LLOYD] Uh?
It regenerated itself.
This specimen is truly
an amazing discovery!
The Chimera is
continuously rebuilding.
We've got infinite samples
now! Just think of it.
This could lead to cutting
edge breakthroughs
in regenerative medicine!
And not to mention--
That'll be enough.
Thanks for the demonstration.
Now if you'll excuse us,
we can see ourselves out.
[REAL]
Uh. Well... Sure.
I'll just get back to work then.
Oh, yeah!
I saw your interviews in "The
Monthly Mistgun" the other day.
It got me wondering...
Tell me, Miss Yuri.
Is it true you're only
interested in dating men
who are stronger than you are?
[YURI]
Huh? Oh. Um, I guess.
Yeah. It does seem
to be the case.
Well, I'll keep
that in mind.
Maybe this means I should
start hitting the gym myself.
Well, anyway. I'm glad I got
to see you again today.
[REAL inhaling]
[FREON]
Do you understand now?
Our enemy is evolving
at an alarming rate.
We need more Sky Wizards
who are strong enough
to stand against
the Devil Beetles.
So that's it. That's the reason
behind the tournament.
[FREON]
Yes.
Are you okay? You're looking
awfully pale, Yuri.
Uh. Yeah, I'm all right.
I think I just need a little
fresh air after that.
I know. The stench in
that place was repulsive.
[CHLOE] That was certainly
an informative field trip.
[FREON] Before you go,
there is one more thing.
Yuri, there's something
I need you to handle.
A job for me?
--[LLOYD] Hm?
--[CHLOE] Uh?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GIRL STUDENT A squealing]
Fireteam E-644.
You're in Block B.
You'll be taking
slot number twelve.
[GIRL STUDENT A] We're up
against a team of A-Rankers?
You just had to pick
the worst one!
[whines]
[BOY STUDENT A]
Aw, yeah!
[BOY STUDENT B] We've totally
got this one in the bag.
[BOY STUDENT C]
Oh, crap, they're B-Rankers.
[TOURNAMENT OPERATOR] And next
up we've got Fireteam E601!
[GIRLS gasp]
Make your choice!
Right! A-Ah! Okay!
Good luck! Pick us a good one!
Choose the wrong ball,
and we're dead.
I've got this, no problem!
[MISORA grunting]
[grunting, screams]
Let's see, team E601.
You're in Block D. On the
board in slot number four!
But what team are we
matched up against?
Fingers crossed, guys.
[MISORA sighs]
It's another E-rank team.
Yeah! Go Misora! You did it!
Well. I'd have been fine going
up against a higher-rank team.
[KANATA]
Ah, did you already draw?
[GIRLS gasp]
Kanata, look! We're fighting
another E-Ranked team!
Yeah. Maybe if we
win against them
everyone will see we're
not losers anymore!
[YURI]
May I have a word?
[GIRLS, KANATA]
Uh?
What are you doing here?
I thought S-Rankers
weren't allowed
to take part in the tournament.
Don't worry, I'm not
here as a participant.
But my students are going
to be in the competition.
The crap are you
talking about?
You didn't hear? Freon's
given me a new assignment.
I've been made the instructor
of an A-Ranked fireteam.
Yay...
[YURI grunts]
I am kinda bummed, though.
My fireteam, A-227, is in a
different block than yours.
I guess we won't have the
chance to go head-to-head.
It's a real shame. I was
looking forward to it.
[KANATA]
That's just what you think.
[YURI]
What do you mean?
[KANATA] Well, if your team
manages not to choke,
then maybe they'll
get to join us
in the final round of
the tournament.
[YURI]
Uh...
[ALL]
Uh?!
What's wrong?
You shouldn't look so shocked.
Oh wait, are you afraid of
losing against my fireteam?
What?! I most
certainly am not.
Because my fireteam could
annihilate your girls
without even using
their weapons.
I see. So you think they'll
take home the prize?
It's a sure thing.
Okay. Then let's make a bet.
If we win, you get
to join my fireteam.
[gasps]
Are you crazy?! There's no way.
Your team can't even defeat
other E-Rankers like themselves.
You want a bet? All right,
then. I accept your wager.
You might regret that.
[LECTY]
Um, are you sure about this?
I think I must have
heard you incorrectly.
I thought you said something
about us winning
the entire tournament.
Are you completely mental?!
No, it's just the
pact that I made.
Freon said that's how
we can save our team.
All we have to do is
win this whole thing.
Otherwise, I'm gonna get fired
and then E601 will be disbanded.
[ALL gasp]
[KANATA] Hm? Oh, did
I not mention that?
[ALL growling]
[ALL]
You've gotta stop doing that!
[STUDENTS chatting, laughing]
Freon here to tell you
about the other divisions
operating in Mistgun
alongside my Sky Wizards.
For example, there's Medicine,
which includes the secret
lab we visited today.
In addition, there's Machina,
Alchemy, Industrial, Logistics,
Economics, Information,
and Relics.
Each division plays an important
role in keeping our city afloat.
Any questions so far?
[REAL]
Well, yeah, I was wondering--
[FREON]
Great. No questions.
Catch our next episode,
"Beyond the Rankings."
[REAL]
This is Real... by the way.