[FREON]
This is Freon Flamel,
leader of the Sky
Wizards division.
Thanks to traitors,
a younger sister who
thinks she's a goddess,
and the embarrassment
that is Fireteam E601,
my days aren't the easiest.
However...
What?!
Devil Beetles are
attacking the city?
All right, Sky Wizards,
let's show those bugs
what we're made of!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Warning!
Devil Beetles have been spotted
in the skies above Mistgun.
Alpha security protocols
are now in effect.
Regular students and
non-combatant citizens
must evacuate to a nearby
shelter immediately.
This is not a drill.
I repeat.
Devil Beetles have been spotted
in the skies above Mistgun.
Alpha security protocols
are now in effect.
Regular students and
non-combatant citizens
must evacuate to a
nearby shelter immediately.
This is not a drill.
[gasps]
[FREON]
Status report!
[FEMALE OPERATOR]
Enemy forces have entered the
southern quadrant,
and they've got reinforcements
right behind them.
[FREON] Send E-Ranked fireteams
to help with evacuations.
They'd just be in the way.
All A-Ranked wizards
should take to the sky.
This is it!
Send those devils back to hell!
[MISORA]
Done with this side! All clear!
[RICO] Hm. My duties have
been completed as well.
[KANATA] Seems like a
successful evacuation.
Hold on. Why are you
helping us down here?
You used to be an
ace Sky Wizard.
Wouldn't you be more help to us
taking down Devil Beetles
on the front lines?
[KANATA]
Technically, but I'm afraid
it's more complicated than that.
[RICO]
Complicated? Explain yourself.
[MISORA] Wait, has anyone
heard from Lecty yet?
[RICO huffs]
Where is she?
Um! We've got a problem!
[ALL]
Huh?
I found this girl all by
herself on the street.
Hey, where did my
mommy go? Who are you?
We've gotta get
her to a shelter!
[KANATA]
No use.
[MISORA, RICO gasp ]
We don't have time.
Our enemy's attacking.
[sighs]
Whoa!
You took out that whole
squad with a single shot!
[CHLOE] Huh? You can do the
same thing with your spear.
So, why are you
using that sword?
Oh, I've decided I'm not
gonna use a spear anymore.
It didn't seem like
the right fit for me.
[CHLOE]
Hm.
[LLOYD grunts]
Hey! We've got a problem.
A different squad
of Devil Beetles
has punched
through our defenses.
[CHLOE, YURI]
Huh?
[LLOYD] They're about to
flood the streets of the city!
[FEMALE OPERATOR] The Devil
Beetles have breached our walls!
We're counting at least five
hundred of them inbound!
[gasps]
[FREON] Get me the
head supervisor!
Mistgun is yours to protect.
Use any means necessary
to stop the beetles.
Understood, ma'am.
Contact every one
of our students,
even those helping out
with the evacuations.
Tell them to prepare for combat.
These bastards can't
land in our city!
We're giving them
all we've got!
[gasps]
--[MISORA gasps]
--[YOUNG GIRL sobs]
Don't you worry,
it's gonna be okay.
There's no need to cry!
[SOCIÉ] Just remember
that when I'm away,
I'm busy keeping
our city safe.
Yeah, I know.
[BOTH giggle]
I suppose I should protect
you and your daddy too, huh?
[grunts] I'll make
sure no one gets hurt!
[gasps]
I've just gotta lock
on to my target.
There's no way these
bugs are getting past me.
[gasps]
What? I missed!
Take this!
I got it!
Wow, that was a
great shot, Misora!
[MISORA gasps]
Your accuracy still needs
some work. But that'll do.
Nice.
[RICO] I guess all the
training is paying off.
You only screwed
up the attack once.
[MISORA sighs]
You keep shooting.
We'll protect this girl and--
[RICO]
Misora, wait!
[MISORA] I'm gonna take all
these Devil Beetles out at once!
Whoa, I did it!
[ALL grunt]
I'm so gonna get
blamed for this.
[RICO] Hmph. I can't
believe you released a
Strike Blaster in the
middle of the city.
You destroyed a
whole neighborhood.
[ALL]
That was really stupid.
What? That was an accident!
I just wanted to
destroy the enemies.
And I didn't see any
of you helping out.
[KANATA] You're gonna
feel pretty terrible
when you realize that you
demolished your dad's café.
[MISORA gasps]
Huh?
Oh no!
[FEMALE OPERATOR] Enemy numbers
are approaching ten thousand.
Only 30% of our
Fireteams are operational.
Then we've only got one
chance to defeat them.
We have to kill their commander.
[YOUNG GIRL] Look mom,
I found a kitty on the street!
Can we keep him?
He's really sweet, I promise!
I'm so glad
you're okay, come here.
Thank you!
[BOTH giggle]
[gasps]
[KANATA]
This isn't good.
[gasps]
[FEMALE OPERATOR] There's a
large Devil Beetle approaching!
Signs indicate that
it's a Chimera Deneb.
Location?
[FEMALE OPERATOR]
It's in Block 24, ma'am!
[FREON] Send all functioning
units to that area.
Focus our firepower on it!
Everything we have!
If we kill that Chimera,
then the rest of the Devil
Beetles will fall away!
[COELA grunts]
[AMIE shouts]
[BEACH yells]
[FEMALE OPERATOR]
Confirmed!
The Chimera Deneb is destroyed!
Good. Now Reallocate
the fireteams.
Focus on eliminating any
enemy stragglers and then--
[FEMALE OPERATOR]
Excuse me, Ma'am!
There's no sign the
enemies are retreating.
Oh, no.
Say what?
You think there's more than one
Chimera attacking the city?
Yeah, that's the
most likely scenario.
There are way too
many smaller bugs
for there to be only one,
didn't I mention that earlier?
[ALL]
No, you didn't.
If what you say is true,
then we've got to find
that other Chimera.
As long as the
beast still lives,
the other beetles will
continue to attack Mistgun.
[KANATA]
Yup. That's what it looks like.
So, how do we find it?
[RICO]
Hm. Don't you worry.
It's time you all got a
glimpse of my true power.
[LECTY]
Uh, Rico?
[RICO] Though it pains
me to wear anything
that obscures my
gorgeous features,
my eyesight suffers whenever
I activate my Clairvoyance.
It's truly the greatest
tragedy of our time.
I dunno, you look
pretty good in glasses.
[gasps]
Oh? You think so?
I guess it's
no surprise, really.
[gasps]
[RICO] I've spotted
an abnormally high
concentration of hostiles.
That must be where
the Chimera is.
We've got to
get to Block 68!
[YURI gasps]
Chloe! Lloyd!
Shouldn't we fall back?
There are too many of them!
It wouldn't make a
difference, even if we did.
And at this point,
I'm not sure we have a safe
spot to retreat to anymore.
Reports say that there are
multiple chimeras
attacking the city now!
We've got to go
down there and help!
[CHLOE]
It's going to be okay.
Kanata won't let anything
happen to Mistgun.
[YURI]
What are you talking about?
That traitor's probably already
run off and abandoned us!
Yuri.
Please, you have to
believe in Kanata.
But, Chloe!
[CHLOE] Regardless of
what you think about him,
I know he'll pull
through for us.
He's a good guy at heart.
[LLOYD]
She's right.
There's nothing Kanata
loves more than playing
the knight in shining armor.
[gasps]
All right. Let's go.
[LECTY gasps]
Go where?
You three are gonna take
down that Chimera.
[ALL gasp]
Um, I don't wanna.
This is our first time
in the field for real.
And you're gonna send
us after a Chimera?
Misora has a point for once.
We're not prepared
for a task like this.
[MISORA gasps]
[KANATA] So you girls
just wanna give up
now that the fight
is getting hard.
[RICO gasps]
[gasps]
You've been training to protect
the people of this city.
Not so you can stand
around and watch it
get destroyed by some
nasty bugs, right?
The people here
are counting on you.
I believe you can do this.
You just have to have faith
in yourselves and each other.
Huh?
[grunts]
[MISORA]
Yeah. Right.
He might be a filthy pervert,
but he's also a
pretty good instructor.
If he thinks we can beat this
monster, we have to try.
Let's prove to this city
that we're not some
coward like he is.
So, what do you say?
Are you guys with me?
Yes! That's the reason I'm here.
I'm training to be a Sky Wizard
in order to protect others
and make them feel safe!
So, I'm with you, Misora!
Let's go get that Chimera
before it can hurt anyone!
[RICO] Hm. This could
be a good opportunity.
If Freon sees how powerful I am,
maybe she'll finally
realize I'm superior to her.
[MISORA]
Wait, what was that?
Um. Shouldn't we be
getting to the Chimera?
[KANATA]
It sounds like you're all in.
[MISORA]
Hm?
Now, let's kill the bastards!
This is our city.
It's time to take back our sky!
Let's go.
Okay!
Yeah!
[MALE OPERATOR]
It looks like most of the
Devil Beetles are
converging on Block 68.
Most of our forces are
fighting in other places.
What the hell's
happening out there?
[gasps]
[KANATA]
Remember the plan, everyone.
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
[KANATA]
Step one.
Lecty distracts the Archenars
by taking the fight to them.
I'm on it!
[LECTY] C'mon, there's no
reason to be nervous.
These are monsters, not people.
I can't hold back!
[LECTY grunting]
Wow, Lecty's doing great!
She' putting that
Eisenach Style to work.
I'm impressed.
[MISORA]
More beetles!
[KANATA]
Yep, just as I expected.
[MISORA]
Huh?
[gasps]
[KANATA]
Step Two.
Rico uses long-range
sniping to cover Misora.
[RICO gunts]
[gasps]
Now it's your turn!
[MISORA]
Yeah, I know the plan, okay!
[KANATA]
Step Three.
Misora uses her
superior flying skills
to move into firing range,
then she blows the enemy
away with a Strike Blaster.
One shot and it's all over.
[MISORA grunts]
Get out of my city!
[MISORA shouts]
Bye! Huh?
[MISORA]
There are too many of them!
[MISORA grunts]
[MISORA gasps]
[KANATA grunts]
Careful, don't
wear yourself out!
We can do this!
I'll keep you covered
from down here!
[MISORA grunts, gasps]
What ugly little monsters.
A goddess who brings so
much beauty to the world
shouldn't even have
to see such creatures!
[gasps]
[MISORA]
This is for Rico and Lecty.
For Mom. And her memory!
This ends now.
We are the Sky
Wizards of Mistgun!
Yeah!
[LECTY gasps]
[RICO gasps]
Wow! We really did it!
[KANATA]
Misora!
[MISORA]
Huh?
[ALL gasping]
[KANATA grunts]
[MISORA gasps]
[LECTY, RICO gasp]
[KANATA grunts]
Whoa! Kanata!
[BOTH gasp]
[RICO, LECTY gasp]
What is that monster?
I've never seen a
Chimera like that before.
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps, yells]
[RICO]
Lecty?
[RICO grunts]
[MISORA] Where are they?
Did they get crushed?
Hey, are you okay?
[KANATA]
I'm fine.
You know, that was
a pretty good shot.
It didn't stop
them from coming!
Normally, the fight would've
been over already.
But there's something
weird about this Chimera.
[MISORA]
Save your energy!
I saw you during our training.
For some reason your magic
reserves are easily drained.
[KANATA] Yeah, but there's
no way around it.
Such a strong enemy deserves
some personal attention
from the teacher.
[gasps]
[KANATA grunts]
Listen, I know what
I'm about to do
is going to set a really
bad example for you.
[MISORA]
Huh
Just promise me that you'll
never be this stupid!
[MISORA yelps]
[KANATA] You're gonna
want to stand back for this.
[MISORA]
What are you doing?
No way.
What the--?
How the heck is
he moving like that?
Nice try, but I'm way too
fast for such a lame attack.
[KANATA grunts]
[gasps]
[MISORA gasps]
That's not magic power.
It's like some
other force entirely.
That's it.
Time for you to say goodnight!
[KANATA] I can't keep going
like this for much longer.
The Chimera's gonna fire again!
You gotta get out of there!
[KANATA]
Didn't I tell you earlier?
[MISORA]
Huh?
This fight was over
the moment I stepped
on the battlefield.
The bastard never stood
a chance against me!
[gasps]
[MISORA gasps]
[MISORA]
You forgot to mention that.
[LECTY gasps]
The Chimera?
[RICO gasps]
Misora, was that you?
[MISORA gasps]
Kanata!
Is he okay?
Catch him!
[KANATA grunts]
[MISORA]
He's falling too fast!
[YURI]
What happened?
[LLOYD] Looks like he took
care of everything after all.
Wait, you're saying
the traitor saved us?
[CHLOE chuckles]
Isn't it obvious?
The man you love
protected our city.
[YURI gasps]
[CHLOE giggles]
[FEMALE OPERATOR] The Archenar
class Devil Beetles
are pulling out of
the city's airspace.
[MALE OPERATOR]
It appears to be a full retreat!
We're clear!
[FREON] The super-powered
Chimera was defeated.
But who did it?
[REAL panting]
[REAL] I have to make sure
Miss Yuri is all right!
[panting continues]
[REAL grunts]
Um. What is this?
[REAL gasps]
[MISORA] I refuse to
let you die on us now.
We're just starting
to get good at this!
Yeah, Please wake up, Kanata.
[KANATA]
I don't plan on dying just yet.
[ALL]
Huh?
[KANATA grunts]
How dare you run off like that!
You scared us!
I think that means
you scare too easy.
But. Shut up!
[KANATA]
Look at that.
[MISORA]
Huh?
[KANATA]
Our skies are clear.
[LECTY sighs]
[MISORA gasps]
[KANATA] You know what
that means, dontcha?
We're ready to go win a
few ranked matches now.
[MISORA]
You bet we are!
[SPECTATORS chatter]
Whoops, it looks like
I'm a little tardy.
[YURI]
Hello, Kanata.
Hey, what's up, Yuri?
I'm here to see
if your students
have actually
learned anything.
You'd better be
doing a good job.
[KANATA] Hmm. You seem to be
in a particularly pleasant mood.
Are you sure there's
nothing else going on?
[gasps] I don't know
what you're talking about.
And anyway, Kanata.
I thought all the E-Rank teams
were supposed to be helping
evacuees during the raid.
So how did you end
up hurting yourself?
I dunno.
Maybe I tripped and
fell while running away.
You know, you have always
been a terrible liar.
--[whistle chirps]
--[YURI gasps]
[KANATA]
Hey, that's my fireteam.
Don't be surprised
whenever we win.
My girls are about to
outrank the whole academy.
[YURI gasps]
[YURI grunts]
[whistle chirps]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[MISORA chuckles nervously]
[KANATA grunts]
[AMIE]
We demolished them!
Yeah, and we
weren't even trying.
They're a disgrace
to the Sky Wizards.
Well. We're losers.
I can't believe it.
This must have been
your fault, I was perfect.
[YURI]
Hmph. So, Instructor.
What were you just saying about
how good your fireteam is?
Well, you know.
Uh, maybe they could use a
little more training, after all.
[laughs]
Good. I accept your proposal.
[FREON]
Thank you.
[CHLOE]
So, what happened?
Did the supervisor
sign off on your idea?
Yes.
We can now accelerate the
Sky Wizard training program
and more thoroughly
evaluate our students. So...
It's time. For the
tournament to begin.
[MISORA]
Hey Rico, exactly how much
are you able to see
with your Clairvoyance?
[RICO] Hmph. Well, I can see
that the panties you've got on
under your uniform have
ruffles and bows all over them.
[MISORA]
What? Hey! Stop looking!
Close your eyes or something!
[RICO chuckles]
Just joking.
I can see for extreme
distances in every direction,
but not through solid objects.
[MISORA] So, you were just
guessing about my underwear?
[RICO] Yes, but who
knows what'll happen
as my skills improve.
[MISORA]
Seriously?
[RICO] Oh, our next episode
is "Mistgun Tournament."
[MISORA shouts] Keep your
prying eyes off of me!