[FREON] As the Sky
Wizards Division lead,
I'd expected Fireteam E601
to be beaten within seconds
of starting their first match.
I may have underestimated
that band of misfits.
Or, more likely, their
success was a fluke.
Surely, there's no way they'll
win their second match.
[LECTY, MISORA]
We won match two!
[ANNOUNCER A]
In a shocking upset,
Fireteam E601 is
advancing in the tournament!
[FREON] They'll definitely
lose the next one.
[MALE SKY WIZARD B screams]
[ALL laugh]
[LECTY]
Yay!
[ANNOUNCER A]
E601 is on fire!
With this win over
a C-Ranked team,
they'll now advance
to the semi-finals.
[FREON]
That was an accident.
They've just had a
series of lucky breaks!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Uh! This is truly unexpected!
E601 has beaten B936 and is now
moving on to the final match!
[FREON growling]
[CHRIS]
Uh?
[MISORA] We did it!
I can't believe we won!
My victory was always assured.
You may say that,
but you're crying too!
[RICO]
Uh! That's just a coincidence!
[KANATA]
Now, then...
[KANATA] Time for the
real battle to begin.
[NEWSIE A]
Extra! Extra!
Check out this special
tournament issue
of the Monthly Mistgun!
What's this headline?
Huh?
[COELA] If the Effed-Up
fireteam doesn't win.
[BEACH] Then they're
gonna be disbanded!
[AMIE]
Seriously?!
[CHLOE]
It's a clever move.
Now that Freon's made
their agreement public,
Kanata can't fight
if his team loses
and is dismissed.
Yeah, that's true.
But it also means Freon
has to hold up her end of
the bargain if they win.
[LECTY]
I always wished I was stronger
so I could protect
the people of Mistgun.
To make them feel safe
and have happy lives.
[LECTY] Even though training
was sometimes weird,
I really do think I'm becoming
a better Sky Wizard.
Slowly but surely I'm starting
to believe in myself.
And it's all thanks to Kanata.
[RICO]
When I first met him,
I thought he was
nothing but a pervert.
Now I know he's more than that.
He's a pervert and an
extraordinary teacher.
[MISORA]
I was always so frustrated
and disappointed with myself
for not being a better
fighter or leader.
[MISORA]
But thanks to Kanata,
I've come so close to
achieving my dream.
To make my mom proud
and become a powerful Sky
Wizard just like she was.
Let's do this!
[LECTY]
Hey, Misora!
[MISORA]
Lecty?
What are you doing
out here so late?
Well I was kinda starting to go
crazy being stuck in my room
and thinking
about the match.
[RICO] It's going to be
a big day for all of us.
Tomorrow the world
will see the full extent
of my divine powers and
they will bow in worship.
It's enough to make even
a goddess feel restless.
[MISORA]
Okay!
If we're gonna train, then
let's get this party started!
[LECTY]
Yeah!
[RICO]
Let's begin.
[KANATA] I was afraid they'd be
freaking out about tomorrow.
But they always do surprise me.
[LLOYD] So far I haven't
seen anyone suspicious.
There's no sign of
our serial attacker.
[CHLOE] Good to hear.
All clear on my side, too.
[CROWD cheering]
[MISORA, RICO, LECTY gasp]
This crowd is
completely insane.
And there's gonna be
a live broadcast, too?
[LECTY] Um, all of these
people looking at us
is making me feel a little
sick to my stomach.
Just keep your cool, Lecty.
They're all so far away that
they might as well be ants.
You're right. It's fine.
You guys. We made it.
[BOY STUDENT A]
I can't believe they'd let
that traitor coach a fireteam.
[BOY STUDENT B] How'd they
even make it to the finals?
[GIRL STUDENT A]
Duh, they obviously cheated.
[MISORA] I don't think
anyone's rooting for us.
[LECTY whimpers]
[RICO]
Well, they're just jealous
because my otherworldly beauty
is making them feel inadequate.
[CROWD cheers]
[ALL]
Huh?
[BOY STUDENT A]
Look, here they come!
[BOY STUDENT B] The team
that's gonna win this thing!
[GIRL STUDENT A]
They're so amazing!
You're right, we aren't
the favorite team.
It looks like all the banners
are for the A-Rankers.
We don't have a single
fan in the audience.
Wait! Is our name on
that one over there?
--[MISORA] Uh?!
--[RICO] Mm?
Don't disappoint us you bunch
of formerly pathetic losers!
Yeah! Cause we're the only
people rooting for you!
Make 'em taste that
Strike Blaster!
At least we've got
someone on our side.
I never dreamed that
we'd have fans!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Welcome to the final match
of the Mistgun Tournament,
where fireteam A227
will face off against E601...
Try not to look
so tense, Lecty.
[LECTY] But I can't
help it! Please stop...
[KANATA]
It's okay.
It might be smart
for you to leave now.
This is gonna get really
embarrassing for you
really fast.
Just remember our deal.
I wonder what kind of costume
I should have you wear
when you're on my fireteam.
[whistle blows]
All right, guys, are you ready?
I've got ya covered, Lily!
Here we go.
[LILY grunts]
Whoa! They're quick!
Nah, you three are
just really slow.
[LECTY whimpers]
Don't just stand there!
Evasive maneuvers!
[MISORA grunting]
[MISORA]
Come on, team.
Don't worry, this'll be quick.
I'm gonna be strong
for my friends!
I won't let the others down.
Not when they're counting on me!
[LECTY yells]
You've got some potential.
I've got your back!
Just give me an opening!
[LECTY gasps]
[LECTY screams]
You're done for!
[RICO] Keep your unworthy
hands off my friend!
You peasant!
Thanks, Rico!
Now let's show her
what we're made of!
You're not getting away...
[RICO]
Uh.
[CROWD cheers]
[BOY STUDENT A]
The redhead's not even fighting!
[BOY STUDENT B] Can you blame
her? They're totally outmatched.
It's kind of a shame.
The final seems like it's
gonna be pretty boring.
Quite true.
[CROWD cheering]
[CHLOE sighs]
I wanted to see the match
but I'm stuck out here.
[LLOYD] You know we
can hear you, Chloe.
[CHLOE laughs nervously]
Moving on.
Can you do me a favor and
check out the back gate?
Our contacts there haven't
checked in with me.
Sure thing! But Lloyd.
I don't think our attacker is
gonna show up at the tournament.
I mean, pretty much every
Sky Wizard in Mistgun
is in the audience.
Would you stop running away
like some scared
little kid and fight?!
[MISORA] I hate to admit
it, but she's amazing.
I don't think I could beat
her if we went head-to-head!
[MISORA grunts]
[LILY grunts]
Her flying is too erratic.
I can't predict her movements!
Your aim sucks! I thought
you said I was slow.
[LILY] Go ahead, keep making
jokes and trying to evade me.
You're fast now, but eventually
you're gonna tire yourself out.
You may think I'm
running scared,
but really you've
fallen into my trap.
[LILY]
Uh...? Uh!
[LILY gasping]
[MISORA]
Hmph. Now I've got you!
[LILY laughs]
[MISORA gasps]
Sorry, but our instructor
taught us well,
and warned us you'd try to
pull something like that.
[BOY STUDENT A]
What gives?
They're just flying around
and chasing each other.
[BOY STUDENT B]
Jeez, what a boring match.
[GIRL STUDENT A]
Let's see some fighting!
I don't get it. Why isn't
E601 kicking butt?
They seemed a lot
more coordinated
when they fought our team.
Come on! Show those
A-Rankers your power!
[YURI]
Look at them, Kanata.
We both know that my fireteam
is more powerful on
a fundamental level.
That said, even the weak
can overcome the strong.
But since we've fought together,
I know your tricks.
And I've trained my
team to expect them.
I knew you'd do this.
That you'd try to throw us
off guard and take the win.
It won't work.
When this is over, I'll
take the trophy home.
And I'll be happy to
finally be rid of you.
You almost have 'em!
Work together!
Finish off those losers!
[SASHA]
Ah!
[LECTY whimpers]
You heard her!
Let's wrap things up. 'Kay?
Victory's ours. Let's go!
In a few minutes,
this'll all be over.
I can't argue with that, Yuri.
But things might not go
as you've planned them.
Come on, Kanata,
this is getting sad.
I've seen through your schemes.
My team's got this locked down.
Oh yeah? I wouldn't be so sure.
[LECTY whimpers]
[YURI] You've instructed
your team to run around
and look scared so that
we'll underestimate them.
And when they think we least
expect it, they'll strike.
[MISORA grunts]
[MISORA]
This is it!
[LILY]
Uh... Uh.
Misora thinks she's
got Lily by surprise.
Too bad Lily sees
the attack coming.
My team is fully prepared
for this kind of tactic.
I won't let you fire!
[YURI] Lily can dodge
the Strike Blaster.
Then she'll close the distance
and defeat Misora easily.
That's some impressive
foresight.
However, you overlooked
one big detail.
[YURI]
Mm?
[LILY gasps]
That's... impossible!
She's not just aiming at Lily!
[LILY]
Greg! Sasha, watch out!
We're all in the
path of her blast!
Uh!
[MISORA yells]
[LILY gasps]
She didn't fire the
Strike Blaster!
It's a feint!
Seeing Misora's attacks
in the previous matches
caused Lily to overreact.
So now she's gonna
be off her game.
I can't believe you thought
you could trick me like that!
Lily, stay calm!
Now she thinks Misora's going
to run around some more.
Just the way she did earlier.
But riled up like this,
Lily can be caught off guard.
What? No way.
You had this planned out from
the beginning, didn't you?
Oh. Didn't I mention that?
Everything that's
happened in this match
has gone exactly as
I wanted it to.
The dynamics on the
field have changed.
Unfortunately for you, failing
to realize that you've gone
from the hunter to the hunted
is the surest way to defeat.
Misora's become a
fearsome predator.
And Lily is a beast
blinded by anger,
which makes her
the perfect prey.
I'm taking you down!
Yeah? Just try it!
Heh! What, are you gonna try
and flee the stadium now?
Everyone can see you're
making a fool of yourself!
[MISORA grunts]
Uh!
[LILY] Not again. Is this
just another fake out, or...
[MISORA]
Uh! Now you're mine!
Yes! Strike Blaster!
[LILY gasps]
[LILY, GREG, SASHA scream]
[LECTY gasping]
Well, that's quite surprising.
[FREON growling]
Incredible.
They went head-to-head with
Yuri's A-Ranked fireteam...
...and won the
whole tournament!
What the heck happened?
If it weren't for the
Sorcerer Field's magic
we would all be dead right now.
There's no doubt about
it. They bested us.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Um. It looks like A227 has lost.
So... The winners of the
Mistgun Tournament are--
Hey, what are you doing?
You can't come in here,
I'm on the air!
Wait, stop.
[ANNOUNCER A groan, screams]
[REAL laughs]
Yuri my beloved,
you look so beautiful even
when you're full of despair.
[YURI gasping]
[ANNOUNCEMENT A]
Warning!
Devil Beetles have been spotted
in the skies above Mistgun.
Alpha security protocols
are now in effect.
Regular students and
non-combatant citizens
must evacuate to a
nearby shelter...
--[FREON] What is this?
--[CHRIS] An air raid alert?
[ANNOUNCEMENT A]
...I repeat, not a drill.
[LLOYD]
A malfunction?
[CHLOE] No, someone managed to
break into the security office
and trigger the alarm!
[CROWD screaming]
Not good. They're clearing
out the stadium.
[REAL laughs] Oh. Finally,
my darling, I'm here.
[gasps] I recognize him.
Yuri. I have so much
love to give you.
And now I'm stronger than
you could possibly imagine.
Who is that guy?
Obviously someone
deeply disturbed.
[gasps]
[MISORA] He's got the same
kind of power signature
Kanata had during the raid.
Yuri. Yes!
After all this time,
I have come for you.
I didn't forget you, my love!
You're the only thing that's
been on my mind since we met!
[gasps]
All of this has been for you,
my dearest, every attack.
And now that I'm strong
enough to dominate you,
you have to accept me as
your lover, isn't that right?!
[YURI]
Huh.
Why do you look so sad?
Is it because of your fireteam
losing this silly tournament?
Don't worry, dear, I can help
you get over that pain!
Here, let me embrace you.
Just let me get my
hands on you, Yuri!
You're the hooded guy
I fought in the park.
That's right. Now move!
I won't let you come
between us again.
Yeah. Let's go!
[gasps]
[KANATA]
Run!
[REAL laughs]
Oh, no you don't!
Yuri! Come here!
Let me put my arms around you!
[KANATA grunting]
Get outta here now!
[YURI]
Uh! No way!
Don't argue!
[YURI growls]
If you want her you'll have
to go through me first!
[REAL]
Just you?
If that's all, then let's
get this over with now.
[REAL grunting]
[KANATA groaning]
[laughing]
You're not going anywhere!
[YURI panting, gasps]
Feel my love!
[REAL]
Weren't you listening earlier?
I've become stronger than
you. You must love me!
[YURI gasps]
[KANATA grunts]
Dammit.
What's with the
look of hesitation
in your eyes, my dear?
Aren't I the kind of man
you've always wanted?
We can finally be
together now!
The hell...?
[MISORA]
Crap, I actually hit him!
[LECTY whimpers]
That wasn't a warning shot.
A blast like that would've
killed a normal person!
I believe you've made
us his new targets.
[REAL growling]
[KANATA]
Wow, it's been a long time
since I've done one of these.
Uh... Anyway, next episode,
Misora, Lecty and Rico
are gonna put on a
big show for you.
They might even save Yuri and
the rest of Mistgun again.
[YURI]
They didn't save me!
I could've protected myself
without your idiot
students interfering.
[KANATA] I don't think you
should be calling them names.
[YURI]
Huh?
[KANATA]
After all, thanks to our bet,
you're one of my idiot students
now. Have some self-respect.
[YURI]
What? Oh, no!
[KANATA]
See you next time for
"Instructor of the
Sky Wizards Academy".