[CHLOE] Chloe here,
talking to Kanata about his,
uh, special fireteam.
Let's hear about Lecty's
"Eisenach Twin Swords"
[KANATA]
They're super powerful,
and her family's namesake.
[CHLOE]
Very interesting!
What can you tell us about
Misora's Magic Cannon Sword?
[KANATA] She can use it to
slash or shoot her enemies.
It's a hardcore,
multi-purpose wonder weapon.
[CHLOE]
Fascinating!
And what about Rico?
What can she do?
[KANATA]
Good question.
[FREON] How long to do
you plan on staying in bed?
At this rate you're
going to be tardy.
Again.
I don't know what
to do with you.
[yawns]
Time is a worry
for common mortals,
not a goddess like me.
How many times must I tell her?
I shouldn't have to abide by the
rules of her silly academy.
[chuckles]
[RICO humming]
[gasps]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[BOTH gasp]
Forget our normal table.
[BOY STUDENT B]
Yeah, I wouldn't want anyone
to think that we're
friends with a traitor.
I've gotta say,
you've impressed me, Kanata.
No one's said that
to me in a while.
Don't tell me you've actually
found someone who respects you.
What a joke.
After all, you're probably the
most hated person in Mystogan.
How does that feel, by the way?
It must be torture.
[KANATA] These are
the opponents my girls
are facing in their next match.
Fireteam E-571, huh?
They're fierce.
Everyone's expecting them to
shoot up the ranks in no time.
Hey, you can't
just ignore me!
Your fireteam is totally
screwed, you know.
Not only were they
crappy to begin with,
now they're being
taught by a traitor.
The whole school's laughing
about how pathetic they are.
Fine, let 'em laugh
all they want.
That way it'll be even sweeter
when my fireteam destroys them.
I hope you're not feeding
those lost causes this kinda BS.
They don't deserve
to be lied to.
Yeah, That would be cruel.
But, I really do
believe in them.
Maybe that's all they need.
[gasps]
Well. For their sakes,
I hope you actually know what
you're talking about for once.
Hey, just leave her to me.
I'll go make sure she's okay.
[KANATA] Regardless of what I
say, we're not winning anything
without the missing
piece of the puzzle.
[RICO scoffs] I didn't realize
you were eating for two.
Oh hey, how's it going, Rico?
[RICO] I'm late to school due
to a celestial disturbance.
[KANATA]
Of course you are.
[RICO]
It couldn't be helped.
One moment I was showering,
and the next,
an ethereal beauty
appeared before my eyes.
A being of
otherworldly radiance.
[KANATA]
Huh?
Did you see a ghost
or something?
[chuckles]
[RICO] Actually, it turned
out I was just looking
at my own reflection
in the bathroom mirror.
[KANATA] I'm legitimately
concerned for you.
It shouldn't surprise you.
There's no one in
the world as beautiful
as I am so it makes
sense I'd be infatuated.
[laughs]
I finally figured it out!
You're trolling me, right?
[laughing conitnues]
[CROWD laughs]
[GUY] What kind of loser
calls herself a goddess?
[GIRL A]
I guess she's cute. Kinda.
[GIRL B] Maybe. But she's
nothing compared to her sister.
[gasps]
Jerk.
[RICO]
Who are they?
[KANATA]
These are your next opponents,
and they're not going
to go easy on you.
If Misora and Lecty can learn
something from their lessons
we might actually have
a fighting chance.
But not without you.
Before you go on,
know that I have no intention
of training with you.
All right. I can't
force you to, after all.
I'm glad you finally
got the point.
The beautiful and
divine were not made
to sweat and toil
alongside mortals.
Hmph.
[LECTY whimpers]
No.
Please, I don't
think I can take it.
[MISORA] Just sit still.
It'll all be over soon.
[LECTY]
I'm really nervous! Yeah, okay.
But please, be gentle
with me, Misora.
[MISORA] I will.
All right here I come.
[whimpers]
I didn't realize
it'd be so cold!
[MISORA]
You're good.
Turn around.
It's your turn to do me, now.
I'm on it!
Hey. Have you noticed that
Kanata's training exercises
have gotten a lot
harder lately?
[MISORA gasps]
They've been tough.
But I can tell our work
is starting to pay off.
I can feel myself
getting stronger
and my skills are
improving each day.
You know what I think?
We might have a chance at
winning our next match!
I feel the same way, but Rico.
[BOTH sigh]
[knocking]
[BOTH]
Hm?
[KANATA] Knock, knock!
Cover up you two, I'm coming in.
[BOTH yelp]
You stay outta here,
you big creep!
[KANATA]
Don't flatter yourself.
You're too young for me.
I was just thinking that
since you girls have
been working so hard,
I'd treat you to some
ice cream as a reward.
If you're interested.
[LECTY]
Ice cream!
[MISORA] Sorry, but we've
got important lady business
to take care of right now!
[LECTY gasps]
If we're gonna win
this next match,
we've gotta talk to Rico and
get her back in the game.
[LECTY]
But ice cream.
For crying out loud,
I'll get you some
ice cream later.
[LECTY giggles]
[RICO]
So, what do you want?
My time is far too precious.
It shouldn't be
wasted by plebeians.
Fine, then I'll get
straight to the point.
Rico, we want you to begin
training with Kanata.
Aren't you fed up with
always being called a loser?
We've got to start
winning matches!
In order for that to happen,
we need to work together
as a real fireteam.
[LECTY sighs]
[RICO] Lecty gave me
this same pitch earlier,
but I'm afraid the
answer is still "no."
Don't think this has
anything to do with you.
As a supreme being,
I simply have nothing
to gain from training.
But I don't think
that's true, Rico!
Kanata's helped us, and I bet he
can teach you something new too.
[MISORA] I honestly hate to
admit it, but Kanata may be
the best thing that's ever
happened to our fireteam.
[LECTY]
But,
now that I've seen the effect
the training's had on me,
I think he might know
what he's doing!
All right. I can't
force you to after all.
[grunts]
You only think he's improving
you because you're mortals.
How do I get it through
your heads that no human
will ever be able to
teach me anything?
[LECTY sighs]
Seriously?!
If that's all you
wanted to ask of me,
I'll be on my way.
[MISORA]
Fine, then don't train.
I don't care.
But at least be there standing
by us during the next fight!
I have no interest in
humiliating myself
by joining a match
we're certain to lose.
[grunts]
But we're a team.
[MISORA]
I'm begging you.
[RICO, LECTY gasp]
[LECTY]
Misora!
[MISORA]
Please, join us, Rico.
Huh? Wait, What are you doing?
[MISORA]
We need your help!
What? Hey!
Why were you on your knees?
On second thought, never mind.
Well, the news is pretty grim.
Last night a D-Rank squad was
attacked, and they were downed.
No survivors.
[CHLOE]
It must have been a Chimera.
That's right.
The Chimeras are
powerful beasts
who command the
smaller Devil Beetles.
We can't let one of them
anywhere near Mystogan.
Destroy it.
Don't you worry, Freon.
The Special-Duty
Fireteam's on it.
In fact.
I'll kill it myself.
[FREON] Before you fly out,
give me a report
on what progress Kanata Age
is making with his fireteam.
I believe they've got a ranked
match coming up soon,
don't they?
[CHLOE giggles]
[FREON]
What's so funny?
Oh, nothing. Maybe I'm mistaken.
But weren't you asking me
about E601 just yesterday?
That's a coincidence.
[MISORA whines]
So this is the
important business
you had to take care of?
I figured something was up when
you turned down ice cream.
You say that like I'm
some kinda greedy pig!
We weren't trying to go behind
your back or anything!
We just really want to win!
[RICO]
Hmph.
Rico's right,
fighting when you know
you can't win is a
pretty dumb thing to do.
[MISORA, LECTY gasp]
I'm infallible.
Of course I was correct when--
On the other hand.
Abandoning your
friends and refusing
to even try to win
is definitely lamer.
[gasps]
You don't know what
you're talking about.
[gasps]
Take your hand offa me!
I've got a present for you.
I'm gonna hand you
the key to victory.
Are you prepared
to take it, Misora?
[BOTH gasp]
You're giving me a key?
[RICO panting]
[RICO]
Hold on!
Wait for me!
--[CROWD cheers]
--[RICO] Sister!
[panting]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[RICO] It's not my
fault I'm late again.
I had a bad dream.
Nightmares should be legitimate
excuses for tardies.
[yawns]
[YURI grunts]
[REAL]
Miss Yuri...
How is it possible that you,
the one true beauty of this
academy, are friends with him?
The traitor who's
brought shame to us all.
[RICO]
What do we have here?
Another stalker?
I'm not surprised.
My irresistible beauty is
no doubt at fault yet again.
But that's not.
[RICO]
Go on, take a photo.
[RICO gasps]
[KANATA]
Listen up.
I'm only gonna show
you this move once,
so pay close attention
to what I'm doing.
[KANATA grunts]
That's the Gladius!
The Sword of Destruction!
That was the weapon you used
back when they
called you "Chronos".
[KANATA grunts]
[MISORA grunts]
That's Strike Blaster for
the Magic Cannon Sword.
It's your key to
winning this thing.
[gasps]
You think I'm ready to do
such a powerful move?
Don't release any
excess magic.
Focus it in your body.
Channel it through the sword.
Um. Like this?
Honestly, this is gonna
be really difficult.
Both your sword and shooting
skills are really subpar.
Well, maybe I should try
something easier to start?
We don't have time to go all
the way back to the basics.
So, let's just see
what you can do.
You really think this
is the key to victory?
You've got a ridiculously high
capacity for magic power.
If you can focus all
of it into one shot...
...you can defeat
the other fireteam.
[MISORA gasps]
There you go! Now, fire!
[MISORA]
Strike... Blaster!
Whoa! Did you see that?
Huh?
[gasps]
Geez, the kickback on this
attack is really terrible.
Why didn't you warn me
that it'd be so draining?
[panting]
[MISORA]
He's still recovering.
I'm adding this move
to your training.
Three shots every day.
That's probably the most
you'll be able to handle.
Understood?
[MISORA]
He used to be an elite,
but he's showing signs of
severe magical exhaustion
after a single attack.
[gasps]
You can use that move
to cut open a path.
That way the rest of your team
will be able to move forward.
Got it.
Hey, my head's not here for you
to rest your grubby hand on!
[KANATA] I know,  but my arm's
so comfortable like this.
[MISORA]
All right, that does it.
I know who the target is
for my next Strike Blaster.
[RICO] If Misora can tap into
her magical power reserves,
she can definitely turn the
tide of battle in our favor.
Still...
It looks like they're
flirting up there.
[LECTY yells]
[KANATA, LECTY grunting]
What's wrong, Lecty?
It doesn't seem like you're
giving a hundred percent today.
[LECTY gasps]
Well.
[KANATA]
Huh?
[LECTY] Don't I get a
special move like Misora?
Maybe a magic
attack or something?
[KANATA]
No.
Oh... That's fine, I don't care.
You know the Eisenach
Style Magic Twin Sword Art.
It was created by your ancestor
and Sword God, Albert Eisenach.
The Art has been honed
by his descendants.
This fighting style
is your birthright,
but it can only be mastered
by those with confidence.
Remember what you
learned in training?
[LECTY]
Huh?
Okay, show me
your confidence!
Here I come!
[yells]
[LECTY grunts]
[KANATA grunts]
[LECTY yells]
[KANATA yells]
[LECTY gasps]
[KANATA, LECTY grunting]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Aw, I still wasn't able to
land a single hit on you.
Yeah, but you have made
some big improvements.
Before you couldn't even look
your opponent in the eye.
I guess I'm a little
overwhelmed when I fight.
But I do feel less nervous than
I did before our training.
You know.
You're doin' great, kid.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
[RICO] The traitor may
be a good instructor,
but does he have to get
so handsy with the girls?
Regardless, Misora and
Lecty have both
improved dramatically
under his guidance.
If I were to study under him.
Would I finally be a
match for my sister?
Foolish. I'll never be like her.
[RICO gasps]
Where did he disappear to?
So this is how you've been
spending all your free time.
[RICO] Wait, how did
you know I was here?
You were just in the air!
Something's different.
The glasses.
[gasps] Oh. Ignore them.
I don't even need them.
Interesting.
Do those glasses
help you to activate
your powers
of Clairvoyance?
Yes. They help bring
everything into clearer focus.
Hey!
Hold on a sec, how do you
know about my abilities?
You have the highest-ranking
detection-type skill.
Clairvoyance.
Wow. Your powers
must be quite strong
if you were watching
us from so far away.
Kanata.
The move you taught Misora.
Is it supposed to be
the "key to victory"
that you offered to her before?
Yup.
[RICO]
I understand that it's powerful,
and if Misora can
master that ability,
she'll be a formidable
opponent on the battlefield.
But that doesn't matter.
It's not going to help you
win the upcoming match.
Yeah?
You see, I noticed
a flaw in your plan.
That special move takes
a long time to charge up,
which means Misora is
wide open for an attack.
To use Strike Blaster,
you'd need a skilled Vanguard
and a Rear Guard to
protect Misora while--
That's correct.
Your analysis of the
plan is totally right.
And it's what makes
you our secret weapon.
[gasps]
Strategizing. Analyzing.
Battlefield awareness and
on-the-spot decision making.
Those calculating
skills are all things
you've mastered on your own.
They're more valuable to
us than your Clairvoyance.
Hold it right there.
What makes you so
sure I'll help out?
Do you really think you can
command my divine powers?
Besides, what you told Misora.
She's supposed to hold the
power to win this, isn't she?
Oh, um. Did I not mention that?
There are actually
multiple keys to victory.
No, you didn't!
You, Misora, and Lecty
are my three keys.
The only way you'll
overcome your opponents
is working together.
Seriously?
You have never showed any
interest in me or my abilities.
You didn't even make
me do any training!
Honestly?
You've got the wrong idea.
You were far too advanced.
The others had to
rise to your level.
[RICO]
What?
I think your abilities really
do make you a kind of goddess.
At least from the little
I've seen, anyway.
Oh?
Well, of course, that's obvious.
I guess.
Uh, Kanata?
[KANATA] Please, Rico.
I need you. I want you.
Whoa, what do you
think you're doing?
Are you completely
out of your mind?
[KANATA] You know. I could
help you hone your skills
and become an unstoppable force.
The thing is, you have to have
the desire to succeed
for that to work.
[RICO]
The desire?
[KANATA] Do you really
want to be called a loser
for the rest of your life?
Or do you want
to show this world
what you can do?
The choice is yours.
I can't force you.
[gasps]
What would she do?
I can't believe Rico
didn't even show up
in the fireteam room.
I'm starting to get
worried that she might
skip out on our match.
[RICO]
You're both terribly late.
[BOTH gasp]
[RICO]
I finally agree to complete
these laborious
training exercises.
And you dare to keep
this goddess waiting?
Rico, I knew you
wouldn't abandon us!
Hey, we're the ones who've
been waiting, you idiot!
The puzzle is finally complete.
It's about damn time.
[STUDENTS chatter]
Oh, look it's that
Effed-Up team!
We won't even have
to break a sweat!
I can't wait for
the victory party.
Those girls are so annoying!
Looking down on
others is a sure sign
that they're low-caliber
human beings.
You've heard the
saying about the pot
calling the kettle black, right?
Uh, I'm starting to get kinda
nervous about this match.
Come on girls, don't sweat it.
What, didn't I tell ya before?
Proving these jerks wrong
is what it's all about.
[MISORA]
Failed to mention it.
No, you did not.
Nope, you didn't.
[ALL giggle]
[MISORA]
We can do this!
Go Team!
All right.
[alarm buzzes]
Hey, is that an alarm?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Air Raid Alert!
Devil Beetles are
approaching Mystogan!
All fireteams
ranked "D" and above
report to your
assigned stations!
Remaining citizens take
shelter immediately.
This is not a drill.
[KANATA] Couldn't this
have happened after we'd
already won the match?
Damned beetles.
[YURI] Chloe, our enemies
are attacking the city!
[CHLOE] Look, those are
Archenar class drones,
the smallest Devil
Beetles we know of.
They attack in swarms,
so it's easy to be
overcome by their numbers.
Then there's the Procyon class
which is one step bigger.
[YURI]
That's great info at all,
but maybe we should
get out there and
start fighting before
they destroy everything!
[CHLOE]
You're right! Sorry!
Next time: "The Skies, Taken."
Be sure to watch as I take out
the enemy and save the
Sky Wizards of Mystogan!
[YURI] That's it, no more
episode previews for you!
[CHLOE]
Aw...