[LECTY]
Oh, uh, hello!
This is Lecty Eisenach and...
I guess I should
tell you that, um,
my Fireteam got a new
instructor. And also...
Oh my gosh, I'm out
of time already?!
But I didn't even mention the
fact that he's a total pervert!
[KANATA]
I think they've caught on.
[KANATA] Today we start your
individual training regimens.
I want to warn you up front:
these aren't gonna
be easy assignments.
You've all got a lot of work
to do if you want to improve.
[RICO]
Heh. Sorry to disappoint you,
but I'll be sitting
this one out.
I don't train.
Uh?
[LECTY whimpers]
You kids have fun,
I'll see you later.
Hey, You can't just
walk out of class, Rico!
[KANATA] Well, we can't
force her to stay.
[MISORA]
Why not?!
Ignore her.
The real question is will
you be able to complete
your own special training?
I'm ready for any challenge!
Just tell us what to do!
That's exactly what
I wanted to hear.
[LECTY]
Um, are you still there Kanata?
I put on the costume
you picked out for me.
[LECTY]
Ah! Stop!
Don't stare at me with that
dirty look in your eyes!
Whoa, Lecty. You look amazing.
Thanks, but I don't
feel comfortable
showing this much skin.
Plus, our fireteam doesn't
have a big budget.
I don't think we should be
wasting money on this.
[KANATA] Ah. Let your instructor
worry about the finances.
This is an important
part of your training.
If you say so...
[KANATA]
Here. Catch.
[yelps]
[KANATA] Your mission is
to hand out all the fliers
in the bag while
wearing that outfit.
[LECTY]
What?!
[KANATA]
Hm? I thought I told you that.
Um, no, you definitely
did not tell me!
Where should we
go for lunch today?
Oh, I dunno, what
do you feel like?
[LECTY]
Um, hi...
[LECTY whimpers]
Uh. Excuse me.
What did you say?
--[LECTY] Um. Well, I...
--Do we know her?
[GIRL STUDENT A]
I don't think so.
She looks kinda familiar.
[GIRL STUDENT B] If by familiar,
you mean super weird.
I think she was crying.
[GIRL STUDENT A]
Let's go.
What should we do now?
I'm thirsty.
That's because of all
the short skirts out.
[BOYS laugh]
It's a maid outfit.
I must be dreaming.
Man, she's got a big ol' bow!
[LECTY gasping]
[BOYS chattering]
What'd she just drop?
Oh... Would... Would
you please take one?
What is it for?
[LECTY] Please, just
take the fliers and go!
[ALL]
Huh?
[BOY STUDENT B] Uh! We can get
some free food with these!
[BOY STUDENT A]
Whoa, this hottie just made me
the happiest boy in Mystogan!
Thanks a lot. See you around.
I did it. That was easy!
[KANATA] Your task is
to find Rico's weakness.
Huh?!
Everyone's got a dirty little
secret or two that can be used
against them by their enemies.
Rico acts like she doesn't
care about anything,
but I bet you can figure out
what makes the girl tick.
[MISORA]
You've got to be kidding!
Rico might not be my favorite,
but I'm not gonna be
--a total creep and--
--Shh!
--[MISORA muffled shouting]
--[RICO humming]
[KANATA] Your target
almost identified you.
[MISORA]
Kanata, you're groping me!
[KANATA]
Hm?
Sorry, didn't realize
I was touching you.
Uh?! Ah! 'Scuse me?!
What are you insinuating?!
That my boobs are so small
you didn't even notice
you were touching them?
Well?! Is that it?!
Rico's getting away.
Better go after her.
[gasps, growls]
Why are you following me around?
[MISORA]
How'd you notice me?!
I was being super sneaky
and moved like a
ninja the whole time!
[RICO]
Ahem.
Don't tell me you've
fallen under the spell
of my divine beauty.
[MISORA]
Um, actually, I was, uh--
[RICO]
Oh, spare me your life story.
Commoners do the strangest
things when they're bored.
[MISORA] Uh, yeah, you're
right, it was totally boredom!
Of course.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
I'll be spending the rest of
the day shopping till I drop.
[MISORA]
Oh, well if that's the case.
Maybe I could go
shopping with you
as some kind of team
bonding thing?
Hey, what did you
do that for, Rico?!
To make sure you
weren't an imposter
or some creep using
an illusion spell.
Since when are you interested in
what I do outside of school?
Uh...
[RICO sighs] Whatever,
mortal. You can come along.
This'll be a cinch. [laughs]
[slurping]
[KANATA]
Huh?
[KANATA] Whoa. You passed
them all out already?
Yeah! I'm finished!
At first I was super
nervous, but, you know,
the more fliers I passed out,
the easier it was
to talk to people.
[KANATA] All right, then it's
time for your next task.
Huh?
[KANATA] This place is in dire
need of some part-time help.
[gasping]
Make me proud.
Wait, I... There's no way
I can work at a busy café!
I'm ready to order!
This menu's got me hungry.
[CUSTOMER B] Can you
get me some more water?
[CUSTOMER C]
What are the specials?
[CHEF] Hey, maid girl. Table
three's waiting on this dish!
[LECTY whimpering]
[CUSTOMERS shouting]
Wait! Don't go!
Come back, Kanata!
Based on what we've
encountered in the field,
it looks like the Archenar
class of Devil Beetles
makes up the majority of
the enemy's population.
[YURI gasps]
[REAL]
Uh!
[YURI]
Oh, no! I'm so sorry!
Uh! Not good.
Here, just one sec.
I can take care of this.
[REAL gasps]
Uh. I'm sorry. I may
have stained your pants.
[YURI]
I can't get it off.
I could always pay to have them
cleaned, or buy you a new pair?
[REAL] Huh? Oh, no, please
don't worry about it, miss.
[YURI]
Uh...
Hey, Yuri!
[YURI gasps]
[REAL] Really, I'm fine.
It was my fault, too.
Go ahead. Your
friends are waiting.
[YURI] Thank you very much.
Again, I'm so sorry!
Yuri, is it?
Oh.
[CLERK] Can I get anything
else for you today?
No, that's all.
Okay!
You read philosophy books?!
How are you not bored to tears
every time you open one up?
It's a shame you can't see
the beauty in pursuing
truth and knowledge.
Maybe one day you
won't be so childish.
Yeah, I'm the childish one...
[RICO] Come along. There's
still more shopping to do.
[gasps] But we've hit
almost every store!
[gasps]
Aw! They're so cute!
I wanna take 'em all home!
Whoa, I didn't peg
you as the kind of girl
who geeks out over cute things.
Uh! Uh, I'm not. I'll take
those bags from you, now!
I just remembered that I have
somewhere else I need to be.
Time is precious, you know.
We have to make the most
of it before it runs out.
[exhales] I wonder if
liking stuffed animals
can be considered a weakness?
[LECTY]
Um. I'm sorry.
Could you please, uh,
repeat your order?
[CUSTOMER D]
Huh? What'd you say?
You, uh, said
you want, uh...
Oh, I think we both
know what I want.
[BOYS laugh]
[CUSTOMER D] How much would
you say to get her on the menu?
--[BOYS chatting, laughing]
--[LECTY whimpers]
[LLOYD] She's one of the girls
from Kanata's fire team.
I'm not cut out for this
kinda stuff. I'm just not.
[MISORA]
Hey, Lecty?
[LECTY gasps, whimpers]
What are you doing
sitting out here?
[whimpering]
[MISORA]
Uh? What's wrong?
[LECTY]
Misora, help me!
--[MISORA yelps]
--[LECTY cries]
[MISORA]
Are you feeling better now?
[LECTY]
I think so.
[MISORA] How is this supposed
to make you a better Sky Wizard?
You mean you didn't have
to wear anything weird
for your special training?
Uh? Well, no, but it was
strange in a different way.
[laughs]
[LECTY]
Oh, I see.
If there's anything I
can do to help you out
with this, don't hesitate
to let me know, okay?
D'ya really mean it?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MISORA] This isn't exactly
what I had in mind.
[LECTY]
We can switch,
but these are the only two
costumes Kanata bought.
Ugh! This is why that perv
shouldn't be in
charge of our money!
Excuse me, could you
take our order now?
Oh! Coming!
[LECTY gasps]
[MISORA]
Welcome to the café!
I think I'm just gonna
start out with an iced tea.
One iced tea coming up!
What do you want?
I'll take the iced
coffee, please.
[MISORA] And one
iced coffee. Sure thing!
[STUDENTS laughing]
[LECTY whimpering]
[LLOYD] Excuse me. Could I get
a little more water over here?
Yes! Of course!
[LLOYD] It can be tough
talking to people, huh?
[gasps]
[LECTY]
Oh, I'm so sorry about that!
The things that
you're afraid of,
they can hold you back,
but you can overcome them.
Uh!
[LLOYD]
Try not to worry so much.
And trust your instructor.
My... instructor?
Just look at your friend.
Maybe you can find some of
her confidence in yourself.
[LECTY]
Uh...
[MISORA] Okay, so that's an
iced tea and hot dog combo.
Can I have the bunny, too?
Sorry, we don't serve rabbit.
[STUDENTS laugh]
[MISORA] Two orders of
curry, comin' in hot!
I've got waters all around!
[CUSTOMER J]
Hey, little cotton tail!
[MISORA] One sec!
I'll be right with you!
[CHEF]
Take this to table seven.
[MISORA]
Not a problem!
Here you go, boys! I hope
you enjoy your meal.
Oh, yeah. Can I get
a coffee, please?
Of course! I'll be
back in a jiff!
[LECTY] Wow. She's working
so hard to help me.
You're right, Mister, thanks for
the pep talk! I think I'll...
[CUSTOMER AA] Excuse me, Miss?
Could I get a refill over here?
[LECTY]
Uh? Oh, well, I, um... Uh.
C'mon, you can do this, Lecty.
Just be confident like Misora.
Okay! Coming! [laughs]
The academy's head supervisor
is coming tomorrow.
Oh. Hello, ma'am.
Nice to see you.
What's this crowd doing here?
[LECTY]
Uh. Welcome to the café!
Um. Have you had enough time
to look over today's specials?
Okay, here's your
hot lunch combo!
[CUSTOMER L]
Excuse me, Miss?
I'm on my way!
--[MISORA laughs]
--[CUSTOMER H sighs]
[CUSTOMER M] I'd like the
pasta and the pudding.
You got it! That'll
be out super-fast!
I've got one iced tea
and one iced coffee.
[CUSTOMER M]
Can I get some service here?
Uh! Yeah, I'll be with
you in one second!
I'm just gonna leave these
dishes up here, okay?
And I need one more lunch combo.
Comin' right up!
[LECTY laughs]
Here's your spaghetti
special and an iced coffee.
All right, I've got
a beef stroganoff!
Hot and ready for
table number eight!
What's up with you, Lecty?
You're so into this, now.
I've got you to thank for that.
What'd I do?
Well, whatever it is, keep
up the good work, okay?
[LECTY]
I will!
Hey, isn't that the maid-girl
who was passing out
fliers earlier?
[FREON]
Interesting.
I wonder what else that traitor
has hidden up his sleeve.
[MISORA] What kind of messed-up
lesson was that supposed to be?
Come on, Lecty.
Tell him about how
uncomfortable that made you.
[LECTY]
Mm... Well, I don't...
Kanata.
Did you know that I have a
problem talking to strangers?
Like, social anxiety.
Listen up, Lecty. You've
got a long road ahead.
Training in the art of the
Magic Twin Sword is difficult.
Especially if you plan on
mastering the Eisenach style.
[gasps] But my family's
known for it.
[MISORA gasps]
[LECTY sighs]
[KANATA] Only those
who've devoted themselves
to their craft and have
proven themselves
in battle can live up
to the Eisenach name.
When we played tag yesterday.
I could tell that you had
skills, but you didn't have
the self-confidence to
put up a real fight.
You couldn't even
look me in the eyes.
If you wanna become a
successful Sky Wizard,
you're gonna have to
overcome that kind of doubt.
[LECTY]
Uh... Well, I...
I've never been able
to look someone
I didn't know in the eyes,
or do things that put me at
the center of attention.
I just get so nervous that
I'll do something stupid
and embarrass myself
or my teammates.
[MISORA]
Uh!
[LECTY] I hate myself
for feeling that way,
but I can't help it.
And thinking about it just
makes everything worse.
That's why I'm here.
To teach you that it's perfectly
normal to feel anxious.
Now you know what you need to
do. Learn to trust yourself.
You have to realize that
all of us make mistakes.
The trick is to learn from them.
[gasps] Got it!
You know, you make a
pretty good waitress.
It tickles whenever
you pet me, Misora.
By the way, thank
you for helping me.
[MISORA] Huh? All I
did was run food.
You inspired me to be like
you and try my hardest.
Even though I was scared
that I'd mess up.
Oh, yeah. Misora. How'd
your special training go?
[gasps] To be honest,
I totally bombed.
I was with her for hours
but didn't find a weakness.
It was kind of
surprising, though.
I found out that she reads
books about philosophy.
And that she likes
cute things, too.
[KANATA]
Good, you made progress.
[gasps]
[LITTLE BOY A]
Thank you.
[MISORA] Hey, weren't you
listening to a word I said?!
I totally blew my
secret mission!
[BOTH]
Huh?!
Here's your reward for
working so hard today.
You earned it.
[LECTY gasps]
Ice cream's my favorite!
[MISORA]
Is this a trick?!
Wow, It's really good!
Hey, wait a minute!
Before today, I hardly
knew anything about Rico,
much less her weaknesses.
And I didn't know Lecty freaked
out about crowds and strangers.
I suck. I'm a total failure
as a team leader.
But now you know what areas
you need to improve upon.
I'd call that success.
[gasps]
[KANATA] Lecty, I expect
you to keep training
as hard as you did today.
Yes! Definitely!
And I'll do my job by
continuing to stalk Rico.
[KANATA]
Huh?
Or not...?
[KANATA] The point of your
training today was to discover
what your own weaknesses
were, not Rico's.
Now that you know your
shortcomings as a leader,
we can focus on fixing them.
[gasps, growling]
Didn't I explain that?
[MISORA] Uh! No, you
most certainly did not!
[LECTY gasping]
[MISORA cries]
You know, Chloe.
You can't just float in here
whenever you want.
This is the guy's
dorm, after all.
Come on, Kanata.
You know this reminds you
of the good old days.
Huh? Is that the girl who was
dressed in the bunny suit?
[KANATA]
Yeah, her magic power reserves
are higher than those
of most A-Rankers,
but her potential is
totally wasted because
she has no talent with a sword.
Well. You're the master
instructor now,
so how are you gonna whip
this wizard into shape?
[KANATA]
Mm...
[MISORA]
What did you just say to me?
[KANATA] You're switching from
vanguard Magic Cannon Sword
to middle guard Magic Cannon.
Your magic power reserves and
flying abilities are impressive,
but they're going to waste.
This is the best way to
make use of your talents
and allow you to
reach your full potential.
In the end, this change
will make both you
and our fireteam much stronger.
[MISORA]
There's no way I can do that!
I don't care if you
think it's best for me.
I am not switching
to another weapon!
[KANATA]
Stop being such a selfish brat.
The Magic Cannon Sword
is too unbalanced
and difficult for a beginner.
Not to mention it's obsolete
as a weapon against the--
I am not being selfish!
I'll train harder if I have to.
But I'm telling you right now
that I'm sticking with my sword!
I understand that you might not
be happy about my decision.
But at this point, no
amount of extra training
is going to help you improve.
You know, I feel so stupid.
What are you getting at?
For one second
there I was happy!
I thought you might actually
be a decent instructor!
You... You think
you're so smart,
but you don't know the
first thing about me!
I'm outta of here!
[LECTY]
Misora, wait!
[LECTY] Oh, uh, hello, this
is Lecty the maid again!
I'm in charge of this part
of the show today so. Uh.
Um... Oh! This is Freon Flamel.
She's the leader of the
Sky Wizards division.
She's super important here,
and never looks like
she's having any fun.
Also, I don't think she
likes Kanata very much.
Wait, now that I think about it,
isn't her last name
the same as...
[RICO] More importantly,
the next episode is
"The Unforgettable Past."
I'll be gracing you with my
divine presence once again.
[LECTY]
Hey, Rico, that was my line!