[RICO] Long ago, the human
race was forced to abandon
the surface of the Earth.
All the land they once
occupied was taken over
by monstrous creatures
known as Devil Beetles.
The humans had
no choice but to move
to giant cities floating
in the atmosphere.
Our epic saga takes
place on Mystogan,
a massive floating academy.
It stars the fiercest,
most beautiful of all
who fight the Devil Beetles.
The exquisite goddess incarnate,
otherwise known as, Rico Flamel.
[MISORA]
Why're you lying to them?!
Hey! Did you hear me?!
[MISORA] I can't believe we're
stuck with a perv for a teacher.
What makes you think
you're even qualified?
[KANATA] The fact that they gave
me the job was my first clue.
All right ladies,
what dya say we get to it?
[MISORA] Get to what?
What're you talking about?
I bet you didn't even
look at the data on us.
The only reason you're here
is because you want us
to do dirty things with you.
[KANATA]
Oh, shut up.
[gasps]
[KANATA] I did my research,
Strawberry Jam.
Your name's Misora Whitale.
Sky Wizards prep,
second year. Age 14.
I looked over your report card
and you're currently
making Ds in all
of your classes.
Except for practical training
where you're making an E.
You're doing so poorly,
the reviewer recommends
you voluntarily drop out.
Well, that's just one opinion.
One's true abilities
can't be measured on paper!
Right...
You know I'm right!
Don't try to act like you don't!
Right...
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[sighs]
[MISORA]
C'mon, you guys!
Don't just sit there
looking at me like that!
Back me up!
[whines] You're no help!
Thanks for nothin'!
[scoffs] I've always
doubted her prowess.
It's nice to know
I'm correct yet again.
Oh, I suppose I should
introduce myself, I'm--
Rico Flamel.
Also a Sky Wizards
prep second year.
Your classroom grades aren't
bad, you're making all As.
Well, A minus for consistently
failing to turn in
your homework assignments.
Wait a second...
So what's with your
practical exam score?
I thought E was
the lowest grade.
How'd you score an F minus?
[RICO]
Hmph. Oh, you know.
I was having a bad hair day,
so I decided to stay home.
Ah... Well, whatever you say.
And, last but not least...
Uh, yeah, that's me!
[KANATA]
Lecty Eisenach.
Yet another Sky Wizards
prep, second year.
Your grades are awful
just like Misora's.
Your practical exams
are inconsistent.
You win and lose against the
same opponents
with wildly varying
scores in each match.
Yeah. I, um...
Uh, I know...
I-- Sorry!
[wails]
Okay, then.
Now that we've got the
introductions out of the way.
Let's get--
[MISORA]
Stop right there!
I cannot stand to hear
another word about this.
I won't be taught by a traitor!
Um... 'Scuse me?
I know why we're
calling him a pervert,
but what makes him a traitor?
From what I heard,
about six months ago,
he fought some Devil Beetles.
He managed to come back alive,
but he's been a
coward ever since.
He's useless.
He avoids special missions
and seems to do nothing
but slack off.
[CROWD cheering]
[RICO] I heard that he skipped
out on a crucial match.
One that would have gotten
his team into the S rank.
[MISORA] All he ever does is
disappoint the people
who rely on him.
And that is why...
...he's called a traitor!
[gasps]
[MISORA] We can't allow
such an irresponsible jerk
to be our instructor!
Go complain to the head
of the Sky Wizards division.
[KANATA]
Someone's gotta teach ya.
Why not me?
I mean, you haven't won
a single ranked match.
Are you embarrassed?
[MISORA growls]
What do you think?
Of course I'm embarrassed!
It's humiliating.
All I've ever wanted is to be a
full-fledged Sky Wizard.
If that doesn't happen,
then I'm wasting my time.
[RICO] Yes, Misora is
perpetually embarrassed.
But my skills are
more than adequate.
From a very young age, I've been
lauded as goddess incarnate.
How could you think
I don't have what it takes?
Um... Yeah!
I know I can do this!
And I'm willing to train
as hard as you need me to!
Do you know what
they used to call me?
Hah. Back in the day...
...I was given the name
Black Swordmaster Chronos.
Yeah, we've all heard.
What's it matter anyway?
[KANATA]
Well, that swordmaster's
gonna be instructing you.
If you do a good job, I think
you could be as strong as me.
Maybe.
Or even stronger, if you're
as good as you think you are.
[GIRLS gasps]
Let me whip you into shape.
With my help, you could defeat
the top-ranked fire teams.
And you could help us fight
against the Devil Beetles.
Imagine how that would feel.
[gulps]
[grunts]
[giggles]
[yells]
[GIRLS sigh]
What d'ya say?
Well, since we don't have
any choice in the matter...
I guess we'll have
to put up with you
until we can reach that goal.
[RICO]
I object to this nonsense.
[MISORA, LECTY gasp]
That's fine for
"Misora the Ordinary".
However, as you know,
I'm a goddess.
Why should I sweat and toil
as if I were a lowly
human like them?
Seriously, Rico!
That ugly, superior attitude
is exactly why
you're not seeing
any improvement!
Please.
You and Lecty are the ones who
aren't getting results, not me.
So...
Fine, you wanna take
this outside, missy?!
[RICO]
Oh, look, I'm outside now.
[MISORA growls]
Hey, Rico. One thing.
Your test scores are no better
than the "lowly humans"
you like to insult.
Yeah, well, why should I care?
Goddesses have no need
for stupid exams,
so I don't think my
scores should matter.
Sorry, but I've never
seen you in action,
so your scores are all I've got.
And judging by those, I'd say
your skills are no better
than Strawberry Jam over here.
Is that okay with you?
How dare you!
You cannot compare
the human incarnation
of a goddess to that!
Hey, you want a fat lip?!
Y'know...
Training would be the
perfect opportunity for you
to prove me wrong.
[RICO]
Hmm... I see how it is.
I'll comply, but once you see
my astounding ability,
you'll know who's better
without question.
By the way...
While you're being entranced by
the grace of my divine skills,
try not to fall in love with me.
Sure.
And what about you?
[gasps]
[KANATA]
You think you're up for it?
Um... I, uh...
Well...
[MISORA]
Lecty!
How many times do we
have to go over this?
When someone asks you
a question,
you look them in the eye
and answer with confidence.
I'm so sorry!
Why're you apologizing?
Are you saying that you
don't wanna train with me?
[whimpers]
No, I'm not.
I was apologizing to Misora!
Sorry you thought
I was talking to you!
Come on.
I accept your offer.
I'd consider it an honor
to have you as my instructor!
[sighs]
Well, that's great.
Guess it's settled, then.
[YURI]
Okay, so...
My next assignment is
to assist with city security?
[CHLOE giggles]
--My god!
--She waved at us!
It wouldn't kill you
to wave back, you know.
Yeah, but I'm not used
to being treated like this.
I'm not a celebrity.
[sighs] Lemme guess,
you're drinking tea?
Uh, yeah. Is that a problem?
So you still find
coffee too bitter?
Kind of nice to see some
things'll never change.
[sighs]
[YURI]
Hey, so, I'm curious.
Are the higher ups
still treating Kanata
like he's away on sick leave?
[CHLOE]
That makes six.
[YURI]
What?
[CHLOE] You've asked me that
question six times this week.
[gasps]
But, yes. Sick leave
is the official statement.
He's definitely not
ready to be sent
on any real assignments yet.
However, he's now the instructor
of an E-level fireteam.
[YURI]
An instructor?!
[CHLOE] Yes. I was
the one who requested it.
What?! That makes
no sense to me!
He's a traitor to his fireteam,
he'd rather spend time helping
Logistics than fighting,
now he's an instructor?!
I can't believe my ears!
How does he get away
with being such a jerk?!
Okay, calm down.
Insulting him isn't going
to help anything, Yuri.
[gasps]
[CHLOE]
Beautiful, isn't it?
As Sky Wizards, it's our duty
to keep the peace.
And, like it or not,
Kanata is one of us.
As badly as he
behaves sometimes,
I know he still cares.
[YURI sighs]
So, where do you think
Kanata is right now?
Hmm... Well, if I had to
take a wild guess...
I'd say up there!
[KANATA] Okay.
That's high enough for now.
I gotta ask. What the heck
are you riding that thing for?
[KANATA] Huh? Oh. I'm just
used to flying like this.
To be honest, I find it
rather insulting.
If you're going to challenge us,
then you should at least
use flight magic.
What?! Hold on a second.
Mister "Grand Master Swordsman"
thinks he's so great
that he doesn't even have to
fly properly to face us?
Well, since you girls
have a reputation
for not having any skill,
yeah, I'd say that's right.
[growls]
Fine! We'll see how this goes.
So what kind of training
are we doing anyway?!
Today's exercise is--
[MISORA]
Out with it!
It's a game of tag!
Did you say "tag"?!
[MISORA] Playing tag is a
beginning exercise for amateurs
who are just learning
how to fly!
[RICO] I'm appalled that you
think a childish exercise
like this is an appropriate
test of my divine ability.
[LECTY] Um... Are you sure this
is the best way to train us?
[KANATA]
Oh. I forgot to mention.
[GIRLS]
Huh?
There's one caveat.
You are allowed to use your
arcana-alchemical weapons
to attack me.
If you can bring me down, then
the training exercise is over.
[gasping]
[KANATA]
Okay, enough talk.
Training starts now!
[LECTY]
Wow, he's fast!
[MISORA]
Ugh! Whatever! It's on!
Let's do what we can to knock
that traitor off his high horse!
Hold up, Misora! Wait for us!
I can't believe her.
So much for strategy.
Only a novice would blindly
chase their target.
[MISORA]
Come back here, you coward!
You're living up to
your scummy reputation!
Man, this is bad.
They don't seem to understand
the concept of teamwork.
[MISORA growls]
--Wow. Okay.
--[MISORA] This isn't fair!
--Her speed is impressive.
--You're totally cheating!
[KANATA]
I'll admit you're fast,
but do you really think you
can catch me on your own?
Of course I do, why else
would I be doing this?!
I'm gonna catch up to you,
and when I do,
I'm gonna knock you out!
Yeah, I'd like to see you try.
I'm not gonna let you
get close enough to me
to land a single blow.
[gasps, growls]
I'm gonna get you,
you stupid traitor!
Huh. She's got pretty
decent stamina, too.
[MISORA]
All right, I've had enough!
I'm done playing games.
I'm taking you down
once and for all!
My Magical Canon Sword,
Ragrid, will teach you a lesson!
[MISORA yells]
Stop that!
[KANATA]
C'mon, it's not a club!
If you don't swing it with
precision, you'll never hit me!
[MISORA]
I could if you'd stay still!
Do you have any idea
how to wield that thing?
Jeez. You're just
flailing like an idiot.
[panting]
You shut your mouth!
Why don't you just give up?
You're going down, traitor!
[sighs]
Let's give this a shot.
[MISORA]
Don't run away!
Come back here and fight me!
What's the matter?
You afraid of little ol' me?
[KANATA] Hmm. She's still
right behind me.
Her speed and stamina
are impressive.
Let's put her to the test!
This thing ends now!
[gasps]
No way. He's gone!
Where did you go, you jerk?!
[KANATA sighs]
[KANTA] I didn't expect
such a simple maneuver
to throw her off.
[gasps]
[KANATA]
She snuck up on me...
'Scuse me... Um,
Mister Kanata, sir?
Ahh... That's a nice weapon.
Do you have a name for it?
[LECTY]
Ah? Oh, uh, yeah...
Amano-habakiri.
That's what these are called.
[KANATA] She could've had
a hit if she'd gone for it.
I wonder why she didn't.
[KANATA]
What are you waiting for?
You shouldn't hesitate.
'Kay... Here goes nothing!
[LECTY yelling,
KANATA grunting]
[LECTY gasps]
[LECTY]
S-Stay away! I'm warning you!
Don't come any closer!
[KANATA]
How can she be so inconsistent?
Hey, Lecty. You're not
going easy on me, are ya?
[panting]
What do you mean?
Of course I'm not!
[LECTY, KANATA grunting]
[KANATA]
She's a natural.
Her moves are refined
and precise.
And her reflexes are fantastic,
but it seems like
she's trying too hard.
I get the sense that she
doesn't trust her own ability.
I've gotta ask you,
are your weapons
the famous Eisenach twin swords?
[gasps]
[LECTY]
I'm sorry, Kanata!
[KANATA]
Huh...?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Please, accept my apology!
Please!
[RICO]
The Magic Gun Athena,
as exquisite as the goddess
who wields it, shall smite you!
[gasps]
[KANATA grunts]
[LECTY screams]
He just stopped my bullet.
How did he do that?
You saved me.
You all right?
[gasps]
Uh, yeah...
It looks like Rico
isn't all talk.
She's got killer aim.
But, when a shot
is too accurate,
it becomes a lot
easier to dodge.
How so?
It was your intent to kill.
You had me, but I sensed your
presence and blocked the shot.
By the way, you two,
that whole combination.
did you come up
with it on the fly?
Yes, we did, but I was
kinda scared to try.
Hah. When compared to Misora,
who flies about recklessly
waving her sword in the air,
Lecty's fighting style
seems almost elegant.
Therefore, it's only
natural that she and I
would be able to sync our
efforts and land a good shot.
I see. So, you can make a plan,
but you can't concern yourself
with the danger
of friendly fire?
As you know, I'm a goddess.
I place no real value
on any human life.
[KANATA]
What a sweetheart...
Okay.
I think I have a good sense
of what both of you can do.
[MISORA]
Come back, you stupid traitor!
Where the heck did you go?!
[panting]
How did he get away from me?!
This is ridiculous!
[MISORA growls]
This sucks!
There were three of us
and only one of him!
We should have been
able to catch him!
I'm sorry that my skills
were inadequate.
Truly!
Oh, do you need some help?
Uh, yeah, thanks a lot.
Don't worry, Lecty.
What happened up there
was my fault.
I wasn't looking out
for you today.
I should have been a leader
and given better instructions.
I guess I still have
a thing or two to learn.
Hum. Finally she says
something intelligent.
The fireteam leader
failed to adequately
assess the battlefield.
[MISORA growls]
Huh. But, my brains
and beauty saved the day.
Why you... I oughtta...
Please don't be jealous.
It's only natural that
my breasts are bigger.
And, of course, I'm taller
and much more beautiful.
That's what separates
commoners from goddesses.
Ugh! Like I would
ever be envious of you!
Giant boobs are so overrated!
And besides, my breasts are
still bigger than Lecty's!
What?
Um...
I don't think so...
Huh...?
What's wrong, Misora?
Are you... all right?
It can't be...
This cannot be true!
I'm just dreaming...
[wails]
[MISORA] How could Lecty
have bigger boobs than me?!
It's not fair! [sobs]
[RICO] Don't let it
concern you too much.
There's no correlation
between bra size and success.
Not for a Sky Wizard.
Yeah?
You mean it?
[RICO] You may not be all
"boing-boing, va-va-voom"
like me and Lecty,
but that doesn't make you
less of a woman.
You're just more "womp-womp,
fizzle, zip, zilch, nada".
Isn't that right?
Uh...
Yeah, she's got a point!
Who cares if your boobs are
"womp-womp, fizzle,
zip, zilch, nada"? That doesn't
make you any less of a lady!
--At least, I don't think so.
--[MISORA whimpers]
Wait a sec!
Rico, how could you make me
say something like that?!
Um, Misora, listen,
I didn't mean it!
I didn't know what I was saying!
The last thing I want
is for you to be upset--
I have had it!
Rico!
Why do you go outta your way
to be such a hateful jerk?!
How dare you!
--That's no way to speak
--You guys are scaring me,
--to a goddess!
--you gotta calm down!
[KANATA] Misora's the
hot head of the group.
She lets her emotions
get the best of her.
[LECTY whines]
[KANATA] Lecty's low
self-esteem gets in her way.
She doesn't trust herself
against the enemy.
Rico has the exact
opposite problem.
She fights well, but her
arrogance undermines
her relationship
with her allies.
[KANATA]
One thing's for sure,
it's not gonna be easy
putting this puzzle together.
Not with these messed up pieces.
But I can do it, if I can get
them to trust each other.
[RICO] I'll never accept you as
the fireteam leader, Misora.
I am a goddess!
I shouldn't be expected to
submit to someone so inferior.
[MISORA] Let's not forget
I started this fireteam!
The founder's always
the one in charge!
That's the way it is so you're
just gonna have to get over it!
[LECTY]
Misora calm down!
[RICO]
Just because you're the founder
doesn't mean you've
earned my respect!
You can't tell me what to do!
[MISORA]
Don't hold me back, Lecty!
I'm gonna shut her
big mouth once and for all!
Okay, ladies, for
tomorrow's lesson--
--Out, you pervert!
--No, you don't, pervert!
[KANATA]
Not this again.
[RICO]
I am the goddess, Rico Flamel.
Today, I am giving
a special lesson.
Consider yourselves lucky
to learn from the best.
A Sky Wizard's role in battle is
determined by his or her weapon.
Lecty's Magic Twin Swords
allow her to perform
close combat in the vanguard.
I, on the other hand,
engage enemies at long range
--with my Magic Gun.
--[MISORA] Hey, what about me?
[RICO] Ah yes,
I almost forgot about you.
No surprise there.
The next episode is called:
"The Potentials of the Weakest."
[MISORA] Is the weakest
supposed to be me?!