[MISORA] How am I supposed
to focus on training
when Kanata is out
spending time with Yuri?
Not that I care.
[LECTY]
Um, I guess it is kinda weird
that he was out with
a rival instructor.
But I did get cake out
of us following them,
so is it really such a bad thing
that they were on a date?
[MISORA]
A date?! Stop saying that!
We don't know it was a date!
[RICO]
If you two don't stop
thinking about our pervy
teacher and desserts,
we're never going to
win the Tournament.
[MISORA, LECTY]
You're right...
Stop right there.
Strike Blaster.
[gasps]
Uh...
[MISORA]
We won the tournament.
[LECTY yawns]
[KANATA]
Hey, nice pace, there, Lecty!
Kanata! I didn't know
you ran here, too!
Usually this path is pretty
empty in the mornings,
why are you up so early?
I try to get a good
jog in every day.
That's what I call discipline.
Good for you, I was afraid
Misora had woken you
with her snoring
or something.
Actually she talks in her sleep.
At least she's not sleep-
casting Strike Blasters.
That girl's already
destroyed one home
because she wasn't
paying attention
to where her attacks were aimed.
That's a sore subject.
[LECTY]
Um, since we're both out here,
there's something I
wanted to ask you.
Have some.
You gotta stay hydrated.
Uh. Sure...
[KANATA] So you're
wondering how, exactly,
the current training regimen
is helping out the team.
Yeah.
[LECTY] I guess I understand
what you're trying to do
by switching up our roles.
You think we might work better
as a team if we've trained
in each other's positions.
But...
I just don't think
this plan will work!
Misora's a really
great Sky Wizard,
but her skills don't make
her a very good vanguard.
And since my melee weapons
don't have much range,
I feel like I can't
help at all when
I'm stuck as the rear guard!
I don't wanna fail.
[gasps]
You're paying attention.
Excellent work.
Um, Kanata, you do realize
that you're petting me, right?
You've got a good
point about Misora.
She's not exactly great
in that position.
Does that mean you're
gonna rethink
the training and we can--
[KANATA] I don't think so.
But you're on to something.
In fact, you're close to
understanding my plan.
Honestly, I'm kinda impressed.
[LECTY] So there is a
point to all of this?!
Yeah, of course there is.
Do you want a hint?
[LECTY]
Huh...?
Ah!
Aw! Why does this
keep happening?!
You're sure you don't mind
taking her on again?
[laughing] Not at all.
I don't think anyone in
the Logistics division
would turn down a request
from you, Kanata.
[MALE WORKER B] The workflow
changes you suggested
have made us super-efficient!
[FEMALE WORKER A]
And thanks again for clearing up
that dispute with our supplier.
We're fully stocked now!
[MALE WORKER B]
Heh.
[KANATA]
Later!
[KANATA] Hey, you'd better keep
your head in the game, Lecty.
The lunchtime rush
here can be a warzone.
[LECTY whimpers]
[BOY STUDENT A] Hey, can I get
some service over here, please?
Do you have any new
specials today?
Can I get the lunch combo
with a side salad?
Um. Let me just write
that down, okay?
[LECTY panting]
Sorry to bother you,
but can I please get another
order of the soup of the day?
[CHEF A] Hot bowl a' stew,
comin' right up!
[exhales]
[STUDENTS chattering]
Oh, wow.
The wait staff works together
like one big machine.
[GIRL STUDENT C]
Excuse me! I'm ready!
Thanks for waiting, miss.
And what can I get for you?
I'm bulking up for
the tournament,
so I'll take a steak.
[GIRL STUDENT D] That's always
what you order here.
Just the usual, then.
[gasps]
Hey, this beef stew's
ready to go out.
Right! Thanks!
Oh, I can drop that off for
you on my way to the front.
Could you handle the customers
who just sat down?
[LECTY gasping]
Sure! No problem.
[gasping]
[LECTY]
Uh! Sorry, that was my fault.
Oh, no worries. Just
keep your eyes open.
And pay attention to
your surroundings.
My surroundings? Okay.
Uh! Your glass is empty,
can I get you some water?
You can take this table right
here, it just opened up!
[CUSTOMER A]
Waitress?
[LECTY] Oh, hi! Are you
ready to put in an order?
All the employees are working
towards the same outcome.
They move in tandem.
Paying attention to
your surroundings
and what your
teammates are doing,
that's how you
achieve your goals.
[grunts] Why am I not hitting
any of these stupid
training beetles at all?
[MISORA yells]
You've got to draw them
in closer and then aim.
Firing recklessly is
what blew up your house.
Yeah, well, I'm new
at this position,
and I bet you're not any more
comfortable as a midfielder!
That was my fifth
consecutive kill.
[MISORA]
Rico, watch it!
There's an enemy coming
in low at your twelve!
[RICO] I'm doing more
than my share of the work.
You handle that one.
[MISORA]
You jerk!
[LECTY]
Please, don't fight!
We're supposed to be
working together, right?
[sighs]
[LECTY whimpers]
Is there something wrong?
No, it's just...
I didn't realize rear guard
was such... a lonely position.
It can be.
You're stuck hanging
back on your own
as our final line of defense
if something goes wrong.
It's easy to feel not just
lonely, but helpless.
That is, if you don't
trust your teammates.
Poor Rico. She always
served as our rear guard.
I wonder if she ever
felt this anxious.
[gasps]
We... have to pay close
attention to our surroundings.
Whenever I was the vanguard,
I only ever looked at
what was in front of me.
Hey, Misora!
Kinda busy here.
[LECTY] The primary job of
a vanguard is to cut through
the enemy's formations
and thin out their ranks.
Uh. I'm aware of that.
Why else do you think
I'm flying so quickly?
Yeah!
I'm really impressed
that you can keep firing
while moving around like that.
Seriously!
There's no way I could keep
up that kind of pacing.
You're amazing!
[gasps] Oh, uh, thanks!
And I think you can
do even better!
Your flying skills and
magic power reserves
are off the charts,
but you gotta make sure
to focus on each attack.
[MISORA] Well, if you really
think that'll make a difference.
It will! Take the time
to make every shot count.
Don't waste your energy
on any extra movements.
Then I'm sure your score
will fly as high as you!
All right. I'll give it a try.
[LECTY]
And, um, hey, Rico?
[RICO]
Huh?
I never knew how much
pressure you had
on your shoulders
as our rear guard.
Now I understand just how
hard it can be to keep track
of everything happening
on the battlefield
when you're so far away.
Good, I'm glad to hear that.
At least one of you is smart
enough to see how talented I am.
So I'll at least
entertain the idea
that I might be able
to do better as well.
Ah! Thank you, Rico!
[MISORA grunts]
[LECTY] With Misora
firing more accurately,
it's easier for Rico
to provide cover
and keep an eye
on our enemies.
Since they're working together,
I can focus on any targets
that slip by them.
We all improve.
[MISORA grunts]
[MISORA gasps]
Oh, no!
Don't worry, I've got
your backs covered,
those targets are toast!
[LECTY yells]
[LECTY]
So this is what it's like
to grow as a team and
truly work together!
[KANATA]
That's enough.
[LECTY gasps]
Great job, Lecty.
You passed the test.
Uh, thanks Kanata,
but you know you're
petting my head again!
Good morning Kanata.
Up early as usual, I see.
Hey, Chloe, have a
good day, all right?
I gotta clean up.
Uh! What happened to you?!
You've got huge bags
under your eyes.
[CHLOE groans] Please try to
ignore these dark circles.
We've been on night
patrol recently,
and I haven't had
any time to sleep.
Oh, right. You're investigating
those attacks.
So, I take it you don't
have any leads yet?
[CHLOE] Not really.
But we did figure out
he's targeting people
who use melee weapons.
But I shouldn't be discussing
this stuff with you.
Say. Is Yuri on night duty, too?
No, she's lucky. She only
patrols during the day.
That way she still has plenty of
time to instruct her students.
Well, good luck
with everything.
We need evidence more
than we need luck.
Kanata! [gasps]
Mm... There you are!
I think it's about
time we stopped
this weird training of yours!
We should be doing more
advanced exercises,
like what the S-Rankers do!
Not a chance.
I don't think you'd even
survive that type of training.
It'd of be of no use to you.
[MISORA] Then can you
at least tell me why
we're taking
different positions?
Lecty and Rico seem to
know something I don't,
and if I can't catch up
to them, I'm finished!
All I want is to make
sure that I get stronger!
[KANATA] She wants to
become more powerful
and rise to the level
of her teammates.
It sounds selfish on the
surface, but there's more to it.
What are you thinking?!
Why're you so quiet
all of a sudden?!
[KANATA]
Okay, let's meet
in the fireteam room today
instead of the skies.
Tell the others and wait
for me there, will ya?
Hurry up. And don't be late!
[MISORA]
I'm going, I'm going!
[MISORA grunts]
You enjoy teaching, don't you?
It's not so bad.
Wow.
You're acting like you did
back when you were
teaching Yuri.
Remember? When you
two used to get along.
[door opens]
[coughing]
[MISORA] Why did you
bring us to this dump?
[KANATA] From now until
the day of the next match,
the three of you are
gonna be living here
together as roommates.
[RICO, MISORA, LECTY gasp]
[KANATA] I want you to spend
every waking hour together.
And I guess the sleeping
ones, too, really.
Wait, he can't make
us move in here!
How could this possibly help
make us a better fireteam?!
I trust whatever Kanata says.
[MISORA groans]
[MISORA] We should probably
start by cleaning this place up.
There's, like, an inch
of dust on everything.
[LECTY]
So gross.
Make sure you're thorough.
Otherwise, my immaculate body
will never be able
to step foot inside.
You have to help, you know!
I refuse. Training is one thing,
but scrubbing this
filthy apartment
is an activity best
left to servants.
I'm gonna hurt you!
[LECTY] Wait a second.
Don't freak out, Misora.
I'll work twice as hard
and it'll be okay!
[KANATA]
Hey, think fast!
[YURI]
Uh! [grunting]
A cream puff?
Nice reflexes.
[YURI]
What the hell, Kanata?
Why did you just throw
a pastry at me?
It's a little gift from
one instructor to another.
Hopefully it'll make our
victory easier to handle.
You can't seriously think
your team is gonna win.
C'mon, Even you
aren't that idiotic.
I don't see what's idiotic about
having faith in my fireteam.
You can stand there and pretend
to be noble if you want to,
but I don't accept
gifts from traitors!
Remember that food
stand in the park
we used to go to after
training together?
Well, I stopped by there to pick
up a few rewards for the girls.
That's when I noticed
their special today
was the super-deluxe
cream puff that you love.
[growling]
Well, on second thought,
I shouldn't waste food.
[KANATA laughs]
[YURI] Don't you dare
laugh at me like that!
It's just not fair for me
to take my hatred of you
out on this innocent dessert!
[KANATA laughs]
[FREON] The newest victim is an
A-Ranker, just like you guessed.
The attacker's sticking
to his pattern.
[LLOYD] We're going to need to
be extra careful on our patrols.
The assailant's next target
will likely be one of us.
Yes, an S-ranker.
[laughs]
Do you want another one?
Uh! That's for me, too?
U-Uh... I mean, no thanks.
Why are you being
so nice, anyway?
Just what are you after?
There's something I didn't get
to ask you about the other day.
Well, go ahead.
The reason you decided not
to use a spear anymore.
Is it because I'm the one who
told you to use it
instead of a sword?
[KANATA sighs]
I was afraid that was why.
Butt out, okay!
You don't have any
right to lecture me.
Oh, I'm well aware of that.
You're no longer my student.
But do you remember why I
had you switch to the spear?
[KANATA]
You had a habit of backing away
when your blade locked
with an enemy's.
That's a fatal flaw
for a sword fighter.
I used a sword during the
recent Devil Beetle attack,
and I didn't run
into any problems.
Don't worry about me.
You're the most stubborn girl
I've ever met in my life.
But then...
It's that same stubbornness
that helps you succeed.
You never would've gotten
so good without it.
[YURI]
Uh!
Y'know, you were impressive
from the very start, Yuri.
If I'm being honest here,
I don't think there was really
much I needed to teach you.
[YURI]
That look on his face.
How can he be so at peace
knowing that he betrayed
us and became a coward?
Actually, there was one thing.
A concept we always talked
about in your lessons.
Something more important
than your weapon.
[YURI] To never give up,
no matter what the odds are.
Yeah. Good to know that
one stuck with you.
As long as you have that,
I know you'll be fine,
with or without me. I have
no doubt your name'll
go down in the record
books someday.
[YURI] Why are you saying all
this now? What brought this on?
[KANATA] Nothing in particular.
I just felt like telling you.
That's not a real answer!
Reminiscing about the past...
What are you trying to
achieve by bringing up
all these old lessons
and memories?
I dunno. You just make
me feel kinda...
[gasps]
You feel... what, exactly?
Well, I feel...
Ah, Yuri. Sorry to
keep you waiting.
But I had to make sure I'd
grown strong enough for you.
You know, you should really
choose your friends
more carefully.
Funny, I figured he
was one of your cronies.
So, finally. We've come face
to face with the assailant.
Whoa, wait a sec.
Stay out of this, Kanata.
[YURI] What an amateur.
I can take him. [grunts]
This'll be easy!
[YURI]
He's fast!
Oh, you're so slow, Yuri.
So slow I almost fell asleep.
Watch out! Don't back away!
[KANATA]
Every time she does that
she's opening herself
up to an attack.
[REAL chuckles]
Don't you wanna be close to me?
[YURI gasping]
[YURI] There's no use
trying to run from him.
[REAL] Please. It's time
for you to accept my love.
[screams]
[REAL laughs]
Oh, Yuri!
Yuri!
[YURI groaning]
[REAL] You can't give
up yet, my darling.
Not until I've proven
that I'm the only one who's
worthy of your affection!
[YURI]
You're asking for it.
I don't know who you are,
but you're dead!
[YURI gasps]
[YURI]
Where will he attack from?
The right?
The left?
Above?
No...
[YURI]
Behind!
Very good, Yuri.
But let's see how you
hold up against this.
[YURI gasps]
A Wind Slash?
Flight magic that's channeled
into a lethal attack!
Have some more. And Tell
me how you like 'em!
[YURI]
Stop it!
That's it, my love.
You can feel my desire
now, can't you?!
[YURI gasps]
I told you to stay
out of this fight!
[KANATA] Yeah, and if
I'd listened to you,
you'd be dead right now.
I'm not gonna stand by
and watch you get hurt.
I was getting so close that my
love had almost reached her!
Kanata Age!
[REAL grunts]
Even though you're a traitor,
you're still the
famed "Chronos."
But you can't dodge
what you can't see!
[REAL whimpering]
Yeah, you're able to move
at incredible speeds.
But who cares? I'm faster!
[REAL groaning]
We Sky Wizards put
our lives on the line
to hone our skills
to the maximum.
And you're nothing
but an amateur
who's highly
overestimated himself.
Yuri is mine. You'll see!
That's enough for today.
But I'll be back for my
darling soon, you bastard.
[gasps] You're not getting away!
[YURI grunts]
This is just a taste,
my love, Yuri.
There's so much more
for me to give you.
[YURI groaning]
[KANATA]
Yuri! Hey, are you all right?
Yuri!
[YURI]
Kanata, help me.
[REAL]
Kanata Age.
Why is he always in my way?
[growling]
[CHIMERA A]
I can help you, Real.
I can give you whatever
your heart desires.
Huh?
[groaning]
It feels like someone's
shouting directly into my head!
[ALL gasp]
[RICO] Yuri's unconscious
and all bruised up.
[LECTY] Her clothes have
been ripped to shreds.
[ALL] What did you do
to her, you pervert?!
[sighs]
[LECTY whimpers]
Hi, this is Lecty.
Did you know that the
Special Duty fireteam members
all have nicknames?
Chloe is Nirvana,
Yuri is Brionac, and when
Kanata was on the team,
he was called the Black
Sword Saint Chronos!
Um, I think that's everyone.
[LLOYD clears throat]
Hi, this is Lloyd,
and apparently I'm
completely forgettable.
[LECTY]
Oh, sorry!
[LLOYD] Hey, you're that
maid from the café!
[LECTY] Wait, is that how
everyone remembers me?
[LLOYD]
I'm told the next episode is
"Potentials of the Zero."
[LECTY gasping]
[LLOYD]
Is something wrong?
[LECTY]
Why am I naked in the preview?