[MISORA]
I can't believe he'd tell me
to give up the Magic
Cannon Sword!
How dare he?
I'm gonna train super hard and
master it like nobody else has!
Earnest, hard work
always pays off!
At least that's what
I read in a manga.
[KANATA]
Let's be real,
manga heroes seem like
super hard workers,
but in the end you find
out they had some kind
of special talent or advantage.
[MISORA]
You ruin everything!
[SKY WIZARD A]
There are too many of them!
[SKY WIZARD B] We can't hold
them off for much longer!
[SKY WIZARDS gasp]
[SOCIÉ yells]
You picked the
wrong Sky Wizard
to mess with today,
Devil Beetles!
[SOCIÉ grunting]
Oh, So you wanna
play like that?
[SOCIÉ]
Alright.
My magic power is fully charged!
Time for Strike Blaster!
[yells]
[SKY WIZARDS gasp]
[SOCIÉ chuckles]
[CITIZENS cheer]
[FEMALE CITIZEN] Thanks again
for all that you do for us!
[MALE CITIZEN B]
She's our hero!
[MALE CITIZEN C]
Socié Whitale!
Awesome!
I'm proud of you, Momma!
[KANATA]
You're switching from vanguard
Magic Cannon Sword to
middle guard Magic Cannon.
[MISORA grunts]
[MISORA]
I refuse to give up my sword.
[sighs]
[knocking]
[LECTY] Um. Excuse me,
I'm here with your coffee.
[LLOYD] You're getting
pretty good at this.
[LECTY gasps]
[LLOYD] Thank you
for all your hard work.
[LLOYD] What do you say
we take a quick break?
Sounds good.
[sighs]
I'm so exhausted.
[FREON] The girl at
the door looked familiar.
She's one of the students from
fireteam E601, isn't she?
What kind of "training"
is waitressing at a café?
If you really want to know,
call Kanata in and
ask him about it.
I would but I doubt
that he'd give me
a straight answer.
You know how he is.
[gasps]
[LECTY]
Hey, Rico!
No, ma'am.
[LECTY]
Huh?
You know that I'm a goddess.
Why should I submit to nasty,
sweaty training
designed for humans?
Yeah, and I hate
to even ask you.
But Misora's been absent
from school for a few days.
I'm a total train wreck without
her here to back me up.
I'm the last person
you should ask.
"People" problems are
so far beneath me
that I can't even
begin to relate.
[LECTY]
I understand.
I guess I'll just have to
rely on Kanata to help.
[RICO gasps]
I'm quite surprised
you would place
so much faith in
a traitor like him.
Yeah, I know!
Well, I was kinda
worried about him, too.
Cuz' he made me wear
this silly maid outfit...
[RICO]
Well, well, Kanata Age.
[LECTY]...The effect
training's had on me...
[RICO] Looks like
you've won her over.
[REAL gasping]
Yuri, my name's
Real Nua. Hi there.
Thank you for drying
my pants the other day!
Yeah, that'll work.
What could you possibly
want with me now, Yuri?
[REAL]
Huh?
[YURI] Don't play dumb, you know
exactly what I'm after, Kanata.
The girls from fireteam E601
haven't trained in days.
I demand to know what's up!
How would you know whether
they've been training or not?
[laughs] I checked the log
book and there's no record
of anyone from your
fireteam requesting
to use the training airspace.
That's public information,
you know.
Don't you have anything
better to do? Get a life.
[YURI gasps] There's no
need for you to be rude!
You're the only Special Duty
member who has any spare time!
I'm just looking out
for those girls, is all.
I wouldn't want
you to betray them
like you seem to do
to everybody else here.
[KANATA]
Whatever.
As much as I'd
love to stay and chat,
I've gotta go check
on one of my students.
Hey, wait!
I'm not finished talking to you!
[KANATA]
Always so serious.
You need to lighten up.
[YURI] Y-You're the one
who's in the wrong, not me!
[KANATA] You don't need to
"look out" for the girls, okay?
That's my job.
[gasps]
[YURI]
D-Don't just walk away, Kanata!
[YURI growls]
Come back here!
[gasping]
[KANATA]
This must be the place.
Welcome, Sir.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for
Miss Misora Whitale.
[MISORA] What in the hell do
you think you're doing here?!
[KANATA] Oh, so you're not sick,
you're just playing hooky.
What does it matter
to you, jerk face?
Watch your tone, young lady.
That's no way to speak
to one of our guests.
[MISORA]
Shut up, Dad!
Just butt out of it, okay?
[GALE gasps]
Wait a sec, you mean
you're Misora's Dad?
She looks nothin' like you.
[laughs]
[GALE] Luckily, she takes
after her mother.
Okay, That's it, I'm done
helping for the day.
I'm sorry. We're not
exactly the model family
when it comes to
relating to each other.
[KANATA]
Huh?
Wow, your wife is a
really beautiful woman.
And you're right, Misora does
look just like her.
[GALE]
Thank you.
I only wish I could
remember her.
[KANATA]
Huh?
That photo is the only
reason I'm sure she existed.
Eat up, kid, this one's
on the house.
It's our most popular entrée.
Well, I'm not here
as a customer, but...
[KANATA]
Whoa! This is delicious!
[laughs]
[GALE] They tell me steak
was my wife's favorite food.
I hear she'd eat
it for every meal.
You must be a Natural, huh?
Yeah, I am. And apparently
I was married
to one of the best
Sky Wizards on record.
But I have no
memory of her.
Seems heartless, I know.
But it's not like
I can control it.
The records are there.
She was real.
I know that, logically, but it
never feels like my memory.
[MISORA huffs]
It definitely puts a strain
on my relationship with Misora.
She's been skipping
school the past few days,
but I can't even punish her.
Are you guys friends?
You know what's
going on with her?
I'm grasping at straws, here.
[KANATA chuckles]
Friends? Guess we'll see.
But, before I get into that,
I've got a question for ya.
[GALE]
What is it?
[KANATA] Why is she so obsessed
with the Magic Cannon Sword?
[GALE] You're more than just
an acquaintance, aren't you?
I didn't mention it before?
I'm Misora's new instructor.
It's my job to help her become
stronger, but she's fighting me.
[GALE]
Hmm...
My wife was an amazing
Magic Cannon Swordsman.
Those who fought beside
her say that watching her
in battle was like nothing
they'd ever seen. But one day,
she left for a mission and
never made it back home.
[MISORA grunts]
Since that day,
it's like she never existed.
None of us Naturals
have any memory of her.
[GALE] I think Misora wants to
master the Magic Cannon Sword
as a way to always keep
her mother's legacy alive.
[MISORA shouts]
[MISORA grunts]
I'll never give up.
No matter what.
[MISORA gasps]
It's Momma! She's home!
Oh, my baby!
[giggles]
Momma!
Misora!
We watched you fly!
[SOCIÉ] I missed you
so much, my sweet girl!
Here ya go!
I know how you love it when
I swing you around like this!
Up, up, and away!
[MISORA screams]
Socié.
Oh, Gale!
I've been so worried about you
I haven't slept through
the night since you left.
I napped, though.
[SOCIÉ] Well, I was
so lonely without you
that I could only manage
to eat four meals a day!
[GALE] We're happy to
have you home, honey.
[SOCIÉ] I'm thrilled
to be back, my darling.
[MISORA screams]
[MISORA]
Momma! Why'd you do that?
[SOCIÉ giggling]
My baby is just the cutest ever!
Hey! Stop it! Momma!
[MALE RESIDENT A] I watched
the live feed, you were great!
[MALE RESIDENT B]
You didn't just defeat
those Devil Beetles,
you pulverized 'em!
[MALE RESIDENT C]
The city of Iris
can rest easy with
you protecting us!
[SOCIÉ chuckles]
No problem!
Just leave the dirty work
to me and I'll keep you safe!
[giggles]
Aw, steak for breakfast again?
Yep! Breakfast is the most
important meal of the day
so you gotta eat
something nice and heavy!
Aw... But, I want cereal.
[door clicks]
[MISORA yelps]
I'm sorry.
I guess I messed up the settings
on the washing machine again.
[MISORA] I didn't know the
machine had a flood setting!
[GALE, MISORA gasp]
[chuckles nervously]
[MISORA]
What happened, Momma?
It's funny.
I was cleaning the house and
it seemed like there would
never be an end to all the
trash, so I had an idea.
And I thought, "Why don't
I just use magic?"
You can't vaporize trash!
[SOCIÉ]
Don't be such a meanie, Misora!
--[beeping]
--[MISORA gasps]
Yes, hello?
Archenar class beetles
and a Chimera?
Understood.
--I'll be there shortly.
--[MISORA] Who is it?
[SOCIÉ] I'm sorry dear, but
momma has to go to work now.
[MISORA] But you just got
home from your last mission!
[SOCIÉ gasps]
[MISORA whimpers]
[gasps]
[SOCIÉ]
Gale!
Good luck, Momma!
[sighs]
That's my girl!
[MISORA]
Momma!
Did you miss me, Misora?
[MISORA]
I missed you so much!
Ah! Momma!
[MISORA]
Wow!
The town looks so
tiny from way up here!
Oh, hey! Is that our house?
Hi Daddy!
[SOCIÉ]
That's right!
Daddy and all our neighbors are
down there safe in their beds.
[MISORA]
Really?
They're sleeping sound
because they know
I will protect them
if there's trouble.
I know it makes you sad when
I leave, but just remember that
when I'm away I'm busy
keeping our city safe.
Yeah, I know.
[BOTH giggle]
[SOCIÉ] I suppose
I should protect you
and your daddy too, huh?
[MISORA]
You better!
[SECURITY GUARD]
Attention Sky Wizard!
Stop right there!
[MISORA]
Huh?
[SECURITY GUARD]
I repeat, stop right there!
You're flying illegally! Halt!
[gasps]
Momma.
Don't Sky Wizards who want to
fly above the city like this
--have to ask for permission
--Just hold on tight, okay?
[MISORA]
We're running away?
[SECURITY GUARD]
Hey, wait! Stop!
You can't run! Stop, I say!
[SOCIÉ]
Eh..I sorta forgot to ask them!
[MISORA gasps]
But that's really important!
[MISORA] I know you're gonna
do great out there Momma!
I'll have a steak waiting
for you when you get back.
[SOCIÉ]
Thanks!
I'd better go!
Be home soon!
[GALE]
Best of luck, dear.
[MISORA]
Good-bye, Momma!
Bye-bye! See you soon!
[MISORA] I wonder if
Momma's coming home today.
Daddy!
[GALE]
Hey there!
Dinner will be ready soon.
I thought that I'd try a new
recipe for beef stew tonight.
[MISORA] Huh? But why
aren't we having steak?
[GALE] Oh, is that
what you wanted?
Well, it's a little
too late now.
--I suppose we could have--
--[MISORA] No, uh.
That's not what I meant--
[gasps]
[MISORA]
Daddy, do you know
if Momma's gonna be
coming home soon?
Momma? It's always just
been the two of us, honey.
[MISORA whimpers]
What is it?
What's got you so
upset all of a sudden?
Misora?
[MISORA]
Momma! Momma!
Socié? I've never
heard that name.
[MISORA panting]
Your mom? I'm confused.
It's just been you and your
dad as long as I've known you.
Hey, wait! Come back!
I'm sorry but I've never
heard of a Sky Wizard
by that name before.
[whimpers]
[SKY WIZARD G]
Huh?
[SKY WIZARD G] Your mother's
sacrifice saved our lives.
She charged in alone to
buy us time to regroup.
She fought bravely but there
were just too many enemies.
Socié was the strongest and
most noble of all Sky Wizards.
We'll suffer this
loss for a long time.
[gasps]
[SOCIÉ] I know it makes
you sad when I leave,
but just remember
that when I'm away
I'm busy keeping our city safe.
[MISORA gasps, whimpers]
[SOCIÉ] But I suppose
that I should protect
you and your daddy too, huh?
[gasps]
That's mine now. Please!
I wanna be a Sky Wizard!
[SKY WIZARDS gasp]
[MISORA]
I'm gonna be brave and strong
and protect everyone
like my momma!
[MISORA yells, pants]
Why can't I be
strong like she was?
All I want is to win,
so why can't I?
I'm so sick of losing!
[yelps]
I try.
I do.
I always give it my best shot.
But for some reason
it's just never enough.
[MISORA]
I can't give up, though.
I'm never going to stop
fighting for mom's memory.
[MISORA]
What are you doing here?
[KANATA]
The Hills of Hope.
The final resting place
of the Sky Wizards
who lost their lives in battle.
Word on the street is
you're here every day.
I'm sure my dad
told you that.
What makes you guys think
you can invade my privacy?
The two of you are
the absolute worst!
[KANATA] Don't be angry with
your dad, it's not his fault.
You won't tell him anything.
Can you blame him
for worrying about you?
[MISORA grunts]
[KANATA] I asked
him why you're fixated
on the Magic Cannon Sword.
I knew by his answer
that I'd find you here.
Misora.
Swear right now on
your mother's grave.
Give up on the
Magic Cannon Sword.
[MISORA gasps]
[KANATA]
You'll never get stronger
if you keep obsessing about it.
You don't know anything
about me, so butt out, okay!
[MISORA] When the Sky
Wizards gave me this sword,
I was handed my mother,
her will, everything about her
that the Naturals like my
dad can't even remember!
I guess a traitor like you
can't understand that!
Hey.
These are called the
"Hills of Hope".
What did the dead hope for?
They hoped to
protect the citizens
and to keep their cities safe.
[KANATA]
That's right.
None of them wanted to die
and be forgotten
by their loved ones,
but they took that
chance in order protect
innocent civilians
from the Devil Beetles.
It's what drove them to fight.
I'm sure your mother
felt that way, too.
Well, obviously.
Of course she did.
[KANATA]
Think about it.
[MISORA]
Huh?
Your mother's goal wasn't
to Master the
Magic Cannon Sword.
That was a means to an end.
As a Sky Wizard,
the weapon she chose
was never as important to
her as protecting her people.
But... It's her sword.
I didn't feel anything.
There was no grief
when Socié died.
I worry it'll be the
same with my daughter.
It scares me to think that I
could lose her feel nothing.
That little girl means
the world to me.
You need to stop
being so stubborn,
or you're gonna make a mistake
and get killed in battle.
[gasps]
[KANATA]
You'd be forgotten.
You'd never get to
make a real impact.
Duh. Yeah, I get that.
I know that the way I'm
behaving is totally selfish.
[KANATA]
Then stop!
But I'm still not
gonna give it up!
I want to protect the people,
but I only wanna do it
with my mom's sword!
If I master the
Magic Cannon Sword
and become as good as she was,
maybe people who see
me fighting with her weapon
will recover the memories
of her that they lost.
That's a tall order.
Naturals have never recovered
memories of lost Sky Wizards.
[MISORA]
So what?
That doesn't mean
it's impossible!
She deserves to be remembered!
We all do!
[KANATA gasps]
[chuckles]
[MISORA]
Huh?
[KANATA laighs] I could tell
from the start you were crazy,
but you're
officially certifiable!
[MISORA]
Yeah, yeah, laugh it up!
No worries.
The crazy ones are my favorites.
[gasps]
[KANATA] I'm gonna
teach you how to be
the best Magic Cannon
Swordsman ever.
You just have to listen, okay?
[MISORA]
Huh?
Thank you for showing
me how resolute you are.
Looks like I'm gonna have to
step up my game from now on.
So, this was a test then?
Misora.
I need to be sure
you understand.
The path you've chosen
is a fate worse than death.
You think you can take it?
I know I can!
[KANATA] Then swear on your
sword and your mother's grave,
so I know you're committed.
[gasps]
[KANATA] Vow that you'll
become an even better
Magic Cannon Swordsman
than your mom ever was.
Swear you'll be strong
enough to protect your people
and yourself, as well.
[MISORA gasps]
Right!
[MISORA]
I swear.
[KANATA]
I won't let her die.
Huh?
I promise you.
Why do you care?
'Cause if I didn't,
I'd be a lousy instructor.
[MISORA gasps]
[KANATA]
I'm here to help you carry
the weight of your burdens.
Our responsibility is heavy.
[gasps]
So we have to be strong.
You got it?
Yes!
[MISORA]
I'm sorry for worrying you.
No, it's alright!
I'm just so happy to have
you back to train with me.
I really missed you.
[KANATA]
Come on, ladies!
It's time to get the show
on the road! Hop to it
or I'll make you bikini
baristas for the next week!
[gasps]
Yes, sir!
Hey! Wait up, Lecty!
[gasps]
[KANATA]
Hm?
[MISORA]
Hey, Kanata.
Thank you!
[chuckles]
[RICO]
Well, Instructor.
You've finally
become interesting.
[MISORA]
Hey everybody, Misora here!
You know, Mystogan isn't
the only floating city.
We've got lots of 'em!
Let's see, there's Oakis,
Lyune, and Bevel.
Those are just some of
the more famous ones!
[LECTY] I used to live on Oakis
before I came to the academy!
[MISORA] Yeah, yeah,
that's nice, Lecty.
Now let's get back to what
really matters here: me!
Don't miss my awesome
performance in the next episode
of Sky Wizards Academy,
"The Key to Victory."
[LECTY gasps] I'll try my
best to help-- ouch!
I'm sorry, I just bit my tongue.
[MISORA] I can't
take you anywhere.