[KOTAROU gasps]
[AIRA]
Yeah, it'll be fun!
When you say date you...
...do you mean
as your girlfriend?
Yes.
I need some time
to think, okay?
S-Sure.
[AKANE]
We've barely spoken since then,
and I still don't
know what to say.
[ROMAN panting]
Hi-yah!
What the hell?
School trip time!
I'm so psyched we get
to take the bullet train!
Did you pack clean
underwear, Kota?
Of course I did.
Guess what?
I'm using this trip to debut
my upgrade from
boxers to boxer briefs.
[SETSUKO]
I just brought everything!
[ROMAN]
I've been wearing them.
[DAICHI]
You showboat.
[HIDAKA] Right, time
for a surprise bag check!
[STUDENTS]
Aww!
[HIDAKA]
Hmm...
Ah?
Hey, now! That's for
ladies only, you know!
Oh!
[HIDAKA clears throat]
Okay.
[RYOUKO] As a lady,
I'll give this a quick peek.
[RYOUKO] Ah-ah,
no phones, remember?
I'll hang on to this for you.
[MIU whines]
She caught me!
Too bad she's
not more gullible.
[HIDAKA]
Hmm... hm?
Hm.
All right, then, next!
Well they caught
a bunch of us, huh?
So, where'd you guys
hide your phones?
Oh, you know,
in my underwear.
Did you hear that?
So hot!
Will you shut up?
[laughing]
[SHOU]
But she said her panties!
[TSUBASA]
That's seriously hot!
[ROMAN]
Ta-dah!
It looks legit. Nice job.
After I put the phone in,
I closed it up with tape.
Here!
[KOTAROU]
Good.
Now I'll be ready in case
she sends me an answer.
[MIU] Move the camera
more towards the right.
Here?
Uh, higher up.
'Kay, uh, like this?
[STUDENT 4A] That's the god
of relationship success!
Hey, do you think
"semi-good" is good or bad?
So mine says, "Your luck
ends where your money ends."
What does that even mean?
Sounds like Nagahara to me!
Cool!
Looks like you got
a really good one!
Yeah.
[CHINATSU]
Akane!
There you are.
Wanna get some souvenirs
for the track team?
Oh, good idea.
How many are there?
Think it's eight, right?
[CHINATSU]
Yep! What should we get?
[AKANE]
How about handkerchiefs?
[CHINATSU] Come on,
they're not old people.
[AKANE]
Maybe keychains, then?
[CHINATSU] Yeah,
and snacks for the boys.
[CHINATSU giggles]
[AKANE gasps]
Hey, Curly- kun !
--What?
--Pick one.
--What for?
--I just need a guy's opinion.
[KOTAROU]
Hmm. Let's see.
Maybe the bigger one?
[CHINATSU laughs]
Typical!
[laughing]
We're choosing
gifts for our club.
Ah, now I get it.
Yeah, and you know
how much boys can eat.
[CHINATSU]
What do you prefer?
[KOTAROU]
Uh, why?
[CHINATSU]
Y'know, for reference.
--[KOTAROU] Anything.
--[CHINATSU] Oh, come on.
But candy is cool, too.
[RYOUKO]
You have ten minutes!
[SETSUKO]
Only ten minutes?
[chattering]
Tiny tub alert.
I'll just grab a shower.
Ew, I found
someone's underwear!
Is there a name on them?
Aw, man, I think
I've gained weight.
What's the damage?
It's none of
your dumb business!
--[ROMAN] Come on! So close!
--[DAICHI] Aw, crap, no fair!
[DAICHI]
You're totally cheating!
[ROMAN]
Special combo technique!
[laughs]
--[DAICHI] I can do this.
--[ROMAN] Take this, sucker!
[DAICHI]
Shoot, I'm gonna die!
[ROMAN laughs]
Dude, I'm owning you!
[DAICHI]
Stop bragging so much.
Aw, check out this sweet move!
[ROMAN]
What was that?
--[SETSUKO] She's gone.
--[MIU] Finally.
[AIRA]
We're clear?
--[MIU] Yes.
--[SETSUKO] Ten-four.
[AIRA laughing]
[GIRLS laughing]
[SETSUKO]
That's hilarious!
[MIU]
It's not that funny.
'Kay, next!
Akane's turn.
But why me?
Who do you like?
You crushing on anyone?
There is this one guy.
I guess.
[GIRLS]
Huh?!
Shut up! Who is it? Tell us!
--[AIRA] Oh, Hira?
--[AKANE] Huh?
Ah!
Ooh, did he ask
you out or something?
--Hira's so cool.
--For real!
Come on, lay off, guys.
But I--
[footsteps]
Man, that was way close!
We almost got busted!
I don't know about this.
What are you clowns
doing in here?
[TSUBASA]
Visiting.
Why, are you mad?
[AIRA] Because we'll get in
trouble if you bozos get caught!
[MIU]
Go back to your own room.
[overlapping chatter]
[AIRA]
Get out!
[DAICHI]
I am unstoppable!
Prepare to be destroyed!
--[DAICHI] Yes!
--[ROMAN] Seriously?
--[DAICHI] Go, go go, go!
--[ROMAN] No! Block it!
[chattering]
[DAICHI] Okay, but let's see
you dodge this one.
[DAICHI, ROMAN chattering]
[chatter continues]
[KOTAROU gasps]
Hey!
[ROMAN laughing]
Whatcha doin'?
[KOTAROU]
Roman!
[ROMAN] Come on!
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
Leave me alone! Stop!
[ROMAN]
Got it! Tag, you're it!
[DAICHI]
Okay.
Ogasawara Buster!
[KOTAROU]
Daichi, stop!
Cut it out, guys!
[ROMAN]
There's a passcode.
[DAICHI]
Probably his birthday.
[KOTAROU] I'm not kidding!
I said let go!
[ROMAN]
All right, I'm in!
--[ROMAN] It's a girl?!
--[KOTAROU yelling]
[ROMAN whines]
[KOTAROU whines]
[HIDAKA] Hey, what are
you still doing up?
[HIDAKA]
I'll take that.
[KOTAROU gasps]
[sighs]
Listen up, you have free time
now until later tonight.
A few final reminders.
Stay safe and make good choices.
Have fun, but not too much fun!
You're representing
our entire school,
so be on your
best behavior today!
Do I make myself
perfectly clear?
Hey, where's Setsuko at?
She's off with Nagahara.
[AIRA sighs]
Well, where to, then?
--What about Tsubasa?
--Ugh, forget him.
[MIU]
Wanna come with us, Akane?
Well, uh...
[AIRA]
Very suspicious!
[AKANE laughs, sighs]
Are you keeping secrets from us?
Not at all.
My parents were just
asking about souvenirs.
[laughs]
Oh, well that makes sense.
Do you wanna hang
with us, then?
Uh, sure.
[KOTAROU]
Uh...
Let's go hit up the gift shops.
We should use the bus.
I heard it's actually faster.
Hey, Kota.
Let's go, man!
[AIRA]
I'm cool with it.
[MIU]
Awesome, it's this way.
--[AIRA] Okay.
--[MIU] I'm excited!
Uhh...!
Oh, have you heard about these?
They're supposed to be
great for your skin.
Hey, um...
There's something I need to do.
Like what?
Some shopping.
We'll come with you.
Which store?
Umm...
You can tell us.
Yeah, we're your friends.
I'm... getting a drink.
--A date?
--Why would she lie about that?
Beats the heck out of me.
Something wrong?
Come on, you can tell us.
What's wrong?
Jeez, enough!
Let's split up.
Does that work for you?
Come on, Miu.
--This way. C'mon.
--[MIU gasps]
[MIU]
We'll see you later...
Come on...
[panting]
[AKANE sighs]
[AOI] Didn't you say you
were gonna train on this trip?
[CHINATSU]
Aw, why'd you bring that up?
[KOTAROU gasps]
[GIRLS laugh]
[CHINATSU]
I think you misunderstood me.
[laughing]
[AOI]
I doubt it.
[CHINATSU]
How dare you.
[AKANE]
He's not answering.
[MALE STUDENT 4A]
It's really pouring.
[STUDENT 4B]
I know! [laughs]
--Jeez, you're drenched!
--It's not that bad.
Here, let me dry you off.
Hey, that tickles!
[AKANE]
We aren't even dating.
I never even gave him an answer.
Why should he meet me?
[KOTAROU]
Wait up!
[CHINATSU]
Oh, it's Curly- kun .
[AOI]
What's up?
You scared the snot out of me.
I thought you were
a thug or something.
Ah! You're way soaked!
What happened?
It's fine!
Want me to wait for you?
No, I'll just catch up later.
So what's up?
Well, uh, the thing is...
Can I please borrow your phone?
Uh, sure.
Here you go.
[KOTAROU]
Shoot, I don't know her number.
Should I ask her
to give it to me?
Is that dumb?
[KOTAROU]
I can't, i-it's just too weird.
Uh, nevermind.
[CHINATSU]
Gee, I bet I can guess.
Akane?
Uh...!
I never said it was Akane!
[laughing]
It's not like you had to.
Oh, nevermind, just forget it.
So, we're calling Akane?
[KOTAROU] Yes, if it's
not too much trouble!
Hello? Hey, hold on.
Here ya go.
Uh, hi, there.
[AKANE]
Huh? Who's this?
It's Azumi.
[AKANE]
But why?
[KOTAROU]
It's a long story.
[AKANE]
I don't get it.
I was waiting.
[KOTAROU groans]
So, where are you?
[panting]
You're pretty late.
I know.
[AKANE] You told me
to meet you here.
And then you didn't show up.
It's raining and you
didn't answer your phone...
[KOTAROU]
I'm sorry.
The teacher confiscated
my phone last night.
[AKANE] Why'd you use
Chinatsu's phone?
You must be really
close, I guess.
[KOTAROU]
She was just there.
That so?
[KOTAROU]
What is?
Oh, never mind.
I don't know!
I don't know.
We can barely talk
to each other.
Yeah.
[AKANE]
I want...
...to talk with you.
To know you better.
[KOTAROU]
Is that...
...your answer?
[AKANE]
Yes.
Wow! She's so beautiful!
[RYOUKO chuckles]
Aren't maikos the
coolest, Miss Ryouko?
Well, they just don't
appeal to me that much.
[footsteps]
Hm?
I'm Roman, the maiko.
[RYOUKO yelling]
[RYOUKO]
Whoa! She's friggin' gorgeous!
Let me just get my camera!
Stay right there!
Hey, let's go somewhere fun.
Okay. I know a great spot. Heh.
[SETSUKO] Wow, he's actually
being dependable for once.
I can't believe that
Nagahara's trying to make
this school trip
so special for us.
He's so wonderful!
[SHOU] You see,
a school trip is special.
Don't you agree?
[SETSUKO groans]
This is a friggin' hotel.
[SHOU]
Shoot!
I didn't bring enough cash!
This is the worst.
Darn. Oh, well,
we should head back.
Sorry, Setsuko.
Would you spot me?
Huh?!
[SHOU] Can you put
a price on memories?
[SETSUKO]
He is such a loser.