[STUDENT 9A]
Exams suck!
I'm so sick of them. Ugh!
Hey! Picked a school?
Not yet.
Daichi?
They say beggars
can't be choosers.
I'll go wherever they'll
accept my grades.
[ROMAN, KOTAROU laughing]
Well, I know what I'm gonna do.
--[DAICHI] What's your idea?
--[KOTAROU] Yeah?
Modeling!
Aiming kinda high, huh?
You're just jealous!
[BOYS laughing]
[DAICHI]
Of what? Your ugly mug?
[ROMAN]
Bring it on!
[DAICHI]
Ah! Ow! That hurts!
[KOTAROU]
High school, huh.
Are your parents
coming to the fall meet?
Yeah, I assume so.
Your parents always go, Akane.
My folks said they're
coming this time.
Whoa, talk about embarrassing.
I know, right?
Wow, sucks for you guys.
[CHINATSU] Maybe I'll get
new shoes for the meet.
[AKANE]
Good idea.
[CHINATSU]
Hmm.
These are starting
to wear down.
Hey, wait, do you
think you guys
will still do track once
you're in high school?
I don't know yet.
Me either, but probably.
[CHINATSU]
Oh, yeah?
Well, first we have to
finish these dumb exams.
[door opens]
Sorry I'm late.
[chuckles] It's fine.
Have you picked
a high school yet?
Yeah. Me neither.
You like private?
Or public?
Probably public.
Uh, cool.
My sister goes to
a private high school.
All girls?
[AKANE]
Mm-hmm.
Will you go there?
I really don't know.
Let's go to high school...
...together.
[KOTAROU]
Mmm...
But that might be hard.
Why's that?
Your grades are
way better than mine.
Nuh-uh.
Still though, at least we
live close to each other.
[door opens]
[DAISUKE]
Oh, Akane!
Good to see ya.
Hello there, Daisuke.
Thank you for watching
the shop for me.
Here, this is for you.
Cool, thanks!
So did you find the
record you wanted?
Yeah, but only
after I went to like
three different places first.
[phone game music]
[AKANE] When do you want
to meet with my teacher?
Anytime works for me.
I can't decide on a high school.
Tough choice?
That's an understatement.
Can you clear off
the table for dinner?
--[AKANE] Sure.
--[HIROSHI] Right, listen up.
I have a very important
announcement to make, so...
What is it?
--Here's the thing...
--Hey, I'm home from school.
[SAORI]
How was your day?
[AKANE]
Welcome home.
[HIROSHI]
Hi, Ayane.
Oh, yeah.
I'm probably getting
transferred at work,
back to the main office.
[AKANE gasps]
We're moving?
Jeez, again?
It's a possibility;
nothing's certain yet.
Well, I guess it is
about that time again.
[AYANE]
The office in Chiba?
[HIROSHI]
That's right.
But this is all
happening so fast.
Hey, Tokyo's close to Chiba,
so maybe we could live there!
Well, at least you're excited.
[SAORI] Dinner's ready,
so put your stuff away
and go get changed.
'Kay.
So if we do move to Chiba,
where will we go?
Maybe the Ichikawa area?
Nice, that'll be super
close to my school.
We're so far now. Hang in there.
Aww. What should I do?
Oh, I guess you don't
know any Chiba schools.
[SAORI]
Now that I think about it,
I've heard good things
about Koumei High School.
Koumei?
Yes, I heard about
it in yoga class.
The instructor has a daughter
who goes to that school
and she absolutely adores it.
Oh, and I heard they're
really big on clubs, as well.
You said Koumei High, right?
It's this one.
[KITAMURA]
You lack the talent.
I don't think serious
literature is your forte,
but you know,
there's a big market
for light novels.
Maybe you should try
your hand at writing one.
[sighs]
[JUNKO]
Kotarou? Dinner's ready.
So, practice today?
[KOTAROU]
Mm-hmm.
[JUNKO]
Speaking of...
Any ideas yet?
On a high school?
[sighs]
I hate to rain on your parade,
but I'm afraid you're not
taking your education seriously.
Not to mention,
you barely cracked open a book
over the summer break.
Are you listening?
Honestly.
Dear, aren't you going
to try and talk some sense
into your son?
I won't, not in the
middle of dinner.
You can't be serious!
Am I the only person
who cares at all?
He's not studying!
He hasn't even chosen
a high school yet!
[RYUUNOSUKE] I'm sure Kotarou
is thinking about it.
I have no idea what
he's thinking about!
He's just delaying his problems.
He needs to decide what he's
going to do with his future.
[taiko drums, music playing]
[KOTAROU]
Let's see.
[DAISUKE]
What's up?
You seem out of it.
Oh, well, uh, it's nothing.
Daisuke?
[DAISUKE]
Yeah?
Have you heard of light novels?
I do run a bookstore.
I meant like have you read one?
[DAISUKE]
A few.
Were they any good?
Hmm. Well, it depends.
A few of them were pretty cool,
but there were others
I didn't really like.
Like all books.
What's up?
Someone recommended them.
If that's the case,
why not read one yourself?
So you can form
your own opinion.
[TAIKO CLASS 9A]
Daisuke!
[DAISUKE]
Coming!
[AKANE groans]
[phone chimes]
[KOTAROU chuckles]
Aww.
[AKANE]
Huh...
[sighs]
Right.
Good luck!
Dad and I will be
cheering for you.
See you later.
It's time.
Good luck.
[BOY 9A]
When do you run?
[BOY 9B]
Later.
Let's get a program.
[BOY 9A]
I'm not made of money.
[BOY 9B]
That's a shame.
[KOTAROU]
Um, I'll take one please.
[phone vibrates]
[starting pistol fires]
[chuckles]
Okay.
[CROWD cheering]
[HIRA] They're lining up
for the girl's 100-meter soon.
[CHINATSU]
Let's go, Akane!
[TRACK TEAM 9A]
You can do it!
Yeah!
Knock 'em dead!
Good luck!
You'd better cheer for us!
[TRACK TEAM 9A, 9B]
Right!
[HIROSHI]
Oh! There she is!
Akane!
[SAORI]
Go get 'em, honey!
[ANNOUNCER 9A] The first
group competing in the girl's
100-meter dash,
please progress
to the starting point.
[STARTER 9A]
On your mark!
Set!
[starting pistol fires]
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 9A] Group two, please
proceed to the starting point.
[STARTER 9A]
On your mark.
Set!
[starting pistol fires]
[cheering]
All right!
That's a new personal record!
[CHINATSU]
Great job, Akane!
[BOY 9C]
Man, it's hot.
Let's get a soda.
I think the boys
run next, right?
Pretty sure.
Congrats on your new record.
Thanks, Aoi!
Aw, thank you, Mom.
You okay?
Yeah.
[CHINATSU]
It's over, huh?
[AKANE]
Yeah.
[CHINATSU]
This is our last race together.
[AOI]
Hey, don't even start.
--[CHINATSU] Sorry.
--[AOI] I'm serious.
We ran so much together.
You're gonna make
me cry, Chinatsu.
And we hung out.
Come on now, quit it.
[AKANE crying]
--You crying?
--I'm not!
Akane.
I just want to thank you.
Oh, not you, too.
Y'know, I would've given
up if it hadn't been
for you guys.
Don't cry.
[crying]
Way to go.
[GIRLS crying]
[crying continues]
[HIRA chuckles]
It's not funny.
Sorry, but your nose
is like bright red.
[CHINATSU laughs]
It is.
Mine too, huh?
A little.
[laughing]
So, track club.
Will you do it? In high school?
Well, are you?
Oh, yeah.
I'm not sure, but probably.
After all,
I really love running.
Well, if you're serious,
pick a good school.
One of the competitive ones--
they have better equipment.
That's what I heard anyway.
Which ones are competitive?
Let's see, Tokorozawa Sakae,
or Saitama Academy.
Ah.
It's a long commute
if I move, though.
[HIRA gasps]
[AKANE gasps]
But, I mean, nothing's
set in stone yet!
Please don't tell anyone.
Uh...
Which area?
Chiba, maybe around
the Ichikawa area.
I see.
I've heard Koumei's a good
school around those parts.
You could probably get in with
a good recommendation.
You really think so?
My mom said it
was a good school.
I guess.
You're really moving?
I said I'm not sure.
[TRACK TEAM 9E]
Mizuno!
The coach wanted to see you.
Uh, right.
[CHINATSU]
And then?
[AOI]
She just started talking to me.
[CHINATSU]
Seriously?
[AKANE]
Oh.
Uh, I think we met
at another track meet.
But you remember her?
[AOI]
Kind of.
[AKANE]
That's so cool.
[CHINATSU chuckles]
Sounds like you've got a rival!
[laughing]
[HIRA]
Listen.
What's up?
Let's go to the
Kawagoe Festival.
The one next month.
Sounds fun.
Like as a club. Sound good?
I'll go.
Are you sure, Akane?
Uh, Azumi.
He's in the festival.
Oh, that's right.
'Kay, great.
I guess that settles it.
Okay.
Let's hit up the food stalls.
My battery's almost dead.
[CHINATSU]
This isn't like you.
Inviting the club out
for a group outing.
Yeah, so?
It'll be fun.
[CHINATSU]
Hmm...
Hey, Hira?
Have you given up?
On what?
The thing is...
I haven't even really tried yet.
[CHINATSU]
I understand.
[AKANE]
That video is so funny!
It's not like you can
change how you feel.
[GIRLS laughing]
[knock on door]
[RYUUNOSUKE]
Can I come in?
[KOTAROU]
Uh, yeah, sure.
So listen...
About high school...
It doesn't have to
be anything fancy.
It's just I want you to be happy
and do what you love.
Don't stress too much.
Well, good talk.
[yawns]
[gasps]
[AYANE]
What?
Uh... Nothing, sorry.
[AYANE growls]
[phone chimes]
I'm telling you,
when it comes to a guy,
you've gotta have
high standards.
He needs to be smart, kind,
super good-looking,
and preferably rich.
[KASAI]
Truck coming through!
This should only take
a few minutes; pardon us.
[AYANE]
So hot!
And that's how
I met my boyfriend!
Huh...
Forget all that other stuff;
those muscles are legit.
In Kyoto, twice.
No way!
[YASUHITO]
Who paid for the room?
Her parents are loaded.
You're the man!
Yeah, for real!
I know, right?
[laughing]
[SETSUKO]
In Kyoto, we went twice.
--[AIRA] No way.
--[MIU] Ew!
[MIU]
Who paid?
My parents are loaded.
That cheapskate!
What a pathetic loser.
I know, right?