We're here!
Dome City!
[HIRA]
It's pretty crowded.
[AKANE]
Yeah, I know.
[BOTH laugh]
Let's ride on
the Thunder Dolphin!
Check it out!
I looked up the rides online.
There's a giant Ferris wheel,
and a bunch of cool
roller coasters, too!
[ROMAN laughs]
We're a pretty big group, huh?
Maybe too big of a group.
[AKANE]
The amusement park?
Yeah, my parents
gave me free passes.
That sounds fun!
I'll invite Azumi,
and Hira can be our fourth.
Dome City?
Me too! I wanna go!
I don't have enough passes.
Uh, well, we'll pay
for ourselves, right?
I can't go, I've got a
practice match that day.
I'll be in Hawaii.
Let's invite Nagahara
and Tsubasa.
Yeah, that's a great idea!
[SETSUKO]
I can't wait!
[AKANE laughs nervously]
[GROUP screaming]
[AKANE] A big group just
makes it more fun, right?
[RIDE ATTENDANT 7A]
Are there any single riders
waiting in line
who want to go now?
[ROMAN]
Ooh, ooh! Me, me!
Sorry, not sorry!
[RIDE ATTENDANT 7A]
Viva off you go!
Have a safe trip!
Okay.
--We'd be one over.
--Someone's a little excited.
Please pick a platform and
wait for the next car.
Make sure to stand
behind the white line
while the other riders unload.
Hey, Azumi, let's ride together!
[overlapping chatter]
[RIDE ATTENDANT 7A]
Viva off you go!
Have a safe trip!
[SETSUKO]
Oh, crap, the ride is starting!
No... oh, no!
Oh, no, oh, no, oh, no!
Hey, what's the matter?
Just don't say it!
Oh, wow, we're so high up!
[AKANE]
I told you not to say it!
[HIRA]
Oops, sorry!
[CHINATSU]
Hey, Azumi!
Are you scared
of roller coasters?
Uh, not really.
We should totally shout,
"Viva! Dome City!" on the drop.
Here we go!
Get ready!
--[GROUP screams]
--[CHINATSU] Viva Dome City!
[laughing]
Viva welcome back!
We hope you enjoyed the ride.
[SETSUKO]
That ride was insane!
I got super scared
on that first drop,
but after that it was kinda fun!
That was awesome! [laughing]
[AKANE groans]
I can't believe you
screamed the whole time.
It was scarier than
I thought it would be.
[AKANE gasps]
You okay?
Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
[SETSUKO]
So, where to next?
I think shopping sounds
kinda fun, right? [laughs]
[SETSUKO] Actually, I think I
wanna go on that ride again!
We haven't gone on
any of the other rides!
Wimp!
Akane, you feeling okay?
Yeah, I'm better now.
[CHINATSU]
Did you get sick?
A little.
There you guys are!
Wow, you look great.
[KOTAROU]
Huh?
Totally!
For real?
You should buy that.
[KOTAROU]
Not likely.
[AIRA]
Oh, my gosh, that's so you!
Akane, you should
try one on, too!
[SETSUKO]
Come over here.
[AIRA]
That is too perfect!
One sec.
Say cheese!
[AKANE, HIRA gasp]
[AIRA]
Interesting.
[SETSUKO]
Right?
What is?
It's nothing!
Looks purr-fect.
Yeah, I'll pass.
[HIRA laughs]
[TSUBASA]
Huh? Where'd Roman go?
[AIRA] You and Setsuko
should get matching hats!
[SHOU]
And mess up my hair?
[KOTAROU]
He was right here.
[RIDE ATTENDANT 7B] Is there
anyone in the line that wants
to ride alone?
Oh, that's me!
He's missing?
I guess.
[KOTAROU]
I'll go look for him.
'Kay.
[KOTAROU sighs]
[CHINATSU]
Hey, Curly- kun !
[CHINATSU panting]
Did you find Roman?
No. [sighs]
Where is he?
[CHINATSU]
Oh, wanna see something cool?
It's our picture.
[KOTAROU laughs]
What the heck?
[CHINATSU laughs] Well, I
thought it'd be a fun souvenir.
Seriously? This pic?
What's wrong with it?
[KOTAROU] For starters,
your eyes are closed, Nishio.
Call me Chinatsu.
Everyone else does, it's fine.
Yeah, I know, but still...
I said it's fine,
and I'll call you Kota.
Kota! Kota!
[laughing]
[CHINATSU]
Okay, now you say my name.
[KOTAROU]
Chi--China--
[CHINATSU laughing]
It's not rocket science.
--[CHINATSU] Try again.
--[KOTAROU] I should find Roman.
[AKANE]
Hey.
Everyone's lining up
for the next ride.
[CHINATSU]
Oh, okay. Let's go.
[KOTAROU]
Uh...
[KOTAROU sighs]
[phone chimes]
[KOTAROU]
What?!
[KOTAROU panting]
[bell dings]
[NURSE 7A]
Yes?
[KOTAROU] Uh, hi, I'm here
to see Roman Yamashina.
[NURSE 7A]
Right! Come in.
Excuse me.
Hey, there.
[KOTAROU]
Roman, what happened?
Uh, heatstroke?
[NURSE 7A] Yes, which is exactly
why you need to stay hydrated.
[ROMAN]
'Kay.
[NURSE 7A] Why don't you
rest up here for a little bit?
[ROMAN]
Yes, ma'am.
[NURSE 7A] Make sure you both
drink plenty of water today.
Right.
[sighs]
You had me worried.
[sighs] I'm sorry,
guess I got carried away.
[KOTAROU]
Don't worry about it.
We can go soon.
[ROMAN]
Something wrong?
Just some stuff.
Ah, girl stuff.
--Say what?
--It's Mizuno.
Uh...
You guys dating?
You knew?
Oh, I had a hunch.
Jeez, sucks you can't be alone.
I've got an idea.
Get lost, like in the park.
Seriously?
[ROMAN] Okay, so first
I'll give Mizuno a call.
[ROMAN]
Hold up.
[GROUP screaming]
I don't understand;
where did they all go?
Relax, we'll find them.
[HIRA]
Here.
Thanks, Hira.
[HIRA chuckles]
Don't worry about it.
I feel bad though.
It's my treat.
No, I've got it.
Wow, you're like an old lady.
Ugh. Fine, I'll just keep it.
[TSUBASA] Man, that show
really takes me back.
I felt like I was
a little kid again!
I was cheering so loud.
Get this, I bet you
didn't know the Big O
has a diameter of 60 meters.
--[CHINATSU] Curly- kun !
--[TSUBASA] Height is 80 meters.
[SHOU]
Wow, you are such a nerd.
[KOTAROU]
Where's Mizuno?
Dude, give them some space.
Yeah, man.
They're so cute.
Think he'll make a move?
[SETSUKO]
Duh! He'd be crazy not to.
--[AIRA] I know, right?
--[SETSUKO] Look at this video!
--[AIRA] Cute!
--[GIRLS laughing]
[SETSUKO]
I mean, it's a surfing cat!
The caption says "meowabunga!"
--[AKANE gasps]
--[BOY 7A] Sorry.
[GIRL 7A] You never watch
where you're going.
You okay?
Let's take a break.
Oh, uh...
Huh?
[KOTAROU]
Mizuno!
Back off. Okay?
[AKANE gasps]
She's my girlfriend.
We're going out.
[GROUP screaming]
Um, seriously?
[AKANE]
Mm-hmm.
Let's go, Mizuno.
Right.
[CHINATSU crying]
[GROUP screaming]
Is our group shrinking?
We keep losing people.
I just left a message on LINE.
[HIRA]
Tsubasa.
--What?
--Where's Mizuno?
--Can I ask you something?
--[TSUBASA] Hm?
Do you know if Mizuno's...
dating someone?
--Huh?!
--Are you gonna ask her out?
--Adorable!
Azumi.
--Huh?!
[ROMAN]
Yep, they're going out.
What? Are you serious?
That's news to me!
[SETSUKO]
I can't believe this!
[AIRA]
And Roman knew before we did!
[SETSUKO]
When did this happen?!
Um...
I'm sorry. About Hira.
Mm-mm.
Don't be. It's the truth.
[BOTH chuckle]
[sighs] I'm kinda hungry.
I am, too.
Where'd everyone go?
Wait a minute.
Not just yet.
Okay, I'll text the group.
[KOTAROU, AKANE]
Thanks for the food.
[BOTH chuckle]
Come to think of it...
...this is technically
our first meal together.
I guess so.
[AKANE giggles]
[KOTAROU]
Here we go!
[AKANE screaming]
Jeez, I'm soaking wet!
We're barely in this picture.
Ah, really?
Let's try again.
Okay, here goes.
[camera clicks]
You startled me.
Sorry about that.
How did it turn out?
[KOTAROU]
Ah.
Yeah. It's much better.
[AKANE]
It's like...
[KOTAROU]
Looks good.
[AKANE] ...we really do
look like we're going out.
That we do.
[SETSUKO]
Over here!
[CHINATSU]
Sorry. I'm kinda late.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Chinatsu?
Check out my awesome hat!
Not right now!
Have you guys seen Akane?
She's off with Azumi.
Yeah, they're apparently dating.
Ah. 'Kay.
Now I get it.
[AIRA]
Azumi?
You okay? Hey.
Do you wanna go
watch the fireworks?
[CHINATSU]
Mm-hmm.
Sorry, that totally sucks.
Yeah, we were surprised, too.
[fireworks boom]
It's almost over.
Let's come back.
Just us two.
Yeah.
[GIRL 7B]
They're kissing!
[MOTHER 7A]
Stop pointing!
[BOTH laugh]
Hira?
What's up?
I'm sorry for inviting you.
Why's that?
'Cause. I'm just sorry.
[HIRA]
It's fine.
I'm not mad at you.
[KOTAROU snoring]
[AKANE]
Sorry.
[SAKURA grunts]
[SAKURA]
What was that?
Did he bump into me on purpose?
I bet he did it
because he likes me.
How immature!
He should just own
up to his feelings.
Apparently, Ogasawara
gets good grades,
and he's a favorite
among the teachers.
He's pretty well to do,
not to mention
he's got muscles for days!
All in all, he's a great catch.
Any girl would be
lucky to have him!
Unfortunately, he's like
way too focused on judo.
[STUDENTS (SONG)] ♪ A light
illuminates the mountain tops. ♪
♪ See how it sets
them all ablaze. ♪
--Look!
--That's seriously hot.
Boys are stupid.
[MIU] Come on, it's not
like you can blame them.
[AIRA]
Yeah, Miss Ryouko's way pretty.
Ugh, maybe for a teacher.
Hmm. You know what?
I think I liked our old
music teacher better
than Miss Ryouko.
I feel the same way.
But I mean, it's not like
I hate her or anything.
There's just something
about her.
Something...
...annoying.
[GIRLS laugh]
[AIRA]
Exactly.
[BOYS inhale]
She smells so amazing!
Oh, man, our teacher must
be some kind of goddess!
[SETSUKO, MIU growl]
[SETSUKO]
Boys are stupid.
[MIU] I thought it was against
the rules for teachers
to wear perfume.
Too much perfume is trashy.
You're absolutely right, Aira.
I found the type
of perfume she uses.
Does that say soap scent?
Really? How childish.
Yeah.
--[MIU] I wanna try.
--[SETSUKO] I got next.
[AIRA]
Stop hogging it!
[GIRLS inhale]
Wow, that smells heavenly!
[MIU] It's nice,
but not overwhelming.
I might buy one.
[AKANE]
Hey, check this out!
[AIRA]
What?
Wait, isn't that Miss Ryouko?
The caption says,
"Charming Women Spotted
Around Town."
I've heard of this website;
it's like super popular!
I can't believe they tagged her!
[MIU] I saw you on
that website, Miss Ryouko!
[overlapping chatter]
[SHOU] Since when did the
girls like her so much?
[TSUBASA]
Beats me.
I wanna break up.
But why?
Well, for one thing,
it's because...
...you never listen to me.
You're cheap and you just
wanna mess around all the time.
Okay, fine, let's talk about it.
[SHOU] This looks like
a great place to chat.
[SETSUKO growls]
I knew it was too
good to be true.
What a loser.
Sorry, can you pay?
You're a total jerk!
[AIRA] So Setsuko
finally dumped Nagahara.
[MIU]
Wow!
Wait, that would mean
the biggest player
in class is single, and
potentially heartbroken.
Maybe he's actually
a super sensitive guy
with a heart of gold
and a soft spot
for cute animals.
What if I'm the only one
who can bring out
his more sensitive side?
"Weird, this is the
first time we've talked,
but it feels like we've
known each other forever."
"Yes, it must be destiny!"
And then, the two of us
fall madly in love!
[BOYS laughing]
[SAKURA]
Nah, that fantasy's dumb.