When did you get
a boyfriend, Akane?
Miu just messaged
me about it, so--
Why Miu?
Oh, we were in the same
class a few years ago.
--News gets around.
--Man...
Yeah, well, it must be
if I'm starting to get
messages about it.
Geez, school check-in
will be rough.
[CHINATSU] You're gonna
get so much attention.
[AOI]
It's next week right?
August 19th?
[CHINATSU]
Yep, it sure is.
[AOI]
Ugh. School is such a pain.
[taiko drums playing]
Right, let's take a break.
[KOTAROU sighs]
[KOTAROU]
Dazai once said,
"There is such a thing
as love in this world.
I'm sure of it.
It's the expression
and the etiquette
that makes love
so hard to find."
Whoa, seriously? No way!
It's true. Azumi and
Mizuno are a thing now.
Jeez, crazy!
I know, right?
No fair.
--I'm so jealous.
--He's so lucky.
[ROMAN laughs]
Kota! You're famous!
Well hey, you little player!
[ROMAN, DAICHI laugh]
[DAICHI] How dare you go
and get a girlfriend?
Way to go, tiger!
--Hey.
--[AIRA] You're here!
Hey!
[AIRA]
Come on!
[AKANE]
Why?
[MIU]
Ugh, just come on!
So what's the deal, Akane?
[AKANE]
With what?
Why'd you pick Azumi?
Jeez, Miu, talk about rude!
It's not rude!
Just kind of surprised, is all.
Sorry.
What is it you like about him?
Well, uh...
[SETSUKO laughs]
Nothing?
[AIRA]
Well, there has to be something.
It's hard to describe.
Know what I mean?
[GIRLS]
Huh?
You do like him, right?
I seriously thought
you'd end up with Hira.
--[SETSUKO] Me too.
--[AIRA] For real.
Well, no more secrets, okay?
'Kay.
Let us know if he kisses you.
Do you think he
could actually do it?
[AIRA]
No!
[GIRLS laugh]
If you're already done
with your summer homework,
go ahead and put it on my desk.
We're already halfway
through the summer break,
so if you haven't
finished your work,
then you need to get on it.
[STUDENTS chattering]
You going home together?
She has club.
So wait for her, then!
You have club too, right?
[ROMAN]
Mm-hmm.
[KOTAROU gasps]
[KOTAROU]
Mizuno!
I have club, so why don't
we walk home together?
[chuckles]
[TRACK TEAM 8A]
Get ready, set, go!
[AOI]
It's hot today.
[CHINATSU]
I'm literally starving.
[AOI]
Let's go get some food then.
[CHINATSU]
Let's get ice cream!
[AOI]
That sounds pretty tempting.
--Which shop?
--[CHINATSU] Let me think.
[AKANE]
Sorry, guys, it's just...
Got plans?
[AKANE]
Mm-hmm.
With Azumi?
Well, have fun.
Later.
[CHINATSU]
She's so lucky.
[AOI] Why? Boyfriends
are such a hassle.
[CHINATSU]
Huh?
[AOI]
I don't get the appeal.
Hi, Akane.
Akane.
--Thank you for the food.
Ah! That hits the spot!
You sound like my dad.
Whatever, it's hot.
How's your club going?
Awesome, just busy.
I can only imagine.
What about you?
We're kinda lax.
[KOTAROU] But I'm busy with
summer lessons and the festival.
Ah, cram school?
Uh-huh.
[AKANE] I guess I should start
going once track season is over.
Oh, in the fall?
[AKANE]
Yeah.
Just a sec.
What's up?
[KOTAROU]
They want me to come practice.
Drum practice?
[KOTAROU]
Yep.
I wanna see!
Can I come watch?
[KOTAROU]
Sure, I guess.
Yay, cool!
Oh, would it bother you?
Not at all!
[AKANE laughs]
[DAISUKE]
Let's take it from the top.
[KOTAROU]
Right.
This is unusual.
So, who might you be?
Hello, there.
It's nice to meet you.
Oh, it's Kotarou's girl--
Shut up!
His girlfriend?
I see!
Way to go, champ! [laughs]
Here.
[KOTAROU]
You can sit here.
Thanks so much.
[taiko drums playing]
[music continues]
[DAISUKE]
How was it?
[AKANE]
Amazing!
I'd never seen it before.
I absolutely loved watching.
[DAISUKE]
Good to hear.
I hope we didn't
intrude on a date.
What? Nah.
Oh.
Have you seen Hikawa Shrine?
Uh...
[DAISUKE]
The, uh, wind chimes are up.
Oh. That sounds cool.
[DAISUKE]
It is.
Huh?
Azumi.
Here, take this.
But...
Just take it.
Wait, are you sure?
How about I finish
up things here?
[AKANE]
Sorry I'm late.
[KOTAROU]
Huh?
[AKANE] I told my mom
we were going to a festival
and she made me put it on.
[KOTAROU]
Ah.
So uh, how's it look?
It looks amazing.
So do you.
Thank you.
[AKANE] It's cool how
everything is potato themed.
I know, right? They're famous.
Interesting!
It's delicious!
We eat them a lot at my house.
Lucky.
Actually, when I was
younger I didn't like them
very much.
But now they're really good.
[AKANE chuckles]
No way! I have one of these.
Feel one. They're super
soft and squishy.
[KOTAROU chuckles]
You're right.
Now I want one!
[BOTH laugh]
[AKANE]
Look over here!
Everything's so cute!
I've always loved
more traditional styles.
Yeah?
It suits you.
[KOTAROU]
Fortunes?
[AKANE]
When's your birthday?
[KOTAROU]
Oh. It's August 7th.
[AKANE gasps]
We missed it?
[KOTAROU]
Hey, no big deal.
Yes, it is!
I'm not upset.
[AKANE]
Well, I am.
But I didn't know about it.
I would have liked
to celebrate together.
Seriously, it's fine.
I feel bad.
Honestly, I'm used to it
since it's during
summer break and all.
[AKANE]
I guess.
Excuse me,
I need to go call home.
[KOTAROU]
Right now?
So pricey.
[AKANE]
Okay, I'm back.
All done, then?
[AKANE]
Yeah.
Ready to go?
[AKANE]
They're beautiful!
I've never been here before.
Oh, wow. Seriously?
Yeah.
[AKANE] Apparently you can
write wishes on the chimes!
I'll take two, please.
[SHOP CLERK 8A]
That'll be 1000 yen.
What's your wish?
Sorry, I'm not telling.
It's embarrassing.
Wanna keep going?
Yeah.
[KOTAROU]
What's wrong?
Sorry, hold on.
I need a minute.
[KOTAROU]
Let me.
There.
[AKANE]
Um, thank you.
Shall we, then?
Uh, hang on!
Here.
It's a belated birthday present.
Thank you!
[AKANE]
Open it!
[KOTAROU chuckles]
[AKANE] Sorry,
I didn't have time to choose,
so it looks just like mine.
Don't apologize, I love it.
Wait a minute,
did you buy this earlier?
[AKANE]
Uh, yeah.
It's so awesome.
[AKANE]
I'm so glad.
I wasn't even sure when
I should give it to you
or if you'd even like it.
I couldn't stop thinking
about it, you know?
[AKANE sighs]
I was so nervous,
even when we were
looking at wind chimes,
my heart was pounding.
I'm so happy you like it.
Um, well, thanks
so much, Akane.
Uh, I--
[AKANE]
It's okay, Kotarou.
[KOTAROU laughs]
[SETSUKO] I don't think I've
ever seen you and Azumi
talk during class.
Yeah, he's a quiet guy.
Come on, Akane,
what is it you like about him?
I know Azumi might not
seem like much to you,
but I feel safe around him.
Aww!
You're different these days.
Well, they say love
can change a person.
[AIRA]
Have you kissed? Tell us!
[MIU]
No secrets, remember?
Hey. I've heard of that girl.
Yeah? Who is she?
She's like a new idol.
Y'know, for TV dramas and stuff.
Isn't she cute?
Hey, babe, why don't
you pose like this?
Ew, why would I do that?
Why not?
Uh... Okay, fine.
Like this?
Wow, I can't believe
you thought I was serious.
[AIRA whines]
You're already cute without
doing that stuff, babe.
[TSUBASA whistles]
[RYOUKO groans]
This is the worst.
Summer break is so long.
[MIU]
Jeez, there's so many people.
Ooh, I want one of those.
[YASUHITO]
I'll take two, please!
[MIU] This day would be way
more fun if I had a boyfriend.
[YASUHITO]
Wait, what the heck am I?
[DAICHI]
Hey, Kota!
[ROMAN]
Wait for us!
Huh?
Nice lip gloss!
[SAKURA]
Ew! What the heck?
Why was he staring at my lips?
Is he checking me
out or something?
Talk about creepy!
Seriously, that guy
has some nerve!
[SAKURA]
Although...
[TRACK TEAM]
One, two, three, four.
You guys call that stretching?
Come on, this is stretching!
[TRACK TEAM 8D grunting]
Okay! I'm sorry!
Oh, come on. What about me?
Yeah, we need some help, too!
[AOI]
Do it yourselves!
Wow, you sure are popular, Aoi.
Boys are such scumbags.
[RYOUKO sighs]
[groans]
[RYOUKO]
I can't wait until graduation.
[JUNKO]
What are these?
I was cleaning Kotarou's room,
and I found all of his
half-finished novels.
Oh? Did you read them?
[JUNKO] I haven't
had time to yet.
Personally, I don't think you
should read Kotarou's novels
even if you are his mother.
We should try to
respect his privacy.
[JUNKO]
If you say so.
[RYUUNOSUKE] He's really got a
good grasp on how women think.
[JUNKO] He's got a terrible
grasp on how women think.