[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
[AKANE]
Do you see your name?
[CHINATSU]
Oh, I'm in Class Three!
[AOI]
I'm in Two.
[AKANE]
There I am.
It says Class One.
Well this sucks.
We're all in different classes.
What about the track club?
None of the other
members are in my class.
[AOI]
Aww.
It's cool, at least we'll
see each other at practice.
[AKANE]
Yeah, that's true.
Maybe our club will get
some new members this year!
[KOTAROU]
Hey, watch it, man!
[CHINATSU] Shoot, I
forgot about the poster!
[ROMAN]
Hey. What's up?
--The lawyer poster?
--[CHINATSU] Uh-huh.
Did you ask her out?
Oh, I will!
Right, Akane?
[AKANE]
Today's the day...
...I start my last year
of middle school.
[SENSEI 1A] Good morning
and welcome, everyone!
Spring not only brings
about new life;
it also signals the start of
a new school year as well.
And for all of you
first year students,
I hope you're excited
for the adventures
that await you in middle school.
Know that if you need help
finding your new classes,
our excellent teachers
would be more than happy
to assist you.
It can be confusing at first.
I'm sure the second
and third year students
will set a fine example.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 1D]
Man, that was so boring.
[STUDENT 1E]
Yeah, no joke.
[AKANE]
Jeez, I'm so nervous.
Just stay calm, just stay calm.
[AKANE whimpers]
Okay.
It's so cool, the graphics
on that game's like so legit.
[KOTAROU] Even in middle school,
inequality is alive and well.
There's the upper class
and lower class.
There's the cool clubs...
...and the not-so-cool clubs.
Whether it's good looks
or good grades,
we'll use whatever tools
we can to establish
some kind of pecking order.
Oh, he just looked at us!
[ROMAN laughs]
Hey!
You sure are popular.
Unbelievable.
Huh? What is?
You know what!
Don't act innocent, player!
[ROMAN]
Here, punch like this.
[DAICHI]
Like what?
--[ROMAN] It hurts less here--
--[DAICHI] Gah!
[ROMAN]
On the back area, see?
--[DAICHI] That friggin' hurt!
--[ROMAN] Nuh-uh.
--[DAICHI] What if I hit you?
--[ROMAN] Go ahead.
[ROMAN]
Doesn't hurt.
[ROMAN, DAICHI grunting]
I said knock it off!
[AIRA]
Is that you, Akane?
This sounds crazy,
but do you remember me?
I'm Aira, we were in
third grade together!
[AKANE]
Mm-hmm.
[TSUBASA]
Hey, aren't you in track club?
Yes. Nice to meet you.
Do you know her?
[KOTAROU]
Mm-mm.
[ROMAN laughs]
Miss Ryouko's here!
[RYOUKO] Okay everyone,
settle down, please!
[bell ringing]
[AKANE] I hope we get some
new track members this year.
[CHINATSU]
Me too!
Somebody has to replace
us when we graduate.
That's right!
Let's go be awesome!
--Awesome!
--[AKANE] Hey, look up there!
[AKANE]
It says "Souper" wanted!
[GROUP laughs]
[AOI]
Spell check fail!
[laughing]
[CHINATSU]
Now I want soup!
[laughing]
[AKANE]
Now I'm hungry!
--[ROMAN] Kota!
--[DAICHI] Kotarou!
[DAICHI]
See ya tomorrow!
[ROMAN]
Let me read your book soon!
[KOTAROU]
Fat chance, Roman!
Hey, I'm taking the key.
[CHINATSU]
Get ready, go!
Yo Akane, your arms!
You've got this!
Keep going, Mizuno!
[AKANE panting]
[AKANE]
I'm home!
[SAORI]
Welcome home, dear.
Hey there.
Hey, Mom and Dad said we're
going out to eat tonight.
Yay! I'm so excited!
[SAORI]
Do you want to freshen up?
[AKANE]
I probably should.
Honey, turn that
off so we can go.
Yes, dear.
Right, I'll try and
hurry up, then.
[WOMAN 1A]
Welcome! Table for four?
Jeez, you're always
on your phone.
Awesome work, Captain Obvious.
Who are you talking to?
I got us a couple
of glasses of water.
Thanks, dear.
Did you want one, Kotarou?
I'll use the drink bar.
I'd prefer you get
tea or something.
[HIROSHI]
Don't go crazy.
She's a growing girl.
I'm not made of
money, you know.
So, what are you getting?
Probably just pasta salad.
Huh? Is that it?
[chattering]
[AYANE]
You aren't made of money.
[HIROSHI]
It's my money!
[chattering]
[HIROSHI] I'm a grown
man and if I want beer
then I'll get beer!
You're my daughter, not my boss!
[chattering]
[SAORI]
I just can't make up my mind.
Gratin and lasagna
both sound like
they'd be delicious.
Now... Think about
your cholesterol.
Just pick something.
[HIROSHI]
Don't rush me.
That sounds good.
[RYUUNOSUKE] Kotarou,
are you ordering a drink?
He said he was going
to use the drink bar.
Hey, Honey, would you
press that button for me?
[JUNKO]
Sure thing.
Kotarou, are you listening?
Yes, ma'am, I'm going.
[KOTAROU]
Osamu Dazai was a writer.
He once said,
"How excruciatingly
arduous and unbearable
it is to live."
He must have been talking
about middle schoolers.
[SAORI] Want me to order
you sautéed spinach, Akane?
It's filled with lots of iron.
[AYANE]
That's gonna stink later.
[JUNKO]
Oh, thank you.
[SAORI] You have a
track meet soon, right?
Spinach is great for
your digestive system.
Mom, please stop it.
[SAORI]
Why? What did I do?
Ha! The poor lil piggie!
[AKANE] I'm going to
get something to drink.
[SAORI] Akane, can you get
some for the rest of us?
Just the usual.
[HIROSHI] On second thought,
make mine melon!
[AYANE] Hey, Sis,
do you need help with that?
Who's that?
He's just a boy from my class.
[AYANE]
Here you go.
[SAORI]
Thanks, sweetie!
Oh, my gosh, Mom,
you gotta hear this.
No kidding?
So you see, my daughter's
actually in his class!
[JUNKO]
You don't say!
But why didn't you say
anything sooner, Kotarou?
Well, I'm Junko Azumi.
I'm his mother;
nice to meet you.
[HIROSHI]
Oh, hello there!
I'm Akane's father.
Hi! It's a pleasure!
[WOMAN 1B] Just let me know
if you need anything else.
I can't wait to see
you eat all this!
Hilarious!
Leave her alone. Eat up!
Hey, she's pretty cute,
don't ya think?
Now, you cut that out
before you embarrass him
in front of his
little friend.
Kotarou has eyes;
he knows she's pretty.
[KOTAROU coughs]
[JUNKO]
Are you okay, sweetheart?
It's bitter.
[WOMAN 1C]
Thank you for dining with us.
Maybe we'll see you again.
Jeez, I'm so nervous.
I wish I had my squeezie.
Uh, listen.
Please don't tell anyone...
Y'know, about us
running into each other.
It's so embarrassing.
Um, thanks so much.
But being in your track suit
doesn't embarrass you?
[KOTAROU]
We haven't spoken.
Not since that night
at the restaurant.
Even though we've
noticed each other a lot.
Okay, that should
just about wrap up
the duty assignments.
Next we'll have a briefing.
The Sports Festival Task Groups
will have a meeting
after school.
So once the announcements
are over at the end of the day,
you can go ahead and
break up into your groups.
Any questions?
[HIRA] Thanks for
meeting with us today.
Let's get started.
I'm Hira from the track club.
This year we'll be taking on
the equipment group's work
for the sports festival.
It's a big job, so we're
going to need everyone's help
to pull this off.
If you helped us
last year, then great!
You probably already know what
some of our tasks include...
It's curling up.
Huh? The LINE app?
Yeah, that's right.
Last year we made a group
for the task members
and it helped a lot.
You should ask everyone.
Hey, I need your help, please.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[AOI]
What's up?
[ROMAN]
Yo!
[DAICHI]
Don't you have club?
[KOTAROU]
I'm not going today.
[ROMAN]
You skipping?
[KOTAROU]
No, I'm just writing at home.
[ROMAN chuckles] Man, when
are you gonna let me read it?
Never.
[ROMAN] Aw, it's not like
it's top secret info!
[KOTAROU]
Doesn't matter.
[ROMAN]
Yes, it does!
[GROUP laughing]
[DAICHI]
Oh, yeah? Still doesn't hurt!
Ow! Ow!
[chattering]
[AKANE]
LINE.
[AYANE humming]
[phone whistles]
[AKANE]
Okay, got it.
Now I just need
to get Curly- kun 's ID.
[SETSUKO]
Oh, yeah. Hey, Nagahara,
did you check
LINE yesterday?
Because you never
responded to me.
[SHOU]
I was at the arcade.
[SETSUKO]
You're the worst.
[SHOU]
Dude, come on!
--I said I was sorry!
--Sorry isn't good enough.
[SHOU] But I set the new
high score in Taiko !
[SETSUKO]
Actually, that's pretty cool!
[SHOU]
I'm like a drum god!
[AIRA]
What's Taiko ?
[SETSUKO]
It's like a drum rhythm game.
[AIRA]
How do you play it?
[SETSUKO] You should ask
Nagahara to teach you.
[SHOU]
My fee is minimal.
[SETSUKO]
No one's gonna pay you!
--[AKANE] Uh...
--[KOTAROU] Uh...
[MIU]
Hey Akane, can you help me?
Uh, yeah, sure!
[DAISUKE]
Hey.
Hi.
[DAISUKE] We're practicing
for the festival next week.
Cool.
[DAISUKE]
That's a great short story.
[KOTAROU gasps]
Dazai writes a
girl's inner thoughts
from a first person
point of view.
Though personally
I don't think a guy
can truly understand
a girl's feelings, y'know?
[KOTAROU chuckles]
Yeah.
[DAISUKE]
Oh, here's this.
It's the thing we were
talking about before.
[KOTAROU]
"Yudemen"?
That's right.
It's the original album
by a folk rock super
group called Happy End.
All of the band members went on
to become well known
in the music industry.
They're pretty amazing.
[DAISUKE]
Borrow it as long as you'd like.
I'll take good care of it.
[DAISUKE]
Any books you want today?
I guess I'll get this one.
Then this one's on me.
[DAISUKE] You should
read all kinds of books.
[KOTAROU chuckles]
[GYM TEACHER 1A] Azumi,
care to explain why you missed
the equipment meeting?
[AKANE]
Huh?
[KOTAROU]
I'm... I'm sorry.
[GYM TEACHER 1A] Everyone
else is doing their part.
Get with the program.
[KOTAROU]
Okay.
[AKANE gasps]
LINE!
[GYM TEACHER 1A] ...storage
room. Can you manage that?
[KOTAROU]
Yes, sir.
[AKANE]
Excuse me.
[KOTAROU gasps]
You scared me!
I'm actually the one
who forgot to contact you,
I'm sorry!
[AKANE] There's a contact list
for the equipment group.
Uh... oh.
Do... you have a LINE ID?
I made a LINE group
for the task members.
Oh.
[KOTAROU] I don't have
my phone on me right now.
[AKANE gasps]
Wait, I've got it.
Here it is.
Here's my ID.
Right, thank you.
I can help you!
[KOTAROU]
Uh, it's okay.
But it is kinda my fault.
[KOTAROU]
Don't you have club?
Yeah, it's okay.
It won't take long
if we work together.
There's dust on your jacket.
Where at?
On your back. I'll get it.
[AKANE]
There, much better.
I really am sorry.
[KOTAROU]
It's fine.
Bye.
[KOTAROU]
[KOTAROU chuckles]
[phone chimes]
[KOTAROU]
Dazai once said,
"The feeling of joy is
perhaps like a speck of gold,
glimmering faintly at the
bottom of a river of grief."
[AYANE]
Your boyfriend?
[AKANE]
Butt out, nosy!
This'll teach her.