Okay, pencils down.
[STUDENTS sigh]
[chattering]
[RYOUKO] Only one more day
of exams. You can make it!
[MIU]
How'd you do?
[SETSUKO]
Terrible.
[AIRA]
Wanna go with us, Akane?
--[AKANE] Huh?
--[AIRA] Come on.
We're shopping
for the school trip.
[AIRA]
It's coming up soon.
Sorry, but I have
practice today.
Too bad.
Tomorrow's test
is language arts?
[AIRA]
I hope it's not hard.
[ROMAN]
Kota!
Hey, come on, why do you
look so depressed, man?
Uh-oh, did you fail?
Fail is a strong word.
Yeah, meaning
it's the right word.
Wanna see my new move?
[KOTAROU]
Not really.
[DAICHI]
Ogasawara Dynamic!
[KOTAROU]
Stop! Let go!
Fine, take this!
Jeez! That hurt!
To be fair,
I did ask you to stop.
I thought you said
it was a new move.
[DAICHI]
It is!
[SHIGE]
Hm?
Well, good morning!
You're here early.
What about school?
Uh, it's an exam day.
[SHIGE laughs]
Sounds exciting.
[KOTAROU] You're up
pretty early yourself.
Yes, we're cleaning
up Kagura Hall.
Good morning, Kotarou.
You're here early. No school?
[KOTAROU]
I-It's exam week.
[DAISUKE]
Uh... Is that about your book?
The one you let me
look at recently?
You read my second story,
but this was about my first one.
[SHIGE]
Hey Kotarou!
We're looking forward to seeing
you on Sunday. For practice?
[KOTAROU]
Uh, yep!
So then you've submitted
an entry before?
What did they say?
Must be hard to
focus on school.
[JUNKO]
Kotarou!
You had better be studying
up there, young man!
[KOTAROU]
I am!
I'm trying to, at least.
Is that too weird?
[phone chimes]
Akane, did you take your bath?
[AKANE]
Oh, yeah, a while ago.
Okay.
Well, I guess I'll
go take one, then.
[KOTAROU]
What's wrong with me.
Why can't I talk to her
this easily at school?
[phone chimes]
[KOTAROU laughing]
[RYOUKO]
Right, pencils down!
Please pass your papers forward.
[ROMAN]
Kota!
Wanna hang out
after school today?
Nah, I have to go to my club.
--[ROMAN] Aww...
--I have club today, too.
[ROMAN]
Seriously?
You guys are so lame.
Come on, let's go
do something fun.
[DAICHI] We're not here
to entertain you, man.
[ROMAN]
We never hang out anymore.
[MIU]
Bye, Akane!
See ya!
Have a good one.
[AKANE]
Uh, yeah. See ya!
[DAICHI]
I guess that sounds fun.
[ROMAN]
And we'll hit the arcade!
Just skip out on your club.
I can't! I've skipped
too much as it is!
[ROMAN]
Come on, it's just one day.
[DAICHI]
I'll get in trouble!
I'm so excited to run today.
Yeah!
Hold on.
I'm just gonna go throw
this away real quick.
'Kay.
[CHINATSU]
Hey!
What's up, Curly- kun ?
Hi!
Oh, he and I
are friends now.
Thanks to you,
because you told me
he was really cool.
The meet in is one week,
so do your best!
[GROUP]
Right!
[AOI] Have you noticed
all the hook-ups?
[CHINATSU]
Like, everyone's in love.
[AOI]
It's 'cause of the school trip.
[AKANE]
That's just silly.
[AOI]
I know, right?
Huh? No, it isn't.
A boyfriend would
be awesome, right?
I think I'm good, actually.
Not even Hira?
--[HIRA] What's that?
--[AOI] Nothing, nosy!
[CHINATSU]
You two should date!
What, why?
[CHINATSU] I heard a girl
asked him out but he said no.
--Why, though?
--There's someone he likes.
[AOI]
Definitely Akane.
[CHINATSU]
That's what I think, too!
Man, I bombed.
Those tests were pretty hard.
How'd you do?
[KOTAROU] The literature club
has this superstition.
[KOTAROU]
Pick out a random book.
Whatever your situation is,
the pages inside
will have the perfect advice.
That's it.
Fine.
[CHINATSU]
He should just ask her out.
Hira?
[CHINATSU] I'm positive
Akane would say yes.
He'd better not
before the track meet.
[CHINATSU] After it's over then,
when emotions are high!
[AOI]
Yeah, that might work.
Um, have you chosen
a high school yet?
Oh, yeah, more or less.
Don't they usually
ask you after midterms?
I've just been focusing
on the track meet for now.
Oh, that's right.
Don't you worry, sweetie,
Mom and I will come--
Why don't you go to
your sister's school?
Hey, yeah, my school's awesome.
Oh, really?
You'd like it. They're like
super club-oriented or whatever.
I think it'd be good for you.
[AKANE]
Hmm...
But it's so far away.
So then why don't we
move back to Tokyo?
Knowing Dad, he'll probably just
get transferred again anyway.
Way to have faith in me, dear.
Come on, it'd be
super convenient for me.
Can I have seconds?
[starting pistol fires]
Go, go! Let's go,
let's go, Akane! Go, go!
Let's go, let's go, Akane!
[CHINATSU] Let's go,
let's go, go go, Akane!
[TRACK TEAM] Let's go,
[CHINATSU]
You can do it! Akane!
[CROWD clapping]
Great job...
Akane!
[CHINATSU]
I won't give up.
[TV 3A] The baby giraffe was
debuted to the public today.
Needless to say,
the adorable critter
has captured zoo-goers hearts.
The zoo-keepers say...
I noticed you're on LINE
an awful lot lately.
Mind your own business.
[TV 3A] Tomorrow will be partly
cloudy with a small chance--
Aww... The same day
as my practice.
[CHINATSU]
He should just ask her out.
Hira?
[CHINATSU] I'm positive
Akane would say yes.
Ah, jeez...
I wanna ask, but should I?
Come on! Think already!
[phone chimes]
[chuckles]
[KOTAROU]
Okay, let's do this.
[starting pistol fires]
[ANNOUNCER 3A] The winner of the
last race was the participant
in lane six.
Miss Kimura from Jounan.
Her winning record is 14.21
seconds with a tailwind
of 1.3 meters per second.
Are you okay?
[AKANE]
Yeah.
Do you think you'll
beat your own record?
[AKANE]
I don't know.
I bet you will.
I mean, you have been
working really hard for this.
[AKANE]
Mm-hmm.
Let's do our best out there.
[AKANE]
Yeah.
[HIRA]
Hey...
[AKANE]
Hm?
Um, uh, Mizuno?
Come on! Let's go!
Ah, forget about it. Bye!
[CHINATSU]
Oh, Hira.
[HIRA] Hey, I'll be
cheering for you guys!
Here we go.
Oh, boy, Akane looks nervous.
Akane! Go get 'em!
Let's go!
[STARTER 3A]
Set!
[starting pistol fires]
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
Lane five takes the lead.
It's Akane Mizuno!
Come on!
[taiko drums playing]
[KOTAROU]
I wonder how it went.
[cash register beeping]
[TRACK TEAM 3G]
Ugh. This line sucks.
[TRACK TEAM 3C]
I know what I'm getting!
Think I'll get the large shake.
Hey, where you'd
get so much money?
[AOI] My parents gave it
to me as a reward.
[CHINATSU]
No fair.
You hungry?
[AKANE]
Uh, definitely.
[taiko drums playing]
[HIRA]
Did you see that one girl run?
[TRACK TEAM 3C]
Which one?
[HIRA]
The one in the third lane.
[TRACK TEAM 3G]
Oh, yeah!
She was fast.
I've made up my mind.
I'm gonna train harder!
--[AOI] Oh?
--Seriously!
What about the school trip?
Uh...
[AOI] Are you gonna
train in Kyoto?
--[CHINATSU] Maybe I will!
--[AOI] Yeah, right.
[laughing]
Hey, did you guys hear?
I heard Tsubasa asked Aira out.
Aw, jeez, really?
Aren't they in
your class, Akane?
[AKANE]
Uh, what?
Who are we talking about?
--What happened?
--[CHINATSU] This is girl talk!
No boys allowed.
Hey, what's wrong?
Uh, bathroom break.
[faint taiko drums]
[KOTAROU sighs]
[GIRL 3B]
Thank you for today!
[ALL]
Right! Really nice
work, everyone.
See ya later.
[KOTAROU]
Mizuno, hi.
Oh, hello.
Come on. This way.
[AKANE]
Uh... Mm-hmm.
So, what's that?
It's um...
For the festival?
Uh... Mm-hmm.
Wow, that's so cool!
Are you in the march?
That's awesome!
Nah, it's nothing.
So, um...
How was the meet?
Well, I set a new
personal record!
That's awesome!
Congrats!
Thanks so much.
I was wondering how it went.
Sorry, my phone kinda died.
Oh. [laughs]
[AKANE chuckles]
Um, I was hoping that
you might still be here.
And you were.
[AKANE]
This is... awkward.
[KOTAROU]
Someone translated "I love you"
into "Isn't the moon beautiful?"
Was it Daizo Osamu?
Or Natsume Souseki?
[KOTAROU]
The moon.
[AKANE]
Huh?
I know. Isn't it beautiful?
[giggles]
[KOTAROU]
Would you... date me?
[AKANE gasps]