[KOTAROU gasps]
[phone ringing]
[AKANE]
Kotarou?
[KOTAROU]
Uh, sorry, but you're moving?
[AKANE]
Yeah.
[KOTAROU]
Where? When?
[AKANE]
Chiba, probably.
I'm looking at schools there.
Have you ever heard of Koumei?
[music playing]
[KOTAROU] Excuse me,
but... can you help me?
[music playing]
Oh, Akane has excellent grades.
There shouldn't be a problem.
[SAORI]
Really?
That's so wonderful to hear!
[RYOKO]
Moving must be stressful.
I heard it's because your
husband was transferred?
[SAORI] Yes, but knowing Akane
will go to a good school
is such a relief.
[WOMAN 10A]
Here's the application form.
[AKANE]
Thanks so much.
[KOTAROU]
Akane!
I just wanted to see you.
Yeah?
So, we met with Miss Ryoko.
And...?
I'm applying to Koumei.
With a recommendation.
[AKANE]
I'm sorry.
[KOTAROU]
Hm?
Well, you know,
we'll be separated.
I'm just not sure what to do.
[KOTAROU]
It's not your fault.
We'll be okay, even far apart.
Yeah, you're right.
[KOTAROU] Maybe I'll apply
to the same school.
[AKANE gasps]
I don't have your grades,
but I'll try.
Seriously?
Yeah, though it's kinda far.
Isn't it over a
two-hour commute?
[KOTAROU chuckles]
I decided to go to your
cram school in the fall.
[KOTAROU]
Really?
Awesome!
Let's head back.
[AKANE]
'Kay.
Isn't the festival this weekend?
[KOTAROU]
Yep.
[AKANE]
I'll come watch!
[KOTAROU]
Okay.
[TAIKO CLASS 8A]
Cheers.
[PERFORMERS]
Cheers!
[PERFORMERS singing]
[PERFORMERS]
Heave ho! Heave ho!
--Heave ho!
--[singing]
[STALL OWNER 10A]
Candy apples!
Come get your candy apples!
[CHINATSU]
It's really busy!
[AOI]
Yeah, no joke.
[CHINATSU]
Where's Hira at?
This was his idea.
[HIRA]
Hey, there you are!
[CHINATSU]
About time!
[TRACK TEAM 3B]
Yeah, sorry.
[AOI]
Let's get going.
[singing, chattering]
[STALL OWNER 10B]
One, two, three shoot--Ah!
You won, Akane! Yeah!
[STUDENT 10A]
I can't believe I missed!
[HIRA laughs]
--[CHINATSU] Delicious!
--[AOI] Free food is the best!
Hey, you guys wanna go
with us to the haunted house?
[CHINATSU]
That sounds fun!
[AOI] Isn't that place like,
for kids and stuff?
Oh. I think you're just scared.
[AOI] Yeah, I'm not
gonna fall for that.
[CHINATSU screams]
[CHINATSU]
That was so horrifying!
[AOI] I'm sorry I ever
made fun of you!
[CHINATSU]
But I kind of wanna go again.
[AOI]
Yeah, me too!
--It was sorta fun!
--[CHINATSU] Totally!
[taiko drums, music]
[AKANE]
There he is!
That must be Kotarou.
[CHINATSU]
Wasn't that Azumi?
[AKANE]
Yeah.
[AOI]
He looked pretty cool.
Yeah.
[PERFORMER 10B]
Nice job, everyone.
Not too shabby.
[chattering, laughing]
I'm telling you, she was cute.
She's the one.
[KOTAROU]
It's so hot!
Hey, you looked
good up there earlier.
[KOTAROU chuckles]
I guess.
Wow, high standards.
[DAISUKE]
Oh, yeah.
Remember when we were
talking about light novels?
Yes?
[DAISUKE] I don't think
you should change it.
I'm not following.
[DAISUKE] That story you
let me read a while back?
It's just--I'm almost positive
it would also work
as a light novel.
[TAIKO CLASS 8A]
Hey! Nice work.
We have a little time
until the next parade.
Why don't you boys take a break?
Uh, 'kay.
Don't have too much fun.
[DAISUKE]
You heard the man.
[CHINATSU]
Okay, hands in!
Loser takes the trash.
[STUDENT 10A]
Right.
[ALL]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[cheering]
[TRACK TEAM 3C]
Here's your trash!
[AOI]
Don't forget this one!
[GIRL 10A] Hands down,
imokoi is my favorite.
[GIRL 10B]
Oh my gosh, it's mine too!
[AKANE]
Aw, now I want some imokoi .
[HIRA chuckles]
Wow, You're still hungry?
Yeah.
Jeez. You should pace yourself.
[AKANE]
No one asked you!
[HIRA]
Hey, Mizuno.
[AKANE]
Huh?
Come on. Wanna get some?
[AKANE]
I'm so excited.
You must be hungry, huh, Mizuno?
[AKANE]
Maybe.
[HIRA]
You look so happy.
It is my favorite.
It's a Kawagoe specialty.
Bet you'll miss it
when you move, huh?
You don't have to
rub salt in the wound.
My bad.
Sorry.
It's okay.
[HIRA] I guess it's
just... I feel weird.
When you told me that
you were moving to Chiba,
I didn't know what to do.
[HIRA]
I've always had a crush on you.
[HIRA] The passion you
show when you run...
You're so captivating.
Sorry.
But, look, the thing is...
I'm dating someone.
[HIRA]
I know, but still.
Why'd you pick Azumi?
Like, we've been on the track
club together for years!
It's just--It's not fair!
I've loved you way longer!
[AKANE]
Listen, Hira.
You're an important
friend to me.
But that's all.
Sorry.
[HIRA]
It's fine.
I just wanted to tell you.
Okay, then.
[phone chimes]
[AKANE gasps]
There you are.
This place is huge!
I'm so glad I get to see you.
I told the track team
I was leaving early.
Is something wrong?
[KOTAROU]
Were you with Hira?
Uh, yeah.
[KOTAROU]
Just the two of you?
Yes.
We were throwing away trash.
Why do you ask?
[AKANE] By the way,
I saw your dance earlier!
[KOTAROU]
Hmm.
It was really impressive!
So how long will
you be on break?
I don't have very long.
I have to go back soon.
Oh, okay.
I'm kinda hungry.
Want some imokoi ?
I'm actually full.
[PERFORMER 10I]
Hey, look who it is!
[PERFORMER 10J]
It's Kotarou.
[PERFORMER 10I]
What's up, man?
[PERFORMER 10K]
Looking good, buddy.
Who's the girl?
[KOTAROU]
None of your business.
Jeez, what's your deal, huh?
[KOTAROU]
It's not like that.
[PERFORMER 10K]
Man, to be that young again.
Ha. Don't worry, we won't
tell your old man
about your girlfriend.
[PERFORMER 10K]
Come on, let's go get a drink.
Kotarou?
You're acting kinda weird.
Am I?
Are you upset?
Not really.
See?
I'm not upset.
Yes, you are.
[sighs]
--Is it about the move?
--Not really.
So why are you angry?
I'm not!
[AKANE gasps]
Just let it go, already.
I'm not angry.
Please, just tell me!
What's wrong?
I wanna know.
Please, Kotarou.
What'd I do wrong?
It's because...
...I saw you--
[AKANE]
Huh?
You and Hira.
[STALL OWNER 10C]
Nice throw, young man!
[AKANE]
Hey.
Hira... confessed to me.
I turned him down, though.
[KOTAROU coughing]
[AKANE]
I'll get you some water.
[KOTAROU]
It's fine. [coughs]
I don't have time.
[KOTAROU]
I've gotta go. See ya.
--[chanting]
--[taiko drums]
--[music]
[crying]
[KOTAROU groans]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[SETSUKO]
I keep falling asleep.
[AIRA]
Me, too.
[MIU] Studying is so boring
I can't seem to stay awake.
I just want exams
to be over already
so I don't have to
stress about high school.
[SETSUKO] And I'm so over
my mom nagging me.
[MIU] Nagging just makes
me want to study less.
[SETSUKO]
I know!
[MIU] Parents just don't
understand our struggle.
Okay.
That changes up
the whole equation.
So watch out for that.
[AKANE]
Excuse me, sorry to bother you.
Why do you have this book?
[STAFF 10A]
Oh, someone requested it.
They said...
...someone requested
this book.
[AKANE]
Was it you, Kotarou?
[KOTAROU]
I'm applying.
I haven't told my parents yet.
They're probably gonna be mad.
But I don't care.
I was gonna tell you
after I talked to them.
I've thought about
my future a lot.
About writing, and stuff.
I've made up my mind.
I want to be with you.
I believe in us.
[AKANE]
Thank you...
[crying]
I'm so happy...
I was a jerk. Sorry.
[AKANE]
I'm sorry, too.
I couldn't talk to you.
I wanted to,
but I thought you hated me.
[KOTAROU]
No way! I'd... never hate you.
Literature club, picture time!
This is for the
graduation album.
[KOTAROU] When did we
get so many members?
[KOTAROU]
You're in this club?
Yeah, so what?
[KOTAROU]
Cool.
Where's everyone during the day?
[RYOKO]
Okay, say cheese!