[DAISUKE]
That's it! Yeah, good!
Then up, and stop.
Hold.
Nice job! Next!
[taiko drums playing]
[KOTAROU chuckles]
[KOTAROU]
Dazai was very wise.
He once said,
"People exist for love
and for revolution."
[AOI] Your time was
awesome, Chinatsu.
[CHINATSU]
Well, the race is next week.
[AOI]
Maybe you'll make prefecturals.
[CHINATSU]
Stop it, no, I won't!
[AOI]
You never know.
--Maybe in my dreams!
--[AOI] Don't be so negative!
Hey! Let me try your ice cream!
Eat your own!
Mmm! It's so delicious!
What flavor did you get?
Kinako mochi soda.
I'd better test it for poison.
[giggles] Nope, tastes good!
You're safe for now!
[laughing]
Whatever, I'm a hero!
Yeah, you're a real life saver!
Your language arts grade
was pretty good, wasn't it?
[KOTAROU groans]
[JUNKO] Look, I'm not saying
you shouldn't participate
in the festival.
But, I am worried
about your exams.
This is no time to be
slacking off, you know?
[phone vibrating]
Uh, hello, Azumi speaking.
[KITAMURA] Hi, this is Kitamura
from Kadoyama Publishing.
I'm calling regarding
your submission
for the newcomer award.
[KOTAROU]
Kadoyama Publishing?
Yes.
Uh, could you give
me just a minute?
No, no, no. I'm not busy.
[HIROSHI]
♪ Dinner time, dinner time! ♪
Here, take that to the table.
[AYANE]
Jeez, are you feeding an army?
[SAORI]
Maybe.
Oh! You've outdone
yourself, honey!
Let's dig in!
Come on Akane, I know
how much you love food!
Thanks for dinner, Mom.
You've got a meet
this Sunday, right?
This looks great.
We'll come cheer for you!
Why?
It's time to eat!
"Why?" Why not?
I dunno, maybe there's
new cheerleader.
[HIROSHI]
What's that mean?
Like a boy.
[BOTH gasp]
[AYANE giggles]
Right, Akane?
[SAORI]
Oh?
Is that true?
[phone chimes]
[AKANE chuckles]
[door opens]
Well, good morning.
[AKANE]
Really? Cool!
[KOTAROU] Yeah, and then
the publisher asked for me
to go meet with them.
That's incredible news!
Nothing is certain yet.
Uh-huh.
I'm not even sure
what they want.
To award you! Duh.
Mmm... Well...
That's exciting.
You know, you really should
be proud of yourself.
Your dream is coming true.
[KOTAROU] Oh, but the thing
is... the meeting is Sunday.
Ah, the day of the meet.
[KOTAROU] I'm sorry
I can't come cheer for you.
Don't worry about it.
Kind of ironic, though.
[KOTAROU]
Mmm.
Let's do our best!
I promise.
[KOTAROU]
What about you?
Huh?
You wanted to talk
about something?
Oh, well, uh...
It's fine.
It's really not that important.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
[JUNKO]
Where are you going?
Uh...
Wh-Who, me?
The library.
You're studying now?
What about lunch?
Oh, no thanks.
I'll be fine.
See ya later.
[JUNKO]
Don't stay out too late.
[KOTAROU]
Let's see.
That was pricy.
[KITAMURA]
Hi. I've been expecting you.
Come in.
Thank you for seeing me.
Hey, Akane.
[AKANE]
Hm?
About that text the other day...
[AKANE gasps]
[CHINATSU]
Hm?
Um, sorry.
Huh? What about?
Well, actually...
I'm, uh...
...dating someone.
[CHINATSU gasps]
And, it's uh...
Well, it's Azumi.
[CHINATSU]
I know.
It's kinda obvious.
We are friends, y'know.
Oh, right.
But thank you for telling me.
[CROWD cheering]
[STARTER 6A]
Set!
[starting pistol fires]
[CROWD cheering]
[TRACK TEAM 3C]
Wow!
Mizuno's next to that girl
from Nishi Middle School.
She's like super fast.
Mizuno! Let's go!
Come on!
[CROWD cheering]
[STARTER 6A]
Set!
[starting pistol fires]
[HIRA gasps]
Mizuno, slow down!
[KITAMURA] I'm Kitamura.
We spoke on the phone.
[KOTAROU]
It's nice to meet you.
I'm sorry. I know it's a trek.
It's okay.
[KITAMURA] So, let's skip
straight to the business, eh?
I'm one of the editors here
at Kadoyama Publishing.
As you're well aware, we're
searching for some new talent.
Yes, sir.
[KITAMURA] You're in
middle school, that right?
[KOTAROU]
Yes, sir.
[KITAMURA laughs]
Lucky you, being so young.
[KOTAROU groans]
[KITAMURA] Look, I'm
gonna cut to the chase.
I'm not certain that serious
literature is your forte.
[KOTAROU gasps]
[KITAMURA sighs]
You lack the talent.
I don't think it's for you.
And let's be honest here.
It doesn't really make
that much money anyway.
[laughs] I wouldn't wish
that job on anyone.
[laughs]
But you know,
there's a big market
for light novels.
Have you ever tried writing
one of those before, huh?
Personally, I think
your time and energy
would be better spent
on something like that,
not literary awards.
I mean, you don't
wanna be in your thirties
and still struggling
to be a writer, do you? Ha!
I think you should try this
out while you still have
youth on your side.
[CROWD chattering]
So is Nishio the only one
who made it to the semifinals?
Yeah, but get this.
Nishio set a new
personal best record!
That's great.
[HIRA]
Mizuno.
[HIRA] What the heck
happened out there?
Your time was actually
worse than last year.
I mean, jeez, you could've
made it to prefecturals!
But instead you just
threw it all away!
[HIRA]
Are you listening?!
[AKANE crying]
[HIRA] You're better than this,
and I like watching you.
If running makes you happy,
then don't give up!
Hey, I'm back.
[JUNKO]
Kotarou!
[JUNKO] Your father
told me what happened.
Tell me the truth,
did a publisher call you?
[KOTAROU gasps]
Now, dear, try and calm down.
We could at least hear him out.
Being contacted by a
publisher is a pretty big deal.
I will not! He has to
stop living with his head
in the clouds all the time!
I've been fine with this
festival nonsense,
but nothing good
can come of writing!
[RYUUNOSUKE]
Oh, Mother.
[HIROSHI]
Oh, yeah? Hmm.
Well, there will be more
races to win, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Definitely.
[SAORI] Can't you say
anything besides "yeah"?
[HIROSHI]
Yeah! Uh...
[AKANE sighs]
[AYANE]
I'll go talk to her.
You've got this!
[AYANE]
Right.
[AKANE]
Today really sucked.
[AYANE]
Hm?
[AKANE]
My time was awful.
Boyfriend problems, huh?
You know what they say.
A woman can't have everything.
If you try, you'll just
lose everything.
[AKANE]
Shut up.
I just couldn't focus,
that's all.
[AKANE sighs]
It's actually about
my best friend.
[AYANE]
Hmm...
[AKANE]
She likes my boyfriend.
[AYANE gasps]
[AKANE]
What should I do?
That's a big bag of nope!
[AKANE]
Huh?
You have to ditch that girl!
What? No way.
--[AYANE] And why not?
--[AKANE] Because!
She's my friend, you know?
[AYANE]
Well, you're asking for trouble.
Is she really that
great of a friend?
[phone chimes]
Wow, really?
Mmm. I didn't make it.
[KOTAROU sighs]
How was your meeting?
Not good.
I am sorry.
I really wanna focus
on the track club.
Ah, but you are.
More, then.
I'll do more.
I'll work harder.
I love it.
Then I'll work hard, too.
[AKANE]
Huh?
I won't give up.
We made a promise, remember?
[BOTH chuckle]
[AKANE] I've been
wanting to talk to you.
[CHINATSU]
Oh?
[AKANE] I'm sorry I didn't tell
you that we were dating.
And I'm sorry, too.
For falling for him.
[CHINATSU]
Are you mad at me, Akane?
[AKANE]
Mm-mm.
[CHINATSU]
Thank goodness.
[AKANE chuckles]
[AKANE]
The truth is...
[CHINATSU]
Yeah?
[AKANE]
I'm not sure what to do.
[CHINATSU]
Ah.
I just...
...want us to be friends.
[CHINATSU chuckles]
[CHINATSU]
Thanks for being honest.
So, can I tell him how I feel?
I just want some closure.
[ROMAN]
Hey, Tanaka!
Come with me!
[SAKURA gasps]
[YASUHITO]
Back off, pal!
She's all mine. I love her!
[TSUBASA]
Whatever! She's mine!
[overlapping chatter]
[SAKURA]
Boys, boys! Stop fighting!
How could I ever choose
between the three of you?
[TSUBASA]
Come on, hurry!
Just give them
to me already, jeez!
[SAKURA] On second thought,
that fantasy's dumb.
Hey, what is it
you like about me?
Duh, I like everything.
Don't you think that
Miss Ryouko's really cute?
Huh? I never noticed.
[MIU giggles]
What do you think
I want for my birthday?
Huh, maybe a stuffed bear?
[MIU]
Eh?!
[YASUHITO] But the other day,
she was looking at one.
[gasps] It wasn't the bear!
[RYOUKO] Not that I
have any plans, but...
Oh, hi, Miss Ryouko!
What? Uh, this is for a friend!
Too bad. I'd love
to see you in a dress.
You'd look beautiful.
We accept credit.
[MIU]
Let's take a selfie!
[YASUHITO]
Yeah, sure.
'Kay, say cheese.
Actually, move the
angle higher up, please.
Like this?
Ew, I look gross
from that angle.
Can you try more from the right?
Uh, like this?
Yeah, I think
that'll probably work.
All right, now from that same
angle, try and match my pose.
Awesome!
Make sure the
expression matches,
and no matter what you do,
don't take the picture
until I tell you to, okay?
[YASUHITO]
Mm-hmm.
[MIU]
Hmm...
[YASUHITO chuckles]
All right, go!
Okay, then, say cheese!
Disgusting!
Ew, there's no way I'm
gonna post this on my feed.
Let's try it again
from a different angle!
I think that one--
[YASUHITO]
Girls are so picky!
[MIU]
Take it again!