I mean, can you
believe Nagahara?
He ruined the school trip for me
with that ridiculous stunt.
I thought he had actually
planned something romantic,
but a hotel?
What a colossal jerk, you know?
[AIRA]
But he's your jerk.
[SETSUKO]
Don't remind me!
[GIRLS laughing]
[SETSUKO]
Come on, now, this is serious!
[AIRA]
Is it?
He's been really selfish
lately and he's not thinking
about my feelings!
He's not thinking
about anything!
Well, I guess he
thinks about one thing.
If you call that thinking.
[laughs]
[MIU]
Hm? What's up?
Oh? Me? Uh, nothing's up!
[AKANE] It's kind of
a secret, but recently,
Azumi and I started dating.
I'm worried about your scores.
Your exam results
can influence your future
after middle school.
[CHINATSU]
Thanks again.
Look, Azumi...
You have a lot of potential,
but you really need...
[CHINATSU]
His hair's flat.
[RYOUKO] ...and how you can
apply yourself to your studies.
[KOTAROU]
Thank you, ma'am.
Your hair's not curly.
Are you depressed?
[giggles]
I'm just teasing.
I was wondering...
Yeah?
I'm really struggling
with language arts.
Do you know any
good cram schools?
Well, the one I
go to is decent.
Very cram school-y.
I should hope so!
[laughs]
[TRACK TEAM 5A]
One, two, three, four.
[TRACK TEAM]
Five, six, seven, eight.
[TRACK TEAM 5A]
Two, two, three, four.
[AOI]
Uh, Chinatsu?
[CHINATSU]
Uh...
What's up?
Nothing.
[TRACK TEAM]
Five, six, seven, eight.
[HIRA]
Hey, Mizuno, Nishio.
Check it.
[CHINATSU]
Huh?
[AKANE]
What is it?
A new sprint training plan.
We're going with this
until the meet.
Oh, wow, that looks
pretty strict.
[CHINATSU yells]
What is wrong with you?
I just wanna do my best!
Come on! Time to train!
[taiko drums, music playing]
[GIRL 3A]
Thank you for today.
[KIDS TAIKO CLASS, SHIGE]
[SHIGE]
Okay, the adults are up next.
[KOTAROU]
Hey, Daisuke.
Yeah?
I've been thinking
about my next story idea.
And how are things going?
What things?
Y'know, studying for exams.
[KOTAROU]
Mmm...
Well...
Well, what?
Hey, can I ask you something?
Sure.
[KOTAROU groans]
It's about, um, relationships.
Okay?
Uh, you know!
For my book!
Yeah?
[KOTAROU groans]
[DAISUKE]
I'm... sorry.
[AKANE sighs]
Dating has so many... rules.
[AYANE laughs]
You're ridiculous.
'Kay, goodnight.
Hey, Sis?
[AYANE]
Hm?
So, uh, what do you
do in a relationship?
[AYANE chuckles]
What?
Wait... You're dating someone?
Aw, congratulations!
Uh, please don't
tell Mom and Dad!
Don't worry, I won't.
Ha. You could go on
a date or walk together.
Let's see, what else?
Hang out at each other's place.
At his house?
Or over here.
There's no way!
[JUNKO]
Kotarou?
[KOTAROU gasps]
You need to be
studying, young man.
Yeah, I know, Mom.
[JUNKO] If you don't
do well on your finals,
I'll ground you from
writing and the festival,
understand?
[phone chimes]
I hope that didn't
sound too needy.
[laughing]
[phone chimes]
[STUDENT 5A]
It's so stuffy in here.
Let's eat outside.
Huh? Kota, you leaving?
Uh, yeah.
[SETSUKO]
Man, I'm starving!
[MIU]
I know, right?
[SETSUKO] Can you believe I
almost forgot my lunch today?
[AIRA]
That would have sucked.
[SETSUKO]
For real, I was freaking out.
[AIRA laughs]
[ROMAN]
That's strange.
[DAICHI]
Bathroom break?
[AIRA, SETSUKO laugh]
[SETSUKO]
Well, some friend you are!
[laughing]
[MIU]
Akane?
Aren't you hungry?
[ROMAN]
Yeah, right!
[DAICHI] Don't judge me!
I'm a growing boy!
What's wrong?
Uh...
Uh, let's eat!
[DAICHI] Everyone knows
muscle weighs more than fat!
[GIRLS]
Hm?
[KOTAROU sighs]
[door opens]
[CHINATSU]
Oh, hey Curly- kun !
Though your curl is MIA lately.
[laughs]
[AKANE]
Anyone in here?
[CHINATSU]
Awesome, thank you!
[KOTAROU]
Sure.
[CHINATSU]
This is great!
You're a real lifesaver!
[CHINATSU]
Hey, Akane.
[KOTAROU]
Uh...
Wait a second.
Were you two meeting?
Uh, uh, no way!
Not like that!
Sorry. That came out wrong.
It's not a huge deal, right?
[KOTAROU]
Uh, uh...
[CHINATSU] Azumi goes to the
cram school by the station.
[AKANE]
Oh, yeah?
I'm thinking of joining up.
--Huh?
--[CHINATSU] Right?
Uh... mmm.
Wanna go check it out with me?
Our club takes up so much time.
And my grades kinda suck.
[laughs]
They're not that bad.
Thanks for again for the help.
Sure.
Well, I'll see you guys later!
[door opens, closes]
[KOTAROU sighs]
Oh, man, I wasn't
expecting that to happen.
[gasps]
Uh... Sorry.
Did you wanna
go to cram--
[AKANE]
No.
[KOTAROU]
Oh... mmm.
[KOTAROU whines]
[HIRA]
Get ready! Go!
I'm really sorry, Coach.
[TRACK COACH 5A] Not at all.
Your grades should come first.
[HIRA]
Get ready... Go!
Mizuno.
[AKANE]
Huh?
[HIRA]
Look, your time was pretty bad.
[AKANE]
Sorry.
Guess I was distracted.
Is something wrong?
Why don't we
talk about it later.
[HIRA]
All right!
Let's get back to practicing!
[TRACK TEAM]
Okay.
[HIRA]
What's going on?
[AKANE groans]
[HIRA]
Look, it'll be okay.
--[HIRA] Hang in there.
--[AKANE] Hm?
[HIRA]
We don't have much time left...
...to run together.
[HIRA]
See ya.
[SENSEI 5A]
Kokoro is a classic book.
Written by the novelist
Natsume Souseki.
The setting is during
the Meiji era,
and the plot of the story
revolves around a love triangle.
Now, just because it's a classic
doesn't mean it's boring.
[CHINATSU] Not many kids
from our school, huh?
[KOTAROU]
No.
[CHINATSU] Maybe that
will help me focus better.
[KOTAROU chuckles]
Possibly.
[CHINATSU]
Anyway, I'm gonna sign up.
That's cool, I guess.
[CHINATSU]
What's your LINE ID?
--[horn beeps]
--[KOTAROU] Let's see here...
[BOTH gasp]
Oops, sorry!
Whoa. Are you okay?
[CHINATSU]
I'm fine.
[DAICHI groans]
I am stuffed.
[SETSUKO] I'm thinking
of dumping Nagahara.
Huh? Seriously?
But he's so awesome!
[SETSUKO]
Well, for one thing,
he's not even that
much fun to date.
[AIRA]
Why not?
What else has happened?
Nothing's happened!
He's so lazy!
We don't talk, we don't cuddle,
we don't go on dates!
[MIU]
That sucks.
[SETSUKO]
He doesn't respect me!
[AIRA]
Unless you're at a hotel.
[SETSUKO]
Exactly!
[GIRLS laugh]
You know what? Dating's hard.
That's the truth.
Are you having boy problems?
Huh? Uh, no way!
Hm. I see.
[SETSUKO]
But yeah, I think it's over.
[ROMAN] Check it out,
I found a new pressure point.
Ow!
[KOTAROU]
Leave me out of this!
[ROMAN]
It's too late!
[SETSUKO]
Am I wrong?
How would you guys handle it?
[AIRA]
No idea. That's a tough one.
[AKANE humming]
[TRACK TEAM 5A]
Excuse me, Mizuno?
[AKANE]
Huh?
Some of us were just
wondering if you and Hira
are, like, dating or something.
[AKANE]
Huh?!
Someone saw
you guys walking home
together recently!
What? No!
[TRACK TEAM 5A]
Really?
[TRACK TEAM 5B sighs]
What a relief!
[GROUP]
Thank you so much!
[TRACK TEAM 5A]
So they weren't dating!
[chattering]
[door closes]
That was... weird.
[KOTAROU sighs]
[DAISUKE]
What's wrong?
[KOTAROU]
Nothing, really.
Got a case of writer's block?
[DAISUKE] You asked about
dating not long ago.
So how's that working out?
[KOTAROU]
Not so hot.
Ah.
[KOTAROU]
We're never alone.
Are you keeping it secret?
[KOTAROU]
Mm-hmm.
[DAISUKE]
I see.
And you can't go out on a date
when you don't have any money.
That's quite a pickle.
[DAISUKE]
Hey, Kotarou.
[phone chimes]
[AKANE]
Um...
[KOTAROU gasps]
Thank goodness!
You found it okay!
[AKANE]
Yeah, I used my GPS.
Where are we?
My friend's bookstore.
Listen.
[AKANE]
Huh?
I just wanted to
be alone with you.
[KOTAROU]
It's hard at school.
[AKANE]
Mm-hmm.
After all, we are dating.
We're the only ones here.
What about your friend?
Oh, he'll be back at seven.
[AKANE]
You know what?
[KOTAROU]
What?
I have a hard time
talking at school.
[KOTAROU]
Yeah, me too.
Sorry for the library.
[AKANE]
Uh...
Chinatsu... went to cram school?
She visited.
Okay.
How'd you do? On the test?
Decent.
[KOTAROU]
Lucky.
My scores sucked.
Wow, really?
Yeah, I haven't been studying.
Because of your book?
Then it's fine.
Uh, at least I think so.
[BOTH laugh]
[AKANE]
I'm struggling, too.
The preliminaries are coming up.
[KOTAROU]
Oh?
[AKANE]
But I can't improve my time.
You're different when
you run, Mizuno.
[AKANE]
Hm?
I just...
I just really...
love watching you run.
Wow, thank you.
Maybe I'll go next time.
Huh?
And cheer.
Huh? Oh, uh, okay, then.
Uh... Or I could not!
It's fine!
No, it's fine, really.
[KOTAROU] Dazai once said,
"One thing that humans have
that other creatures don't:
We have secrets."
Once again,
I guess he was right.
[phone chimes]
[AKANE]
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
Hey, Roman,
have you gained weight?
How can you tell?
Eh, looks to be
around four pounds.
Awesome! You're exactly right!
I can guess a person's weight
with only a quick glance.
[GIRLS gasp]
[AIRA]
Don't use your voodoo on me!
[MIU] What kind of
superpower is that?
Oh, hey.
[YASUHITO]
Huh?
--Which one's better?
--[YASUHITO] This one.
[MIU]
Hmm...
I like the other one.
[YASUHITO]
So why bother asking me?
Which one of these is better?
Uh, oh, well I like
whatever you like!
Wow, you're useless.
[YASUHITO]
I seriously can't win!
What an obnoxious vehicle!
Probably some hooligan!
Mom! Dad! What's up, you guys?
[BOTH gasp]
Ayane?!
[AYANE] My boyfriend
gave me a ride home.
Hello there,
I'm Ayane's boyfriend.
My name is Riku Kasai.
Nice to meet you!
[SAORI]
What a polite young man!
[HIROSHI]
Complete loser!
Are you going to college?
Yes, and thanks to my boss,
I'm also apprenticing
in carpentry.
Through hard work, I hope to
become a respected craftsman.
[SAORI]
What a dedicated young man!
[HIROSHI growls]
And a suck-up!
[toy squeaks]
He actually gave that to you?
What a respectable young man!
[toy squeaks]