[KOTAROU sighs]
[KOTAROU]
I'm applying.
But I still haven't
really told my parents.
Right.
[JUNKO]
Can you believe Kotarou?
He's finally studying!
I'm so happy.
[JUNKO] I'm so glad
that the festival is over.
Without that silly drum
practice to distract him,
Kotarou actually seems to be
taking his future seriously.
[KOTAROU]
Dazai once said,
"To decide that I'm hopeless
before I even begin
is nothing but laziness."
I can't afford to be lazy.
[JUNKO] He was just so absorbed
in that little festival.
Not to mention his novels.
He just wouldn't listen to me!
[chuckles]
You don't say?
About a high school...
We would most prefer for him
to attend something public.
And of course the closer
to home, the better!
I really think that's what
would be most suitable for him.
It sounds like you might want
a municipal school, then.
[KOTAROU]
No.
I want a private school.
One like Koumei.
[JUNKO]
Huh?
[RYOUKO]
Koumei?
Wait... isn't that where
Mizuno is applying?
[JUNKO gasps]
What's the meaning
of this, young man?
Who's Mizuno?
Why didn't you tell me about it?
--Where is this school even at?
--[RYOUKO] Well, uh...
Answer me!
[JUNKO]
Well?
What's going on?
Why didn't you tell us
about Koumei?
[KOTAROU]
I literally just decided.
I literally don't care.
This wasn't your
decision to make alone!
Your entire future
is riding on this!
Do you get that?
Yes, I'm aware.
Kotarou...
Why does it have to be
that particular school?
Uh, Koumei, was it?
Because some girl
is going there?
Wait, a girl?
Yes, his teacher said
something about it.
I think she said
her name was Mizuno?
Ugh. I was so embarrassed.
I can't believe you'd let
some silly little crush
rule a decision as big as this!
[KOTAROU]
I've thought this through!
It's clear that you haven't!
Yes, I have, Mom!
If that's the case, you tell me!
You tell me, why go
all the way to Chiba?
Tell me why it's so important!
[JUNKO]
That's what I thought.
Just shut up already.
[BOTH gasp]
Kotarou!
[KOTAROU]
Sorry.
Now just calm down; yelling
won't help. Let's talk--
You're being way
too easy on him!
As his parents, we know
what is best for Kotarou!
Koumei High School is nothing--
[KOTAROU]
I don't care!
I've made up my mind.
[JUNKO]
Excuse me?
Kotarou!
[phone chimes]
Aren't you supposed
to be studying?
I am.
[AYANE]
You'd better not fail.
Fine.
Back to it.
[AKANE sighs]
All done.
Wow, you've gotta
be kidding me.
[AKANE gasps]
[AYANE] You're actually
knitting a scarf?
Yeah, what's so
weird about that?
[AYANE]
Hmm?
Things must be serious.
[AKANE]
Yup.
[AYANE chuckles]
Oh.
But what happens
after graduation?
What then?
[AKANE]
It'll be fine.
[AYANE] Long distance
is harder than you think.
We're going to the same school.
Hold up.
You mean like, your
boyfriend's gonna apply
to Koumei High?
Whatever, just don't
tell Mom or Dad, okay?
[AYANE]
That's so stupid!
Come on, it's not like you
guys are gonna be together
your whole lives!
What if you break up?
I just want you
to think this through.
We won't break up.
[AYANE sighs]
If you say so.
[TEACHER 11A] So, let's review
what we've learned tonight.
The present progressive
form is "am waiting."
The past progressive
form is "was waiting."
Hey, I'm home.
[JUNKO]
Welcome back.
Dinner's ready, so go wash up.
I'm not hungry.
[knock on door]
Come in.
[JUNKO]
You need to eat something.
[door closes]
[stomach growls]
[STUDENT 11A]
Really?
That's what I heard.
[STUDENT 11B]
That's him.
That's so romantic!
Like right out of a movie!
[STUDENT 1A]
Think he stands a chance?
[STUDENT 1B]
No way!
[giggling]
You're so awesome!
I just heard that you're
applying to Koumei!
Everyone's talking about it.
Um, they are?
[SETSUKO]
That's unreal!
Seriously?
It's not a big deal!
Just get married already!
Yeah, totally!
[SETSUKO laughing]
[AIRA laughing]
I kind of hate you.
Yeah, lucky dog.
You don't stand a chance.
Her grades are way
better than yours are!
[KOTAROU grunting]
But he has love on his side!
[DAICHI]
Love won't pass your test!
[KOTAROU]
Uncle, uncle! Uncle!
[KOTAROU coughs]
Hey, are you actually serious?
About what?
Getting into Koumei!
You have to get a
score of at least 60.
I mean, I could do it.
[laughs]
Don't worry, I believe in you!
Jeez, Roman, stop hugging me!
--I mean it! Get off!
--Dude, you're so handsy!
[JUNKO sighs]
[vacuum cleaner running]
The mock exams results are in.
Here.
Azumi.
[CHINATSU] Are you really
applying to Koumei?
--Yeah.
--That's so awesome!
I'm probably gonna
try for a public school.
Oh.
[JUNKO]
Thanks.
[JUNKO] Excuse me,
I'm looking for Miss Sonoda.
[RYOUKO]
Oh. Hello!
Thank you for coming in.
No problem. You wanted to meet?
[DAISUKE]
Exams are pretty brutal, huh?
Yeah, and, my grades suck.
Is that so?
I'm just worried.
I might fail.
You look kinda pale.
Are you eating right?
Your parents are
probably worried, too.
Yeah, worried I'll go to Koumei.
They don't really approve.
Regardless,
take care of yourself.
Get lots of sleep,
eat well, all that jazz.
After things calm down,
maybe you should try
talking to your folks again.
[door opens]
[KOTAROU]
I'm home.
Hi, welcome back!
[phone chimes]
[KOTAROU groans]
[GIRL 11B]
Look, this bear is huge!
[GIRL 11A]
So cute!
[KOTAROU panting]
[AKANE]
Huh?
Hey, were you waiting long?
[AKANE]
Not at all.
It's been a long time
since we've hung out.
[KOTAROU, AKANE]
Hey. Uh...
[BOTH chuckle]
[AKANE]
Sorry. I know you need to study.
[KOTAROU]
It's okay.
So, this is...
[KOTAROU]
Hm?
...for you.
[KOTAROU gasps]
Wow, thank you!
Oh, uh, here.
Is it okay to open it?
[KOTAROU]
Sure.
[AKANE gasps]
[KOTAROU] I thought maybe
you could use it for track.
It's so cute!
Thanks so much!
[KOTAROU chuckles]
So? Can I open mine?
[AKANE]
Uh-huh.
Um...
I'm so sorry!
I know it's bad.
[KOTAROU gasps]
It's actually my
first time knitting.
Uh... Seriously?
It's awesome!
What's wrong?
[gasps] What the heck?
It's totally ginormous.
[gasps]
I'm sorry.
[KOTAROU]
It's perfect!
See?
Cozy!
Well, that's good.
Thank so much, Akane.
[AKANE]
You're studying a lot, huh?
[KOTAROU]
Mm-hmm.
[AKANE]
You always look sleepy lately.
[KOTAROU chuckles]
Eh.
[AKANE]
Are you staying up real late?
[KOTAROU]
Yeah.
[AKANE]
I see.
[KOTAROU]
I'm running out of time.
[AKANE]
Hm?
My mom's against the
whole Koumei thing,
so I tried to get
my test scores up
to prove her wrong.
But I'm still really struggling.
[AKANE] Having your family's
support means a lot, huh?
You know what?
For my last track meet,
my mom made me
a special lunch.
It had a note that said,
"Good work over
the past three years."
[KOTAROU]
Huh.
[AKANE] My parents were
always cheering me on.
It really meant a lot to me.
[KOTAROU] No matter
what, I'll try my hardest.
[AKANE]
Hmm.
Me too.
Exams are just
around the corner.
[KOTAROU]
Let's do our best!
[AKANE]
Yeah.
[KOTAROU groans]
[CHINATSU]
Uh...
[KOTAROU groans]
Oh, hey, waiting
for Akane's results?
[KOTAROU]
Mm-hmm.
[gasps]
[giggles]
Wait, was that Akane?
So did she get accepted?
--[CHINATSU] Ah! That's awesome!
--[KOTAROU] Yeah!
[CHINATSU laughing]
I'm so happy for her!
Your turn next, Azumi!
Yeah.
[footsteps]
[KOTAROU yawns]
[KOTAROU]
Morning.
Were you up all night?
[KOTAROU]
I was studying.
[milk pouring]
Listen, about high school--
Please don't start, Dad.
You can apply to
Koumei if you want.
But, if you don't
pass the exam,
you have to apply
to a public school.
Okay?
[RYUUNOSUKE]
Deal? Does that sound fair?
Yeah, sure.
[RYUUNOSUKE]
The other day,
your mother met
with your teacher.
Your teacher thought
Koumei was a poor choice
due to your current grades.
[RYUUNOSUKE]
However...
Your mom was inclined to
disagree with Miss Sonoda.
She asked her to
give you a chance.
Since you're trying so hard.
[RYUUNOSUKE] I know she's
a bit naggy sometimes.
But it's because she cares.
[KOTAROU groaning]
[KOTAROU sighs]
Oh. Is something wrong?
Are you hungry?
I was just about to
bring this upstairs.
Have a seat.
[JUNKO] I wish you'd start going
to bed a little bit earlier.
You're looking a bit run down.
You're working so hard.
But what good is it if you
get sick before the exam?
[JUNKO]
Here's some tea.
Goodnight, dear.
Uh, goodnight.
[JUNKO]
Don't stay up too late.
Do you have your exam ticket?
[KOTAROU]
Yep, got it.
I wrote down the
train schedule for you.
Don't you dare take
the wrong train,
or else you'll miss your exam.
I won't, Dad, I promise.
Here, it's your lunch.
Thank you, Mom.
Okay, well you'd better
hurry or you'll be late!
See you later.
We believe in you.
[KOTAROU]
Dazai once said.
"I must live up to my
precious promises.
And that is all that
matters to me now."