[ITALY] Last time on Hetalia!
The Newspaper Club
went around W Academy,
interviewing everyone about
their group activities.
They all sounded like fun to me!
Pasta!
Listen up!
More clubs need
to be interviewed!
No matter how stupid they are,
we have to talk to them all!
Germany, Germany!
I think it's time for merenda!
Can I have a gelato, please?
No snack-time
until we are done!
He is correct.
Let us wait for now.
Denmark here!
And Norway.
And Iceland.
I'm Finland!
[SWEDEN] We're--
[GROUP] Der Scandihoovians!
Any questions you
have, ask away!
Whatever you want to know
about us I'm ready to tell!
Close your legs, it
smells like blue cheese.
I want the camera
to get my best side!
Just flat-smack him.
Tell me about
these hooves.
Our ultimate goal is
conquering de academy, slowly,
with cheap and
easy-to-assemble furniture!
I'm so sorry.
Really, all we do is think up
Viking names for end-tables
and eat
lingonberries.
Honest!
I do not think
I am spelling
"lingonberries"
correctly.
I'll bet you
didn't know this!
In de times of greatest peril,
Scandinavian furniture
from all over the world
combines to form giant robot!
Domo arrigato!
Furniture Roboto!
Not really.
[GERMANY] No scheisse.
Whoa, what the--?
Why am I a rice-ball?
Freaky. But I'm still
the hero, so whatevs, bro!
I'm so glad you're asking
aboot joining the Canada Club.
We wear flannel shirts,
and eat poutine,
and tap maple trees for
their delicious sap,
and then sip our coffee and
gaze at our snowy mountains
as we smile aboot
our free health-care
and lack of gun crime, eh?
But you don't
really have to join.
That sounds cool.
But also
I am conflicted.
Because
of Bieber.
The Leave-Me-Aloners?
I don't like getting mixed
up in other people's drama,
so we don't ever have meetings.
Basically I just sit at home!
And that's a club?
Saved me from you.
Going home is too
much-a ball suck.
Huh? What's the
matter, big bro?
Drag me home,
you bastard!
Your group sucks even worse
than Switzerland's did!
[ELEPHANTS]
Elephants!
What's that?
Interview the Swim Team?
That's so sweet!
Yeah. Start
with cup-size!
[HUNGARY giggles]
[HUNGARY] Not to brag, but
we've won a lot of trophies.
Was it for the
breast-stroke?
Finally, a
respectable bunch.
[AUSTRALIA] Oi?
[JAPAN] Hmm?
G'day! Fancy a
ten-kilometer swim?
This is the part
where I say maybe,
but I definitely mean no!
It just don't feel
like a proper swim
unless I cross
the Dover Strait!
[PRUSSIA air guitars]
That's what Friends of Music
has become, thanks to him.
All day, with the broom.
Gott, he's an idiot.
--What's up!
--Ah!
So you speak Mexican?
No. Italian!
The clubs at this
academy are so weird!
I wonder why that might be.
[JAPAN] Hai.
Really? I thought
they sounded like fun.
Your standards
are rather relaxed.
[GERMANY] Why did
you stop, Japan?
Many clubs meet in that room,
including the Friends of Stucco,
the Lick-Your-Own-Elbow Club,
and the Competitive Sarong Team.
These ones sound even
weirder than the other ones.
I suppose we have
to check them out.
Correcto! It is our duty!
Duty?
Ja. I am with you.
But there is no telling
what we'll see in there.
[GERMANY] Huh?
[JAPAN] Hello?
[ITALY] M. Night Shyamalan!
[GERMANY] Uh.
[ITALY laughs]
Welcome to my lair,
Newspaper Club!
If you were wondering who was
the president of all those
awesome-sounding things,
it is I--Italy! Gotcha!
[GERMANY grunts angrily]
Why'd you set up all
these wastes of time,
you little dummkopf?
If you stop squishing my brain,
I'll make you vice-president!
Time for dessert!
Idiot.
[FEMALE NARRATOR] Having gotten
to the bottom of things,
they published their issue
and lived snackily ever after.
Especially him.