[FEMALE NARRATOR] The Earth.
She's a big blue ball-buster
who takes no crap from anyone.
So like me.
She's home to the W Academy,
a unique school where
the countries of the world
hone their mutant pow--
I mean, live the student life.
[GERMANY] All right!
The focus of our
next issue is clubs!
[VOICE] Italy!
[ITALY] Aww!
But blunt-force trauma is
such a downer, Germany!
I think we should write
about pasta, or girls! Yeah!
I don't mean the
weapons, idiot!
I mean the student
organizations!
It was an
honest mistake!
Please, do not fight.
Let me mollify you with
empty carbohydrates.
Carbohydolateso?
Yum!
Permission to speak?
We have to raise our hands
this way because Germany!
I promise,
it is relevant.
All right. Talk about
your elephant.
[JAPAN] I have created
a list of all weird groups
at the academy,
like, Karamu Siesta.
What in the hell
is that one about?
Oh, I know!
They have parties with
piñatas and churros an--!
"Siesta," not "fiesta!"
Jawohl! We will interview
all of the activities.
Even the one for that
little-girl pony cartoon!
Newspaper Club go!
Ah, yelling and organizing;
classic Germany.
What?
You want to write about us?
I suppose I don't mind
putting it all out there.
Oh--you know, like what
you do at your meetings
and why I hear timpani drums
every time that you move.
Manners!
Estonia, would you
talk to them for me?
Okay. I'd be happy to.
Many of W Academy's
best students
have gravitated to our
little choir group.
Latvia and Lithuania are both
famous for their choruses,
so we Baltic states are
fitting right in around here.
His compliments
border on Lithu-mania.
You know, it is
not for the nothing
that they call me the "Singing
Revolution" back at the home.
It's Mister Sparkle!
The one most important
thing about the Madrigals--
[RUSSIA] Eh...?
--is that the Soviet Bloc wants
to lock us in the basement.
If you die, I get
great pleasure-smile.
Gott im Himmel!
Bro, enough of that!
Start asking questions about
my Daring-Dudes already!
We do cool crap 380 days a year!
You can quote
me on that!
What the--? Ahh!
The Cold War's over,
dude! Cut it out!
Perestroika! Perestroika!
[JAPAN] Oh my.
[AMERICA] I thought
that was the safe-word!
[JAPAN (RICE CAKE)]
So, that happened.
It's about time!
I wondered when you'd get your
act together and come over!
We are very exclusive group-
it is just the three of us!
We are a triumvirate
of refined palates,
the intrepid epicureans of
the academy's Gastronauts!
Aww. I wanted to
be a Gastronauts,
but you guys wouldn't let me!
Because--watching you drown
everything in tomato sauce
would be the death of me.
We turned down Britain,
as well, so cheer up!
[TURKEY]
Posting pics of my food!
[FRANCE]
Paying too much for cheese!
[CHINA] Putting
rare animal on menu!
Gastronaut
powers, activate!
They're certainly full of
themselves, aren't they?
Certainly full
of something.
[JAPAN (RICE CAKE)]
Moving along.
Welcome to the lair
of the Hellfire Club!
But what sort of coven would
we be if we blabbed our secrets
to every stringer
who came a-knockin'?
So, if you truly are
dead-set on talking to me,
just bend this spoon with
the power of your mind
and I guess I can allow it.
I cannot help but wonder
which of the four houses
the hat put you in.
What?
You know, I have ways
of making you talk.
[BRITAIN]
What?
Fork that spoon!
Your Teutonic prowess
is the stuff of legend!
We having so
much fun here!
In fact just last week,
we venture down into dungeon
to fight band of orcs,
and Britain leveled up his
wizard twice, and rolled a...
Oh, so you're nerds!
Bollocks! Now they know the
truth about the Hellfire Club!
Really we just get
together and tabletop!
The best of luck to you
in your future wizarding.
All of the groups had
something in common.
There didn't seem to be a single
normal country in the bunch.
That's what makes them
interesting, right?
Don't you judge!
You three are the freaks!
It seems in some way
we are all unusual.
[ITALY] Worst cliffhanger ever!