[GERMANY]
Gut.
I was able to finish work
sooner than expected.
Maybe I should take a vacation
and go recharge myself.
[sighs]
Yay, we should go to Italy
because Italy is super fun!
[VOICE A]
Italy!
What? Italy? Why? I traveled
there not too long ago.
--[EVIL ROMANO snickering]
--[VOICE B] Italy!
Don't worry about it.
You don't have a choice.
Stupid potato eating bastard.
What?!
Wait!
Both of you are
telling me Italy!
[ITALY]
Rolling, rolling, rolling!
Hey, Commander!
I have a report for you!
Sitting around in
the tent is boring!
It's a serious problem for me!
How sad.
So you can't even make
good use of your down time?
I've no choice. We can
do something together.
No snuggling or
cuddling, though.
Yay! You're a great commander!
Look. What do you
think about trying this?
Japan told me all about
the pressure point stuff,
and he said you can get healthy
just by touching specific
points on each other's bodies.
[BRITAIN laughs]
Oh, yes. A piece of cake!
Sneaking into those fools'
camp is nothing for me,
for I am the great and
powerful British Empire!
--[GERMANY grunting]
--[ITALY screaming]
Wait! What in bloody hell?
Hey! What's going on in here?!
Why are you fighting?
You two are friends, aren't you?
Is that Britain?
This isn't what it looks like
if it looks like anything!
I was trying to follow
instructions in this book.
Apparently, there
are pressure points
around your shoulder blades.
--[bones crack]
--[BRITAIN screams]
[OWL hoots]
[ITALY]
Hetalia.
[NARRATOR]
This little tomato is Italy
from a long time ago.
Back then, he cleverly
and skillfully
made his way through life.
My, how things change.
--[MEDICI] For you.
--[ITALY] Wowie!
Thank you, Mister Medici.
[NARRATOR] The boy was loved
by someone who could TCB.
[ITALY cries]
Grandpa...
[NARRATOR]
Known as sexy Grandpa Rome,
he left the boy a
huge inheritance.
Italy didn't realize what
a comfortable existence
his life had been....
But he was about to find out.
[ITALY]
Hetalia.
Britain, ciao!
[BRITAIN]
Hm?
I have some scary news.
Um, your boss has decided
to change your religion.
I don't know if that will
be all right, do you?
Well, don't be absurd. Of course
I think it will be all right!
After all, my boss is
strong and very impressive.
Oh... You think so?
Look at him, he's
tough as it gets!
[KING HENRY VIII laughs]
[ITALY] I guess Britain's
boss is pretty popular.
It looks like Britain
is still doing well,
even after the
religion was changed.
[POPE CLEMENT VII]
Ahem. That man shows no respect!
An insult not to be forgiven!
I'm left with no option--
What are you going to do?
I shall make a statue
that annoys him!
[ROMANO]
Hetalia!
That's a legitimate
historical fact.
--Crazy.
--Interestingly,
each statue in Vatican City
has its own special meaning.
Italy, may I ask a question?
I'm curious as to why we are
touring Mister Vatican's place
so late in the afternoon?
[ITALY] This way we can
take our time sightseeing
since no entry after 5:00.
We practically
have the whole place
to ourselves until 5:30!
[NARRATOR]
At Mister Vatican's place,
you have about half an hour from
the time admission is closed
until they kick
your sweet ass out.
[ITALY] Also, Sunday afternoon
is hell, literally hell.
Literally hell?!
[NARRATOR] Even though many
people come during the weekdays,
tourists who can't enter
Sunday morning due to Mass
choose to go in the afternoon,
so things get fairly crowded.
Although it's not literal hell,
it can give you a panic attack.
I like to see sights.
It makes my place
seem very peaceful,
when the truth is
I'm in a not great fix.
Seems like everyone's having
a hard time these days.
Si, this scary guy
wouldn't let me
clean my brother's dirty room,
and said scary guy is calling
all the shots in politics now,
on top of me not having
very much money
and the shipping costs in Venice
being high no matter
what you're buying, so...
Basically, I have no other
choice but to accept my fate.
[JAPAN]
I feel you.
However, I plan on protecting
pasta with everything I got.
[BOTH]
Bam!
[GROUP]
Hetalia!
[CATS meow]
Ciao, friends! Just
call me Italy-cat!
--[CAT meows]
--What?
Si, I'm a real cat!
[CAT meows]
Catch you later.
--[ITALY snores]
--[CATS meow]
[GROUP snoring]