[FRANCE sighs]
Allez!
I'm about to quit
waiting for you.
Ah, bonjour, friends.
C'est moi, France,
the one we all love!
I'm certain you already know who
I am, but I wanted to assure you
I will continue to bring
beauté to the world!
It is with deepest pride
and greatest pleasure
that I announce I will be the
main character from now on.
No more filthy eyebrows
and crude food
for life will be magnifique.
Shut it! No magnifiquing here!
Boo.
[FRANCE]
Even if you somehow defeat me,
my second and third selves
will attack your quadriceps!
[GERMANY]
Uh?
In France, there
is a law that says
you cannot name a pig Napoleon.
Isn't that amusing?
[PIG] It's extra funny because
pigs are smart, oink.
They understand a lot of
what humans are saying,
and they can even operate
simple devices, oink oink!
[FRANCE]
Hetalia.
[FRANCE sighs]
My reflection on the Seine River
is even more beautiful today.
[PIERRE coos]
Oh no, Mister France!
We've got a big problem!
Germany is already approaching
very close to the border.
What'll we do?
What? Germany is?
That brawny ox sure doesn't
waste time, does he?
Oh, there he is! I can
see him headed towards me.
Oh no, je suis dans la merde!
Come back later, no one is home!
Un moment, Germany!
You are too late, I've already
constructed the Maginot Line!
--[VOICE A] Maginot.
--[GERMANY] Hm?
[FRANCE]
You cannot cross this line
for that is against the rules!
[VOICE B]
Maginot!
[GERMANY]
Marsch, marsch, marsch...
[FRANCE screams]
I never imagined
he would come here
through the Ardennes Forest.
What a nightmare.
[BRITAIN] All right,
chin up, there, stubble.
Now that France is over himself,
we can resume the meeting,
discussing, of course,
the Axis Powers and
how to stop and/or destroy them.
I did defeat Italy, so you
are all welcome for that.
No one thinks you're badass.
[FRANCE]
They don't?
Aw, what must they think
of you then after getting
pretty much knocked out
by Italy the other day?
Oh, just shut it, frog face.
Look, are you seriously daft?
If you keep arguing with me the
meeting cannot move forward!
[FRANCE] But your reactions are
so much fun to watch, mon ami.
Britain, I want to discuss
an important matter with you.
What is it?
You may not know, but I
was very busy last night.
Your point?
My point is I'm shutting down
for the day since I'm sleepy.
No, don't go on strike!
[FRANCE]
Here we go!
Magi-Magi Magical Strike!
Now that it's come down to this,
I'll use my right to go on
strike like I usually do!
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
What's up with that
ridiculous ensemble?!
In Britain, after
a certain incident
that shall not be named,
they created a law prohibiting
mail carriers from making any
eye contact with dogs, woof.
Magi-Magi Magical Stri--
Will you stop wearing that?!
You're trivializing
people's feelings
and making me very
uncomfortable.
Here, I came all this way,
but I can't go inside
because of strike.
Britain, your jacket is
so twenty years ago.
Oh, let me design
a new one for you.
Forget about me.
You should stop dressing like
you need attention
from everyone!
Hold it! You're just
disagreeing with me
for the sake of
disagreeing with me!
But your face makes
me disagreeable.
[AMERICA]
Dude, meetings go nowhere
when you guys are involved.
Complain to this stubble
who gets off by making
fun of my fashion!
Stop!
How dare you pull on my noble
stubble, you damn bastard?
[AMERICA laughs]
What are you laughing at?!
You crazy kids always talk at
each other not to each other.
Don't you know that's
bad form, dude?
--[FRANCE] Oh.
--[BRITAIN] Hm.
Let's take a sec to listen
to each side, and then...
...I can judge whose
opinion is most like mine,
and therefore better!
You don't have the
right to do that!
You're such a frightening child.
--[FRANCE chuckles]
--[BRITAIN grunts]
[MONACO gasps]
Mm!
So yummy! I knew you were a good
cook, but I did not expect this!
Feel free to continue
praising me.
I took out the smellies.
And the dirties.
I wanted to make sure it
was clean and delicious.
[MONACO]
Well, it is amazing!
But there's someone
even more amazing
when it comes to escargots!
What? Who is amazing?
[MONACO] I think we should
have a day to celebrate
the first person who thought,
"that snail looks good,"
and ate it so that the
rest of us could know.
[FRANCE] I honestly
don't know what to say.