[GERMANY] That concludes
today's training.
Dismissed!
Yay, thank you,
Commander!
But first, here is
your good-bye hug!
Ja, ja.
Addio, Germany!
I'll be seeing you tomorrow!
[GERMANY] I still can't
figure out what he's thinking.
What is with the kissing and
the hugging all the time?
Gimme hug! I like you, Germany!
[GERMANY] Cultural
differences, maybe?
Hmm?
"Understand How
Other People Think"?
Wunderbar!
Jew Gramps!
Give me a copy of that book!
And do it on the double!
[JEW GRAMPS 21A] Danke! Danke!
[JEW GRAMPS 21A]
That book didn't sell at all
in Italy and Spain,
but for some reason,
it's selling like
schnitzel in Germany!
[GERMANY] Hey, Austria.
Are you going somewhere?
You are so stupid,
so very stupid.
Do you have any idea how
important tomorrow is?
It's the day men give
gifts to women they love
or maybe just have
bodies they love?
Duh! Valentine's Day!
Ja, whatever, just
don't get lost again.
I don't have the time
to come get you.
Fine, then.
Thanks for nothing.
He was expecting
to get lost?
[GERMANY] Hmm. Let's see,
where's the Italian chapter?
Huh?
[explosion sounds]
This book is fail.
I've just finished making
these, won't you try them?
What sort of cooking
makes explosion sounds
come from
the kitchen, eh?
So, I have
ein question.
Let's say I see a
person every day,
and we are constantly
hugging and kissing,
and taking baths, and
sleeping in the same bed.
What sort of relationship
do you think that is?
An indecent one,
obviously.
[GERMANY] Indecent?
Well, unless
he meant Italy.
[ITALY] Morning, world!
Today, I'm going to kick
war stuff training's ass!
And yay, it's also
San Valentino Day, too!
Hey. I should get presents
for Japan and Germany!
Scusi! Can I buy some flowers?
Of course-a;
you're in luck.
I just-a made a few
fresh rose-a bouqets!
Ooh, che bellissimo.
I'll take two, please!
Going to work
with roses. Yay!
I'm so fancy and I like it!
[ITALIAN MALE FLORIST 21A]
Thanks, signore!
I see.
Italy just likes me
as a close friend,
so that means I've got
nothing to worry about,
nothing to worry about at all.
Morning. Hope you're
well, Commander.
I've got good news!
"Good news"?
Great.
This is from me!
It's a present for
the Valentine's Day!
Germany?
What's wrong?
[GERMANY] You are giving me red
roses on today of all days?
What does it mean?
Um. Exactly what
it looks like?
[GERMANY]
"Exactly what it looks like?"
But it cannot be;
he is just ein friend.
Who else have you
given roses to today?
Well, I guess you're
the only one, Germany!
Why?!
Does it not seem strange
to be only giving me a gift?
I'm confused.
Come on, there must be ein
girl or zwei that you like?
Surely, you've been
in love before.
Oh, yeah, I guess that
is technically the truth,
but it's uh--complicated.
So, this was just a
Three's Company style mix-up.
Um. It was kind of
a guy, though.
Ahhh! I'm sorry;
I'm so sorry!
[ITALY] So.
You want to play football?
[GERMANY] Ja. Good idea.
Okay. Here we go!
[GERMANY] He confessed
his feelings to me.
I feel as though a
response is necessary.
Do I tell him, "Nein"?
But it is not like I
hate him or anything.
Wait!
That was pretty good.
Wrong, not
good or pretty!
Fine! I'm sorry!
No football, then!
[GERMANY] Oh, what am
I supposed to do now?
Miss Hungary, looks like
you've got a package, here.
Oh, something for me?
Who sent it?
[HUNGARIAN DELIVERY MAN] Sorry;
I'm not supposed to tell you,
but I'll give you a hint.
It was someone wearing glasses
who had one weird cowlick.
Oh, okay! I got it!
Jew Gramps,
I need another!
Fetch me. The book
which is titled
"The Beginner's Guide
to Relationships:
for the Hard-Hearted German"!