We got together to have
a horror movie screening,
and I peed my pants.
[BRITAIN] Are we all ready?
I borrowed one of India's
recent horror films.
Namaste.
I feel like I should
be able to guess
what one of those films
would be like, but no clue.
Hm?
[INDIAN MAN 18B yells]
Oh no! What have you done?
This story is about a knight
who died after being betrayed.
Then his soul came back so he
could slaughter the bad guys?
Germany!
I'm so scared!
Yeah.
Gotta say bros,
that does look freaky.
[INDIAN MAN 18A] Oh...
[INDIAN MEN] Hah!
[chanting]
[BRITAIN] Are they dancing?
That's not scary!
What kind of murderous
ghost does a dance number
with those responsible
for his death?
Just what I'd expect!
India always makes everything
we suck at look like it's easy.
It makes me right happy
knowing more people
are watching our horror
movies these days, eh?
Who are you?
I'm Canada.
Wait a minute; y'sayin'
this is a Canadian flick?
Figured it was from Hollywood.
Hang in there.
No, it's all right.
I'm kinda used to it.
[FRANCE] I understand.
Please know at least
one of us appreciates
the charm of your movies.
You mean it, France?
The setups of your cinematic
works are so elaborate.
[FRANCE] Oui, they
are très élaborer.
Exceptionnellement élaborer.
And, in the end.
They throw it all away!
Uh, yeah. I guess so.
That sounds
well good to me!
[ITALY whimpers]
[JAPAN] What is
the matter?
[ITALY] In that
British horror film,
the main character
died at the very end!
Why are you such a strange,
twisted little creature?
You must be so lonely.
Germany made that
movie with me!
Blame him. Gah!
Oh, then let's watch
the one Germany brought!
Hey, girl! Oooh!
[AMERICA laughs]
All the boobs and stereotypical
gay guy throw me off.
[AMERICA laughs]
Fair.
Make boobs,
not gore!
[RUSSIAN MAN 18A screams]
[RUSSIAN MAN 18B] I see shadow!
Where is this
one from?
[ITALY] It's stressing me out!
[RUSSIA] Oh, sorry.
Is just video I made
at home, though.
My bad; wrong one.
[ITALY yells]
[RUSSIA chuckles]
[AMERICA] You know.
After seeing what
they make, dude,
I don't think my horror
movies are all that weird.
I hate to say this,
but I agree.
We got some real
freaks out there.
[ITALY mutters]
[JAPAN] Sleep well.
Now is time, I believe, to watch
one of America's scary film.
--Yeah!
Rock out! Hah!
[AMERICA roars]
Zombies!
There's no
way to get out!
[AMERICAN MAN 18A gasps]
Who are you?
Heh. I'm just an
ordinary cook.
Yeah...
Buddy...
[GROUP] Definitely weird!
See?
Jealous, huh?
[FRANCE sighs]