Hey Japan, you like to
use those throwing stars
whenever you fight, don't you?
[JAPAN] Eh?
Can I see a ninja throwing
ninja throwing stars?
Can I? Per favore?
Shuriken? Really?
Germany wants to
see ninja stars, too!
Uh, Ninja--?
Ja. I suppose. Show me.
Germany looks so
happy right now!
German ninja movies are
very popular, to Germans.
Germany.
I hate to be bearer of bad news,
but we said we'd be honest, so.
[SAMURAI 1A] Intruders!
After him!
Ninja!
Ooohh!
[SAMURAI 1A grunts]
Unlike in the movies, throwing
stars do not fly or stick.
It is highly unlikely that they
will even hit their target,
so they're rather
unreliable as a weapon.
I was unaware
of this.
Sharpened chopsticks
are far more better
because you can throw
them with precision
and also they are good
for stabbing things.
Nein. Lies.
Stars still
look cooler.
Piacere! Piacere!
[FEMALE NARRATOR] War
historically leads to shortages
in items such as rubber,
metal, and nylon.
In this particular
wartime tragedy,
they've run out of coffee.
Germany! Austria's angry
face gives me nightmares;
and now I'm afraid
to go to sleep.
Well.
What did you
expect, dumkopf?
We are completely
out of coffee.
[ITALY] I know.
That's why you have
to do something!
We don't have
what we don't have.
Have faith; you
can do anything!
I believe in you!
No way!
I believe in you.
[GERMANY]
"I believe in you."
That gets me every time.
[FEMALE NARRATOR] So true;
it gets him every time.
Germany tried to find
a substitute for coffee.
Wha...!
Here we go, Italy; this is
a coffee made from dandelions.
Do you love it?
You're so amazing,
Germany! Wow.
It's been so long, I almost
forgot what it tasted like.
All this from a pretty flower?
Ja, and it's more
nutritious than real coffee.
Get out of Europe!
Austria is going to
lose his mind over this!
Sadly, there is
one major drawback.
Excuse me, Germany?
Could you spare me some oil?
Why is Germany picking
pretty flowers like France?
[ITALY (RICE CAKE) sobs]
[GERMANY (RICE CAKE)
grunts angrily]
Germany! Germany!
What do you think?
This is one of my
super cool tanks!
Oh, so that is the M
eleven thirty-nine, huh?
[ITALY] Doesn't
it look super cool?
It's tall like you!
And has rivets all over.
So super cool!
[GERMANY] Ja, Italy.
I don't want to rain on
your tank parade, but--
Normally, the artillery guns
are not placed right there.
Can you even use it?
[ITALY mocking]
M eleven thirty-nine
has an artillery gun
attached to its body,
so all you have to do
to aim at your target is
to spin it around like whee!
It's a breakthrough in
looking super cool, right?
The priority
should be function!
Kay, so Germany didn't like it,
but you guys think it's
super cool, don't you?
[crowd cheers]
We'll crush Britain
to gnocchi with this!
[BRITAIN] Pardon?
Crap! Look out, Britain is here!
The British are
coming for our pasta!
[ITALIAN SOLDIER 1A]
Save the marinara!
[ITALIAN SOLDIER 1B]
Al dente or death!
Poor bastard. Rough day?
Germany! Germany!
This is the upgraded,
super cool-er Carro Armato!
The artillery gun is exactly
where it's supposed to go, too!
That is not really
worth bragging about.
Now, I'm going to show you
how super cool this tank is,
so don't look away or you
might miss the super cool!
"Cool." Ja.
[ITALY] One, two...
So far, not cool.
[ITALY] Yay!
[ITALY coughs]
[ITALY] Do overs!
I'll just leave this open.
Do you not get
the point of a tank?
Every time they fired a shot,
the tank got filled
up with smoke.
The soldiers inside
didn't like that,
so they decided to
leave the doors open!