[chuckles]
Congrats to me for winning the
"Carry Your Wife" competition,
not that anyone was
very much surprised.
It was fun taking the
pictures with Finland.
I'll put them up on my blog.
Ah!
What the holy heck is this?
My precious blog.
It's been turned into
a fan site for Russia!
Is big problem!
All Estonian
websites are hacked!
Oh no! I just found out
my blog has been with
the hijacked as well.
[MALE ESTONIAN B]
Agh! Such horror!
[ESTONIA] Who would draw a
picture of Russia looking cute?
And then why would they
put it all over my page?
The truth is...
...only one person
could have done this.
[RUSSIA] What?
Someone broke into
your blogging website?
That's not all--
They put up a drawing.
It was of you!
A drawing of you having
all the cuteness!
[ESTONIA] Why does he
always do this to me?
Not to be rude, but--
I am doubtful of your
innocence, Russia.
Who else would pull
this kind of crazy stunt?
I do not know
friend Estonia.
It is not me,
I swear it.
Do I need to
convince you?
Because I know
what will solve this
with no more
questions asked.
Magic metal
pipe of pain!
[ESTONIA screams]
Eh?
Estonia, dude!
Lithuania told me the deets,
so I'm here to help, bra!
Oh, America?
When it comes to
this internet stuff,
I am the man, my man!
Now let's track this bad
guy down, blow him up,
and send him to hell!
Wow. Yes thanks,
please be having at it.
[bird chirps]
S'up, bird! What's the haps?
Brah, your connection is slow.
[ESTONIA] Well,
it is a DSL line, so.
[FEMALE NARRATOR] Estonia's
internet is notoriously slow,
so connectivity
tends to be an issue.
Or 90's retro
for the hipsters.
Of course, American
sites don't help,
what with Flash pages, huge
images, full-screen videos,
and hilarious cats.
[ESTONIA (RICE BALL) yells]
We're getting
close here, dude.
And you?
Find anything?
Thanks to you, I think
we'll get him soon.
While you've been closing
in on his location,
I've been analyzing the
records left on the server.
I am starting to see
traces of him, now!
It is very exciting.
Check and
mate, hacker!
[ESTONIA] This is
where you lose, Russia.
Wasn't me!
Yes,
it was.
Yeah!
Heh. Who's that?
The hero
strikes again!
[ESTONIA]
I don't understand.
According to my calculation,
the culprit was--
Estonia!
I'm sorry about the
other day, buddy!
So the culprit
has been caught!
I'm glad to hear that, yeah,
now I can read your blog again!
I've been cleared
of suspicion.
And things have
been settled amicably.
What? Are you for serious?
No, is funny joke!
You knew this would not be end.
[ESTONIA] Ah, that was funny.
[RUSSIA]
Magic metal pipe of pain!
[ESTONIA laughs]
The end credits were three
times longer than the movie!