[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Once upon a time.
Once upon a very different time.
Believe it or not, Russia
was the one being bullied.
Those mean old
kids from Mongolia
used to chase him around.
And then, a rather
strange child joined them.
Hey asshat face,
you're going down!
[FEMALE NARRATOR] The Teutonic
Knights later became
the delight known as Prussia.
Back then, lonely Russia
thought the world would be
a better place if only Lithuania
would be friends with him.
Hey! I said stop; why
are you not stopping...
I don't want to stop because
you are very not nice to me.
Not so fast, Russia boy!
Attack!
Denmark and Sweden?
You guys are trying to
get me just like they are?
I don't want to play.
Help me!
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
General Winter.
A fearsome general with a
killer jaw line who previously
overcame insane armies
that tried to invade Russia.
However...
[GENERAL WINTER] Laters!
[FEMALE NARRATOR] Though
General Winter brought down
Napoleon and the Germans, he
wasn't effective on these guys
because they're used
to cold weather, too.
[GROUP] Huh?!
General Winter blows.
[KID RUSSIA] Ukraine!
Big sister!
Huh? Oh no, Russia,
what is wrong?
Besides obvious arrow?
Those meanies do
not listen to me.
Oh brother.
At times like this, why
don't you try using a spell?
What kind spell?
One that I do
all the time.
It's good for telling
people how you feel.
All you have to do is
show them your boobs.
show them your boobs!
Why say that twice and
why so loud the last time?
Now I am embarrassed!
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Nine times out of ten,
if it has to do with Ukraine,
there will be boobs.
What did I say?
[KID RUSSIA sighs]
[KID RUSSIA] I wish at
least I had one friend.
[KID RUSSIA] Do you happen
to be alone, like I am?
[KID RUSSIA]
Heh, heh! Come here!
Don't you want
to be friends?
[KID UKRAINE] I'm sorry,
he's in shock right now
what with being
rejected by a hamster.
Lame-o.
I see you!
I have got you, now!
Crap, Teutonic Knights!
Pledge your loyalty to
the Teutonic Knights,
although I am currently
shopping around for a new name!
[KID RUSSIA] You know, you
should consider the situation
more carefully before
you try to pick a fight.
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
In twelve forty-two,
on the mostly
frozen Lake Peipus,
Russian Troops and the Teutonic
Knights fought each other
in the "Battle on the Ice."
Looking around us,
we are both on the thin ice!
I don't care about that!
Eat my holy sword
with your butt!
Agh! Wait, your
sword's not that big.
[KID RUSSIA] No!
Please, stop the charging!
[yelling]
Wow. That was close.
[KID RUSSIA chuckles]
[KID RUSSIA]
Teutonic Knights;
I want you to listen to
me while you are choked.
Your impulses keep
getting the best of you.
I know you think it is awesome,
but I believe it will
be even more awesome
when those impulses
get the worst of you.
Right. I'm sorry, man.
[KID RUSSIA] I fought
the Teutonic Knights'
large army today.
It was hard fight for sure,
but we managed to win!
[KID PRUSSIA] I went to Russia
for some basic recon today,
when that crazy face attacked
us with his dirty tricks!
[KID RUSSIA] When Teutonic
Knights comes next time,
I hope he will come with
new name and also as friend.
[KID PRUSSIA]
Yeah, we lost a bit,
but it's too cold
there, you know?
I don't need Russia.
I don't need anyone;
I am awesome!