This is from me!
For the Valentine's day!
[JAPAN] Germany mistook Italy's
feelings for him as love.
So, he began reading a
book conveniently titled:
"The Beginner's Guide
to Relationships:
for the Hard-Hearted
German." And, then.
Do you maybe want to
go to dinner tonight?
Okay, yeah.
Sounds good to me!
What's going on?
You've been unusually
nice to me recently.
Not complaining.
[JAPAN]
Germany decided to respond
to Italy's confession of love.
[GERMANY]
Now that I think on it.
With the exception of mein own
family, I'm used to being hated.
My life has been a long series
of fights and suspicions.
That is until now.
[ITALY] Germany! Germany!
[GERMANY] Ja, he annoys
the scheisse out of me,
but he can be fun
to be around, too.
Maybe? And, if I'm being honest.
He has a very nice climate.
Perhaps I should think it over.
What the hell is wrong
with you, Germany?
[ITALY laughs]
Oh. Italy. You are here.
Yep. Lookie. Lucky me!
What?
You Scheißkerl!
Um. Okay, I'm sorry!
Seriously, what is
wrong with you?
Inappropriate doesn't even
begin to--I was right there!
[ITALY] All right?
I am more than aware
of your "habits."
[ITALY] I don't understand
why I'm in trouble with him
when we just got together.
Maybe it's because I bailed on
jogging to go get pizza instead.
Who can turn down pizza?
Oh, or maybe he found out I
drew pictures on the tanks.
I don't know.
Everything I do
makes him mad.
[ITALY] I'm sorry, Germany.
[GERMANY sighs]
I'm glad you understand.
Mi scusi!
Can we get some menus?
[GERMANY] Oh, yes.
There're some things
I want to give to you.
Although, I doubt
you'll like them.
[ITALY] Ah--Heliotropes?
You seem to enjoy
Greek mythology,
so I got them for you because I
heard they show up there a lot.
Wow, thank you.
But why are you giving
me flowers Germany?
It's weird.
Uh... Ahh!
No, no, I didn't mean
weird like that.
I meant it's not
Germany's style;
he's not big on fun
and spontaneity.
Oh. I still have
another gift for you.
[ITALY] Huh?
[GERMANY] I asked them to
make it into a tomato shape
since that seems
to be your thing.
Ahh!
Ahhh!
Ah. Wait. No, you've
got it all wrong;
I swear to you, this
doesn't mean anything!
[GERMANY sighs]
[GERMANY] From the
flowers to the ring.
I went through all the
steps the book suggested.
All that remains is the climax.
Hey, Germany.
Is this a good time to say I'm
sorry for drawing on the tanks?
[GERMANY] Ah! Italy!
Ahhh!
I said I was sorry! Ahhh!
[HUNGARY laughs]
Seems like you found
an interesting book
or something
completely random.
Hey, would you mind putting
some jam on my cake for me?
And yes, this book
"The Beginner's Guide
to Relationships: for the Hard
Hearted German" tells the reader
how to do things from
dating to a proposal,
but it's all
unbelievably crazy town.
So. When you say crazy, do
you mean like it is funny?
[HUNGARY] Oh, yes,
it's hilarious!
The funniest part was about
the marriage proposal.
Ahhh!
[HUNGARY] If someone
proposed to me like that,
I'd probably laugh so hard
I'd end up passing out,
or peeing my pants, or both.
Hey, uh, so,
uh, Germany?
Huh? Oh--
You there, Germany? Hello?
Germany? Germany?
Are you okay?
Achtung! Get it together;
we are getting behind.
Ja, but-- I still am not sure
where I'm supposed to
be storing all these.
You are a loser!
Does anyone else have an
idea where we can put them?
Nein! Run away!
[yelling]
What's the matter
with you, Germany?
You're burning.
That's not healthy.
[JAPAN] It is said that
it took about a week
for Germany's misunderstanding
to be cleared up.
What do we do with him?