[SPAIN] Romano!
No. No talking to me
when you look stupid.
Come on, faces sticking
in holes is hilarious!
Do it with me?
If it will get you to
shut the hell up, okay.
No, defin'ely
not hilarious.
Sei ridiculo.
[FRANCE laughs]
[BRITAIN] Bollocks!
Why do I have to
dress like this?
Because it is
April Fool's Day!
Wrong, loser!
This is all the
fault of a wanker.
What else shall I have to
endure to get my hands
on that bloody photograph?
Oh, you know, only
something you alone can do.
A fan request from
Ms. O from Tokyo.
"I want to see chibi
versions of everyone."
Of course, I realize
this needs special powers.
So work that magic of yours,
and make it rapide!
Heh. You want me to
make you small, eh?
Oh. You naughty wizard boy.
[BRITAIN] Get ready to be wee!
Give me that picture,
you tiny pervert!
No way in hell!
[AMERICA] Stop!
Bullying kids isn't PC anymore!
Please help; he does not
understand no means no!
Dudes, I hardly
recognized you.
What's going on?
Why is France a midget
and Britain dressed like
he's about to torture
Jack Nicholson?
I dunno, why are you dressed
like a gay pride parade float?
Shut it, limey!
I got this costume along
with a letter this morning.
There's a picture of me
I'd rather people not see,
so to get it back I had to
show up here, dressed like this.
Canada was sent
the same letter,
but he doesn't seem
that worried about it.
Not worried about it.
[KUMAJIRO] No way, eh?
Too busy with hockey?
[CHINA] I received same
creepy letter, additionally!
[AMERICA and BRITAIN]
Uh, China?
Okay, for real, who would pull
such a disrespectful stunt?
This is so much embarrassment.
I do not like it.
[RUSSIA] So it's not just me.
Oh good, I have
greatness relief, now.
[BRITAIN] Russia, what the hell
are you doing in the sewer?
[CHINA] Literal gross mistake!
[RUSSIA] I'm embarrassed!
[GROUP] Hetalia!
Germany! Hey, Germany!
Check this out, it's an
embarrassing photo of me!
Don't show it off,
you imbecile!
Oh no, I remember
doing that now.
If someone were to see this,
I would not be happy.
I wish I could show
this around, I'm hot.
[FINLAND laughs]
That picture of me,
you took it didn't you?
What are you meaning,
you piece of blackmailer jerky?
You snuck a picture of me!
Stop! This is
not the funny.
I should be embarrassed,
but I'm just not!
Ha! Don't forget
also the fishnets!
[GROUP] Hetalia!
[AMERICA] Are you kidding me,
dude? France was behind this?
Hey, guys! Wait for me!
You look like you are breaking
your own pro-hate law.
[AMERICA] Dude.
You need to give it up
already, Midget France.
Now where are those pictures?
I'm not the one in charge!
Wha--? All right,
then who is?
Get out,
it was you?
[SPAIN] Si, that
is right. It was me.
And I am muy, muy
furioso right now, too!
Uh!
We were supposed to all
meet at the plaza, not here!
Also, you guys look
funnier than me!
Uh!
[SPAIN] Although,
taking the time to show up
does mean a lot,
you know. Gracias!
[CHINA] Spain!
Explain what
is this about!
It's about April Fools
day, silly amigos!
I thought we could do
something different this year.
So, my plan was to get everyone
together and take the craziest,
most ridiculous picture ever!
See, like this funny one!
France, what kind of
invitation did you send
to get everyone
to show up?
[FRANCE] Uhh...
France made me
take their pictures
in compromising positions.
It was terrible.
Ah. Let's have
a little chat.
Help me, Pierre!
[FRANCE] I knew you
guys wouldn't come,
so I figured I'd invite you
in a more creative way.
Don't worry, I get rid
of these eventually!
Au revoir! See you next time!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
[GROUP] Agh!
Give me my picture!
[PRUSSIA] Huh?