Yo! What's up?
Let's start the
Nordic Council meeting!
Oh, it's a lovely day!
Perfect for a nice meeting.
Yeah, you're welcome!
You know it's always
sunny when I'm around!
[NORWAY] Meh, you know it's
always sunny when I'm around.
Whoo! Come on! Nordic Council
meetings rock the house!
--Ha, ha, ha!
--[ICELAND] I don't get it.
How come no one has
noticed I'm here?
I agree, today is
perfect day for meetings.
Have some of homemade
sweet treats I brought.
[ICELAND]
First, I've gotta compete with
this glasses
wearing non-Nord?
Of course, I have no
doubt you'd love to let me,
a most excellent
nation, join you.
Estonia! You didn't
have to bring these!
Kiiti, that was so thoughtful!
Eat the sweet treats, everyone.
They're sweetie and treatie!
[ICELAND] And... I'm already
losing to Baltic Four-Eyes.
[ESTONIA]
Hm?
[chuckles]
[ICELAND]
Gross.
What's his deal?
--[SWEDEN] Ice.
--[ICELAND gasps]
Are you okay?
[ICELAND]
Yeah, Svi.
I'm fine. It's just...
I think there's
something weird
happening with this meeting.
[ICELAND]
Second, our meeting site
isn't exactly what
I'd call "appropriate."
Let's meeting!
We can't start without a little
of this to get warmed up!
So, bring on the booze!
[ICELAND] Third, we're here
for a so-called discussion,
but Dan's already busted
out the alcohol, again.
Oh, don't worry.
I brought you a very
special beverage.
Aren't you lucky to have
such a capable big brother?
[ICELAND] There he goes with
his gratuitous consideration.
I'm just going to pretend
I didn't hear him.
[FINLAND]
Don't worry, Ice!
As long as you're at
Mister Ta's house,
if you're with a guardian,
you can drink no problem!
Takk, but I'm not a child.
[ICELAND]
Fourth, normally Finland would
add some random comment here.
But he's already gone.
So much eating and drinking.
If we had a sauna, this would
be the best meeting ever!
That's what I'm screaming!
[ICELAND]
Fin's in his fantasy land.
Hey, Svi...
I have a question.
Ja?
Don't we usually have
more dignified and,
you know, indoor meetings?
[SWEDEN]
Mm.
[ICELAND]
Today's meeting is, I would say,
kind of on the strange
side, don't you agree?
[SWEDEN]
Hm.
Oh, good.
Thank you for being normal.
[ICELAND]
Uh...
[ICELAND] Does this mean
I am the weird one?
I do live the farthest away.
[VOICES]
Yes!
--[DENMARK] Yo, Ice!
--[ICELAND gasps]
Happy Birthday to you,
our funny Ice Man!
This wasn't a meeting at all.
It was a surprise party for you,
and you're wery welcome!
I raised Ice, you know!
Oh, thank you,
but I'm guessing this gathering
must be some new European fad?
For real, it's not even
my birthday, guys.
Of course not, it's halfway
between your birthday and mine.
You're telling me grown men
throw these "parties"?
Don't be angry.
We only lied to you
to be friendly.
Now, let's celebrate
your birthday?
We're too old to be
celebrating getting older.
[DENMARK]
Let's party!
I don't do childish fantasies.
[DENMARK]
Let's party!
Or you could get some work done!
I don't need to work,
and you haven't let us
celebrate your BD with
you in like ten years.
We chose a location that
wouldn't be too obvious.
Why are you against it?
[ICELAND]
No matter how much older I get,
the age difference between me
and them will never shrink.
Why care? So what? It's stupid.
[DENMARK]
Eh?
Hold the phone, Ice.
You're not wearing your
normal ugly sweater today.
How are we supposed to
know that you're you?
[VOICE]
Lopapeysa!
Why do you care so much
about what I wear?!
Aw, now, don't
listen to him, Ice!
I think... you dress... cool!
Cool like when
you see the ugly,
you wish you were
frozen to death.
Ha, ha!
That is true.
Whatever, you guys are just
too old to get my fashion.
Ha! You better wear your
normal ugly sweater
at the next meeting!
Hey, Ice, can I get
a sweater like--
No! We're also too old to
be wearing matching outfits.
It's creepy!
Oh, come on, we should
all match next time!
[SWEDEN]
Mm...
It's so wonderful when
we can get along.
Your next Nordic
member, Estonia,
signing off for the night!