[NARRATOR]
Previously on Hetalia,
Italy went to Africa because who
knows and you don't really care.
We have proven to
Germany and Italy that
on this the African war front,
British Empire intelligence
cannot be bested!
Go suck it, Kraut!
[BRITAIN laughing]
Those tossers were like babies
before my brilliant boiled
egg manufacturing machine!
--[honk]
--[EGG CAN] Adorable!
Yeah, boiled eggs are well good!
Having tea peacefully
like this after a victory
makes me feel just-- Let's
see how should I put it,
simply terrifically gentlemanly.
[explosions]
Yo, Bri-tan!
[BOTH gasp]
[AMERICA] Sorry to keep
you waiting, dude!
But, you don't gotta worry
nomore because the hero,
which is me, is here.
[AMERICA]
America!
[BRITAIN]
Hetalia.
What's the deal, bro?
Not like you to have a hard time
dealing with those creeps.
You got old, huh?
I'm not old!
And you wouldn't dare say that
if you had seen me fight!
Yeah, whatever dude.
The point is, I'm here now,
so you can chill out.
Meet the elite, brah--
My troops!
--[CROWD chattering]
--[AMERICAN SOLDIER A] Cool!
--African selfie!
--OMG, I'm in Africa!
Great, I've never
been more worried.
But why?
[ITALY]
Yahoo!
[AMERICA]
Are you serious?
You can't go with that
lame ass operation!
Oh, yes, I can!
Some of us like to be careful
and make informed decisions,
instead of charging in all willy
nilly like an impetuous toddler!
You need to work on your
indecisiveness, dude.
Yeah, well, you need
to work on shut up!
There's no shame in caution!
[AMERICAN SOLDIER D]
This dude is Mister Britain?
I know you guys are brothers,
but you don't really
look that much alike.
[BOTH gasp]
Well, of course we don't.
I mean we are brothers,
but you know, not like--
Oh how shall I put it, um...
This is awkward when you
just say it out loud.
What were you saying?
Who me? A big brother?
Flattery will get you nowhere,
or everywhere, depending.
If we keep looking at each
other maybe, he'll go away.
[AMERICAN SOLDIER D]
Uh...
[AMERICA]
Dudes, I'm a hero!
I'll go say hello
to all the locals,
and subtly let them
know that I've arrived!
What?!
You did not seriously bring
your military band with you.
Duh, Bruh. Can't be
flashy without music,
and the African people have
kinda been waiting for me.
I do not understand!
why did you even come here?
Uh, because a real
hero was needed.
Yo!
I hate the British.
Please go away forever.
[BRITAIN laughs]
You are quite pathetic.
Oh, come on. What's
the matter, big fella?
Well, now what am I
going to do with you?
Listen, don't let
it get you down.
This is just how Africa is,
and you're not used to it yet.
I'm not wanted here very
much, either. Trust me.
There's no reason
to feel gutted.
[AMERICA]
Uh...
Thanks, but I'm good.
I was just roasting
a marshmallow.
Damn it! No more
comforting for you!
[AMERICA]
America!
Dude, seems like the weather
in Africa is just always hot.
We gotta have something else
besides this Marmite
poo-food, don't we?
It's nutritious, so
eat it. Eat all of it!
I bet I could beat you to
that hill over there because
you suck at life!
Your stupid challenge
is accepted! Start, now!
[AMERICA]
Let's go! Yahoo!
[BRITAIN]
I refuse to lose!
--[AMERICA] Huh.
--[CREATURE] Ohh...
No, that's poisonous!
Don't touch!
They may be ferocious, but
I'll be a-okay, buddy boy.
'Cause I'm the hero!
[screams]
Ew, it's a snake!
No worries, even heroes can
get into a little trouble
every now and again!
[BRITAIN screams]
[BRITAIN panting]
Oh, thank the gods.
It was just a silly nightmare.
[rooster crows]
This gentlemanly atmosphere
is definitely more
appropriate for me.
After all, it's hardly
reasonable for someone my age
to play nanny.
Yo, Bri-tan!
[BOTH gasp]