But I'm a virgin!
Just shut up
and keep going!
No! I'm not running
from you anymore!
[TEEN BOY 17A yells]
[AMERICA] All right!
That dude's the hero!
America. You should
know an important fact.
The main characters
in your horror movies
are far too strong!
[KIDS] Yeah!
[KIDS] Yeah! Yeah!
The way they can always
take down evil monsters
is not realistic!
Uh, yeah it is.
No, it's not!
Dude. We also have
a chick possessed
by a demon who kills her
whole family on video.
Sacre bleu! That's terrifying!
Okay, why did you want us to
bring over our horror movies
at such a busy time?
I thought we could compare
different styles, bro!
[FRANCE] Ignore him.
I thought we could
prove to America
how weird his horror
movies really are.
I like this game!
Can we watch the movie I brought
over first, please, can we?
My Spaghetti Horror
is one of the things
I'm the most famous for!
[FRANCE] Somehow I doubt pasta
is a decent medium for terror.
[GERMANY] I would not make fun
of Italy's movies if I were you.
No?
To put it simply. Italy's films
are a chaotic bombardment
of various entrails
and naked women.
Especially the entrails.
Sounds gratuitous.
Why would you have
a horror movie
without putting in the insides?
Because! People are sensitive
about their entrails!
[ITALY] Why?
Without guts,
what makes it horror?
Am I right?
I see your point.
Next I show you the best
horror movie ever made.
Wait. It does not fit in here.
Because you're trying
to put in a CD, ninny!
[FEMALE NARRATOR] You, too,
can learn how to compress
video files onto a CD.
Just go ask the internet.
[ITALY] Oh! A Chinese Zombie!
Yeah, that doesn't
really hurt at all.
Dude, check it out;
China's horror is hilarious!
[ITALY] Whoa!
You know, lately,
we've been making scary,
supernatural movie, too.
[MALE VOICE] Ka-boom!
[FRANCE] There's something
right behind you!
[JAPAN] How long has it been
since I last visited
my hometown?
The villagers were distant,
and seemed to be hiding
something from me.
It looks as though the
school has been closed.
[ITALY screams]
Japan's horror is dark.
It's good at giving
you anxious poops.
Thank you for
the compliment.
Yeah, they're pretty
frightening, but I mean.
I always feel like the
hero should be doing more.
More like what?
You know, go for the
easy answer for once.
Like don't let
them make it out.
Keep 'em in the TV.
Or no freaking out at
some blurry bullcrap.
Or just don't answer
the phone, dude.
It's easy!
[CROWD cheers]
Classic America
comment.
Please don't
say such things.
Japanese ghosts
are very sensitive.
[FINLAND] You like weird horror?
Don't forget about my movies!
Santa kills!
Right. Finland
knows weird.
[FINLAND] It all
starts with a scene
where a scary, frozen
Santa Claus gets excavated.
[BRITAIN] Excavated?
[SANTA CLAUS] Merry Christmas.
[FINLAND] The climax
shows naked Santa Clauses
running all over the places.
And their junk is blurry!
[BRITAIN] Scary in
more ways than one.
[ITALY] Why? Santa
is a good person!
Why?
If you want true horror,
mine are bueno?
Shut it!
We do not need to
traumatize everyone!
I want to see them
for sure, now!
[FEMALE NARRATOR] Spanish horror
movies are fairly well known
for stabbing you right
in your brain space.
Ah!
I just got traumatized!
[GHOST groans]