Belgium here! Hello, everyone!
I sometimes get overshadowed
by my flashier neighbors.
But I assure you,
I am totally neat too!
My waffles are world famous!
You should come by and try one.
And we can watch
Jean-Claude Van Damme movies!
Tastes like merde.
My older brother Netherlands
is tall, handsome, and aloof!
Keep it in your pants, girls!
I cannot sell
it for less.
Your sales strategy
is unparalleled!
But if I had
to nit-pick,
I suppose I'd say my
brother's a bit stingy.
[seagulls caw]
[NETHERLANDS] Yo! Lithuania.
Ah! Hello, Netherlands!
More cod and
herring, please.
I'll pay with cash, of course.
You are always to buying
much fishes from me.
I am so grateful.
I never knew the Netherlands
had such tasting for the stuff!
Do not stick your nose
where it does not belong.
[POLAND]
Uhh...
He loves fishies.
He buy big bunch
like this every days.
He will come back
tomorrow for more.
Every days?
But how does he keep
his place from smelling
like Red Light District?
Buy the fish cheap, use a dash
of salt, then pickle them.
Then sell them off
for a hefty profit.
'Cause cash is king.
Big Brother's
always so blunt!
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
The War of Devolution.
It involved the Spanish
Netherlands, not New Wave Music.
Ay! That went pretty poorly.
Netherlands is a lot
tougher than he looks.
He whipped it, whipped it good.
Pull it together,
you jerk bastard!
I tell you,
it is no use.
Even if you combine
all the food and weapons
we produce in España.
There is just not enough.
--Hey.
--Que?
Crap! Netherlands!
Lookin' for a fight,
you blonde bastard?
I'd be willing to part with
some food and some weapons,
for the right price.
Is that a joke?
We are at war
with each other!
Why burden yourself
with such technicalities
at a time like this?
Que? Seriamente?
It's like he's nice and
a jerk at the same time, eh!
But Señor, why
show such kindness
to one trying to
crush your cajones?
[NETHERLANDS] Money makes
the world go 'round.
[NETHERLANDS] Cha-Ching!
[SPAIN] Heh, heh, heh, heh...
Business is business,
as they say.
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Young Netherlands worked
with relative autonomy.
Without "The Man"
keepin' him down,
he had a low Gini coefficient.
That's G-I-N-I--
Oh, just Google it.
One day, his little sister
Belgium came to visit.
[KID BELGIUM] Big brother!
Would you like to
come to my house?
[KID BELGIUM giggles]
Make yourself
at home!
Try anything you like!
Okay, brother?
[KID NETHERLANDS stammers]
Is it not to your liking?
Won't you eat it?
Huh? Oh... yeah.
Money makes the
world go 'round.
Have a heart, mon frère!
That's as low as
I'm willing to go.
It might sort of be my fault
that Big Brother
grew up to be so mingy.
Hey Dutch Guy! Long time
for no see! Eh, buddy?
[NETHERLANDS] Come in.
[LITHUANIA] Well, you can
certain tell he is put time into
the maintain his
house and gardens.
Wow! Décor is less
drab than expected!
Like you have pulse!
Thanks for having us!
Is lovely house you have here!
I spend all my free time
cleaning the place,
so it's only natural.
Bro!
Your kitchen
is like mine,
except is missing
all the cockroaches!
[POLAND]
U-Uh...
Don't touch my kitchen.
I like to keep it tidy.
I always just
bring home take-out.
He clean area
he never use?
How OCD is that?