Japan. You look much
more serious than usual.
I am.
It is from this new game.
The main character's
company is failing
because his irresponsible
friends hid their debt.
You must save the company,
and your honor.
But the amount your company
owes is prohibitive,
and your so-called
friends betray you,
so all roads lead to seppuku.
This fantasy
sounds quite final!
Trouble is, nobody has ever
successfully beaten this game.
Perhaps you will be
the one, Germany.
You think so?
I guess it couldn't
hurt to give it a try.
[game sounds]
[GERMANY] What is this scheisse?
You can't do a damn
thing in this game
without buying the DLC!
Just skip to the
quick-time disembowelment.
[GREECE] Hey, Japan. Hey.
Somebody needs a widdle
belly-wub, Japan,
and this cat would
probably like one, too.
[SEALAND] Hm?
The Principality of Wy
was founded in Australia?
Finally, another country that's
even more of a noob than I am!
[SEALAND]
Don't fret, Wy!
As the former new kid
on the block myself,
I consider it my duty
to show you the ropes!
Micro-nations
for the win!
Why're you lumping
the two of us together?
Uh, 'cause
we're so alike?
Look, I know
we're both small.
--but that is all we
have in common, okay?
Hmph. I'm in the books
all official-like!
[SEALAND] Uh...
Strange news from Australia.
A family has declared
its nationhood
after a fight over a driveway!
Huh?
If there is new addition,
I betting Sealand
is pestering them!
He can be such
little spaz boy!
I need reining him in
before he does stupid thing!
[phone rings]
Hey, uh, Sealand?
You are being good?
[SEALAND and WY laugh]
[LATVIA] Oh! So,
you are get along?
That is greatly news, you two!
[SEALAND and WY]
Ahh! Upside-down...
[LATVIA] Wait, what you
are talking about?
Did you say "upside-down
dead guy in tree?"
[SEBORGA] Ciao--it's a
pleasure to meet you!
My name is Seborga!
I was Italian, back before
I became my own man.
Ay-yi-yi, that's enough freaking
out over me for one day.
This is a red sauce, and hanging
like this is molto relaxing!
You're disrespecting the
sovereignty of my tree, mister!
And that's a massive
waste of tomatoes!
You're Wy, is
that right?
Ah. I may have to look you up
when you're a little older, eh?
You always wanna put your best
thumb forward, as they say.
You know--I didn't wanna
get stuck in this tree.
But these are the
sort of crazy hi-jinks
we micro-nations get up to, no?
I dunno--people
show me respect.
What's the big idea,
scaring us like that?
I mean it! You frightened
us half to death, you dummy!
How'd you think we
were gonna react...
[WY] I wonder.
Will people lump me together
with these knuckleheads
just because I'm new?
Wow!
That folk costume you're
wearing is so pretty, Ukraine!
I like yours!
This one is a little too loose!
See?
Maybe they're
old-fashioned,
but you find some very
interesting clothes
when you go digging
through history.
"Interesting?"
How exactly do you
mean, Hungary?
Like this
colorful one!
Wow!
He's a rainbow!
And some European men wore
their swords like this!
I, uh, cannot look!
How he does
not trip over it?
And then there's this fellow
with his cute little hood!
Aw, he's just
adorable!
Go ninja,
go ninja Pole!
Ruffs like this were
popular a long time ago,
but they would have been a
bother in day-to-day life.
Is that so he does not
lick his stitches?
And now!
The very best of the bunch!
[CRETAN WOMAN 19A] Omorfi Kriti!
Why are they out?
Go on! I think it
would suit you!
But they'd see
my Carpathians!
[LIECHTENSTEIN] So, the
ladies of Crete wore stuff
that made spectacles
of their breastacles?
Honestly, it's a wonder the
men ever got anything done.
Pasta!
Put your
tomatoes away!