[CANADA]
Hello, I'm Canada.
[VOICE]
Canadaan.
[CANADA] People often
mistake me for America.
But they also say
that he and I have
very different personalities.
This is Mister Kumandengakuro.
He's my conversation
partner and good friend.
Who are you?
[CANADA]
He never remembers my name.
We've been friends
for a long time, too.
Who are you?
[BOTH]
Hetalia.
[CANADA] My neighbor's
kinda really noisy,
--[AMERICA] Neighbor!
--but my place is
nice and quiet.
[AMERICA screams]
[CANADA] Yeah, he's more
than kinda really noisy.
Canada, my man!
Oh, hello there, America.
Don't you think
you're overdoing it
with all the maple stuff, dude?
What? I enjoy maple stuff.
[KUMAJIRO]
Hm.
[NARRATOR]
Mister Canada's house is
ridiculously full of
maple-themed items.
What's weird is he
actually likes it.
Give me your fur! Do it, France.
Do it now or else! Give it!
I am trying to get past you,
so get out of my way!
[BOTH grunting]
[NARRATOR]
Mister France and Mister Britain
have always acted like
children with each other.
They fought in many
different places.
[BOTH growl]
[NARRATOR] And that includes
Mister Canada's house.
I'm gonna defeat Britain and
make you my little brother
for sure, okay, Canada?
[CANADA]
Yeah, okay.
But we're completely
surrounded right now,
how can you be positive
we're gonna be safe?
[FRANCE]
I never said we'd be safe.
However, I won't give up
no matter how many
decades it takes!
Aw, thank you for caring.
The point is, I don't
know what's going on.
The local militia's
fighting style is offensive.
It lacks fashion, as if
they're not even European.
[FRANCE]
Then, why don't we change it?
Let's give them something
with a little more flair!
Of course, undoubtedly our
lives should come first, though.
[NARRATOR]
It's said that the fight
between Mister Britain and
Mister France over Canada
ended in half of an entire hour.
That was scary!
--[CANADA] Hetalia.
--[KUMAJIRO] Who are you?
I wonder why people keep saying
that I don't really stand out.
You know, I think my maple
syrup is pretty great, eh?
I remember when I used to
be pampered by everyone.
That was so nice...
Oh Canada, I can introduce
you to your brother today,
if you would like?
So, um, what kind of
person is my brother?
Well, let's see...
He is a bit mischievous, but I
think you'll like him all right.
[CANADA]
My brother.
I hope I can get along with him.
[BRITAIN] Hey, America!
Come over here for a bit!
Why? What do you
want me over there for?
[CANADA gasps]
Huh?
Wow. I can't believe that
we both have the same face!
[AMERICA laughing]
Nice to meet you. I'm Cana--
Boring.
Uh... Did you know
that you're my brother?
[AMERICA]
Britain! I'm hungry!
Stick some food in my face hole!
[CANADA]
Never mind.
I guess it's been like
this my whole life...
[BOTH]
Hetalia!
[CANADA] I was hoping I
could have lunch with him,
but it looks like
he's kinda busy.
--[KUMAJIRO] Hey!
--[CANADA gasps]
[KUMAJIRO] Are you positive
you wanna back down here?
[CANADA]
Huh?
You didn't ask.
But I'm just saying
it's not always best
to take the passive route.
It's okay to speak up
and seek attention, eh.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I'm gonna try to speak to him!
[AMERICA laughing]
It's... lunchtime?
Lunch! Lunch! Lunch! Lunch!
All right, you both want lunch.
I've got it, now, shut up!
[BOTH]
Hetalia!
[NARRATOR] The Internet is
popular in Mexico, tambien.
Hey, you.
Yep? What is it,
Mister Kumasaburo?
[KUMAJIRO] Mexico is calling
for ideas to be submitted online
on how to help them make a
better overall impression.
I emailed them and said
they should put Canada
in their country.
What? Why me?
A reindeer!
How weird.
Quiero hot milk suddenly
for some unknown reason.
Quiero ver la puesta de sol.
And I wanna play in the snow.
[NARRATOR] It seems Canada
is a symbol of happiness.
They do have a pretty
hot prime minister.
I don't think it'll
be like that.