[GERMANY]
Hm?
Japan, what is that
on top of your rice?
Ah... This is my
delicious canned beef.
What? You're eating canned beef?
I'm eating canned beef, too!
Why are you having
to that eat today?
I expected more pasta.
Either way, it's Italian,
so it's bound to be delicious.
--[ITALY] Uh...
--[BOTH] Huh?
I'm sure they used normal,
yummy beef for this,
but it tastes like
the cow flesh was in
some weird chemical reaction
at the manufacturing factory.
[groans] Our military
canned food tastes like
maggots might have been eating
it, but not in a good way.
[GERMANY]
Italy...
Would you like some chocolate?
[ITALY]
Yeah...
[JAPAN] Would you like
delicious canned mackerel?
[ITALY]
Yeah...
This is molto bene!
My Yamato-ni beef
is delicious, too.
[ITALY]
Grazie.
Once upon a time, you
weren't supposed to think
your food was tasty or that
would be considered a big sin.
Talk about a living hell.
What?! "Delicious"
was forbidden?
But why?!
Delicious things are wonderful!
[ITALY]
That's what I said!
Wow! They just went old
school, reminiscing on us.
I remember those days...
[DEVIL BOSS] Back then,
I was completely overflowing
with all those people,
which forced us to work 24/7.
Talk about a living hell,
but literal!
[JAPAN]
Mister Germany, look.
I made these based
on the biscuits
you taught me how to
make that one time.
[GERMANY]
Really? My recipe?
I tweaked it a little and
made it for our military.
It's hardtack. I don't
know if you'll like it.
Whoa!
I wish I could have seen Germany
teaching you how to cook.
Nein.
I wanna try some hardtack!
All right... But it
may taste plain.
Well, food on the
battlefield is usually plain.
That's true.
Hey, you can use this, though!
This is called Vegemite;
Australia dropped it.
Italy! You can eat
anything but that,
it will be too much
for you to handle!
[BRITAIN]
Boing.
Hardtack is mild
and easy to eat.
Ja...
So this is Vegemite, huh?
[GROUP chattering]
What the bollocks do
they look so happy for?
[NARRATOR] Since they
had to carry their food
around with them during the war,
both the Allies and Axis
Powers tried to develop food
whose quality wouldn't change
in harsh environments,
such as deserts and the tropics.
We have potatoes...
But how to cook them?
Konpeito! Salmon! Hardtack!
Let's just put
everything in a can!
Dude, I know we thought
this old canned food
might still be good, but so
far, everything tastes like
we're licking the wrinkles out
of a buffalo's salty satchel.
My body rejects it,
and tears are coming out of
my eyes all on their own.
Probably not our
smartest endeavor.
We're almost done; we can
do it! The last food is...
...the fruitcake stored in
Colonel Taylor's basement
for over one hundredish years!
[BRITAIN] Are you taking
the piss, America?!
After all the nastiness
we've put in our bodies,
why save the worst for last?!
I don't think we can
digest food that old!
[BRITAIN]
Oh? It's edible.
[AMERICA]
Yep, not bad.
[GROUP]
Hetalia!
Our field rations
are freakin' awesome!
Granted we are on
the battlefield,
but do you think you'll
be okay eating all that?
What? This is normal.
There is nothing normal
about that amount!
God bless it.
--[VOICE] Modest.
--[AMERICA] Hm?
[BRITAIN]
To be perfectly honest,
I'm getting tired of eating
biscuits and oatmeal
every bloody day.
Britain-bro, wanna
try some of mine?
Dig in, dude!
[BRITAIN] Oh! Are you
sure about that?
Duh.
[BRITAIN]
Thank you!
First, whatcha gonna give me?
I don't want it, then! Rude!
So, why don't you let go?
America won't do much for you
unless he gets
something in return.
[GROUP]
Hetalia!
There's like a crap
ton of German soldiers
around here.
We need to be careful.
The hell, man?!
Why are you swillin' tea
like a fairy princess?!
Actually, you ninny,
it's a gentlemen's habit to have
tea every day at a set time.
--[VOICE] Pleasant Britty.
--Try a cup
and enjoy the moment.
I drink coffee, not tea!
Whether on the battlefield or
simply drinking tea at home,
having a lovely, strong cuppa
always makes me feel
gentlemanly and oh-so-calm.
One cannot call
themselves an adult
until they can
appreciate a good tea.
[gun cocks]
So that tea your
drinking doesn't have
some sort of special escape
plan in it, does it?
Classic!
Guess what?
While enjoying their tea time,
they got surrounded by the enemy
before they realized it. Yay!