[ITALY] Oh yay!
I love it when we
get to go to Japan's!
Ja, just promise
to behave today.
First, I'm going to have a snack
and pet a calico kitty cat,
and then, after that,
I'll take a bath
and have another snack
or two, and then--!
[GERMANY] Will you shut it?
Japan, we have finally arrived.
[JAPAN] Oh, hello to you both.
Thank you very much for
travelling all this way
to attend this
meeting I am hosting.
[ITALY] Japan!
Ciao, Japan!
Ciao, Japan! Ciao, Japan!
[JAPAN] By all means,
please take a seat.
[ITALY] Taking!
Thank you, Japan, for
inviting us here today.
Germany and Italy,
I would like to offer
gratitude to both of you
for taking the time out of your
busy schedules to make it here.
I'm most humbly
delighted and honored.
Welcome to my home, gentlemen.
Additionally, to celebrate
the one year anniversary
of the signing
of our alliance,
I have prepared a
modest little soiree
that will be held after
our scheduled meeting.
It would be most appreciated
if you could attend.
[ITALY yells]
Come on! We're friends!
Stop being so formal, okay?
Apologies, Italy,
but at my place,
this is how we greet others;
it is proper manners.
Just let the poor man
finish his greeting!
This is my super
good friend, Japan.
Like his stereotype, he's
a very serious character.
I'm finding the main
problem is with the spring.
It makes a sound
like chika-chika.
Why don't you try
a chikaclanker?
A chika-clanker?
Perfect! Danke schoen!
[ITALY] Japan's not so
uptight with Germany,
like he gets to think
they're equals.
They even talk
about the hard stuff.
I don't know why neither
one of them are into
chitchat during a meeting.
Now, I must sing.
[ITALY and
the cat sing]
There is no singing
during science meetings!
Do you have something
to contribute?
[ITALY] There is another
thing that makes me think
Japan is too serious.
Oh, yeah, I don't
understand that.
[ITALY] When he
talks over my head.
Therefore, I think
it would be best
if we explained it
to Italy this way.
Nein, we should just
stick with my plan.
This way.
[ITALY] He holds a meeting to
discuss the best way to hold
the other meeting to make it
easy for me to understand.
Perhaps we should let
him decide which way
will help his comprehension
ability the most.
Italy, wake up!
[JAPAN] His brain
has made him tired.
[ITALY] All right! Bath time!
I've been looking forward
to this all day long!
Splish-splash! Splish-splash!
Looks like your energy has
returned at full force, Italy.
I heard both Japanese
Samurais and Grandpa Rome
loved the hot springs.
Seems like we have
a lot in common, huh?
It is also my understanding
that they were rather
fond of springs.
Grandpa Rome liked it best
when he drank his face off
while he was in the
hot spring water!
He'd drink again when
he got out, and then,
everyone would get ready for
the entertainment district
and manscape
like crazy!
Seriously?
Rome's place was
like that, too?
Are you seriously?
It's like they were
practically identical!
I guess, but those activities
weren't limited just to them.
Oh, I forgot; I brought my
super secret samurai with me!
I'll show you, but
you can't tell anyone!
[JAPAN] How do you
have a samurai?
[ITALY] Zoom!
Where are
you going?
[ITALY] Look! Check out
my way cool samurai!
All right, what is all
this excitement about?
[GERMANY gasps]
Hey there,
Germany!
We were comparing
our samurai spirit,
so I thought I'd show him
what I was working with!
[FEMALE NARRATOR] His vest has
several pockets to let him carry
a lot of military goods.
Since it resembles
samurai armor,
it's referred to as a "samurai."
I don't know what's going
on and don't tell me.
Right there with you.
Here's to our
pact! Evviva!
--Kanpai.
--Prost.
Nicely put. I'll drink to that.
No, Japan, you
can't drink this!
It's called alcohol, and it
will make you wastedy facedey.
You should wait to
drink until you're older.
You are much
younger than me.
You do realize that, right?
[ITALY] Get out!
Japan the Serious
made a funny!
Have some
juice, silly.
Oh.
[GERMANY] Japan is
unexpectedly amusing.
But I am telling you the truth!