[LISA] When I was 19,
I took a trip alone to
France, in the Spring.
I've always been captivated
by the idyllic scenery
of Mont San-Michelle.
[LISA] There was so
much beauty all around.
I nearly filled my camera's
memory on the first day!
Oh wow! What a hunk!
[LISA gasps]
I'm sorry.
I took your picture
without asking.
Oh! No problem, ma cherie.
And I'm sorry for
approaching you so brutishly.
You're magnetic.
[LISA] Uh...
Are you here on holiday?
If you would like, perhaps
I could show you around?
Not if it's
any trouble.
Vous etes tres belle!
Bien sur je vais bien!
Come, Madame!
Your tour awaits!
[LISA] And that was
my introduction
to the charmingly
narcissistic France.
[FRANCE] Come. This way!
[LISA] Okay!
O-Ohh...
To bring cute,
impressionable tourist girls,
there is no finer
spot on the island.
Sorry, what was that?
[FRANCE chuckles]
[LISA] So, uh.
My name is Lisa.
I don't think I
got yours, good sir.
Oh? Moi?
They call me France, my darling.
I strike when the
mood strikes me.
If you're a tour guide,
you have credentials, right?
Never mind that.
There is so much more!
How do you say
'Rohypnol' in French?
On a lighter note, have you ever
heard of the Hundred Years' War?
I know a bit.
Smart and pretty?
A war raged between
Britain and France.
Many things led
to the conflict.
Claims on territory,
the Throne, flocks of sheep.
They captured our king.
And Britain demanded a
ransom of three million écus
for his release!
My bad!
I got caught.
Sadly, due to lavish living,
we were bankrupt!
It was the king, not me!
Even the breathtaking
Mont Saint-Michel
acted as a stronghold!
For real?
[FRANCE] When things
seemed absolutely hopeless
during the war, a girl was
sent with a divine mission.
She knelt before the
Dauphin, and said--
[JOAN] Your Highness.
God has spoken to me.
He commanded me
to make you king!
And do you know who
that brave girl was?
Joan of Arc. Like, duh--
Of course! That's so
awesome that you know!
'Cause I totally knew it too!
[LISA] Where did those
head sparkles come from?
[FRANCE] Joan's first job was
reviving the flagging hope
of a disheartened king.
After lifting the
siege at Orléans,
she brought the king to Reims,
the traditional coronation site,
where he assumed the French
throne as Charles the Seventh.
Just proves what
a girl can do
when you take away
the glass ceiling.
[FRANCE] She accomplished
all of this in four months.
Only the Home Alone
kid could top that.
But, there was
no happy ending.
'Cause y'know, they burned her
at the stake and all, right?
[FRANCE] Sadly, yes.
In Fourteen Thirty-One, during
the closing days of May.
She put the king on his throne,
and he abandoned her to flame.
It seems the stronger
one's patriotism is,
the more often they are
beset by tragedies, oui?
[LISA] I suppose so.
[FRANCE] I may have taken that
bit from a fortune cookie.
That is enough
history talk, eh?
Let me tell you a
little about myself.
Of all the countless
people tossed into
the crushing jaws of history.
I wish their souls
a chance at rebirth.
Into a peaceful life--
a warm home.
And all the love they're due.
When I first laid eyes on you,
I realized a true
miracle had occured.
May you always find happiness.
And my wish came true!
I could not've picked
a finer person.
Thanks, but what do you--?
Huh?
He was here
just a second ago.
Who was he?
Then like the wind, my
mysterious stranger vanished!
[MOTHER] Sounds like
my Harlequin novels!
[LISA laughs]
[AMERICA] Jeez, man.
France is a total playah!