[ITALY-CAT yawns]
Ciao, friends!
Just call me Italy-cat!
What? Si, I'm a real cat!
A real cat who loves
girls that are cute,
pasta that is al dente,
napping that is in the sun,
and singing that is like so:
[meows]
Basically, I am one of the
friendliest kitty cats.
All I want are
snuggles from ladies
and, well, how should
I put this, exactly?
[BOTH]
I'm just like this guy!
[ITALY sneezes]
This is my best friend
in the whole world
who lives next
door, Germany-cat!
[GERMANY-CAT]
Hm?
Hey, Germany, these are our
new friends who can see us
even though we can't see them.
You should join us, amico!
Your words are nonsense
to me once again,
but I will humor you.
[GREECE-CAT]
Smirk.
[ITALY-CAT]
Germany-cat is the facilitator
of many Euro-cats such as
myself, Greece-cat, Spain-cat,
and we all trust him so much.
[GERMANY-CAT grunts]
That is not true.
Why, if Germany-cat were
to get sick or something.
We'd all get the sick, too.
[GREECE-CAT, SPAIN CAT groan]
That is too much responsibility!
[GROUP]
Hetalia!
[NARRATOR] Including the
ones we don't care about,
there are almost two hundred
wondrous nation-cats.
The most popular of which
decided to form the G8, or G7,
depending upon on
Russia's attitude.
They discuss household policies
as well as arrange "canned
cat food trade agreements."
Sometimes, Italy-cat forgets
to use his inside voice
when saying the American
President's name.
[QUEEN ELIZABETH-CAT]
Why does he have to shout?
[GROUP murmur]
[NARRATOR] These meetings
are held once a year
by the following kitties:
America-cat!
Britain-cat.
François-chat.
Germany-cat.
Italy-cat!
Canada-cat.
Japan-cat.
Russia-cat.
[NARRATOR]
These are the G8 pussies.
[GROUP meows]
I wonder if they have any food.
[GROUP]
Hetalia!
[FRANCE-CAT groans]
I smell something unpleasant
coming from your house.
Nah, dude, I'm so over all that
Leh-meow Brothers debt business.
Everything's fine. Probably.
[BRITAIN-CAT]
That is hardly convincing!
The owners of us Euro-cats
had their income cut,
which means, tragically,
so has our food.
[BRITAIN-CAT]
Terribly depressing, isn't it?
[GROUP meow]
Then, we need to come up
with ein solution... Hm?
[ITALY-CAT] But, we can't
do anything special.
we're just a little
kitty cats, you know!
[RUSSIA-CAT]
Is true!
You losers are dummkopfs!
[JAPAN-CAT]
Huh?
[GROUP]
Hetalia!
[FRANCE-CAT chuckling]
[NARRATOR] Mister France-cat
loves to arrange the interior
of his house based on
his so-called taste.
Never one to sharpen claws
on his own furniture,
he's careful with his home.
[FRANCE-CAT] That being said,
houses in Paris are old.
They haven't been kept as
nice as my house, just look.
This house used
to be "tres bien".
But now, see how vulgar it is!
My sense of beauty cannot
allow such atrocities!
Oh, how I wish a special fairy
would appear and restore it
while I'm taking one
of my many cat naps.
[SPAIN-CAT]
Time for me to show my skills!
[FRANCE-CAT]
Hm?
I can do it!
Actually, it will be fine.
Don't do anything.
[GROUP]
Hetalia!
America...
I think you might be my
friend, is that right?
Duh, I'm your friend.
I'm friends with like
the whole world, dude.
Hong Kong-cat hasn't
been coming home lately.
Do you know why?
[AMERICA-CAT]
Negative.
[CHINA-CAT]
I'm so lonely now.
I just want anyone to
pet me and rub my belly.
I honestly don't care who it is.
[AMERICA-CAT]
Try this.
Tuna cures everything!
Even loneliness and
lack of likeability!
[CHINA-CAT inhales]
Oh xièxiè, my friend, America!
Now, hold on a second.
Are you trying to feed
me tuna made in China?!
Well, I would be if
you'd open the can
and start eating already.
[BOTH]
Hetalia.
Japan-cat! Japan-cat! Ciao!
Have you heard the rumor
that's been going around?
Could you be more
specific, please?
I'm talking about
your fancy Avenomics.
Abe.
Teach me about it because
I don't understand
how Avenomics works.
Come on, tell me
about the Avenomics!
It's... Abe.
Oh no! I've been
saying Avenomics wrong!
What other word do you have for
the economics of the hopeless?
Avenomics! Avenomics! Avenomics!
--Avenomics! Avepasta!
--Abe! Abe! Abe! Abe!