[ITALY]
Germany, help!
I'm surrounded by
adorable kangaroos!
Kanga-who-now?!
Where in fresh hell are you?!
[ITALY]
Australia fresh hell!
Ahh! Don't bite me there!
--Bad touching!
--[GERMANY] Italy!
[GERMANY] I'm Germany, a
country in Central Europe.
And at the moment,
I'm having the biggest
problem in my whole life.
[ITALY]
Ciao!
Hey, Germany, I just happen
to be in the neighborhood
for no real reasons!
Are you on your way home?
'Cause I can give you
a ride in my L-Three!
You know sitting next
to me will be fun!
C'mon! Sit down!
Agh! My L-Three just broke!
[ITALY]
No problema!
See, I cover it up!
[GERMANY growls]
What's wrong? Does
your head hurt?
[GERMANY] My only "problema"
is that he's my friend.
In order to better
understand my special pal,
I decided to learn from the
wisdom of our predecessors.
[GERMAN BOOK]
Are you German?
Ja or Nein.
[GERMANY]
Ja.
[GERMAN BOOK]
Do you currently have friends?
Ja or Nein.
[GERMANY]
Ja...
[GERMAN BOOK] For a strategy
with more than two countries,
please turn to page 1287.
If you actually have friends and
aren't just fooling yourself,
cooperate and attack your
enemy using teamwork.
Use teamwork? Really?
[ITALY]
Germany! Look what I can do!
The pizza dough got
all stretch-ded!
--Stretchy...
--[GERMANY] The book doesn't
--stretchy...
--say what to do
--stretchy... pizza...
--when the friend is foolhardy!
...piz-- Ah! I pee
pants with fear!
[BOTH]
Hetalia!
[GERMANY] Foolhardy,
with emphasis on fool.
--[VOICE] Italini!
--I'm not prepared
even a little, Germany, but
I'll still fight with you!
[ITALY]
Whenever I'm with Germany,
I feel like good
things will happen.
That seems rather
groundless to me.
[GERMANY] His reason
for becoming my friend
was rather groundless, too.
The Mediterranean Sea is
calling, so I'll visit Africa!
No, wait!
[GERMANY] He wanders away the
second I take my eyes off him.
[ITALY] When I get there,
I'll do a lot of nothing!
[GERMANY]
Scheiße!
How can he stand being so happy?
[GERMANY]
But, I suppose being loveable
isn't technically
the worst trait.
[sighs]
[BRITAIN]
Now, what is that Italy up to?
According to the report, he's
been doing a lot of nothing.
Moving forward at
a snail's pace,
and complaining about his
canned food constantly.
Ah, he truly is a dim
little wimp, isn't he?
If he's just pissing
around like a willy,
then I can go ahead and
make my first strike!
There are not a lot
of enemies that I,
the handsome and great
British Empire, cannot defeat!
Hey, you're talking to
yourself really loudly again.
I can take down
that namby-pamby wimp
before my afternoon
tea time and-- Ah!
Pawooon! I'm an elephant.
You're like a moth
flying directly into
the flame, aren't you?
Have at thee!
[ITALY screams]
He knew I wasn't an elephant!
How did he even recognize me?!
Hold it! You do realize
you won't escape me.
You're too slow, so give up now
and bow before the power of my
gorgeously pasty British legs!
[panting] Why? W-Why
are you still running?
What?
[NARRATOR] The Italian
military was known to be slow,
unless they had to retreat.
In the desert, they
were able to travel
over 25 kilometers per day!
No conversions, America.
Learn metric.
Ugh. Britain was too scary.
For real. Maybe I should
just call it quits.
Nein, you were only scared
because you went there
without thinking it through.
I'm on my way.
Don't go anywhere.
Bene, follow the
sound of my tears!
[GERMANY growls]
[GERMANY]
Are you okay, Italy?
Germany! That was creepy fast!
[GERMANY]
I... ta... ly!
[ITALY]
Germany!
[NARRATOR]
With his hot summers,
Italy was rather
used to the weather
when he traveled to Africa.
However, Germany's summers
are pathetic at best,
so he had difficulty figuring
how to dress in the desert.
So, what made you think
you needed to wear so
many layers in Africa?
[GERMANY gasps]
[ITALY] Rock those shorts
like a Hugo Boss!
--Pawooon.
--You win...