[AMERICA (RICE CAKE)]
Let's go! Heh, ha, ha, ha, ha!
S'up dudes?
Today commemorates my one
hundred year anniversary!
Everyone have
fun rockin' out!
Can't believe it's already
been a hundred years.
It's no wonder I feel
so old these days.
Thanks for your
support, dude.
I gotta say, these years
have flown by for me, too!
Heh. To celebrate this
momentous occasion,
I have brought to you a present.
Seriously, bro?
That's kick ass!
You're the best
gay friend I have!
Uh-Uh....
Wait, does this
mean you want me
to put that thing
together myself?
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
It was rather expensive
to assemble so many
separate parts,
so New York City
was reluctant to pay
for setting up the
Statue of Liberty.
Ahem--cheap!
After that, I asked for
help with it and got
a lot of donations
and support
from all kinds of people
all over the country!
For a long time, no one
thought it would ever happen.
But eventually, the
Statue of Freakin' Liberty
was finished in New York Harbor!
Dude, that statue ended
up being the coolest gift
anyone's ever given me;
thanks so much!
Hearing you say
that makes me feel
it was almost
worth the trouble.
She inherited my beauty,
don't you think?
[AMERICA] No, I don't think.
[BRITAIN] Blimey, it's been
more than one hundred years
since the little bugger
became independent.
As the gentleman I am today,
I think I can at least
celebrate his birthday--
[retches]
Wait a tick, what is it
he said about my gift?
Dude, that bell you gave me
got like totally cracked, man.
Did he even try
to be careful?
[chuckles]
Ah, what the hell.
I'll repair it for him anyway.
[AMERICAN OFFICIAL 23A] Nah,
you really don't have to fix it.
I mean, no one
asked you to.
Right...
[FEMALE NARRATOR] Aw,
he got turned down.
[QUEEN ELIZABETH II] A gift
for the two hundred year
anniversary of his independence?
Indeed.
I believe sending one
would be a nice gesture.
Why, I think that
is a splendid idea.
For both sides, really.
Although, I'm rather surprised;
this type of giving
isn't like you.
I've become a mature adult
and a gentleman, Your Majesty.
I shall celebrate
with a wink and a sm--
[retches]
[QUEEN ELIZABETH II]
You don't have to try
so hard to look good.
Right. My apologies, mum.
Rubbish.
[AMERICA] S'up dudes?
Today commemorates my two
hundred year anniversary!
So everyone have
fun rockin' out!
Don't drink and drive!
I got these for you.
[AMERICA]
Oh, thanks!
[BRITAIN] Oi, guess who made it.
And surprise, I brought a
special birthday gift for you.
Dude, this is a celebration,
not a Disney villain conference,
so knock that off!
Tell me the birthday
gift is a joke because
I do not need any more of
your sarcasm, okay, dude?
[BRITAIN laughs]
Will you think it's not
sarcastic if I say it is?
If you would just open
your eyes and look,
you'd see the Two Hundred
Year Anniversary Edition
of the Liberty Bell!
[FLYING MINT BUNNY giggles]
[AMERICA] Uh...
Huh!
Whatever, if you
don't want it--
Wait a minute, dude,
didn'tcha call one of
my government offices
like twenty some
odd years ago
about those cracks I
told you were on the bell?
I certainly did, but I
was turned down flat.
[AMERICA laughs]
Okay, I get it. This is
a nice gift, my brother.
Just like ya, too.
Thank you, dude.
I appreciate it.
Well.
After two hundred years,
you're still a kid, so--
[retches]
[AMERICA] British food,
yeah, I know.
[bells ring]
[AMERICA (RICE CAKE) laughs]
By the by, I got another gift
for you, from me personally.
For real, dude?
I get more stuff?
It's a unicorn; now,
take good care of him!
Noooo!