[SEALAND]
Previously on Hetalia!
We're traveling around trying
to find new micro-friends.
Next up, we get to research
a likely new role model! Yay!
Did you just say a model?
I don't really need anyone,
thank you very much.
Why not? Hello? I'm
talking to you, Wy!
Huh? Right. I don't care.
[WY]
What's with this car?
This whole area
seems well-equipped.
A bilby?!
We're in Australia, right now.
I'm out!
Wait, come back, Wy!
[HUTT RIVER]
Flap!
Why don't you at least
say hello before you go?
[NARRATOR]
A micronation in Australia,
this drongo's a wild one.
Whoa! It's Hutt River, and
he looks wicked amazing!
Hey, asshole, try not to let
that cape go to your head!
Join me inside instead
of standing here.
The visa for my house costs
two Hutt River Dollars.
Oh, no, don't worry about us.
We'll be fine in the sunshine.
You should become a member
of our group!
That way, you'll get to be
--friends with us!
--[HUTT RIVER] Oh, Crikey.
It seems these people wish
to be friends with me.
Normally, I wouldn't
even speak with someone
from the lower echelon.
But still, one can't
have too many mates.
I shall think about it!
If you think that's an
answer, get stuffed!
Hey! What's your problem, man?
[WY] This is why I didn't
want to see this poser.
[SEALAND] All right, make up
your mind by next time, then!
Yes, laugh it up, now.
You won't be having
that fun much longer!
[MOLOSSIA] Hah! Talk about
a total prick face loser.
--[WY] Too right.
--[SEBORGA] I thought
he was provocative.
[SEALAND] Onwards and
upwards to the next friend!
[WY]
Sealand!
Better not be another tosser who
goes off like a frog in a sock!
Oh, no worries, Wy.
I've met him before.
I mean, he is a tosser, but
at least he's a quiet tosser.
Republic of Niko-Niko, no!
[REPUBLIC OF NIKO-NIKO]
Eggs taste good.
Eggs taste very good.
[SEALAND cries]
Oh, say it isn't so!
[LADONIA]
How tacky!
I've been watching you,
softies that you are.
You don't even know how
a country should behave!
[GROUP]
Uh...
Unlike you fools, I'm
a conventional country.
I even had a dangerous
fight with Sweden,
not to mention I'm
adored by foreign lands!
I'm assuming you must be the kid
that's been following us
around since this morning?
Seriously?!
[LADONIA]
Ah! That's not true.
You're just mistaking me for
someone else, how tacky!
I'm going to ignore
the small potatoes.
I came to talk to you,
the sea brat right there!
[SEALAND]
Huh?
[LADONIA] I've had my eye
on you, and you're hopeless.
It's going to take a
conventional country
like myself to unify
the micronations.
Why, I'm so strong I even
defeated scary Sweden!
[SWEDEN]
I lost my meatballs.
[LADONIA]
A huge house!
Worldwide popularity!
Do you have anything that
you can beat me in or with?
--I think not!
--My punches are really strong.
--No, don't!
--D'you want to see?
[SEALAND] I also used
to be in the military.
So that should count
for something.
And my king is ace!
What? You mean you
have a real one?
Well, I don't care!
Jerk, I hate you!
What a sook.
That thing has been annoying
the crap out of me for too long.
Shut up!
Look, micro-kids,
I'm your new leader now
no matter what you say.
So just blindly obey me,
and we can all get along.
[WY screams]
The dingo took him!
Where did he disappear to?
[LADONIA] Why did you turn
this off without asking?!
Who said it was okay
to turn it off?!
Turn this computer back on!
Well, that's creepy.
Oh, fun! You went
into the computer.
Color me very impressed!
[LADONIA]
Shut up! Turn it on already!
And stop looking down at me!
All right, but first I
have a few questions
I want you to answer for me.
What's your name? I have no idea
how to correctly address you.
Ladonia! Why? Do you
have a problem with that?
[NARRATOR]
A mysterious country online
that became independent
from Sweden.
Next question.
How did you get in there,
a spoonful of sugar?
[LADONIA] It's because I'm
on the Internet, obviously!
Yeah, I'm super high
tech, unlike you.
Hashtag sorry not sorry.
Okay, last question.
Would you like to be
friends with us? Please?
Who would want to be
friends with you jokers?
You're all a mess!
And I hate you!
You don't want to?
That's all right.
I still like you because
you're interesting.
[LADONIA]
What did you say?
Great. Now I feel bad.
[SEALAND] What a very
productive day today, friends!
We've new members! Welcome!
There's so many micronations,
I feel empowered!
No one will think I'm a fishing
store in Okinawa, now!
Who's ready to try and
join the United Nations?
Let me hear you!
--[GROUP] Yeah!
--[KUGELMUGEL] Ja!
Wait, you mean you
let them all in?!