[AMERICA] Yippee ki yay,
little bro!
O.M. freaking G,
it's Santa!
Ain't you supposed
to use the chimney?
You got glass in your face!
You didn't see
a thing, got it?
Do you really have to give
me anything I ask for?
'Cause like, you so almost
killed me with that entrance!
Good ol' blackmail!
Then you will get it
to me by Christmas?
Dude!
I'll order it online!
[BOY 13A sighs]
Just because I'm British doesn't
mean I'm bloody Sherlock, mate.
But three Santas are missing
and we still have
all these presents!
Yes, well, em.
Have you considered asking
Sweden for his assistance?
The world isn't ready
for that level of terror!
Jesus Murphy, no sign
of him up here, either.
Well that's just a
darn shame, ya know.
Breaks your heart, eh?
[KUMAJIRO]
No, don't give up, eh!
Christmas would be brutal
without Santa Claus
and brown pop!
Let me help, Canada!
Let me help!
[CANADA] Heh, heh...
[BRITAIN] Eh? What's so funny?
Wow. I think Santa dropped
off my present after all.
[AMERICA] I ain't
got time to bleed!
[AMERICA] Christmas
is so saved, dawg!
Who cares about a few AWOL
Santas when you've got
the best Kris Kringle
of like, ever?
You tit!
Thank you! But how do we
get all the gifts on time?
Prime, baby!
[BRITAIN] Piss off, arsehole!
Today I'm going to get presents
from every Santa in the world!
Everyone always
loves to buy stuff
for their cute and
adorable relatives like me!
All right, jerk Britain Santa,
you better be listening!
♪ A pony, a skateboard,
warship armada. ♪
♪ Bazookas, a new goat,
a copter, a slingshot. ♪
♪ A tropical island,
a pony for war, ♪
♪ and holiday truffles
of chocolate! ♪
But none with the
nasty cherries!
♪ Please don't you dare
disappoint me, or else! ♪
♪ A pony, a skateboard,
warship armada. ♪
[SEALAND] Hey guard, wake up!
I have to know if Santa's
already visited us.
I thought of more things he
needs to give me! Wake up!
Jingle-jingle bells
all the way. Heh.
[SEALAND'S GUARD]
Oi, sorry kid.
Totally forgot to buy
you a gift this year.
We'll just order
somefin' online.
Not even the
guard...
Does he do anything
besides cry?
Whoops, I totally forgot
to buy him a gift this year.
[FRANCE] Christmas.
All of Paris lights
up with the aura.
[phone rings]
Simply magnifique under
the pale moonlight.
Ugh.
Sacre bleu! What do you want?
I was in the middle of
splendid tranquility, damn it!
Forget that, we have
a Santa Claus crisis!
Hello Britain. So
what's up with Santa?
A few have
gone missing.
You wouldn't happen to be
having another mass execution,
would you?
Please, it's not like
we do that every year!
Now then. I suppose I
could lend you a hand...
...for the right
compensation.
I'll pass.
Suffice it to say,
we could do without one
of your labor strikes.
[FRANCE] Have it your way,
but might I suggest asking
Hungary to be Santa and
visit me later tonight?
I wanted her
to visit me!
Never mind that,
I'll just do it.
No human alive wants
to see Santa Claus
drunk off his ass
and in the nude!
Bollocks, I won't
go to the pub first!
[FRANCE] No, you're always
stealing and pillaging, too!
If you're not naked and drunk,
then you're being
dickish and eery and pervy
and creepy and nasty and
cruel and weird as hell!
Mean ol' dummy!
Don't make me laugh,
hurry and hit me
with your best shot!
Hey stupid idiot Frenchie face,
when'd you escape
the jerk store?
[FRANCE laughs]
That can't be the best
you've come up with.
English is not a very
compelling language!
You just don't know
when to give up,
dumb stupid bugger headed dummy!
It's nice to see you still
suck at slinging insults!
[BRITAIN] What?
Why you bloody,
cheeky moron stupidface!
Some things never
change, Sherlock!
[BRITAIN] Yeah? I'm a
Cumber-bitch and proud!
Excellent work men, looks
like we're right on schedule.
And it's all thanks
to you, Germany!
What'd you two pack
in the packages?
I went with pasta!
[GERMANY] What is
wrong with you?
[JAPAN] What did you include?
[GERMANY] Me? The usual.
Toys and bratwurst.
[ITALY] Ha, ha! Great idea!
And you, Japan?
I made a series of boxes
with smaller and smaller
boxes inside of them.
Whoa! There's another
box inside this box!
And yet another box
inside that smaller box!
And this one has--
no way! Another one!
It's like Box-Inception!
When do I wake up?
[GROUP] To all a
Merry Christmas!