So, I will tell a story
about Nasreddin Hoca.
Now, clear out
your ears or else!
One day, someone
asked Mister Hoca,
"How long do we have
to keep repeating
this life and death thing?"
He replied, "Until
heaven and hell are full!"
Hope that will happen
later than sooner though!
[laughter]
But death is not
the end, friends.
Ah!
When your body ceases
to exist anymore,
is that when
death occurs?
If evidence you
existed disappears,
then would that not also mean
those who failed to leave...
Great, look.
Greece has slipped into his
philosophical mode again.
Go. Bring me sweet food, Egypt!
[KID EGYPT] Right.
[KID GREECE]
Want to pet cats.
Spoiler alert.
I want to pet cats.
Want to pet cats.
I want to pet kitties.
Hey, what's it
doing, Greece?
Are they hanging,
as it is said?
I don't know how to answer that,
so I'll say I guess so.
Do you not get my
hippity hop lingo?
[GREECE] Ehh...
Does that mean
you want fight?
I'm up for it if you are.
Let's go.
Okay! We're gonna
brawl, mother trucker!
[FEMALE NARRATOR] One of
the few things these frenemies
have in common is a passion
for the power of dance.
I was just
practicing drums,
now these weirdoes won't
stop with the twerking.
[cat meows]
It's time for you to make
friends for real with Turkey,
and don't tell me no, Greece,
just find a way
to make it happen!
I'm trying.
Believe me, Cyprus.
The problem is I can't help
but punch him in the face.
My eyes, whenever I close them,
I see so many
Turkeys I get scared.
You see
multiple Turkeys?
That is what they
call a nightmare!
You've known each
other so long;
surely you've got some
good memories with him.
[GREECE] Uhh...
[TURKEY] Ha, ha! What the
junk are you talking about?
Come with me you
lazy dumb moron guy!
Uh... So hot.
[TURKEY laughs]
See, guy? Aren't you glad
you got naked with me?
How's it feeling?
Owie.
It's what they are calling
a "whole body scraping,"
and you're welcome!
Please don't do that
to my front side.
[TURKEY] No man alive
has the stiffy-ness
after this glorious attack!
[grunting]
Yeah, not stiff, just
numb; you can stop!
Is cool bro, I wash
you all the way to hell!
Meet the madly
dancing scrubber move!
I suppose taking a bath
with him was pretty fun.
Wait, I thought you
only took baths with me!
[cat meows]
[FEMALE NARRATOR] According to
the Internet, the Galata Bridge
is a "great place to grab a
bite and watch the locals."
Germany!
Smile for the camera!
Nein. My face is perfect
just the way it is.
Ha! Yoink!
--Hey!
--Achtung!
[FEMALE NARRATOR] Reviews also
say watch out for pickpockets.
Apparently, they're a lot
stronger and faster
than they look, so they
can be difficult to catch.
Look, it is thief!
[TURKEY] Uh!
You bad man!
Picking the pocket
in broad daylight?
What the kebab are you thinking?
Pulling stunts like that
will keep these suckers
from visiting me!
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Good thing Turkey ain't
havin' none of that.
He's a lot stronger
than I thought!
Oh yeah.
Turkey is the
strongest ever!
[ITALY] Ciao Turkey!
[TURKEY] Selam!
Thank you for
catching that guy!
Tante grazie!
I just want you to
be able to rest easy
and enjoy the splendor
and radness of my home.
Tee-hee.
Go figure, man.
I can't believe how you
have the mellow now, Italy.
Tee-hee.
That's right; I did a lot
of crazy things, huh?
Wait.
Italy did what?
Yeah.
I made the mistake
of bullying him.
He kicked the baklava out of me.
Wait.
Italy did what?
I still can't believe you
took me down all by yourself.
I thought for sure,
you were a demon.
Wait! Italy did what?