Here it comes!
[grunts]
Have a lil' taste
of my Babe Ruth Swing!
Oh no!
[TRIO grunts]
[loud banging]
--This is bad!
--I'm scared. Are we gonna die?
[ALL screaming]
We need to go now.
Is Transportal close
to being ready?
I just need a few more seconds!
--[gasps]
--Transportal!
I appeal to homesickness,
I appeal to nostalgia.
Far away, many miles away.
My old home
across a vast distance.
[shouts]
The whole backside is wide open!
[ANCIENT DRAGON grunts]
[grunts]
--[groans]
--[ANCIENT DRAGON growls]
Stay low, Hardhead! Ha!
Tokiko!
What are you doing here?
I disobey your orders
all the time, you know!
Vice-Captain. You're a pain
in the you-know-what.
[growls]
[gasps]
[BOTH yelp]
Careful, you two, that dragon
almost burned you up!
[growls]
Satsuki!
[MOMOCHI screams]
Please be okay!
We need you in this fight!
I'm still way faster
than you, Satsuki.
And don't you forget it.
Hey! Don't you quit on me, Momo!
[gasps]
Maya! Move!
Mari, are you all right?
--Don't worry, I'll heal you!
--[weakly] Listen.
Another caster...
continuing an aria...
after it's been interrupted--
there isn't precedent for this,
but I know in my heart
you can do it.
[gasps]
Listen to me. I can't continue.
You'll have to open
the gate without me.
No, there's no way
I can do it by myself!
Of course you can.
[energy hums]
Go. Now.
I don't know if I can do this.
Just watch me, Mari.
I'll make you proud!
I'm doing this one all for you!
Get up!
[LESYA]
What are you doing?
I'm scared.
She's not moving at all!
[ANCIENT DRAGON roaring]
Come, we need to draw
its attention away right now!
Okay. I'm with you!
[BOTH grunting]
I appeal to homesickness.
I appeal to nostalgia.
Far away, many miles away.
My old home
across a vast distance.
Oh, place that exists
beyond my reach.
--[gulps]
--[EDWARD grunts]
[EDWARD]
My lady. I'm so very sorry.
I did not mean
to keep you waiting!
Sir Edward, is that you?
[EDWARD]
Could you be a dear
and finish chanting that aria
as soon as possible?
I want to watch with my own eyes
when the jack-in-the-box opens.
Sure! Comin' right up!
Oh, place that exists
beyond my reach.
I appeal to delusion,
I appeal to hatred.
With these feelings,
bridge this vast distance.
With this mighty, ancient hex,
warp the distant world.
Now, Transportal! Open!
[gasps]
That is Moroha. Right?
Yes, but something
appears to be wrong.
[ANCIENT DRAGON growling]
[ANGELA] This is no ordinary
Metaphysical. What is it?
[SHIZUNO] Doesn't this
all seem a little odd?
With firepower like that,
it should be able
to reduce everyone
and everything in the vicinity
to ashes in a matter of moments.
But for whatever reason,
it's toying with us.
Impossible. There's no way
a Meta's that intelligent.
Or maybe it's waiting
on something to arrive.
--What do you mean waiting?
--[ANCIENT DRAGON roars]
Get ready, here it comes!
[SATSUKI moans]
No, Lesya!
Hey! Come get me! You jerk!
--[growls]
--[SATSUKI whimpers]
What in the heck was that?
Big brother!
He's finally here.
There can only be one
Ancient Dragon on this earth.
[JIN grunts]
I'm not done healing you yet!
There's no time to rest!
Everyone,
get on your feet right now
--and give Moroha some back up!
--[MOROHA] This is my fight!
[BOTH gasp]
I don't need you interfering.
Just take the wounded
and get out!
I don't give a damn who you are
or what I mean to you,
just stay the hell away from me!
You can't mean that!
Moroha?
[thinks] In my former lives,
this monster destroyed
anyone I ever cared about.
Now, it's time for some payback!
Let's see
how you handle this chant!
Spelling!
Purgatory in the netherworld.
Wildfires on the ground.
The flames are impartial,
and consume good,
evil, and chaos alike.
They purify all
with fierce charity.
All must die,
and return to dust.
God has forsaken mankind.
The age of decadence
shall not end.
Let the trumpets sound.
The time of judgment has come!
[MOROHA] Divine Judgment!
Yin Yang Kurikara!
[shouts]
[gasps]
There's no point in trying
to use magic against it,
the curse will
only get dispelled!
Fine then, I'll kill
the bastard with prana!
[MOROHA grunting]
Be careful!
Come on! Fight me!
[roars]
[screams]
[groans]
The Fortress Class
Sonic Attack?
How do we defend against it?
Not sure we'll be able to!
[STUDENTS scream]
[EDWARD] Oh no!
Is he going to fight
the dragon all by himself?
--Moroha.
--[YURI] This is not good.
[grunts]
The Ancient Dragon's
seemingly unstoppable.
How can he defeat an enemy
that has the power and ability
of every single Metaphysical
he's fought?
You stay here!
I'm going to help him out!
--Don't you see?
--Huh?
It was waiting...
for Moroha to arrive.
How is that possible?
[thinks] This is it!
I can save them this time!
[ANCIENT DRAGON roars]
[gasps]
No!
[shouts] No!
[SATSUKI gasps]
[SHIZUNO] This is
what it was waiting for.
No. Please.
Not again.
I couldn't protect them.
[YOUNG MOROHA crying]
[crying]
[shouts]
What the hell?
It's almost like
he's turning into a monster.
Haimura's no
Jack-in-the-box today.
[MAYA gasps]
He's a Pandora's box this time,
one of rage and despair.
[angrily]
You die today!
[grunts]
Come! Fight me!
[shouts]
[grunts]
Die! Die! Die!
Look at the wounds!
Those are magic letters!
What is he casting?
The level 13 that beat
the Russian Terror?
[groans] Since letters
are carved into its body,
the beast will not be
able to dispel them.
This is brutal thing to do,
and he has lost all control.
Die, you bastard!
Stop it, Haimura!
If you don't slow down,
you'll wipe the entire city
off the map!
He's not normal Moroha at all.
He is now murderous beast.
Exactly liking I used to be.
[WAITRESS]
What's happening over there?
I have no idea,
but it isn't good.
I will destroy everything
if that's what it takes!
But you're gonna die!
I'm sending you back
to the fire where you belong!
[SARASHA]
What do you think you are doing?
[SATSUKI]
Who's there?
[SARASHA] Why are you
lying there doing nothing,
when something terrible
is happening
to big brother
at this very moment?
[SATSUKI]
Because he doesn't want my help.
[SARASHA]
Remember.
[SATSUKI]
Remember what?
[SORCERESS] If this is
all it takes to finish off
the Netherworld Sorceress,
then I would say
you are insignificant.
[SHIZUNO] You can think
whatever you like.
But I tried to help Moroha
and there was nothing
I could do.
[SORCERESS]
Remember.
[SHIZUNO] Remember?
[SARASHA] While Fraga was
off taking on countless enemies,
you were always at home,
safe and sound.
[SATSUKI] Yeah, but that's
because he was worried about me!
He was protecting me!
[SARASHA] That's right,
and you are a cowardly girl
who relied on his worries
to keep you from harm.
[SATSUKI] You're wrong.
That's not true at all.
The truth is--
the truth is
I always wanted to go with him!
[SARASHA]
Then maybe it is time
to finally
do something about it.
[SATSUKI] Huh?
[SARASHA] How many times
must you watch him go away
and leave you behind
in the dust?
[SATSUKI] I don't know.
I don't know!
Well, then maybe
it is time to rise.
Walk the same path
as big brother
and fight by his side
till the bitter end.
[SORCERESS]
Have you forgotten already?
You were once a nameless slave
without a single thing
to call your own.
[SHIZUNO]
I could never forget that.
I had no hope
for the future back then.
I lived only
for the sake of living,
because what else could I do?
[SORCERESS]
So, who was it that freed you
from your chains
and gave you life?
Who was it that instilled
in you a new sense of hope?
[SHIZUNO]
Who else? Shu Saura.
[SORCERESS]
It is your turn to pay him back
for what he gave to you.
It is time for you
to free him from the shackles
that bind him.
[SORCERESS] Do not forget.
A good wife always stands beside
her husband, no matter what.
[BOTH]
I remember. Everything!
[MOROHA]
But you're gonna die!
I'm sending you back
to the fire where you belong!
[shouts]
[gasps]
[cracking]
[MOROHA]
Satsuki? Shizuno?
Or is it?
[SHIZUNO] You are
half correct, half incorrect.
It is me and yet it is not me.
[SATSUKI]
Remember, big brother.
We will always be together,
no matter what.
In our past lives, or this one,
we stand by you.
And in our next life,
we will be there.
--For all time.
--For eternity.
I remember now. Everything!
I'm Fraga,
the Master Swordsman!
I'm Shu Saura,
the Dark Lord!
And now...
Moroha Haimura!
Did Haimura just transform?
He's embodying two former lives
within one flesh
at exacting same time?
In the end,
good ol' Jack was able
to pull something wonderful
out of Pandora's Box.
Yay! He's okay!
--Unbelievable!
--He's so cool!
Amazing.
He's a Savior all right.
[STRIKERS]
We are the Saviors!
Kamee ran around
using healing magic
on everyone
and really saved our skin.
--[humphs]
--It's true.
Every once in a while,
he's useful.
I've said it before
and I'll say it again.
When things get dangerous,
a real hero always runs!
Listen up, Strikers,
we have a job to do.
We're going to create
an opening for Haimura!
[STRIKERS] Yes, sir!
[shouting]
[emphatically]
Suck on this!
[grunting]
All right,
give 'em hell, Moroha!
Thanks a lot, guys.
You're not alone this time,
big brother.
Now. We have work to do.
Come, my love.
Let's finish this!
Spelling!
Purgatory in the netherworld.
Wildfires on the ground.
The flames are impartial,
and consume good,
evil, and chaos alike.
They purify all
with fierce charity.
All must die,
and return to dust.
Is this really the world,
or nirvana?
This still desolate irony of my
home, burned to the ground.
Endless despair, as far
as the eye can see.
[TOKIKO laughs]
Here's a level 3
that's topped off
with some naughtiness.
You freak!
Watch out,
cause here comes the pain!
Hah!
[growls]
Don't worry, Moroha,
we're here, too!
From Russia with Love,
Ancient Dragon! Ha!
Go! Take him out now!
All right.
Thank you, guys,
for everything.
--Haimura!
--You've got this!
Yeah! We're all rooting for you!
Beat that damn dragon down,
Moroha, just like you did to me!
Moroha's come back to us, Mari.
He's home for good now.
For the first time in a long
while, I feel like there's hope!
[grunts]
It's the sonic attack again!
[EDWARD]
Silvery Peak Argasten!
I see the young girl I met long
ago has grown up quite a bit.
--Sir Edward!
--[EDWARD] Oh dear me!
All right then, lad!
It's your turn now!
Yeah. Time to end this thing.
Big brother.
My love.
[shouts]
[ALL gasp]
[MOROHA] Dragon!
I never forgive
those who take from us!
And now it's time
for you to pay the price!
So, take this!
Yin Yang Vritra!
[STUDENTS cheering]
The son of a bitch
really did it!
All right!
[WAITRESS whimpers]
[gasps]
You're awake!
Moroha saved
every last one of us.
[CROWD chattering]
Well, this was quite fun.
Let's do it again, Jack.
I've told you a million times,
I hate when you call me that.
It's past time for us to go.
Angela, if you're
ever feeling lonely,
--you can text me anytime, okay?
--I would rather die!
Oh, that's reminds me.
You'd be wise
to keep your eye on Charles,
--the head of the French Branch.
--Huh?
[EDWARD]
Tah-tah!
I'll go find Tatemura.
He's giving us a ride home.
--Hey, I'm curious.
--Hmm?
The dragon.
You don't remember anything?
Not even fighting with me?
Hmm. Hey! You know what?
The whole thing
felt like a dream.
Oh, really?
It's the same dream
I always have.
Of our past life together.
When you were Fraga
and I was Sarasha.
Enough about that.
This is a happy day!
[giggles] I'm just glad
we're finally alone!
Y'know?
--Uh...
--[SHIZUNO clears throat]
Would you look
at this grotesque little fish?
I am not a fish!
I think your fish is done
boiling now, she's red hot.
We'll see who's a fish
after I scale your face!
Aw, I'm kinda bummed out.
You and I shared so many
wonderful memories in there.
Well, I guess
we're just gonna have to make
some more memories, then.
Hey, we should
totally move in together
and live happily ever after!
Just me and you.
For the rest of our lives!
Oh, has he not told you?
--Huh?
--Sorry to tell you this,
but Moroha's going to live
with me for a while.
Ah, hell nah!
And as for you, Satsuki,
I'll let you stay in the pen
where we kept
our family pet, John.
I see, so now I'm a dog?
--No, actually, John was a cat.
--Ah!
--Same difference!
--Girls, please. Calm down.
Let's go!
Better hurry
or I'll leave you behind!
[laughing]
Why do you suppose she's
so cheerful all of a sudden?
She's a messy little puppy,
that's just how they are.
A "messy" puppy?
You just had to work in
an insult, didn't you?
--Hey, Shizuno?
--Yes? What is it?
When I was fighting that dragon,
right as my power was
about to get out of control,
I had this clear vision
of the Netherworld Sorceress.
And I think she's... you.
It was...
We'll keep that between
the two of us, okay? [chuckles]
Oh, no you don't!
Take your hands
off of him right now!
Uh... uh...
Guys, this is not good!
[yells]
[theme music playing]
[BOTH sigh]
[MOROHA moans]
[LESYA] I am so glad
you are home, dear master.
What's with the outfit?
I heard in Japan, this is how
you welcoming someone.
And what am I being welcomed to?
What do you think, ya big idiot?
This is your homecoming party!
What took you so long
to get here, sexy?
Surprise! [laughs]
Let's party like no tomorrow!
I love where
your head's at, Katya!
--[BOTH laugh]
--[MOROHA] Katya, Yuri,
you're still here?
I wanna express my appreciation
for everything you've done.
Thanks to you,
the school is saved.
[MOROHA]
It's such a shame, though.
The school is
almost completely wrecked.
But we're okay. And as long
as all my students are safe,
then that's good enough for me.
[MOROHA]
Yeah. That's a good point.
Today we celebrate, Moroha.
Not only his triumphant return,
but his heroic victory!
[TOKIKO] Now,
everybody go bananas!
--[STRIKERS] Yeah!
--[laughter]
To you, Big brother!
To you, My love.
To you, Big bro!
--[gasps]
--[MAYA] I win!
[TRIO gasps]
[MAYA]
Today was a great day.
And as long as I live,
no matter what happens,
I will never forget it.
Moroha has
come home at last.
Everybody's got
a big smile on their face.
And all is well with us.
Come what may,
no matter
how many times I'm reborn,
it'll stay with me forever.