[WOMAN singing]
[growls]
I do not forgive.
And I don't forget.
[WOMAN singing]
Now and forever. I will remember
those who take from me.
Till the end of time!
[shouts]
We stand as
the swords of salvation!
[ALL]
We stand as the Saviors
of everyone!
Spelling!
[MOROHA]
Dance, dance, thundergod!
Thunderclaps,
hundredfold, invoke!
Fight back with everything
you have. Don't give up!
Nothing lives forever.
An instant, a flash,
indulge in pleasure!
British HQ will deal
with the left wing!
[MOROHA] Abandon all
in the blink of an eye!
You need to be more careful,
Sir Edward. Stay on your guard!
[MOROHA]
Regret not, belated one.
For tonight is the banquet
of carnage.
Wow! Talk about claws!
[SOFIA yells]
[JIN yells]
Perish, perish, perish, perish!
Freezing Shade, penetrate!
[SATSUKI yells]
Scatter to the winds, all life.
Souls grow light in liberation.
Impart this lightness,
this vibrancy, this liberty,
this blessedness, to everyone!
Level 8, Dark Art!
Thunderstorm Helix!
Everyone. Thank you all!
[yells]
Moroha. Wow.
[thinks] This is what I believe.
True hope can only live
in the hopelessness that comes
from staring death
right in the face.
Yes, like one solitary speck
of gold dust
buried amongst an infinite pile
of gray gravel.
[MARI]
I suspect
this has already
been explained to you.
But each and every one of you
is unique and special,
handpicked from all across
this country.
You have inherited memories
of former lives, and as result,
you have the ability to harness
a miraculous power
called "Ancestral Arts."
I can't lie to you,
this won't be easy.
The process is confusing
and difficult.
But you must rise
to the challenge
and never lose heart!
If you work hard,
I promise, one day
you will fly away from this nest
as a Savior,
capable
of smashing the Metaphysicals.
I am Mari Shimon,
your principal,
and on behalf
of the entire faculty...
[inaudible dialogue]
Hmm.
--[SATSUKI yells]
--[MOROHA grunts]
That's what you get
for being rude enough
to nod off on
the first day of school
like some stupid idiot!
Lame. If there's one thing
I simply will not tolerate,
it's a slacker!
Sarasha? Whoa!
Fraga?
--Fraga! [laughs]
--Oh!
Oh! You don't know
how much I've missed you!
Look, my name's not Fraga,
it's Moroha Haimura!
No way, you're my big brother
Fraga, I know you are!
You called me Sarasha! How else
could you know my old name?
I'm really sorry
to disappoint you.
But the truth is,
I don't remember much
--about my former life.
--Really?
I'm afraid so, the name Sarasha
just popped into my mind
all of a sudden.
No, that can't be right.
Wait. Maybe if I try
head-butting you again?
No, thanks, I think I'm good!
[MOROHA]
What happened?
[SATSUKI]
Should we go get the nurse
or something?
Hey, are you all right?
Shu Saura?
Good morning, my dear.
Uh, uh, uh, ooh!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Do not do that!
[MOROHA]
No! Don't fall asleep!
Wake... up!
What do you think you're doing,
making a pass at my Fraga,
you little home wrecker.
Huh?
I thought he was someone else.
[SATSUKI] And you didn't
think to check first?
I was half asleep.
What, you kiss people
when you're half asleep?
I really don't understand
why you're so upset.
Duh, I'm upset because
I wanted to kiss him, too,
and you beat me to it!
Girls, girls, just relax.
Was the kiss good?
Out of curiosity.
You're seriously asking
for feedback?
You're really calm, I mean,
this is kind of shocking, right?
Not at all, actually, it really
isn't that big of a deal.
[MOROHA]
Yes, it is.
How so?
We don't even know each other.
Well, that's a
silly thing to say.
Hello! I'm standing right here!
Can we please
stop acting like
I don't exist?
First you pretend
you don't remember me
and now this? You big jerk!
How dare you?
--Whoa, calm down.
--You've always been this way,
why did I expect
anything different?
[sobbing]
Weird.
Okay, ladies and gents,
how about
you introduce yourselves,
one at a time?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, pick me first!
Very well, and you are...?
My name's Satsuki Ranjyo,
and I just wanna say
I'm glad to be here!
I promise to work hard
every day and be a Savior
for each and every one of you!
I will do my very best
to be your dutiful leader!
Ah, huh...
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
Who does that girl think
she's talking to?
Why should we follow someone
we've never heard before?
I don't know,
but I definitely don't like her!
Everyone, calm down,
I'm simply trying
to set an example
you can strive to achieve
since you're all
clearly underachievers.
Come on! I thought
you would be thrilled!
[BOY]
Talk about nerve!
[GIRL]
Get off your high horse.
[MOROHA thinks]
This girl's a basket case.
Excuse me, sir?
Since we're a
little pressed for time,
can we continue
with the introductions?
Ah, yes, of course.
[TANAKA]
Remember, you are a group,
and as such, it's important
you all get along.
[TANAKA]
Let's move on
with the attendance,
and start at the top
of the list with number one.
Ah... well...
Miss Shizuno Urushibara,
that would be you.
Oh, come on now,
are you seriously
still sleeping?
[SATSUKI]
They may think I'm some nobody
right now, but I'll show 'em.
I'll blow everyone
out of the water
and then they'll have no choice
but to respect me.
And then Fraga will
shower me with praise
and finally recognize
how wonderful I am!
Plus! In this life
we're not brother and sister!
Our love will not be forbidden!
[laughs]
[SATSUKI]
Hey, hey! Wait up!
[giggling] Let's
go on a date after school!
Um, I wish I could, but actually
I'm going to look
for a part-time job, so...
Sorry to tell you,
but the Academy
doesn't allow that.
Wait. Seriously?
Weird, what the heck was that?
It's another dimension
inside the martial arts stadium.
Even if you're seriously
injured in here,
just step through
the protective field,
go outside
and you'll be good as new.
[MOROHA]
Wow. You seem to know a lot
about this place.
So, there are
two different kinds
of Saviors.
Shirogane, who use Light Arts,
and Kuroma, who use Dark Arts.
Today, we'll begin
your education
with an introduction
to Light Arts.
--So cool!
--Whoa, what is that?
It's called "Prana,"
and it's the power source
for all Light Arts.
[GIRL A]
Can you teach me how to do that?
[GIRL B]
Yeah, I wanna learn, too!
Each of you has memories
from a former life.
Therefore, you must feel,
instinctively, the way
to draw out prana
from that past world
you lived in.
Trust your inner self
and you can't go wrong.
Sounds easy!
Cool, I'll give it a try!
[BOY] Something's coming out,
but it's not Prana!
Stand back!
She's doing it!
How did she master it so fast?
No, please don't!
If you learn to
harness your Prana,
you'll be able to do things
you never thought
would be possible!
I don't weigh that much
to begin with,
so if you think
I'm impressed, you're wrong!
[laughs]
Oh, man, I feel like
I'm gonna puke!
[SATSUKI]
Oops, my bad!
Cool, huh? Hey.
You were watching me, right?
[GEN]
How lame.
This class is nothing
but a big waste of time.
Man... I wish a Metaphysical
would go on a rampage right now!
Oh, yeah? Why's that?
Because
if it was hardcore enough
to kill a bunch of people,
the higher-ups would have
to send us in to fight,
first-years or not.
You're sick, man.
[laughing]
What's funny, jerk?
Huh?
You three are garbage.
A disgrace to Saviors!
Oh? Is that a fact?
What makes you think
you can get away
with calling me names?
Assuming that brain of yours
still works,
think about what you just said,
and you'll have the answer
you're looking for.
You're not one of those losers,
are you?
"Duh, I just really
love justice, duh!"
Those skills are wasted
on you, girlie!
Yeah, well, garbage smells
disgusting, so if I were you,
I'd go stick my head
in an incinerator!
What the hell did you say to me?
[BOY]
Wow!
[GIRL]
It covers his whole body!
All right, guys, break it up!
Nobody's fighting here today!
Come on, now.
You've got two people
who clearly have a handle
on using prana.
How about
a little practice match
--just for fun?
--Well, we don't normally allow
hand-to-hand training
on the first day.
Please, sir,
just give me a chance!
Okay, you two, you ready?
I can't wait to get a look
at how powerful
your brand of justice
really is, girlie!
And I can't wait to teach
this filthy piece of garbage
what it truly means
to be a Savior!
Arcule! Come forth!
Crazy!
If you fill your tag with prana,
it will transform
into the weapon you used
in your former life.
Whoa.
[MOROHA]
Um, more importantly,
do you think she'll be okay?
Take that!
Ha! Come on, girlie!
Is that really all you've got?
Not at all, jerk!
Hhh. Weak.
The point of this match
is to show everyone
how it's done,
so why don't we reset
and give it another go,
unless you need a break.
You're gonna be sorry
you went head to head with me,
you scumbag!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[laughing]
[MOROHA]
Hey. Are you okay?
How sweet. Your little friend
has come to save the day!
[laughs]
Wait, you're the loser
who couldn't
even generate prana,
aren't you?
[laughs]
All right, Gen, that's enough.
If there's one thing
I will not tolerate,
it's the bullying of those
who can't defend themselves.
Yeah, you're right.
You hear that, girlie?
Guess you're too weak
to defend yourself.
[sobbing]
Hold on!
[GEN laughing]
Don't forget!
The weak always bow down
before the mighty!
[laughing]
Come on. Cheer up, okay?
Listen. I may not know
what it means to be a Savior,
but I know this.
Having your heart
in the right place
and being a good person
matters more
than whether people think
you're weak or strong.
Yeah. Sure.
When I was growing up,
the town where I lived
was brutally attacked
over and over again
by Metaphysicals.
So I had to move around
quite a bit.
That must've been tough.
Truth is, that's why
I've never been very good
at making friends.
But you know what?
I wasn't ever lonely.
Because I had Sarasha's memories
to keep me company,
and I got to see Fraga
in my dreams every single night.
Then one day, the test revealed
I was a Savior,
and I discovered
that there were others out there
just like me.
And when I learned
there was a school
where Saviors come together,
I thought maybe, just maybe,
it was possible.
[MOROHA]
What's possible?
That if I was lucky,
I'd meet Fraga again.
Wait, me?
To be honest,
justice and saving the world
and all that is secondary.
What I really wanted
was to show off in front of you
and hear you
compliment me again.
And when I had my chance,
I failed.
[crying]
I wasn't thinking.
When I looked at Gen,
it was like seeing my own faults
reflected back.
I couldn't stand it!
So I picked a fight, and I lost.
I'm sorry. It's stupid.
Oh, Fraga, I beg you.
Tell me I'm the worst.
Lecture me like the old days.
I'll listen.
Please, I swear!
If a lecture's what you want,
I'll oblige.
Great, it's her!
Did you--?
Noooooo...
Getting a head start
on the dating game,
who's the home wrecker now?
What? I don't know
what you're talking about,
but you'd better stop
eating my fries or else!
After losing, I imagine
you're too depressed to eat.
I'm just trying
to ease your burden
so you can relax.
Yoink!
Both of you cut it out
right now!
Look.
We had a special relationship
in a past life and have much
to discuss.
So, since
you're a complete stranger,
why don't you just butt out?
No, thanks.
I certainly hope
that I'm not being
too forward here.
[muffled speech]
This... is disgusting!
Oh! So it feels that good,
does it?
You jerk!
Perv! Leech! How dare you
behave this way in public,
it's repulsive!
Stop... right... now!
Do you love boobs so much
you're willing to throw away
your reputation?
And what about you, Jugs?!
Aren't you ashamed of yourself
for using your oversized tatas
to seduce an innocent boy?!
Just because you're president
of the Itty Bitty
Titty Committee,
doesn't mean you get
to speak to me that way!
They may be little,
but they're perky!
Lady "Sag A Lot!"
You know what?
We should stop this right now,
I apologize.
You can't apologize now,
I'm not done insulting you yet!
No, I feel awful.
When I invoked the
"Itty Bitty Titty Committee,"
I crossed a line.
Will you please stop being
so nice to me?
Don't worry, we're both
very young,
and we both have plenty of room
to grow as individuals.
Wait, does that have some kind
of double meaning?
Forgive me. As a way
of saying "I'm sorry"
I will give him back to you.
Since you're crazy about boobs,
how do these stack up?
Come on, give me
your honest opinion.
Do you like them?
I know they aren't
as gigantic as hers,
but what I lack in size
I make up for in personality!
Oww, it's like
motorboating sandpaper!
Whatever! I'm done
trying to be nice to you!
You're nothing
but a big old stupid-head!
[crying]
I think that could've
ended much worse.
Sure she's mad, but at least
she's mad at somebody
besides herself.
You may not realize it,
but you just
did her a huge favor.
Listen, I-- never mind.
It's still too early.
Oh, boy.
--It sounds fun, let's play!
--Cool. I'm in !
Look, kid. I appreciate
the balls this takes,
but it's not gonna happen.
Apologize now
or you'll be sorry.
Huh?
Ahh... I see what this is.
Pick your poison, chump.
Unless you're too afraid.
So you want me to apologize, eh?
Then beat me.
'Cause I'm not taking orders
from no weak-ass loser!
What is the deal
with that Shizuno girl,
she's totally all over him!
But still...
Moroha was really kind to me,
wasn't he?
Just like before.
Satsuki, there's trouble!
It's Moroha!
[SHIZANO]
Oh!
Man, I just tossed you
across the arena
like a rag doll,
and I didn't even hit you
with everything I have!
I can't keep up
with his movements.
He's too fast!
My boy's quick as lightning!
Gen! Show him
your Celerity technique!
Ha!
-Oh, crap.
-Crap is right.
Moroha!
[GEN]
Huh. Awesome.
Your girlfriend
gets to watch the fun too.
After I finish destroying you,
I'll pick up
where I left off with her.
And this time
it won't just be her top!
I'll strip her completely naked!
Say... you're... sorry!
You shut your mouth, boy!
Oh, no.
He's gonna lose.
He has no chance.
This isn't over yet.
Keep watching.
This is for you.
Moroha's fighting for your sake.
So no matter the outcome,
good or bad,
do him the favor
of watching until the very end.
I won't allow you
to avert your eyes,
do you understand me?
[whimpers] I do.
Come on, kid!
Right! Now left!
You better keep it up
or you're gonna get knocked out!
Some people
say school is boring.
I'm having a freaking blast!
I know. No matter what happens,
you will not lose.
You're the guardian
of the holy sword.
You are the ultimate swordsman!
[SATSUKI]
Don't give up yet,
it's not over!
You can't lose,
'cause you're the guardian
of the holy sword!
You're the ultimate swordsman!
You're greater than them all!
No matter what
difficult battlefield
I encounter and no matter what
vicious enemy I face,
in the end I will be victorious.
And when it's over,
I'll return to you.
Now it's time
to finish the fight!
If you beat him,
I'll do whatever you want,
I swear, I'll even kiss you!
Please!
Oh, wow. I remember.
Salatiga, now! Come to me!
You two! Stop th--
How can the kid move so fast?
It took me over two years
to learn Celerity!
You may be quick, but let's see
which one of us has more power!
Quick. Get help!
Moroha!
I did that? Whoa.
Hey! Are you okay?
--Moroha.
--I believe we're looking
at the Ancient Dragon.
[GIRL thinks]
Unbelievable.
The Ancient Dragon?
The "Oldest Fallen Hero"?
The moment I heard Mari
utter those words,
it was if my heart was going
to burst right out of my chest.
[SATSUKI]
By the way, Moroha,
what did you mean when you said
having your head in my chest
was like
"motorboating sandpaper"?
--[MOROHA] Uh, no comment.
--[SATSUKI] Next time,
"Dwell Within My Sword,
Magic Flame"
[BOTH] Carve through
this tumultuous life!