She's suspended?
Seriously?
Afraid so.
Wait, I don't understand.
What the heck
did Shizuno do wrong?
I wasn't told the reason.
but all I know is
Lesya is out today too.
So whatever happened,
I'm guessing it has something
to do with her.
You're probably right.
I think it's time we found out
what's going on.
You didn't have
to come see me today,
but thanks.
Sure.
Are you okay?
Your leg's pretty banged up.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Have you ever heard
of the Maneater?
No. Who's that?
She's a deadly
Russian Branch assassin
with a magic sword that
consumes prana and mana.
Rumor has it she once even
wounded Sir Edward in a duel.
What?
Elena's not who she says she is.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but she is the Maneater.
[gasps]
Lesya, an assassin?
This has got to be
some kind of mistake.
But it's not.
Trust me.
I confirmed it yesterday.
Oh yeah, how?
Sorry I didn't come
to you first,
but I had to know.
I challenged Elena
to a duel.
I hope you're able to forgive me
for doing this behind your back.
But in the end,
my instincts were exactly right.
That is enough.
Didn't you hear me?
She's an assassin.
I said that's enough!
[gasps]
I'm just glad you're okay.
Moroha.
You've gotta be more careful.
What if you had gotten hurt?
If anything happened to you,
I don't know what I'd do.
I really am sorry.
[crying]
Even if Lesya is the Maneater,
that doesn't
change anything for me.
I know this sounds crazy,
but deep down,
I know she's a good person.
[panting]
Brother...
Lesya! Lesya!
Lesya, you have to wake up!
[gasps]
I hardly think this is
the time to be taking a nap.
We have a situation
on our hands.
It's likely Moroha's
discovered the truth
about who you really are.
Da. I know.
Tell me, why didn't you
kill Urushibara?
Don't you want
to complete the mission,
and live happily ever after
with your brother by your side?
Da. Of course I do.
[bell rings]
It isn't safe here.
[sighs]
Well, it looks like
she's still alive.
You are so rude.
Don't you know staring into
someone else's window
is an invasion of their privacy?
Yeah, my bad.
Hi.
I'm really sorry about
what Shizuno did yesterday.
An icy Dark Art,
with a hex thrown in the mix?
It looks like it did
quite a number on you.
She can be
pretty harsh sometimes.
This'll take a while to heal.
But eventually,
you'll be good as new.
There is plenty of Kuroma
at Russian branch,
But no one ever uses Dark Art
for healing on me.
It's very unusual.
Bon appetite!
It's Satsuki's special risotto!
Great, are you up for eating?
I can feed it to you,
if you need some help with it.
Spoon feeding another woman?
With me here?
Get real.
You and I both know
that's not gonna happen.
[MOROHA] Course not.
I am confused.
You two are brother sister, da?
We're not.
But in a former life
we used to be.
This is simply unbelievabling.
Two siblings reincarnated
during same period
is practically miracle.
True love does
make miracles happen!
Honestly, true love aside,
the fact that we
actually cross paths
with someone
we knew from a past life
is pretty miraculous
in and of itself.
And us too, Lesya.
We're together right now
due to basically
an incredible
series of coincidences.
Here, this risotto is going
to knock your socks off!
Well, say "ah."
Ah.
[grunts]
-[muffled screaming]
-Oh, uh...
So sorry about that.
It is clear that Miss Ranjou
wants to be murdering me.
Now I must take my own life
before she does.
Sweet death!
I already told you I'm sorry!
Please forgive me!
This is getting way outta hand.
[baby crying]
What are you to Moroha?
I am very curious
to know this answer.
I'm his friend.
And a future member
of his harem.
[giggles]
I am not in
understanding of this.
[giggles]
Huh?
[crying]
Why do I always cry like a baby
when I chop up onions?
Aah!
Oh god, oh man, oh god!
Help me!
Uh...
[SATSUKI] Ta-da!
I thought you might be longing
for a taste of home,
so I made a special
Russian dish just for you!
It's borscht.
[SATSUKI]
Be honest. Is it tasty?
All right then! There's way more
where that came from
If you eat a lot
and get plenty of rest,
you'll be back to one hundred
percent before you know it!
Da, I will dos.
And if you don't want
to sleep alone,
feel free to call me
whenever you like
and I'll be right there!
Okay, will dos.
You should totally
take her up on that.
Maya's an awesome hug pillow!
That I am.
Hey.
Hold on a second,
does that mean you're
using her as a hug pillow
when you're
sleeping at night?
[MAYA] That he is!
-[SATSUKI] Huh? What the hell?
-[MOROHA] No, no, no, no, no.
Of course I'm not!
Hi, Elena!
How are you?
Uh...
Enjoying your time
at Akane Academy so far?
Da.
Yeah, me too.
I'm even considering
officially staying on
with the Japanese branch
after graduation.
You should stick around, too,
it's a perfect place
to start your career!
Uh...
[laughing]
[SATSUKI]
Moroha!
[MOROHA]
What's up?
No, I can't.
I would be betraying my brother.
Just give it some time.
When graduation comes around,
and you've made
some more friends,
I bet you'll
totally love it here.
So much so, that you'll wanna
live in Japan forever.
Girl, you're home.
Trust me. Kay?
[LESYA] I worry
this plan is not working.
Hey.
I'm glad you've returned.
And I'm glad to see you
on your feet again.
Just don't push it too hard.
Do not worry, I am feeling fine.
And so, I have request for you.
On our next day off.
I want you to go
on date with me.
Thanks for calling
and letting me know.
Goodbye.
[phone ringing]
[groaning]
I'm here. What?
[SHIZUNO] Satsuki. Did Moroha
happen to mention
anything about what
he's doing this afternoon?
As a matter of fact he did,
and it made me mad!
He says he's going on another
date with the ruskie!
-The nerve of that boy!
-[gasps]
Why aren't we walking
arm-in-arm today?
Huh?
Leprazam!
They call me the Maneater.
My sword devours
any insidious villain
who dares threaten the mighty
soul of Mother Russia.
Oh, Lesya.
Mister Moroha Haimura,
Today you die.
[SATSUKI]
Lesya, a Russian assassin?
Do you really think it's true?
I know it is.
You go ahead,
we'll talk later.
Right.
[SATSUKI]
Sofie, it's you.
Sorry.
Hate to do this,
but I can't let
you two interfere.
But why not?
I don't understand?
Because the American Branch
stands to benefit
from the Maneater
attacking Moroha.
They want Elena dead,
and they think he's the only one
who can do it.
But what if he gets hurt?
You go on in.
I'll hang back here
and take care of her.
Please, be careful.
I just told you,
you can't go in there!
That was fast.
Come on, then.
Let's duel.
[grunting]
This isn't good.
She absorbs prana?
persisting will!
Her sword is powerful.
She's really good.
Herculean strike!
Her sword can even absorb
prana from a distance?
Ugh.
Go on then,
take your best shot.
You came her to kill me.
So go ahead
and do your job.
[yelling]
[grunting]
Summer training camp
did wonders for you, Satsuki.
You've improved.
Well, losing isn't really
an option for me.
I know.
But unfortunately, I can't
afford to lose either.
May the best woman win, right?
Staying on the defensive
won't get me anywhere with her.
I've gotta do something
before it's too late!
Strange.
Typical Shirogane
apply swordplay
based on strength
of their prana.
Why spend so much time training
to improve
your swordplay itself?
I don't really know.
When I first started fighting
I struggled to keep up,
so I decided I never wanted
to feel that way again.
I can do better than this.
I can still fight harder.
I have plenty of room to grow.
Plenty of room to improve!
I remember.
I remember everything!
[LESYA]
What are you up to?
Well, if you wanna know,
come over here and find out.
I will grant this wish.
Uh... that's unbelievable.
In my former life,
I never found a weapon
that could withstand my prana!
And I would imagine
that's still true today!
Aah!
How much prana do you have?
I've heard about American excess
but this is ridiculous!
You gonna make this
a contest or not?
Find your courage.
Set your heart and soul ablaze!
I know you can do it, Satsuki!
Listen, calm down
and take a deep breath.
You're psyching
yourself out right now.
Don't lose heart,
just stay focused on your goal.
Come on!
Adamant!
Aah!
[panting]
[gasps]
Well. I can't fight
if my weapon's gone, can I?
Darn. You did it.
Wow! You never give up,
and I adore that
about you.
-You're the cutest thing
-[muffled] Sofie, stop it!
-I've ever seen.
-Seriously, I can't breathe!
Go on. Pick it up.
Fight me.
That's what you came here for,
so grab your sword and do it.
I have to kill you,
I have no choice.
There is not another way!
I do understand.
It's your brother, right?
If you don't kill me,
then those jerks at the Russian
Branch will kill him.
Let me help you, Lesya.
Listen up.
If I rescue him from the Terror,
you'll be free.
I'll make sure you're released
from her grasp forever.
I promise.
Such a thing is not possible.
I know what it's like
to not be able to save
someone you care about.
I went through it
when I lost my parents.
I never want anyone
to have to feel that way.
Please, let me help you.
You are kind.
You would risk everything
to save my brother.
Elena!
I know why you think
you're doing this,
but you've been deceived
by the Russian Terror.
I swear to you!
She lied!
You don't have a brother.
You never did.
Of course I have a brother.
How dare you say this!
The director of the institution
told me the truth.
When you were discovered,
you were alone on
a dark, snowy night.
[baby crying]
[SHIZUNO]
You couldn't have been more
than a few weeks old at most.
Think about it.
If you did have a brother,
where did he come from?
Cause he wasn't with you.
I've had enough
of your stupid lies!
Okay. You should at least
be able to tell me his name.
Yes, of course,
my brother's name is...
His name is--
My brother's name is...
Can you tell us
what he looks like then?
Or his age?
His age...
No.
No, I--
I can't.
Why not?
Why not?!
Because what Miss Urushibara
said is absolutely true.
It's pleasure to meet you both.
I am Kondrat, of the venerable
Russian branch.
I don't understand
what's going on here.
My brother, he is real.
On the contrary, my dear.
I planted it in you,
this idea of a brother.
But unfortunately,
that's all he is.
An idea.
The only thing harder
than inventing a false reality
is maintaining it.
All it takes to destroy
the illusion
is one wrong thought,
and all those years of hard work
are down the drain.
[MOROHA]
What kind of monster are you?
How could you do this?
[LESYA]
I understand.
I have no one,
and I never did.
If I were to die,
what difference could it
possibly make?
Lesya!
Hahaha!
Don't waste your time!
I'm afraid no one's voice
will be able to reach her now.
Where the hell's it going?
Oh, don't worry.
I am right behind you!
Hahaha!
Isn't this a neat trick?
If their spirit is broken
badly enough,
I can even occupy
a Savior's body!
Now, let us get back
to the battle,
although I imagine fighting me
and protecting Urushibara
at the same time
will prove to be
a bit of a challenge!
Good work, Lesya.
Haimura cannot kill you.
Nicely done.
[laughing]
[gasps]
Excellent!
Your prana is
impressive to be sure!
But let's see how you do
when I absorb it
and use it against you!
No. you can't
lie asleep any longer.
I remember
everything from my past!
Come, Salatiga! Now!
Ha!
Let's go!
But how?
Saturn!
Aah!
Don't say it doesn't
matter if you die,
because of course it does!
If you need a reason to live
then I'll be that reason,
because your life matters to me!
I will be your family.
Now and forever.
[crying]
[KONDRAT screaming]
Please! My eyes!
They burn! Help!
Funny...
I do not seem
to recall telling you
that you could touch my foot.
Aah!
The one thing
I will not tolerate is failure!
Well, Mister Haimura,
you have freed Elena
from my grasp
by burning away
her possessed mind.
You're quite a clever boy.
How did you know?
Ah, just a hunch.
I thought you might
make a run for it.
This is something that
I need to do on my own.
[MOROHA]
You sure are stubborn.
I am very sorry.
And while I thank you for
everything you've done for me,
I have to leave now.
Please just let me go.
Sleep. Near Death.
[phone ringing]
Well, I'm certainly surprised
to hear from you, chap.
I take it this isn't
just a courtesy call?
[MOROHA]
I need your advice, Edward.
I'm gonna go to war
with the Russian branch.
But I'm going alone.
[MAYA]
Elena Arshavina.
May your life be reformed
into a shining beacon,
like Holy Sword Salatiga.
May you be reborn
with peace and happiness.
A nice prayer, indeed.
But one that led Moroha
into starting a war.
[ELENA] Moroha, how many
children would you like to have?
[MOROHA] That's not
what I meant by family.
[ELENA] Next time,
"Journey to Siberia."
[BOTH] Carve through
this tumultuous life!