[whimpering]
[SATSUKI]
Fraga!
--roaring]
--[SATSUKI screams]
[glass shattering]
[MOROHA]
Damn you.
Stop this.
Stop taking from me!
Stop it right now!
[gasps]
[MOROHA]
What was that?
Mmm?
[MOROHA thinking]
Don't panic! Act natural!
--[ANGELA moans]
--[MOROHA] Okay. Stay calm.
Figure out what's happening.
We're totally not wearing
any clothes right now.
Oh, Sir Edward, it's so chilly.
Please come back to bed.
I need your warmth.
[MOROHA muffled]
Angela! Stop it!
This is not good! I think we're
breaking all your rules!
Oh, you're awake already.
Uh, yeah.
I'm wide awake.
Oh! That's wonderful!
[MOROHA]
Just so we're on the same page,
you know your boobs
are touching my face, right?
[ANGELA screams]
I don't know what you think
that was all about,
but it was definitely not some
sort of post-coital scenario.
So don't let your perverted mind
run away from you!
'Course not!
I didn't think it was!
Look, if I hadn't done all that,
then you might not have made it!
[MOROHA screams]
[grunting]
[ANGELA]
Haimura!
[ANGELA grunting]
An idiot.
A stupid idiot!
That's what you are!
You said you were fighting
this war on your own,
and yet you still went to
the trouble of saving my skin!
For now, this will have to do.
Let's hope it works.
Wake up.
Please, you have to.
Well, things could've been
far worse.
I suppose you could be dead.
You saved my life.
I owe you big time for this.
[screams]
You perv! Stop watching me
getting dressed!
Okay, sorry!
Ugh! This is
so incredibly embarrassing.
Good morning, everyone!
Uh...
Whoops, pardon me very much.
I didn't realize you two
were having sexy time.
Carry on then! Bye!
[ANGELA]
We didn't have sex!
My name is Katya Eskevna Honda.
I'm a half Russian, half
Japanese Savior from Russia.
I'm 18 years old
and currently head of the
Yekaterinburg field office.
How very interesting.
So, tell us, how did you
know about our hideout?
Oh, well,
that's an easy question.
One of my staff members tailed
you when you arrived at station.
If you knew we were here
the whole time,
then why didn't you
come after us sooner?
[laughs]
You didn't look very friendly.
As a matter of fact,
you looked like
you were ready to kill somebody.
--[KATYA chuckles]
--[ANGELA grunts]
You see,
I'm not looking for fight.
I'm looking for
a peaceful resolution.
You and I have
something in common, Moroha.
Neither of us has desire
to take human life.
That's why I know you're
the right person for this.
You're the only one who can
help make my dream reality.
Your dream?
My friend, Yuri.
I need your help saving her
from the Russian Terror.
In Russia,
Saviors do not really have
any family to speak of.
That way,
if they're treated badly,
no one will step forward
and complain.
The Terror seeks them all out,
and forces them
to fight one another.
The winners become
her bodyguards,
and the losers are cast aside.
So, your friend Yuri
was picked to be a bodyguard,
and now
she lives like a prisoner.
Well then, I suppose I know
exactly where we're headed.
To face the Terror.
We're going to Yekaterinburg
where the Russian Terror lives.
All right.
Yes. I'll speak to you soon.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
Why, you wanna come with me?
You're not funny.
Not one bit.
But what if I fall in?
[ANGELA]
Idiot.
Anyway, did you know that things
would turn out like this
in the end?
What do you mean?
The war with the Terror.
You knew we'd
find someone like Katya
who'd have the courage to
face her and rally the people.
[MOROHA]
No, I didn't know.
Wish I could say I did,
but the truth is,
I got really lucky.
I certainly hoped
the Russian branch
would have some
decent people in it like Katya.
I guess I'm just
an optimist at heart.
[BOTH chuckle]
You know what I think?
That you're quite a guy,
Haimura.
Second only to
Sir Edward, of course.
Right?
[KATYA]
Here we are at last.
[MOROHA]
Nap time.
Oh. Oh no.
The flick. Works every time.
[MOROHA]
That should knock her out
for a little while.
[ANGELA]
She seems like she might
be handy in a fight.
Perhaps we should
bring her along.
[MOROHA]
Katya can't come.
The Russia of tomorrow
is gonna need people like her.
Why do you care so deeply
about what happens
to someone else's country?
what does that
have to do with you?
[MOROHA]
We live on the same planet.
What's good for one
is good for all.
Am I right?
Ugh. Ridiculous idealism.
[ANGELA]
Look, are you certain
you don't need
my blades just in case?
If anything happened to you,
I'd never be able to
face Edward again, so no.
I'm perfectly capable
of taking care of myself!
[MOROHA]
Enough of the bold words.
I'm gonna be busy
fighting the Russian Terror,
and I won't have time
to worry about protecting you
or anyone else.
[grunts]
Sometimes, I hate you
so much, Haimura!
That sucks,
'cause I was actually
starting to like you
quite a bit.
[gasps]
[quietly] Dammit.
[DARKO]
Madam Terror,
Haimura didn't kill
a single one of us!
His leniency is
clearly his weakness.
Empress, I returned to you,
not because I ran in fear,
but because I wanted you
to know the truth!
[VASILISA]
That's enough.
Ma'am?
Whatever the case,
in the end you failed.
You know what this means.
You must die now.
[DARKO]
No, please don't do this!
Don't kill me! Terror Empress,
please spare my life!
[DARKO screams]
[VASILISA]
Worthless.
Oh.
[MOROHA]
You want me?
Come and get me!
Time to give you proper
Russian welcome, my friend!
Spelling!
Dance, dance, thunder soldiers.
Thunderclaps,
thousandfold, invoke.
Nothing lives forever.
An instant, a flash,
indulge in pleasure.
Perish, perish, perish, perish.
Scatter to the winds, all life.
Souls grow light in liberation.
Cast off your weight!
Kill, kill, kill, kill.
Impart this lightness,
this vibrancy,
this liberty, this blessedness,
to everyone.
Oh death, how sweet thou art!
What's happening?
[VASILISA]
Now, behold
my level 13 Dark Art,
Cruel Crusader.
How will you survive against
this army of lightning, Haimura?
[laughs]
Salatiga, come to me now!
Ha!
[MOROHA grunting]
[MOROHA]
There's too many of them!
I can't keep up!
Come on!
[roaring]
She has air interceptors, too?
Let's go.
[grunts]
What?
[MOROHA grunting]
What sort of trickery is this?
My Cruel Crusader once defeated
a Dreadnought Class Metaphysical
in a matter of minutes.
This child should be easy work.
With all due respect,
Terror Empress.
I suspect these are tactics,
not mindless trickery.
Look closely.
He is moving so fast,
even the lightning beasts
can't keep up.
He's focused only on the enemy
directly in front of him.
This isn't one versus 1,000.
It's one versus one
repeated 1,000 times over!
He's more than just
tactically brilliant.
It's like he's
completely comfortable
fighting entire armies
by himself!
[VASILISA laughs]
Very well.
If this is the way
the foolish boy wants to fight,
then I will have to employ
a few tactics of my own.
Bring it on!
[gasps]
Ha!
[BOTH grunting]
[MOROHA]
These must be
the captive bodyguards
Katya was talking about.
We really have to do this?
What other choice do we have?
This is your chance to show
the Empress a little gratitude
by helping her
defeat this villain!
[MAN]
Ah!
[grunting]
[MOROHA]
These guys are on your side!
Uh... Ah!
Just stop!
Stop this madness right now!
[laughs] Well, well.
Looks like Darko's report
was true.
The boy's unwilling
to kill anyone.
So, tell me, what you think
of my tactics.
Well done, Terror Empress.
Ha!
I feel so heavy.
Yuri's gravity restraint
is working on him!
[MAN]
For the Terror Empress!
[screaming]
Now, time to die, Haimura!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[ALL gasping]
Angela Johnson, of British HQ!
By order of the White Knight,
Sir Edward Lampard,
I am hereby aiding
Moroha Haimura
in his quest to beat
the Russian Terror!
[KATYA]
As am I!
There's no way I'm
sleeping through this one!
You two came. Wow.
I'd count again.
Huh?
[SATSUKI]
Big brother!
[MOROHA]
Satsuki! Shizuno!
So this is
the Russian Terror's mansion?
Talk about horrible taste.
[ANGELA]
But what perfect timing!
We were just about to teach
these boys and girls
--about combat!
--Oh no!
What do we do now?
[YURI]
Hmm.
[KATYA]
Yuri!
Wait. How do you know my name?
I've never seen you
before in my life.
What?
Bring in as many pawns
as you like.
This queen already has
check mate.
[LESYA]
Children of Russia, hear me!
My real name is Elena Arshavina,
the woman formerly known
to most of you as the Man-eater.
But I am here to tell you
that Man-eater is no more.
She went to Japan,
fought Moroha Haimura,
and now she is gone.
I was reborn there,
simply as Elena.
Moroha gave me good advice.
He said, "Start over. Now."
I'm here today so that each of
you may be reborning as well.
Live this life for yourself,
not for the Terror.
Fight only to protect others!
[gasps]
No. I will be
taking care of this one.
Yuri! What're you doing?
You know me!
It's your friend, Katya!
I don't know you. Sorry.
[LESYA]
Yuri Olegovic Zhirkov!
[grunts]
[gasps]
Oh no. Forgive me, please.
--She's back.
--Yuri!
--You're Katya.
--That's right, I'm Katya.
And I'm never
leaving your side again!
All right! We've got lightning
beasts to destroy, people!
Leave that to us, Angela!
Mmm.
We will be kicking their butts!
I'm in!
What about the rest of you?
Uh...
No. We can't do that!
Come, take back your lives
and help us defeat the Terror!
[ALL]
Mmm.
Time to turn off the lightning!
Ha!
[grunting]
Back off, creep!
[talking over each other]
Go. Freezing Shade, blow!
Incinerate! Now!
[BOTH] Ha!
[VASILISA]
Contact the Russian government
right away!
What do you want us to say?
Tell them the city of
Yekaterinburg
is about to leave the map!
[MOROHA]
Ha!
Haimura! We can handle this.
You go deal with the Terror!
I can't!
You're the only one
who can defeat her!
[VASILISA singing]
Singing?
What is that?
A giant!
[gulps]
She has an army,
air interceptors,
and a lightning giant?
Is there anything this tyrant
doesn't have on hand?
[talking over each other]
--[SHIZUNO] Dreadful Blizzard!
--[KATYA] Blaze Storm!
Spelling!
Purgatory in the netherworld.
Wildfires on the ground!
The flames are impartial,
and consume good and evil,
and chaos alike!
They purify all
with fierce charity!
All must die
and return to dust.
God has forsaken mankind!
Yin Yang Kurikara!
Ha!
His Yin Yang isn't working,
either!
[ALL gasping]
[MOROHA]
Everyone, get down! Hurry!
No way!
Here comes the next one!
Shizuno, use your
Defensive Magic!
No, it won't work!
[whimpers]
--[KATYA] Yuri!
--[YURI] Oh, Katya!
This is the end.
Uh...
I remember... everything!
You're the one
who did it first, Terror,
so no complaining
when I return the favor.
Spelling!
It all began in the water.
It all returns to water.
In other words, water is life,
and yet death, too.
The mother that bears us...
Wow. It's a level 13 spell.
Haimura is about to
throw a curse at it!
[MOROHA]
But that cruelty and uncertainty
have already forgotten the face
of their most beloved mother.
I will devour billions of lands.
An eternal void, never filled.
An eternal pleasure,
never satiated.
All things in life must change
and return at long last
to my maw!
Ouroboros!
Whoa. Ah!
He did all this?
Amazing.
A brand new curse.
Help me! I can't swim!
Here, grab this!
Mmm.
Hmm.
It's not possible.
[sighs]
[MEN]
Uh...
Stop it! Where the hell do you
think you're going, you cowards?
[MAN]
Who cares?
Anywhere that's
far away from here!
I'm more afraid of Haimura
than I am of you,
and that's saying something!
[VASILISA breathing heavily]
[MOROHA]
A tyrant's end
is a miserable thing to behold.
[scoffs]
What are you talking about,
you fool? I haven't lost yet!
Hmm.
[chuckles]
Ah! Thunderbolt Dragon, go!
[VASILISA gasps]
[MOROHA]
Now are you done?
I swear to never trouble you
again, Moroha Haimura!
In fact,
if you'll let me back you,
I'll do whatever you say
from now on, no matter what!
Let me live, and I promise you
I'll be your slave forever.
[MOROHA]
When your people made mistakes,
you didn't forgive them.
You purged them from this earth,
and now you're
begging for your life?
I'm not ready
to leave this world yet.
I don't want to lose
the empire, either!
Please, just allow me
to keep living,
and I promise
to be a good person.
You have my solemn vow!
[grunts]
[gasps]
It's so simple,
but for some ridiculous reason,
it's the hardest thing for
people like you to understand.
[whimpers]
You don't want things
taken from you?
Then don't take from others!
[scoffs]
[sighs]
[VASILISA]
I've lost... everything.
--[SATSUKI] Big brother!
--[LESYA] Big brother!
[chuckles]
He did it.
The tricky bastard actually
managed to pull it off.
[ANGELA]
He waged a successful war
and didn't kill
a single person.
[MARI]
All right. I understand.
Well, don't leave us hanging.
How did it go?
Everybody's okay.
[gasps]
He beat the Russian Terror
and he'll be coming home soon.
Hooray! Moroha's coming home!
[MAYA]
The days run long in the north.
So now, I'm sure the sun
must be gently shining
on Moroha and the rest of them.
But, at the time I didn't know.
I didn't see.
No peaceful night
would come to Yekaterinburg.
The sun would eventually set
followed by a cold,
ominous darkness.
[KATYA]
I'll do whatever it takes
to keep Haimura from leaving,
no matter how drastic!
[YURI]
Katya!
Put some clothes on, please!
[KATYA]
Next time,
"The Nightmare
from a Former Life."
[BOTH]
We are the Saviors!