Huh?
--[BERNARD grunts]
--[tires screech]
[growls]
[BERNARD speaks Russian]
Hi. I'm Moroha. You know me.
[BERNARD laughs]
[speaking in Russian]
[grunts]
[yells]
[shouts]
--[BOTH grunt]
--[MOROHA laughs]
I remember everything!
[growls]
Dance, dance, thunder god spear!
[speaking in Russian]
[MOROHA] Thunderclaps,
hundredfold, invoke!
[continues chanting]
--...blessedness, to everyone!
--[gasps]
Thunderstorm Helix. Banish all!
[BERNARD grunting]
[BERNARD screams]
[MOROHA sighs]
So, did you kill him or not?
He's fine. I'm not killing
anyone in this war,
not unless I have
no other choice.
[boat horn blares]
[train whistle blaring]
[MOROHA] A fake passport
and a fake visa.
British HQ did an excellent job.
Bollocks. Why must
I leave Sir Edward's side
to look after a wanker like you?
It's quite an insult
to my character.
Thanks.
I'm excited you're here too.
Then, of course, there's
Sir Edward himself to consider.
He's helping you
with this private war
against the Russian branch,
which confounds me.
If this foolishness
were to go public--
[MOROHA]
You're exactly right.
That's why I don't want
you getting involved.
I know I'm right. I don't need
to be reminded of it!
--[chuckles nervously]
--Enough of that.
Before, when you said
you wouldn't kill
unless you have no choice,
was that meant to be
some sort of joke?
No. I was dead serious.
I'm really not
gonna kill anyone.
[scoffs]
What, are you deaf?
I have no idea where Terror is,
and if I did,
I wouldn't tell you.
[MOROHA]
Yeah, I figured you'd say that.
That right?
I want you to send your "Terror
Empress" a message for me.
"Haimura has come here
to wage war."
Just what in the hell do you
think you're doing right now?
After this, I'm gonna go speak
to the Khabarovsk
field office chief,
so feel free to pass
that along to her as well.
Stop this! You came here
to wage a war, did you not?
Typically one doesn't give
the enemy valuable intelligence!
Yeah, but I don't have time
for prisoners and interrogations
--and stuff like that.
--[gasps]
[BERNARD laughing]
You Japanese really are
a lenient bunch, aren't you?
Peace has made you soft,
which is why
no one takes you seriously.
He's making fun of you!
Are you going to let that stand?
[MOROHA]
Lenient, eh?
--[gasps]
--[groaning]
[chuckles]
Y-- you will pay for this.
When you're asleep,
do you see your previous life?
Does the past come back
to you like a dream?
Why are you asking what
you already know answer to?
I dream a lot. I'm always alone
on the battlefield, fighting.
Taking on countless numbers
of enemies all by myself.
[gasps]
[humphs]
[MOROHA] You think
the Japanese are lenient?
You think we're soft?
'Cause if you do,
then you don't know
the first thing about my people!
[screams]
[MOROHA chuckles]
[ANGELA]
Well done.
[MOROHA]
Come on. Let's get outta here!
Wait! You're not really going
to spare him, are you?
Think about it, right?
That guy's a Rank "A"
from the Russian Branch.
It'll take more than a little
pinprick to slow him down.
Well, then you should've
bloody finished the job.
At any rate,
isn't the Russian Terror
the one you're really after?
--Don't worry, I've got a plan.
--[sighs]
Look. We don't have
a clue where she is.
Sir Edward's intel
hasn't helped us,
and interrogating a bunch
of field chiefs won't either.
But if I start beating up
her people one by one,
then I'll have her attention.
And once I have it, she'll be
forced to make the first move.
Good plan.
Except for the fact
that once he teams up
with the others,
you'll most likely have
to fight him all over again.
--You're wrong.
--Hmm?
As a matter of fact,
I don't think he'll circle back
with the other officers at all.
He'll be so ashamed
of his failure,
he won't want anyone to know.
[ANGELA]
I do hope you're right.
The chiefs are extremely loyal
to the Terror, though,
so that's something to consider.
[groaning]
But what if he does tell her?
Even if he knows his loyalty
might cost him his own life?
It's a possibility.
I meant it when I said
I didn't wanna kill
anyone in this war.
But if she does,
then she'll show the whole world
what kind of a monster
she really is.
So, it's not leniency,
it's strategy.
Yeah. This is
absolutely the best way.
In the end, you'll see.
--Just like a Jack-in-the-box.
--Huh?
That's what you are.
With you, you never know
what's going to pop up.
[VASILISA] You may look me
in the eyes now, Bernard.
--[grunts]
--[VASILISA] Now.
[groans]
Empress!
Never mind pleasantries.
Just state
your business quickly.
I'm quite sleepy,
as you can see, so go on.
Madam Terror, I'm sorry, but I
was defeated by Moroha Haimura!
[VASILISA] And?
By all rights, I should take
my own life right now!
But if I'm going to die,
with your permission,
I would like
to take him down with me!
--[VASILISA] Nyet.
--[grunts]
I do not allow failure,
as you know.
Die, please.
Will you let me say
one last thing?
Make it quick.
[BERNARD] Tell our people
Haimura is weak.
He failed trying to kill me
with his Thunderstorm Helix!
--[VASILISA] Hmm.
--[chuckles]
[humphs]
[both laugh]
[VASILISA] You hear that,
everyone? How truly admirable.
I see the strength
of your loyalty, Bernard!
[VASILISA]
We will tell your story,
so that all Russia
knows of Haimura's weakness.
[BERNARD] Nothing would
please me more, Empress!
You will die for worthy cause.
[BERNARD]
[VASILISA] Dance, dance,
lightning-scaled dragon.
Thunderclaps, azure lightning,
invoke.
Cast off your weight, and impart
this soaring sensation
to everyone. Oh death,
how sweet thou art!
Thunderbolt Dragon,
take him now!"
--[thunder rumbles]
--Ah.
[roars]
[screams]
[BERNARD]
So. You see, Haimura?
This is power of Terror Empress!
You'll never reach her level
no matter how hard you try!
Death is pure bliss.
Ecstasy! Heaven!
[BERNARD]
Long live the Russian Terror!
[KATYA thinks]
What a damned fool.
[DARKO] According
to Bernard's final report,
it appears Haimura plans
to strike Khabarovsk next.
What shall we do to prepare?
--We needn't do anything at all.
--[DARKO] Huh?
We'll let Haimura make
the first move.
In the meantime,
those of you here
will strengthen our defenses
around Krasnoyarsk.
[DARKO gasps]
Madam Terror,
are we to abandon
everything east of Siberia?
[VASILISA] Even if I order them
to surround him right now,
they won't be
in position in time.
--[KATYA sighs]
--[DARKO] Ah, yes, of course.
Very insightful,
Terror Empress!
That is clearly
the best course of action!
I demand this: Should any
of you meet Haimura in battle,
if he defeats you,
you must cut off
one of his arms before you die.
[DARKO and KIRSAN laugh]
So. Uh.
We're not both gonna sleep
in the same train car, are we?
Well, well, well.
Does the boy have trouble
falling asleep
in unfamiliar places?
Perhaps he would like a little
cuddle to help him fall asleep?
--Are you offering?
--Ah!
Cause that sounds
like fun, actually.
Hey! What do you think
you're doing, creepster?
I was just joking, you hornball!
You are not to cross this line,
do you understand me?
Do it and I'll kill you
on the spot!
And what are we supposed to do
when we need to change clothes?
We face away from each other,
and cover our eyes!
If you so much as do
anything remotely creepy,
I'll nut punch you! [grunts]
Well, good night then.
This was a great talk.
[wind blowing]
[whispering]
Yes. We're quite all right.
[sighs]
[train whistle blows]
[shouts] Huh?
You hear me, loud and clears.
I'm his little sister now.
You are no longer needed here.
Look. My big brother
only has one little sister,
from now till the end of time,
and that little sister is
right here, Ruskie! [grunts]
I beg to be disagreeing.
Moroha told me
he and I are family.
Ugh! Fine, if you wanna be
part of his family,
you're gonna have to be
his big sister!
No, I am little.
[growls]
Please shut up.
There's no reason for you
to keep fighting over something
so incredibly trivial.
It's not trivial at all!
As a matter of fact,
my entire identity as a human
is based around it!
Someone shoot me now.
[muffled scream]
Please, Miss Urushibara.
--Hmm?
--I am wanting you to help me.
Talk some sense
into this person,
so she will give up
her little sister crusade.
And what makes
you think I would actually
--help you with anything?
--[BOTH gasp]
Well. Well. Well. Well. You see?
Urushibara's on my side,
not yours, you weirdo!
[LESYA]
Sweet death, take me.
Listen, you two.
It's past time you put an end
to this silly feud of yours.
Moroha'd be so disappointed
if he came home to find you
fighting over something
as meaningless as who gets
to be his little sister.
[BOTH gasp]
He's out there
putting his life on the line
and fighting a war
all by himself. Come on!
[BOTH whimper]
--[laughing]
--Huh?
[BOTH laughing]
[SHIZUNO groans]
--[giggles]
--Hey there!
Well, you all look like you're
getting along swimmingly!
[BOTH] Uh...
[chuckle nervously]
[SATSUKI] More or less,
we are. For big brother's sake.
[sighs]
I just hope he's okay.
I worry about him being
over there all alone.
Yeah!
I hate the idea
of Moroha not having me.
I keep him warm during those
bitter, cold Russian nights.
All I desire is him to live.
I want him to show me
the smile on his face once more.
[SATSUKI]
Don't worry, ladies!
He's not about to lose
to those Russian idiots!
--He'll beat 'em!
--[MAYA] Right!
Moroha Haimura.
Remember that name,
so you can tell everyone
who it was that beat you.
[MAN groaning]
[groaning]
Sir Edward. You naughty boy.
Saucy little minx,
your tie is crooked.
Whatever am I going
to do with you?
--[squeals]
--[sighs]
Freezing Shade!
[beeps]
We have company.
Yeah, I count eight.
[ANGELA]
Don't you mean seven?
[MOROHA]
Eight. Trust me.
[ANGELA groans]
I hope you're happy.
This is what happens
when you share intel.
[MOROHA] Enough of that.
I've gotta find a safe place
to fight them where no civilians
will be put in harm's way.
[ANGELA sighs]
Every time I turn around,
you're on your cell.
I am using my phone
to help you solve
your problem,
if you must know!
It's a walk, but there's
a secluded wooded area nearby.
Oh.
--I'll be back in a few.
--Oh!
Wait. You're not
going alone, are you?
I need you to stay here
and look after my luggage, okay?
[gasps]
Hey! Come back!
I'm not some bell hop
you can flick a coin at!
[grunts]
[thinks] They're following me.
I know you're out there.
Show yourself!
I'm the Krasnoyarsk
field office chief.
My name is
Kirsan Romanovich Pavlyuchenko.
My name's Moroha.
[KIRSAN]
I know exactly who you are.
There's no point
trying to escape us.
You're surrounded by Rank A
Russian field office chiefs.
You don't stand a chance.
[MOROHA]
What makes you so sure?
[grunts] This doesn't have
to end in bloodshed, Haimura.
Just leave here
and go back to Japan in peace.
--[MOROHA] Huh?
--If we do battle here today,
you'll take me
and my men down with you!
Defying an order
from the Terror means death,
but if it will save lives,
I don't care what happens to me.
[DARKO] Why don't you
just give it a rest, Kirsan?
--[gasps]
--[DARKO] Her imperial command
was to slay that monster,
not to let him go.
There can be no exception.
[growls] For the glory
of the Terror Empress!
Salatiga now, come to me!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[thinks] Freezing Shade?
There's gotta be a weak point.
[WOMEN shout]
[MOROHA]
She split in two?
Time for you to die, Haimura!
This is for Bernard
and Mother Russia!
No. They're twins.
--You can run...
--But you can't hide!
[SISTERS gasp]
Impossible!
--You're going down!
--We're going to make you pay
for what you did to Bernard!
Look. I didn't kill
Bernard, okay?
Yeah, right. Liar!
Your boss did it, not me!
[gasps]
[thinks]
That could kill them!
[SISTERS]
Time for you to die!
No! You're the ones
who will die! [grunts]
[SISTERS grunt]
[gasps]
So hot! Jeez!
I really do hope
those twins made it out alive.
[gasps]
What the...?
[grunts]
Some kind of poisoned mist?
[chuckles]
Breeze Blade! Go!
--[clangs]
--[grunts]
[rock music playing]
That's one more of 'em down.
[gasps]
Hey. What happened to all
the talk about not fighting?
[grunts]
[MOROHA] I won't fall
for the same trick twice!
Defy gravity!
[grunts]
[MOROHA] What's wrong?
Is this your first air battle?
Nyet! [shouts]
Spelling Formless blade,
invisible fine sword!
Come forth and rend
thy way for me!
--[grunts]
--Breeze Blade!
[screams]
[KIRSAN] Look out!
[WOMEN gasp] Oh!
That's four down.
As for the rest of 'em...
There's another one over there.
[gasps]
[MOROHA]
I could tell, you know.
[gasps]
You held back with your Freezing
Shade when the fight started.
I guess I should
say thank you, shouldn't I?
--Uh...
--[MOROHA] Tell me why!
Well. You're the one
who saved the twins
instead of letting them die.
Why don't you tell me?
'Cause dying sucks,
no matter who you are.
[chuckles]
Mmm.
Da, you're right. That's true.
[OLDER SISTER]
Haimura!
--[BOTH gasp]
--I defeated you.
--Just go along with me here!
--Huh?
[gasps]
A forehead flick?
--Get back here!
--This is for Bernard!
I told you!
I didn't kill him, okay?
--[grunts]
--[SISTERS gasp, yelp]
That should leave me
with only one more to go!
Now then.
[grunts] Oh damn!
There really were eight of them!
Angela?
What are you doing here?
I told you
that I'm not some bellhop
to carry your luggage!
This one is all mine!
Perish, perish, perish, perish.
Scatter to the winds, all life.
Souls, grow light in liberation.
Cast off your weight, and...
--The Terror!
--That's her?
Oh death. Oh death,
how sweet thou art indeed!
[thinks]
She's done with it!
[BOTH grunt]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Haimura, no!
[MAYA] Tonight again,
I say a prayer
for those far away
in the land of Russia.
[roaring]
Oh!
[shouts] Haimura!
[MAYA] I pray that a wind
would blow and blow
into the west,
carrying our wishes with it.
[screams]
[MAYA] That, if nothing else,
no misfortune
would befall Moroha.
Please winds, carry him home.
[SATSUKI]
I have a terrible feeling
Moroha is flirting
with other women!
[SHIZUNO]
Then we'll have to scold him.
[SATSUKI] Next time,
"Showdown at Yekaterinburg."
[BOTH]
I remember everything!