[EDWARD] As far as
the Ancient Dragon is concerned,
I went and tested
his true strength.
[TADANORI]
Sir Edward,
are you saying
you fought Moroha?
No need to worry.
It was only a small test.
No one was hurt,
I can assure you that.
So, what was your opinion
of him?
Utter disappointment,
I'm afraid.
Sadly, I simply cannot
endorse him for Rank S.
Damn it!
I was testing him.
And the bastard
took it easy on me.
[EDWARD] Sad but true.
I wish I could say otherwise.
Sorry, chap,
but my honest opinion
is that he just isn't ready.
Maybe he did
have some assistance,
but he still defeated
a Dreadnought Class!
Put three Rank A's
in the same place
at the same time,
and they might just
create a miracle.
Besides, the other two,
aren't they skilled
in their own right?
[theme music sung in Japanese]
[MOROHA]
Home, sweet home.
Hello, Moroha, welcome home.
Ahh!
Maya, why are you--
how did you--
Guess you didn't hear the news,
as of this very moment,
I'm your new roomie!
Huh?
This is gonna be amazing!
Just think of me
as the warmest, softest,
most adorable body pillow
you've ever had
in your whole life!
Listen to me.
I think you'd better hurry up
and get back to your sister.
She's okay with it.
Actually, it was her idea.
--For real?
--For real. This'll be fun!
Well, time to get some sleep.
Oh, boy.
I really hope this isn't
against the law.
Study... abroad?
According to Sir Edward,
British HQ is in short supply
of talented Kuroma.
Considering you helped defeat
that Metaphysical,
I'd say you'll be receiving
a warm welcome.
--Then, after graduation...
--No!
That isn't what I want at all!
Shizuno. Sit down.
I won't go!
This is what
the family desires.
[MOROHA]
Hey!
You havin' a good day so far?
Pretty good, and you?
You're not gonna believe
what I just found out!
The principal has decided
that this Maya psycho
is Moroha's new roommate!
I'm excited to have new friends.
Hope you are, too!
Buds.
--Oooooh...
--So, do you care to fill us in
--on the details?
--To be honest with you,
I have no idea
what's going on, either.
[bell rings]
All right, time to eat!
[laughing]
Please! Where I come from,
we know how to make lunch
with a little bit
of style and grace.
See?
Feast your eyes on this!
Satsuki, have you never
had rice balls before?
They're not fancy,
but they're really good.
Of course I've had rice balls,
what do I look like to you,
--a hobo?
--Curry bread doesn't seem
like your cup of tea, Shizuno.
It's not really, but I heard
it was pretty good here,
so I thought I'd give it a try.
I heard the cook here
perfected his curry bread recipe
in a former life!
Wow, that's crazy.
Maybe I should've
ordered the curry bread, too.
You want a bite of mine?
That'd
be awesome! Ahh...
No way!
Just what the hell
do the two of you
think you're doing?
Yup, that's pretty tasty.
Who cares how it tastes?
That's not the point!
You put the same food
she had in her mouth
into your mouth. That's almost
like an indirect kiss,
you two-timing jerk!
All I did was eat bread.
In our former life,
you weren't heartless and cruel
like this,
you were gentle and thoughtful.
You used to feed me treats, too.
Wonderful treats, every day!
'Kay. Fine. Now say, "Ahh!"
And then, I'd close my eyes,
open my mouth,
and you'd give me a smooch.
You do realize
we were brother
and sister, right?
[SATSUKI laughs]
[MOROHA]
Well, have a good night.
[SHIZUNO]
I'll see you tomorrow.
--Man, that was good.
--Yeah, it was, what was
your favorite thing?
--Bread.
--Don't bring that up again.
Seriously, it's so gross!
I can't believe you actually
--put that bread in your mouth!
--Are you ever
gonna get over that?
I envy Satsuki, I really do.
They have such
a close connection.
She gets all the attention
she could ever want from him.
And yet I'm just...
Why is it always
like this for me?
It's not fair.
Nothing is, ever.
[sobbing]
[bells ringing]
Hey, guess what? I just
ran into Principal Shimon!
I asked to be your roommate,
since I'm your sister
from a former life,
and you wanna know
--what she said?
--Sure. What did she say?
She said, "No way."
That's what I figured.
You listen to me, bub,
I don't like your new roommate,
not one bit.
Shizuno is one thing.
I can handle that!
But this! This is where
I draw the line, mister!
I think she's losin' her mind.
Huh, that's weird.
I wonder why Shizuno's
not in class today.
You haven't heard from her
by any chance, have you?
No.
[MAYA]
Oh! There you are!
Shizuno's in trouble
and I think she needs our help!
[EDWARD]
I truly am beyond thrilled
you've chosen
to study abroad, Shizuno.
[TADANORI]
My sister can't refuse
a personal invitation
from you, Sir Edward.
Pardon me, sir,
but there's
an urgent telephone call
waiting for the young lady
from Principal Shimon.
That insufferable woman,
always sticking her nose
where it doesn't belong.
Shizuno, you have a phone call,
make it quick.
Yes.
Hello, how can I help you?
[MOROHA]
Shizuno? It's me.
Hey... you okay?
[SHIZANO]
Just have a little cold.
That's a lie.
Tell me the truth
or I'm gonna show up
at your place uninvited
and embarrass myself.
[SHIZUNO]
I'm going to study abroad
in the UK.
[MOROHA]
That seems a bit sudden,
don't you think?
Yeah.
[MOROHA]
If you're the one
who wants to go,
then I'm all for it.
But if you're being forced to...
[MOROHA]
Don't listen to your brother.
You don't have to do
what he says.
--Yes, I do.
--Why?
Help! Help! No! Please!
Don't! Stop!
[screams]
I have no choice. I'm bound
by the Urushibara family name.
[MOROHA grunts]
Listen, Shizuno...
in this world,
no chains can bind you.
Not unless you let them!
It's your life!
[SHIZUNO]
Even without your memory,
you still say the same things.
You haven't changed a bit,
Shu Saura.
Don't worry about me,
I'll be fine.
--I promise.
--No, wait!
Moroha.
My intention is for Shizuno
to become an executive
as soon as she graduates.
It certainly sounds like
we're on the same page.
You will miss her, Tadanori.
Very much.
Oh, don't worry about that.
As far as
my family is concerned,
you can keep her
as long as she proves useful.
--Master Haimura is here.
--Politely insist he leave.
[sighs]
Thank god.
[glass breaking]
Sorry to barge in like this.
Oh--
I told you I'd crash your place
if you lied.
What the hell are you thinking?
This is private property!
I could have you
thrown in jail for trespassing!
My entrance was a bit
on the dramatic side.
But... if you think
I'm gonna apologize,
you're nuts.
Well, well, if it isn't
the Ancient Dragon.
You and the rest
of your fancy pants friends
in the Head Six may think
you know everything about me,
but you're dead wrong.
Oh?
No, wait! Don't say it!
I killed the Metaphysical.
And I did it on my own.
Liar! You already
had your chance
to climb the ladder
to Rank S, and you blew it!
Do you understand
what you're doing here?
What this means?
If you become Rank S,
your life belongs to them.
You won't have
any freedom anymore.
Yeah. Don't worry about me,
I'll be fine.
Moroha... I don't get it,
why would you do something
like this for me?
You're really asking that?
If it makes you happy,
there's nothing I wouldn't do,
Shizuno.
I don't deserve happiness.
I deserve to be damned.
You've always been a fool.
Death ripped us apart already,
and here we are,
standing together once again.
Me going abroad is nothing
compared to what
we've been through.
I'm not doing this because
of what happened
in our former life, Shizuno.
Not at all. I'm doing this
because of the person you are
right now.
All I know is I can't stand
the thought
of us being separated.
--Is that what you want?
--No.
Just tell me
what will make you happy,
and I swear that's what I'll do.
I just want to be
with you, Moroha!
I want to be with you
in this life and the next.
I want us to be together now
and till the end of time!
Good! Come with me!
[sobbing]
Listen to me, if you think
I'm going to sit back
and watch
while you kidnap my sister,
you've got
another thing coming!
[raspberry]
Quick! Hurry up
and get in, guys!
Let's blow this joint!
--[SHIZUNO laughs]
--What's funny?
[laughing]
That maniac kidnapped
my sister, Sir Edward!
So why are you
just standing there?
Wish I could help you, chap,
but it's a tad outside
my purview.
Fine. As an executive
of the Japanese Branch,
I am formerly requesting
that you bring her back
--in one piece.
--Hmm.
Just for the record,
I'm annoyed
that you carried her
in your arms like that.
[screaming]
[MOROHA]
The chains of hell
seize and hold fast
all the dead!
Bind!
[ALL screaming]
I feel dizzy! I think
I'm gonna throw up!
Didn't see that coming.
[MOROHA]
Oh... so that's
what your face looks like.
Well, nice try, chap,
but it's all over,
--so give us the girl.
--No. If you want her,
you'll have to take her, chap.
If you really did defeat
that Metaphysical
all on your own,
there's no longer a reason
for her to study abroad
at British HQ.
Only problem is,
you have no proof.
But what if I defeat you?
Challenging me to a duel,
dear fellow?
Very well, as a knight
I'm obligated
to accept your offer.
Do it, Satsuki.
I hear you, loud and clear.
Salatiga now!
Come to me!
Well...
what an impressive sword.
Mine is a tad bit shabby,
but you won't be disappointed.
It still gets the job done!
All right! Ha-ha-ha!
Let's put an end to this,
shall we, mate?
Ready or not, here I come!
Venus!
What the--?
[EDWARD laughs]
Aaahh!
That was too easy.
You want some more, do you?
Come and get it!
[SHIZUNO]
Freezing Shade.
If that was the best you can do,
we got this, no problem!
You're certainly cocky
for someone who's about to die.
Aren't you?
[EDWARD laughing]
Breeze Blade, go!
That's the spirit!
Those are some fancy moves
you've got there, Sir Edward!
Well, pay attention, you might
learn something valuable.
First, a defensive Light Art
that condenses prana
at one point on the body. Sun.
Second, a Light Art
that condenses time,
making the entire body
invincible for just an instant.
Moon.
And both of them
are applications of Adamant.
There's gotta be a weakness.
I know!
Even if he uses Moon
to block a fire spell,
the embers would still
burn him to pieces.
Wildfires on the ground.
The flames are impartial,
and consume good, evil,
and chaos alike!
You will never become Rank S
like that!
All must die,
and return to dust!
He's way too fast,
I can't keep up!
All must die,
and return to dust!
[MOROHA cries out]
[EDWARD]
Care to call it quits?
Protect us all,
Field of Dreams!
Oh, wow.
Is this a protective field?
It is!
So give it
everything you've got
and don't worry
about anything else!
I owe you big time
for this, Maya.
I can finally fight
at full power.
Oh, yeah?
Purgatory in the netherworld.
Wildfires on the ground.
The flames are impartial,
and consume good, evil,
and chaos alike.
You never learn, do you, lad?
[MOROHA]
All must die and return to dust.
What?
His dark art was a feint?
The age of decadence
shall not end.
Let the trumpets sound.
The time of judgment has come!
Yin Yang. Kurikara!
Huh? Playing the trump card,
are we?
Oh, my. Well, bollocks.
[yells]
He has two ID tags?
[EDWARD]
Well done, Mr. Haimura.
You've actually forced me
to manifest
Silvery Peak Argasten.
Sir Edward...
I hope you're okay.
[EDWARD]
Ha! Don't you see?
It's useless.
I'm indestructible!
You're wrong!
Nothing is indestructible!
[laughing]
Well, you're just full
of surprises, aren't you?
He's strong. But there's
gotta be a way to beat him.
I have to do this for Shizuno!
Shizuno.
You will bring many lands
to ruin, and on your quest
you will take many thousands
of lives.
But, a greater number of lives
will also be saved.
You'll save them.
Just as you saved me.
Even if the whole world
turns its back on you,
I will always be by your side.
Because after all, I am yours.
I am your wife.
Now and till the end of time.
I remember now. Everything!
Defy gravity!
Spelling. Enders, ice wolves,
lend me your breath.
Let your freezing
be more silent than death.
In this world,
even the prosperous
inevitably decay.
It is inescapable,
divinely ordained karma.
Just as water flows downward...
That's grand. Quite grand!
He's using a Level Eight
Dark Art.
I thought the Russian Terror
was the only one
who could do that.
[SHIZANO]
Then I would say
you thought wrong.
He's singing the curse
of a Holy Swordsman
like it's an aria.
You've done more than prove
your worthiness,
you've completely
blown me away!
I desire a beautiful
world of death.
Join us! Come,
abandon your humanity!
I desire for all to stop!
I desire for everything
to stop! Now!
Cocytus!
You'll become a caged monster
just like the rest of us!
You'll be
our lucky number seven!
[laughing]
Sir Edward, no!
[SATSUKI]
What do you mean
you didn't technically
beat him?
I just froze him so he'd stop
coming after me like that.
I wanted you to get revenge
for me almost throwing up
in the car.
[MARI]
Throwing up?
Sorry, guys, but I tried
everything I could think of,
and all I managed to do
was crack his helmet a little,
so if there was a way
to beat him once and for all,
then I'd love to hear it.
How's your knee, Satsuki?
It'll be fine in a few days.
And are you holding up okay
after all that?
I'm great.
Mainly because Satsuki
was there to watch my back.
[SATSUKI giggles]
[MARI]
I'm really happy
you're all okay.
Sorry it's not very roomy
here, but it'll have to do.
Please make yourselves
at home, everyone.
[MOROHA, SATSUKI, SHIZUNO]
Thank you so much.
(doorbell rings)
Hello, loves!
Worry not,
I won't try anything.
As a knight, I admit it freely.
You won that duel,
fair and square.
And as previously discussed,
Shizuno will not have
to study abroad.
Great.
So what are you doing here?
There's something
I've been dying to ask you,
my friend.
That day at the cafe,
when I attacked you.
Why didn't you dodge my punch?
[MOROHA]
Well, because I knew
you weren't really
gonna hurt me.
[EDWARD] And how did
you know that exactly?
It was obvious.
I could tell by looking
at your prana.
Come now, you silly fellow,
there's no way you could see
something like that.
Mr. Haimura, I can say
without a doubt
you have absolutely
not disappointed me.
As one of the Head Six,
and as commander of British HQ,
I officially endorse
your promotion to Rank S.
What did he say?
That someday it's very likely
that you'll become the core
of the Order
of the White Knights.
And that I should do everything
in my power to seduce you.
Now.
Your brother's a big jerk.
But, I'm just glad
that you and I
aren't gonna end up
being separated after all.
So you're cool with this whole
Netherworld Sorceress thing,
right?
Well, I'm not quite sure.
It's a little late
to play innocent.
I'm not trying to play games
at all.
But the thing is,
I don't want to force anything
on you like Satsuki does.
Take it slow.
You're just going
to have to remember
our former life
on your own, okay?
You're free.
In this world,
no chains can bind you.
Not unless you let them.
I was nothing but a slave
till you granted me freedom.
And now
you have a responsibility
to hold onto me.
Don't you see?
Now and till the end of time.
No matter what happens,
I'll be here.
Even after we die
and we're born anew.
My love is yours.
For this moment and forever.
You saved me.
You set me free,
but you chained
our hearts together.
Come what may,
I will always be by your side.
I promise.
[MARI]
Hey Maya. How is Moroha?
[MAYA]
Surprisingly barrel-chested.
[MARI]
Why do you know that?
[MAYA] Next time,
"We Are the Summer!"
[BOTH]
I remember! Everything!