[SATSUKI]
I never doubted you
for a moment.
I had faith, no matter
how difficult things became.
I knew you'd keep your promise.
I knew you'd return victorious.
And now,
I have to keep
my promise as well.
Satsuki.
[MOROHA]
Your lips are soft and gentle,
like an angel.
Uh. Who're you?
Somebody who knows
you're not in pain anymore.
[MOROHA]
Ms. Principal?
Don't be afraid.
She just used her lips
to fill you with magical power
and restore your health.
And as a result, the prana
you lost will now repair itself.
Let me get this straight.
Are you saying she just
healed me with a kiss?
[whimpers]
[muffled screaming]
[MARI]
Ah yes, we caught Ms. Ranjou
trying to sneak
into bed with you,
and since illicit
sexual relations are forbidden,
she's in time out.
[muffled whimpering]
I watched your fight
with Gen in the arena.
I knew it instantly.
You're the Ancient Dragon.
Uh--
There are other names.
The Order of the White Knights
calls you
the "Oldest Fallen Hero."
But what does that even mean?
Every Savior
who's ever walked this earth
is a reincarnation
from a former life.
However, it's extremely rare
for a Savior
to have been reborn
more than once
and to possess memories from
two former lives simultaneously.
We can't be certain, but that's
our working theory for now.
Hold on, I'm confused.
I only just now remembered my
former life as the warrior guy.
but I might have another one?
[MARI]
During the battle with Gen,
when you delivered
the final blow with your sword,
You were using
a level three Dark Art.
At any rate, you didn't suffer
any physical damage.
It's a good thing that fight
happened in the arena.
Guess so.
If I were you, I'd go back
to my room and get some rest.
I see trouble with women
in your future,
so you'd also be wise
to exercise caution
with the fairer sex!
Huh?
Oh, and if you would be so kind,
please take your
writhing classmate with you
when you leave.
Right.
[muffled scream]
[SATSUKI]
Fraga!
Oh! Thank goodness for you!
You remembered everything!
I knew you would!
"Everything's" a bit of
an exaggeration!
[SATSUKI] Here is your prize!
[MOROHA] My prize?
My, my, look at this
grotesque little fish
that washed ashore.
Ugh! You keep showing up at
the worst possible moment!
He and I were just about
to do the thing!
You know, uh, we were, um...
[sighs] Tell me,
is this the sort of thing
you had in mind?
Uh-- Mmm.
How dare you bust in
and steal my big moment!
Sounds like your fish
is done boiling.
[SATSUKI]
That's enough!
You take your hands off
my big brother right now!
You hear me?
Yeesh. "Trouble with women"
might be an understatement.
[SATSUKI]
Hey, Moroha!
Let's exchange phone numbers
and email addresses.
--[MOROHA] Yeah, sure, why not?
--[SATSUKI] Awesome!
All right!
I finally have a contact
in my cell phone
that isn't my mom or dad!
Happy to help.
Congrats on graduating
from total loser
to girl with one friend.
Why don't you go find
a steep cliff and jump?
It was just a joke.
Do you wanna trade info?
Mm. Not that I want yours,
but I guess.
Oh, this is bad.
I slipped and
accidentally deleted it.
How about we just settle this
in the arena?
[SHIZUNO]
My favorite beauty salon,
not your number.
Oh.
[door opens]
[JIN]
Is there a Moroha in here?
Yeah, that's me.
[GIRLS exclaim]
Come with me, please,
if you don't mind,
and Ms. Urushibara,
that goes for you as well.
Hmm?
Wait, what?
Rank C? How come?
[JIN]
You have the principal's
highest recommendation.
Also, I had a chance
to see you fight in the arena,
and I was very impressed.
That was my little brother
you were fighting.
Oh.
Rank C is an honor.
You'll be paid in
the form of a scholarship
that covers all your expenses.
After graduation,
you'll be guaranteed a position
with the Order of
the White Knights.
So what's the catch?
Aha. Not only are you strong,
but you're also sharp.
Well played, and you're
absolutely correct, Mr. Haimura.
once you reach Rank C,
you are also required
to join up with
my elite team of Strikers.
And that means what?
[JIN]
You'd be part of an
anti-Metaphysical combat unit,
the best of the best.
We deploy once or twice a month
on various assignments,
but these missions
are dangerous.
Take some time and think about
what you wanna do.
[MOROHA]
Before I answer,
I do have one more question.
How much does this
scholarship pay?
[chuckles]
[whispers]
[gasps]
Yes! Auntie, I made it!
Are you sure you wanna do this?
Thank you for the opportunity!
Just don't screw it up.
Well, if he's in,
I guess I'll start
showing up from now on.
What?
[JIN]
Ms. Urushibara's had
a standing offer
to join the reserve unit
for some time,
but she hasn't ever
shown much interest.
Congrats. See you soon.
[SATSUKI]
Please, you have to
let me join, too!
Huh?
[JIN]
Uh. And you are?
If Moroha and weirdo
are joining your unit,
then I, Satsuki,
deserve to come!
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
but the truth is I don't know
what you're capable of.
She was capable of getting
her ass handed to her
by your little brother.
You shut your stupid mouth!
Gen's not ready for this.
If you lost to him,
then neither are you.
Maybe another time.
Aw man!
See ya!
Hey, cheer up.
Don't worry about me,
I'm totally fine.
I'm not depressed at all!
I'll just have to
train really hard
so I can get super strong
and then they'll have no choice
but to recognize my talent
and offer me a position
right next to you guys!
[crying]
Poor thing.
[JIN]
Welcome to the Strikers.
Everyone,
meet our newest recruits,
Moroha Haimura
and Shizuno Urushibara.
With the old third years
officially out the door,
anyone who has the skills for
battle is more than welcome!
Hey, check out the new guy.
He's pretty cute.
We're gonna bust your butts,
so you'd better
make sure you come
ready to get to work!
Cool.
All right.
Strikers, let's get started!
We stand here as
the swords of salvation!
[ALL]
We stand here as
the saviors of everyone!
[JIN]
You're better than that.
Say the next part loud
so I can hear it!
[ALL]
We stand as
the Strikers for our people,
our beloved way of life,
our values, our peace,
and our justice!
Hmm.
Huh?
Should I shout that, too?
Sorry, I didn't know?
Yes, you should.
Mmm. All right, here goes.
[JIN]
One more go, people.
This time, try to say it
like you mean it!
[ALL]
We stand here as Saviors!
[SHIZUNO]
Jin Isurugi, our leader,
is part of what's commonly
called the Golden Generation.
They've exterminated
more Metaphysicals
than anyone at
the Japanese Branch
can even come close to touching.
In other words, these kids
are stronger than the adults
in the Order of
the White Knights?
[SHIZUNO]
Yes.
They're nearly all
Rank B or higher.
Man, I sure hope I can cut it
in a group this intense.
Trust me, you're gonna
do just fine.
[signs] I am worn out.
[BOTH grunting]
[MOROHA]
Geez. I don't think
I've ever been
this exhausted before.
I wouldn't
stress about it too much.
Eventually you'll learn
how to pace yourself.
[SATSUKI]
You're late!
If you weren't my big brother
in my former life,
I would tear you a new one
for making me
wait around like a loser!
I don't know how to argue
with that kind of logic.
[giggles]
So I don't know about you,
but I'm starving!
And there's a really delicious,
inexpensive okonomiyaki place
not far from here!
Wait, for real?
Yeah! Come on!
Let's go eat there right now!
I'm so sorry,
but if you're going,
you'll have to go alone.
Huh?
Moroha and I are tired after
a long day of training.
We would rather go home
and try to get as much
rest as we can.
But I'm hungry.
You and I will have practice
every single day
from here on out.
Sorry to break it to you,
but they're paying you
to be ready to fight, not to
spend your money at restaurants.
[SATSUKI]
It's no problem.
She's right.
I was being selfish
and not thinking.
No, it's not your fault, really.
It's just we're gonna be late
everyday because of practice.
I think you'll be
disappointed if you
spend all your time
waiting around for us.
Yeah, I guess,
but can we get together
and hang out
when you have a day off,
at least?
We'll try to work that into out
schedule if there's any time.
I think, maybe,
you're being a little bit--
Sounds great!
Hey, come back!
I don't get it,
why do you say things like that?
It's simple.
You shouldn't be wasting
all your money
on going out to eat.
Besides, it's clear
you're fond of Satsuki.
I did her a favor
by telling her the truth
about what to expect
from here on out
so she doesn't
get her feelings hurt
when things don't go her way.
[MOROHA]
That's not what I mean!
Look, Shizuno.
I don't like when
other people speak for me,
and I don't need you
to play the bad guy.
I appreciate you trying to help,
but I want you to remember,
it doesn't make me happy
when you act that way.
In fact, it makes me
really unhappy.
Hey, I'm easy. If you want
to do something for me,
all you have to do is smile.
Satsuki, wait up!
I suppose some things
never change, do they?
[crying]
Shizuno gets to hang out
with him every day,
and I don't.
[phone rings]
Yes? Satsuki here.
[MOROHA]
Are you okay?
It sounds like you're crying.
Oh, don't be ridiculous!
I'm perfectly fine!
What in the world would
I be crying about anyway?
Gah, it's like your
silly imagination takes over,
and all of a sudden,
you get these
super strange ideas
in your head!
[MOROHA]
Liar.
I know you're
balling your eyes out.
Hey! Will you please stop
acting like you can see me?
--It's weird!
--[MOROHA] But I can see you.
Sneaking up on someone like that
could give them a heart attack!
[MOROHA]
When I have a proper day off,
You and I should eat together.
Maybe we can cook
and save some money?
Oh! I'll make a homemade meal
that's so delicious you'll be
begging me for more!
My food will knock
your socks right off!
Mm. I know I'm busy,
but I'm wondering.
Could I call you
on your cell sometime?
It would be awesome
to have someone to talk to.
[gasps] Of course. If you ever
need to talk about stuff,
you can call me
anytime you want!
But don't call too late,
because you're not
the only one who's busy,
and if I don't get
my beauty sleep,
you won't want to
talk to me anyway!
[MOROHA chuckles]
I'll make sure
not to call too late.
I don't wanna see you grumpy.
[SATSUKI] Oh, you!
[MOROHA chuckles]
[phone rings]
It's so early.
[SATSUKI]
Good morning!
What are you up to?
How about you and I
go out and spend
the day together?
[SHIZUNO]
Sorry, but I don't wanna
be your girlfriend.
I'm already interested
in someone else.
[SATSUKI]
I meant as friends,
you big weirdo!
The sky looks strange.
So, why'd you ask me to come
to a dumb place like this?
If I remember right,
you did say
you wanted to hang
on your days off.
I was just trying to be nice.
But I specifically asked you
to meet me at the mall,
because I really wanna buy
Moroha an awesome present
to celebrate his promotion
to Rank C!
Why does that
involve me, exactly?
Right.
That's a very good question.
The thing is,
I don't have a clue
about what to give him.
Plus, I'm a little short
on cash, to be honest.
So I thought we could
go in on a present together
and split the cost.
--[SHIZUNO] See ya later.
--[SATSUKI] No, don't go!
[crying]
Well, if I must.
--[whines] Still no luck.
--[CHILDREN giggling]
I think I'm just about done.
I'm really sorry I made you
go through this.
You know, when I'm exhausted,
a little sugar
always does the trick.
Huh?
Strawberry banana
will suit me just fine.
Uh!
[SHIZUNO]
See ya later.
[SATSUKI]
All right, all right!
I'll get you a crepe!
Thank you for waiting.
lease come back and see us!
Oh wow. It's so good!
[giggles] Huh?
[SATSUKI]
Uh-oh. I hope it doesn't rain.
Wha-- Uh!
[screaming]
[whimpers]
[roars]
A Metaphysical?
[screaming]
Oh no!
What do we do?
[roars]
[whimpering]
[crying]
[SATSUKI]
I'm scared,
but if I run away now,
then I don't deserve
to be with Fraga.
Arculth, come forth!
If you're planning on
hurting these people,
you'll have to
come through me first!
Shizuno! Look after the kid
while I handle the monster!
Satsuki, wait!
You can't do this on your own!
It's fine, I just gotta
keep that thing occupied!
[MAN] Quick, let's get him
out of here!
That's right, I'm the one
you want to fight, not them,
so don't go trying
to cheat on me
with anybody else, you hear me?
[yells]
Spelling,
darkness of ice, snow spirits,
lend me your breath,
let your freezing be
more silent than death.
You're doing it!
I contacted Moroha
and the officials at the school.
The shopping center is
being evacuated as we speak.
Then you've done your part.
Just make sure you
get yourself out of here!
I'm not going anywhere
if you aren't.
In my former life, I was revered
as the Netherworld Sorceress,
and since you definitely
need a helping hand,
I'm happy to watch your back!
Not that I actually
need your help, Shizuno,
but I appreciate it
all the same!
[grunting]
[SATSUKI]
It's working!
[gasps]
[SATSUKI]
Another one?
There's no way.
This cannot be happening!
It's a multi-headed type?
We don't stand a chance
against this thing!
--[SHIZUNO] Satsuki!
--[SATSUKI gasps]
[SATSUKI]
My legs!
You need to boost your prana
and resist
the petrification's magic!
[hissing]
Hey, stop hissing and fight me!
You might kill me,
but I'll take as many
of your heads with me as I can!
[hissing]
I don't know how
we could defeat this.
What's our next move?
[whimpering]
[whimpers]
[SATSUKI]
Moroha!
[MOROHA]
You guys, I just heard!
[JIN]
The situation is
a dire one, Moroha.
You remember the
Dreadnought Class Metaphysical
that appeared in Tokyo Bay?
With nine heads,
this monster's just as powerful,
if not more so.
Then what are we all
just standing around for?
Satsuki and Shizuno
need reinforcements!
[JIN]
I can't send back up.
Huh?
[JIN]
If this was
an ordinary Metaphysical,
that thing would be
no match for us.
But we've never seen one
like this before,
and it would take 100 men
and women to bring it down!
[MOROHA]
No.
I'm so sorry.
[grunts]
[CHILD]
Mommy! Daddy!
Please, sir, use my blood!
I'm begging you.
Just give me a chance
to save my Mom and Dad!
[MAN]
You're not big enough.
You can't offer
a blood transfusion.
No. Please.
[MAN]
I'm so sorry.
Listen to me.
In my opinion,
there's no such thing
as an acceptable loss of life!
[gasping]
How can we call ourselves
the swords of salvation
if we can't even save our
friends when they're in need?
[ALL murmuring]
[SATSUKI]
Come on! Open your eyes!
Shizuno, please!
[hissing]
[whimpering]
[SATSUKI]
Moroha!
As if Moroha would
even want to save me
after a failure like this.
It's over. It's done.
[MOROHA]
Salatiga, now! Come to me!
Sorry I'm a little late.
Wow! You're really here!
[grunting]
Damn these things!
You can beat it!
You will not lose, I promise!
I know for sure,
because there's another power
hidden deep within your spirits!
Wait, what? Another?
If you keep on fighting,
you can do this.
Whatever you do,
just don't give up!
[MOROHA]
I remember.
I don't forgive,
and I never forget.
I always remember
those who take from me!
Spelling!
Purgatory in the netherworld!
Wildfires on the ground!
The flames are impartial,
and consume good,
evil and chaos alike!
Come on!
More, more!
More!
The age of decadence
shall not end.
Let the trumpets sound.
The time of judgment has come!
More.
More. More!
What's that?
Level five Black Gehenna.
Isn't it incredible?
Let's go!
Ha!
Yin Yang Kurikara!
[MARI]
I was right about him.
Wait, huh?
Me? In the reserve unit?
When lives were on the line,
you faced danger
without flinching.
That's way more than
I can say about myself.
You have a strong
sense of justice,
and the Strikers
would be honored
to have someone like you.
The opportunity's yours
if you want it.
Wow! This is so incredible!
Me a Striker!
Mr. Haimura.
I don't think my decision
to exercise caution
was a mistake in any way.
[JIN]
But...
I also think your brave
decision to fight was amazing.
You're a Striker.
Will you stay with us?
Yes, sir.
Glad to hear it. Then I will see
all three of you at practice!
[laughs] I'm really in!
Now that I won't be
left out anymore,
we can all hang!
Guys, I am so happy.
--Yay, me!
--[SHIZUNO] Hey, just make sure
you don't start to get on
my last nerve, okay?
You know what? I've decided to
make it my personal mission
to improve your personality
and make you less
of a stupid jerk face.
It's gonna be tough,
but that won't stop me!
[laughing]
Shoot me now.
Hey, so, in a former life,
were you and I together?
I've gotta go.
Another time, perhaps.
[MAYA]
In what kind of places
do you find miracles?
Lost deep within a forest?
At the top of
a tall, tall tower?
Miracles happen everywhere.
Two former lives.
Two sets of memories.
The more you remember,
the stronger you'll become,
inside and out.
This is your fate, Moroha.
You're the Oldest Fallen Hero.
[SHIZUNO]
Moroha, I'm dying to know
which kiss was better,
mine or Maya's?
Please tell me the truth.
[MOROHA]
Uh, not touching that one.
[SHIZUNO]
Next time,
"The Netherworld Sorceress!"
[MOROHA]
Spelling!