Quick, step on it!
We need to get as much distance
from here as possible!
[KIRAKO] Hey, Naomi, are
you sure they'll come for us?
The people from the Agency?
I have faith in my brother.
I'm know he'll come and
get us out of this mess.
[STEINBECK]
What a great lodge!
If we plowed the land, we
could grow a nice orchard here!
Shall I capture the girls?
You'd just end up
ripping their heads off
if we used your ability.
Why don't we use mine instead?
There you are.
[crunch]
Huh?
What the--?!
Something's lifting the car!
I can't open the door!
Are those roots? Ah!
If this keeps up we're
gonna get totally crushed!
That must have been scary.
Apologies, m'ladies!
Tell me, do either of you
know much about grape vines?
What they do is
they seek out other plants
to attach themselves to,
and then graft their
shoots together.
Allow me to demonstrate.
[STEINBECK]
By merging my grape vines
with the surrounding flora,
I can use all the
plants in this area
as an extension
of my own body.
And because the senses
of this vegetation are in tune
with my own,
I'm afraid that running away
from me is simply
an impossibility.
Now, now, don't look so upset.
All I need is a little favor.
When a villain asks
you for a "favor,"
all they're going to do is
take something from you
and then throw you away.
Not everyone is
the Guild is pure evil.
I'm just pragmatic.
I have a really large
family back home.
Every time we have dinner,
it feels almost like a war zone.
I have a sister who's about
your age who loves pie,
and always takes my share.
But she's so adorable,
I let her get away with it.
Could you do
the same for us then?
[screams]
I'm sorry if I gave
you the wrong impression.
The work's a bit seedy, but
the pay itself is quite good.
If I were to lose my job,
--my family would starve.
--Please, stop this!
This is for my sister...
I don't care in the slightest
what happens to you two.
[LOVECRAFT]
Hm?
Snow? In this season?
[gunshot]
[STEINBECK]
Oh?!
[JUNICHIROU]
Naomi! You guys okay?
Junichirou!
Listen to me.
In five minutes,
a train's gonna pass by here.
Kunikida and I will take
care of these Guild guys.
You just get on that train.
I'll be okay!
Just keep running!
[STEINBECK] I had a
feeling this might happen.
It seems my sources weren't
as reliable as I thought.
[DOPPO] If I understand
his ability correctly,
he could use his power
to manipulate the roots
at the base of this hill,
effectively stopping the train.
If I can keep him occupied
for the next five minutes,
that should buy enough time
for our people to escape.
[JUNICHIROU]
Kunikida!
[STEINBECK]
Let me guess,
your plan is to keep me
away from the vegetation,
so I can't use my powers
to stop those girls.
If you oversimplify
battle strategy,
you become easy to predict.
Is that so?
I'll have to write that
down in my notebook.
By that same token, allow me
to guess your line of thinking;
If you remove my firearm,
you remove any means of attack.
Doppo Poetry!
"If you oversimplify
battle strategy,
you become easy to predict."
You should heed your own words.
A secret group from a superpower
goes abroad to abduct people.
[STEINBECK]
Those are hurtful words.
But as my boss once said,
the purpose of the Guild isn't
to be a force for good...
...it's to do what
needs to be done.
[gasps]
Kunikida, behind you!
[DOPPO] Does his ability
make him immune to bullets?
[STEINBECK]
You're late, Lovecraft.
What took you so long?
[LOVECRAFT]
I was sleeping.
[STEINBECK]
Oh, you.
[LOVECRAFT]
Sorry.
Junichirou!
Use your ability to hide!
Is this even possible?
I've never seen
a gift this powerful!
[LOVECRAFT]
Are we supposed to kill them?
[STEINBECK]
I'm not sure.
We can ask for orders
after we catch the girls.
Let's see where they are...
[NAOMI]
There it is!
[KIRAKO cries out]
Haruno!
It's leaving...
[STEINBECK]
All right.
That wraps up our story.
Let's get out of here
before the police show up.
[JUNICHIROU]
There's no point hiding myself
with Light Snow now.
What else can I do?
I'm borrowing
your sister for a bit!
[JUNICHIROU] What are
you gonna do with Naomi?
She'll be out of my hands,
so I couldn't say.
If I had to guess,
they'll probably torture her.
You'll never get away with
this outrage, you bastard!
[STEINBECK]
This is just a job.
But I realize that's
something you moralists
could never understand.
Moralists?
[STEINBECK]
Huh?
A truck?
Things could get nasty
if we're seen like this.
[JUNICHIROU] It's true that the
Agency has a set of morals.
But when it comes to Naomi, it's
a different thing altogether.
You can talk about
justice or morality,
but her life means more to me
than all of those
things combined.
[STEINBECK]
That's strange...
Hasn't the driver
noticed us by now?
No way!
Do we look like part
of the road to you?!
[JUNICHIROU]
If it was for Naomi,
I would gladly burn
this world to the ground!
The roots let go!
We gotta go!
[KIRAKO]
Okay!
Grab my hand!
[groans]
[LOVECRAFT]
How unexpected.
[STEINBECK]
Do you know where they went?
I can't sense them.
It seems that they...
hid themselves.
Damn it.
[police siren]
[OFFICER A]
Freeze!
H.Q., we've located the suspects
of the reported kidnappings.
Looks like the Agency
called us in ahead of time.
[ATSUSHI] Still no
sign of the train yet...
Hope they're okay.
The head of the
Port Mafia embodies efficiency.
You can definitely count on
Mr. Mori for a number of things.
And that includes taking
advantage of our weak spots
especially while we
have our guard down.
All right, we should
be safe here for now.
[KIRAKO]
Thank goodness.
I'm sorry!
Did you say sorry?
I should apologize as well.
Are you hurt?
[OSAMU]
Atsushi.
What's up?
[OSAMU] There's an urgent
errand I need to carry out.
[ATSUSHI]
What is it?!
I need to use the bathroom.
[OSAMU]
I'm not gonna make it!
There's no one else around.
You can come out now
Nice to see you Gin.
Have you've gotten taller?
How did you know we were
watching you this whole time?
[OSAMU]
Well, I was the one who created
all of the Port Mafia's
surveillance techniques.
So... what do you want from me?
[ICHIYOU] Doesn't this
gun tell you what we want?
[OSAMU]
Seriously?
I think you guys could benefit
from better veiled threats.
And, Gin, could
you put this away?
It's dangerous.
We didn't come
here to take your life.
I have a message addressed
to you from the boss.
[OSAMU]
Really, from Mr. Mori?
I'm on the edge of my seat!
The message is this:
[OUGAI]
Dear Dazai,
would you like to return to
the Port Mafia as an executive?
[OSAMU laughs]
Wow, that is such a
pleasant invitation.
[ICHIYOU] I've looked
through your records.
Your blood is Port Mafia black.
More so than
anyone in the country.
What can I say, people change.
I mean, take Gin
here for example.
I remember when
you were only this big.
You were such
a dainty little lass!
[GIN]
Don't change the subject.
[ICHIYOU]
Gin's... a girl?!
[ATSUSHI]
Haruna, Naomi...
Are you all right?
[NAOMI]
We are.
I never thought they'd come
after the clerks in the office.
At least you're safe now.
We're gonna escort you
both to the extraction point.
[OSAMU]
Something doesn't add up here.
Why would Ougai allocate his
trusted staff for this charade?
[ICHIYOU]
It's to protect you.
[OSAMU]
Protect me from what?
The boss has decided to
release Q from his prison.
[OSAMU gasps]
[NAOMI] Oh, I wanted
you to meet someone!
We got to know each
other a little on the train.
[ATSUSHI]
What is this?!
He has razor blades
taped to his arm...
That would mean
even the slightest
bump would cut him up.
Wanna play a game?
[OSAMU]
What stupidity!
Do you have any idea
what he's unleashed?
Q is a walking catastrophe.
He'll doom everyone,
friend and foe alike.
[ICHIYOU] The Port Mafia
achieves its ends
by any means necessary.
Do you even know why Q was
imprisoned in the first place?
Kyuuuuuuu!
[OSAMU] He has the
most vile gift of them all;
the ability to control
people's minds.
Better act fast if
you don't wanna die!
[ATSUSHI] This must
be the enemy's ability.
I have to do what
I can to protect them!
[ORPHANAGE MAN 1]
What can you hope to accomplish?
You're not capable
of saving anyone.
[ATSUSHI]
You're wrong.
I'm not the same as before.
I'm so much stronger now!
Sorry about this.
[OSAMU] Q's curse
induces hallucinations,
causing his enemies
to attack those
around them indiscriminately.
The curse is activated only when
Q's doll has been mutilated.
[DOLL laughs]
However, even when
this event is triggered,
only a designated
receiver is affected.
In order to be targeted by Q,
that person has to hurt him.
You can tell who a receiver
is by the bruise-like mark
on their body, similar to
being grabbed or strangled.
[OSAMU] You mentioned
before that you came here
to protect me
[OSAMU gasps]
Damn it!
Listen to me, Atsushi!
Look carefully!
Atsushi... please stop!
[ATSUSHI]
No way...
The only one being
manipulated was me?
All I wanted to do was
to protect everyone.
[ORPHANAGE MAN 1]
All of this is your fault.
Such is your fate,
using your power to inflict
harm to those around you.
No! I can change, I swear!
I just want to save my friends.
Stop it!
[AKUTAGAWA]
So then...
...do you understand
who you are now?
Enough...
Ability: No Longer Human.
[Q] Your new friends
are so fragile, Mr. Dazai.
But don't worry.
What I really look forward
to is breaking you.
Remember how you made me suffer?
Soon you're going to
feel the pain, Mr. Dazai.
And instead of
capturing you next time,
I'll just rip your heart out.
Can't wait to play again!
See you later!
Come on, get up Atsushi.
It's time to go.
I'm just no good!
I should've never been born!
Look at me.
Listen to me very closely.
I'll give you some advice,
like a proper senpai.
Don't pity yourself.
Once you go down that road, life
turns into an endless nightmare.
Now then, it appears
that the enemy
has forced our collective
hand on this one.
They've played
their trump card,
so I guess we'll
have to follow suit.
[FITZGERALD]
Another strategy proposal?
[ALCOTT]
Uhh... well, I... you see...
Yes.
Did you have to write
an epic novel about it?
[ALCOTT]
Uhh, no!
I-I'm sorry!
I'll... rewrite it.
[FITZGERALD]
I'll read it along the way.
Where's our next mission site?
[ALCOTT]
I-It's not safe right now!
The Zelda was just destroyed.
I'd feel much better if you
stayed here, Lord Francis.
Wherever I go is where
the home of the Guild lies.
Am I wrong?
[KOUYOU]
Hello, young one.
You alone?
[ATSUSHI]
Why are you here?
I agreed to make a
little deal with Mr. Dazai.
If he'll find and
save my dear Kyouka,
I will stay here
and wait patiently.
What about you, child?
Why aren't you
with Dazai right now?
[ATSUSHI]
That's because...
[KOUYOU]
Hmm?
...he went out to negotiate
with a government agent.
[ANGO] Just how
long has it been, Dazai?
I have to say I was surprised
when I received your call.
Ango!
You're looking well!
I'm really glad you came out.
But be honest with me,
did you really think that I'd
forgiven your double-crossing?
I'm just kidding.
I bet you left this thing
unloaded anyway.
What do you want?
[KOUYOU]
I see.
The Gifted
Operations Division...
They're the strongest of
all the gifted organizations.
Get them to join your side,
and they'll be sure to become
the Agency's greatest weapon.
If that actually happens,
then Kyouka might be able
to come back to us soon.
I wonder...
Tell me, boy, do
you truly believe
that with only a few short
months of combat training,
a girl can murder 35 people...
...at only fourteen?
It's her gift.
And for as long as that gift is
bound to her soul, her being,
she will never
escape the darkness.
Much the same way
that I never could.
I ask you... look after Kyouka.
Isn't your job to go after
gifted crime groups?
It was the last time
I checked anyway.
Someone's having a
hard time keeping up.
If it's about the Guild,
we're aware of their activities.
And yet you guys still
let them off the hook?
They applied pressure on a
number of political players,
and thereby acquired
a comparable level
of diplomatic immunities.
They're practically
above the law now.
The police don't
even have the power
to take the Guild's
members into custody.
You need to get
out of here, Dazai.
Right now.
Tell everyone at the Agency
--[OSAMU] Ango...
--that their lives are
in danger and that they--
[ATSUSHI]
Dazai's taking a while.
[FITZGERALD]
Been waiting long?
[gasps]
Such a predictable reaction.
How dull.
[ATSUSHI] Does he have
special combat abilities?
He's strong!
But if I can take him
down, this war is over!
[FITZGERALD]
That was a really nice kick.
I'd say it was worth
about ten grand.
However...
[FITZGERALD]
...it doesn't come close
to the bounty of seven
billion we put on you.
Not what I'd call
a great return.
But I wouldn't feel too badly.
You have other assets.
Now, time to come with me.
[ATSUSHI] It's the same
thing all over again.
I'm right back
to where I started.
[KYOUKA]
Hold it.
[FITZGERALD]
Hmm?
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
Kyouka... so then you...
[ATSUSHI] The Guild
begins its nefarious plot
that could lead to the
destruction of all of Yokohama.
I remember a book that
I'd read a long time ago
once had this to say:
"I've never regretted any
of the things I've done.
I've only regretted
the things that I didn't do."
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs,
episode 20: "Though the
Mind May be Wrong."
This time...
I'm going to protect everyone.