[DOPPO]
Good. Everything's in order.
My minute-by-minute schedule:
A meticulous array of
numbers and letters.
Such a display reflects my
sworn diligence to the people.
I'm ready to begin.
[ATSUSHI yelps]
That's your schedule today?
You've sure got a lot
packed in there...
A counter-terrorism meeting
at the Military Police
headquarters,
and a witness testimony
for a violent crime.
[DOPPO] There's also a number
of other high-priority items
that I can't be even
a minute late for.
[ATSUSHI] I feel like this
might be a little too much
for even you to handle,
Mr. Kunikida.
[DOPPO]
No!
I swear upon my very soul...
...I will complete everything
on this masterful agenda!
Hey, Kunikida, today's
our designated grocery day.
You wanna come with me?
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
you'll have to ask someone else.
Mr. Kunikida, we got some
intel from an informant.
An unsuspecting traveler with
a briefcase full of explosives
is going to kill
a lot of people.
I'll discuss it with you
when I get back.
Kunikida... we don't
have any more snacks.
There should be a small stash
in the staff kitchen cupboard.
Just remember
not to overindulge.
And as for you...!
Dazai.
Give me your word that you won't
interfere with my schedule!
I swear upon my very life!
He's totally planning something.
[DOPPO]
What am I doing?
I don't have time to waste
on this troublemaker.
Shoot. I'm already
18 seconds behind.
Very well. I'll be
taking off now.
[OSAMU snickers]
I have a feeling that
something's gonna happen today.
[ATSUSHI]
Oh, Mr. Kunida... I am so sorry.
[DOPPO]
The train departs at 10:47.
I only have another two minutes
and 15 seconds of walking.
All according to plan.
[PA]
Train approaching on Track 2.
Please stand behind
the yellow line.
If I were to miss this train,
my whole schedule for
the day would be ruined.
[phone ringing]
[OSAMU]
Your phone's ringing!
Hey, come on! Hey! Kunikida!
Your phone--
What is it, Dazai? This had
better be something important.
I'm not falling for
your shenanigans.
Sorry, I know you're really
busy, but you have a guest here.
[DOPPO]
Who is it?
[OSAMU]
The same craftsman who made
that special notebook of yours.
The one and only legendary
notebook artisan...
Master Carlyle is there?!
[OSAMU]
That's right!
Apparently, word got back to him
that you love his notebooks,
and so he came by to see you
before heading back to Europe.
[DOPPO]
Impossible! Is this a dream?!
Well then, I'll be right back.
Make sure he's
treated with respect!
[PA] The train is
approaching on Track 2.
[DOPPO] Dazai...
you rotten troublemaker!
[OSAMU]
Don't be like that!
I'm just opening the
door of possibilities!
Whether you choose your
agenda or the master artisan,
you'll be happy.
It's practically a win-win!
[ATSUSHI]
This man is a complete monster.
[OSAMU]
So, whatcha gonna do?
Dazai!
[PA]
The doors are now closing.
[DOPPO]
T-T-T-T-Tell him...
...that he has my upmost
love and respect!
[beeping]
Aw.
You've got some major issues.
[OSAMU chuckles]
[DOPPO]
I did the right thing.
I'm a detective whose duty
is to serve the people. Hm?
[MAN]
Could you take this briefcase
to the conductor's room for me?
Someone lose it?
No problem!
I got it.
[DOPPO]
A briefcase...
[JUNICHIROU] We got some
intel from an informant.
An unsuspecting traveler...
A briefcase full
of explosives...
...kill a lot of people.
Stop!
[DOPPO]
Hey, shrimp!
[AYA] When I turn around,
I better not find out...
...that you were
talkin' to me, buddy!
You thief!
Damn it!
[yells]
[DOPPO]
Everyone, get down!
I'd like to request an
investigation at Station Exit 5.
Everyone, please remain calm.
I'm with the Armed
Detective Agency.
The local police force
will be here soon.
I ask that you
cooperate with them.
[DOPPO] I believe this
could be a serial bomber.
It may be wise to get the
Military Police involved.
[AGENT]
Understood.
[DOPPO]
Please excuse me.
You've been through a lot today.
The police will be here soon
to take you into protection.
[AYA]
I'll kill him...
That dung bucket!
Ow, ow, ow...
It's just one thing
after another!
Quit pulling my hair!
You're Kunikida.
And you said you're part of
the "Armed Detective Group"
or some pompous crap like that.
What do you think about helping
me beat up that dung bucket?
Huh?!
Are you crazy?!
[yelps]
You need to stay put and let
the police handle this case.
And I have other
business to attend.
Ugh, why do you have to
be so boring, Kunikida?
That's Mr. Kunikida to you.
And you can't deny what
I'm saying is sensible.
You realize I'm the only one who
saw the bomber's face, right?
You're gonna need my
skills to catch him.
Is that so?
And what "skills" would a kid
like you have exactly?
I practice karate everyday!
I work out my mind and
body to fight for justice!
I've trained for
a day like this.
I couldn't forgive
myself if I ran away.
And yet the answer's still no.
I understand that you wanna
go out there and do something,
but we're possibly dealing
with a serial bomber here,
and should be left
to the authorities.
It's too dangerous
for a civilian.
Is that clear?
[AYA]
Crystal.
Then I expect you to cooperate
with the police inves--
[yelps]
Oh, would you look at that?
When the police
finally get here,
I'm gonna have to
tell them all about
how a big, scary looking
man named Kunikida
cornered me and tore my clothes.
Poor little me.
[PEOPLE chattering]
[KENJI]
Hey, Junichirou.
Where's the boss today?
I think he's out on some
important business.
Said he won't be
back till later.
[KENJI] So, who's in change
while the President is away?
The Military Police asked
me who our agency's
second-in-command is.
I never really thought about it.
[ATSUSHI]
Yeah, who would be in charge?
I'm guessing it would
have to be Rampo.
He has the longest and
most reliable record.
[RAMPO]
Nope. Not me!
[JUNICHIROU, KENJI]
Hm?
When it comes to
responsibilities,
I can't say I have
a shred of interest.
That's for sure.
[JUNICHIROU]
Hmm, then...
It'd have to be Dazai.
Well? Am I right?
[OSAMU]
What have I missed?
What else can I do to
annoy Kunikida to death?
What?!
[ATSUSHI] He's not done
tormenting him yet?
[AYA]
All right, Kunikida!
Let's go catch that dung bucket!
My name is Aya Kouda,
by the way.
But you can call me Aya.
My precious agenda...
It's all gone up in smoke.
Sheesh.
You special detectives
aren't nearly as cool
as all the rumors.
You need to
toughen up, Kunikida!
[DOPPO] That's Mr. Kunikida
to you, Miss Kouda.
[AYA]
Just call me Aya.
If your agenda's so important,
what made did you jump off the
train to help me back there?
[DOPPO]
My ideals.
Huh?
[DOPPO]
I strive to create a world
where no one gets
murdered on my watch.
That is my ideal.
Huh?
What's with that face?
You're so sappy. It's
embarrassing to listen to you.
[DOPPO]
Oh, shut up!
Weren't you the one who
was just talking about
"fighting for justice"?!
Kunikida.
[DOPPO]
That's Mr. Kunikida!
What is it?!
[AYA]
Look at that.
Another bomb?
This device is likely
set off by vibrations.
I think you had
better stand back.
If a train were to pass
over these tracks,
hundreds of people would die
from the explosion
and derailment.
We need a bomb disposal
unit on the scene.
This explosive design is
rather familiar however...
Could it be...?
[DOPPO] If I'm right, this bomb
will have to be disarmed
using a remote control.
Aya?
[click]
[gasps]
[DOPPO]
Aya!
[MAN] I suggest you
put down your weapon.
Unless, of course...
you wanna find out how far
the girl will fly once
I hit the detonator.
I'm awfully curious myself.
That's the Kunikida I know!
[MAN]
This is a beautiful little item.
Your ability lets
you materialize
whatever you write
in this notebook.
That means, if I take this
notebook away from you,
you're left powerless.
You've done your homework.
Well, I am up against
the great Kunikida.
Of course I did.
I've worked real hard on this
plot for two long years.
Shousaku Katsura.
I knew it was you.
I arrested you when you were
building an illegal explosive
to try and blow up your school
building two years ago.
So you were the one who
tipped off the Agency.
This was all just a setup
in order for you to exact
your revenge, wasn't it?
Revenge?
Not quite.
All I care about is one thing:
To erase your words.
After you arrested me, you kept
telling me over and over again,
"Overcome adversity."
"Be strong."
"Discipline yourself
and do what is right."
To this day... I still can't
get your ideals out of my mind.
"Be strong"?! Where did you
get off telling me that?
"Weak! So weak!"
That's the crap advice
you spout to someone
who's already so weak
he's become a criminal?!
I can still hear you!
Do you really think
that people are weak
because they want to be?!
[SHOUSAKU]
Now's not the time
to be sleeping on
the job, Kunikida.
There's five minutes until the
train passes over those tracks.
The signal to disarm can only
be sent from this laptop.
You'll be powerless
to stop the explosion,
leaving hundreds to die.
When that happens,
those frivolous ideals
that you've scribbled into this
precious notebook of yours,
along with your pride in
being an Armed Detective,
will be lost.
Kunikida!
[DOPPO]
That's Mr. Kunikida.
Katsura... what I have to
say to you in response
is already written
there in that book.
You can find it
written on page 89.
[DOPPO]
Special ability...
Doppo Poetry!
Stun Grenade!
But he's not even holding it!
[MAN A]
Huh?
What was that noise?
I dunno.
The hell?
[DOPPO]
That's my answer.
My ability has grown
stronger over time.
Ideals can't be attained
through conviction alone.
Aya, are you all right?
Kunikida!
Don't worry about me,
take care of the bombs!
Hurry!
[DOPPO]
Okay. Just hang tight.
[gasps] This isn't good...
[SHOUSAKU laughs]
Kunikida?
Don't move, Aya.
[SHOUSAKU]
That's right...
[laughs]
The signal to disarm the
bombs set on the track
is the same frequency
as the one to detonate the
bomb attached to that girl.
[SHOUSAKU]
I wouldn't do that.
If you try to remove it
by force, it'll explode.
Which means, you have
to make a decision
whether you want
to save the girl,
or the passengers on the train.
Shousaku... you anticipated
this, didn't you?
[SHOUSAKU] You told me that
you'd never allow anyone
to die in front of your eyes.
That's one of your
"ideals," isn't it?
But between hundreds of
passengers and one girl,
can you really hold
true to that?
[AYA gasps]
[SHOUSAKU]
Now... kill that girl,
and prove to me that your ideals
are nothing more than
a childish fantasy.
That you're nothing more
than a flawed human being,
just like I am!
[DOPPO]
You're right.
As hard as we try to stop it,
people die all around us.
It's inescapable.
Cruel, heartless, and
without a hint of perfection.
That is our world.
[DOPPO] But even if the
future seems bleak...
...even if it appears to offer
nothing but pain and misery...
...I will still
pursue my ideals.
That's right. Your only option
is to sacrifice the girl.
Aya... I'm sorry.
It's all right.
After all, I told you
I fight for justice.
What're you doing?!
I'll be here right alongside
you until the very end.
[SHOUSAKU]
So that's how your life ends...
Dying along with that girl.
[SHOUSAKU]
What?
Impossible...
How are you alive?!
Guess you didn't do enough
research after all.
[gasps]
[DOPPO]
In the Armed Detective Agency,
fatal injuries aren't an issue.
I've lost track of how
many times I've heard
that "stun grenade"
move of yours.
My detailed schedule covers
not just myself, but everyone.
I knew that she would
be shopping nearby.
So... you're saying that trick
with the stun grenade...
...was actually used
as a distress signal.
[AYA]
Seriously?
What were you gonna do if
no one came to help in time?
[DOPPO]
Find another way.
I already told you.
I won't let anyone die.
No one.
[CHUUYA]
No, Boss, it's nothing.
Looks like someone with a
grudge against the Agency
cooked up a harebrained attack.
I would've enjoyed the show more
if he'd gone after that idiot
Dazai instead of Kunikida.
But that thug wouldn't
have stood a chance
against Dazai anyway.
[AYA]
Hey, Kunikida?
[DOPPO]
Mm?
I'm sure that someone like you,
who's only focused
on your ideals
wouldn't have a
girlfriend... or wife.
But if you ever
changed your mind...
...ya know... I could, uh...
[DOPPO]
Aya...
Of the current 58 conditions
of my Spousal Plan Project,
you fail to meet
31 of them.
So I must decline.
[AYA]
What?!
[DOPPO] And for the last
time, it's Mr. Kunikida.
You must respect your elders in
order to become a proper lad--
[CHIEF TANEDA]
The older you get,
the more you can't help
but worry about the future.
[YUKICHI]
Thank you.
[CHIEF TANEDA] I understand that
the Gifted Business Permit
was given to you
personally, Mr. Fukuzawa.
Maybe I shouldn't be concerned.
But I do worry the Armed
Detective Agency--
if something unspeakable
were to happen to you...
[YUKICHI] Naturally,
I have considered that:
The future of the
Agency after my death.
[OSAMU] Who will be the next
president of the Agency?
Actually...
Someone's already been chosen.
[KENJI]
Huh?
I didn't know that.
Who is it then?
[chuckles]
He's the perfect
flag bearer for us.
Unwavering, unyielding, and
compassionate toward the weak.
A man born to be a leader.
Yup... Who else could it be...
...but our very own Kunikida?