[door opens]
[OSAMU]
Odasaku!
What's up?
Sorry to wake you, Sensei.
Sensei?
Why'd you call 'im that?
[OSAMU]
Just look how wise he looks.
He even gives up his seat
when I have guests.
So you're not gonna believe
what happened today.
There was a ridiculous
shootout inside a warehouse.
[ODA]
Really...
I wound up trading shots with
a very energetic group of guys!
Their truck featured
a machine gun!
[ODA] Sounds like
a rather hairy situation.
So... those injuries of yours...
I'm assuming you got
those from the hail of bullets.
Actually, it was my own
fault because I had to pee
and in my rush I tripped
right into a ditch.
That so...?
I guess when you gotta go,
you gotta go...
[OSAMU]
So true.
[ODA]
This is Osamu Dazai...
An executive in the Port Mafia,
a criminal organization.
[OSAMU] In the end, those
guys fell right into my trap
and ran away crying, even though
I barely roughed them up.
I really thought they'd be able
to take me out, but no dice.
I was disappointed
to say the least.
[ODA] We have a
saying in the Port Mafia
"The biggest misfortune
for Dazai's enemies
is that they are
Dazai's enemies."
His body of work is written
in darkness and blood.
Makes even the members
of the Port Mafia tremble.
He was practically
born to be one of them.
[OSAMU]
Oh, man!
Isn't there some
simple, reliable way
for me to commit
suicide somewhere?
[ODA]
Doubt it.
[OSAMU]
Odasaku...
[ODA]
Hmm?
[OSAMU] Man fears death,
yet at the same time,
is also drawn to it.
Death is endlessly consumed in
literature, in cities, in life.
It is the singular event
that none may reverse.
That's what I pursue and desire.
[OSAMU]
Barkeep!
One glass of bleach, please!
We're all out.
Aw, that's a shame.
How 'bout a
bleach-based cocktail?
We're all out.
[ODA]
Looks like you're outta luck.
[ANGO] You shouldn't let him
talk like that, Odasaku.
[ODA, OSAMU]
Hmm?
He might not go off the rails
if you called him out
every now and then.
Ango!
Although a hammer
to the back of the head
might work better than words.
Oh, just a tomato juice.
I have to drive.
[OSAMU]
It's been a while.
How's work been?
Well, today was pretty rough.
Buying the necessary
smuggled items was tedious.
After hours of negotiating, all
I got was this antique watch.
This rounds out about 74%
of transactions that have...
[ODA]
This is Sakaguchi Ango.
He's one of the Port Mafia's
intelligence officers.
Just about all critical and
classified information passes
through Ango when
communicating with outsiders.
The secrets he carries
about the Port Mafia
are more valuable than gold.
There must be as
many people who'd love
to torture him as there
are stars in the sky.
It's not a job for the weak.
[OSAMU] So, it sounds like
you fuzzed your job too then.
I "fuzzed"?
That's right,
we're fuzz buddies!
Come to think of it,
it's been a long time
since we first became
drinking buddies, Odasaku.
but I don't think I've ever
heard you complain about work.
As the lowest ranking
member of the organization,
I'm afraid my stories
would only bore you.
There you go being secretive...
Come on, tell us about your day.
Let's see, I punished a kid
for stealing from a store
in a shopping district that
pays us protection money.
I resolved a fight between
the lover and the wife
of one of our shell
company executives.
And lastly, I disposed of a bomb
found behind one of our offices.
Wow! I wanna go out
and dispose of bombs too!
Do you think that the two
of us could switch jobs?!
You wouldn't be
able to handle it.
[ODA]
Yeah, you'd get blown up.
You serious?!
Hey, did you hear that, Ango?
He said blown up!
That I'd get blown up!
[ODA] As the
lowest ranking member
of the organization,
the jobs that come my way
are the ones no one
else wants to deal with.
You could say I'm basically
a glorified handyman.
Moving on, did the two
of you come here tonight
for some kind of official
business meeting?
[ODA]
Nah, it was merely coincidence.
[OSAMU]
But I did have a sneaky feeling
that I'd run into
both of you here.
Was there something you
needed from either of us?
[OSAMU]
Ah... no.
I just thought if
I showed up here tonight,
it might turn out
like the old days.
That's all really.
So then what are we toasting to?
[OSAMU]
Anything you like.
Who says we need a reason?
[ODA]
To the Stray Dogs.
[OSAMU, ANGO]
[OSAMU]
Hey Ango, do you have a camera
in your bag by any chance?
Yeah, I use it for work.
[OSAMU]
Why don't we take a photo?
To remember.
What do you mean?
Yeah, remember what?
That all three of us
were here together.
The three of us come here
to drink all the time.
[ANGO]
Heh.
Whatever you want,
Mr. Executive.
Make sure to get
my good side, 'kay?
I want you to capture
all my manly charms.
[ANGO]
I don't want my picture taken.
[ODA]
Uh...
[ODA] So, why do
you suddenly want a picture?
Call it a silly hunch
if you like,
but I just have this feeling
that if we don't do it now,
we might never
have another chance
to prove we were
all together like this.
Hey Odasaku, say cheese.
[ODA]
Huh?
[ODA] As it turns out,
his hunch was correct.
That was the last time
that special friendship
between the three of us
was ever captured.
Because soon after that
photograph was taken
one of us would be dead.
[ODA]
Someone of my low status
would ordinarily never enter the
headquarters of the Port Mafia.
The reason for his
summoning me was unknown,
but his word within the
Port Mafia was absolute,
and so I beckoned to his call.
Name's Oda.
I'm here on official business
at the request of the boss.
I'm Oda.
[ODA]
Boss, it's Oda.
I'm coming in.
[OUGAI] Come on, Elise,
just wear the dress. Please!
Just for a bit!
A teensy-weensy little bit!
[ELISE]
No!
I don't wanna!
[OUGAI]
Come on, my dear.
Just try it on, all right?
I put a lot of thought
into picking this out.
I mean just look at
these crimson frills!
Don't they look
like flower petals?
I'm sure you'll look great!
Look, it's not like
I hate pretty clothes.
But I do hate
you groveling, Rintaro!
[ODA]
Boss, you called for me?
How may I serve you?
[ELISE, OUGAI]
Hm?
Now then, to begin...
Yes?
[OUGAI] Nothing you hear
leaves this room, understand?
Yes, I wasn't even here.
I appreciate you making
the time to meet with me,
despite your very pressing
issues with that young lady.
What matters did you
wish to discuss with me?
Well...
Uh.
[chuckles]
Never mind.
I called you here
for a singular reason.
I'd like you to find
someone for me.
Find someone?
You'd entrust someone like me
with such an important task?
I've heard good
things about you.
I personally wanted to ask
you to carry out this job.
The missing subject in question
is intelligence officer
Ango Sakaguchi.
Our sources say he was reported
to be missing as of last night.
It seems he never
even made it home.
Whether he vanished
of his own free will,
or if he was taken
away by brute force,
we still cannot
say for certain.
As you well know,
his position gave him access
to sensitive information.
Such knowledge could
be used to decimate us
if sold to rival organizations.
[OUGAI] However, taking that
element out of the equation,
Ango is still a
valuable employee.
If something has happened
to him, I wish to help.
Take this with you.
It's a Silver Oracle.
If you show this to anyone
in the organization,
including executives,
you will receive assistance.
Speaking of executives,
I understand you have a personal
relationship with Dazai.
It seems friendship
surpasses hierarchy.
His capabilities are astounding.
I'm sure in five years or so,
he'll have assassinated me and
taken the throne for himself.
One more thing...
[ODA]
Yes, Boss?
[OUGAI] I understand that for
as long as you've been with us,
you've never killed
anyone with that gun of yours...
Why is that?
[ODA]
Are you ordering me to reply
as the leader of
our organization?
[OUGAI]
Not at all.
It's just simple curiosity.
Well then,
I'd prefer not to answer.
[chuckles]
Very well.
You may go.
I hope that you will soon
bring me good news.
[RYUUROU] Ensure that the
city police do not hear of this.
Make a call to
the cleaners as well.
They'll move the bodies.
Investigate as to whether
these three men have families.
In the event that they do,
I'll personally make
contact with them.
I believe an executive will be
here to assist us shortly.
[OSAMU]
Good morning, everyone!
Hang on a second,
I'm almost through
this really difficult level.
Aw crap, he got ahead of me!
Well, how about some of this?
What?! He dodged it?!
Thank you for taking the
time to come out here, sir.
It appears our
armory guards were killed.
[OSAMU] It's been a while since
we had anyone reckless enough
to attack a Port Mafia depot.
Each of these men was hit with
ten to twenty rounds of gunfire.
A number of firearms were
then stolen from the armory.
[OSAMU]
I'll go take a look.
Take over for me, okay?
Wait, I...
I-I... Wait! I don't...
[OSAMU] The rounds went
clean through their bodies,
meaning they were
killed at close range.
The assailants
were skilled pros.
But I'm just getting
my hopes up.
Lemme see the
surveillance photos.
[RYUUROU]
You want some of this?
Oh, I'll give it to ya!
[OSAMU] They look like
hoodlums at first glance,
but they must be
well-trained soldiers.
The way they cover each other's
blind spots is proof enough.
But why appear to be otherwise?
[RYUUROU]
You little...
Doh!
[OSAMU]
Mr. Hirotsu...
I have no excuse to offer.
Please give me a chance
to rectify this failure.
[OSAMU]
Do you recognize this gun?
[RYUUROU]
Hmm... It's an old model.
Even older than me.
But I believe that
would be a Graugeist.
It's a traditional
European pistol.
[OSAMU] I actually saw this very
same type of gun last night...
[OSAMU]
...which seems to indicate
that they attacked me shortly
before the raid on the
armory was carried out.
[OSAMU] Then was it
all just a distraction?
[chuckles]
How very interesting.
They're a far more
ingenious bunch
than I had first
given them credit for.
Mr. Hirotsu, these men
hit one of the Port Mafia's
most secure storage units.
They gained entrance
with the official passcode
that is only known to members
of a sufficient clearance level.
[RYUUROU] Are you saying that
we have a traitor in our midst?
That we don't know
who's behind these attacks?
[OSAMU] My subordinates did
torture one of them yesterday.
But the man killed himself
before revealing very much.
He swallowed a cyanide pill
he'd tucked inside a molar.
But it wasn't a complete loss...
We learned the name of
their organization... "Mimic."
[ODA]
He was living in a hotel, huh...
Ango Sakaguchi...
Intelligence officer
of the Port Mafia...
A man both accomplished
and mysterious.
Truth is... none of us
know very much about you.
You fool.
[ODA]
A ventilation shaft...
Sniper, huh?
[phone ringing]
[ODA]
Dazai!
[OSAMU]
What a surprise.
You so rarely call me.
[ODA] A sniper
fired at me in Ango's room.
I'm going after him.
He's at the building
across the street
from the secondhand bookstore.
[OSAMU] You want me
to cut off his escape route?
[ODA]
Yes.
I have the Silver Oracle with
me, so if you need me to, I'll--
[OSAMU]
There's no need.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Wait for me to get there.
[ODA]
Don't move!
This some kind of trap?
They must be after this safe.
Odasaku, duck!
[OSAMU] You are always such
a troublemaker, Odasaku.
I know you could've
easily and quickly killed
every one of these gunmen
if you had wanted to.
[ODA]
My ability... Flawless,
allows me to see up to
six seconds into the future.
You killed all of them?
[OSAMU] They wouldn't
have given us information
if we took them alive.
They already proved
they love the taste
of their poison pills
too much for that.
I know...
It wasn't the methodology
that you were concerned with.
Listen to me, these men
were combat professionals.
Even you wouldn't have been
able to avoid killing them.
True.
If you hadn't have shown up,
I'd be dead now.
[OSAMU]
Listen, Sakunosuke...
I understand that you have
a creed against killing anyone,
no matter the circumstance.
But it's that creed
that's holding you back.
It's why the Port Mafia is only
using you as an errand boy.
You have so much more potential.
Thanks for your concern,
but I've heard this lecture
more times than I can count.
Onto more important matters...
Just who were these guys anyway?
You see that gun
holstered on his waist?
It's a very old style
firearm from Europe...
It's called a Graugeist.
They're using vintage pistols.
They have a low accuracy
and firing rates.
Not exactly something
that would be well suited
for modern combat.
Most likely, its sole purpose
was to deliver warning shots
in a narrow alley like this.
That pistol most likely serves
as their personal emblem.
You haven't
answered my question.
They're called "Mimic."
Never heard of 'em.
I'm still investigating
the specifics.
Perhaps the fact that they had a
sniper staking out Ango's room
will give us a clue as
to their intentions.
I'm pretty sure that
they were after this safe.
That so?
[ODA]
It was hidden in Ango's room.
I wasn't able to
find a key, though.
Well then... I think I can help.
Let's take a look-see.
Allow me.
Huh.
[click]
And voila!
[ODA] He's sure
clever with his hands...
[gasps]
No...
It can't be...
If what you said
earlier is true
and this gun is some
kind of emblem of theirs,
does this mean Ango
was one of them all along?
We shouldn't jump
to conclusions.
He may have taken this
gun off of one of them
during an altercation,
or it's possible that
they planted it in his room with
the purposes of implicating him.
[sighs]
Yeah, I guess you're
right about that.
[OSAMU]
I will say...
I did notice something
odd yesterday.
When the three of us
were drinking at the bar,
Ango said he had just
come back from a deal.
I think that was a lie.
How so?
Did you see the
inside of his bag?
It had cigarettes,
a folding umbrella, a camera,
and his prize,
the antique watch.
The umbrella was wrapped in
cloth and had clearly been used.
He'd gone for business to Tokyo,
where it had been storming.
So his umbrella was wet
because it was raining.
What's odd about that?
What's odd is that
he supposedly commuted
to his appointment in his car.
So when did he have a
chance to use his umbrella?
It wasn't before the deal,
because the umbrella was
on top of the antique watch.
And it wasn't afterward.
Why's that?
Going off the
condition of the cloth,
the umbrella was
more than lightly used.
It had to have been
soaking in the rain
for a good half hour or so.
But for being in
the rain for so long,
neither his shoes nor his pants
showed any evidence of it.
If his deal was at eight,
and we met at the bar at ten,
two hours wouldn't
have been long enough
for his shoes and pants to dry.
Maybe he changed
his clothes before coming.
If so, I would've seen some kind
of evidence of that in his car.
He happened to drive
me home that night.
I don't think
Ango made a deal.
I think he went to
meet someone in the rain.
He talked to them
for about 30 minutes,
and then killed some time
before heading over to the bar.
Intelligence officers like
Ango will sometimes choose
a rainy road on which to conduct
their classified meetings.
It's more secure
than an indoor space.
He's the Port Mafia's
classified intelligence officer,
of course he'd have
one or two meetings
he couldn't tell anyone about!
If it was business as usual,
why not say so?
If he'd told us he
couldn't talk about it,
we wouldn't have
pressed any further.
Isn't that right?
[ODA]
He has a point.
[OSAMU] But instead,
he made up an alibi.
Why would he go to such
lengths to hide a meeting?
Would ya look at that...
You sure don't go down easily.
To be perfectly honest, I'm
really impressed by all of you.
No other organization
has had the gumption
to go head-to-head
with the Port Mafia.
Dazai! Stop!
[OSAMU] Can you see the
glimmer of pure joy in my eyes?
With just the slight squeeze
of your finger on that trigger,
you can deliver to me what
it is my heart most desires.
My only fear is the possibility
that you'll miss your target.
But you won't.
Because you're
a sniper, aren't you?
Dazai!
Either way,
you won't make it out alive.
You might at least try to kill
one of the enemy executives.
What do you think you're doing?
Come now, take me
with you to the afterlife.
Please, won't you wake me from
this oxidizing world of a dream?
Don't!
[gunshot]
[OSAMU]
Sorry if I worried you.
Was quite the
performance, wasn't it?
Performance...
[OSAMU]
I knew that he'd miss.
His left cheek had the imprint
from his sniper rifle,
meaning he was left-handed.
He was using his
non-dominant hand,
and he was so unsteady
that he could barely walk.
And with the type of
pistol he was using,
he would've had to press it
right up against my forehead.
I knew you'd take action if
I distracted him long enough
and whittled down his
stamina until he couldn't--
Just shut up, Dazai.
I've heard enough.
Odasaku...
Please find Ango.
[ODA]
Yeah, I get it.
[ANGO] The Graugiest you
found has a special engraving.
It proves, without a doubt...
...that the owner belongs
to the Mimic organization.
It took me a year to get
my hands on that pistol.
[ODA]
Ango... are you actually...
[ANGO]
If we could,
I would have liked nothing
more than for the three of us
to go drinking together
at that bar again.
[ODA]
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs,
episode 14: "Nowhere to Return."