[ATSUSHI] The head may err,
but never the blood.
[YUKICHI sighs]
Hmm?
[OSAMU] I really
don't feel like working.
Are you seriously gonna
mope around like this
the whole morning?
Any other time I'd be up
for having this conversation
with you, but not now please.
[DOPPO] What happened
to the energetic young hero
who just helped save this town
from the brink of destruction?
[OSAMU] The boss has me
lined up for this new job,
and I don't wanna.
Is that the same
one Atsushi and the boss
were talking about yesterday?
Correct.
Good morning, sir.
Dazai, what's the status of that
meeting with the Port Mafia?
[OSAMU]
I've made the arrangements.
[YUKICHI] Do you think
their boss will come?
[OSAMU]
I'm positive.
It's a perfect opportunity
for him to kill you, after all.
I'd prefer that to having
bloodshed amongst our people.
Hey, Dazai...
What's this secret meeting
with the Port Mafia all about?!
Well, I have to admit
our little Atsushi's idea
has really snowballed.
Since the Guild is now
our biggest threat,
we've decided to--
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
I'm totally lost here...
First of all!
Why are you the one
arranging this meeting?
Because... I used to
be with the Port Mafia.
[DOPPO]
Huh?!
[OSAMU]
Oh, did I not tell you that?
My bad.
[DOPPO]
What?!
[CHUUYA] We've incurred
over a hundred casualties
in our organization alone.
I hate to admit it, but if Dazai
hadn't neutralized the curse,
that number would have
increased by ten fold.
I imagine my
predecessors would've been
rather upset with me.
[OUGAI]
Why are you here?
Dazai decided to kick me out
of the Armed Detective Agency,
saying he had no need
for such a useless prisoner.
He was even having me run
errands in exchange for my stay.
This is from the
boss of the Agency.
It seems he'd like
to meet with you.
Oh?
So that's his play...
[OUGAI]
How are you feeling today, Boss?
[BOSS] Doctor, tell the
board this is an order:
Kill all enemy organizations,
military police,
anyone else who opposes
the Port Mafia by sundown.
[OUGAI]
That would be most unwise.
I don't care how many
of our own need to die.
Just kill them.
Just kill them all.
Kill them. Kill them.
[OUGAI]
I hear you loud and clear.
[OUGAI] The boss
has succumbed to illness.
He left behind a will,
entrusting me with his position.
You're the witness to that fact.
Understood?
[OSAMU]
Welcome, "Boss."
[OUGAI]
It's been four years.
Do you happen to remember
the coat that I gave you Dazai?
[OSAMU]
Of course.
I had it burned.
[YUKICHI] Ougai Mori,
Boss of the Port Mafia...
[OUGAI] President of the
Agency, Yukichi Fukuzawa...
[YUKICHI]
So the time has finally come.
If the government
found out the leaders
of the most powerful
gifted organizations
were meeting like this,
I'm sure they would be
absolutely furious
to say the least.
I'll get straight
to business then.
A new member of the
Agency proposed an alliance
between our organizations.
And?
I objected at first.
The idea of cooperating
with criminals
goes against
everything we stand for.
But the request came from
someone who has been shot,
kidnapped, slashed, and
beaten by the Port Mafia.
Thus his words carry weight.
I felt that I should investigate
his request, at the very least.
It would seem that we are both
in rather a difficult position.
[YUKICHI]
These are my thoughts.
At the very least,
I would like to propose a
temporary truce between us.
Heh. Have you ever read
the works of Schelling?
[YUKICHI]
Hmm?
Or are you more
familiar with Kissinger...
[OSAMU] Both are researchers
of strategic studies.
Taught by a certain
you-know-who.
[YUKICHI]
I do read Sun Tzu.
[OUGAI] There is a parallel
between state warfare
and the strategies of
organizations like ours.
No force shall reprimand us
if we violate an agreement.
What sanctions could be imposed
if the Port Mafia suddenly
broke a ceasefire?
Or your people for that matter.
Only the party that decided
to uphold the
agreement would suffer.
As long as circumstances prevail
which incentivize betrayal,
a limited ceasefire
cannot be established.
The only option left...
is for complete cooperation.
That's also impossible.
[OUGAI]
Indeed.
The Port Mafia
is an organization
of pride and resentment.
Many of my people
have been dragged
through the grime and muck.
Many of mine have been brought
to the brink of death, as well.
But they didn't die, did they?
That is a source of great
shame for the Port Mafia.
[YUKICHI] Then why
don't we have it out now?
Let's settle this and put
all of our grievances to rest.
I thought you had
discarded your katana...
You really haven't changed
at all, have you Fukuzawa?
And you still haven't
outgrown your obsession
with scalpels, Doctor Mori.
You still carry on
like a little girl.
This from the man who thinks
he can communicate with cats.
Huh?
A hologram ability, I see.
I enjoyed our encounter.
Let's continue it
on the battlefield.
[YUKICHI] The Agency
will be recovering Q tonight.
[OUGAI]
What of it?
[YUKICHI] I would advise you
not to get in our way.
For our sake, as well as yours.
Why's that?
We actually have
something in common,
something important to us.
We both have
a love for this city.
As people who live here
and work to keep it safe,
we cannot allow
outside forces to destroy it.
[OUGAI]
The Guild is powerful.
You stand no chance
against them.
That's right, before I go,
my offer still stands
if you wish to come back
into the fold, Dazai.
Not a chance.
After all, you're the reason
why I was pushed out
of the Port Mafia
in the first place.
As I recall, you left
out of your own volition.
You were afraid of me,
weren't you?
Afraid that I would aspire
to take your position,
that one day I'd run a
knife across your throat.
Just like you did
to your predecessor.
They say that evil
expects evil from others.
I don't like the idea of
allying with you, either.
[OUGAI]
Our troops?
[RYUUROU] They've been
deployed as ordered.
You're aware I've
been with the Port Mafia
under you longer than
with the previous boss.
[OUGAI]
You are quite senior here.
[RYUUROU] The organization
was practically in ruins
toward the end of his tenure.
He was gravely ill,
and his orders were
erratic to say the least.
In what we thought
were its last throes,
the Port Mafia engaged
in one fruitless
conflict after another.
If not for you, he would have
eventually destroyed this city.
Is there a point
to all this babble?
[RYUUROU]
I simply wanted to state
that I believe Dazai fully
understands your intentions.
[OSAMU] So this is
where Q is being kept.
[STEINBECK]
Pleasant evening, isn't it?
Seems our strategist has hit
the nail on the head once again
in predicting your movements.
Figures it'd be a trap...
[OUGAI] Even in the event
that Dazai didn't intend
to usurp my position, all of
my decisions in the moment
were calculated and optimized.
Therefore, I have no regrets.
But if Dazai had stayed
to be my right-hand man
against the Guild,
they'd have been no match.
They say that evil
expects evil from others.
[OUGAI]
Mr. Hirotsu,
fetch me the communicator
to the frontlines.
I have it right here, sir.
[OUGAI] Despite what
I said to the Agency,
there is a rational path
toward a proper alliance.
Advance payment is
the essence of trust.
One party initially
incurs a loss up front,
with the prospect of gaining
a return hundreds of times over.
Only then will an
alliance quell bad blood.
Those two once defeated an enemy
gifted organization overnight.
Their alliance was considered
the most devastating
rivalry in history.
Tonight shall
mark their reunion.
[CHUUYA]
Let me set one thing straight.
Once I'm done taking out
the trash, you're next buddy.
Gimme a break, will ya?
I knew there was a reason
today was gonna suck.
The hell?
I never heard anything about
this in the strategic forecasts.
[OSAMU]
Sorry, I can't let you do that.
The cancelling ability...
This is such a drag.
[CHUUYA]
Hey, don't be stealin' my lines!
Now, let us take back our lead.
This retaliation will be our
common front against the Guild.
[OSAMU groans]
For cry'n out loud,
this is the worst day
I've had in years.
[CHUUYA]
Yo, Dazai, ever heard of Petrus?
[OSAMU]
The exorbitantly expensive wine?
[CHUUYA] The night you
vanished from the organization,
I opened up an
'89 bottle in celebration.
That's how fed up
with you I was.
[OSAMU]
How sweet.
I remember setting a bomb
under your car that night.
[CHUUYA]
Wait, that was your doing?!
You make me sick.
Yeah, well you're no
ray of sunshine either.
Only thing I like about
you is your taste in shoes.
[CHUUYA]
Huh?
You do?
Yeah, as if.
Why you...!
[OSAMU]
Give it up.
I know your moves far too well
to be hit with a kick like that.
[CHUUYA]
I was going easy on you!
If I were serious,
you would've been toast!
Oh, yeah...?
You're so scary.
[OSAMU]
There he is.
The sleeping beauty
awaiting his savior.
[CHUUYA] Wouldn't have
gone with "sleeping beauty"
but all right...
[OSAMU]
Gimme your knife.
Why?
[OSAMU] Oh, wait, I swiped it
off you earlier, just in case.
[CHUUYA]
God I hate you!
[OSAMU]
Not gonna stop me?
[CHUUYA] My orders were
to take him back alive,
but seeing that kid's face
again gives me flashbacks
to all the body bags
my people came home in,
thanks to his curse.
Do what you want.
[OSAMU]
Very well.
I'll do just that.
[CHUUYA grunts]
You sure got soft.
This angelic behavior
doesn't suit you one bit.
As long as Q is alive,
the Port Mafia still needs
my ability as a counter measure
against his curse.
Therefore it won't be in
their interest to kill me.
It's a strategic move.
[CHUUYA]
I dunno if I buy that...
Hey, Dazai...!
How about you gimme
that doll, you jerk?!
You wish!
This doll right here
is my insurance!
[CHUUYA]
Asshole...
I swear I'm gonna--
[LOVECRAFT] This shoulder
has been stiff as of late...
Perhaps I have been
working too hard.
What was that ability?
[OSAMU] I'd expect
no less from the Guild!
What amazing power!
[CHUUYA]
Get offa me!
Hey Dazai, what's the plan?
Whaddya mean "what's the plan"?
With my gift,
all I have to do is touch them
with one itty-bitty finger and--
Dazai!
That punch... was strong...
[OSAMU grunts]
[CHUUYA]
Hey!
[OSAMU chuckles]
[CHUUYA]
You okay?
Yeah...
No, you're not...
What happened back there?
[OSAMU] Those tentacles
are very strange.
I can't disable them
with my ability.
[CHUUYA]
No way.
How can that be?
There are no exceptions
to my disabling ability.
Which leaves only
one possible answer.
It's not a gift at all.
[CHUUYA]
What?!
[CHUUYA] Come on, you've gotta
be joke'n with me now, right?
If it's not some kind of gift,
then just what is it?
Who's to say?
We'll do things the
old fashioned way.
How about
Operation Shame and Toad?
Huh?
What is this,
Rain Beyond the Window?
I'm not so sure about that.
[OSAMU]
Come now.
Have my tactical decisions
ever led us astray before?
[CHUUYA]
Hmm... Ugh!
I'm so very hungry...
[OSAMU]
Yo!
[LOVECRAFT]
After I dispatch this enemy,
I'm going home.
He was a decoy?
Interesting...
Gravity manipulation...
My special ability controls
the gravity of those I touch.
It's time for a nap, octopus.
Nicely done!
[CHUUYA]
I can't believe you...
So sleepy...
I'd rather not move...
However...
I still have to fulfill my side
of the deal with Francis.
Dazai!
Huh?!
[CHUUYA] Oh come on, you gotta
be kidd'n me with this crap.
[OSAMU]
It's... something inhuman.
[CHUUYA]
Hmm?
Dazai, your arm...
Chuuya, there's something you
should know before I die...
What the hell, man!
You're not dying
in a place like--
Psyche!
I just love that old gag!
And it seemed like the
perfect time to use it!
How about concentrating
on how to kill that thing
instead of your
second rate magic tricks?
It's hopeless.
We should probably give up.
But maybe we have one
more course of action.
Hang on...
...is it what I'm thinking of?
We could show that
creature how we wiped out
an entire gifted
organization overnight
and received the title of
"devastating rivals."
Of course, if I don't get
to you in time, you might die.
I'll leave the decision to you.
Really, you're gonna
put the ball in my court...
I hate it when you
say stuff like that.
It always means that
I actually don't have a choice.
Grantors of dark disgrace...
[CHUUYA]
...you need not wake me again.
[STEINBECK] What am
I even looking at right now?
[OSAMU] Want me to
fill you in, worker bee?
That right there is the fully
realized form of Chuuya's gift.
[OSAMU]
His corrupted form allows him
to manipulate nearby gravitons,
creating a black hole which
swallows everything in its path.
The drawback is
he relinquishes control,
attacking in a blind rage
until he wastes away.
[OSAMU] Seriously though,
just what is that creature?
[OSAMU] No matter what he does,
it regenerates immediately.
Given that you're its partner,
I imagine you must
know what it truly is.
I don't.
And even if I did know,
why would I tell you?
[OSAMU]
This is bad.
Chuuya's body won't
last much longer.
[STEINBECK]
That's a shame.
Doesn't matter 'cause there's
no way to destroy Lovecraft
from the outside
when he's in that state.
[OSAMU]
The outside?
So does that mean
that he's vulnerable
if he's attacked
from the inside?
All right, Chuuya... finish him.
[laughs]
You've annihilated the enemy.
It's time to take a break.
[CHUUYA] I told you to stop
me as soon as it was over.
[OSAMU] I was going to, but it
was so entertaining to watch!
The reason I used Corruption
was because I trusted you.
You better listen
to me... If you don't...
...take me to the
extraction point...
...I'm gonna kill--
Don't worry, buddy.
I've got you.
I can't believe it.
Lovecraft's really down.
Just who in the world
are you people anyway?
The bad guys' enemy.
That's all.
[RAMPO]
Yes!
The Guild challenged me
to a detective game.
Maybe it'll save me
from my boredom.
But who's this "Poe"
who sent me the challenge?
Eh, whatever.
If I win, he'll give me
secret documents
on the Guild's flying fortress.
[POE] That would be
incredible intel if you got it.
It would change the
outcome of this battle.
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs,
episode 22, part 1:
"Poe and Rampo";
part 2: "Where the
Moby Dick Goes."
[RAMPO] You think the boss
will praise me if I snag this?