[FITZGERALD]
All right then, Tiger Boy,
time to come with me.
[ATSUSHI] It's the same
thing all over again.
I'm right back
to where I started.
[KYOUKA]
Hold it.
[FITZGERALD]
Hmm?
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
You're with the
Port Mafia, aren't you?
Not quite.
I'm with the Agency now.
Name's Kyouka.
[FITZGERALD]
What a barbaric display!
And from such
a young girl at that.
Huh? No, wait!
Good grief.
[ATSUSHI] We've been
looking all over for you.
Where have you been?
[KYOUKA]
In the slums and back alleys,
where I used to live.
But I realized that I didn't
belong there anymore.
I made a call to the police
from a pay phone.
The Guild will have a
difficult time moving around
with them on the scene.
[ATSUSHI]
Kyouka...
[KYOUKA]
Hm?
You didn't have to get
involved in this war.
All you had to do
was stay hidden away.
But my only real home
is at the Agency.
[KOUYOU] Kyouka is destined
to kill many more times.
That gift is bound to her,
and she will never
escape the darkness.
Much the same way
that I never could.
[KYOUKA] For the first time
ever, I wanna be more.
I'll fight for that.
And if that means using
what lurks inside me, so be it.
[KYOUKA]
They're here.
[ATSUSHI]
Excuse me, sir.
[OFFICER A]
What happened here?
[ATSUSHI]
Somebody attacked us.
They were armed.
That's horrible...
Captain!
Unit six here,
calling for headquarters.
[OFFICER C]
This is headquarters.
What's your location?
We're currently at dock three.
[OFFICER C]
We've received reports
of a serial killer in that area.
Subject is a young girl dressed
in traditional Japanese clothes.
She is approximately
14 years of age.
Take any necessary precautions.
Tell me young lady,
how old are you?
Headquarters, we have a--
Captain!
How could you do that?!
[OFFICER A]
Captain!
Just hang in there!
Headquarters,
requesting backup!
Just flawless.
[FITZGERALD] Even the
target's escape measures
were accounted for.
Miss Louisa's strategy proposals
are perfect, as always.
[KYOUKA gasps]
[TWAIN whistles]
Right on the money.
I used a rubber bullet so
we don't seriously hurt her,
but it's will string like hell.
[FITZGERALD]
Nicely done, Mark.
Well then, my little princess...
I'll be taking your
prince charming.
You can't!
Give him back!
[FITZGERALD]
I'm ready, Mr. Melville.
[MELVILLE]
Understood.
It's been a while,
my old friend.
[FITZGERALD]
I know we've only just met,
but allow me to give you some
advice, my little princess.
Your talents aren't
suited for helping people.
I don't believe I need
to spell out for you
what they are suited for.
[KYOUKA]
Why...
Why did you have
to show me the light?
to go and give me hope?
[GUARD]
Hands up!
You're under arrest
on suspicion of murder.
[KYOUKA]
Goodbye.
Don't show me any more light.
I can't take it.
[Q]
Ahh, it's so beautiful out.
I wonder who we
should play with today?
Oo!
How about him?
Hey, Mister, do you wanna
have some fun with me?
You're from the Guild,
aren't you?
I'm sorry. "Have fun"?
Like a child?
[LOVECRFT]
Oh.
Here you are.
A dachshund.
Uh. No thanks...
Okay, it's my turn
to pick a game!
One, two, three!
There!
Because you "hurt" me,
now you get a special mark!
Now, show me, Mister...
Show me true madness!
[LOVECRAFT] I'm sorry,
but I'm not sure I understand.
Would this be true madness?
[Q screams]
[FITZGERALD]
Good to see you awake, pastor.
[HAWTHORNE]
Lord Francis...
How are you feeling?
[HAWTHORNE]
Where's Margaret?
[FITZGERALD]
In critical condition.
She may never wake up.
[HAWTHORNE chuckles]
[FITZGERALD]
Hmm?
What an impudent woman.
She protected me
in that last moment.
That's why I'm still alive.
Before that happened,
Margaret said she would
take back her family's honor.
What did she mean by that?
She joined this operation
in order to repay
her family's debts,
and by doing so,
revitalize their reputation.
But that's nothing more
than a fleeting dream.
[HAWTHORNE]
It was never fleeting.
Not until you made
it so, Lord Francis.
What was that?
[HAWTHORNE] I will not
depend on you any longer.
If you chose to do nothing,
I will take back
her honor myself.
[FITZGERALD]
Louisa!
[shrieks]
[FITZGERALD]
Show me the emergency plan.
[ALCOTT]
Huh? But that plan
will incur a terrible amount
of collateral damage!
Yokohama will become
a sea of flames!
Don't forget that everything
here belongs to me.
You, the pens and ink, the
carpet which you're standing on.
All of it... including
the rest of my crew.
I will not allow harm
to befall my people.
You are all my property,
and as such I have
the right to protect you.
Notify everyone the
emergency plan is in effect.
Yes sir!
I'll end this all
in the blink of an eye.
[LOVECRAFT]
A dachshund...
[Q moans]
Hey, how's it going?
[Q]
My body... It hurts.
[STEINBECK] Well, if you're
looking for someone to blame,
try the people who
put this plan together,
or blame yourself
for the very foolish idea
of trying to destroy
Lovecraft's mind.
Why you... I'll kill you all!
[grunts]
[screams]
[FITZGERALD]
How are you enjoying your cruise
on the Moby Dick?
[LUCY]
Pardon me.
Hmph!
Why's she here?
[FITZGERALD] That's right,
you and Miss Lucy have met.
She's of no strategic
value to us now that her ability
is out of the bag, but she
insisted on staying with us.
Now then, back to business.
We are looking
for a particular book.
[ATSUSHI]
A book?
[FITZGERALD]
There's only a single copy of it
in the entire world.
It's said to be impervious
to any amount of firepower
or type of special abilities.
Someone with a gift foresaw
that it would be found
sealed away here in Yokohama.
[ATSUSHI] What does any
of that have to do with me?!
[FITZGERALD] You are very
much like the Tiger Beetle;
a term that can also
mean guide post.
I brought you here because
I wouldn't want you turning
to ashes along with
the rest of the city.
Ashes?!
[FITZGERALD] We've neutralized
the Gifted Operations Division.
But the Armed Detective Agency
and the Port Mafia
have both proven
to be quite a pain.
If we simply burn the city down,
we eliminate them and
make our search easier.
There's no way anyone
has such a powerful gift!
Does this look at
all familiar to you?
[gasps]
[STEINBECK] This plan makes
use of both of our abilities,
essentially combining
them together
to create the desired effect.
My ability gives me
the power to share my senses
between a host and vegetation.
I've connected you
to every tree in Yokohama.
The civilians will
proceed with their day,
blithely walking on roots,
hitting the trunks,
and cutting down branches.
All of that pain is being
transmitted into you,
even as we speak.
Now then, time for a pop quiz.
What do you think would happen
if your ability were
to be activated now?
[FITZGERALD] The moment
I rip this doll's head off,
roughly 20 percent of this city
will be afflicted by the curse.
This is our emergency plan.
We call it the Yokohama
Incineration Operation.
[STEINBECK] This city will
be destroyed all because of you.
Why me?
It's not like I had ever
asked to have this ability
in the first place.
So why do all of these terrible
things have to happen
because of me?
Isn't everyone equal
in the eyes of God?
You'd think so.
But this world
isn't nearly that kind.
So allow me to
tell you the bitter truth:
God does exist.
But... he has no love for you.
Liar!
No, it can't be.
I won't allow it!
I'll burn this world down!
I'll curse it!
I'll curse it all!
[laughs]
[WOMAN]
Hey, sweetie...
[MAN]
Yeah? What's up?
[WOMAN]
Did you always have that scar?
[laughs]
So it begins...
Now, to activate the ability,
all that's left for me
to do is destroy this doll.
[ATSUSHI]
Wait!
[SOLDIER]
Hey!
I give up!
The Agency and
I will help you accomplish
whatever it is you're after!
I'm begging you though,
please don't destroy that doll!
Is that your proposal?
How very interesting.
Fine.
Let's form a cooperative then.
[FITZGERALD] But only...
with the lucky survivors.
[MINOURA]
Ugh... a traffic jam.
It's kinda relaxing.
Not the word I'd use.
What the hell's going on?!
[POLICE OFFICER]
Sir, look!
[MINOURA]
Huh?
[ATSUSHI]
Let me out!
Damn it!
[ATSUSHI]
I've gotta do something!
[LUCY]
Oh my,
I thought I'd check on you
on my way to the garbage.
What a pleasant sight.
[ATSUSHI]
It's you...
Please, let me out of here!
[LUCY]
Not a chance!
I hate privileged
people like you!
Always looking down
on the rest of us.
Maybe you'll know how
it feels to be someone like me
when this place burns down,
and you're thrown
away like this doll.
Believe it or not,
I know exactly how you feel.
It must be--
How would you know anything?!
Have you ever been made to wash
dishes until your fingers bled?
Have you ever been tortured
with a hot iron poker?
You have absolutely no idea
how much pain and agony
I went through
to get these scars!
The first day,
it's the bones that hurt.
But the third day is the worst.
Oh!
[ATSUSHI]  Your skin burns
every time you move.
The pain is excruciating.
I know that feeling of horrible
isolation all too well.
But loneliness isn't some tyrant
that can keep us down forever.
It's more like a rain cloud
that can vanish
as quickly as it's formed.
A lot of people down there
have the same wounds we do.
If you abandon them...
[ATSUSHI] ...you abandon who
you were before all of this.
Is that what you want?
[gasps]
Where am I?
[LUCY]
You're too late.
Yokohama's done for.
[ATSUSHI]
No, there's still a way.
Dazai only needs to
be able to touch the doll
in order to stop the curse.
You must be delusional.
Did you forget
that we're in the sky?
Just how do you plan
to get the doll to him?
So... you're serious then.
You'll probably get shot
and killed in the air.
Maybe you'll hit
the ground and then die.
Or get cut up by
the mad men down there.
But you know all that already.
And you're still going to do it.
There was an old book
I read back at the orphanage.
One of the passages
stood out to me.
It read, "I've never regretted
any of the things I've done.
I've only regretted
the things that I didn't do.
Now that I think about it, what
was the name of that author?
[LUCY]
It's a parachute.
I kept one hidden in case
I needed to escape.
I connected the white door
to Moby Dick's exterior.
Hang on.
Won't the Guild punish you
for letting me get away?
Don't worry,
I've always been a lonely girl.
Besides, as long as I'm in
this room, they can't touch me.
Hey...
Are you sure that you're
gonna be all right here?
[LUCY]
Hm?
I know you said you'd be safe
while you're in this room.
But if that's true,
doesn't that also mean you
can never leave this place?
You're a bit slow on the uptake.
It was simply an excuse.
Live...
And then,
you can rescue me
from this place someday.
I'll be waiting.
It's a promise.
[FITZGERALD]
The tiger has escaped.
To your stations!
I repeat; The tiger has escaped!
Prepare the anti-air cannons!
Down there...
Keep the chaos under control!
If this keeps up, we won't have
anywhere left to do business.
Protect it with your life!
[ATSUSHI]
I see...
So that's what's going on.
[TWAIN]
All right, then.
If you have a moving target,
and you need to blow it out
of the sky, just leave it to me!
I can see you!
[ATSUSHI]
What the...!
Tom has pinpointed the target.
Yeah, atta boy, Tom!
All right now, Huck,
let's load the second shell.
[FINN]
Yes, sir.
Trajectory, check.
Accounting for firing
velocity with target, check.
It looks like Huck's shot
ripped right through
the kids parachute.
Yeah!!
So, how's our tiger boy doing?
He passed out from the blast.
At this rate, he'll be
dashed to pieces for sure.
But weren't you given
the order not to kill him?
Ah... As long as
his people find the body,
I'm sure they can figure
out a work-around.
[ATSUSHI]
I wasn't any help after all.
I couldn't do anything.
[tiger growl]
[ATSUSHI]
It's you.
Of course...
[tiger growl]
[ATSUSHI]
You hate me, don't you?
I hate myself, too.
[ATSUSHI]
Thank you... for everything.
I'm alive?
[DOLL laughs]
I have to deliver it!!
[gasps]
[ATSUSHI]
I need to stop all of this, now!
Amazing...
First he survived
such a huge fall,
and now my rain of bullets
can't even touch him.
He must be really desperate
to deliver that disgusting doll.
[TWAIN] Well! This is
no longer a hunt then.
This is a duel between two men.
[ATSUSHI]
What?
Has that thing always been here?
[TWAIN] Now's not the time
to lose focus, Tiger Boy.
There's no telling which way
trouble will come at you.
That's an oil truck!
This is over.
[ORPHANAGE MAN 1]
Stop your struggling.
You've reached your limit.
[ATSUSHI]
Shut up.
Huh?!
You did very well, Atsushi.
Dazai...
It's dangerous here.
They'll shoot at you from above!
I don't think they will.
Smoke?
[FINN] I think there's
more to it than that!
All heat sensors and
radars have been disabled.
It's a sensor jammer!
[TWAIN] He's been setting
those things up all over town.
He knew the kid would
get there with the doll!
[laughs]
Looks like ya got me!
[OSAMU]
Good job, Atsushi...
Yokohama is saved.
Though I can't say we're
out of the woods just yet.
As long as the enemy has Q,
they'll repeat this carnage
as many times as they need to.
So, what should we do now?
Dazai...
There's a passage from a
book I read a long time ago.
I remember it said the head
may err, but never the blood.
So I have an idea
about what to do.
I know it might sound out of
the question to everyone else...
But to me, right to my core,
in my blood and soul,
I feel it's the
only right answer.
[OSAMU]
What's your idea?
[ATSUSHI]
An alliance.
They're the most powerful
group in Yokohama,
and they're fighting
to defend this city.
I can't think of a
better organization
to help us in our fight
against the Guild.
And which organization is that?
[ATSUSHI]
The Port Mafia.
[ATSUSHI] "The head may,
err... but never the blood."
[OUGAI] An alliance between
the Port Mafia and the Agency?
[YUKICHI]
As a part of an organization
that operates
to protect this city,
I cannot allow foreign
gifteds to destroy it.
[OUGAI]
Could the two organizations
see past their grudges
to form an alliance?
If we pulled off such a feat,
the most powerful
duo will be revived.
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs,
episode 21: "Double Black."
[YUKICHI] Still obsessed
with little girls, I see.