Bring it.
Ability... Beast
Beneath the Moonlight!
Rashoumon: Demonic Armor!
[BOTH grunting]
[ATSUSHI, AKUTAGAWA gasp]
[ATSUSHI, AKUTAGAWA groan]
That all you've got?
I hope I didn't spend all
of that money for nothing.
[ATSUSHI]
Only three minutes left.
[OSAMU]
Kyouka, if you would prefer,
I can arrange for you
to be an assassin
for the rest of your life.
[OSAMU] But... your anguish
isn't yours alone.
What should one do,
when what they want to be
isn't what they're best at?
Everyone searches
for some kind of meaning,
for the correct way to live.
[OSAMU]
What do they fight for?
How should they live?
No one can answer
these questions for us.
All we have...
is the right to waver.
[OSAMU] Like stray dogs,
who have hit rock bottom.
Impossible!
Weretiger!
[ATSUSHI]
Can I escape my memories?
Is it possible?
[AKUTAGAWA]
Of course it is.
The words from your past are
fundamentally meaningless.
They do not dictate
who you are now.
[ATSUSHI] If I may shed
away my burden now, I will.
Go die, weretiger!
[yelling]
[yells]
[ATSUSHI yells]
[ATSUSHI]
I'm spent.
if he stands back up...
...I don't know what I'll do...
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[AKUTAGAWA gasps]
I did it...
Zelda...
I'll be there soon...
...and bring you...
...the happiness...
...you've always deserved.
[gasps]
He still has the
control terminal!
[AKUTAGAWA]
You idiot.
Weren't you paying attention?
I took it from him
during the last attack.
What?!
Why haven't you stopped it?!
I would love to rip you
to shreds right now,
but I've used up
all of my strength.
So this will have to do.
[ATSUSHI] You're gonna
pay you for this, I swear.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Hmm?
[ATSUSHI]
Descending?!
Buy why?
I haven't done anything!
[AKUTAGAWA]
Hand it to me!
It's not responding.
Something's going on.
[ATSUSHI]
It's no good!
It's not responding
from here either.
The ship is going to fall!
Is that him?
[ATSUSHI]
We're running out of time.
We need to do something,
or everyone's gonna die!
[MELVILLE]
It's no use.
Someone has infiltrated
this ship's navigations.
They're in control now.
That can't be...
[KYOUKA]
There's still a way.
I know that voice--
that you Kyouka?
[KYOUKA]
I overheard the situation.
Even if the Moby Dick can't
be stopped from falling,
we can destroy it
prematurely, making it crash
before it reaches the city.
I can do that using this drone.
[ATSUSHI]
Kyouka, that's an amazing idea!
We can save everyone!
Could you help us get
the parachutes ready?
You'll need to plan
your escape as well.
I can't.
I'm a prisoner here.
My ankle is
chained to the floor.
I wouldn't be able to make
it to the evacuation system.
[ATSUSHI]
But... then how are you gonna...
[KYOUKA] Forget about me
and go ahead with the plan.
Don't be stupid!
We'll find another way.
You've gotta change course!
[KYOUKA]
I didn't think that there was
any ray of hope left for me.
But today, I finally
understood something.
I still have the power
to make a choice.
If I sacrifice myself
in order save everyone,
I'd also pass the entrance
exam in the process.
I'd become a real
member of the Agency.
That's something
I'd never regret.
Please, don't do this!
[ATSUSHI]
Let go of me, Akutagawa!
Kyouka, listen to me!
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Kyouka, no!
[ATSUSHI splutters]
[ATSUSHI]
Why?
Why did it have
to happen to her?
[AKUTAGAWA coughs]
Kyouka... What a little fool.
If she hadn't embraced the hope
of living in the world of light,
she would still be alive now.
[OSAMU] This was the outcome
we had hoped for, Atsushi.
[gasps]
[ATSUSHI]
Dazai!
President?!
[OSAMU]
Kyouka conquered her demons
and saved this city from harm.
She demonstrated the virtues
expected of the Agency.
[ATSUSHI]
But I-I still don't understand.
Why did she have to die?!
[OSAMU] I'll admit, the
process seems merciless.
However, there's a reason all of
this had to play out this way.
My ability is called
All Men Are Created Equal.
Its field of range applies only
to members of the Agency.
[OSAMU] His ability
allows an individual gifted
greater control of
their own ability.
The reason you're able
to control your weretiger
abilities now is because
you joined the Agency.
Kyouka was able to pass the test
and become an official member.
Right before the impact.
Do you see what I'm getting at?
[gasps]
Using Demon Snow's blade,
I was able to cut
the chain and escape.
So I'm back.
[ATSUSHI]
Welcome back.
[KYOUKA]
You're hurting me.
[ATSUSHI]
Ah! Uh... My bad.
[OSAMU] Sorry we had to keep
it a secret from you both.
But if we hadn't,
it wouldn't have made
for a proper entrance
exam, now would it?
[gasps]
[OSAMU]
Will we end up in the mountains?
The sea.
Roger that.
Did you guys... plan
this from the beginning?
The enemy's been defeated, and
Kyouka's back, safe and sound.
Isn't that all that
matters right now?
Wait, Dazai!
What about me?
After that final battle,
do you think I'm strong?
[OSAMU]
Let's see now,
you did help take out Francis.
But you look like you're about
to fall over from exhaustion.
Does that really matter?
I still won!
You have become strong.
[OSAMU]
Oops...
[OSAU]
It's a nice view, isn't it?
This is your city, Atsushi.
You saved it.
[ATSUSHI]
Is this my city... really?
[ANGO] The war amongst
the gifted may be over
but it caused enormous
damage in Yokohama.
Now, the government's work
is just getting started.
Cleaning up after
such a huge mess.
I don't think I'll be sleeping
at home for days.
Setting all that aside
for now however,
have you considered our request
for your assistance,
Mr. Melville?
It would be very
much appreciated.
[MELVILLE] I just want
to watch the sea for now.
Your information would
help us out a great deal.
We wouldn't even have
to arrest any Guild members
who weren't
involved with that plot.
[MELVILLE] Do you really think
a mere grunt such as myself
would have that
kind of information?
Yes, I do.
Because a long time ago, you
were the leader of the Guild.
[MELVILLE] I wish that
you young'uns wouldn't
insist on bringing up the past.
You would save me a lot of
sleepless nights by cooperating.
And I'd rather not
have to use these.
[MELVILLE sighs]
[TWAIN] I never imagined that
ship would end up underwater.
It's a shame.
I was comfortable there.
[STEINBECK]
On the Moby Dick?
[TWAIN]
In the Guild.
Now that the boss
is missing in action,
I hear all sorts of
insurgencies have sprouted up
within the group.
It was all fun while it lasted,
but it's time to bid
a kind goodbye.
Yeah.
Life goes on like
it always does.
[TWAIN sighs]
That's true.
Well, I'm gonna go back home and
finish workin' on my biography.
What about you two?
I'm going to look
for Lord Francis.
I'm sure he's alive...
Hmm...
Guess you're gonna go back
to your family, right, John?
Not just yet.
Huh?
I have to stop the revolts
happening in the Guild.
Come again?!
Heh. That's a surprise.
And here I was thinkin' that
you hated the boss's guts.
[STEINBECK]
I do.
I hate anyone who uses
money to control people.
But he depended on
his wealth to save his family,
and unfortunately for him,
this was the result.
I can't leave things
on this note.
[LOVECRAFT]
The contract...
...it is finally fulfilled.
Still kickin', huh, Lovecraft?
What are you gonna do now?
Go to sleep.
[TWAIN]
Just who was that guy?
[STEINBECK]
Does it really matter?
All I know is he's
one of my few friends.
Hey, Kyouka...
...after you.
[RAMPO]
One, two...!
Congratulations!
Welcome to the Agency!
[ALL]
Cheers!
[DOPPO]
Atsushi.
How are your injuries?
[ATSUSHI]
Oh, I'm all better now.
Because of your heroic actions,
this city was saved
from destruction.
As your senior,
there's something very
important I wanted to tell you.
First of all, despite the fact
that you engaged in a solo
operation, I will remind you
that we typically conduct
our missions in teams!
Also, I expect you to be
an upstanding gentleman
towards Kyouka now that she'll
be working closely with us!
Don't let me catch you doing
anything shameful towards her,
do you hear me?! I know...
[AKIKO] Give it a rest,
Sargent Buzzkill.
Leave the poor
kids alone, will ya?
Why don't you come
have a drink with me?
[DOPPO]
I'm not sure that's a good idea.
Wasn't there something
else you wanted to tell them?
You did well, the both of you.
[AKIKO] All right,
let's drink the night away!
[DOPPO]
Hang on a moment!
[AKIKO] Are you gonna leave
me high and dry, Kunikida?
[ATSUSHI]
An "upstanding gentleman"
would probably apologize.
[ATSUSHI]
Haruno... Naomi...
[BOTH]
Huh?
Please forgive me!
[BOTH]
Uh?
I know that I was
under Q's curse,
but I did some
awful things to you both.
If I'd had more control
over my emotions,
that never would have happened.
[BOTH]
Ohh! Now I remember!
[ATSUSHI]
I'm sorry.
Will you ever forgive me?
[KIRAKO] Atsushi, you don't have
to worry about that anymore.
All of that stuff's
already in the past now.
A-Are you sure?
We're sure.
Thank goodness.
I really do feel
terrible about it.
I can't believe he was able to
get me to do all those things.
[JUNICHIROU]
Atsushi...
This is the first time
I'm hearing about all this.
What exactly did
you do to Naomi?
[ATSUSHI]
W-Wait a minute, calm down...
Oh, Rampo?
I brought over the new piece you
asked about over the phone.
[RAMPO]
Hmm?
Hey! Ed, you came!
Glad you could make it.
Is it really all right for me
to be here like this, Rampo?
I am from a rival group.
Gimme a moment.
I'll be right back.
Huh?
Ah! Wait don't leave me alone!!
[GROUP chattering]
[YUKICHI] That was
impressive work out there.
The Agency would be
nothing without you.
[AKIKO]
It's a party, drink with me!
[DOPPO]
Well, I guess one couldn't hurt.
Well Karl, seems like everyone's
having fun, aren't they?
[CHUUYA]
It's a Romanee-Conti.
[KOUYOU]
So generous!
Isn't this your treasure?
If there's a better occasion
to open this baby up,
then I don't know what it is.
Let's make a toast.
To victory.
[OUGAI]
Hmm. Delicious.
[CHUUYA] Boss... how should
we punish Akutagawa?
[OUGAI]
Punish him?
He was a crucial element
in our success.
Akutagawa has always been
a bit of a loose cannon.
As many times as
he's gone rogue,
causing mayhem in the process,
he's always gotten results.
As long as he
continues to succeed,
there will be no repercussions.
I wanted to ask you, Kouyou,
when you were
captured by the Agency,
why didn't you try and escape?
It ought to have been
quite easy for you to pull off.
Now why didn't I...?
Perhaps the tea
was just to die for.
[OSAMU] Hey, Sister, let's make
a deal, just us two grown-ups.
I have a plan for saving Kyouka.
I'm listening.
If we succeed, we'll be able to
save not only Kyouka's life,
but her happiness as well.
Dazai had already seen how
all of this would play out
to the very end.
What a terrifying man.
Listen, Kouyou,
your powers are undeniable.
If you wanted to leave the
Port Mafia and go after Kyouka,
it would be quite difficult for
me to stop you from doing so.
I know that.
Sadly, I have to help
a clumsy leader
with reestablishing
their organization.
[OUGAI] Heh.
I'm quite grateful for that.
But I prefer the women in
my life to be under 12.
Don't start.
Or I'll sew your mouth shut.
Damn you, Dazai!
I'll kill you next
time for sure!
[chirps]
[KIRAKO]
He's so adorable!
Is it all right if I touch him?
[AKIKO]
Well, I guess he is pretty cute.
[JUNICHIROU] Hold on.
I got it. I got it. Here we go.
Oh, that's right, where's Dazai?
[footsteps]
[RYUUROU]
What a wierd piece.
I bet I could even paint
something like this.
[OSAMU] I wanted to thank
you for your help, Hirotsu.
[RYUUROU]
I did practically nothing.
I merely leaked
the infiltration route
of the Moby Dick to Higuchi.
[OSAMU]
Yes, but once she knew,
it was a sure bet
she'd tell Akutagawa.
And once he knew,
it was obvious he'd go there
on his own to get Atsushi.
Why did you go through all
that trouble to bring Akutagawa
and the Tiger Boy together?
You could call it "insurance."
We need to be ready.
A real disaster
is coming our way.
And he's already on the move.
[DOSTOYEVSKY] So the destruction
of the Moby Dick was a failure.
Still, just about everything
else is going according to plan.
We succeeded in creating
a rift within the Guild,
and recruited talented
gifteds such as yourself.
I'm only helping for
the time being to fulfill
my end of the deal, and to see
that Margaret is resuscitated.
[DOSTOYEVSKY]
That's fine by me, Pastor.
We'll work together.
And paint this land
with the blood of the guilty.
All for the sake
of a better world.
[OSAMU] From past experiences,
I know that we won't be able
to avoid going to
war with the Demon.
Akutagawa is formidable enough
by himself, but his abilities
are most effective when
used in a supporting role.
He would be a powerful ally
when complementing an attacker
such as Atsushi, who excels
at speed and pure strength.
[OSAMU] We'll need something
more ingenious than ever
to fight against the Demon.
Something even stronger
than the former Double Black
team of me and Chuuya.
They might pull it off.
Tell me something...
Why do you treasure Yokohama?
You work so hard to defend the
people who live in this city.
[OSAMU] Heh. An old friend of
mine once told me something.
"Fight for the side of good
and protect the vulnerable.
At least then, It'll make your
world a little more beautiful."
[RYUUROU]
Teni Muhou.
[ATSUSHI]
This is the city we protected.
[AKUTAGAWA coughs]
[AKUTAGAWA]
What worthless nonsense.
[ATSUSHI] This city
and all the people in it
have become my home.