[ODA]
Ango Sakaguchi...
[ODA] Intelligence officer
of the Port Mafia...
A man both accomplished
and mysterious.
Truth is...
...none of us know
very much about you.
[OWNER]
How's the curry today?
[ODA]
The same as usual.
How're the kids doing?
They're all upstairs
if you wanna say hello.
[ODA]
It's me.
Coming in.
How's it going?
You bein' nice
to the old geezer?
[ODA]
Hmm?
[KOSUKE]
I've got ya now buddy!
Wow, that was easy!
Ya give up?!
Looks like I'm gonna
have to show you guys
just how scary
the real Mafia is...
Do you surrender?
Not a chance!
[ODA]
In that case...
It's time for some
Mafia-style torture.
[laughs]
Stop it!
I'll gonna die! Stop it!
Please! Please!
No more! Stop it!
It's too much! I give up!
We're all gonna get you
next time for sure!
I'm looking forward to it.
[OSAMU]
This is too hot! Hah...
Did you add lava to it as a
secret ingredient or something?
[OWNER] Odasaku gets
that dish all the time.
So, how'd things
go with the kids?
The same as usual.
Are those the orphans
from the Ryuuzu Dispute
that happened two years ago?
You're a member of the Mafia,
but you don't kill anyone,
you have no interest in moving
up, and look after orphans.
You're a strange one.
I don't know anyone else
in the Port Mafia like you.
You're stranger than I am.
Here, this should cover
the kids for the time being.
Sure you don't
want me to pitch in?
You really don't have
to foot the bill yourself.
You've already done
more than enough,
giving them a place to stay.
Long as I can eat
your curry whenever I want,
I don't need anything else.
You come here
about that "issue"?
Uh... Yeah... that's right.
I've come to the conclusion
that they're an organization
of gifted members from overseas.
They were chased
by a British group
called the Order
of the Clock Tower,
which prompted them
to make their escape
from Europe to Japan.
Why would a group like
that have gone through
the trouble of coming
all the way here?
It does seem a
bit out of their way...
Perhaps there was something
waiting for them here.
[ODA]
I suppose that's possible,
but there's one thing
that's been bugging me...
[OSAMU] You mean how skilled
the soldiers were, right?
[ODA]
Yeah.
[OSAMU]
They're all veterans...
According to my information,
the head of that organization
uses a powerful gift
in order to make
them all act as one.
So that's how
he commands them...
Is the boss already
aware of this information?
[OSAMU]
I gave him my report.
He asked me to develop
an anti-Mimic strategy,
and see to it that
it was implemented.
I've already set up
a variety of traps.
This might be a stupid question,
but considering the
group we're dealing with,
wouldn't this be a matter
for the government?
[OSAMU]
You're referring to the
Ministry of Home Affairs'
secret department, yes?
The Gifted Operations Division
doesn't technically exist.
They rarely get involved.
[ODA]
And what about Ango?
[OSAMU] It's fairly certain
that he was responsible
for leaking the passcode
for the storage unit.
[ODA]
Did he betray the organization?
[OSAMU]
Everything does seem to line up
if we want to believe that.
[phone ringing]
[OSAMU]
It's me.
I understand...
Hmph.
A mouse sprung one of my traps.
[MIMIC MEMBER]
Our info was right.
What?
[coughing]
Sleeping gas...
...damn it.
[gunshot]
[ODA]
This is an accounting facility
that the Port Mafia uses
for money laundering.
Three years ago, Ango Sakaguchi
was scouted by the Port Mafia
and briefly assigned here.
Their records
detail that history.
If you'll excuse me, I must
be getting back to my duties.
Don't worry about me.
It's really nice here.
Maybe I'll ask to be
transferred to this position.
[OFFICE CLERK] Every young
person who's ever said that
ends up running out of here
in less than three days.
It's just too dull for them.
But take as much
time as you need.
[ODA] I found some
information that bothered me.
Two years ago, Ango went
to Europe on a business trip...
The purpose was to meet up
with a local stolen car broker.
That must have been
when he agreed to become
a double agent for them.
[ODA] This was the room where
Dazai and I first met him.
[ANGO] I'd appreciate it if
you didn't come any closer.
You reek.
[ODA]
Two years ago,
Dazai and I were put in charge
of taking care of the bodies
of organization members
who had died during
the Ryuuzu Dispute...
Do... I smell bad, Odasaku...?
[ODA] Primarily, we were
to recover their belongings.
If the police were
to find them first,
they could be used
to our detriment in accordance
with their anti-crime laws.
[OSAMU]
You must be new here.
[ANGO]
Mm?
Why don't you tell us your name?
It's Ango Sakaguchi.
Well, Ango... you're
a fascinating character.
Smelly!
Are you sure that
the boss approves
of what it is you're
up to right now?
And just what
are you insinuating
that I'm "up to" exactly?
That you're writing an
obituary for those who died.
Am I wrong?
He's writing obituaries...?
[OSAMU]
These are the three that died
during the attack on our
executives last night.
Kurehito Umeki, Shoukichi
Saegusa, and Miroku Ishige...
Umeki was a former MP
who was shamefully discharged
for killing a coworker.
Both parents are dead.
[OSAMU]
You're keeping a record
of their life events
and family history.
[ANGO] It's the least
that they deserve.
Every one of their lives has
to have had some meaning.
I wanted to do more
to remember who they were
than just chalk them up
as part of a body count;
to honor their sacrifice.
What did the boss
say about this?
I managed to convince him
to account for everyone
who had been reportedly killed
as a result of the incident.
He was very opposed
to the idea at first,
but he eventually saw great
value to the Port Mafia
in keeping such
detailed records
[OSAMU]
See?!
Isn't he fascinating?
What kind of person
goes through the trouble of
creating such a unique job?
There's only one
way to find out...
Let's take him out for a few
drinks at our usual spot.
[OSAMU]
That's a lovely idea.
Huh?! I can't do that!
I have work to do!
[OSAMU] I think I know just how
we can get him to leave early...
If we hug him real tightly,
the stench will be
unbearable for him
and he'll have to call it day!
Let's do it.
Gah! Hang on!
This is my best suit!
You can't do this!
I'm gonna be
very cross with you both!
[shrieks]
I'd like a full explanation...
[CURLY] We were able
to capture the group
that attacked the casino using
the knockout gas as planned.
One of them committed suicide,
but we were able to secure
the others and bring them here.
We had planned to interrogate
them about their other members.
We even removed
the poison capsules
that were hidden in their teeth.
I already know all that.
I was the one who put
those plans in motion.
I'm talking about afterward.
[CURLY] Well... one of the
soldiers regained consciousness
earlier than expected.
Before we could restrain him,
he stole one of our guns
and took out his own comrades,
most likely to silence them.
Then he proceeded
to come after us...
That's when I stepped in
to take care of the matter.
Do you have a problem with that?
[OSAMU]
Now I understand...
Of course not, Akutagawa,
you defeated the terrible,
monstrous enemy, and protected
our comrades from certain doom.
That's absolutely splendid.
If it weren't for
your awesome powers,
our men would've
been utterly helpless
to stop such a fearsome foe.
Nothing less from
my subordinate.
Thanks to you, all of the
planning that I did is ruined.
It's a little hard to
get the enemy to talk
when they're not breathing,
and now the trail's gone cold.
If even only one of
them had been left alive,
we might have uncovered
important information
their headquarters, motive,
their commander's background,
and the powers they use to
command the organization.
"Uncover information"?!
Do you really think that I would
go through the trouble of--
[OSAMU] If you thought
I was going to be appeased
with some excuse, I apologize...
...but you're sadly mistaken.
Hand me your gun.
My friend, Odasaku...
He's working hard to take care
of some orphans at the moment.
[AKUTAGAWA coughs]
[OSAMU] If he had been the
one to find you in the slums,
he would've taken you in
and done all he could
to see that you
were brought up right.
Because he's a virtuous person.
Regretfully for you,
I'm not interested in
virtue or saving anyone.
I'm only interested in results.
And you are useless to me.
Well!
[OSAMU]
Would you look at that...
How many times
have I told you...?
Your powers have far greater use
than that of a simple butcher.
You're capable of using
them for defense as well.
But I've never used
my powers like that before!
[OSAMU]
Well, you just did, didn't you?
Isn't that great?
Just remember this...
Next time I won't be so kind.
Got it?
[OSAMU]
Now then,
we should check the
bodies of the hostages.
We might find something.
[CURLY]
Sir...
what should we be looking for?
[OSAMU]
Anything and everything...
Whatever might trace
back to their hideout.
Their pocket lint,
the soles of their shoes,
any foreign bodies...
All of these could be clues.
Come on...
Being in the
Port Mafia means more
than just knowing how
to beat someone to death.
At this rate, Odasaku might
figure this all out on his own.
I'm aware of the
individual that you speak of.
Despite being in the Mafia,
they say he lacks
the guts to kill anyone.
It's hard to imagine a person
like that being your associate.
[OSAMU] You've made
two errors of judgment.
Huh?
[OSAMU]
Guts have nothing to do
with who we
should associate with.
The other is a warning...
If you value your own
safety, remember this:
Don't make him angry.
If he ever was to
become truly incensed,
I can assure
you without a doubt
all of us would be dead
within the blink of an eye.
When Odasaku unleashes,
he's more terrifying than
any Port Mafia member.
You could never hope
to defeat him
in a million years, Akutagawa.
Ridiculous...
That can't be...
Are you saying that
you actually believe I--
[OSAMU] All right,
let's get back to work.
We need to hurry up
and make sure
that everything is
cleaned up here.
We don't want the Supernatural
Special Operations Division
getting involved.
[phone ringing]
[click]
This is Oda.
[OSAMU]
Hey, Odasaku...
I found something
I want to tell you about.
Could we meet up and talk?
It's about the
enemy's hideout, isn't it?
[OSAMU]
Yup.
[ODA]
Did their soldiers tell you?
[OSAMU]
Not verbally,
but we were able to
get results from a dried leaf
that was stuck to the
bottom of one of their shoes.
[ODA] Ango Sakaguchi--
traitor to the organization.
This is where the
information leads.
[ODA] Dazai's men should
be arriving here shortly,
but I wanted to check
things out beforehand.
[ODA]
I wanted to confirm a hunch...
[ANGO]
Odasaku?!
What are you doing here?
This place is too dangerous!
The enemy is using
this facility as a hideout.
[ODA] You trying to tell
me that you don't need my help?
[ANGO]
I can handle things by myself!
Clearly...
Allow me to deduce why you're
in this position right now.
Mimic found out you
were a spy, didn't they?
Uh! How did you...
[ODA] Everyone
in the Port Mafia believes
that you're a spy for Mimic.
But they're wrong...
You've actually been
a spy for the Port Mafia
that infiltrated Mimic.
The reason that those guys
were staking out your room
with sniper rifles was to make
sure that the pistol hidden
in there wouldn't get stolen.
Some might wonder
why they weren't just sent
to the boss's hideout
to assassinate him.
That's because you lied
and told them you didn't
know of his location.
Which information
you decided to give up
and which you
decided to withhold,
it was all predetermined
by the boss.
[ANGO]
You need to get out of here...
Huh?
For all my planning,
I really screwed this one up.
They've set up a host
of timed explosives
all throughout this building.
They want to send
me straight to Hell
for being the traitor that I am!
[ODA]
You see?
It looks like you do
need my help after all.
[ODA]
Let's go...
How much longer 'til
the bombs go off?
Your powers can answer
that question better than I can.
if only they were
as convenient as that...
At least...
our time's not up yet!
[ANGO]
Odasaku?
Ready to jump?
What?!
[ANGO pants]
[ODA]
You all right?
All this excitement is a
little too much for me.
Still... thanks for saving me.
So how much of this
does the boss know?
[ANGO]
Nearly everything.
The boss was the only person
who knew about
me infiltrating Mimic.
[ODA] So the reason
he had me look for you
was to cover his ass.
He knew that I'd agree
to go searching for you,
while still being
kept in the dark.
[ANGO]
I need to report to him.
The head of Mimic is
extremely dangerous.
He plans to crush
the Port Mafia.
Who is this individual?
The name of
their leader is Gide.
He has a very powerful gift.
We mustn't fight against him.
Especially you, Odasaku.
[ODA]
Hmm?
The pistol that
was in that safe...
It serves as a type of emblem.
It has a unique carving
in the cocking piece,
which proves that its owner
is a member of Mimic.
What the hell is Mimic, anyway?
[ANGO] They are the
remnants from the War.
They only know how
to live on the battlefield.
Even now, what they
endured in the war haunts them.
Odasaku... what's that...?
A ball?
This is bad...
It's poison...
My ability, Flawless,
allows me to see several
seconds into the future.
However, it can't help me
if I've already fallen
for the trap by the time
I sense the danger.
Whoever set this up knew
how my powers worked.
[ODA]
Ango... Run...
[ANGO]
Odasaku...
Everything that I told you about
Mimic just now is the truth,
every last bit of it.
I didn't lie to you about that.
You have my sincerest
gratitude for saving me.
Farewell.
I wish that I could've gone
drinking with you and Dazai
at our usual spot like we
used to just one last time...
[ANGO] Are you aware that there
are people who actually think
you guys use your special
abilities to seduce women?
[OSAMU]
Yeah, they don't understand
that even if we wanted to,
it wouldn't work.
They'd just get creeped out,
and we'd fuzz it all up.
[ANGO chuckles]
"Fuzz it up"?
That's right... We'd fuzz it up.
[ODA coughs]
Sorry... Dazai...
Looks like I... fuzzed up...
[GIDE]
We are Mimic.
An army of criminals
forsaken by God.
Fight me, Sakunosuke.
You and you alone are
capable of purifying my soul.
[ODA]
No... I don't kill people.
[GIDE]
I wonder if you'll feel the same
after I show you the
hell inside my head.
[ODA]
Someday, I wanna be able
to just sit at my desk, and...
Next on Bungo Stray Dogs,
episode 15: "Some Day in
a Room with a Seaside View."