[ODA]
I remember it was raining...
[STRANGER] You're always
reading that same book, boy.
[ODA]
Hm?
[STRANGER]
Is it really that good?
[ODA]
It is.
I've read it several times now.
[STRANGER] But there are so
many other stories out there,
much more
interesting than that one.
And where's part three?
[ODA]
I don't have it.
I've looked for it
everywhere, but no luck.
[STRANGER]
Well, now it all makes sense.
Because the third installment
is the worst of the worst.
Best to be content
with those chapters.
Just forget about the rest.
[ODA]
I can't do that.
[STRANGER]
Why don't you write it then?
[ODA]
Me, write it?
[STRANGER] That's the only
way you can keep that story
as perfect as
you've envisioned it.
Writing a story is akin
to having complete
control over a person;
choosing how they
will live and die.
From my vantage point, you
have all the right qualities.
[ODA]
Just who are you anyway?
[STRANGER]
Who am I?
My name is...
Hmm? Huh...
[OSAMU]
Good to see you awake, Odasaku.
How do you feel?
[ODA] Like every
bender I've ever had in my life
just caught up
with me all at once.
I went to the place
you told me about,
and Ango was there.
So it would seem my suspicions
were correct then.
Yeah...
He disappeared into the night
with a group of
soldiers dressed in black.
[OSAMU]
If I had to guess,
I'd say they were
a Special Ops squad.
It looks like we can
divide these events
into two separate categories.
[ODA] Which one
do the soldiers fall under?
[OSAMU] They're different from
Mimic, so we can take them
out of the equation
for the time being.
Mimic is a far more
prevalent threat.
They've been causing
trouble in the city.
So we've assigned Akutagawa
and other members
of our combat division
to deal with them.
But we still don't know anything
about what kind of ability
their leader possesses.
We're at a loss.
This Akutagawa guy
you mentioned...
He's one of your
subordinates, right?
I understand he has
high offensive capabilities.
He's a naked sword
without a scabbard.
In time, I have no doubt he'll
become the strongest
member in the Mafia,
but right now, he needs to be
taught how to sheathe his blade.
But I digress.
This morning, the council of
five top executives convened,
and decided to attack Mimic
with everything the
Port Mafia can muster.
At the same time,
Akutagawa and some of my team
were hit by a surprise
attack at the art museum.
They're probably still fighting.
What are you doing?
Are you going?
Didn't you just say we're
hitting them with all we've got?
I didn't think you'd be
excited about fighting,
considering your stand
against killing anybody.
[ODA]
I'm not excited.
Why're you going then?
[ODA] I've acquired
a lot of debts in my life.
If your guys are in trouble,
then I should help.
You should forget
those debts, Odasaku...
After all, no one else but you
remembers what you owed
them in the first place.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Guns are the weapons of fools.
Not even worth my time.
[GIDE] So you're the
one they speak of,
the gifted one in black.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Who are you?
You may call me Gide.
I am the leader of Mimic.
[AKUTAGAWA]
He will never acknowledge me,
no matter how many
underlings I defeat,
so I'd like to challenge you.
[GIDE]
First, a question...
The ability you possess.
Is it sufficient enough
to release our souls
from the prison of original sin?
Why don't you find out?!
Nice try!
It seems that you
are not the one...
No way!
Is this one of his abilities?
You bastard!
Are you able to read
what I'll do next?
[gunshot]
[GIDE]
With enough time,
you may become powerful
enough to grant our wish,
but unfortunately for us,
we have no time to give.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Kill me.
Defeat means the same as death.
I only regret that I was not
able to be the enemy you wanted.
Farewell.
[gasps]
Are you able to walk?
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
Put me down!
Let me go!
[ODA]
Name's Sakunosuke Oda.
I heard about you from
Dazai and came to help.
[AKUTAGAWA] I've heard of
you from Dazai as well.
You're one of our lower-ranking
members, aren't you?
[ODA]
That's right.
[AKUTAGAWA] And I heard
that you and he are friends.
Is that true?
That's not for me to say.
And I never use
that word lightly.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Dazai told me...
He told me I could never hope to
defeat you in a million years.
[ODA] This isn't
the time for an argument.
Tell me...
...why doesn't Dazai
acknowledge me?!
No way!
[ODA]
Sorry...
...but I have to bring you back.
A friend of mine has
high hopes for you.
[GIDE]
It did come true.
What are you talking about?
[GIDE]
I had a vision
that I'd be able to find
the person I seek here.
I am Gide.
I have been
searching for the one
who can release the
souls of ghosts like us.
[ODA]
Well, I can get you a discount
with a local undertaker
if you'd like.
No need for that.
You're just the
person for the job.
[gasps]
Can't be...
[GIDE]
What's the matter?
I haven't even made a
move yet, and you're sweating.
[ODA]
What did you do?!
[GIDE]
I simply saw a future
where you would
dodge to the right,
so I proceeded to adjust my aim.
But it would seem that
you saw that future as well,
and compensated accordingly,
which I also witnessed.
Your ability to see a few
seconds into the future...
I know it well
because I have it too.
The predictive ability
we have is omnipotent,
which is why you
are the only one
who can kill me
and end this war.
As a member of the
Port Mafia, killing me,
the enemy leader,
must be your greatest desire.
[ODA]
Not interested.
I'm only here to help
one of my colleagues out.
What?
What kind of
Mafia member are you?
One that doesn't kill people.
[GIDE] Guns are tools
for killing people!
You put yourself in a war zone!
[ODA]
I'm not interested in violence.
What...?!
The only thing I'm interested
in is living my life.
Life is nothing compared
to the glory of death!
Excellent!
That's the way!
What?!
Is this your way of telling me
that you refuse to fight me?
[ODA] I have my
reasons for not killing people.
You'll have to look elsewhere.
Why is that?
My subordinates and I have
been wandering this world
like tormented spirits,
looking for a worthy end.
You are the one
who can deliver that to us.
You must fight me!
If you don't, then--
[ODA] I can't help
you with your dream
because I have a dream
of my own to fulfill.
Some day, when I can
quit the Port Mafia
and become a free man,
I'll find a quiet room,
one overlooking the sea...
[STRANGER] Then why
don't you write it then?
That's the only way
you can keep that story
as perfect as
you've envisioned it.
Then I'll be able
to become a writer.
Take up a pen, and throw
away my sword for good.
Someone once told me
writing a story is akin
to having control
over a person's life.
A man who takes
a life has no right
to be responsible for another's.
That's why I don't do it.
And that's the reason
why you refuse to
deliver respite upon us?
Is this really your answer?!
That's right.
[gasps]
Stop this!
[GIDE]
A bullet-proof vest, huh?
That pain is a
privilege of the living.
It's something we lost long ago.
We are already dead.
Our souls have
long left our bodies,
to be replaced
by vengeful spirits.
It doesn't have to be this way!
I don't know what
happened to you in the past,
but you still have a choice over
how you live in the present!
[GIDE]
Don't you see?
Only you can end our suffering!
If you truly understood, you
would grant my wish and kill me,
yet you refuse.
And because you are the only one
who can guide us to the
battlefield of purification,
I cannot kill you either.
I must make it apparent
to you who we really are.
Then you will understand,
between the two of us,
only one can be allowed
to remain here.
I hope you'll
look forward to it.
[OSAMU]
The night is the best time,
and it belongs
to the Port Mafia.
[ODA]
So what do we do now?
[OSAMU]
Can't say I know.
That was quite a
fiasco you got into.
Who would've thought
the enemy leader
would turn out to be
such huge fan of yours?
[ODA]
They're a strange bunch,
looking for a place to die
that they feel is
"worthy" or something.
[OSAMU]
I see...
Having some kind of
creative control over
how they die is something
I hadn't considered.
How long do you
think this conflict will last?
[OSAMU]
Mimic's army aside,
their leader's ability
is a nuisance.
Surprise attacks won't work.
That means we need
some kind of inside info.
Any leads you can think of?
Ango's the only one.
That's just who
I was thinking of.
I don't suppose that there's
anyway we could find him...
There is.
You serious?
As a matter of fact, we don't
even have to look much further.
[ODA]
He's really here?
[OSAMU chuckles]
Of course, where else?
Hey, you guys,
I started without you.
[ODA] You know,
you could've given us a call.
[ANGO] I had to spend
a little more time
covering my tracks than usual.
Though today, I can spend
as much time here as I want.
So then... how did
you two know I'd be here?
[OSAMU]
Just a hunch, I suppose.
[ANGO]
I feel lucky.
I didn't think I'd ever be able
to come back here again.
You know, I've gotta say Ango,
you're awfully
sentimental for a mole.
Even before you
joined the Port Mafia,
you had a different identity.
You were an agent of the state.
Specifically, of the Ministry's
Gifted Operations Division.
Your mission was to
monitor the Port Mafia.
While the Division
oversees all gifted activity
within our nation, an all-out
war with the Port Mafia
would incur heavy casualties.
Therefore, their primary purpose
is to supervise our activity,
as opposed to engaging
us in a skirmish.
That's why they had an
agent infiltrate our ranks
in order to keep tabs on us.
But all that changed when Mimic
pulled up a seat at the table.
This gifted
criminal organization
had been planning
to enter Japan
and were proving to be a real
headache for the Division,
so they decided to
have you monitor Mimic
as the Port Mafia's spy.
As a lowly salaried
government worker,
it was a job entirely
above my pay grade.
[ODA]
So, in other words,
you weren't a double agent,
but actually a triple agent.
Do I have that right?
[OSAMU]
Tell us about Mimic.
[ANGO] I understand that you
and Gide traded blows, Odasaku.
Did you happen to get
a glimpse of his ability?
[ODA]
I did.
[ANGO] He's an elusive man
and we never know
exactly where he is.
The brass intends to leave
this case to the Port Mafia.
[OSAMU] Well, that's very
convenient for them,
but even the Port Mafia is going
to have a difficult time dealing
with a special
ability like that.
Of course,
that's only in the case
that we don't consider
using a... certain someone.
Both of us can only
see into the near future,
so I wouldn't have any
meaningful advantage over him.
If push came to shove,
the outcome would
most likely come down
to our skills in combat.
The unknown variables
would matter a lot.
There's also the
ability's singularity.
What "singularity"
are you talking about?
When you used your ability
in the fight against Gide,
didn't something rather
unusual happen to you?
Yeah, it did...
Through observation, the
government has determined
that certain abilities when
interacting with one another
will become imbued with
entirely new characteristics,
although these cases
have proven to be quite rare.
You know, I'm really not
supposed to be here,
telling you two any of this.
If they knew what
I was doing right now,
it would cause a lot of problems
between me and the brass.
I'll have to go underground
for the time being.
That's cute.
You think we're gonna let
you walk out of here alive,
just like that?
You really gonna
start a fight here?
[ANGO]
This was a mistake.
I was naïve to come here.
I thought that maybe
if we met up like this again,
things would go back to normal,
back to how they were.
Ango.
You need to get out of here
before I change my mind...
[OSAMU]
It's all right. I'm not sad...
I knew this would happen
from the beginning...
It wouldn't have mattered
what side you were on.
Because anything I never
want to lose, is always lost.
This is how it's
always been for me.
Everything worth wanting
is lost the moment I obtain it.
And nothing I pursue is worth
the cost of
prolonging this life.
This suffering.
[ANGO] Listen, you two,
if there... if there
ever comes a time when
our sides don't exist anymore,
when we all become free men,
I want us to all
come back here and--
Ango, just stop.
[ODA]
Don't say anything more.
No...!
[ODA]
Hey!
Kosuke! Katsumi! Yu!
Shinju!
Sakura!
A map?
[engine revving]
[gasps]
[ODA]
My throat felt raw...
I couldn't breathe...
Somewhere in the distance,
I heard someone screaming.
Eventually, I realized
the reason my throat hurt
was because I was the
one who was screaming...
[STRANGER]
Why don't you write it then?
That's the only way
you can keep that story
as perfect as
you've envisioned it.
[ODA]
I can't...
[STRANGER]
Hm?
Not anymore...
I can't write a story anymore.
[ODA wails]
[ODA]
Alas, that is not the truth.
He is simply a child who happens
to be exceptionally clever.
A child, crying
in the dark, alone,
left to fend for himself
with a hole in his heart
as large as the world itself.
Now I regret not having stepped
in to ease his loneliness.
[OSAMU]
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs,
episode 16: "Bungo Stray Dogs."