[RAMPO] To think I'd receive
a challenge from the Guild.
Hopefully this'll stave
off my boredom for a bit.
[AKIKO]
Feels like a trap to me.
Looks like he wants you to
fill in the correct answers.
Afraid I can't help you there.
Wouldn't happen to have a
pen on you by any chance...?
[RAMPO]
Are you the mastermind
who issued a challenge
against me?
[POE chuckles]
It's been a long time, Rampo.
Were you able to solve
the riddle I left you
at the entrance?
Of course,
I'd expect nothing less from
you, my worthy adversary.
I believe that I've earned
myself a question.
Who are you again?
Huh?!
You... don't remember me?
The reason I joined the
Guild in the first place
was so that I could redeem
myself against you!
I am Poe!
For the past six,
grueling years of my life,
I have endured the crushing
shame of being bested
by the likes of--
Um, yeah, could you
speed this up, please?
You're boring me to sleep.
Gah! I'm setting up
the backstory here!
This is a game
between detectives.
You read the
mystery novel I've written,
and then use your skills
to determine the identity
of the serial killer.
[RAMPO]
You're already losing points.
You can't even decide if you
are a detective or a writer.
[POE]
Ooh, the plot thickens.
If you can solve my mystery,
I will reveal to you
the Guild's weakness.
The floating fortress
that is the Moby Dick
will stand no chance
against your assault.
[RAMPO]
Okay, now you've earned a point.
But why dole out such a silly
challenge in the first place?
[POE] The Guild's operations are
barbaric and unbearably dull.
There's only one
thing that humanity
ought to have a
curiosity about,
and that's your ability,
Ultra Deduction.
Am I wrong?
Nope, you're not! Yoink!
Let's do this. Heh!
Allow me to set
the scene of our story...
Once upon a time, a band of
travelers found themselves
trapped in a mansion as a
result of a fearsome snowstorm.
On this dark and stormy night,
our protagonist is awakened
by a strange sound.
Bear witness to my gift!
The ability to draw a reader
into the world of a novel!
[POE] I hope that you
both enjoy your stay.
[POE]
The protagonist opened a door
with a key only he possessed.
[POE]
And what he found there...
[RAMPO]
...was a victim.
The windows were sealed,
making it impossible for
anyone to have entered
or left in such a manner.
Two doors, and a matching key...
[RAMPO gasps]
My glasses are gone...
Is he really dead?
Everybody stand back!
I'm a doctor.
Sir!
Uh... Th... The door...
Poe stipulated that
this was a serial killer.
If we don't track
the killer down,
the rest of us may soon
become victims as well.
[AKIKO] Poe's ability is
a serious pain in the ass.
The corpse, the blood,
everything about the crime
is disgustingly convincing.
On top of that,
my healing ability doesn't
appear to work here.
Cause of death appears
to be hypovolemic shock.
I was told he was
the mansion's caretaker.
No fingerprints on the
weapon to speak of either.
It's the quintessential
impossible crime.
A locked room with no
apparent way for anyone
to go in or out of it.
How was the killer able leave
the room after the murder?
You're sitting there struggling
with all these questions.
Why don't use
your ability already?
I've lost my glasses.
They were a special pair
that the boss gave me.
I need them to in order
to activate my gift.
But what difference
does it make?
Didn't you just mention
that your healing ability
wasn't working on the guy?
Then my powers
of Ultra Deduction
probably wouldn't work
in this place either.
Uhh... So that's how
it's going to be, isn't it?
Rampo still doesn't realize
he's just an ordinary person
who doesn't actually have
any special abilities.
Then how about the two of us
investigate the crime scene
and try to piece together
what happened?
Get real, that sounds
so lame and boring!
I don't wanna do
all that tedious work!
That stuff's for suckers,
not Master Detectives like me!
Of course, I didn't off the guy.
I had nothing to do
with it either, I swear!
I wouldn't do
anything like that.
I don't even know why I'm under
suspicion in the first place.
Do any of you have an alibi?
I was still sleeping in my room.
I was gathering firewood
from the kitchen
to use in my fireplace.
I was in the library looking
up the famous curse
of this mansion,
Pluto, the one-eyed cat.
Why do I have to explain myself?
You're just a doctor.
Just who do you think you
are to question me like this?
Eek!
Huuuuuuh?
[shudders]
I was only joking,
I guess it wasn't funny.
I'll gladly tell you
where I was!
I had gone back to my room
for the night to arrange
my wardrobe for tomorrow.
[REIDA]
There was a painting of Pluto
in the room he was found in...
Was it the curse?!
The key to the
locked room was found
inside the victim's clothes,
so I bet you this is a
trick involving strings!
The single matching key was
never used until right before.
The suspect killed the
caretaker, took the key,
and locked the room
from the outside.
The killer then used a string to
pull the key under the door
and returned it to his pocket.
He cut the string, collected it,
and disposed of it.
What do you think, detective?
[RAMPO]
Are you a complete moron?
[UKAI]
Wha?
Sorry, rhetorical
questions are rude.
You are a moron.
The key's too thick to be
able to fit under the door.
Not only that, but the
corpse was on his back
and the key was
in his hip pocket.
Did none of that
even occur to you?
Uh... Well then...
what if the killer
removed the iron bars on
the window, went through it,
and used tools to put
the iron bars back again!
That'd be quite a trick
to pull off in a snowstorm
you can barely see through.
There also would've been melted
snow outside the window.
You're really on a roll,
aren't you Rampo?
[RAMPO]
I'm not!
I'm not.
[AKIKO] With your
abilities as a detective,
you must have drawn
some kind of hypothesis...
[RAMPO] I can't do any of
that if I'm not able to use
my special Ultra
Deduction ability...
I need to have the glasses
the boss gave me!
Or are you trying to say that
he lied to me about all of that?
[gsaps]
Of course not.
You're absolutely right, Rampo.
[POE laughs]
Not even you will be able
to solve this mystery.
It's a remarkably
unusual puzzle I've written
specifically for
you, my dear Rampo.
Once you're in the book,
it's all but over.
You'll never figure out who the
killer is or how they did it.
This is no mere challenge.
This is revenge!
Unlike you, I will never forget
the day when you defeated me
in a battle of wits.
I was so thoroughly humiliated
I could barely look
anyone in the eye.
I felt like I was lost
in a dark maze.
But I found a reason
to press on...
...and that was to receive
the same bountiful praise
and adulation that you did.
Maybe then I would attain
the peace of mind I craved.
[POE]
That warmth will belong to me...
...even if it means taking
it from you by force.
If I understand the
killer's MO correctly,
locking myself up in this room
will surely put me at risk
of being their next victim.
They better not
keep me waiting long.
[AKIKO moans]
[RAMPO]
Doctor Yosano...
Sorry.
It looks like I messed up.
I didn't see...
who the killer was.
[RAMPO]
Stop!
Save your strength.
[AKIKO]
I'm no help at all.
But... for the world's
greatest detective...
I'm sure it'll be... no problem.
The Armed Detective
Agency was established
with the sole purpose
of making use of your gift,
for the sake of innocent people.
[gasps]
I'm grateful... that I was
invited to the Agency...
...and met... you all...
[POE laughs]
That's one enemy down!
Unless you solve my mystery,
you will spend the rest of
eternity wandering aimlessly
through the hell-scape
that I've created!
[laughs]
Miss us?
[POE]
What?! Impossible!
You couldn't have
solved the mystery!
[RAMPO] I'll admit, it was quite
an impressive piece of work.
You just made one mistake
and that was challenging me.
[POE] Y-You actually figured
out who the killer was?
[RAMPO]
Of course.
The murderer...
...was me.
The locked room had
nothing to do with it.
The protagonist killed the
victim, and the author
deliberately omitted
that part of the narration.
The truly ingenious element
was how you managed
to conceal any evidence
of the killer's presence
once I entered the scene.
No matter how
thoroughly I searched,
it seemed like the murderer
never even existed.
How did you figure
it all out then?
[RAMPO]
You went too far
with the murder in
a locked-room theme.
It'd be one thing if you
singled someone out,
but the killer had no motive
to create such a puzzle.
That's when I figured it out:
The killer and the
author were in cahoots.
The proof of that was in the
glove used for the murder
that was hidden behind
the door under the brick wall.
The caretaker pointed to
the wall just before he died.
That may account for
the first of the killings,
but you couldn't
have found anything
that pointed toward the second.
[RAMPO] The answer
was quite simple, actually.
You made use of a special
automated contraption.
You manipulated the magnetic
properties in that room
to fire the killing weapon.
Do you really think that such
a thing is even possible?
Anything's possible.
Especially in a world
that you yourself created.
There were hints
scattered all about.
The all too pristine
medical tools...
Our cast of characters
wearing clothing
clearly provided to them.
I'd estimate this story
was set in the year 2050.
The mansion itself
is actually a rest stop
attached to a massive
elevator in space.
As convoluted as a
mystery novel may get,
once you figure out the
author's ulterior motives,
you're already halfway there.
[POE]
Damn it...!
I spent six years on this...
[RAMPO]
And your intellectual devices
were much more
beautiful this time.
I just saw through them.
Hold on.
So then you do remember
your battle against me then?
[RAMPO]
There's no way I'd ever be able
to forget about a
mystery I cracked open.
I remember it well.
It was just the two of us,
pitting one mind
against the other.
It was the first time
another detective's
ability gave me chills.
It was the last time as well.
I look forward to seeing what
you come up with for me next.
You better work
hard now, you hear me?
[POE]
I promise... I will.
[AKIKO] We'll need to hold
a celebration for you later.
[RAMPO]
What for?
[AKIKO] Our Great Detective
has finally learned the truth.
You don't actually
possess a special ability.
You simply use
your deduction to--
That's not true, I have a gift.
But you just
outsmarted Poe's trap,
and explained
everything with pure logic.
[RAMPO]
Hey I'm gifted, all right?
It wasn't anything special,
I got lucky this time is all.
It's just...
[AKIKO]
It's just what?
I'd look really stupid if I
turned out to be normal now...
[AKIKO laughs]
[RAMPO]
Hey! No laughing allowed!
[AKIKO]
Whatever you say.
[RAMPO]
Don't you patronize me!
[ATSUSHI] Is it true we have
information we can use
against the Guild?
[JUNICHIROU]
Yeah.
They're figuring out
a plan as we speak.
[OSAMU] This is some
amazing intel we've got here.
It's worth its weight in gold.
Now to figure out how
to maximize our efforts
to take out the Guild
once and for all...
Infiltrate them with a bomb?
No good.
Our comms would give us away,
and we'd be shot down.
[OSAMU]
Hmmm...
Yeah, you're right.
Well, what if we made use
of Kenji's super strength?
That would only lead to
a stalemate in a ground battle.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
How about Atsushi, then?
[RAMPO] Hmm... Paired with
Junichirou, that could work...
Excellent.
I'll get right on it.
Will we end up in the mountains?
The sea.
Roger that.
[LUCY]
Let go of me!
[STEINBECK] You've got a lot
of guts, betraying the Guild.
I actually admire your courage.
But did you really think that
we wouldn't have countermeasures
in place to deal
with your ability?
[LUCY]
I course I knew that.
But I had to convince
him that I'd be all right.
Otherwise he never would
have gotten out of there.
Look, I know it's not easy
to be one of the bad guys.
Louisa!
What's our Chief Strategist
have planned for us next?
[OSAMU]
Ango!
How're you feeling?
I've come bearing
gifts and good tidings!
The Agency has agreed
to treat your injuries in-house.
Under the care of Doctor Yosano,
you'll be as right as rain.
[ANGO]
And what do you want in return?
One of our newer recruits
was recently captured
by the military police.
We'd like to get her released
before our final battle
with the Guild.
Ah... the girl who
killed 35 people.
I'm told she's being kept
on an unmanned plane used
to quarantine dangerous gifteds.
It would be in our power to make
a plea to grant her immunity.
But we could only fulfill
that request if this girl
is truly an Agency member.
Understand?
[ATSUSHI] What do you mean
Kyouka's not a member?
Well, she's not a
member yet to be exact.
There's an entrance exam
that you have to take
to make sure you're qualified.
Unless you pass the test,
you can't be officially
accepted as an employee.
You remember yours, don't you?
[ANGO]
Very well then.
I will accept your offer
of medical treatment
in exchange for my cooperation.
But only if you tell
me one thing,
when that unidentified car
rammed into us that day,
for some reason my airbag was
the only one that didn't deploy.
Would you happen to
know anything about that?
[OSAMU chuckles]
[JUNICHIROU] The exam involves
observing the subject's behavior
to determine if they're
suitable for the Agency.
It's kept a secret
from the applicant.
[ATSUSHI]
Whenever Kyouka is in danger,
she looks for an
escape by hurting
or even killing the
person responsible.
It may just be her nature.
But if that's the case, she may
never be able to pass that exam.
[JUNICHIROU]
Okay, we're here.
Huh? A library?
[JUNICHIROU] I'm Junichirou
of the Armed Detective Agency.
[MAN]
We've been expecting you.
After you.
[JUNICHIROU] This is
our micro-assault fighter,
the Night Bird.
The plan is for me to pilot this
and deliver you
to the Moby Dick.
[ATSUSHI]
A solo infiltration?!
The Guild is in
the midst of organizing
an all-out ground assault.
You'll sneak onto the Moby Dick
while it's sparsely staffed,
and move in to take control.
Are you sure it's wise to send
me out for this mission?
[OSAMU]
For this type of job,
a gifted with combat
experience is preferable,
due to their innate ability
to work well under pressure.
You've also been held
captive aboard this ship,
so you're familiar
with its layout.
Furthermore, even if you
do fail in your mission,
there's a pretty
high probability
that you'll be captured alive.
You're the most
qualified man for the job.
Will you do it?
Turn it down.
It's too much for you.
You'll be a pathetic weakling
until the day you die.
[ATSUSHI] "...I've only ever
regretted the things
that I didn't do."
I'll do it.
[RADIO] Entering visual
range of the Moby Dick.
Understood.
You ready to go, Atsushi?
Yeah.
Special ability: Light Snow!
The sensors of the Moby Dick are
disabled for just a few seconds
while their transport
helicopter is docking.
We'll stay hidden and
close in during that time.
[TECH A] Hey, how come
the pilot isn't responding?
[TECH B]
Maybe they're having some
trouble with
their comms device.
What the...
[AKUTAGAWA coughs]
[ATSUSHI]
Dazai, I've made it inside.
[OSAMU]
How's it look in there?
[ATSUSHI]
No one's around.
Something's wrong.
[ATSUSHI]
Where is everyone?
[MELVILLE]
They've already evacuated.
Why would this be,
you might ask?
It's because we've
already reached
the final chapter of this war.
[ATSUSHI]
Wasn't this the same man
who called down the
Moby Dick in the first place?
[MELVILLE]
The Guild's next attack
will take all their enemies
down, along with this ship.
The Moby Dick will be no more.
[ATSUSHI]
Explain yourself!
[MELVILLE] No doubt you
thought it best to attack
while this ship was
sparsely populated.
But did you not suspect
there was something amiss
when the Guild's
main forces chose
to abandon this station now?
[STEINBECK] It would be terrible
if we became collateral.
It's finally time
for us to advance
to the second stage
of our operation.
The Moby Dick will act
as a huge explosive,
and annihilate Yokohama
and its accursed inhabitants.
And the area that'll
be ground zero...
...are the Agency and
Port Mafia headquarters.
[MELVILLE] This ship is set
to crash in less than an hour.
[ATSUSHI] If the Moby Dick
is your special ability,
shouldn't you be
able to stop this?!
[MELVILLE] It's understandable
that you would believe that.
However, most of
this ship's operations
have been placed outside
of my jurisdiction.
I no longer have
the ability to control it.
Did you catch all
of that, Dazai?
We need to abort the operation
and retreat immediately.
[OSAMU]
We're continuing as planned.
[ATSUSHI]
What?!
[OSAMU] You have to take control
of the Moby Dick yourself
and stop its descent.
It's up to you now.
You're the only person
who can do it.
You predicted this would
happen, didn't you?
[OSAMU] I felt it was
a distinct possibility.
That was part of our reason for
choosing you for this mission.
[ATSUSHI] What do I need to do
to stop this ship from crashing?
[MELVILLE] You'll have
to use the control terminal.
It's in the office
on the highest floor.
Though you should expect
it to be well guarded.
[FITZGERALD]
Hmm?
[ATSUSHI]
Thank you.
One more thing,
If everyone else has evacuated,
why are you still here?
[MELVILLE] If the Moby Dick
is to fall on foreign soil
and cause destruction,
I figure the least I can do
is go down along with it.
This ship was once
a beautiful creature
before its flesh
became hard and cold.
The same could be
said of the Guild.
[OSAMU]
What is it?
[OUGAI]
How are you doing, Dazai?
[OSAMU]
Hmm...
What do you want, Mori?
I thought we had
an understanding.
The Mafia agreed
not to interfere
in our current operations.
Funny you should mention that...
I just received word from
one of my subordinates.
That agreement
isn't going to hold.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Finally...
I've tracked you
down, weretiger.
Akutagawa!
[AKUTAGAWA]
What a massive disappointment.
I never thought you
were such a fool.
I could kill you
a hundred times,
and it would still feel like
I've accomplished nothing.
[ATSUSHI]
What are you talking about?
[AKUTAGAWA] Until I can
properly prove my worth
on the battlefield,
that man'll never accept me.
Damn that Dazai!
[ATSUSHI] "That man"?
He means Dazai...?! No way!
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs,
episode 23: "Rashoumon,
The Tiger and The Last Emperor."