My name is Hideo Okayama.
I'm the teacher in
charge of Class Seven,
also known as "Handa's Class".
To be frank, it's a
mixed blessing at best.
I bet he keeps the
other kids in line.
[OKAYAMA]
Some teachers are envious.
[TEACHER 9B grunting]
[OKAYAMA]
Others are, uh...
The point is,
I refuse to have my life
swayed by a single student.
For the students,
school is its own world,
so it's easy for
them to place Handa
at the center of it
in a fit of fancy.
But I have bigger problems.
No way!
What do you mean we can't
dissect frogs anymore?!
I was about to lose
the only cool part
about being a biology teacher.
This is wrong!
Don't you know how much I
look forward to this ev--
I mean how important this is?!
[croaks]
Sorry. But we've received
a great number
of complaints from parents.
Also, we always have girls
who get sick and go
to the nurse's office.
No good.
[OKAYAMA] Who cares?! They still
need to learn! It's important!
Looking at a frog's insides,
then wondering if your insides
look that icky-gooey, too.
Doesn't that excite you?
No, it's gross!
[OKAYAMA] This is hopeless.
And what a hypocrite!
He wants the students
to value their lives,
but not learn about organs?
What does he think is keeping
them alive in the first place?
[sighs]
[OKAYAMA] I just want to give
them a taste of reality!
[OKAYAMA]
Hm?
It's Handa.
Even if you're popular,
you still have the same
organs as everybody else!
Uh! Hold on. Maybe he can help!
If he gets behind
the dissection,
then all the other students
will follow suit!
[OKAYAMA]
Handa!
[HANDA]
Huh?
[AIZAWA]
Hm?
[OKAYAMA]
Mm. And, Aizawa.
Is something wrong, or...?
[clears throat]
[OKAYAMA] Boys love doing cruel
and disgusting things, right?
I'm sure they'll
see things my way!
Handa, you're looking forward
to dissecting frogs in class,
aren't you?
Uh!
I'm confused, sir.
I thought that lesson
was canceled
because we received
too many complaints.
It was.
Though I really don't
want you all to miss out
on such an important exercise.
[exhales]
[HANDA] I know my mom
was totally against it.
[HANDA'S MOM]
Nope.
It's only a few parents
that are causing the fuss.
I agree that it's a valuable
part of our study.
Uh!
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] Lately schools
have been prohibiting
anything controversial
in the name of
"protecting the children."
Aizawa!
Finally a student with
real passion for learning!
I'm so glad to have you!
[HANDA] The school already
decided. Just give it up.
[AIZAWA]
If people object to the frog,
perhaps we could dissect
a fish, instead?
[OKAYAMA] We're not making
sushi, we're learning biology.
I think we can still
fight for the frog.
[HANDA] Why do you want
to dissect frogs so badly?
Okay, here's the plan.
We'll collect signatures from
everyone who wants to do it!
With your help,
we'll be knee deep in frog
guts in no time at all!
I'm counting on you, Handa!
Wait, but I--
Ha! If those dissenters
won't bow down,
we'll teach them the
value of cooperation.
[HANDA]
Uh...
I'm done for.
I can't say no to that!
[AIZAWA]
And you call yourselves men?
The book has pictures.
Don't need to cut up a frog
to see the same thing. Right?
What if I get frog juice
on my hands? Gross.
We have to go through
with the frog dissection!
The alternative...
...is making pressed flowers
like grade school kids!
[STUDENTS]
Huh?!
[KONDO]
How is that the same at all?
[AIZAWA] We have to make our
stand now, before it's too late!
[HANDA]
No, no, no, no, no!
This is mean, and it's gross
and it's scary and just bleh.
[KONDO]
Well, I can see one person
who's not too keen on
this whole frog thing.
Actually, I'm in the
same boat. Wait!
Hey everyone. Let's see what
the class rep has to say!
Good call! Yeah! Let's
do whatever Handa says!
We should do that every time!
Well, Handa?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[KONDO]
Just tell them how you feel
and we'll be done
with this mess!
[HANDA grunts]
I bet he wants to press
flowers for his mommy.
What a wuss.
I... I think...
Go on, mister fancy man!
[STUDENTS chuckle]
I always like a walk
on the wild side!
[STUDENTS]
Whoa!
[KONDO] I don't even know
what to think anymore!
[AIZAWA]
Well, there you have it!
Thanks to you, all the guys
who were opposed to the
dissection see it our way now!
Blackmail wasn't even
necessary with you on board!
[sighs]
Now, let's deal with the girls!
Frogs are icky, why would
anyone want to do that?
The flower thing is
easier anyway.
Uh, hold on a sec.
Hey, Handa, would you
back me up here?
Tell them you don't wanna
press flowers or something!
Huh?
[HANDA] You really like making
me do all the work, don't you?
[AIZAWA]
C'mon, go!
[GIRLS gasp]
The girls said they don't
want to do it, okay?
What's wrong with flowers?
[HIROE]
Handa.
[HANDA]
Mm?
If you feel that strongly,
we'll do it. Right?
Uh-huh. Dissection is fine.
Victory!
[HANDA] Did you change your
mind just to pick on me?
What did I ever do to you?
[cries]
Now that's what you
call. "Handa Power!"
[HANDA] That is so not a thing.
Ugh, I hate this class!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[OKAYAMA] The anesthetic takes
a while to fully set in.
In the meantime,
everyone can line up
and we'll hand you a frog.
That's quite a collection
you've gathered!
Normally it's five
students per frog,
but we've got plenty
this time around!
The controversy inspired me to
catch a bunch of these guys!
Overpopulating the area made
each one of you expendable.
But thanks to Handa, now your
deaths can have meaning!
You should be grateful!
[HANDA] Laying it on a
little thick, aren't you?
Like froggy genocide
was my idea!
[OKAYAMA] They can still move
until the spinal incision,
so don't let them escape!
[GIRL 9A]
Ew, it's so slimy!
[BOY 9A]
The anesthetic isn't working!
[HANDA]
I wanna go home.
They talked me into doing
this, but now I'm not sure.
I mean, the thing's still alive.
I gave mine a name!
I bet you're cute on the inside
too, Handa Hoppylegs!
[AKIKO]
You're making this way worse!
We couldn't have done
this without you, Handa!
As thanks for your efforts,
I'll give you the biggest
frog in the whole class!
[HANDA] Even the teachers
are bullying me!
[croaks]
[HANDA]
I can't even look at the thing.
I'm about to jump out a window
and run all the way home.
[croaks]
[TSUTSUI] Sorry little dude,
but you are pretty gross.
[HANDA]
Humans truly are cruel.
[OKAYAMA chuckles] This is
what biology is all about!
It's bloody and disgusting
and maybe a little scary,
but when their fragile young
minds are exposed to death,
they'll learn to be
just a little more kind!
Aizawa, you do this stuff
at home, don't you?
[OKAYAMA]
The frog's tiny life
will nurture the
students' hearts.
I really can't thank
Handa enough.
Would a hug be inappropriate?
Uh? Uh-oh.
[croaks]
[HANDA groans]
[OKAYAMA]
Handa!
[HANDA yells]
[TSUTSUI groans]
[STUDENTS scream]
[AIZAWA]
Huh?
That's not good.
[MIYOKO] Handa Hoppylegs!
Don't leave me!
Calm down.
Uh. Death is scary, I know.
But it's okay! What's going on?
Handa, can you do
something, please?
Uh? What the...?
[STUDENTS screaming]
[MOB GIRL 9A]
Handa's dead!
[KONDO]
Oh, he is not!
Well, this sure went
downhill fast.
Quiet, let him speak.
I've reached... my ribbit.
Is that a joke? Did he
just say "ribbit?"
[TSUTSUI]
He's been possessed.
Ah! Tsutsui, you need to
go to the nurse immediately!
Quiet. Let the frog
spirit speak to us.
Uh?
I just want to go home.
As a science teacher,
I'm skeptical,
but I suppose I can
listen at least.
Let me go. This is awful.
Humans are so horrible.
[frog croaking]
[HANDA]
Why would you... do this?
It hurts. It's scary.
[IKEUCHI cries]
That poor little froggy!
What have we done to you?!
You allowed yourself
to be possessed
to teach us a lesson
in human cruelty!
No dissection. No...
Let me go. No more.
All right, then.
Let's free them.
For the frog's sake.
And for Handa's sake, too.
Uh, sure.
But I really think you and Handa
need to get the nurse's office
before we do anything else.
[TSUTSUI] We've been
relying on Handa too much.
How many times has his wisdom
saved us from ourselves?
[FROGS croaking]
[REO] I think we just wanted
someone else to decide for us.
[AIZAWA] We were going to kill
all those frogs for nothing.
Just because we weren't willing
to think for ourselves.
[OKAYAMA] Aw... But I went to
so much trouble to catch them!
Just checking, but are you sure
it's okay to release them,
like ecosystem-wise?
Seeing how cruel and
disgusting people can act,
I realize we should all try
to be just a little more kind.
[gasps]
Uh! Hey, look!
A four-leaf clover! Ha, ha!
Wow, really? Maybe we can
press those flowers after all!
[AIZAWA sighs]
C'mon! You wouldn't want
to miss out, Yuki!
[KONDO]
Yeah, sure, all right.
[OKAYAMA]
I can't believe it.
The students, the frogs and the
flowers, in perfect harmony.
I didn't have to harm animals.
I didn't have to
show them ugliness.
They learned to be
kind on their own.
I see now... the true
extent of Handa Power.
[croaks]
[OKAYAMA]
No, I shouldn't dwell on it.
I can't be swept away
by the Handa tidal wave
like everyone else in the class.
As their teacher and
as a biology enthusiast,
I must simply observe
with fascination.
In the end,
being Handa's homeroom teacher
is a blessing after all.
[KONDO]
Huh?
[KAWAFUJI] Meanwhile,
in the nurse's office...
[sighs]
[frog croaking]
[HANDA muffled groans]
[KAWAFUJI]
One frog takes revenge.
[AIZAWA]
As leader of the Handa Force,
I can't ignore my duties.
And today, my duty
is to watch Handa.
[gasps]
[HANDA grunts]
Ah! You're running away?
But why...?
[AIZAWA panting]
[AIZAWA]
He's done this before...
Like he's trying to
escape from something.
Or maybe someone!
[TSUTSUI] What?! You think
Handa has a stalker?!
[AIZAWA] We've been thorough
in our daily observations.
I don't know how this happened!
[TSUTSUI]
We let him down!
[REO]
Ah, now I see.
So he's been taking
all these weird routes
to get away from the stalker!
[AIZAWA] And when he suddenly
starts running and disappears,
it's because he's
hiding from them!
Who would do this?
Give poor Handa his privacy,
you twisted monster!
[KONDO]
Anybody notice the irony here?
No? Nobody?
[crash]
[gasps]
This is exactly why
the Handa Force is here!
We will protect him from
that stalker at any cost!
Well! Looks like I'm
finally useful.
Now we can give back to Handa
after all he's done for us.
In that case, let's start
talking strategy!
Super glad you're
on board, pal!
[KONDO]
Oh, yeah, totally.
[KONDO] This is going to be a
disaster from beginning to end.
[AIZAWA]
According to my observations,
Handa uses one of two different
routes to escape the stalker
when he's going home.
Let's split up. I'll cover
one route with Yuki.
Reo and Tsutsui can
take the other.
[TSUTSUI]
When I get a hold of them,
I'm gonna smash their teeth in
and make them eat them
like candy corn!
[REO]
That's really specific!
[KONDO] They're so invested.
I didn't have time to complain!
[AIZAWA]
It's him!
Lay low, lay low...
If we wanna protect
him from the stalker,
why don't we just
walk next to him
like any normal friend would--
Blasphemy!
Does your arrogance know
no bounds, you fool?
The Handa Force does not aspire
to be equals with Handa.
Our duty is to support
him from the shadows!
[KONDO]
Hey, it's your life, man.
On a different note,
you really jump to the
name-calling fast, don't you?
[AIZAWA]
Hm?
[KONDO gasps]
[AIZAWA]
Who's there? Come out!
[KONDO]
The stalker!
[KONDO gasps]
[VOICE 1A]
Eraser!
Oh, it's just Miyoko,
nothing shady going on here.
Are you kidding me?! She's
the definition of "shady!"
Uh? No, look, she's harmless.
[KONDO] Oh, come on!
She's got the crazy eyes!
What is she doing now?!
If Handa has a stalker,
it's definitely her!
Like the Handa Force, she
understands boundaries.
Let's just say she
keeps some of the more
"problematic" fans in line.
What?
[AIZAWA] If someone seeks
special attention from Handa,
she drags them back
into the shadows.
Thus her nickname, "Eraser!"
[VOICE 1A]
Eraser!
Where did all this come from?
She was just a normal girl.
I guess Handa isn't
taking this path today.
Hey, look. Isn't
that the bookworm?
[laughs] If Handa won't
come to the library,
I'll bring the library to him.
And if I give him the book
personally, he can't say no.
[laughs]
[MIYOKO grunts]
[KASUMI gasping]
[VOICE 1A]
Eraser!
Why?! She's just a librarian!
She tried to put herself
above the other fans.
That's asking to be erased.
[REO] Handa's not coming,
let's get out of here.
[TSUTSUI gasps]
Is something going on?
Yeah, I think someone
was watching us!
[REO]
Huh?
It's gotta be the stalker!
[KONDO] By the way, Aizawa, do
you even know where Handa lives?
No. I've followed him
around the area,
but I've never been all
the way to his house before.
Couldn't you just look
in the school database?
[AIZAWA]
Unbelievable!
[HANDA] Damn it.
What's with everyone
following me today?
If a bunch of weirdos
come to my house,
it's gonna freak my mom out.
Mom aside, I'm supposed to
meet with Kawafuji today.
I'd better make a break for it.
[AIZAWA, KONDO]
Uh?
[HANDA grunts]
[KONDO] Why'd he start
running all of a sudden?!
[AIZAWA] Clearly, it's because
the stalker is nearby.
Actually. It's us. Isn't it?
Anyway, Handa sure is fast, huh?
We have a secret weapon
just for the occasion.
[HIGASHINO yelling]
The race is on! Let's go!
[AIZAWA] We can follow
Dash on the Dash Radar
and if he sticks close to Handa,
we'll find out where he lives.
Were you just trying to find
his house this whole time?
All it takes is one
conceited idiot like you
to completely ruin the entire
Handa fan equilibrium.
Your life isn't some
sappy romance novel
and you're sure as hell not
Handa's special princess.
[KASUMI]
But he fixed the library for me.
If that's not love, then--
I will go for the... kill!
[KASUMI groaning]
[KONDO]
Nope. I didn't see a thing.
Whoever this stalker is,
they're one sneaky bastard.
I'm sure they went this way!
How do you know the
person watching us
was the stalker, though?
The really bad dudes
always have this dark aura
you can just feel.
Whoever this stalker may be,
they're a force of true evil.
That sounds like someone we
should be running away from,
not chasing.
[gasps]
See something?
There! Look!
[REO]
Wait!
We've got you now, stalker!
I don't see them.
[gasps]
[REO whimpers]
--[dog growling]
--[REO, TSUTSUI whimper]
[BOTH yelp]
[REO]
What the heck is going on here?!
Come back here and
fight me! Hey!
[dog growling]
Oh, no!
[REO, TSUTSUI scream]
Josephine!
You awful dog, why do you
keep running from mommy?
[TSUTSUI, REO screaming]
[DOG OWNER 6A]
Uh! Josephine!
[REO]
Save me, Tsu-Tsu!
[TEO, TSUTSUI screaming]
Screaming? Why is there so
much screaming everywhere?
[AIZAWA]
Huh?
--[HIGASHINO] Handa!
--[AIZAWA] It's Dash...
Did you find him?
[Well, I was running fast
enough to catch up to him.
[panting] But then Handa
took a sudden turn.
And frankly, I'm not
too good with those.
You lost him?
He can't help it.
Let's not murder anyone.
[REO]
Aizawa!
[ALL]
Hm?
[HIGASHINO] What the heck
happened to you two?
[REO] Tsu-tsu protected me
with his life!
[KONDO]
From what?! A dragon?!
Handa's in some real trouble.
[REO]
We ran into the stalker.
What?!
[MIYOKO] I think I know
who you're talking about.
[ALL gasp]
[AIZAWA]
Eraser!
[KONDO]
What's the story with them?!
I've sensed an evil presence
lurking around Handa
several times now.
Naturally, I've tried
to hunt it down,
but somehow it manages
to escape me every time.
That's creepy.
I told you it's bad--
even Eraser agrees.
So, that's just what
we're calling her now?
We will hunt you down
and we will destroy you,
whoever you are!
Count me in!
And me too.
[AIZAWA] Victory will be ours.
In the name of the Handa Force!
And in the name of Eraser!
[VOICE 1A]
Eraser!
Also, in the name
of Handa Disease!
[VOICE 1A]
Handa Disease!
[KONDO]
Oh, yikes.
[HANDA panting]
[HANDA]
I think I finally lost them.
This day couldn't get any worse.
[HANDA]
The café is right there.
I just have to get
over this wall.
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
[HIGASHINO slobbers]
[HANDA]
Uh, uh...
[AIZAWA]
Handa. But why...?
He's the picture of divinity.
How can we possibly respond?
[AIZAWA]
Maybe not that divine!
Perhaps he's here to
grace us with his wisdom?
[HANDA]
What do you want?
How did you know
I was coming here?
[HANDA]
The goal is so close.
Kawafuji's waiting for me.
I'm always making him suffer
because I'm too much of a coward
to do anything about this.
Wait. What am I so afraid of?
They're the ones
causing me trouble.
I shouldn't have
to run from them!
They're just bullies!
[KONDO]
Weirdo.
[AIZAWA] Why are you standing
on a wall, you moron?
[TSUTSUI]
I wanna punch him.
[REO]
He's so lame.
[MIYOKO]
I dropped my contact.
[KASUMI]
Me too.
[HIGASHINO retches]
[HANDA] You're selfish.
And you're cruel.
And I'm not taking this anymore!
[HANDA]
I've had enough of you!
What the hell are you even
thinking? Stop following me!
What did I do to deserve
this, huh?! What?!
We've done it now.
[HANDA] You're going to ruin
the only friendship I've got!
Go away! Don't ever
come near me again!
Got it?
[REO, AIZAWA]
Handa!
[footsteps]
[KONDO]
He's never said his feelings
straight to our faces
like that before.
I guess this is a good thing?
That was intense.
He's really angry, isn't he?
[KONDO] I wonder what
everyone's thinking right now.
Are they finally aware
of how much trouble
they've been causing him?
It's pretty clear, isn't it?
[AIZAWA laughing]
What's so funny?
Did you hear that, stalker?!
We know you're here,
you little cockroach!
That was a declaration of war
straight from Handa's mouth!
You can run, but you can't hide!
[KONDO]
Aizawa, would you listen?
[TSUTSUI] What an honor!
What at honor to hear his words!
He said that he doesn't
want the stalker
to ruin our friendship!
You just hear what you want to.
We will never leave his side!
If you dare to oppose
Handa, you stalker,
you will face our wrath!
Not to mention, my wrath!
I'm wrathful!
[AIZAWA]
Mm!
Until the day that Handa can
go home in peace, we fight!
Uh. Guys? No...
[REO] What are you doing, Yuki?
C'mon get your butt over here!
[KONDO]
Ugh, fine.
[ALL] Ready? Handa's
Handa Force... Go!
[KONDO]
I'm sorry, Handa.
They're never gonna get it.
You're doomed.
[bell jingles]
[HANDA]
Sorry I kept you waiting!
There were a bunch of jerks
from school following me today.
[KAWAFUJI]
You're gonna have to run faster!
[HANDA]
Why are you covered in dirt?
Oh, yeah.
I was playing with a
dog on the way here
and I didn't have
time to clean up.
Seems like a lot of dogs
around these days.
Oh, but listen,
I finally told off those jerks
that have been stalking me!
[KAWAFUJI] Really? We'll
see how that works out.
[HANDA]
Huh? What does that mean?
[HANDA] Have you ever
had alcohol before?
Not yet.
But I'll be throwin' back
champagne and tequila,
all that stuff, just as
soon as I'm old enough!
[KAWAFUJI]
Why yes...
[HANDA]
Man, Kawafuji's so cool.
[HANDA, KAWAFUJI]
Cheers!
Here's to you, pal,
happy birthday!
Hell yeah! I can finally
get my booze on!
Uh-oh. Um... Hello?
[KAWAFUJI]
Next time, this stuff! [laughs]