[CROWD chattering]
[PSYCHO] Get your
bishoujo fix right here!
[TAKOYAKI] Our Handa- chan
special edition, now on sale!
[gasps] Can I... help you?
[RAI] What's this crap?
A comic book? How much?
It's only 500 yen.
[BROW-BOY] I thought you
only read manly comics.
[RAI]
I just wanna see it.
[NEO]
Uh. Thank you.
I got a bad feeling
about those guys.
Maybe, but they've got
good taste in manga.
You didn't notice
their uniforms?
Look close! They're from
Kuro High! The thug school!
Pretty cute.
[CROWD chattering]
Glad we finally get
to take a breather.
So Old King Lear's
wearing down already, huh?
It's a good excuse to see
the rest of the festival.
Remember, our next
performance is at 1:30.
Acting isn't all
fame and fortune.
[AIZAWA] Let's check out
Fake Handa's booth
while we have the chance.
Oh, good idea!
Then when we do the play again,
the whole cast can be Handa!
[3RD YEAR 12A]
Handa Force!
[ALL gasp]
[3RD YEAR 12A groans]
Got bad news.
What?! Wait, who are you?
We're the basketball club,
only we don't play basketball
'cause we're all punks.
Ignore him. That's not
the issue here. It's Kuro.
What?!
Kuro High?
They're walking around
like the own the place.
They sent some of their
tough street thugs.
I think they're after Handa.
So, you tried to kick
them out of here,
but then they beat
you up, I take it?
Oh, 'cause of the blood?
No, actually, we were trying
to look up girls' skirts
and got caught in the act.
[GIRL 4B]
Carnivore Punch!
[GIRL 4A]
Meat Kick!
[3RD YEAR 12B] I blame the
infectious festival atmosphere.
[AIZAWA]
In any case,
we need to stop those thugs
before they get to our queen.
I mean, Handa!
[ALL]
Handa's Handa Force, go!
[GIRL 12A screams]
It's Kuro High!
[GIRL 12B]
No! They're savages! Beasts!
Damn it. Is there anyone with
a spine in this whole school?
We're just askin'
where to find Handa.
They don't have to
scream and run away.
Huh? Hey, it's him!
[HANADA]
Heh.
[RAI]
Wait a sec.
Real funny!
You did that on purpose,
huh? Where's Handa?
He's right here. A whole
bunch of him... somehow.
[BROW-BOY]
What's up with this school?
[SHAVE]
Creepy!
Impeccable work,
wouldn't you say?
Thanks to my genius,
soon the entire world
will be covered in Handas!
[laughs]
[RAI] Okay, but maybe just...
close your mouth first.
Where's the real one?
[HANADA whimpers]
Never! I have sworn my
allegiance to Handa!
Even if I die...
...I will take the secret of his
location to the grave with me!
Do what you like,
but you'll never know!
Hey, pal! Let's head to
Class Seven to see Handa!
[cries]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[RAI]
Cool. Class Seven. Thanks, man.
Ahh! You've ruined
everything, Higashino!
--[HIGASHINO] Huh? I what?
--Handa's gonna die
--and it's all your fault!
Took long enough,
but his classroom should
be right down the hall.
[TSUGUMI] You will soon be met
with a terrible misfortune.
[BOYS]
Huh?
Say what?
All right, creeper,
what do you want?
[TSUGUMI]
You're doomed.
I don't buy that crap.
And I'm fine, thank you.
I can see the shroud
of death around you.
That's not even a thing!
Just give it a rest!
Justice will rain from the
heavens, bringing... ruin.
I can't hear you, creepy
girl! La-la-la-la!
Don't worry, Rai,
we can take you to an exorcist
when we're done here!
[TSUGUMI]
Wait, come back!
You have to listen all
the way through to the end!
[SHAVE]
We're going the wrong way!
[MIYOKO] Students from another
school were looking for Handa?
It looks like they're a
small group of delinquents
from Kuro High School.
Oh yeah?
Let's erase them.
Now there's a good idea.
You never can be too careful.
[OKAYAMA]
I didn't hear a thing. Nope.
I can't find those guys
from Kuro or Handa.
Yeah. Same.
What a mess!
So much for enjoying
the festival, huh guys?
Uh-huh.
[HANADA]
Bad news.
Did you run into Kuro High?
Yeah, they said they
were looking for Handa
and then Dash ratted him out!
I just... said his homeroom
number, that's all.
What?! We have to get to
Class Seven right away!
You want some bishoujo ,
we got it!
Don't break Handa- chan 's
little heart!
Hi there.
[JOMOTO] Yeah, hey. Uh,
how many do we need?
[NAGAMASA] One for every
person in our class, so 30.
[ALL gasp]
[KOMICHI]
We'd better hurry.
[KOJIKA]
Carry mine for me.
[JOMOTO]
Fine.
Thanks so much!
[ALL squeal]
Handa- chan love is alive!
I didn't think her influence
would spread quite so quickly.
Wow, what an honor.
Yeah, and those weren't just
nobodies who bought it either!
Didn't you see?
That's Shiro High's
Ichimiya Force!
Is everybody ready? Say--
Ichi-eese!
Thank you!
What a nice way to
commemorate our visit.
They've got spirit.
All courtesy of Handa's
influence, no doubt.
Eat this! Right in the eye!
[BOY 12B] Are you ready?
Check this out!
I hope our festival
turns out this fun.
According to this,
Handa's class is doing
a Romeo and Juliet Café.
[HANDA sighs] The afternoon
show'll be starting soon.
Seems like everyone's
enjoying themselves.
Except me, of course.
It's not that I have a problem
playing Queen Elizabeth.
Really, I'm happy they
gave someone like me
such an important
role in the play.
Maybe I feel empty
because I'm here,
but I'm not really involved
with the rest of the cast.
In fact, it's just
like class, isn't it?
I'm silently sitting in a
chair while everyone else
does stuff together.
All right, then.
Maybe I'll try saying
my line this time.
That's really gonna mess
everyone up though, isn't it?
They might get mad.
No, I don't care!
It's my last chance!
I wanna show them
what I can do.
Whether it's awkward or not!
[door opens]
[RAI]
All right, guess this is it.
[gasps]
Hey! Anybody in here?
This is Class Seven;
you think they tricked us?
[SHAVE]
Nah. They didn't seem too smart.
[HANDA]
The customers are here already?
My cue is a knock on the wall.
I'll say my line then.
Just calm down and
wait for the knock.
They should be
back soon enough.
Are you sure this is how
you wanna do this, Rai?
It doesn't feel right
putting our leader
out on the front line.
Nah, man. This is the only way.
This high school has the entire
area in the palm of its hand.
We lost a lot of our old turf
when that Tsutsui guy showed up.
But Handa is the
real mastermind.
We gotta do this...
[HANDA]
They knock, then I say my line.
[door opens]
[ALL]
Hm?
[ICHIMIYA]
How odd. Did I miss the memo,
or do all low-class goons attend
theater productions these days?
Shiro High, huh?
[footsteps]
[REO] Those guys from
Shiro are here, too!
[AIZAWA]
This could get messy!
I don't know their intentions,
but they don't get along
with Kuro either!
Your accessories are ruining
your credibility here.
If we don't stop them,
this could be a three-way
standoff with Handa!
You brought your whole gang
here to disrupt the festival,
because you're afraid of a
single student that goes here?
Some people have
no manners at all.
Yeah?
Like the spoiled rich boy
throwin' his weight around?
'Cause I sure as hell didn't
ask for a lecture from you.
How dare you speak
to him that way!
We're not here to fight.
Since Handa is involved,
if we cause a ruckus,
it may reflect poorly on him.
It's not like I'm
arguing with you,
but you're kind of turning into
Aizawa junior these days.
[JOMOTO grunts]
Fighting is bad?
Ask that before you
start throwing punches!
I feel like we've seen
this scenario before.
[JOMOTO] I just did
what Tsutsui would do.
Wait, I forgot, now
what did they do next?
Ugh, they ran away!
Oh no, you don't!
[gasps]
[RAI]
You just dug your own graves.
Handa may be a worthy rival,
but you're nothin' but a
bunch of spoiled rich brats.
Ha, ha! Oh, you think so?
Then I'm gonna give you the best
ass-kicking money can buy!
[HANDA]
They knock, then I say my line.
[grunting]
East this!
[ALL grunting]
[screaming]
[HANDA]
They knock, then I say my line.
They knock,
then I say my line...
Just wait for the knock.
[yelps]
Cease your fighting immediately!
So says your ruler!
[HANDA]
I came out too soon.
[BROW-BOY grunts]
[KOJIKA]
Handa?
[JOMOTO]
Uh...
Does that mean he was
listening this entire time?
We should all be
ashamed of ourselves.
We nearly ruined their school
festival by hurling insults
and fighting like children.
Truth is... we didn't
come here to brawl,
we came here to
surrender to Handa.
Surrender?!
[SHAVE]
Ever since he showed up,
our school's gotten
weaker and weaker.
We used to have pride in our
thuggery, but what are we now?
[BROW-BOY]
If we can't rule the streets,
then we might as well
live in peace.
Of course, we had to find a way
to meet with Handa first.
We didn't want trouble.
It all makes sense now.
This must have been
a difficult decision
for a school that prides
itself on strength.
Thugs have a code
as well, I suppose.
I respect your humility,
and your desire to protect
your school, as well...
...King of Kuro.
[ALL]
Uh?
[FEMALE VOICE 12A screams]
[ALL gasping]
[ALL]
He's... dead?
[KAWAFUJI] And so, with Handa's
unintentionally poignant words,
the long-standing rivalry
between Shiro and Kuro High
was brought to an end.
[RIKIMARU] Although I'm sure
it passed in a flash,
our school festival
is coming to an end.
The student council extends
its heartfelt gratitude
for the efforts you poured
into today's event,
and for the priceless memories
that you helped create.
Please enjoy the finale
of the Handa--
I mean, the Seishu Festival.
[AIZAWA]
Time for the bonfire, huh?
Looks like it'll
be big this time.
Watch me bust a move
at the folk dance!
No question. Our café was
the highlight of the festival.
I dunno.
Class One's calligraphy event
went over pretty well, too.
Yeah, but Handa's
the only reason
anyone gives a damn
about calligraphy.
My makeovers were
a big hit, too!
[KONDO]
Hm?
[HANADA] Like parting the
Red Sea. Every single time.
[microphone squealing]
Good evening.
You've all done well.
Thank you again
for your hard work.
I truly believe that this event
will be remembered for
many years to come.
You may have heard
of a violent incident
that some outside students
were involved in...
[HANDA]
Wow. I'm glad I missed that!
All right, I'm sure you're all
sick of these formalities.
Relax! Catch up with the other
classes, and have fun!
[STUDENTS cheering]
Just go, Juri, don't be shy!
Cut it out, I'll say something
when I'm ready, okay?
--[[HANDA] Mm?
--[ALL gasp]
[HANDA] Is there something
I'm missing here?
[HASEGAWA]
That's crazy!
[HANDA] It's Kawafuji.
Surrounded by friends, as usual.
[KAWAFUJI]
Hm?
[HANDA]
He noticed me.
[KAWAFUJI]
Hmph.
[HANDA]
What's he smiling about?
If people see him doing that,
they'll find out we're friends!
[RIKIMARU]
We will now announce the winner
of the Seishu Festival's
Best Presentation award.
The crown will be given
to the representative
of the winning class.
[HANDA]
I forgot about that.
At last, we shall claim
our well-earned victory!
[RIKIMARU] Now, unveil the
crown, fit for a true king!
[STUDENTS]
Ooh!
[KONDO] That's not a
crown, it's a helmet!
[REO, TSUTSUI, AIZAWA]
Totally.
[TSUTSUI]
Why do I get the feeling
we have her to blame for that?
[SAWAKO]
Don't worry...
[REO] She knows how to take
charge. I'll give her that much.
A little weird, but
Handa can pull it off.
This is my time
to shine. Finally!
[RIKIMARU]
First, our runners up.
Who sold all 5,000 copies
of their self-published
manga in one day.
The Bishoujo Pictures Club!
--[PSYCHO] Thank you Handa-chan!
--[TAKOYAKI] Manga power!
[RIKIMARU]
The student council president
will present their crown to the
chief of club, Neo Sakurame.
You bring glory to our school.
Please accept this cardboard
crown with pride!
[NEO]
I am honored, milady.
[ALL] I mean, at least it's
a crown. That's something.
[TAKOYAKI]
We don't have disband after all!
[NEO]
We did it, we really did it!
[AIZAWA] Heh. In the
history of the world,
I don't know if anyone has
ever been this excited
about a cardboard crown.
[RIKIMARU]
All proceeds from their sales
will be donated to the school.
And now the award for the
best class presentation.
The winner of this
year's festival is...
[drums play]
[yelling]
[RIKIMARU]
...year two, Class Seven,
for their Romeo and Juliet Café!
Would the class rep please
come to the stage?
[HANDA]
Huh...?
[STUDENTS]
Yep. No surprise there.
[HANDA]
What?! No! I can't believe it!
[RIKIMARU] Class Seven's café
had students lining up to enter
and the adlibbed dialogue
from Queen Elizabeth
really kept the audience
on their feet.
Do something!
[AIZAWA] You're the star, Handa!
Show 'em what you've got!
Which is what?!
[STUDENTS]
Handa! Handa!
Handa! Handa! Handa! Handa...
[HANDA]
It's a nightmare.
I know how this ends.
They call someone
they hate to the stage,
then humiliate them in horrible
ways in front of everyone!
How do I get through this
with my dignity intact?
[SAWAKO] Sei Handa of
year two, Class Seven,
you showed the school
amazing creativity.
It brought a breath of
fresh air to this festival.
Therefore. I will bestow--
[KAWAFUJI]
Hold up a second!
[gasps]
I've got a favor to ask.
[HANDA]
Kawafuji?
Ugh. Let's hear it then.
[HANDA]
What is happening?
Well, our calligraphy event
was pretty awesome and all,
so I was hoping you guys
would give me the crown.
How dare you defy the judgement
of the student council!
This crown belongs
to Handa alone!
[HANDA] I didn't know he
wanted the helmet so bad.
Now I feel awful for having it.
I see. I guess there's no
arguing with that, then.
Oh, I have an idea!
Just lend it to me.
Since we're friends.
[STUDENTS groaning]
[HANDA]
No! We gotta keep this a secret!
I don't care about the helmet.
But it's gonna be a disaster if
people find out we're friends!
We've known each other
forever, don't be so cold!
We're best buds!
Get your hands off of him!
Who are you?!
[REO]
This isn't funny!
Shut up!
Don't you dare talk
that way to Kawafuji!
If someone other than
Handa gets the crown,
then it's gotta be me!
[HANDA FAKES]
Yeah, and us!
[STUDENT 12C]
Keep, dreaming!
You think you deserve
it more than us,
just 'cause you
have Handa's face?
[BOY STUDENT 12D]
I want it!
[BOY STUDENT 12G]
Why you--
[STUDENTS yelling]
Calm down! Handa is
still the winner!
Everyone, shut yet traps!
That punk up there is lying!
Get him off the stage!
They're not friends!
Handa would never give
the crown to that monster!
[STUDENTS shouting]
Stop it! You don't want
to hit Handa, do you?
[gasps]
Ah!
[HANDA]
Uh! Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But this situation is no good.
Just give me the helmet
and get out of here,
everything'll be fine.
I can't!
After what you said,
that'd be like telling the
whole school we're friends!
With the way things are, don't
you know how they'd treat you?
You deserve better than that!
Heh. "The way things are," huh?
I think you need to
take a closer look.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[JURI]
Handa! Don't give up! You won!
[IKEUCHI]
You earned that victory, Handa!
[HANDA FAKES]
We love you!
[HIGASHINO gags]
[STUDENTS cheer]
[ALL]
Handa- chan !
I'm... looking, but I
still don't get it.
I admit, it's a strange
phenomenon to digest.
The bottom line is our
classmates don't dislike you.
In fact, you're a star.
There's nothing you
could do that would
make these people hate you.
So why don't you give me that
stupid helmet already.
And leave the stage in style.
But I--
Let 'em throw crap at me.
I don't care. C'mon.
[HANDA grunts]
[BOY STUDENT 12J]
Get off the stage, stupid!
[GIRL STUDENT 12C]
Stop picking on Handa!
[BOY STUDENT 12K]
The crown belongs to him!
[HANDA]
Really, this shouldn't be mine.
Handa?
Don't let that
jackass bully you!
It's not Kawafuji's, either.
[HANDA]
Everyone here worked together.
Therefore, this honor belongs
to the entire school!
[STUDENTS gasping]
It isn't fair to make
this a competition.
We poured our hearts
into the festival.
We all did our best
to make it great.
This is our victory.
That's why... I won't
claim this for myself.
[STUDENTS murmur]
I see.
The festival is Handa.
It's all so clear now.
Listen to the message that
Handa is imparting to us!
He belongs to everyone equally!
We're all his best friend!
Huh? Wait. What does that mean?
That's not--
[SAWAKO chuckles]
By sharing this honor, your
glory has become greater still.
Your words ignited the
hearts of the people.
And now... the grand finale!
[STUDENTS gasping]
That's gotta be the biggest
Handa I've ever seen!
[TAKOYAKI]
It's like a parade float!
I special ordered this
because I had confidence
in Handa's victory,
but it would have been
awkward if he lost.
This level of obsession is
exactly what I expect from you!
[STUDENTS cheering]
This felt positive at first, but
now it's getting kind of weird.
Uh, yeah. No kidding.
But even if they show
it in a creepy way,
the point is that
everyone likes you.
[STUDENTS]
Honda! Honda!
I guess so, but...
...weren't you the one who
said they all hated me?
Did I? I don't remember that.
Well, I do!
In fact, it kind of
wrecked my whole life!
Oh, yeah? [laughs]
[AIZAWA] Handa! Why don't
you ride on the float?
Huh? But why?
Because you're the star!
Try it out!
It'll be fun!
Yeah, come on!
We're waiting!
You-- [coughs]
[ALL]
Handa- chan !
Kawafuji!
Might as well. Let's go.
--[REO] Yes! Ha, ha!
--[TSUTSUI laughs]
Here, we'll help you climb on.
How's this gonna work?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENTS scream]
If I was on that,
I'd be dead right now.
I mean, sure, but let's
not think of it that way.
It's beautiful! Don't you think?
Huh?!
Oh, man. I can feel his warmth.
I can see his light!
[HANDA]
Uh?
He's like a god of fire.
Huh?!
[KAWAFUJI laughs]
Well... that's okay.
[HANDA] They can see it
however they like.
[NEWSCASTER 12A]
A fire broke out
at a local school
festival last night.
But despite the large number
of students in the area,
no injuries were reported.
[HANDA gasps]
Hey.
Whoa, what are you doing here?
Can't we let all this
cool down a bit first?
I mean, what if
someone else sees you?
Why don't you ask her?
Uh!
So, how am I
supposed to act now?
[KAWAFUJI]
Hm? What d'you mean?
I just...
I don't really know what
the rules are anymore.
[KAWAFUJI]
Just be yourself.
Break down that wall the
same way you did last night.
That's enough to
change the world.
Hey, good morning, Handa!
Good morning, Handa!
Lovely day, isn't it?
Hey Handa, good morning!
[HIGASHINO]
Hand-- [gags]
[TAKOYAKI]
Morning, Handa!
[HANADA]
Morning!
[PSYCHO]
[MAIKO]
Hi, Handa!
[OOTANI]
Good morning!
--[ISHIDA] Hey, what's up?
--[HASEGAWA] Hey, Handa!
[OKAYAMA]
How's it goin', Handa?
[JURI]
Good morning Handa!
[HANDA chuckles]
Morning.