No, just go. You'll probably
have a good time.
I can't.
C'mon, this is a
good opportunity
for you to make friends.
Well, I guess I could try.
[CROWD chattering]
[KOMICHI] I'm what you
call a regular teenager.
Average in grades
and average in sports.
[KOMICHI]
But that's okay.
I may not be anything special,
but that doesn't mean I
don't know someone who is.
The person that
captivates my mind...
The king of the school...
[KOJIKA]
What should we do?
[KOMICHI]
...Asahi Ichimiya!
The answer to that is obvious.
We should go on our school trip
and have ourselves a good time.
[NAGAMASA]
That's Ichimiya for you!
[JYOMOTO] No one's as cool as
him. Not even that Handa guy.
Handa?
[TSUTSUI sighs]
I can't believe we gotta travel
with those Shiro High punks.
[REO] Chill. This trip's
supposed to be fun,
so just relax.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess
you're right about that.
Hey, everybody! Take one
and pass it around!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[HANDA]
This is awkward!
I know they hate me, so maybe
I shouldn't take one.
But if I don't, then it's
like I'm punking them.
Maybe it won't come to me.
[MIYOKO whimpers]
Handa. Something sweet?
[HANDA]
It's here!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[HANDA] I knew it! I wasn't
supposed to take one!
Oh well. At this point, I'm
screwed whether I eat it or not.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[AIZAWA]
Uh.
Reo!
[BOY STUDENT 8A]
I'd have brought candy, too,
if I knew he'd eat it!
[HANDA] I didn't expect
them to get this mad.
[STUDENTS]
He spit it out!
Hey! You guys lookin' for
a way off this train?
Hey, don't start
trouble, Tsu-Tsu!
What are you, the
'big man on campus'?
Man, that sad excuse
of a comeback
was as old fashioned
as your hair cut!
[JYOMOTO]
Says the guy with a ponytail!
[HANDA] I'd better
get rid of this candy.
Now where did I put
that wrapper? Ah-ha!
[TSUTSUI]
Uh!
What the heck...? Uh!
Wow. Would you look
at that scenery...
[gasps]
So, you think it's funny
getting your trash stuck
in my hair, do ya?
[HANDA whimpers]
[ICHIMIYA ]
That's enough, Jyomoto.
Right.
Forgive my acquaintance.
This was a mistake.
As a Shiro High student...
...I, Ichimiya, apologize.
[STUDENTS gasping, giggling]
Well, if you'll excuse us.
[TSUTSUI]
That guy with the white hair.
What in the world is his deal?
He's the "king" of their high
school, if I'm not mistaken.
[STATION ANNOUNCER 8A]
Now arriving in Kyoto.
[OKAYAMA] All right, class,
you're free to do as you please.
Just remember to be back
by the designated time.
[STUDENTS]
Okay.
[REO] Hey, guys! Let's see
if love's in our fortunes!
[KONDO groans]
[REO]
What do you say, Handa?
[HANDA]
Uh!
It seems like a complete waste
to spend my allowance
on something like this.
It's practically gambling.
But that's where I'm
at right now anyway.
Betting it all that this
might help me make friends.
'Kay! Here I go, guys!
Dun-Dun-Dun!
It says "Ask again later"?!
Mine's "Outlook is Good."
Yeah, so is mine.
"Most likely."
So, how 'bout yours?
It's gotta say "Yes,
definitely." Right?
As if there's anything
else it could be!
Well, you never know, it
could say "Very Doubtful"!
[HANDA]
This is way too much pressure.
[NAGAMASA]
"Reply is Hazy."
[gasps]
[ALL]
Shiro High!
Well, well, well, if it isn't
the losers from Hai High.
We all wanted to see how our
fortunes stacked up, too.
Are you ready, Ichimiya?
[REO] Oh, the "leader"
has to go first, huh?
[NAGAMASA]
You misunderstand.
He's about to draw
all of our fortunes.
[KOMICHI]
And that's because...
...Ichimiya is indisputably
loved by the gods!
[ALL]
There's no way!
[KONDO] That was amazing, but it
kind of takes the fun out of it.
[JYOMOTO]
There, you see?
Nothing "hazy" about that,
unlike the hack you follow!
Why, you...!
That's it, I'm getting a
"Yes, definitely" right now!
Me, too!
[KOJIKA laughs]
Don't make me laugh.
You had your chance!
It's not like you're going
to get better results.
No matter how much you try.
[TSUTSUI]
This isn't about our fortunes!
You jerks laughed
at Handa's results.
But he doesn't need luck
'cause he has us!
What? That doesn't make sense.
Ah. He's got some
loyal subjects, huh?
[HANDA] Please bring me
good luck in the future.
[ICHIMIYA]
Handa.
[HANDA]
Uh. Yeah?
Can you believe this drama?
Over some silly fortunes.
Still, how were you
thinking of settling it?
I'm not thinking anything.
It has nothing to do with me.
[ICHIMIYA]
So, that's how it is.
What an audacious
leader they've got.
[KOJIKA]
I had a thought:
our goal is for Ichimiya
to become popular
at both schools, right?
Instead of swaying Handa's
fans to follow our lead,
we should just drive him out.
Wouldn't that be easier?
[JYOMOTO] What heck's wrong
with your eye? Freaky!
Chill out. Never heard of
circle lenses before?
[NAGAMASA] Hm. Going after Handa
like that isn't a bad idea.
I know their group is staying
on the floor below us,
but any action we take
will require finesse.
[JYOMOTO]
They're literally beneath us?
That's like a metaphor
or something.
Actually, I know the
perfect way to do this.
[JYOMOTO]
Whoa. I forgot you were here.
[ISHIDA]
That was a nice bath.
[OOTANI] Yeah, we'll
have to go again later.
[HANDA] I was kinda hoping
for the vacation experience.
Oh well.
Uh? I can't use the public bath?
Nope. That's why your
room has a tub.
Because of your reputation,
you understand.
[HANDA] He must think I'd
try to peep on the girls.
--[HANDA gasps]
--[JYOMOTO] You're a genius!
[KOJIKA]
Keep it down, stupid!
[HANDA]
Sounds like they're having fun.
They must be having one
of those "pillow fights"
I've heard about.
[HANDA]
H'ya!
[AIZAWA] All right, guys.
It's up to us to make sure
Handa has fun on this trip!
[TSUTSUI, REO]
Yeah!
Now. All together!
[ALL]
Handa's Handa Force...
...go!
[ALL]
What happened?
[HANDA]
Stupid buckwheat shell pillow.
[HANDA gasps]
[REO]
Hey, guys?
Random thought, but this inn
is like 580 years old, right?
[TSUTSUI]
Looks pretty new if you ask me.
[AIZAWA] It's probably been
renovated since then.
[REO] I was hoping there'd
be some sign of its history.
Like ghosts.
[HANDA gasps]
I'm sure there's some.
I mean, Kyoto's been home to a
lot of battles over the years.
With all that negative energy,
someone with a
really nasty grudge
might have left behind a
vengeful spirit lying in wait.
[REO sighs]
[TSUTSUI]
Mm?
You think they're
waiting? For what?
Someone who's strong enough
to finish what they started.
[ALL gasp]
[TSUTSUI]
The hell is this?!
It fell from above.
Must be Shiro High.
Those lousy bastards!
We should take 'em down!
Right, Handa?
[HANDA]
Uh...
Whoa. He's asleep.
Harassment like that doesn't
faze him at all, I guess.
We should have never
expected any less!
Let's follow his example
and get some rest, too!
[REO]
Good night.
[AIZAWA] Handa Force
commemorative photo time!
[HANADA]
Sei "Handa!"
Yeah, looking good!
Now gimme one that's
a little wilder!
[JYOMOTO] That's the
Shinsengumi, I proclaim!
[ALL gasp]
Shiro High!
The clothes fail to make the
men this time, I proclaim.
We should clean these
streets, I proclaim!
Calm down, I proclaim.
Those Ryoma Sakamoto
impressions stink.
You buncha goons
are about to pay
for tryin' ta shame
Handa last night!
Keep calm, Tsu-Tsu,
because anything you do will
reflect negatively on Handa!
--[TSUTSUI yells]
--[JYOMOTO groans]
You okay, Jyomoto?
[AIZAWA]
Don't smile at me!
You guys are in for
some real trouble now!
First blood is yours,
but make no mistake.
We will win the war!
[AIZAWA, KONDO panting]
[STUDENTS giggle]
[HANDA] Hm? Oh wow.
What's with the crowd?
Well, if you'll
follow me, ladies.
It's time for the next
location, I proclaim.
[HANDA]
A Ryoma tour!
[KONDO]
What should we do, Aizawa?
We don't have much choice but to
act like we didn't see anything.
That way, it's only Tsu-Tsu
that gets expelled.
[NAGAMASA] I'm afraid
it's too late for that.
[AIZAWA]
I guess I should have expected
you to find us, Nagamasa.
Wait a second, you've
actually heard of me?
I make it a point to know
everyone who earns
the top 100 scores in
the nationwide exam.
So yes, you're Souichi Nagamasa.
The man who placed 98th
in the last exam.
[NAGAMASA grunts]
[KONDO]
He barely made it.
[NAGAMASA] Considering
you always take first,
I assumed you would never give
anyone else a second thought.
A person's test score
isn't everything.
That's a valuable lesson
I learned from Handa.
Oh?
I must say, I'm happy to
hear you think that way.
After all, it means you'll
have an easier time
accepting your defeat
once Ichimiya
is recognized as the king
of both our schools.
That's how it is?
A declaration of war.
By the way, which historical
figure are you?
The dawning of Japan's
time is near, I proclaim!
Do you guys only know
Ryoma Sakamoto?
Y'know, now that I look at you,
you've got a good
sense of style!
[exhales] That's not
much of a compliment
seeing as you dress
like a mannequin.
But thanks, wannabe.
[gasps] "Wannabe?" I don't
know what you mean.
[KOJIKA] I mean there's
a boy at your school
that's cuter than you
could ever dream of being.
Huh?
I was actually hoping to
meet him on this trip.
Huh?!
[KOJIKA] Last year at
the Cultural Festival,
I saw a guy with an androgynous
style like mine.
[BOTH gasp]
[TSUTSUI]
I'm sorry.
[KOJIKA] Akane Tsutsui.
He was the vision of an angel!
So, did he come with
you? Where is he?
[REO] The thing is...
he transferred.
[TSUTSUI yells] Behold,
the staple souvenir of Kyoto!
[JYOMOTO grunts] You bought a
wooden sword, too. Impressive.
I felt I had to,
even though my buds
kept trying to talk me out of it
'cause it'd "get in the way."
[JYOMOTO] I feel ya.
My friends felt the same.
They told me it would
collect dust in the corner
and that I'd never use it.
[BOTH yell]
I can't believe the way
the Handa Force is acting
around those guys
from Shiro High.
Yeah, it's tough
being in a group
with the popular kids, huh?
Eh?
But at the same time,
it feels good to support
cool people like we do.
Because then we're important!
[KONDO]
Uh...?
Without plain people like us,
Ichimiya wouldn't
stand out as much!
We're the reason his
greatness gets to shine
and be appreciated
the way it is!
[KONDO]
Yikes, he's crazy, too.
Sorry, but I don't worry about
that social standing stuff.
Then what's your purpose for
being in the Handa Force?
It has to be to elevate Handa!
With support and stability,
we raise our leaders to reach
the pinnacle of their potential!
Without us, they would
fade into mediocrity!
[KONDO]
Yup. Totally insane.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Look, there's Ichimiya now!
And he's surrounded by
girls from your school.
[KONDO] Uh! Yeah, girls
from my school and Handa!
Hey, would you mind if we
got a quick picture together
for me to show my mom?
'Course not. I proclaim.
[KONDO]
He's Ryoma, too?!
If I didn't know better,
I'd think even Handa wants
a picture with him.
It looks like it's
finally your turn.
Really? Yes!
Hey, would you mind giving
us a hand over here?
Wait. Who, me?
Here, put this on.
It should make the memory more
"historical." I proclaim.
Ryoma!
'Kay. Now say, "cheese."
Uh?
That's a pretty good
photo of you, Ichimiya.
[HANDA]
So, that's his real name.
I guess aside from being a
student at that other school,
he also works here as
a character tour guide.
[KONDO]
Handa? Handa!
[gasps]
I hate to ruin your fun,
but you know,
you gotta return that costume.
Here, let me help you!
I'll even turn it in for you!
See you back at the room!
[KONDO] Guess this was payback
for that thing on the train.
That Ichimiya guy acts nice,
but he's pretty spiteful.
[OKAYAMA] It's not uncommon
to see squabbles
between schools break out.
But that doesn't excuse
your actions.
The three of you are going
to stay here like this
until it's time for bed.
[KONDO]
Thanks for coming.
Aizawa asked me
to pick up a gift
for the Student
Council President,
but it's kind of trick to pick
out something for her y'know?
[HANDA]
Mm...
[KONDO] Okay, you don't
want to be here. I get it.
[KONDO]
Uh?
[ALL chattering]
Code Red: go to ground!
Where'd he...? Oh, crap!
[KONDO]
Phew! That was a close one.
[HANDA grunting]
My arm!
[KOJIKA]
Hey, there. What are you doing?
He's done for!
I was reaching under to
get something I dropped,
but now I can't get my arm out.
Man, we've all be there
before. Let's help.
[JYOMOTO]
And up!
[ALL grunting]
Is your arm okay?
Yeah. Thanks, I appreciate it.
[ALL]
It's Han--!
It's the guys from Shiro High!
How's it going?
So, what brings you fellows
to the souvenir shop?
[KOJIKA]
What the heck did you just do?
Wasn't that Handa?
Handa's here?
Where? No way!
Hold on! You're right!
It's Handa!
[HANADA]
It's me!
[JYOMOTO]
He's tryin' ta sneak past us!
[KOJIKA]
So, this is the real one?
[NAGAMASA]
Seems like it!
Sorry I blindsided you.
[HANDA]
What was that for?
Hey, Kondo.
Yeah, what?
Listen.
I know you removed the candy
that Ichimiya planted.
If you keep taking action
against my leader,
we're gonna have problems.
I'm not looking for trouble,
but you guys should
leave Handa alone.
He may seem cold, but he's
actually really sensitive.
Sounds rough, but only one
of our kings will survive.
Mark my words.
You're so much fun to
hang out with, Ichimiya,
it's like you're a
prince or something!
You probably feel that way
because he's so well spoken.
He's way more of a gentleman
than that Handa.
I dunno. Comparing them feels
like apples and oranges.
Especially because we've
never spoken to Handa.
[ICHIMIYA]
Wait, are you being serious?
I was under the
impression Handa was
the most popular kid
in your school.
He is.
But no one really talks to him,
not even the Handa Force.
Uh! Speaking of, they just
stepped out of the store!
See you later, Ichimiya!
Don't worry, there's no way
you're going to lose to him!
Yeah, he's just a loner with
no real friends, anyway!
Would you mind giving me
a moment to myself?
[HANDA]
Damn it. I'm so lost.
I'll be lucky if I can
find my way back
before some ghost
turns me into its lunch!
Uh?
My, what perfect timing.
I was hoping to see you.
Do you have a moment
to speak with me?
I guess I do.
[ICHIMIYA]
Don't you find it tiring?
Find what?
Being what people
want you to be.
As opposed to what
you really are.
I'm supposed to be perfect,
never show any faults.
It's difficult being popular.
[HANDA]
Now he's bragging?
[ICHIMIYA]
Tell me, Handa.
[HANDA]
Uh?
When you're with others,
do you feel surrounded
by enemies?
Not really.
I wouldn't say that's a pressure
I come across too often.
Don't worry, if
there's one person
you can open up to in
the world, it's me.
I'm no ordinary commoner.
Together, we may
converse as kings!
Now, reveal to me your
disappointment! Your truth!
[HANDA]
Commoners? Kings?
He talks like we're in some
kind of roleplaying game.
He's trying to trick me
into saying something dumb,
so he can spread gossip.
Forgive me.
I didn't mean to make
you uncomfortable.
Let's try again.
Never mind Kings, why don't
we start out as friends?
[TSUTSUI, AIZAWA]
Handa!
[REO]
He's nowhere to be found.
What if those Shiro High guys
managed to get the drop on him,
and then buried him alive?
Handa!
[JYOMOTO grunts] Man, you
guys make a lot of noise.
[TSUTSUI] Speak of the devil,
here they are now!
So, where's Handa?
Beats me. We haven't
seen him at all.
Is he missing or something?
If he is,
we can ask Ichimiya to give
you a hand finding him.
One of his 10,000
followers from Kyoto
is bound to have seen
Handa somewhere.
All right!
You guys are the best!
[KONDO] And now they get along
like nothing ever happened.
[KOMICHI] What are you doing?
Don't get cozy with them!
Hai High's the enemy!
Maybe, but they're in trouble.
Yeah. Plus, we'll owe you one.
But helping them find
their leader only serves
to further strengthen
Ichimiya's competition!
It's not that big of a deal,
dude, just come along.
You're not my boss!
Don't tell me what to do!
[KOJIKA]
Look, it's Ichimiya!
[KONDO]
And Handa's with him.
[JYOMOTO]
Told ya he could help.
Hey! There you are!
We can never be friends.
[ALL gasp]
[JYOMOTO]
What exactly's goin' on?
[TSUTSUI]
Did Handa just refuse
Ichimiya's gesture
of friendship?
[REO, AIZAWA, TSUTSUI]
If so, that means...
[NAGAMASA, JYOMOTO, KOJIKA]
...we're going to have...
[ALL]
...an all-out war!
[HANDA] Because if we
did become friends,
a lot of people'd
be jealous of me
for knowing
someone so popular.
Besides, you have friends.
[NAGAMASA]
Ichimiya!
[gasps]
What happened while you
were alone here with Handa?
Are you hurt?
A king should never
face his enemy
without the support of his men!
[KOJIKA, JYOMOTO, NAGAMASA]
Ichimiya!
[ICHIMIYA]
I see.
This whole time, I only
saw them as my underlings.
Handa, you shouldn't
wander off like that!
[HANDA]
Complaint.
If it took much longer
to find you,
there's no telling what
I would have done!
[HANDA]
Threatening.
We'll forget all about this
if you buy us some juice!
[HANDA]
Extortion.
Let's just get out
of here already.
[HANDA]
Demand.
[ICHIMIYA]
Meanwhile, by Handa's standards,
everyone is his friend.
We're not them,
and they're not us.
There's no reason for
our two groups to fight.
We should become friends.
[ICHIMIYA] But first, I have
to become friends with you.
[ALL]
Ichimiya...
What the hell are you
trying to say right now?!
[gasps]
I've devoted my life to
you being number one.
But Handa's... ruined you!
[TSUTSUI]
Here he comes!
[KOMICHI]
Handa!
[AIZAWA]
Handa, watch out!
[KOMICHI]
Handa!
Ow!
[KOMICHI whimpers]
Hey, what's your problem?
You told me you don't care about
this social standing stuff!
[KONDO] I also told you
to leave Handa alone.
That even though he appears
cold, he's sensitive.
[screams] Ichimiya, save me!
It's okay, calm down!
You've done enough, Yuki.
I'm sorry. Can you please
forgive him for me?
He can't help it.
As long as we're all cool.
[TSUTSUI]
Phew. Back to normal.
Well then, I think we can
put this whole affair
between our schools to rest.
Sorry I hit you.
My body moved on impulse.
See ya.
Take good care of
your wooden sword.
I know a shrine where you
can pray for good skin!
Yeah? I'm there!
[NAGAMASA] I will look forward
to seeing you at the next exam.
[AIZAWA]
Hm...
So, this is goodbye
for now. Take care.
[ICHIMIYA] It would appear
he has the ability
to awaken a person's
hidden nature.
Sei Handa, you are
truly powerful.
Yeah. No doubt about it.
He's one of ours.
Just tell him to hang tight
until I get there.
[HANDA]
So, yeah.
The trip was about
as bad as I expected.
[KAWAFUJI] Sounds like
it was a hell of a time.
[HANDA] I know it would
have been difficult
'cause we're in
different classes,
but I'm sorry we never met up.
[KAWAFUJI] Ah. It's fine, I
actually didn't go to Kyoto.
The whole school trip thing
is too much of a pain.
[ALL laughing]
[HANDA]
Huh. You don't say...
[KAWAFUJI] Next time,
"Handa- kun and the Frog."
"Handa- kun and the Stalker."
You're gonna love it.