[SAWAKO]
The school cultural festival
not only marks the
coming of autumn,
it shows the pride that we
have for this institution.
It celebrates the
strength and friendship
that we have nurtured
during the past semester.
Therefore, to better capture
our feelings of comradery,
I've decided to give
the festival a new name.
[STUDENTS chattering]
It will hereby be known
as the Handa Festival!
[STUDENT COUNCIL]
Too obvious!
Like, not subtle at all!
[STUDENT COUNCIL 11D] Forget
that. What's with her hair?
[STUDENT COUNCIL 11E]
I was afraid to mention it.
It's a beautiful name,
don't you think?
It has nothing to do with
Sei Handa, of course.
"Han" notates "half"--
celebrating the first
half of our lives.
And "Da" is the
character for "paddy"--
honoring our
rice-farming heritage.
[STUDENT COUNCIL]
Just give it up.
I like your passion, but we
can't use a student's name.
[SAWAKO] I'm telling you,
it's just a coincidence, okay?
[AIZAWA] Handa's souvenir
game is really on point.
He won the president's heart
with a single hairpin.
Whatever our class
does for the festival,
we'll be the stars of
the show, for sure.
[AIZAWA]
After a bit of negotiation,
the president withdrew
her suggestion.
And thus the "Seishu
Festival" was born,
with its totally original name.
[MORI]
Isn't "Seishu" Handa's pen name?
[OOTANI] The word is
"pseudonym," bro. Learn it.
[ISHIDA]
Seriously?
[HANDA]
I want to go home.
Anyway, since the festival just
so happens to share a name
with our very own class rep,
we're all but obligated
to take the "Best Class
Award" this year.
With that in mind,
any suggestions for
our classroom activity?
Oh, I know! It's obvious, right?
We gotta go with a maid cafe.
[STUDENT 11A]
Not on your life!
[STUDENT 11B]
Keep dreaming!
Does that mean you're okay
with wearing a dress?
Yeah, I'd look good.
Instead of some pansy maid café,
we should do a street
fighting café!
I can see it now.
[HANDA]
How does that work?
I think putting on a play
would be way more fun!
We should totally do
Romeo and Juliet .
I can sew the costumes,
no problem!
I was cool with maid
outfits, but actually,
I might be even
hotter as Juliet.
Why would you be Juliet, dude?
You really want to wear
a dress, don't you?
Well, I'm cuter than all
the girls, so why not?
Sorry, but you're the only
one who thinks that.
[REO]
Who's cuter than me, huh? Who?
Any ideas, Yuki?
Let me think. A haunted house?
So cliché.
And you thought a
maid café was bad.
[MORI]
We should come up with something
that really makes
our class star shine!
[OOTANI] Yeah, but if the rest
of the class does nothing,
it'll make him look bad.
[HANDA]
Who's the "class star?"
--[ISHIDA] Let's do a barbecue!
--[SAITO] A host club!
[HAYASHI]
Storytelling!
--[WADA] Zombie makeovers!
--[TAKAYAMADA] Maybe a museum?
[HANDA]
This is going to take all day.
I'm supposed to meet
with Kawafuji later, too.
[AIZAWA]
...we should let him decide!
[gasps]
Yeah, you're right.
He might as well, since he gets
the final say in all this.
[HANDA]
Huh? I do?
[AIZAWA]
Okay, simple enough.
We narrowed it down to these
three, so just go with your gut,
and we'll be fine, Handa.
[HANDA]
My gut wants to go home.
Or you can take your
precious time, if you like.
We can wait right here all
day and all night, too.
[HANDA]
No pressure, huh?
[HANDA] Well, this one is
the obvious choice for me,
but I have the feeling
it's so obvious
everyone else will complain.
Nobody wants to see me
in a dress. Me included.
And I couldn't act
to save my life.
[HANDA groans]
[KONDO]
Handa looks super stressed out.
There's gotta be
something I can do.
[KONDO]
Hey, Handa?
[HANDA] It's that guy
who keeps picking on me!
You like musicals
a bunch, don't you?
[STUDENTS gasp]
[HANDA] What the hell are you
saying, you serial harasser?
You like musicals?
Wow, Handa, I never knew.
[HANDA]
Uh, no, no, no.
[KONDO] Musicals are super
popular these days.
If we do one together
as a class,
I'm sure you'll make
a lot of friends!
[HANDA]
Are you starting a fight?
Huh. That one's a surprise,
but I'll put it up on the board.
[HANDA] Damn it!
Don't give me more choices!
Now I really am gonna
be here all night.
I don't want to keep Kawafuji
waiting at the café again!
Aw... The café.
[AIZAWA] Oh, so you want
the maid café after all?
[STUDENTS yelling]
[HIROE]
Handa's gonna be a maid?
[IKEUCHI]
Aw! I wanted the play!
[ISHIDA]
Can we at least be butlers?
[AIZAWA]
So, not the café?
[HANDA]
Bathroom break!
[AIZAWA] Handa? You think
it was something we said?
I think he just
got stressed out,
'cause everyone in the class
was yelling at once.
Handa is a man among men,
he'd never submit to stress.
I dunno. I like his
sensitive side, too!
We made the same
mistake again,
forcing Handa to decide
for everyone.
[BTOH] Don't blame us!
That was all you, dude.
But if Handa couldn't
make a call,
there's no way we can
do it on our own.
Why don't we just do a show
of hands like normal?
Handa's sudden retreat
was intended to bring us
to that very conclusion!
[HANDA]
This sucks.
I mean, I know I can't please
everyone, no matter what I do.
They asked my opinion.
So of course, I'd like
to do calligraphy.
But I feel like I'm the
only person in the class
who would care about that.
[SAWAKO] It seems something
is troubling you, Handa.
Perhaps I could be of help?
[HANDA] Whoa. What's
happening with her hair?
There's no need to be shy.
I promise I won't
make you wear a skirt.
[HANDA]
Seriously. What?
Has your class decided
on an activity yet?
Uh, we're working on that.
[SAWAKO] It's difficult
to lead people sometimes.
[HANDA]
That hair...
[SAWAKO] Sometimes an unpopular
decision is the right one.
[HANDA]
So weird!
That's fine.
It's a leader's burden
to suffer scorn
for the sake of a revolution.
[HANDA] I think your hair is
suffering for a revolution.
I need... to ask
a favor of you.
Uh?
Could you paint
the festival sign
for the front of the school?
And the pamphlets as well,
if you don't mind.
Um.
I realize you're a professional
calligrapher and everything,
so it may be rude to make
such a selfish request.
Of course you're free to
refuse if that's not okay.
Sounds perfect.
So even though you're really
famous, you still don't mind?
[HANDA]
Not at all.
At last, a worthy legacy to
leave behind as president.
[HANDA] If I said no,
she'd probably flip out.
All right Handa,
it's a promise.
I'll give you the materials
later. Have a nice day!
[HANDA]
Okay.
I'm really grateful. [laughing]
[HANDA]
She means that, doesn't she?
I bet she got a lot of flack
for involving me at all.
That must have been one of
those "unpopular decisions"
she was talking about.
[HANDA grunts]
[HANDA] She gave me just
the perspective I needed.
If they want me to decide,
then that's what I'm gonna do.
It's calligraphy lessons
or nothing. Deal with it!
Listen!
[HANDA]
Hm?
Hey Handa.
Don't worry, we made our
decision, so everyone went home.
It was clear that the
only logical choice
was a musical Romeo
and Juliet Café.
Also with maids.
[buzzer]
Why'd you cross out
the calligraphy class?
Not everyone's as good
at calligraphy as you.
So that option made the
least amount of sense.
[AIZAWA]
Now there's no pressure on you.
Right. It doesn't make sense.
[HANDA]
The one thing I can do!
Okay! Gonna be long
hours starting tomorrow,
so get a good night's rest
and be ready to work hard!
[KAWAFUJI] Our class couldn't
make a call either,
so I just went with my gut.
We're doing calligraphy
with super-sized brushes.
Uh! I really wish I
was you right now.
[laughs] Being me
is pretty great.
Can't blame you for
that one. [laughs]
[HANDA sighs] This is
the last free afternoon
I'll have in a while.
I'll practically be
living at the school.
Hope I can get along with
the rest of the class.
[RAI] You expect me
to believe that crap?
[BROW-BOY]
C'mon chump, just do it.
[screaming] Somebody help me!
[SHAVE] Give it up. Nobody's
here and nobody's coming.
[HANDA] They're mugging him!
Should I call for help?
Or is it too late?
Uh?
[HANDA] Nice timing! I've never
been so happy to see you!
You love beating up guys
from other schools, right?
Well, here's your chance, pal!
Don't just stand there!
Help him out already!
[HANDA]
Wait. Did they just say my name?
[TSUTSUI] Why isn't Handa
tearing those punks a new one?
He could, like, sneeze and
they'd hit the ground running.
Wait. Sneeze? Maybe he's sick.
[HANDA] Are you gonna kick
their asses or not? C'mon!
You got a crick in
your neck, don't you?
I'm gesturing for
you to go fight!
[TSUTSUI] Okay, that does make
more sense. Leave it to me!
[ALL]
Huh?
[TSUTSUI grunts]
[RAI]
Who the hell are--
[BROW-BOY]
Cut it out!
[HANDA]
There! Now was that so hard?
[SKELETOR]
It's a monster!
[HANDA]
Also, am I nuts
or was he like... waiting
for my approval almost?
Listen up!
We're starting on the costumes,
so everyone get measured!
[STUDENTS]
Okay!
[HANDA]
It's getting late.
I'm gonna be here until
after dark for sure.
What if those street
thugs are out there?
What if I run into them?
[IKEUCHI, HIROE]
Um, Handa?
[HANDA]
Uh?
I know you're busy right now,
but do you mind if we
measure you first?
Take off your jacket
and I promise it'll
be over in a flash.
[HANDA]
Uh, sure.
[IKEUCHI] You don't have to feel
awkward. I'm a professional.
Okay, maybe that's an
exaggeration.
But I do hope I can work in
the fashion industry someday.
Huh.
And I wanna sell clothes
in a cool boutique.
Well... Not that that's relevant
to you, but whatever.
[HANDA]
I guess it isn't relevant, no.
Still. When I hear
you talk like that,
I want to do my best too.
[IKEUCHI, HIROE gasp]
He's so cool!
[HANDA] I'll give this festival
sign everything I've got!
Hey guys, I called
some old industry pals
and found a place that'll donate
the fabric for our costumes,
so feel free to worship me!
[STUDENTS gasping]
All that's left is
to pick out a menu
and get a license to sell food.
Um. Can I do something to help?
No. Just sit down
and take it easy.
You're the class rep, so all
you need to do is supervise.
[HANDA]
They pushed me away again.
[KONDO]
Wow, that's nice.
[HANDA]
This is so boring.
[clattering]
[HANDA] I'm sure they just
want me out of their hair,
but when they do
stuff like this,
it almost feels like they're
treating me nicely.
[IKEUCHI, HIROE]
Bye-bye!
[TSUTSUI] Guys, make sure you
see all the ladies home safe!
[OKAYAMA]
Be careful out there, okay?
[STUDENTS]
Okay.
[KONDO]
I hope Handa's okay with this.
[TSUTSUI]
He's tired. Let him rest.
[REO] Watching a whole
class wears you out
more than you'd think.
[AIZAWA] We need him in tip-top
shape for the festival.
[HANDA snores, gasps]
[HANDA] Aw... Was waking
me up that much trouble?
[HANDA gasps]
Finally!
It's been a pain, but somebody
has to put him in his place.
[SHAVE] Our school has the best
thugs in the whole nation!
He's screwed!
[RAI] Yeah, and he's
all alone too. Go!
[GUYS] You think you're bad?
We'll show you!
[gasps]
[hisses]
[fighting, grunting]
[HANDA] More street thugs.
Don't look. Don't look!
[HANDA] Hm... I feel like
some of these designs
are pretty interesting,
but I don't know if they work
for a school festival.
No one cares who wrote it,
so I might as well go
with something legible,
rather than something I'd do
for a calligraphy competition.
Okay! I think this is the one.
[NEO] Behold! The Handa- chan
special in all its glory!
3-D girls can take a hike,
this is where it's at!
It staves off my
crushing loneliness!
[chuckles]
[PSYCHO] How many do we need
to sell to save the club?
[TAKOYAKI] Two hundred is
usually pretty good, right?
Our school has about 500
students and I assume
that they'll buy five
copies each, so...
...I ordered 5,000!
[PSYCHO]
That is way too optimistic!
[TAKOYAKI] Also, you don't
know how to do math at all!
Okay, time to
practice our lines.
Our librarian here cooked up
these brilliant scripts for us!
I'm not even in this class.
Someone please set me free.
Hey, Aizawa!
What's up with this
crackpot casting?
Why the hell am I Juliet?!
This is a travesty.
I'm the cute one here!
Tsutsui as Juliet
is obviously funny--
with you, everyone will
just roll their eyes.
[REO]
They will?
[TSUTSUI] Oh, so you're trying
to make a laughingstock
out of me, is that it?
If you don't want
people to laugh at you,
then get small again.
Your transformation will
be the key to our victory!
What exactly are you
expecting of me?
While we're at it, what's up
with your role? King Lear?
[TSUTSUI]
I don't remember him.
You wrote him in just
so you could be king!
Romeo and Juliet
doesn't have enough parts
for the whole class. So, we
added some notable characters
from Shakespeare's other famous
works to round things out.
I don't give a crap!
I'm not playing Juliet!
Do I have to wear those
lame, white tights?
'Cause... ew.
Trade roles with me!
I'm good at leering!
Everyone gets a cool part!
--[WADA] This is so much fun!
--[MORI] It'll be great!
[HANDA] Looks like they settled
everything without me.
Uh, so what part do I play?
Oh, it's very regal.
Wait till you see the
costume. You'll love it.
Your job isn't to
sweat the details,
it's to look after the class,
like a mother looks after
her children, okay?
[HANDA]
Uh?
[HANDA] I've got a bad
feeling about this.
Dear Handa...
[IKEUCHI] I just realized,
Handa's gonna need a wig.
Oh, good point...
[HANDA]
A wig?
[HIROE] I'm thinking like...
a light brown color?
Something with a
natural wave to it.
A lot of body.
Needs to be pretty long.
Huh?
[HIROE]
Sacrifice your hair for Handa!
[IKEUCHI screams]
[HANDA]
I didn't see anything...
[HANADA]
Looks like you slackers
still have a lot
of work left to do.
[AIZAWA] We're fine.
What about your class?
[HANADA] We've got it easy,
thanks to my special talent.
We're doing celebrity
look-alike makeovers.
The catch is...
I can only do Handa.
Hey, why would you
wanna do anyone else?
Now you can make even
more fake Handas!
Hey, could you try it
on me as a warmup?
Try it on me next, okay?
[AIZAWA]
You can go third, Yuki.
The whole Handa Force
should do it!
[KONDO]
Uh...
[HANDA]
Even though we're all working
on the festival together, I
still feel like I haven't made
a connection with
anyone in the class.
It's depressing.
Uh?
[HANDA]
That's my sign.
[HANDA] Whining about it
isn't going to help.
If at first you don't succeed,
try-try again, right?
I'll try to be more
open from now on.
I'll give it my best
in the play, too.
[AIZAWA]
Uh... Handa?
[HANDA]
Nope. Forget it.
You guys think Handa was
impressed with our Handa faces?
Yeah, so impressed that he
left and never came back.
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] That's the sign
he made! They put it up!
[TSUTSUI, KONDO, REO gasp]
But there's no signature.
How are people gonna
know who wrote it?
Oh! I think I know the solution!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[HANDA gasping]
[HANDA] No! Now it looks
like it's my festival!
[AIZAWA]
The days have been long.
And the struggles
have been trying,
but you've all done well.
Now, the time has finally come
to unveil our masterpiece
to the world!
Let's go! To the school
festival of our dreams!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 11AA]
Free samples! Try it out!
[ALL]
Come get your Handa- chan !
Calligraphy! Giant calligraphy!
[KAWAFUJI]
Write your favorite words
with a giant brush and we'll
take a photo for you!
Oh, wow. Sounds like fun!
All that calligraphy practice
was getting boring,
but now we get to show off
in front of the whole school!
No thank you.
You're gonna fumble around
with the brush and be like,
"oh my gosh, look how
tiny it makes me look!"
If it makes me look tiny, it'll
make you look regular size!
Fine, I'll do it if you write,
"Little pink-haired traitor."
[MAIKO] And you write,
"literally nothing
interesting about me
except my giant head."
Is it just me or is it really
scary when girls fight?
[HASEGAWA]
Mm-hm.
--[MAIKO laughs]
--[JURI] Yeah, yeah...
[ALL grunt]
[HANADA]
Why, hello!
It's been a huge hit!
I told you. As long
as Handa's around,
calligraphy's gonna
draw big crowds.
Speaking of which,
did you hear?
His class is doing
something nuts.
The theatrical café, right?
I heard that if you go, they
grant you divine protection!
Say what now?
[KAWAFUJI] This is gonna
be a disaster, isn't it?
[IKEUCHI] Sorry for the wait,
but we're all full!
I was expecting a big turnout,
but nothing like this.
--[crash]
--[STUDENTS gasp]
[TSUTSUI yells]
[GIRL 4A, AIZAWA screams]
That doesn't sound very
Shakespearian to me.
[HIROE]
Okay, the next group is up.
[KAWAFUJI]
Oh, cool!
Go on in and take a
seat wherever you like.
[KAWAFUJI] Wow, they really
put a lot of work into this.
[HASEGAWA gasping]
Hello, I'm ready to
take your order now.
[HASEGAWA]
Look at the costumes!
Oh, and the bricks are real!
Well, let's see here.
[KAWAFUJI exhales]
It's all poison. Great.
I'll have the round and
the square poison things.
Red one, please.
[KONDO]
Coming right up.
[music plays]
[KASUMI] We bring you a tale
of love as old as time.
This is Romeo, a son of
the House of Montague.
The big dance is starting soon.
I'm gonna pick up
all the hot girls!
[GIRLS screaming]
Reo!
Here is your poison, sir.
[KASUMI] ...a lovely daughter
of the House of Capulet.
[TSUTSUI]
This party is so lame.
I wish some sexy dude would come
sweep me off my feet already.
[BOY 11C]
Whoa! Who is that?!
[BOY 11D] Handa's class is
gonna take the prize for sure!
Well, maybe not so lovely.
This party is so lame.
I wish some sexy dude would come
sweep me off my feet already.
[KASUMI] Needless to say,
Juliet's diet didn't work out,
so this is what we're left with.
[GUYS]
Tsutsui!
Guess he's got a
few fans at least.
[TSUTSUI, REO]
Check out that hottie!
I gotta get me some of that!
[KASUMI]
Never before has the world seen
such a perfect couple.
[TSUTSUI, REO]
Come, leap into my arms!
It's hug time! Yeah!
[KASUMI]
However, the House of Montague
and the House of Capulet
were locked in a feud,
because fate is cruel like that.
[KAWAFUJI] Huh. I thought
Handa would be the lead.
[KASUMI] Still, the flame
of passion that burned
between the lovers could
not be extinguished.
Let's break this shiz down, yo!
[STUDENTS] O Romeo, Romeo!
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
You know how it goes!
[KAWAFUJI] I'm getting
nervous waiting for Handa.
[STUDENTS]
♪ La, la, la, la...! ♪
[AIZAWA] You're not the only
ones with family problems!
[KASUMI] Suddenly, King Lear
hobbled onto the dance floor.
But was it compassion
or jealousy
that drew him to this scene?
I just want to be loved!
Despite his name,
he isn't leering much.
Oh! How can we make
our love succeed
so we don't end up like you?
You cannot make
love do anything.
It must find and nurture itself.
Wise words from King Lear.
I'm killing myself.
[KASUMI]
So she says,
but she's only pretending to
be dead until Romeo wakes up.
For attention, I suppose.
[STUDENT 11F]
Drama queen.
[REO gasps]
Oh, no! My Juliet!
[ACTORS]
Focus on healing!
[REO]
But you're too young to die!
[ALL] Focus on healing!
Focus on healing!
It's back to the bachelor life!
[grunting] Here I go!
[ACTORS]
Show no mercy!
[MIYOKO] You better not put the
mack on Desdemona, you creep!
[KASUMI] Then, for some reason,
Othello showed up.
When Juliet awoke
all hell broke loose.
King Lear is not having it!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[KASUMI] Shakespeare
crossovers are dangerous.
[KAWAFUJI] People like this?
It's all over the place.
Cease your fighting now!
These dignified words
echoed across the room
and all the unruly fictional
characters went silent.
[KASUMI]
The one who stopped the conflict
was none other than
Queen Elizabeth I.
For who else could it be?
[STUDENTS cheering]
[KASUMI]
Elizabeth was like a mother.
And the subjects, her children.
[KAWAFUJI]
What the hell are you doing?
[KASUMI] ...for truly did
the people love their queen.
[HANDA]
What the hell am I doing?
I only had one line and the
narrator stole it from me.
What's to cheer about?
I'm just some idiot
sitting in a chair.
Also, why is the whole room
acting like they're praying?
The audience too!
Everyone except--
[HANDA gasps]
[HANDA]
Kawafuji? Why are you here?
[KAWAFUJI]
Is this... my fault?
[HANDA] I can see the pity
in his eyes. I'm sorry.
It must be terrible having a
clown like me as your friend.
If you're embarrassed,
I can hardly blame you.
I can't take this anymore.
I've gotta get off this stage!
But I can't ruin the show.
What would Elizabeth say
at a time like this?
[STUDENT 11C gasps]
[STUDENT 11D]
The queen is standing up!
[STUDENT 11B]
She's going to say something!
I'm off to defeat...
the Spanish Armada.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[STUDENTS cheer]
[GUY 11A] I dunno what that
means. But kick their ass!
[STUDENT 11C]
Good luck, your majesty!
[HASEGAWA]
Our future is in your hands!
[TSUTSUI]
Wait for me, my queen!
[AIZAWA]
King Lear, to battle!
It looks like everybody's
fighting the Spanish Armada.
I guess that's the end.
[HIROE] We'll have another
show this afternoon,
so please come again!
[KAWAFUJI]
Aw, man.
[HANDA screams]
[KAWAFUJI] I think he's
really upset this time.
[STUDNETS]
Handa!
[HASEGAWA] Shoulda known
we couldn't compete
with Handa's class.
[KAWAFUJI]
Oh. Uh, yeah...
C'mon, that was a blast!
What's with that totally
bored look on your face?
I'm not bored. I've just
got a lot on my mind.
[SHAVE]
Gotta hand it to 'em,
this is one hell of
a school festival.
[MOB BOY 11A]
It's Kuro High!
[BROW-BOY] We may as well
enjoy this while we're at it.
Let's pay our respects
to Handa, shall we?
[ALL chuckle]