[STUDENTS chattering]
[KAWAFUJI]
Sei Handa.
A second year
high school student.
His father, Seimei Handa,
is a famous name in the
world of calligraphy.
So it's little surprise
that his son is a prodigy
in the art as well.
Wherever he walks, people
naturally clear the path.
Men gaze upon him with envy.
Women gaze upon
him with longing.
Or something like that.
[JURI]
So you came after all. Good.
I don't know what this is all
about, but make it quick.
Huh? Is that a joke?
How could you possibly
not know what this about?
Subtlety isn't my
strongest point.
[BOY STUDENT 2D]
That is such a cool line.
[BOY STUDENT 2E] He's gonna
make them come out and say it.
[BOY STUDENT 2F]
He must get this a lot.
[HANDA] On the upside, looks
like it's just these two.
No gangster boyfriends,
so it's probably just
a verbal smack down.
I can do this.
Just be ready for
whatever they say.
[MAIKO squeals]
[HANDA gasps]
[MAIKO]
My heart's all bumpy-dumpy!
[STUDENTS]
Aw...
[HANDA] Okay, definitely
wasn't ready for that.
Whatever it was.
[HANDA gasps]
[MAIKO] I'm too nervous to say
it, so I brought you a letter.
Will you accept it--
--[JURI grunts]
--[MAIKO yelps]
I'm sorry.
I guess my hand slipped.
[MAIKO]
Don't startle me like that!
Boy, good thing we're friends,
'cause with power like that,
you could sure smash
my poor little bones!
Anyway, if you don't mind--
[JURI grunts]
Guess it slipped again!
[gasps]
[MAIKO]
What? Why?
Okay, Handa, here--
[JURI]
Oopsie!
[MAIKO]
What is going on?
[JURI]
Oh, clumsy me! What a shame!
[MAIKO whimpers]
Wait... Stop-- Juri!
I sure am slipping
a lot today, huh?
This isn't slipping--
it's way beyond slipping!
[HANDA] Wait. So, they're
not fighting me?
[JURI]
Handa! Run away!
[HANDA gasps]
I can leave?
[JURI] She may be cute,
but I'm warning you,
her heart is as
black as the night!
This is super not cool of you...
[HANDA] Wow. I have no idea
what they're talking about.
Sadly, I'm not worthy
of you either, Handa.
[MAIKO] Juri, you are seriously
blowing this for me.
[HANDA]
Nope. Still don't get it.
There you are, Kawa! Hey!
Some girls are fighting
over Handa behind the gym.
It's nuts!
[KAWAFUJI]
Hm?
[BOY STUDENT 2I]
Let's check it out!
Eh, I think I'll pass.
Not really my scene.
[HASEGAWA]
Well, aren't you sophisticated!
Fine!
[BOY STUDENT 2I] We'll let you
know how it went tomorrow!
[KAWAFUJI] What the hell
is he doing this time?
[JURI]
Just tell him it was a mistake.
He's more of a man
than we can handle!
[MAIKO]
Shut up and let me go!
You're the one who told me
to do this in the first
place, remember?
[JURI]
I changed my mind, okay?
Maiko, if you look deep
within your heart
you'll find the answer,
just like I did!
When I read Handa's letter,
the clouds parted and
everything was clear!
[HANDA]
So she read it after all.
[JURI]
Listen.
In the end, your soul is
the only thing that matters!
Even if you're not cute,
someone out there will love you!
[HANDA] I don't remember writing
anything even close to that.
[JURI] You saw me there
in Maiko's shadow
and your heart was warmed
with sympathy, wasn't it?
It's okay, I can tell!
[HANDA]
Well, I can't tell anything.
The truth is, my soul
was tainted by jealousy.
I was ugly inside and out.
Forget me.
Don't say a word
and just walk away!
[HANDA] You've got a giant head
and you're in my class.
How am I supposed to forget you?
Also, this is insane.
But hey, whatever.
At least I can escape.
All right, I'm out of here.
[STUDENTS gasping]
Handa's leaving!
[MAIKO]
No!
[JURI]
Would you just give it up?
Go find someone else!
[MAIKO]
But I don't wanna!
I'll say one thing.
[BOTH gasp]
True friends aren't
that easy to come by.
You should treasure them more.
[STUDENTS gasping]
That was cool. And they
say that chivalry is dead.
Handa, wait!
Maiko!
[MAIKO panting]
[MAIKO]
Please! Read it!
I poured my heart
onto this paper.
I'm not letting you leave
until you read it!
[HANDA]
Your writing's a mess.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[MAIKO sobs]
[KAWAFUJI] Henceforward, those
who dared confess their feelings
to Handa, were known
as "the brave."
[MAIKO cries]
[JURI]
Stop crying.
[MAIKO sobs]
Why shouldn't I cry?
Now Handa hates me!
He just said your handwriting
was bad, that's all.
But handwriting's
everything to Handa!
How about you and I learn
calligraphy together, then?
[MAIKO]
Wha...?
And once our handwriting
is all pretty,
we can write Handa a new love
letter, what do you say?
Your handwriting
is already cute,
even if the rest of you isn't.
[JURI]
You know what's not cute?!
That crappy personality
of yours! Jeez!
[MAIKO] I'm not going
to lose Handa to you.
[JURI] Yeah? We'll see
about that, won't we?
[MAIKO laughs] Okay, but
we're still friends, right?
Uh. Best friends
to the very end!
[MAIKO giggles]
[JURI] But when it comes
to love, we're rivals.
[HANDA gasping]
[AIZAWA]
My name is Junichi Aizawa.
I'm known as a brilliant man
with a keen mind and
strong leadership skills.
In other words, the class rep!
I have maintained my role as
a class chairman for 10 years.
Since I have served
with pride and wisdom,
I assumed that my position
would be uncontested.
All right, everyone.
Let's vote for the class rep.
[AIZAWA] But then... my
world came crashing down.
[OKAYAMA]
We'll hold a secret ballot,
so there's no hard feelings.
[AIZAWA] All thanks to cruel,
unjustly popular Sei Handa!
Huh, what?
[AIZAWA growls]
[AIZAWA]
Why am I so anxious?
My victory is practically
assured after all.
What a fool you are to
challenge me, Handa!
What could you possibly
hope to gain?
You'll regret this!
[HANDA] Some jerk must have
nominated me after I dozed off.
Being a class rep
is a real pain.
We should make Handa do it.
It's not like he's in
any clubs or anything,
so I'm sure he has time.
[HANDA]
I let my guard down.
I did everything in my power
to stop people from
nominating me, too!
But if I try to give up now,
I'll just look like a coward.
That Aizawa guy must
be in same boat.
Sorry man, I feel ya.
[AIZAWA]
Hm? Is that a look of pity?
You think your popularity will
triumph over my intelligence?
[OKAYAMA]
Let's count the votes... Aizawa.
[cheering]
[OKAYAMA]
Handa.
Aizawa.
Aizawa. A- A- A-
[AIZAWA]
I've never felt such a thrill!
Will this battle
bring glory or defeat?
Every vote is like a lightning
bolt to my heart!
In gratitude and in despair,
I feel their weight!
Knowing that he feels the same,
I share a wordless
bond with my rival!
We are the chosen ones!
None other can
understand our burden!
[OKAYAMA]
And the last one goes to Handa.
Huh? It's a tie.
[HANDA, AIZAWA gasp]
[MIYAMAE]
We have 22 students total,
but one of them
never comes to class.
How could we have a tie?
Oh, I voted in his place.
I didn't think he
would mind too much.
[MIYAMAE]
Well, you're the teacher.
[BOTH]
Wait, so who did he vote for?
What should we do now?
[HANDA] This is my chance
to be free of this mess!
If I bow out now,
it won't look so bad!
I, uh--
We need answers!
Both Handa and I are here
because of our earnest
desire to lead this class!
We're having a serious
battle between men!
Don't take this
situation lightly!
[HANDA]
Actually, I--
[OKAYAMA]
Fair enough.
How about rock-
paper-scissors, then?
I said "battle"! Not "game"!
[HANDA]
They're not listening.
I like it. At least it's quick.
Might as well.
[AIZAWA]
This isn't a joke!
Another vote would just
turn out the same, so--
And you're both
qualified, right?
[AIZAWA growls]
[HANDA]
Please, stop this madness!
If the citizens have spoken,
who am I to disagree?
[HANDA sighs]
With you as my witnesses, I will
settle this in short order!
Now behold our
battle of destiny!
[STUDENTS cheer]
One bout to decide class rep!
[HANDA] Hold on; he actually
wants this stupid position?
I thought we were in the same
boat, but this is even better!
Okay, I just need a plan.
Ah!
I'm throwing rock every time.
Got it?
--[STUDENTS] Whoa!
--[AIZAWA] What?
[AIZAWA] Why would he tell me
in advance? To deceive me?
Or is he simply deceiving
me into thinking
I've been deceived?
That's the grin of
a double-deceiver
if I've ever seen one!
[screams]
[BOTH]
Now, ready and... go!
[STUDENTS]
Whoa!
[AIZAWA]
Ahh! You filthy schemer!
[HANDA]
Why didn't you believe me?
Do you hate me that much?
Does the whole class
think I'm a liar?
Well, that settles it then.
Handa's the new class rep.
[HANDA gasps]
[AIZAWA]
Wait! This was far too abrupt!
Two out of three!
Best two out of three!
If I recall, you're
the one who said,
"one bout to decide
the class rep."
Can't you see this is
serious business, sir?!
We have to be sure!
This isn't chalkboard-cleaning
duty we're talking about here!
Okay, if Handa agrees.
I'll keep playing
you until I lose!
[AIZAWA]
I just want to win!
[HANDA]
And I just want you to win.
It seems like there's a
screamingly obvious solution
to this, but I'll just
see how it plays out.
Okay, round two.
--[STUDENTS] Whoa!
--[KAWAFUJI] Huh?
[AIZAWA]
Yes!
[HANDA]
He trusted me this time!
[AIZAWA]
He's smiling?
How far did he plan this out?
I can't get inside his head.
Maybe I should do rock myself
and hope for a tie
to buy some time.
They say that people
tend to favor paper,
so scissors is the safest bet.
But if Handa indeed
puts out rock,
I'm the one choosing
the obvious "paper."
Then he'll trap me
by playing "scissors,"
so I should do rock,
only if he does
live up to his word,
then the suffering
will never end!
There must be some way for me
to cut through this dilemma.
To sever this chain
of suffering,
cut through this dilemma,
sever the-- Uh! Cut!
[STUDENTS]
Ready, and--
[AIZAWA]
Go!
[AIZAWA crying] The only thing I
severed was my own lifeline...
[OKAYAMA]
I don't want to get my hopes up,
but maybe this will
teach you something.
Okay, once again, Handa
is the new class rep.
W-Wait a sec!
Save it. There's no way
we're doing best of five.
[AIZAWA cries]
[HANDA]
I see...
He made me think he
wanted the position.
Then when I took pity on him,
he dumped the whole thing on me.
And now that he's
pretending to cry,
I can't complain without
looking like a jerk.
I fell right into your trap.
I guess I'm stupid after all.
It's my fault.
This only happened
because I couldn't put my
faith in other people!
[BOY STUDENT 2K] He really
did play rock every time.
[BOY STUDENT 2L] Handa sure
is a man of his word, huh?
[HANDA] My already crappy school
life just got even worse.
Now, the teacher
and the students
will both have me on a
leash for the whole year!
I didn't want to resort to this,
since it makes me look bad, but-
[OKAYAMA]
Hm? Yes, what is it...
...class rep?
I want to resign.
[STUDENTS]
What?!
I just realized I'll be
too busy with my work.
Aw! Goodness, really?
[HANDA]
Okay.
[AIZAWA]
Stop!
I don't want the position
if you're relinquishing
it out of pity!
[HANDA]
What is he talking about?
Look, this isn't pity.
I always thought you were best
for the job, that's all.
If that's the case,
why didn't you turn down
the position from the start?
I dunno, I guess 'cause
I felt sorry for you.
[HANDA]
I thought we both got screwed.
[gasps]
[HANDA]
Anyway, I'm done here.
You guys can figure it out now.
[OKAYAMA]
Hey! Handa!
[BOY STUDENT 2M]
He just up and left.
Wow.
[GIRL STUDENT 2B]
Pretty irresponsible--
[AIZAWA]
You're wrong.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Up until now, the only
thing I cared about
was having the title
of class rep.
I never considered
anyone else's feelings.
But through this battle,
he taught me how precious
each individual is,
and how we all have to
believe in one another.
All because he "felt sorry"
for my conceited self.
He is truly a great man.
Oh, I missed all that.
A shame he resigned
out of pity, though.
I feel a bit unworthy.
It wasn't pity at all.
[AIZAWA, OKAYAMA]
Hm?
[MIYAMAE] Handa voted for
you in the first place.
No one else has
handwriting this beautiful.
[OKAYAMA]
So much for a secret ballot.
[gasps] He really did believe
in me, all this time.
[AIZAWA cries]
[BOY STUDENT 2N]
There he goes again.
[BOY STUDENT 2O]
Still, nice one, Handa.
[BOY STUDENT 2P]
If Handa voted for Aizawa,
then, maybe he should
be class rep.
[AIZAWA]
No.
Today's incident has made
everything clear to me.
The person most qualified
for the job should take it.
Today has been a roller
coaster of emotions,
but now my heart is free.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[HANDA]
Uh...
I've been had!
So, we all talked
after you left,
and the class decided
you're best for the job.
[HANDA] The moment I step away,
evil rears its ugly head.
I know you're busy
with your calligraphy,
but don't worry, I'll take
care of all the grunt work.
[HANDA sighs]
We can't lose to
the other classes,
so let's give it our best,
day in and day out!
Okay, but one question.
Uh-huh?
What exactly does a
class rep do, anyway?
[crash]
[AIZAWA]
Huh?
[REO]
The name's Reo Nikaido.
Seventeen years old.
It's all right. I don't
blame you for staring.
[REO]
After all, I am handsome.
That's right, I'm a model.
And that means I'm popular
with the ladies, of course.
I'm the school superstar!
[sighs]
[REO] High school life
is one big party for me.
Or so I thought.
[REO sighs]
Come now, ladies.
Don't be greedy.
Huh?
[GIRL STUDENT 2C]
He's here! Hurry! Come look!
[REO] Why do I have to be
in the same class as Handa?
[IKEUCHI]
Reo, you were in
"Men's Revolution"
this month, right?
[REO]
Oh, was I?
I lose track.
[REO]
I'm lying, of course.
[SUZUNOKI]
Oh, I know that designer!
[IKEUCHI] It's Caroline
Yamauchi, isn't it?
Yeah, that's it!
[REO]
I've got my fair share of fans.
Though that's only natural
for a famous model.
[IKEUCHI] This would look great
on Handa, don't you think?
[SUZUNOKI]
Totally!
[REO] How did his name
get dragged into this?
You're supposed to be my fans,
you dirty two-timers!
[IKEUCHI]
C'mon, he's gonna hear us!
[SUZUNOKI] I wish I could see
him out of that uniform!
[IKEUCHI]
Jeez, that sounded dirty.
[REO] I better set this
straight once and for all.
[REO]
Okay, be honest.
Who's hotter, me or Handa?
[BOTH laughing]
[REO]
Huh?
[REO] That's not the kind of
laugh I want to be hearing.
You're a model and you still
worry about that stuff?
Is Handa your rival
or something?
What? I don't even know him!
You brought him up,
so I thought I'd ask.
Obviously, I'm confident
in my looks.
I just wondered why you
like him so much, 'kay?
So which one is hotter, huh?
Well, honestly. With that
face, Reo is hard to beat.
He is a model.
Small-time, though.
[REO]
Yeah-ha!
[IKEUCHI] But there's more
to Handa than just looks.
[REO growls]
[SUZUNOKI] Yeah, there's
something about him.
[HANDA] Those girls are
trash-talking me, aren't they?
Yeah, but I'm nicer and
easier to talk to, right?
Sure, but Handa's all
cool and mysterious.
He may be short with people,
but Handa is an artist.
He's not being rude,
he's just deep!
He's hard to talk to.
But that's just 'cause
he's cultured.
Not shallow like a model, right?
[IKEUCHI]
Like a flower on a lofty peak!
Oh yeah, I get what you mean.
After all, models are on
a peak of their own, too!
And how tall is
that peak, exactly?
Like, knee high?
[GIRLS laughing]
[REO]
These girls aren't my fans,
they're demons
in human guise.
So Handa's got something
that I don't, huh?
[REO]
Let's see it, then.
Show me what makes you
so special, hotshot.
He's not in any clubs.
Whatever he does, he must
do it outside of school.
Maybe he knows a secret
spot to pick up girls.
Or maybe he doesn't
pick them up!
Maybe he pays them off!
[REO chuckles] If it's a
good trick, I'll steal it!
If it's a bad one,
I'll rat you out!
[KAWAFUJI]
Hm?
Some creep is tailing Handa.
Wonder what that's about?
[GIRLS laughing]
[REO] All right, we
got a girl sighting.
Let's see what you got.
He disappeared! Where'd he go?!
[GIRL STUDENT 2D]
Hey, it's Reo.
Hey there ladies, lovely
weather we're having, huh?
[GIRL STUDENT 2F]
What's up with the sunglasses?
Are they for a photo shoot?
Uh, yeah, you know me!
I thought I saw Handa
coming this way just now.
Did you catch him? He's sneaky!
[REO]
Oh... that guy?
Nope, sorry, didn't
see him anywhere.
[REO]
Dang it, now he's getting away!
Good luck with your
photoshoot today!
[REO]
Thanks!
[growls] Now where did he go?
[REO screams]
[panting]
[REO]
Handa!
Handa! Handa!
[REO gasping]
[REO]
What is he staring at?
A... cat?
It's not even cute.
[REO]
Does he like cats?
Does he hate cats?
If you like it, just pet it!
If you don't then leave, stupid!
[HANDA gasping]
[REO] I think he's
pissing the cat off.
[REO]
Finally!
He stared at that thing
for like half an hour!
You got some kinda secret, cat?
[meows]
[REO]
Hm...
[REO] It's not the cat,
it's the stare!
He practices it on animals,
then uses it to enthrall girls!
You think you're clever,
but I'm onto you now!
[sneezes]
[HANDA] Okay, what did
Mom need me to buy again?
What the hell is "shu-shu?"
[REO]
Wait--I know this place.
This is the shopping district
where Caroline scouted me!
And since it's after school,
that means there're
modeling scouts
lurking around every
corner, everywhere!
If Handa catches their
eye, it'll be fittings
and photoshoots and
magazines in no time!
My modeling career is the
only thing I've got on him.
Must you torment me
everywhere I go, you devil?
I have to stop him!
I'll kill him if I have to!
[REO yells]
[CAROLINE]
Say, Taniguchi?
How do you like him?
Nice catch.
I'll go flag him down-
[REO]
Hey! What is up Caroline?
How's it goin'?
Goodness! It's Reo!
But why in the world
are you so filthy?
Say, is that handsome boy over
there one of your classmates?
[REO] You're crazy!
There's nobody there!
Shu-shu? Maybe there's
a shu-shu store
or something, 'cause
I'm coming up blank.
The one in the uniform,
right over there!
[REO]
Nope! Didn't see him!
[CAROLINE]
I'm getting good vibes.
[REO]
Totally not there!
Maybe a train? But that's
choo choo, not shu-shu.
[CAROLINE]
I need to speak with him!
Would you please move?
[HANDA]
Hm?
[CAROLINE] I'm trying to do
my job here, you imbecile!
My precious face!
How could you-- Ah!
Young man, excuse me!
Could you try this on?
[gasps]
[REO]
No! Don't do it!
If you put those clothes
on him, I'll die!
[CAROLINE]
Need I remind you...
[HANDA] I don't know
what they want from me,
but they're clearly insane.
[REO sobs]
Try it. It's fun.
[HANDA]
Nope! Nope! Nope!
Just wear what I tell you
to and with looks like that,
you'll be a star in
no time, guaranteed!
[REO]
Damn it.
Being a model was the
only thing I was proud of
and now I've lost it to him.
I just wanted to be special.
I just wanted people to love me!
[HANDA]
What are you saying?
I don't need these clothes.
If you're going to give them to
someone, give them to him.
Huh?
I don't know what these
clothes are worth,
but they're meaningless to me.
There are people
out there in need.
Why don't you try reaching
out to them instead?
Now excuse me.
[CAROLINE stutters]
Wait!
[REO cries]
What is this feeling?
[REO]
It's so... warm.
So, this is why
everyone loves him.
Untainted by fame,
or worldly desires,
he looks kindly upon all,
without expecting
anything in return.
[TANIGUCHI]
Maybe next time...
[REO]
I revere you, with all my heart.
[HANDA]
Homeless at such a young age.
I can't even imagine what
he's going through.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[SUZUNOKI]
You quit being a model?
Word sure travels fast.
There was an angry post on
Caroline's blog late last night.
I don't think I was
cut out for it.
And I didn't quit, I was fired.
Sounds like you've turned over
a new leaf or something.
That's real mature of you!
[REO chuckles] Let's just say
that I learned how meaningless
pride is in the face
of true kindness.
I know what it means
to be a real man now.
Because I saw a living saint.
Someone above pettiness.
[HANDA]
Uh!
[KAWAFUJI]
Meanwhile, that very saint,
was being incredibly petty
to a woman who cut in
line at the bus stop.
[HANDA]
I hope the bus hits you!
[JURI]
Maiko, what's with the box?
[MAIKO]
Isn't it obvious?
I baked cookies for
Handa last night.
I hope he likes them!
Ee! He's here!
I'm so excited! He's gonna
love them to death!
I just know it!
[JURI] He put them in the lost
and found like it was nothing!
Like it was less than nothing!
[BOTH]
No, no, no!
[KAWAFUJI] Next time,
"Handa- kun and the Truant."
"Handa- kun and Cooking Class."
"Handa- kun and his Friend."
You're gonna love it.