[AIZAWA]
Hey, Handa.
Could you take these printouts
to Akane Tsutsui's house please?
Uh?
It seems I've angered
you somehow.
That Tsutsui?
[KAWAFUJI] There's a
student in Handa's class
that no one has seen
in a very long time.
[AIZAWA] Don't worry. All you
have to do is hand it to him.
I wrote a note inside
that should cover things.
He's a bit of a runt and
not exactly the manly type,
so he was probably
picked on a lot.
Even his name sounds
kind of girly.
[HANDA] Sounds like he
really had it rough.
Poor guy.
[ringing]
Okay. He's not home.
[HANDA] Lucky me!
I'll just put in the mail slot.
[TSUTSUI]
Hey.
You got some business
at my place?
[TSUTSUI] You screw with me
and I'll mess you up, punk.
[HANDA]
He's like one of those wrestlers
who cheats when the
ref isn't watching!
I, uh.
I just need to deliver this
to Akane Tsutsui, that's all.
Well, you're looking
straight at him.
[gasps]
[HANDA gasping]
[HANDA]
This Akane?
As in, the same Akane
who got picked on
and stopped coming to class?
That's me.
[HANDA]
Seriously?
He doesn't look like Akane.
He looks like he'd eat
Akane for breakfast.
Actually, at his size, he
might eat several Akanes.
Damn it.
Last thing I need is someone
waving this around.
Anyway, you don't
even need to say it.
You're here 'cause you want
me to come back to school,
aren't you?
No. I just need to
give you this. Okay?
[TSUTSUI] I ain't going back,
you hear me?
No way!
[laughs] Really standing
your ground on this one.
[TSUTSUI]
He didn't even blink!
That's freaky!
You think you're a badass?
[HANDA] I should probably
be freaking out right now,
but I'm frozen solid.
All right then,
I'll tell you a story.
Happened last year.
Buncha jerks were bullying me.
Who do you think you are, wuss?
You're one sissy-looking
twerp, you know that?
Are you gonna cry?
[TSUTSUI whimpers]
Damn it, he's so freakin' cute!
It's sick! Look at
those eyelashes!
You're making me
extremely uncomfortable!
[TSUTSUI] Day after day,
they taunted me.
You're too fragile
to play with us!
[TSUTSUI] Other guys gave
me the cold shoulder.
[GIRL STUDENT 3A]
Stop seducing my boyfriend!
[TSUTSUI] And with girls,
it was even worse.
By the end of the first
semester, I was at my limit.
I shut myself in my room,
tears running down the face
of my tiny, weak body.
Then one day--a
miracle happened.
You wanna get swole with
sick muscles like these?
Ditch the gym and
put on this belt
and you'll be flexin'
with the best of them
in only 30 minutes a day!
[TSUTSUI]
Hello? I need muscles right now.
[TSUTSUI growls]
[TSUTSUI] I realized that
people picked on me...
...because I lacked power!
I could...
...crush them!
[TSUTSUI yelling]
[TSUTSUI]
Crush them all!
[TSUTSUI'S MOM gasps]
[PUNK 3A]
This is our turf.
[TSUTSUI] In no time at all,
I was able to kick the ass
of every no-good punk
in the neighborhood.
[TSUTSUI grunting]
[TSUTSUI] No one would
ever pick on me again.
I stood alone atop a
tower of my enemies.
Now that I know I'm the
strongest guy in town,
there's no point in
me going to school.
Huh...
[HANDA]
Why are you bragging to me?
I don't even know you.
I'm not interested
in making friends.
And not even the cops can
force me to go to school.
[HANDA]
Okay, don't care.
Just give him the papers.
Take it!
[TSUTSUI gasps]
I've been in enough fights
to know what this is about.
He's bluffing...
He can't be that strong!
What if I say no?
Is he gonna start a fight.
Should I care?
Just knock him out!
[TSUTSUI]
He's standing just out of range.
This is no coincidence.
He's an expert.
[HANDA grunts]
[TSUTSUI]
Here it comes!
His face is calm, but
he's ready to rumble.
I can feel it in
the air around him!
[HANDA] My bag is heavy.
Can I put my arm down already?
[TSUTSUI]
Am I really shaking?
What am I scared of?
Nobody can beat me!
Just take this so I can go.
[TSUTSUI]
Ahh! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[PUNK 3A] I finally tracked
you down, bastard,
you're in for it now!
Those punks from Kuro High.
[HANDA]
More cartoon villains.
We're here to pay you back
for messin' up our
friends the other day.
[PUNK 3B]
You pissed off the wrong dudes.
You're a dead man!
[TSUTSUI]
Damn it!
That dude with the papers
is enough trouble.
How am I supposed to
beat these guys, too?
[TSUTSUI]
Uh?
You got my back? Really?
[BOTH grunt]
[HANDA]
Okay, cool. I can leave now.
[PUNKS chattering]
C'mon, let's see what you got!
[TSUTSUI]
I don't even know your name,
but I feel like I can
trust you with my life.
[HANDA]
Excuse me.
Just trying to leave, here.
[TSUTSUI]
Whether we win or lose,
I'll never forget my
debt of gratitude.
[PUNK 3C]
Wait up!
You're friends with him,
aren't you?
[HANDA]
Huh?
[screams] Never mind... Sir.
[HANDA] My brushes are
in here! Be careful!
[PUNK 3C] Damn, that look
sent chills down my spine!
Hey. That's...
That's Sei Handa, right?
[PUNK 3C]
Beats me. Who's that?
You've never heard of Handa?
Students and teachers are
both afraid of this guy!
I heard he rules his
class from the shadows
while everyone else
does his dirty work!
I heard he has 666 girlfriends
and they're all hot!
He stole a motorcycle
when he was only five
and rode it through
a ring of fire!
[PUNK 3C] That guy?
The one who wrestled a bear?
I bet he won, too!
Tsutsui, what's going on here?
How do you know Handa?
[grunts] We're just in the
same class, that's all!
That is a lie!
You don't even go to school!
And why was he here?!
[PUNKS grunting]
Run for your life, man, Handa
is gonna squash us like bugs!
I don't wanna die.
I'm outta here!
[PUNK 3A growls]
We'll get you next time!
[TSUTSUI] Seems like everyone
knows this Handa guy but me.
What the hell went down
at school after I quit?
What do I care?
I'm not going back.
[gasps]
Damn. C'mon man.
You're gonna change my life one
way or another, aren't you?
[TSUTSUI sobbing]
[AIZAWA]
Wow, Handa!
I just heard the news
from the front office
and I can hardly believe it!
I don't know what you said
to Tsutsui, but nice work!
He's coming back!
[STUDENTS gasping]
[AIZAWA whimpers]
Oh my.
He's a great deal larger than
his school photo implied.
[HANDA]
Imagine how I felt.
It's good to have him back...
[TSUTSUI] Handa. I know I'm
just some thug right now.
I'm not worthy to be friends
with a guy like you.
So instead, please think of me
as your personal security guard.
I'll be watching.
[HANDA]
What did I do?
What did I do to you?!
[TSUTSUI]
And when the time comes,
I'm gonna swoop in
and make you love me!
[HANDA whimpers]
Someone, help!
Hey, Kondo! Let's walk
to home ec together.
[KONDO]
My name is Yukio Kondo.
Just a regular teenager.
Average in grades,
average in sports.
Got a couple of friends
and no enemies.
I don't need to be popular
and I don't need to stand out.
This is the perfect
high school life.
I'm just gonna go with the flow
and drift right
through graduation.
[HAYASHI]
Can't the girls cook for us?
[KONDO]
Why don't you ask them that?
Today we'll make salad, sweet
and sour pork, and pudding.
Now, break into groups
if you haven't already.
[KONDO] Then one day,
a tragedy happened.
I ended up in the wrong group
and my beloved normalcy
was burned to the ground.
First, there was that
stuck-up class rep,
or vice class rep,
Junichi Aizawa.
Then there was Reo Nikaido,
a former model.
With just a wave of his finger,
mobs of girls come flocking.
This one is Akane Tsutsui.
He disappeared for a semester
and came back a monster.
And finally...
...there was him.
The least average and least
normal student: Sei Handa.
A charismatic superstar
cloaked in mystery.
To some, a gentle
and benevolent god.
To others, a demon with
an inescapable wrath!
I can't take it!
This is too much
pressure for me!
Okay, Tsutsui can
wash the vegetables,
Kondo can peel them
after he's done,
and Reo can ready the dishes.
Hey shrimp, who died and
put you in charge here?
We've got a real leader
in this group, y'know.
Yep. That's what I was thinking.
C'mon, guys, don't fight.
Allow me to explain the
situation more clearly.
[REO, KONDO, TSUTSUI]
Uh?
Handa can't be the leader,
because he has to relax while
we prepare a meal for him.
Oh! Good call! I get it now!
I'll give instructions
from the textbook.
You know I can't cook
for crap, right?
Same here.
That's fine--we can
count on Kondo.
[KONDO]
Huh?! Maybe a little...
[TSUTSUI]
What does that mean?
[KONDO]
That's weird.
Handa's getting
special treatment,
but he looks really
lonely over there.
But, this is for class, so Handa
needs to participate, too.
[HANDA]
I don't care.
Who said I wanted
to do this anyway?
[KONDO]
Huh?
[HANDA] If you guys wanna go
to the trouble, that's fine.
This class is for housewives
anyway, right?
It's not like I'm ever
gonna use any of this.
If you wanna lower yourselves,
then be my guest.
[KONDO]
Laying it on a little thick.
You heard him!
Handa has his pride
to uphold, after all.
We have to honor
that, right guys?
[KONDO] Uh. He was
obviously putting on an act.
Is there some sort of
"weird people secret code"
I'm not in on or something?
[REO]
Hey! You're pretty good at this!
[KONDO]
I think I'm just normal.
Is that it?
Why don't we put
them on this plate?
Are you stupid?
That's too small.
There're bowls on the
shelf right over there.
[sighs]
[KONDO] I heard scary
rumors about these guys,
but they're actually
pretty harmless.
Well, excluding Handa at least.
[REO] I'm the only one with
any sense of aesthetic here,
so I'll arrange the salad.
I'll make it look like
a rose in bloom!
Extra special, just for Handa!
[KONDO] Gross! Also, that looks
more like a cactus than a rose!
With a lovely aurora
of mayo and ketchup!
[KONDO] This is like-
straight-up bullying.
See? Handa's about to
flip out over there!
[SUZUNOKI laughing]
We'd better get the
rice started, too.
[KONDO]
Huh?
Is he leaving?
No...
Maybe he wants to
cook the dessert?
Well, "cooking" is a
little bit of a stretch,
since you only need
to add hot water.
[HANDA] "Just add water?"
That's ridiculous.
Screw this.
[KONDO]
So, he's not making pudding?
Then what is he making?
[HANDA] If you want to
make something good,
you have to make
it from scratch.
Cooking is an art
and I'm an artist.
My pudding will be perfect!
First, a hint of brandy.
Not too much.
Then an egg.
Based on the color,
I'm guessing that caramel's
made with soy sauce and sugar.
Then add a little chocolate
to even out the flavor,
salt to bring out the sweetness,
and potato starch for
the right consistency.
I'll show them!
[KONDO] I take it back.
Maybe Handa's the bully.
So this is how I'm going
to die, isn't it?
[AIZAWA screams]
Please, no violence!
[KONDO]
Whoa! Whoa! What's going on?
This moron told me the
wrong amount of oil!
[AIZAWA] You should've checked
before you put it in the pan!
It'll be fine!
We can drain it. There's no need
to bust any heads, okay?
[REO] Wait. You were cooped up
in your house all that time
and you never learned
how to cook?
You're making a scene
and food is burning.
Calm down and-- [screams]
[TSUTSUI growls]
What did you say?!
You think you're so tough,
but I'm not afraid of you!
[KONDO]
Bunch of morons...
Hey, Handa! Can you--
[STUDENTS gasping]
[GIRL STUDENT 3B]
Flambé?
I'm confused. The oil was
burning, so I put water on it.
And then--
[TEACHER 3A]
Everyone, evacuate!
If one of you little snots
gets hurt, I'll lose my job!
Stand back, Handa!
Water! Water!
[REO] I heard that it helps
to put honey on burns!
Aw, jeez. I gotta do something.
UH! Hurry! Move!
[ALL]
Uh?
[KONDO grunting]
[ALL]
Uh...
Come on! I told you guys
to move, didn't I?
All I can see is white.
What happened?
[TSUTSUI] Holy crap, your
eyes look really stupid!
[AIZAWA]
Don't laugh! I can't help it!
What can I say?
Handa did it again!
Pretty clever way to get
us to stop fighting, huh?
Really taught us a lesson.
[KONDO yelps]
Anyway, sorry 'bout that.
[KONDO] Seems like a
happy ending, though?
Still, I hate to see our food
get ruined after all that work.
Maybe it's not a total wash.
I did see Handa put
something into the fridge.
[gasps] Don't eat that!
[TSUTSUI]
Pudding?
Handa saved it just for us!
[ALL]
Thank you for this bounty.
No, you can't!
Nobody die, please.
[REO whimpers]
[TSUTSUI] I've never tasted
pudding like this before.
The soy sauce caramel's
real creative, huh?
Yeah, Japanese-style
is Handa style!
Don't force yourselves
to eat it!
This muddy and sandy
texture is gonna be big.
Just you wait!
I don't normally like sweets,
but I can't get enough of this!
Who are you trying to impress?!
There's no way you
like that crap!
[ALL]
Huh?
Why wouldn't we like it?
[ALL] If Handa made it,
then it's good.
[TSUTSUI]
Here, there's one for you, too.
[KONDO]
This is sick.
But, I finally understand
Handa's power.
The laws of reality
bend to his will.
Um. Okay, here goes.
[REO]
It's good, right?
[KONDO] I'm too normal to ever
understand the true appeal
of Handa. But at least
I know to fear him.
I heard a fire broke
out in home ec class.
From what I heard,
Handa's flambé was
too hot to handle.
--[gasps]
--His what now?
[BOY STUDENT 3I]
He raised a pillar of fire
for the final touch
on his pudding!
That is so creative!
He's a true artist!
[KAWAFUJI]
Blissfully ignorant
of the rumors
swirling around him...
[screams]
[KAWAFUJI] ...Handa finds
a completely different way
to ruin pudding.
[HANDA] Naturally, everyone
at school hates my guts.
Yeah, that sounds
pretty good to me.
[HANDA] But even someone like
me has at least one friend.
[HANDA gasps]
Huh?
[HANDA panting]
[KAWAFUJI]
Hey! Handa!
[HANDA] And yet I have to
pretend like I don't know him.
For his sake!
[HANDA] I hope I didn't hurt his
feelings, running away again.
But I can't have Kawafuji lose
his other friends because of me.
I'll suffer in solitude if
that means I can protect him.
[gasps]
[HANDA]
An eraser?
Aw, damn it.
She didn't notice!
Now what? Give it back?
It's awkward, though!
You dropped this.
Get your disgusting
hands off that!
Keep your smelly germs to
yourself, you gross freak!
[HANDA] I don't think I could
ever recover from that!
Wait, I know!
[ERASER]
Uh? Where's my eraser?
Use this.
[ERASER gasps] What happened?
Did he trade erasers?
Like, he was worried
mine might run out?
[HANDA]
Good, I don't think she's mad.
Lucky I had a spare.
Who could complain
about a free eraser!
[gasping]
[HANDA]
Oops, made a mistake.
[HANDA] Uh! She planted
a pencil lead inside?
This is bullying!
Also, how petty can you get!
[ERASER]
It's too precious to use!
[SUMIKA]
Oh, look.
Handa's rocking that
"cool guy" look again.
[AKIKO]
For real.
Who needs a desk when you're
as smooth as him, right?
Speaking of which, you're
lucky you sit next to him!
I'm afraid to even
turn my head!
He makes me so nervous!
You should pretend to trip
and give him a big hug!
No way! That's not funny!
[AKIKO]
Don't blow your chance!
[ERASER] Yeah? Why don't you
try sitting next to him
and see how brave you are!
[HANDA]
Don't cry.
[OKAYAMA]
For cleaning duty today,
make sure you sweep the floor.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir.
Oh, it's okay,
you don't need to.
Uh?
You have calligraphy
work to do, right?
[HANDA]
Yeah, but I hate to skip out.
It'll be fine!
Any doofus can sweep the floor,
but everyone knows
there's only one Handa!
Do it and don't complain!
[GIRLS]
Bye bye! See you later!
Did we nail that one or what?
We're scoring major
Handa points!
He might be our new best friend!
[AKIKO]
Ohh! Or more than friends!
Huh? Hey, that was quick.
If you don't want me
around, just say it.
You don't have to pretend
to be nice to me.
Are you... crying?
Of course I'm not!
[HANDA] Hey, uh. Is it cool
if I stop and buy some paper?
[KAWAFUJI]
Sure.
[HANDA] It's for practice so
I need to buy a whole bunch.
[KAWAFUJI]
Fine, but I'm not carrying it.
[YAYOI]
This is the place.
Hey! It's Kawafuji!
How's it going, Akemi?
Buying paper alone?
All your friends busy?
Who said I'm alone?
Look.
[KAWAFUJI]
What the hell are you doing?
Do you have any idea where
they keep the paints?
[KAWAFUJI]
Oh, uh-- No.
Wait. I think they're
right over there.
Sorry about this.
Yeah. You just keep doing
that weird thing you're doing
and I'll make sure
that nobody sees you.
[YAYOI]
Later.
See you, Kawafuji!
Bye then!
Are they gone?
No more scary girls.
Now would you mind
explaining yourself?
Well. I thought it would
be bad if they found out
you were friends with me.
[grunting]
You're stuck.
Aren't you?
Maybe.
'Scuse me!
We need a lubricant of some
sort-- Something slimy?
Please?
[HANDA]
Sorry.
Even after all that, I still
needed you to carry my paper.
Getting stuck was an accident,
but you were planning
the paper thing.
Ah! Don't be silly, I-- Ah!
It's an enemy! Retreat!
What?!
[HANDA grunting]
[GIRL STUDENT 3D]
Hey, it's Kawafuji!
Handa. Seriously?
Bye-bye! See you tomorrow!
[KAWAFUJI]
See ya!
[HANDA]
That was a close one.
So, do you do that every time
a classmate comes by?
I don't hide when
I'm alone, of course.
I just don't want to
cause you any trouble.
You're really something.
[GIRLS laughing]
[KAWAFUJI]
Uh-oh.
[HANDA growls] Why are there
so many people today?!
What do you want to drink?
Black bean tea.
We'll have a black bean tea
and a black coffee, then.
[WAITRESS 3A]
Got it. Thanks.
Straight black coffee
is a dad drink.
Yeah? Says the guy ordering
the grandpa drink!
[HANDA grunts]
Look who it is!
What's up?
Have you seen Handa?
No. Why would you ask that?
I heard that he was
writing poems
and selling them on
the street around here.
All the girls we
keep running into
must be looking for him, then.
[HANDA] That's obviously a lie,
but I can't say anything!
You're nuts--Handa would never
do something like that.
[laughs] Good point.
See ya!
[sighs]
Sorry again.
And thank you.
[WAITRESS 3A]
Here you go!
[KAWAFUJI]
C'mon. Stop apologizing.
I don't care if people find
out that we're friends.
You don't need to keep
hiding like that.
Kawafuji...
[KAWAFUJI]
Now drink your grandpa tea...
[HANDA]
He really doesn't mind at all.
Even though he's so popular,
Kawafuji treats me
just like anyone else.
He's my one true friend
in the entire world.
And after today,
I'm even more sure that I'm
doing the right thing.
I'm going to pretend
like we're strangers
until the day we graduate.
I'll do everything in
power to protect you.
[KAWAFUJI]
Hm?
So, funny story,
I'm actually the reason
he's like this...
Are you the son of that
famous calligrapher?
You know who my dad is?
[KAWAFUJI] I first met Handa
during our entrance ceremony
in middle school.
He was excited to meet another
kid who loved calligraphy.
There's all different
kinds of brushes,
but even the pros...
[KAWAFUJI] Sure, he was kind
of an oddball, but deep down,
he was like any other kid
and we got along great.
Then one day...
Can you deliver this to
Handa for me, please?
You're his best friend, so...
[KAWAFUJI] This girl I had
a crush on approached me.
But despite being popular,
I wasn't the one she
was interested in.
I was just a stepping stone.
Hey! Handa!
[HANDA]
Yeah? Something up?
That girl from the other class.
She's telling everyone
you're an ink-sniffing,
paper-humping brush face.
[KAWAFUJI]
Handa was purer than pure.
Shocked that such
a beautiful girl
would say such an awful
thing about him,
he believed my
transparent lie
and shut his heart off
from the world.
I was just kidding!
[KAWAFUJI]
I tried to tell him the truth,
but the damage had
already been done.
[gasps] There's a whole group!
[KAWAFUJI]
Someday, I'll try again.
I'll explain every little
misunderstanding
and tell him how much the
whole school admires him.
I'll give him peace.
But for now...
[HANDA] It's bad!
They're closing in!
[KAWAFUJI] I'm having way too
much fun to give this up.
Hey, is it true Tsutsui
came back to school?
Sure would be a pity
if we missed a chance
to pick on him again
after all this time!
Yeah! Let's see if
the wimp remembers us!
I hope he breaks out in tears
as soon as he sees our faces!
That would be so cute!
What?
[ALL crying]
[KAWAFUJI] Next time, it's
"Handa- kun and Handa- kun ?"
And two others.
You're gonna love it.