[KAWAFUJI]
Recently, what little trust
Handa had in others
really took a hit.
Is someone there? No. Wait! No.
[KAWAFUJI]
But I can understand why,
considering how rough
his classmates were
when they tried to get
his memories back.
If this keeps up, he's
gonna have a meltdown.
[KAWAFUJI]
Hm.
[HANDA]
Ahh! Phew.
For a second I thought
you were gonna hit me.
[KAWAFUJI]
I gotta help him through this.
Without ruining my fun, that is.
You wanna... hang out later?
[HANDA]
Huh?
[KAWAFUJI sighs]
[HANDA]
Hey, sorry to keep you waiting.
You're late.
[HANDA]
I said sorry.
Is that you?
Yeah.
I thought changing my appearance
would be a good idea.
[KAWAFUJI]
No uniform for once?
It's in my bag.
But by donning this outfit,
I can live life to the fullest!
Reign it in, carrot top.
We can't leave just yet.
[HASEGAWA]
Kawa!
[BOTH]
Uh?
[HASEGAWA]
Hey! Thanks for inviting me.
This should be a lot of fun!
Yeah, this'll be a good time.
[HANDA]
Okay, stay calm.
After all, Kawafuji never said
that it was only
going to be us today.
This runt here is Hasegawa.
Despite being on the basketball
team, he's a total goober.
Don't make fun of me!
Fine. This is my pal Han--
I'm Hanzawa. Nice meeting you.
[HASEGAWA]
Yeah...
[HANDA] I've gotta protect
Kawafuji's name.
I'm guessing you know each
other from grade school?
Uh...
No, I uh, studied abroad!
Whoa! So does that mean you
can speak another language?
[HANDA] Uh! Iyay usway
orcedfay ootay ealizeray
owhey ownlylay Iyay amyay.
Cool! Of course, I have
no idea what you just said.
[KAWAFUJI]  Thanks, Handa,
for always being entertaining.
[HASEGAWA]
Come on, let's go!
So, uh. Sorry.
But I don't think I can do this.
You can, you just need
to unclench first.
He's a really nice guy.
That's why you're here.
I wanted you to make
another friend, see?
Kawafuji.
How can you be so kind to me?
[HASEGAWA] There they are,
the Triple Apple Straps!
Aren't they adorable?
This is the last
day to get them.
It takes three
games to win them,
but I'm only good at one.
That's where you guys come in.
[HANDA]
Uh?!
Got it. You can count on us.
Are you ready?
[HANDA]
Darts, basketball, and bowling.
I've never played
any of those before.
[HASEGAWA]
Let's start with bowling.
To win Nana, we need to throw
12 strikes for a perfect game.
That's a pretty challenging
task for a lousy strap.
Well, it just goes to show ya
how much they're
actually worth.
Have you found yourself
a ball yet?
I did. But it's stuck.
Yeah, 'cause it's a kids ball!
[laughs] This guy's hysterical!
Man. If that hand's hurt,
your career is over with.
You must have learned
comedy like that overseas.
Use mine.
Uh. Thanks.
[KAWAFUJI]
Yeah, he wishes it was joke.
He's probably never even
seen a bowling ball.
[HANDA yelping]
[KAWAFUJI laughs]
[HASEGAWA]
Hanzawa!
Let me guess, you've never
gone bowling before, have you?
It's been... a while.
[HASEGAWA] Well, for starters,
your form isn't right.
Swing your arm
like this. Got it?
[HANDA]
Uh. Yeah.
Now go for it!
--[KAWAFUJI laughing]
--[HASEGAWA] Whoa, Hanzawa!
[HANDA groaning]
All right, boys,
step back and watch
how a real man plays.
You even have your own brace!
Strike!
[HASEGAWA] Now that's
the way to do it, Kawa!
[HANDA] Wow, Kawafuji is
really good at everything.
Unlike me.
[HASEGAWA]
Thank you so much.
I'd have never gotten
her on my own.
It wasn't that big of a deal.
[HASEGAWA]
Next up: darts.
This one is where we get Foo
by hitting three
bullseyes in a row.
Another doozy of a challenge.
[HANDA]
I have to redeem myself!
You do know how to play
this one, right?
Uh. Yeah. Sure.
Well, I sure am glad
you're here, then.
Personally, I kind of
suck at darts, heh.
[HANDA]
Huh?
[grunts] Sorry.
My arm's kinda worn out from
bowling all those strikes.
Oh, no! It's up to you, Hanzawa!
[HANDA] Focus, focus, focus,
focus, focus, focus, focus...
[KAWAFUJI]
Don't overexert yourself.
[HANDA]
Focus!
[music plays]
[KAWAFUJI]
Whoa!
[HASEGAWA]
Yes!
[HANDA]
Hey, guys? I think I hurt...
...my arm.
Are you serious?!
There's that trademark
humor again!
Anyway, thanks Hanzawa,
couldn't've done it without you!
[KAWAFUJI] It's not broken,
so you probably just
pulled a muscle you
don't normally use.
[KAWAFUJI]
Out with it.
I know what you're going to say.
I've never played basketball.
Huh?! Is that a joke?
Basketball's super trendy!
Every kid plays it when
they're growing up in PE
and during recess!
[HANDA]
Is it really that big of a deal?
[KAWAFUJI] Only Handa could
live a life so sheltered.
[HASEGAWA] You know, with
the focus you showed earlier,
I bet you would have made an
awesome three-point shooter.
Kind of a waste!
Sorry.
Hey, don't be, I was
just surprised.
You know, you should've told me
that you had such a cool friend,
Kawa, we could've
hung out sooner!
[gasps]
[HANDA]
I don't believe it!
Cool! He said I was cool!
He is a nice guy!
[grunts] Swish!
Oh! Nothin' but net!
[HANDA]
There may be a chance
he'll become my
friend after all!
Come on!
Uh?
[HASEGAWA] Oh. They're so cute
when they're all together!
They look so sweet!
Stop it with the gross
tongue thing, please.
I'm thirsty.
How about I go grab us
something to drink?
Sounds good!
I'll come give you a hand.
Nah, you stay put and
chat with Hasegawa.
[HANDA]
I understand.
Okay. I'll do my best!
So, are there any pop
stars that you like?
[gasps] He's not
wasting any time!
Um...
Honestly, I don't really keep
up with that sort of thing.
Okay, then do you
read any comics?
[HANDA] Just the short
ones in the newspaper.
That's where everyone
gets their start!
I should lend you
my basketball manga.
Uh! You'd really let me
borrow your books?
[HASEGAWA]
Of course!
I can lend you my
Triple Apple DVD, too!
[HANDA]
He's treating me like a friend!
I never knew it would
feel this good!
Am I doing this right?
Like, not acting weird?
I bet, at this point, I could
tell him that I'm Handa,
and he'd still accept me!
Uh!
Uh! Hasegawa!
That hurt.
What's wrong with you?
[3RD YEAR 6A]
Huh? Hey, it's that second year.
We didn't see you with
how small you are.
Oh, hey.
[HANDA]
They're tall.
They must be from the
basketball club, too.
It must be nice getting
to goof off here
without a care in the world
while the rest of the club
is stuck taking
crappy makeup exams.
Well, I mean, you guys are here
now, so it's not like you
aren't going to get
to have your own fun.
That's a pretty smart
mouth you've got there.
[HASEGAWA grunts]
Huh?
Uh! Uh-oh!
Triple Apple Straps!
And it's the whole set!
I dropped those. They're mine!
Give them back to me!
How about 'finder's keepers'?
[HANDA]
This is awful.
I thought they were
on the same team!
Hurry up, Kawafuji,
where are you?
[HASEGAWA]
Don't take those away from me!
My friends and I put a lot of
effort into winning those!
[HANDA grunts]
[3RD YEAR 6C]
Wait, aren't I your friend, too?
[HASEGAWA]
Rin-Rin! Foo!
[3RD YEAR 6A laughs]
[HASEGAWA grunts]
Give them back!
What a baby!
[HANDA]
I may not be able to fight them,
but I can at least take
the pressure off Hasegawa.
It isn't much. But...
I won't let them hurt him!
[HASEGAWA]
Let them go!
[HANDA]
He's my friend!
[3RD YEARS grunting]
Who did that?!
[ALL gasping]
[HANDA]
That's right.
The guy everyone hates is here!
If someone should
get hit, it's me!
[3RD YEARS gasp]
Handa?
[3RD YEARS]
Holy crap.
He's threatening to kill
us if we hurt Hasegawa!
Here you go, dude.
We were just kidding. See ya.
You should have told us you
were friends with Handa.
[gasps] But I'm not his friend.
[HANDA grunts]
Wait a sec.
Handa?
[gasps]
Yo. I was just talking to
this super-hot girl at the--
[HANDA]
Don't act like you know me
just because I
came to help you.
Okay. Sure.
[KAWAFUJI]
What's going on?
There you are! Handa!
Handa was just here, dude!
And he was super badass!
Uh, cool.
So where's Hanzawa?
Don't know! And I don't care!
Forget about that,
Handa was awesome!
He saved me like I was
a damsel in distress!
[KAWAFUJI]
Is that a fact?
[HASEGAWA]
Yup!
[HANDA]
If I told Hasegawa the truth,
he'd start getting hazed, too.
This is the least I can
do for my friends.
[HANDA gasps]
Aw, man.
Let me help you.
Thanks.
[gasps]
Uh. Handa!
[HANDA]
Hasegawa!
Oh my gosh.
You just told me to not act
like I know you yesterday.
I'm so dumb!
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid, stupid...
I guess I should
have expected that.
[KAWAFUJI laughing]
And so, Handa's inability
to trust others only got worse.
At least at first.
But when Hasegawa
made good on his offer
to lend "Hanzawa" his
basketball manga,
Handa started to feel
a little better.
[KAWAFUJI]
His name is Kotaro Higashino.
He's the 100 meter ace of
the track and field club.
There isn't anyone in the school
who can outrun this
super sprinter.
He's so fast that everyone
calls him by the nickname
"Dash" Higashino.
Good hustle.
It's nice seeing you
push yourself.
[chuckles] I gotta stay
on top of my game!
It's a shame someone
with your talent
has to be wasted on
our low class team.
Now don't say that.
It's true that I refused offers
from schools with elite teams,
which makes me a hero, but--
[MANAGER 6A]
I wouldn't go that far.
[HIGASHINO] The reason
I go to this school...
...is Sei Handa!
I can't leave until I make
him grovel for mercy!
I swear I'll make him taste
the bitter sting of defeat.
Just like I did that fateful
spring day in middle school.
They made me race
Handa in gym class.
Even though I had a
stomach ache so bad,
I thought my appendix
was bursting.
He, on the other hand,
was in rare form.
That roided out beast
must have been doping
just so he could beat me.
Set!
[HANDA grunts]
[HIGASHINO gasping]
[HIGASHINO]
Every step of the way
he did whatever he could
to hold me back.
[HANDA laughing]
[HIGASHINO sobs]
[PE TEACHER 6A]
Goal!
[HIGASHINO]
That little cheater cheated!
Didn't you see him jump the gun?
There's no way I could
have lost this race!
Handa ran the track
same as everyone else.
Don't make wild accusations.
You're pretty fast.
[HANDA]
Really?
[HIGASHINO] That was the
day I lost my innocence.
It was taken by Handa's
dirty schemes!
And I won't let him
get away with that!
Today, I'm going to challenge
Handa to a 100-meter race
and beat him fair and square!
[HIGASHINO yelps]
He saw me!
Why does he look so pissed off?
Forgive me! I'll never follow
you again! [whimpers]
[HANDA]
I forgot my notes in my desk.
[HIGASHINO] The trauma I endured
runs deeper than I imagined.
Pathetic.
I was so terrified,
I couldn't even talk to him.
[HIGASHINO gasps]
Han--
Wow, your obsession with Handa
must be bad if you're crying.
[HIGASHINO]
Are you stupid?
I'm not obsessed with that tool!
I just haven't found the right
moment to ask Handa to race me,
that's all!
I dunno, is that something
a normal person would do?
All I want to do is take
him down to the track!
But every time he looks
at me with those eyes,
my heart starts beating so fast,
I think it's gonna burst.
And I can't stop crying.
That's a severe case
of Handa Disease!
I thought only girls
got it that bad!
Fortunately, I can help you
deal with your symptoms.
If you race me in a
hundred meter dash,
I bet it'll be just like
racing the real Handa.
Yeah? How?
Because if everyone
wants Handa,
then there needs to
be more than one.
Okay, on your mark.
Set!
[HANADA]
Presto.
[screams]
[gunshot]
[screaming]
Holy guacamole!
10.87 seconds!
[HANADA]
Higashino.
You're way too fast!
That was my best
time to date!
[HANADA] So what's the secret
to reaching that kind of speed?
[HIGASHINO]
Easy!
You just gotta run as
if your greatest fear
is nipping at your heels!
That's smart, if not... weird.
So...
If you can't work up the courage
to challenge Handa to a race,
why not create a situation
where he has to run?
I'm listening.
[HIGASHINO] Are you sure
this is gonna make Handa
take off running?
[HANADA]
I mean, it should.
It's just gotta scare him enough
to get him moving, right?
Fire!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[HIGASHINO]
Run!
This is it, Handa.
I'll pass you up in an instant!
[BOY STUDENT 6B]
Everyone! Do what Handa does!
[GIRL STUDENT 6I]
Remember the three "No's"!
'No pushing,' 'No running,'
'No talking'!
[HIGASHINO] I am so
gonna deck Fake Handa
for giving me that bright idea.
[MANAGER 6A]
Dash.
I heard the principal
tore you a new one
for starting a fire today.
What about it?
Don't you think it's about time
you gave up on this
feud with Handa?
Uh!
At this rate, you're
going to ruin your life!
I mean, you've never acted
out like this before now.
Running is the only
thing you're good at,
and you're throwing away your
future all because of one guy.
[HIGASHINO]
Now that I think about it,
the only thing I've really
managed to hone these
past two years in the
Track and Field club
was my ability to stalk
people undetected.
Could it be that I've
been veering off track?
Don't forget, your friends
are still by your side.
[gasps]
[TRACK MEMBERS]
Hey! Come run sprints with us!
We may be a lower class team,
but everyone here supports
each other to the very end!
My friends. Of course!
Underdog sports stories always
have happy endings, right?
So never stop running, Dash.
Not until you reach
the finish line!
[HIGASHINO grunts]
I see.
There's another
path I can choose!
That's it!
I'll take this ragtag team
all the way to Nationals!
Ha!
[HIGASHINO] This is the real
Dash Higashino's starting line!
[TRACK MEMBER 6A] Check it
out, guys. Isn't that Handa?
[TRACK MEMBER 6B] Yeah, but I've
never seen him run like that!
[TRACK MEMBER 6A]
Man, he's really bookin' it.
[HIGASHINO grunts]
Wait, what about
your breakthrough?!
[HIGASHINO]
This is it!
I'm gonna beat Handa
no matter what!
It all comes down to this!
The feeling that your greatest
fear is nipping at your heels.
That Fake Handa made me
remember what that was like.
And now I'm gonna put
that fear behind me!
I won't chase after you anymore.
From now on you'll
propel me forward!
That means it's your
turn to stare at my back!
[HIGASHINO]
Wait. He bailed?
[HIGASHINO] Why was he
running in the first place?
It's almost as if something
was nipping at his...
...heels.
[HIGASHINO screams]
Oh, my! Bad dog!
You know better than to run
away like that, Josephine!
The way you act during
mating season is ghastly!
Bad, Josephine, bad!
[HIGASHINO]
Handa used me as bait
so he could get
away from the dog.
I swear...
...he'll pay!
[KAWAFUJI] And so, Dash
Higashino's inferiority complex
became that much worse.
[HIGASHINO screaming]
[HANDA] This huge mutt was
chasing me after school.
I got away.
But he ended up catching
some Track and Field kid.
Was that "kid" Dash Higashino,
who we've known since
middle school?
As in, the guy who's
always following you?
Maybe? Who is that, again?
[KAWAFUJI]
You are the absolute worst.
[TSUGUMI]
I became interested in palmistry
after I saw an ad on TV
and read my friend's hand.
Okay, Miyo.
This says you're a single-minded
type of person.
Wow, Tsugumi, it's like
you're peering into my soul!
[TSUGUMI]
I've always had a tendency
to get hooked on things easily.
And fortunetelling
was right up my alley.
But before I knew it,
I had a reputation
throughout the school for giving
highly accurate readings.
Did you pick up a new hobby?
Like Calligraphy?
How did you know?
That's amazing, Tsugumi!
You should go pro!
People would pay
big money for this!
Come on. Stop flattering me!
[TSUGUMI]
Although, I'd be lying
if I said that hadn't
crossed my mind.
But all the palm readings
I've done have been simple.
I need a real challenge
before that can happen.
[AIZAWA]
You want to read Handa's palm?
[TSUTSUI] That isn't exactly
something you can just do.
And seeing as Handa doesn't
believe in that stuff,
you're out of luck.
Don't feel bad.
If you'd like to hold hands,
you can always test out
your skills on yours truly.
You're fickle, stupid,
flashy, shallow,
and can't read a person's
mood to save your life.
Oh, wow.
You didn't even need my palm.
[HANDA] What did this
week's fortune say?
[gasps]
[HANDA
"Too bad.
It looks like you'll be in shock
from something unexpected.
You can bring luck to your side
by being helpful to others."
It's amazing how things
like this can bother you,
even when you don't
believe in it.
[REO]
So.
Why do you want to read
Handa's palm so bad?
[HANDA] Wait a minute.
They're talking about me?
A fortuneteller's credibility
is based on statistics,
so I need to read
a lot of people.
Diversity helps with that,
so I need to read the palms
of super popular and super
unpopular people too!
[HANDA]
Now I get it.
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
[HANDA] Well. I guess if letting
her see my hand helps her,
there's really no reason not to.
Right?
[KONDO]
That's a weird way to sleep.
[REO] Do you think he overheard
us talking about him?
That could explain why he's
holding his hand out like that.
[HANDA]
What's taking so long?
I feel like an idiot!
[TSUGUMI]
Okay. Let's do this.
No, that can't be right!
It sounds like you found
something juicy!
[TSUGUMI]
But... Why?
How can his palm be so plain?
I thought he'd have
the Simian Line.
And the line showing
popularity is so weak!
She's writing so much!
This cannot be good!
What a professional--
she's not even nervous!
I wonder what she sees!
[TSUGUMI]
That said.
There's something
I can't ignore.
As shocking as it is,
his hand clearly states that
he suffers from paranoia!
How is it?
I bet you've never seen
lines like that before!
[TSUGUMI]
What now?
I didn't expect it
to be so boring.
As a matter of fact,
it's actually kind of bad.
It's too disappointing,
but I have to say something!
Anything!
I know one thing.
Handa must endure
a very harsh fate.
[HANDA gasping]
No way! Are you serious?
How harsh are we talking?
I'm not sure.
Uh. I don't have
all the details.
But he may be alone forever.
He'll face impossible odds.
Like walking in a
never-ending desert.
Man that fortune's
right on the money!
He's a loner who does
what no one else can!
The desert must be a
metaphor for his life!
[HANDA] How can they be so happy
hearing everything sucks for me?
Tell us something we don't
know, like his future!
Okay.
Uh.
Palms can change, but I may be
able to see five years from now.
[gasps]
[TSUGUMI] Nothing on his hand
says he'll get married.
But he's still going to be
surrounded by children?
Six? Seven?
So many children
in so little time!
They must be from
different women,
but I'm reading a
very low sex drive!
Stop!
I'm getting lost in
the Handa Labyrinth!
[ALL]
Tell us!
Keep in mind, I'm self-taught
in the ways of palmistry.
So I could be wrong.
This is no time for
you to be modest!
Just tell us his future!
Well, the truth is,
Handa is doomed to a life
of indecency, and hardship.
[TSUGUMI]
I was arrogant.
Only an amateur would
skew the results
of a palm reading like I did.
Until I can present the
reading with confidence,
there's no way I can be
a real fortuneteller.
I'm sure Handa opened
himself up to me
so I could learn that lesson.
And for that, I am grateful.
[HANDA]
I'm a dead man.
Life is too cruel.
Y'know, she probably
said all that stuff
because she knew you were awake.
In fact, I bet the results
she got were perfectly fine,
and you'll live a happy life.
She was just having a
laugh at your expense.
You're right! Of course!
Everyone does hate me,
after all!
[KAWAFUJI]
That's what I'm sayin'.
So you're good.
[HANDA]
I'm so happy! They hate me!
What a relief!
[KAWAFUJI]
I guess that's an improvement?
I don't even know anymore.