[KONDO]
My name is Yukio Kondo.
Just a regular teenager.
Average in grades,
average in sports.
Got a couple of friends
and no enemies.
I don't need to be popular
and I don't need to stand out.
[KONDO]
Good morning.
Uh, yeah.
Thanks. You, too.
Gotta go!
[KONDO]
Huh?
Jeez, not very
friendly today, huh?
[KONDO]
Was it something I said?
Oh, hey.
Good morning, Yuki.
What's up? You look extra dull.
This is how I always look.
[TSUTSUI] You should
take a cue from Handa.
The guy's got style.
[AIZAWA] Not to mention
that sharp look in his eye.
Uh?
[STUDENTS whispering]
What's the matter now?
I think I'm being watched.
Ha, ha! Yeah, right! As if.
[KONDO]
It could happen!
[KONDO] I don't care what
he says. Something is up.
Why so glum, Yukicchi?
I'm not. We just can't all
be as chipper as you, Reo.
Oh, come on, you can tell me.
It's obvious something's
bothering you.
How about this? After school,
we'll go to the Handa Force
headquarters, and we'll talk.
Do you promise not to make
fun of me if I tell you?
[REO]
I would never!
Not even if the
thing bugging you
was that nothing
was bugging you!
[KONDO] You're making
fun of me right now.
[REO]
Maybe a little.
[KONDO]
Should've known.
Reo doesn't have a
care in the world.
I can't expect him to
relate to my problems.
But I'd be the same way if girls
fawned over me like they do him.
[KONDO gasping]
[KONDO]
Uh! Holy crap!
Someone gave me a note sealed
with a heart-shaped sticker!
Morning.
I hope you're all ready for
an exciting biology class.
[KONDO]
That can only mean one thing.
It's a love letter!
But that's crazy...
I've barely spoken to any
girls at all this year!
Well, either way,
this is awesome!
Except I have no idea what I'm
supposed to do with this thing.
I guess I could ask Reo.
No, wait!
Showing this note to everyone
would be rude to the girl
who gave it to me.
Besides, how do I know
it's a love letter?
It's not like I've ever
gotten one before.
But I mean, with a
sticker like that,
what else could it be?
What are you planning on using
your pressed flower for, Kondo?
A postcard? A bookmark?
Maybe... harassment?
[OKAYAMA]
Whoa!
[gasps]
Well that's a new one.
"Harassing people
with pressed flowers."
To each his own! [laughs]
That's not what I meant.
You don't understand!
Way to go, Yukicchi!
[KONDO]
This sucks.
Even if they are harassing me,
I still don't know how I'm
supposed to deal with this.
I see. A love letter, huh?
Yeah, I was hoping you could
help me take a look
at this objectively.
You came to the right man.
Huh?
'Cause I know from experience
that this is a challenge!
It is? Then why is there a
sticker shaped like a heart?
To mislead you.
[TSUTSUI laughs]
[TSUTSUI] This very thing
happened to me last year.
They came out of nowhere,
ripped off my clothes,
and forced me to--
That's enough, Tsutsui!
Not another single word!
The girl that sent this
to you is Yoriko Maki,
who most people would
call a five-out-of-ten
on the beauty scale.
Wait, you mean you know her?
I never did find out
what that was about.
[AIZAWA] She's plain and
average in every category.
Which, no offense, makes
you perfect for each other,
so it has to be a love letter.
Phew. That's a relief to hear.
But honestly, I don't have
any idea who this girl is.
Well, she doesn't really
stand out much.
What's this now?
Spring's finally come
to our late bloomer?
Oh, crap, you were listening?
This is a big day for the Handa
Force, and deserves celebration!
We should have a party
at headquarters
tonight after school!
[KONDO]
Will you cut it out?
It's not like anything's
happened yet.
[TSUTSUI]
You ask me,
I don't think romance should
be allowed in the Handa Force.
[REO] Huh?! But I have,
like, 300 girlfriends!
--[TSUTSUI] Liar!
--[REO] It's true!
[TSUTSUI] But the idea
that she's plain and average
is just so--
[REO]
So Yukicchi?
[KONDO] Hey! What's
the problem with that?
[TSUTSUI, REO chuckle]
[HANDA]
I never would have guessed
that pressing flowers
was so much fun.
[REO]
You should comb your hair.
That way you'll look your
best for her confession.
And we should come up with
a romantic response, as well.
Why not use the pressed flower
we made in class as a card?
You can write how you feel on it
and give it to her at the gym.
That's... a little out
of character for me.
All right, guys, don't worry,
I've got you covered.
[KONDO]
Not literally those words!
Tsu-Tsu!
Well, it's at least
better than nothing.
Right?
[gasps]
[STUDENTS whispering]
[KONDO]
Of course!
This is why everyone's been
acting so weird around me!
Even if I'm boring, being
part of the Handa force
has made me popular
by association.
And regardless of who sent it,
I got a love letter from
a girl! That's huge!
So the reason everyone's
talking about me
is 'cause they're jealous!
Well take a good, hard look,
because I'm transforming.
Thanks to Handa, this
duckling has become a swan!
[HANDA laughs]
You're too average to be a
member of the Handa Force,
so you should just quit.
That's all I really
wanted to say.
[YORIKO'S FRIEND] So Yori,
are we done here or what?
[REO]
Oh, snap.
[AIZAWA] Man, the poor guy
never even stood a chance.
[TSUTSUI] She used that heart
shape to toy with his emotions!
[REO] Hey, don't let
this get you down!
Yeah, forget what she said.
You're a member of
the Handa Force,
and we'll always have your back!
That kinda blew.
Yukicchi?
Honestly, I should have
known this would happen.
I'm just an average nobody.
Guys like me don't get love
confessions behind the gym,
you know? It's just
a sad fact of life.
[laughs]
You okay?
Yeah, totally fine.
Don't worry. 100%-- okay!
[ALL gasp]
[AIZAWA]
Yuki?!
[REO]
He's so not okay!
[TSUTSUI]
Wait, come back!
[KONDO] I've spent my whole life
being nothing but average,
so why did I get
so carried away?
Once a duckling, always
a duckling, right?
For a second,
I actually believed someone
thought I was cool like Handa.
I'm so stupid.
[BOTH gasp]
S-Sorry about that.
Yeah. Me, too.
[KONDO]
Oh, it's you.
Uh! Wait, I know you!
[inaudible]
You attacked me in Kyoto.
[chuckles nervously]
So, uh, what are you
doing out here, anyway?
Are all those flowers for class?
No, of course not!
Don't go jumping to
conclusions, okay?
They're, uh... Well...
I'm gonna use them
to harass people!
[KONDO] He does realize I
didn't mean that, doesn't he?
On that note, why does he always
say things he doesn't mean?
All right then, good
luck with all that.
I don't need luck! Harassing
people's easy for me!
[HANDA groans]
[KONDO]
Handa goes through so much
trying to live up to what
people think of him.
But he's really just a shy
guy with a kind heart.
That's probably why he's
swayed by others so easily.
Same as me.
Handa. Take this.
[HANDA]
Uh?
Well, I'll see you in class.
[HANDA]
Uh. Hold on.
[KONDO]
Huh?
Thank you. I... guess.
No thanks necessary.
[KONDO] I think I belong in
the Handa Force after all.
[REO]
Yukicchi!
Huh?
[AIZAWA] What are you doing
running off by yourself?
[KONDO]
Ha, ha. You guys.
[AIZAWA laughing]
[KONDO]
I'm good.
[TSUTSUI]
Don't scare us like that.
As long as you're okay.
[KONDO]
I don't know how I ended up
joining them in the first place.
But I'm sure Handa had
something to do with it.
[HANDA humming]
[KONDO] He just has
that effect on people.
[HANDA]
That was so nice of him.
[HANDA] Ah! He really does
harass people with flowers!
[KAWAFUJI] And so their
relationship got even worse.
[NEO] We are the
Bishoujo Pictures Club!
What is a bishoujo ? you ask?
Some may say it's
simply a "cute girl,"
but those people are casuals!
Filthy plebs!
In order to better explore
the concept of " Bishoujo ,"
we release a periodic bulletin,
filled with manga and
charming illustrations.
Hmm...
[TAKOYAKI]
Let's see!
[NEO] Despite having
only three members,
we're quite satisfied with our
club activities. However...
The Student Council has
decided to terminate
your cute girl club
as of this term.
[NEO]
...we are in a serious bind now.
No, you can't!
We are not just cogs
in the imperial machine
that can be taken out!
My heart aches in pain!
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
Why is the Empire taking its
base frustrations out on us?!
Because, there's no
reason the school
should be spending its precious
funds on three students' hobby.
Understand?
Damn your eyes!
Your words don't scare us,
Student Council dog!
Look, you guys
are more than free
to keep the club running
if you fund it yourselves.
So why not make
something profitable?
What?!
How dare you imply that What
is Bishoujo? doesn't sell!
Then how do you
explain that stack?
These books are worth
a lot of money!
The male 14 to 25
age group loves it!
Do you have any idea how
hard it is to make money
off of a self-published
manga, you fool?!
No, but I'm sure if you made
a comic based on Handa's life,
it would sell great!
[ALL]
That's... kinda genius!
Of course, there's no telling
if he'd give you
permission to do that.
But, do you know what
you're saying?
That would require the
Bishoujo Picture Club
to draw a guy!
Well, yeah, that's obvious.
More like unacceptable,
as we've taken a vow
to only draw cute girls!
Manga staring male protagonists
does nothing to
progress the medium!
We will not be swayed by your
blasphemous words, heathen!
[NEO]
Away with you!
[ALL sigh]
We'll be coming by to pick up
recyclable paper next week,
so get your stack ready.
[ALL]
Get out of here!
[NEO]
It seems we're out of options.
The question is: what to draw?
Light bulb!
Yes, what've you got, Doctor?
[PSYCHO] Why don't we turn
Handa... into a cute girl?
[TAKOYAKI]
Uh... What you're suggesting
is a pretty drastic measure.
Wouldn't that defeat
the purpose?
Plus, it might be a little
on the creepy side.
Not if we explain
how it happens.
Then there will be
nothing keeping us
from making a gender-swap
slice-of-life comedy!
We'll just make up some story.
Let's do it.
[NEO] That was all the
convincing we needed.
Do we have any idea what
kind of character Handa is?
[TAKOYAKI] No clue. We stay
away from the popular crowd,
so we never really see him.
He's always by himself, so maybe
she should be a cool loner.
No. I've heard he's
compassionate,
so she'd be better as
an older sister figure.
Or a spunky tomboy
with a cool catchphrase.
[HANDA-CHAN]
Believe it.
[ALL groaning]
Okay, new plan: we split up
and make character profiles
based on our own tastes.
Yeah, good idea.
I mean, the character doesn't
have to be exactly like Handa.
Then we'll meet back up
once we've each finished
our first drafts.
Whichever manga is the
best is the one we sell.
May the best Handa- chan win!
Good luck, you guys!
Yeah!
[NEO] The only problem
with this new plan
is I still don't know
anything about Handa.
And I'll never make a good
manga without research.
My only hope is tricking him
into an interview.
It won't be easy without
something to catch his interest.
[NEO]
Hey, hot stuff!
[HANDA]
Uh!
[NEO]
I'm the magical maid Merina!
Will you please help me
cast a spell, Dear Master?
[NEO]
Take the bait, Handa!
[HANDA] Oh, no, someone's
talking to me.
Obviously this is some sort of
prank, but I sure don't get it.
[NEO]
Hello, Master?
[HANDA] What should I do?
Say something?
[NEO]
Oh, please help me!
Uh...
[NEO]
Yes!
[HANDA]
Why's your outfit so skimpy?
[NEO grunts]
[NEO] Well. Because I...
I like to feel the breeze!
[HANDA]
Wow. They responded!
Okay. I guess that's a reason.
[NEO]
I'm glad he replied.
For a second there,
I thought I was stupid
for taking this approach.
Gotta focus. Be one with Merina!
Then I can get closer to Handa!
[NEO] Tell me, Master.
What do you really think of me?
[HANDA] That's a pretty
forward thing to ask someone
you just met. But ignoring
them now would be rude.
Think... Be nice...
You seem fine...?
[NEO]
Wow! You think I'm fine?
Oh, my! You're such
a smooth operator!
[HANDA]
All right.
I don't know why, but they
seem happy with that.
[NEO chuckles]
So even Handa
is no match for Merina's
feminine charms!
[NEO]
I guess I can give him a treat.
[NEO] Oh, Master,
I can't contain myself!
I want to give you my body!
Will you please
take off my skirt?
[HANDA groans]
[NEO] Hurry, please!
Before someone sees us!
[NEO] It doesn't matter
how stoic he usually is,
he doesn't stand a chance
against Merina's sex appeal!
Once I see Handa's
kinky side in action,
I'll have everything
I need for my story!
[NEO]
Take it off! Take it off!
[HANDA groaning]
[NEO]
This is it!
[HANDA]
You may just be a toy,
but you're still a lady and
should be treated like one.
I don't need that
handkerchief back.
Next time, play with someone
who appreciates you.
Not me.
[NEO]
"Someone who appreciates her?"
Merina and I have been together
for over ten years now.
I've always treated
her this way.
Have I been taking
advantage of her?
Forgive me. I'm...
I'm so sorry, Merina!
I never even thought twice
about taking off your skirt!
Thank you, Handa.
You've shown me
there's another way!
I swear... the next comic I
draw will be worthy of you!
[HANDA]
I know.
[bell rings]
All right, who wants to present
their manga pitch first?
Oh, pick me, I wanna go!
[NEO] I like the
enthusiasm, Dr. Psycho.
Our story begins
with our heroine
bumping into Handa- chan
after coming around a corner.
Oh, I see!
A classic beginning.
By utilizing this
tried and true method,
it relieves the burden of
character development.
[gasps] Wait.
In this panel you...!
You exposed Handa- chan 's
p-p-p-p...!
Yeah, it's a little treat
to hook our readers early!
This isn't hentai, you goon!
You ought to be
ashamed of yourself!
What the heck's gotten
into you, chief?
Handa- chan would never
act so indecently!
Uh! But there's no point
in making a manga
without some fan service!
Handa- chan would never
resort to such a crude tactic!
As an otaku , you
have lost your way!
[NEO groans]
How about you both calm
down and read mine?
In here, she's a space soldier
that fights
intergalactic battles
for her captain boyfriend!
[NEO grunts]
[groaning]
My poor face!
Don't tarnish her purity with
a two-bit love interest!
[TAKOYAKI groans]
We're just following
the tropes of the genre!
Well don't!
The inner charm and natural
beauty of Handa- chan is all
that we'll need to have readers
coming back, begging for more!
Don't you dare imply
that our audience wants
quality entertainment!
For real, talk about
disappointing!
No one's happy
seeing word balloons
when they should be seeing
a girl's balloons instead!
[PSYCHO] Everyone goes
in expecting cleavage
and dirty jokes in these
kinds of stories!
[TAKOYAKI] You can't make this
something it isn't, Chief!
Why you...!
[NEO] I know you're right.
As much as I hate it.
But, in this case, we
have no other choice
but to take a
different approach.
What, do you think
the comic you wrote
is going to make us
change our minds?
Yes, I do.
I spent this whole past week
getting to know Handa- chan ,
and, quite frankly,
it changed me.
After this experience,
my standards for a
leading lady have matured.
So as we cast off this
drivel for recycling,
we now make room
for Handa- chan .
[BOTH gasping]
No way! How...?
What you see doesn't even
scratch the surface
of her compassion.
She is not unlike a goddess!
It's beautiful!
You're wrong. She's beautiful.
This is the heroine the world
has been looking for!
Handa- chan ! I'm not
worthy of your love!
This panel where she puts
the robe on the naked girl
is truly inspiring!
I know.
The first time I saw it,
I was so moved that I wept
openly like a child.
We can't waste any more time!
If we're going to
make our deadline,
we have to get the copies
ready for print!
You're right.
The school festival is
right around the corner!
But first, we need
Handa's permission.
What if he says no, though?
Nah, there's no way he can
decline after reading it!
Come on!
[NEO]
All right! Let's go!
[TAKOYAKI] Time to find him
and show him this masterpiece!
Handa!
[NEO] Woo! My chance to
speak to Handa face-to-face
has finally arrived!
[ALL laughing]
[footsteps]
'Scuse me guys. I'm here
to get the recycling boxes.
Huh? Guess this is it. Comics?
Where is he?
I don't know, but we
really need to find him.
Oh, hey. It's the Cute Girls
something something club.
Bishoujo . Anyway, you know
if Handa's still here?
Yes, he's currently helping us
collect the recyclable paper
like a responsible
student would.
Speaking of, have you prepared
your garbage for pickup yet?
It's ready for you
to take at any time.
See? It's right here on the
desk waiting... for... you.
Someone must have come by
and collected it already.
Hang on. Where are...?
Is something wrong?
Oh, no. We left our...
...manga pages...
...on the table.
No, no, no, no!
[ALL whimpering]
[TAKOYAKI] You idiot! Why would
you put them with the box?
[NEO] I didn't think anyone
would just barge into the room!
[PSYCHO]
Who cares?
We gotta find them
before they're destroyed!
[NEO]
I staked my life on that manga!
Whoever took it is going to pay!
[TAKOYAKI] We have to hurry!
There isn't much time!
"Manga"?
[TAKOYAKI gasping]
It's leaving!
[ALL panting]
[TAKOYAKI]
I'm so tired!
Oh, no! Too late.
[NEO]
Handa?
But why is he
chasing the truck?
[HANDA] I'm the one
who threw them away!
[ALL gasping]
He's so fast.
Save Handa- chan !
[TAKOYAKI]
Whoa! The truck's coming back!
Handa did all that to protect
our waifu from harm!
Yatta!
Yeah! Guys! This is
the best day ever!
You were right all along, Chief,
Handa is as pure and as kind
as Handa- chan herself,
even if he isn't as cute!
[PSYCHO laughs] Let's make
sure they're undamaged!
Handa! Truly. Thank you.
[HANDA]
That was tough, but worth it.
I bet they were itching
to tell everyone
I threw away their
stuff on purpose.
[NEO]
Well? Have you found them yet?
[TAKOYAKI] Where are they?
Oh, wait, oh! Is this...?
Man, that sure was a close
one, wasn't it, Handa?
Wow, I wonder what
idiot threw them away.
[HANDA]
You trying to start something?
[TAKOYAKI]
Oh. They gotta be here.
[ALL gasping]
[HANDA grunts]
[HANDA-CHAN moans]
[HANDA gasping]
[NEO]
Yay! We found them at last!
[HANDA]
What the...?
[TAKOYAKI] We've still got a bit
before the school festival,
but our presales
are stacking up!
You know, none of this
would be happening
if Handa hadn't protected
our comics for us.
That's true.
What are you sketching now?
Is it a new cutie?
It's not what it looks like!
I'm just improving
my talents, okay?
[bell rings]
[KAWAFUJI]
That's all it took
for the chief to wander
down the forbidden path.