[STUDENTS chattering]
[HANADA] Sei Handa is the
object of my admiration.
Or rather, he was.
To admire someone is to yearn
for them, to look up to them.
That implies that they are
something greater than you,
that the two of you will
never become one.
[HANDA]
Must be my imagination.
[HANADA]
But that won't do at all.
I can't spend my whole life
yearning for Sei Handa.
No, I was born to be Sei Handa.
And now, I will make
that dream a reality!
[HARU]
Ta-da!
Is this super cool or what?
A Handa original?
He set up a spot
in Oohirogi Park
and was selling these
to anyone who came by.
I heard he was working as a
street artist after school,
but I didn't believe it.
We should go check
it out today!
[IKEUCHI]
Mm!
Sounds great!
[HANDA] So, evidently
I'm a street poet now?
I don't remember writing
anything like that.
Or any poetry actually, ever.
[HARU] We should make it
the official class slogan!
[HIROE]
Yeah!
[HANDA] Are they doing
this to torment me?
That poetry sucks!
Don't put my name on it!
You think it's legit?
I don't know if Handa
writes poetry or not.
[KONDO]
Stop standing next to me.
We're not friends.
According to my observations,
Handa always makes an
effort not to stand out.
He goes straight
home after class
and works on his calligraphy.
I think.
Though he does buy art
supplies sometimes.
I think.
He doesn't have the time
to sit around some park
selling poems and stuff.
I think.
Wow. You know Handa so well.
[ALL]
Because I've been stalking him.
Anyway...
Whatever is happening,
Handa's likely not involved.
But we should go check
it out just to be sure.
Kondo.
Why am I a part of this?
[bell rings]
[HANDA] I sat here staring
at that crap all day
and never worked up
the courage to complain.
It pisses me off knowing
some moron's out there
putting my name on this garbage.
And it pisses me off even more
seeing people post that garbage
and laugh about it!
[KAWAFUJI]
Hey, Handa...
[HANDA] It's time for me
to show those bastards
my white hot rage.
[KAWAFUJI]
You okay?
[TSUTSUI]
So do we just stand here
and wait to see if he shows?
[REO]
Huh? Hey, isn't that him there?
[ALL]
Huh?
[AIZAWA] But he was in the
classroom just a second ago!
[HANADA groaning]
You can't just walk
onto the scene
and start throwing punches!
Sorry.
His face was like
pineapple on a pizza.
Y'know.
Are you trying to tell me
you punch your pizza?
[REO]
Whoa, you all right?
[HANADA]
Uh. That hurt.
You won't get off lightly
for assaulting a famous
calligrapher like me!
[HANADA grunting]
[KONDO] No punching
and no slapping either!
[TSUTSUI] So it was a Handa
imposter! Of course.
You were using
Handa's popularity
to make money off
your crappy poetry.
[chuckles] You think I'm some
phony, chasing chump change?
I was born to be Handa,
you fools! You'll see!
[KONDO] Okay, whatever, but
cover your mouth, it's weird!
[REO] You can be more like
Handa or less like Handa,
but make up your mind!
[HANADA] I am the true
evolution of Handa.
The miraculous second coming!
I'm sorry! I'm Kei Hanada!
Which you have to admit,
sounds a lot like Sei Handa,
which is what I thought when
I saw him at the high school
entrance ceremony and I
realized how awesome he was!
Now please don't cut my hair,
it takes me two hours
to get it right!
So, you're not in
it for the money,
you're just an overly
enthusiastic Handa cosplayer
who doesn't know where
to draw the line.
[HANADA]
More or less.
At first I just admired
Handa like anyone else,
but then I got in too deep and
started thinking I was him!
You're not a fan,
you're completely insane.
If we aren't careful,
this could happen to us.
[HANADA]
After thorough observation,
I've captured all of his
mannerisms as well.
This is the Handa Walk!
Yeah. Got the bad
posture and everything!
[HANADA]
Handa Calligraphy!
[ALL]
Ooh!
[HANADA]
Window Handa!
[ALL]
Nice, nice!
[HANADA]
Running to the Bathroom Handa!
[AIZAWA]
Actually, I haven't seen that.
[REO]
Seems right, though.
[KONDO]
You guys are roped in already.
This can't end well.
[GIRL 4A]
Hey, isn't that Handa?
[GIRL 4B]
Let me see!
And would you look at that;
we don't have to wait
in line or anything!
[HANADA]
Huh?
[GIRL 4B] C'mon! Why don't
you ditch this boring park
and come someplace
fun with us?
Carnivore girls.
They're not afraid
to grab some man meat.
And eat it?!
[GIRLS chattering]
[REO] That phoney's gonna get
eaten alive if we don't help.
[KONDO] Surely they'll be
able to tell he's a fake.
[REO] I don't know if
they've seen Handa before,
so they might not catch
on till it's too late.
[TSUTSUI]
This is complicated.
[gasps] I told you he'd be here!
[GIRLS chattering]
[AIZAWA]
Uh-oh! More incoming!
[HANADA whimpering]
[GIRL STUDENTS]
Handa! Handa!
[REO] This is like watching
a train wreck in slow motion.
[HANADA] My Handa mimicry has
become sublime, but like Icarus,
I fear I have flown
too close to the sun
and my fake Handa wings
can carry me no longer.
Alas, I submit.
[HANADA]
I'm not fit to be Handa.
[HANADA groans]
[GIRL STUDENT 4C]
Huh?
[GIRL STUDENT 4A]
Oh. Oops.
I thought that was Handa
for some reason.
[GIRL STUDENT 4B] I don't know
where we got that idea.
[GIRL STUDENT 4C]
He's just some weirdo.
[GIRL STUDENT 4A]
Well, so much for that.
[KONDO]
Although I don't know why,
as we gazed upon this scene,
our tears flowed freely
and would not cease.
[AIZAWA]
Handa had cleanup duty today,
so he might still
be in the classroom.
I'm sure he'll forgive you
if you apologize properly.
[HANADA]
Okay...
[TSUTSUI]
That doesn't mean
that you're not gonna
get punched, though.
I'm just regular Kei
Hanada from now on.
Even if I was reincarnated
a thousand times,
I could never be the real Handa.
I'll leave the Handa
life to Handa alone.
[ALL gasping]
[HANADA cries]
Handa!
[KONDO]
I don't get it.
[HANADA]
Ta-da!
I got braces to fix
my crooked teeth!
Huh? So you can look
more like Handa?
[AIZAWA]
I thought you gave that up!
What's the deal?
Handa's message said:
"if you're going to copy
someone, be better at it,"
so I'm gonna take
his expert advice
and rework my Handa game
from the ground up.
[KONDO] Handa really knows
how to attract the weirdoes,
doesn't he?
I thought I knew everything
there was to know about the man,
but now I see that
my understanding
was only skin-deep.
He really is a profound
and mysterious person.
Is that the real Handa?
Ah! I gotta get a taste of that!
[inaudible]
Holy crap!
Now this is news!
[KAWAFUJI] The story echoed
through the halls of the school.
"Handa had a super-hot
girlfriend."
[GIRL STUDENT 4A]
Did you hear?
[GIRL STUDENT 4B]
Yeah, I saw the picture, too.
This sucks. That big traitor!
[KAWAFUJI]
With the appearance
of Handa's so-called
"special someone,"
the Handa fad came to a halt
and Handa hate began
to run rampant.
Of course,
this is how Handa thought
things were to begin with.
[REO] What do you make
of this, little Tsu-Tsu?
Call me that again, and
I will pound your face in.
But yeah, crazy, huh?
I mean, it doesn't
really bother me.
But the girls are losing
their damn minds.
I don't blame them.
Seeing him with an older woman
really puts them in their
place, doesn't it?
[TSUTSUI] We gotta step
up our sophistication.
[REO]
I guess you're right.
[KONDO] You guys don't
even speak to Handa
in the first place.
How hopeless can you get?
[TSUTSUI] Right now,
I'm more worried about
my parent-teacher conference.
Whoa, was it bad?
Yours' was yesterday, right?
[TSUTSUI]
Well, it was awkward.
My mom was so happy to
see me back in school
she broke down into tears.
[REO laughs]
It's really Handa she has to
thank for all this, though.
Bums me out I can't return
the favor somehow.
By the way, looks like I might
be repeating a grade.
[REO]
Sucks to be you, man!
[KONDO] You sure that's not
why your mom was crying?
[GIRL STUDENT 4D]
"Die"?
[TSUTSUI]
Uh?
[GIRL STUDENT 4D]
Isn't that a little harsh?
[HANDA] I'm used to being picked
on, but this is pretty blunt.
Whatever.
[STUDENTS gasping]
Who the hell wrote that?
That conference
put me off guard.
I'm supposed to protect Handa
from this kinda crap.
[BOY STUDENT 4A]
What a jerk, huh?
[OKAYAMA]
All right, let's begin.
[BOY STUDENT 4B]
Little extreme, isn't it?
[HANDA]
Now that I get a closer look,
their penmanship is quite nice.
Especially for graffiti.
That last stroke's a
little rough, though.
Wonder if they were trying
to communicate something.
Other than the obvious, I mean.
That's going to bug me.
I need to find the
person who did this.
[KONDO whimpers]
[OKAYAMA] If everyone
would turn to page 44...
[KONDO] I guess it's a like
a spurned love thing.
Girls sure can be scary, huh?
This girl better hope
she's strong, too.
Cause I'm gonna chop her in
the face when I find her.
[KONDO]
No mercy, even for the ladies!
So what's the verdict,
detective?
[AIZAWA] Hm... The ink is fresh,
so we can assume it was written
by someone in our
class this morning.
But I wonder if it's actually
a poorly-worded
statement of intent.
[REO] Cause it's written
so nicely, you mean?
If that's the case, then she--
[GIRL screams]
[ALL gasp]
Someone help!
A girl's gonna jump
from the fourth floor!
No way!
Then it was a suicide note!
This is bad news!
Wait a sec. I can replace
my desk with a spare.
[wind howling]
[SUMIKA]
Miyo!
Whatever it is, I know we
can work it out together!
Don't do anything drastic, Miyo!
You were so happy before!
Try to remember!
This isn't like you at all!
Grab some mats from
the gym to be safe.
[HANADA]
Okay!
[TSUTSUI]
Who is she, anyway?
[AIZAWA]
Miyoko Kinjo.
She sits in the desk
next to Handa.
She does well in school,
has lots of friends,
and is highly regarded
by teachers too.
Then why would she do this?
Her life took a turn
for the worse.
After Handa gave her
an eraser one day,
the incident twisted her mind.
[KONDO]
Why does he know this?
And how?
The eraser...
Handa! Am I nothing?!
How could you!
I thought this tiny eraser
was innocent and pure!
But it's defiled, just like you!
It sounds like she's
off her rocker.
The question is,
what will Handa do?
[BOY STUDENT 4C]
Don't do it!
Everyone sure is loud today.
No one can understand
the torment in my heart.
Or the pain this eraser brings!
It can only be expressed
through song.
♪ The eraser you gave
is so precious to me. ♪
♪ I can hardly study. ♪
♪ How could I?
I dare not get it dirty. ♪
[ERASERS]
♪ We are eraser boys ♪
♪ Nothing but a trap is this
little while thing ♪
♪ chaining my heart. ♪
♪ It tears me apart. ♪
[ERASER BOY 4A]
♪ We are eraser boys ♪
♪ My grades look bleak, ♪
♪ said the teacher this week
with a hint of pain. ♪
♪ It seems my life is
going down the drain ♪
[ERASERS]
♪ Going down. Going down ♪
♪ Down the drain, Miyoko. ♪
♪ But don't you see? ♪
♪ I cannot allow my eraser
to ever be dirty for I know ♪
♪ each little mark is bears
is like a filthy stain ♪
♪ on Handa's purity. ♪
[ERASERS]
♪ So we remain beautiful! ♪
♪ But at last I see. ♪
♪ That you lied to me. ♪
♪ And your heart was already
dirty as it could be! ♪
[KONDO] At least she's
not jumping, I guess?
[MIYOKO] It's true,
that I longed for Handa.
But it was a mutual
understanding that I desired,
not romance!
I didn't want to lock
him up in a bad way.
I'm confused. Is there a good
way to lock someone up?
[OKAYAMA] She's still
yapping--bring the mats!
C'mon! C'mon!
I was content being just a fan.
I was content sharing
him with everybody!
Handa belongs to the whole
class, or he belongs to no one!
That's why his fans
are rising up in fury,
because he betrayed our trust!
He broke our unspoken promise
and chose to give his heart
to one woman alone!
But your den of love
is a den of lies
and you've left us all
out in the cold!
I bet you're laughing at us,
aren't you, Handa?
[KONDO] Boy, am I glad I don't
have to sit next to this girl.
I feel bad for Handa!
So, in hopes that our
Handa will see the light,
and return to his rightful
place at our side,
I offer my life.
[OKAYAMA] Whatever this is,
it's not worth it!
[MIYOKO] So please etch this
into your memory, Handa.
And should any woman ever
threaten to ensnare your heart,
think of the sacrifice
I made today,
so that you could be ours...
...forever, and ever.
[gasps] Handa?
What's he doing?
That's the desk I wrote
my suicide note on.
Is he trying to
tell me something?
Why else would he bring it here?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[AIZAWA]
She turned around.
[TSUTSUI]
Must be someone there.
[MIYOKO]
My resolve is unwavering!
If you think you can stop me,
I'd like to see you try!
[HANDA] None of these
are the right height.
My calligraphy suffers if
the desk isn't just perfect.
[MIYOKO]
Well?
[HANDA] I realize now how much
I took you for granted.
[gasps]
[HANDA]
You really are irreplaceable.
One of a kind.
It hurts to think that you ended
up this way because of me.
I'm sorry.
[gasping]
[STUDENTS yelp, sigh]
I don't know what
happened, but--
We're fine! No more mats!
[crying] How am I supposed
to hold a grudge
when you say such sweet words?
My heart belongs to you
after all, Handa.
I promise I'll take better
care of you from now on,
Mr. School Desk.
[MIYOKO sobbing]
[SUMIKA]
Miyo!
[AKIKO]
[MIYOKO] You're telling
me that I must go on,
even as the chains of jealousy
tug at my tender heart.
A gentle cruelty.
A cruel kindness.
Dunno what happened, but I
bet we have Handa to thank.
I can see why all the girls
in school fall for him.
I feel like I'm missing half of
the story here, but whatever.
[MIYOKO]
I realized something today.
When you truly love someone,
you shouldn't demand
anything in return.
Love is giving your all,
until nothing remains, right?
So from now on, my love
will be like a tiny eraser.
Even if... Even if Handa
has a--girlfriend!
[AKIKO]
Miyo, pull it together!
I thought I was strong,
but I can't take it!
Ahh!
[SUMIKA] Jealousy sure
changes people, doesn't it?
[AKIKO] She just uninvited
herself from the sleepover.
[MIYOKO sobbing]
Stupid!
Stupid Handa! Why?
[WOMAN]
Do you need a handkerchief?
Yeah, maybe.
Are you having a tough day?
[MIYOKO]
That's Handa's girlfriend!
[WOMAN] ...can you
tell me where to find
the faculty office?
Huh?
I came here for a
parent-teacher conference,
but I think I'm lost.
Hold on. I saw you with
Handa before, right?
I'm his mother.
[HANDA]
Mom was excited to come.
But once she finds out
that everyone in the
school hates her son,
I'm afraid it's gonna
break her heart.
[HANDA sighs]
[AKIKO, SUMIKA]
Hm... Uh?
It was Handa's mom.
[AKIKO]
What about Handa again?
[KAWAFUJI] And like flowers
blooming in spring,
the school's love for
Handa blossomed anew.
[HANDA] So, at the conference,
my teacher said:
[OKAYAMA]
Handa's grades are good,
but he isn't very sociable.
[HANDA]
Then my mom said:
[HANDA'S MOM]
I see...
He wasn't like that
when he was younger.
[HANDA] And then I said, "School
is a place you go to study.
I don't need to socialize at
the expense of my education."
Very responsible.
Who could disagree
with that, right?
[OKAYAMA] I'm not asking
for anything drastic.
Just try talking with your
classmates a little more.
[HANDA]
Talk to them? About what?
[OKAYAMA]
About anything!
Y'know, small talk.
[HANDA'S MOM] Like, "the
weather sure is nice today!"
[OKAYAMA] Do you have
any hobbies you share
with the other kids?
Things like that?
[HANDA]
They have no idea.
They have no idea how much
everyone hates me.
I'm sorry, Mom.
[HANDA'S MOM]
I'm sure you'll do great, Sei.
[HANDA] So now, I have to talk
to someone who hates me
about something I
don't care about.
They're asking too much of me.
I guess I'll try talking
about the weather
with the girl who
sits next to me.
[gasping]
What is it?
[HANDA] Is she being
passive aggressive?
What did I do?
On second thought, maybe I
shouldn't start out with girls.
Don't forget about the
student council meeting
we have after school today.
[HANDA]
That guy!
I should say something
nice to him.
[AIZAWA]
Uh... Handa?
Good work.
Oh. It's nothing.
I do this because I enjoy it,
so it's no work at all!
[HANDA] Aw jeez.
I made it really awkward.
That was condescending,
wasn't it?
He must think I'm completely
full of myself.
[AIZAWA]
I work so hard,
but that was the first time
anyone's complimented me!
[HANDA] Take it easy.
Just be more friendly next time.
Check it out, am I
adorable or what?
Oh my gosh, Reo, you
are such a big doofus.
[HANDA]
I see...
Being goofy can help
endear you to people.
[REO]
Aw, crap.
We were making so much noise,
Handa had to retreat
into his shell.
I'm sorry!
[HANDA]
Well, that didn't work.
[BOY STUDENT 4E]
C'mon, Tsutsui!
The punks at Kuro High
are beating us up
and taking our money!
[BOY STUDENT 4F]
Help us!
I already told you, I'm not
fighting thugs anymore.
[HANDA]
It's that big, angry guy.
I only use these fists if
the right person asks me.
[HANDA]
He's kind of scary.
But I did okay the last
time I talked to him.
[TSUTSUI]
Maybe I should fight those guys.
Uh?
[TSUTSUI]
Uh...
[HANDA] All I have to do is say,
"The weather's nice today.
How 'bout you open
the window?" Easy.
[TSUTSUI]
Did I piss him off, maybe?
No,
this is the face of a man with
something important to say.
You want me to take out those
punks from Kuro High, don't you?
I, uh--
[TSUTSUI]
Whatever it is, I'll do it!
I'll give my life for you,
if that's what it takes.
Nice weather today, huh?
Yeah. Perfect weather
for a brawl, right?
[HANDA whimpers] That's what
this guy does on a nice day?
Well, I've come this far.
I can't back down now.
[clears throat] The window.
[TSUTSUI] Does he want me
to... Open the window?
No, the window is a metaphor!
A wall that I must break through
with the strength of my resolve!
[TSUTSUI] I ain't afraid of
nothing, not even expulsion!
Watch this!
[REO] What the hell
are you doing, man?!
[HANDA] This has been
a complete disaster.
How does everyone else do it?
I can't figure out how these
people think at all.
There has to be
something, anything,
we have in common to talk about.
Huh? Why is there nobody here?
[HANDA] Modern literature's
supposed to be next, right?
Was there a schedule change
and nobody told me?
[HANDA]
Uh?
[KONDO]
Uh.
Handa. This is awkward.
[HANDA]
Lucky me!
[KONDO] What, did he not notice
when the entire class left?
[KONDO]
He's following me, isn't he?
[HANDA] He saved me!
How can I ever repay him?
Well, the least I can do
is start up a conversation.
Okay, think. What do
we have in common?
[HANDA]
Japan.
[KONDO]
Uh? Wha...?
Japan is a nice place to live.
[KONDO]
Huh?
Is that... supposed
to be a question...?
I mean. I guess?
[HANDA]
It was too general!
Too vague! I knew it!
[HANDAS chattering]
[HANDA]
It'd be weird enough
if a friend said
something like that,
but I don't even know
this guy's name!
It is nice, huh?
[gasps]
I mean, I've never
been abroad before,
so I wouldn't really know.
[gasps]
Yep, that's what I thought.
Japan really is a
wonderful place.
[HANDA]
Ha! I knew I could do it!
Uh... I think I understand
Handa even less now.
[HANDA] Try not to be
shocked by this, Mom.
[HANDA'S MOM]
What is it, Sei?
[HANDA] Today, I talked
with one of my classmates!
Oh, good for you.
Now, be careful,
the soup is hot.
I found something we
both had in common
and he replied back to me
and everything! [laughs]
Well, that's nice.
[KAWAFUJI]
After seeing his mother's
overwhelming lack of interest,
Handa realized that his
hard-fought triumph
really wasn't anything
special at all.
This one is a little more
blunt than I'm used to.
Usually, it's like...
Or maybe this...
Or like this even...
[KAWAFUJI]
Next time,
"Handa- kun and the
Student Council."
"Handa- kun and Memory Loss."
You're gonna love it.