[STUDENTS chattering]
[VICE PRINCIPAL 5A]
Ladies.
Those skirts are looking
a little short.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENTS gasping]
[GIRL STUDENT 4B gasps]
Hey! Where you lookin' geezer?
Who do you think you're
talking to, young lady?
[SAWAKO] Vice Principal.
I'm disappointed.
I never thought you'd resort
to sexual harassment.
[MOB GIRL 5B]
Big sister!
[MOB GIRL 5C]
Aw! She's here!
[GIRLS]
It's... Sawako Tennoji!
[GIRLS] And she looks so
cool in a boy's uniform!
What? How dare you, Miss
Student Council President!
They are clearly
violating school rules!
A girl's skirt being a few
measly centimeters short
isn't something you would
just casually observe.
You must have been staring
pretty intently to have noticed.
[growling]
[VICE PRINCIPAL 5A] Make sure
it doesn't happen again.
Sawa!
I brought cookies for you,
they're homemade!
And I knitted this
scarf for you!
[GIRLS gasping]
Thank you.
Funny how when you put
men in their place...
...everyone else is
so well behaved.
[GIRL STUDENT 5E]
How did a gorilla like you
end up as Vice President?
[GIRL STUDENT 5F]
You're so gross!
[SAWAKO] This school will become
a paradise for girls of purity,
righteousness, and beauty.
That is my mission as the
Student Council President.
[SAWAKO gasps]
[SAWAKO]
Oh, great. Sei Handa!
I've been watching him
since last year.
But he only started giving
me trouble recently.
Another disgusting male.
Enemies, all of them!
Just look at that gang of second
years he has surrounding him.
He's clearly been
recruiting for his cause.
[HANDA gasps]
[HANDA] Am I crazy, or was that
girl wearing a boy's uniform?
Must've imagined it.
Yeah, that's it.
I'm probably just imagining
that I have stalkers, too.
Everything's fine.
I love that cool
aura he gives off!
He's the incarnation of purity,
righteousness, and beauty!
[GIRL STUDENT 5I]
How does my makeup look? Okay?
[GIRL STUDENT 5J] Well, your
fake eyelashes are coming off.
[GIRL STUDENT 5I]
Oh, no!
[SAWAKO]
This can't be happening.
This can't be happening!
What is going on?
All Handa did was
walk through the hall!
He didn't even look at them!
But every girl here is acting
like a mandrill in heat!
This is a state of emergency!
Rikimaru!
What do we have on Handa?
[RIKIMARU]
Well...
[RIKIMARU
...not much.
Despite being the talk of the
school, he hasn't displayed
any interest in a member of
the female student body,
or delinquent behavior.
Any weaknesses are well hidden.
Interesting!
[RIKIMARU barks]
Then we'll just have
to make a weakness!
When it comes to the Battle of
the Sexes, I reign supreme!
[bell rings]
[SAWAKO] If there's only
one thing we can exploit
about Handa, it's
that he's a man.
Which is why I've
enlisted the help of...
...you Carnivore girls!
At your service!
Whatcha need doin'? And how bad?
[SAWAKO]
You know Handa?
Every boy dreams of
being with older women.
What I want is for you third
year girls to seduce him.
Going after Handa.
That won't be easy.
We'll do it, but you have to
take us out to Korean Barbecue.
It's a deal.
[GIRLS]
All right!
[SAWAKO]
I expect to see results.
This is it.
Handa! The cougars
are coming to eat you!
[RIKIMARU]
She really is amazing.
Using sex appeal to denounce
sexism is genius!
[laughs] There's our prey!
Let's make him ours!
Eating lunch by himself.
He's like a deer in a
field just waiting to be
inside our mouths.
[GIRLS]
Time to pounce!
Thought you could
sneak up on me, huh?
[GIRLS]
Uh!
Just a couple of stray cats.
[GIRLS]
He caught us!
Oh... What do we do now?
Duh, we bail.
[HANDA]
I know what you came here for.
But I can't give it
to you like this.
The two of you deserve
so much better.
You should be careful
who you approach.
'Cause my meat... is poison.
[BOTH sigh]
[BOTH meow]
Where did you two
come from anyway?
This is what you want
from my lunchbox, right?
[BOTH meow]
That's too bad 'cause,
like I said,
human food can be
poisonous to cats.
Well, you can
probably have this.
[meows]
They're so cute. Must be twins.
[HANDA sneezes]
[CATS meow]
[STUDENTS chatter]
[SAWAKO]
Ridiculous! [grunts]
What do you mean you
couldn't seduce him?
Explain yourselves!
You see, we realized we've
had too much meat recently.
So we were thinking
about trying a diet.
Considering neither of us
have fallen in love before.
[SAWAKO] You what?!
How are those things related?
Who knows, someday,
maybe we'll be strong enough
to eat even poison meat.
I think this means they've
fallen for Handa.
Until then, we'll be eating
our veggies and exercising.
At least they're adopting
a healthy lifestyle.
[COUNCIL MEMBERS gasp]
[SAWAKO] He was supposed
to fall for them,
not the other way around!
[screams] That's it!
Grab Handa and bring
him here immediately!
Amazing!
[HANDA]
What the heck's going on?
Thank you for joining
us so willingly.
For the disorder
you have wrought
throughout this institution,
you shall now be punished!
[HANDA] Hold on a second.
I'm being punished for what now?
Handa!
Why are we here?
I have no idea!
[SAWAKO]
As class Chairperson,
you are supposed
to maintain order.
Instead, you do nothing but
seduce impressionable girls
throughout these halls!
As such, starting today,
you are hereby sentenced
to wear a girl's uniform
for one entire year!
[HANDA]
Uh?
A change of wardrobe can alter
a person's outlook on life.
[HANDA]
Uh?
So by wearing this outfit,
we'll be able to do away
with your vulgar
masculinity at last.
[HANDA]
Dang it.
Nothing she's saying
makes sense!
[RIKIMARU] Listen, it's
not as bad as it sounds.
[HANDA]
Uh! She already has a victim!
Pretty soon, your skin
will be nice and smooth.
You'll feel a rush of estrogen.
Then everything's okay!
[HANDA]
Talk about a lost cause!
Someone should put this
guy out of his misery!
It can be tricky putting
the skirt on the first time,
so I'll help you.
[HANDA] If I can't think
of a way out of this,
the whole school is gonna
be harassing me!
[RIKIMARU]
Start with the zipper in front
and then turn the skirt to the
side after you've zipped it up.
[HANDA]
I'm running out of time!
I don't even wanna think about
what my life is gonna be like.
[HANDA]
Hello, everyone.
I'm Handa.
[ALL laughing]
Nice legs, dude!
[HANDA]
How will I ever live that down?
--[RIKIMARU] All right!
--[HANDA gasps]
Time for your makeover!
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5A]
Ah!
[SAWAKO]
What are you doing?!
Are you ever going
to help me or what?
[AIZAWA gasping]
Don't worry, you'll look great!
[HANDA] I don't need
encouragement, traitor!
[growls]
[RIKIMARU]
Jailbreak!
[SAWAKO]
Everyone! After him!
[HANDA]
What did I do to deserve this?
Also, why is everyone in the
Student Council a lunatic?
[HANDA]
[RIKIMARU]
Wait up, Handa!
[HANDA]
This school is a living hell!
Just try it on once.
I know you'll be hooked!
The Student Council President
always knows what's best!
When I first started wearing
mine, I was horrible to women,
but look at me now!
And once you get used to it,
you'll want to wear
cute underwear, too!
[HANDA]
Go away! Go away forever!
Here, Handa, wear it!
Wear it!
Wear it.
[HANDA screams]
[SAWAKO]
Now...
...it's time to
accept your fate!
We're about to unveil a new you!
I can hardly wait.
Think of all you'll accomplish
in this next year.
Sister.
[HANDA whimpering]
[RIKIMARU]
Handa!
I found you!
[ALL screaming]
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5C]
President!
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5B]
Are you all right?
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5D]
President!
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5C]
Omigosh!
[SAWAKO] Looking back, I've
always hated the opposite sex.
[BOY 5C]
Hey. Get a whiff of her!
Man, she stinks like
seaweed on the beach!
[SAWAKO]
Boys are mean, dirty,
and pick on anyone
weaker than them.
You better apologize! Now!
[BOYS laughing]
[BOYS]
Uh-oh! Seaweedko's angry.
[BOYS chattering]
[SAWAKO sobs]
[BOY 5A] Figures. Girls
just can't take a joke.
[SAWAKO] All I wanted was
to be friends with everyone.
What does it matter
if I was a girl?
Why did they act like
they were better than me?
C'mon, let's get out
of here already.
You better not follow us!
[SAWAKO] All I wanted was to
be accepted for who I was.
[SAWAKO] That's why I decided
to create a new world.
A world where women
reigned supreme!
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5C]
President!
Are you all right?
Say something!
[SAWAKO]
Yes. I'm fine.
Good. That's a relief.
[SAWAKO gasps]
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5D]
But, as for Handa--
[SAWAKO gasps]
How did... I mount him?
When you fell! It was
pretty impressive.
It looked like he was trying
to cushion you before you hit.
[gasps]
That almost makes you think
some guys can be reliable
after all, huh?
[SAWAKO]
No!
Why does it feel like my heart's
going to beat out of my chest!
[GIRL STUDENT 5D]
Thank goodness!
It looks like Handa's
starting to wake up!
[SAWAKO]
This can't be.
Do I have feelings for him?
Have I fallen in love with a--
Oh, wow.
That was kinda touch
and go, but we got him.
So, we should do this while
he's still unconscious.
[SAWAKO screams]
Die, you male, die!
[cries] They're so gross,
I can't take it.
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5C]
You need to get
ahold of yourself, President.
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5D] Yeah,
you're kinda acting like a girl.
[STUDENT COUNCIL 5B]
Uh. She is a girl.
[footsteps]
[AIZAWA panting]
It took a minute, but
I finally found him!
Handa.
Wake up. Hey!
[HANDA groaning]
Where am I?
You're at school.
Can you tell me
what happened here?
I think...
I remember falling
down the stairs.
Someone grabbed me by my uniform
so I'd break their fall.
But everything
else is a blur.
Handa, say it ain't so!
Huh?
Hey. Who am I?
[REO] I can't believe
midterms are so soon.
You started studying yet?
Do I look like the kinda
dude who studies?
Oh, c'mon.
Guys who say stuff like that
are always the ones who
get the highest grades.
And the guys who say
stupid stuff like that to
the guys who are about to flunk
out get a punch to the face.
[HANDA]
Morning!
[REO]
Hm? Uh. Morning.
I guess?
[HANDA] The weather
sure is nice today, huh?
[HANDA laughing]
[REO]
Uh. Sure.
[TSUTSUI]
Uh.
[TSUTSUI, REO gasping]
[GIRL STUDENT 5K gasps]
[HANDA]
Hey. What's shakin?
S'up guys?
[HANDA]
Hey-o! Good morning!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[BOTH]
He lost his memory?
That's what they told me when
I took him to the hospital.
I'm afraid it's the truth.
This is all hush-hush,
by the way.
[sighs] That only
happens in manga.
Is he ever gonna recover?
According to the
doctor, he should be
completely back to normal
within a few days.
Uh...?
Yo, dudes! What is up?
Were you worried I was
gonna be absent?
Well you shouldn't've been!
Because I vow to be here
with you guys every day!
But there's a chance he
might be stuck like this.
So...
Dear god.
[HANADA]
This is unacceptable!
We can't let Handa
become a womanizer
like some washed-up
amateur model!
When did Fake Handa get here?
He was referring to me
just now, wasn't he?
There has to be something
we can do to fix this!
Handa represents
refinement and dignity!
Ah! He's using flamboyant
writing utensils
instead of his brush!
Ah! Look at all of those
glittery cosmetics
he brought that he
would normally hate!
He really is like a
washed-up amateur model!
[REO] Seriously, are you
talking about me?
[HANADA]
I can't take it anymore!
My Handa aesthetic is starting
to lose its potency!
Why'd you even come here
if you were just gonna bail?
Is it wrong that I want
every amateur model in
the country to mug him?
[HANDA]
Hey, you guys.
What's with the loud commotion?
[TSUTSUI]
Uh?
[REO]
Sorry about that!
I guess the reason
you're all worked up
is because of my
memory loss, right?
[TSUTSUI]
He's figured us out.
[HANDA] I'm worried
about my amnesia too.
But it's not like there's
anything we can do about it,
now is there.
Fortunately, I remember the
most important thing about me.
And what would that be?
Duh. The fact that I'm
super popular, of course!
[REO]
Ugh.
[TSUTSUI]
I mean, he's right, but...
[AIZAWA] ...you're not
supposed to say it.
[HANDA]
Now if you'll excuse me.
I really must be on my way.
There are a few kitties in this
school waiting for Mr. Popular
to make them purr.
You think we might get stuck
with pompous Handa forever?
Just thinking about it's enough
to ruin your whole day.
[TSUTSUI cries]
No! Why Handa?
He's the only reason
I came back to school!
If the Handa I love is dead
I might as well drop out!
Don't be like that,
little Tsu-Tsu!
You still have me.
[TSUTSUI]
Screw off!
Ouch.
I don't think we can tolerate
this any longer, men!
It's high time we
put the "force"
back into the Handa Force.
By forcing Handa
back to his old self!
[HANDA]
Good plan!
[REO]
Ahh! Tsu Tsu!
[KONDO panting]
Aw, man.
I'll never make it to class on
time!
[HANDA]
What's the haps, kitty cat?
It was pretty sexy how I just
pinned you against the wall,
wasn't it? Girls like
that sort of thing.
I read that on the internet.
Sure, Handa!
I'm gonna slam my right
hand on the wall, too!
[KONDO groans]
Sha-bam. Right hand slam!
Now what appendage
should I use next, huh?
Heh! Bet you weren't expecting
a right foot slam!
That's something only I,
Handa, could pull off.
Gravity ain't got nothin' on me!
[GIRL STUDENT 5N screams]
Get away from me, pervert!
[KONDO] Looks like we've got
another poser running around.
Poor Handa can't catch a break.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GIRL STUDENT 5O]
Rumor has it
you're changing your
image as of today!
[GIRL STUDENT 5P] Does that
mean normal girls like us
can talk to you?
[GIRL STUDENT 5Q]
What about your "Handa Wall"?
[HANDA]
It's a small price to pay.
'Cause I was born to be popular.
See?
I've looked up to you since I
first saw you in the hallway!
[chuckles] Who could blame you?
Is it all right
if I touched you?
That would depend on where!
Can I get your autograph?
Sure, if you got a marker!
Now, everyone form a line!
I'll kiss each one
of you in order!
[GIRLS]
Uh...
[HANDA]
Huh? What's wrong?
[GIRL STUDENT 5O]
I can't believe
there's
another knockoff.
[GIRL STUDENT 5P] Yeah,
the real Handa would never
cheapen himself like that.
[GIRL STUDENT 5Q]
This one has no charisma.
[HANDA]
Hey, wait.
What was that about? So weird.
They were supposed to start
crying tears of joy.
That's what any rational
girl would have done.
[HANDA] Maybe being popular
isn't that big of a deal.
Or maybe I'm not as
popular as I thought.
What's this I hear about you
giving out free kisses?
[MALE VOICE]
Eraser!
[HANDA] I've got a bad
feeling about this one.
[bell rings]
Oh, so that's why Handa was
acting like a total creep.
Yup, yup.
It's a terrible sight, seeing
him so full of himself.
[AIZAWA]
Eureka!
"To reverse the effects
of sudden memory loss,
the same level of trauma
which caused said memory loss
must be applied!"
Of course!
[REO] For a second,
I thought you were reading
a medical journal,
but that's just manga.
In this case, Handa
lost his memory
when he hit his head
falling down the stairs.
Uh! So he needs to fall down the
stairs and hit his head again!
So in order to fix him,
we need to bonk him on
the noggin with mallets.
I'm pretty sure
that'll kill him.
[HANDA screams]
Stop stalking me!
[MIYOKO]
Handa!
Handa! Handa, kiss me!
[AIZAWA] Well, it's good to see
some things will never change.
[panting] Somehow, I got away.
[HANDA]
Man, this is pathetic.
A popular guy like me
shouldn't be alone,
hiding in a secluded
place like this!
This isn't how it was
before the accident.
[HANDA]
Everybody loved me...
Sei, honey.
Don't you think you should
try to get some sleep?
Would you like some medicine?
It might help you to doze off.
[HANDA] Even if some of my
fans were kind of psycho.
Anyway, that's why I wasn't
worried about school.
I thought my popularity would
make everyone accept me
even with my memory loss.
But it doesn't look like
that's the case at all.
I feel so lonely.
[HANDA]
Huh? And yet somehow,
I feel like everything's
right with the world.
[groaning] Where did this
headache come from?
[screams] What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Handa.
This'll hurt.
But I need you to be
your old self again!
[HANDA screams]
This is a crime! A crime!
Why is this happening to me?!
I'm supposed to be popular!
[TSUTSUI]
Damn it!
I never thought I'd have
to hurt you, Handa.
Please kill me once you
finally return to normal!
[HANDA] He must be jealous
of my social standing!
[HANDA yelping]
I don't want to die!
Wait! Where are you going?
[HANDA]
I'm scared.
Running for my life!
It wasn't supposed
to be like this!
Hey, look!
[AIZAWA]
There he is!
[HANDA]
Everyone's out to get me!
I thought I was popular, but...
it's like everyone
really hates me!
Why does my head hurt so bad?
I just need a second!
[HANDA grunts]
[REO] There's nowhere
left to run, Handa!
After everything you've done,
this is the least we can
do to return the favor.
We're only trying
to put things back
to the way they were before.
[HANDA] My head. It feels
like it's gonna split open!
[HANDA]
Everyone hates me.
Everyone hates me...
[HANDA]
Everyone hates me.
Wh-Where am I?
What happened?
[AIZAWA]
Ready?!
[ALL yelling]
[HANDA]
Well that's... not good.
I gotta run!
[HANDA groaning]
[REO]
Handa! No!
[TSUTSUI]
You alive?
[REO]
That was a pretty nasty fall.
[TSUTSUI]
Oh, cool.
[REO]
He's alive. I'll take it.
[HANDA] I wish I could say
this came as a surprise.
But I've always known.
This just confirms it.
Not only does the
whole school hate me,
they also want me dead.
[ALL screaming]
[HANDA] Nothing left to do
but laugh it off.
[REO]
He's walking away.
You think Handa got
his memory back?
Yeah. There's no mistaking
that look in his eye.
Or that smile.
[AIZAWA]
Because of our efforts,
Handa was restored
to his former self!
[HANADA humming]
Hey, guys!
Good morning!
I didn't think it was possible,
but you're more annoying
than ever, Fake Handa.
[laughs] That's because I
adapted my Handa Aesthetic
to follow his current trend.
Huh? Hey, Handa.
Lovely day, huh?
[HANADA gasping, screams]
[TSUTSUI] That's the Handa
we know and love!
[AIZAWA] He looked at him
with such loathing!
[REO]
It was beautiful!
[KAWAFUJI] And thus, Handa
was back to his old self.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[SAWAKO] These stairs
are far too dangerous.
We should put up a sign
to warn the students.
Rikimaru. Get to work on that.
Huh? I don't take orders
from little girls like you.
[SAWAKO growls]
Oh, yeah?
[RIKIMARU]
Hm?
[KAWAFUJI]
Next time,
"Handa- kun and his
Friend's Friend"
And two others.
You're gonna love it.