Toudou, to your left.
Got it!
Sasamiya!
Aaah!
[buzzer sounds]
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"Brand‐new World" in Japanese]
[girl] Hey, aren't you
Ayato Amagiri,
aka Murakumo?
‐Hmm?
‐Huh?
[girl giggles] Can I please
have your autograph?
Oh, uh, mm‐hmm.
It's no problem at all.
[girl] Oh, wow!
This is so awesome!
‐[Ayato] Here you go.
‐[girl] Thank you so much!
I'll be rooting for you
at the Phoenix Festa!
[Ayota chuckles]
[Ayato] Uh... what's wrong?
Nothing. But it must get
pretty tiring
to have so many girls
chasing after you.
Ayato, you're a little too nice.
It's pretty disconcerting.
Hah‐hah‐hah.
[Ayato] Really?
Chill, ladies.
This guy just went
from being unranked
to becoming number one
in a single go.
Of course he's a star now.
I guess you're right.
Makes sense.
When I became a Page One,
it was after a single duel, too,
but I was only ranked number 11.
Ayato's number one, so he's
much more famous than I was.
Wait, I'm famous?
Heck, yeah, you're famous.
Even our princess here
was a big celebrity
when she became a Page One.
That may be true,
but the hype died down
a lot faster in my case.
Well, yeah, you're not exactly
the friendliest person
to deal with.
Although I am very thankful
for their support.
I only turned them down
as a matter of principle.
I mean, think about it,
why would I have any interest
in helping them line
their pockets?
[Ayato] Huh?
An online auction.
No way!
On the bright side,
at least your autograph's
worth something.
[Saya] It's nothing
to worry about.
You still have real fans here
that truly believe in you.
Like me.
Uh, yeah, that's right.
A lot of kids in my class
are your fans
and look up to you.
I look up to you, too.
Ha. Sure, you say that now,
but what will you do
if you actually draw us
in the Phoenix Festa?
What else? We will do everything
we can to blow you away.
We won't hold back
in the slightest.
We're prepared to give it
all we've got.
Honestly, I've been wondering
how you two decided
to compete together.
Gotta admit,
it really surprised me.
I have a score to settle
with that Arlequint tramp.
I'll make her wish she never
insulted my father's guns
if it's the last thing I do.
And that's why I chose
a strong partner
to fight by my side
in the Phoenix Festa.
When Sasamiya first approached
me to join up with her,
I was a little
on the reluctant side.
But now I know that
I made the right decision.
Well then, wonder how far
your makeshift team can go.
Guess we'll just have to see.
Yeah, you're one to talk,
Riessfeld.
You and Ayato have been partners
for how many days exactly?
Uh... Even so, our teamwork's
still a thousand times better
than yours.
[both sigh]
At least your technique's
on point.
All you two really have to focus
on is just staying in synch,
and building that connection
between you is something
that can't be rushed.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I see.
I now know what kind of training
we're gonna have to do to win.
Huh?
Sorry, Ayato, but Toudou and I
will be skipping out on practice
to do our own thing.
We're going to get
to know each other with
some hardcore socializing.
Huh?
So, um, what kind of exercises
or activities should we do
to get to know
each other better?
‐No clue.
‐Huh?
I have no idea.
I'll give it to you straight.
I've never had to socialize
with anybody before,
so I don't really know what
to do in this kind of situation.
I'd be grateful
if you could show me.
Uh... you really want me
to do that?
Cos I can't be of much help.
I don't have that kind
of experience myself.
That's too bad.
Well, today is our day off.
We should at least take
advantage of that.
Oh?
[Saya] If we do
something together,
we might be able
to strengthen our bond a little.
That makes sense.
So, is there anything you'd like
to do today, Toudou?
Hmm? Well, let's see.
Hmm...
I have no idea.
What about you?
All I want to do
is go shopping.
Go shopping? Seriously?
Uh‐huh. And since
I'm not very good with
directions around town,
if you come with me,
I'm less likely to lose my way.
Sure, I wouldn't mind.
It sounds like a lot of fun.
But if you're worried
about getting lost,
couldn't you just use GPS?
GPS is the worst.
Whenever I follow
its directions,
I wind up
at a completely different place.
I had no idea.
[Kirin] So, what are you
planning to buy?
[Saya] I haven't decided on
anything specific yet,
but it's going to be for my dad.
His birthday's just around
the corner.
[gasp]
‐Huh?
‐Uh...
It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Come on, let's find him
something special.
How about a necktie
or something?
He doesn't wear
that kind of stuff.
[Kirin] Well, what about wine?
[Saya] He doesn't drink
that stuff.
[Kirin] Oh.
OK, how about his favorite food?
Negative.
So, um, Sasamiya,
I've been meaning to ask.
What type of person is your dad?
I guess the best way to put it
is that he's a mad scientist.
Oh! How interesting.
Uh, earlier you mentioned
that your dad made
all your Luxes himself, right?
That sounds so amazing.
How impressive.
Yeah, right.
In fact, ever since I was a kid,
he'd give me a new gun
for my birthday every year. Oh.
What? Is there something wrong?
[Saya] Here. This place.
Do you know how to get there?
[Kirin] Hmm.
Uh, yeah.
I think I can get us there,
but... well, it's just that...
It's totally outside
of the shopping districts.
‐It's just up ahead.
‐Got it.
[murmurs, soft laughter]
OK, I think this is
the place you were looking for.
Thanks for the help.
I owe you one.
Hey, wait, you can't just
leave me alone out here.
Not all by myself!
Hmm?
[gasp] Hey, what kind of place
is this?
Where are we?
It's just a used bookshop
specializing in guns.
They also sell some stuff
off the black market.
Black market?!
This is...
the DK44V model,
and it's even been customized
for the Hermés Special
Infiltration Unit.
[merchant] Well, now, that's
a nice piece of hardware.
You've got pretty good taste.
This gun,
its generator's genuine?
Oh, sure is, but it's a piece
of junk, you can see that.
You sure you want it?
There's better stuff in here.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I'll take it.
[Kirin sighs]
[Saya] Now, that was
a good deal.
So, um, is that what
you're giving your father
for his birthday?
Yeah, it's a DK44V model
with a special generator
that my dad can use.
Hopefully it can help him move
forward with his research.
It has some durability issues
and they didn't make
too many of them,
so even being able
to find a broken one
is incredibly lucky.
It's just what he needs,
I'm sure of it.
Wow, that's great.
I'm glad you found it.
‐Hey, do you know what?
‐Huh?
You get to choose
what we do next.
‐What?
‐[Saya] We already did
what I wanted to do.
What do you feel
like doing today?
Nothing.
I mean, there's not really...
‐Wait.
‐What is it?
Well, um... I don't know,
it's a little embarrassing.
But there is something
I could use your help with,
if you don't mind.
[Saya] Hmm?
[woman singing in Japanese]
Kick your legs up a little.
[gasp] 'K.
[Saya] You know, I never
would have expected
that this is what
you'd want to do today.
Really? What do you mean?
Is it that weird?
No, it's not that it's weird.
It's just that...
Just what?
Well, if you're gonna have
someone teach you,
why did you ask me
and not Ayato?
[gasp]
Why did you start
freaking out like that?
[Kirin] Why wouldn't I?
The question
came out of nowhere.
It really took me by surprise.
Sorry, it's no big deal.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I just want him to see me
in the best way possible.
‐[Saya] Oh?
‐And maybe if I can learn
how to swim without him knowing,
then we can both...
I mean, maybe he'll...
Good luck.
Hey, you're not making fun
of me, are you?
Not at all. In fact,
I think he might even
try giving you a chance.
You are a fearsome rival
after all.
[Kirin] Huh?
I'm gonna get us something
to drink.
In the meantime,
keep practicing.
Right.
Oh, no! Excuse me.
Please move!
I don't know how to stop!
‐Oh, no! Watch out!
‐Huh?
[boom!]
[muffled shouting]
Hey, are you OK?
What the hell...
do you think you're doing?!
Are you looking for a fight?
Because I'm well prepared
to kick your ass!
I'll take you on any time,
anywhere, let's go!
I'm so sorry,
it was an accident!
I didn't mean to!
No. I refuse to accept
your half‐hearted apology.
Here I was, simply unwinding,
and you ruined it!
I am absolutely livid!
Let's settle this with a duel
so I can knock some...
Hmm? Hold on.
[Kirin gasps]
[Violet] Are you
by any chance...
What? What is it?
‐[Violet] Hmm.
‐Why are you staring?
Hey, you're Lightning Blade
Speed, aren't you?
Seidoukan's Rank Number One.
Oh, not anymore.
I'm unranked since I lost
my last duel,
so I'm not a Page One now.
[clears throat]
Well, anyway, perhaps
I overreacted a bit earlier.
But really, what the hell
were you thinking,
slamming into me like that?
Did you even bother to look
where you were going?
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to.
It's just that I can't swim
very well, so I'm still
trying to learn.
You can't swim, huh?
[laughs] Come on,
you must be joking.
You can't be serious.
You're a Genestella,
a former Rank Number One,
and you can't even swim?
How degrading!
[chuckles]
Oh, dear! Have I offended you?
Well, the thing is,
I unfortunately have
a slight stomach ache today,
so I must regretfully
decline your challenge.
I hope you understand.
Of course. It was all my fault
to begin with.
[giggles]
Yeah, damn straight
it was your fault.
Anyway, since you can't swim,
just go splash around
in the kiddie pool
with the rest of the flounders.
Bother me again,
and I won't go so...
Aaaaah!
[Kirin] Sasamiya!
What are you doing?
Sorry I'm late.
Are you OK, Toudou?
I'm OK.
That hurt like hell!
Who did that, huh?
Who would dare
attack me so rudely?
[Saya] I would.
And I would really appreciate it
if you'd stop mocking
my partner.
Did you say partner?
And who are you, exactly?
I'm Saya Sasamiya,
Seidoukan Academy.
Well, I've never heard
of you before.
What's your rank?
I'm unranked.
[giggles]
A second‐rate student like you
dares to be so bold
when you're not even listed
in the Named Cults?
You're the bold one here.
I was watching.
You and Toudou collided
with each other, she apologized.
Now it's your turn
to do the same.
‐Please stop this.
‐[Violet] Come now,
don't make me laugh.
‐Just hold on a minute.
‐[Violet] You're the one that
should beg for forgiveness.
[Violet] And if you don't...
we'll have to duel.
‐[Kirin] You have to?
‐[Saya] We have to?
[Violet giggles]
If you're frightened,
you can beg for mercy.
I happen to be
ranked number 35
at Queenvail Girls' Academy.
I'm known as
the Strega of Bullets.
The name's Violet Weinberg,
the one and only!
Oh, OK, gotcha.
Then let's just get this
over with.
Ehh! You insolent wench!
I'm going to beat the crap
out of you!
Excuse me,
but you have a stomach ache.
It stopped hurting
just this second, OK?
[bystander] Check it out,
they're gonna duel!
[bystander 2] No way.
That's the third time today.
[bystander 3] No wonder
this pool's always crowded.
It's amazing!
In the name of the idol
known as the flag of envy,
I, Violet Weinberg
of Queenvail Academy,
challenge you, Saya Sasamiya,
to a duel!
Challenge accepted.
[announcer]
Let the duel begin!
[Violet] Since duels between
different schools stay off
the official records,
your loss here won't hurt
your reputation,
so you won't have to cry
when I beat you.
All right, time to show you
what I can do!
[Saya] Thirty‐nine‐type
Lux Ray Gun, Wolfdora.
‐[Violet gasps]
‐Say good night.
[Violet grunting]
[buzzer sounds]
[announcer] End of duel.
Winner: Saya Sasamiya.
[crowd applauds, whistles]
[Saya] Toudou, you need
to stick up for yourself.
Have a little backbone.
Weren't you angry
she was pushing you around?
Not at all. I was
to blame for what happened
just as much as she was.
But that's not a valid excuse
for how she was bullying you.
Think so?
I guess I couldn't see it.
Maybe it's because I've gotten
so used to the way my uncle's
always treated me.
That's no good. You're gonna
have to move past that.
You should have more confidence
in yourself, Toudou.
Confidence?
You're a good person
with a lot of great qualities.
You're not perfect,
but nobody is.
Your imperfections
make you beautiful.
Thank you so much.
It means a lot.
So, um, can I ask you
something totally random?
‐Huh?
‐All right.
Well, I was wondering,
why did you choose me
as your tag partner?
Let's see.
For lots of reasons.
Your talent's a no‐brainer.
Strategic compatibility.
Sense of purpose.
These traits alone
make you a good choice.
But the real reason is,
you and Ayato wield your swords
with the same spirit.
After watching
the two of you duel,
there was no doubt in my mind.
True intentions, determination,
and quiet dignity.
That's how I knew.
We were meant to be
tag partners.
Oh, there's one more thing
before I forget.
Um, yeah.
We're more than schoolmates,
we're tag partners.
You can start calling me Saya.
And if it's OK,
I'd like to call you Kirin.
[Kirin] OK.
‐Kirin, go right.
‐I'm on it, Saya!
Haaaa!
[Saya] Kirin!
Aaaaah!
Burst!
[buzzer sounds]
Can't believe it.
How did they improve
this much in a single day?
Guess we're gonna have to up
our game, too.
[Julis] Yeah.
[both giggle]
[Maaya Sakamoto]
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪
♪ I'm bracing
for the thunder ♪
♪ A twig that
wouldn't sway ♪
♪ In the wind ♪
♪ Hear my yearning ♪
♪ See the crimson flame ♪
♪ Like a ruby ♪
♪ It's the hope ♪
♪ In my eye ♪
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ And I don't see you anymore ♪
♪ I still wouldn't sway ♪
♪ But I'd be missing you ♪
♪ Now don't be afraid ♪
♪ You're the flower
couldn't sting ♪
♪ You can hide in my shade ♪
♪ Or maybe I ♪
♪ Could I be safe ♪
♪ In yours? ♪
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪
[Eishirou] As you can see,
the Kirin‐Sasamiya tag team
is looking pretty promising.
[Claudia] I'm glad to hear that.
After all, Seidoukan
needs those two to do
their best out there.
[Eishirou] By the way,
I hear the Phoenix Festa
brackets are out.
How do they look?
Care to see for yourself?
[chuckles]
There's always a ridiculous
number of players, huh?
[Claudia] Well, there are 256
tag teams competing this year.
[Eishirou] OK,
so our princess's team
would be over...
Oh! There they are.
Block C, huh?
And Toudou and Sasamiya
are in Block L,
so they probably won't face
each other until they're
in the final round.
So it's possible
for either of our teams
to win the tournament,
wouldn't you say?
It won't be that easy.
But compared to the Gryps
and Lindwurs Festas,
they do have a better than
average chance at success.
Well, the Gryps Festa's
Silver‐winged Knights
and the Lindwurs' Erenshkigal
were both on
a completely different level.
Compared to back then,
we might just manage
to blow this Phoenix Festa
wide open.
[Claudia] Actually,
I don't know about that.
[Eishirou] Oh?
Why the lack of confidence?
[Claudia] Did you forget?
At least one faction
of this Festa
may cause us trouble.
Someone from Arlequint, perhaps?
[Eishirou] Ah, you mean
those puppets, right?
Also, it looks like ReWolf
is planning something,
sending someone
just as dangerous.
No way! I didn't expect
to see her in the Festa.
The wielder of
the Gravi‐Sheath Ogre Lux,
Irene Urzaiz.
I truly hope our players are
able to avoid fighting her.