What? That's so lame.
I'm not impressed with Act One.
And those are Tenorio's
big guns?
You've gotta be kidding me.
[Camilla] Well, I hear
the real deal is
what comes next.
[Ernesta] You don't say.
Then let's hope that Act Two
will bring down the house.
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"Brand‐new World" in Japanese]
[both gasp]
Please forgive me.
I... never learned how to swim.
Sorry.
No, this is all my fault.
I'm sorry for dragging you
into this mess.
It's OK.
Those things sure are huge.
[gasp]
What's wrong?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Please don't look at me!
I'm not, I swear. I meant
this ballast area is huge.
Watch out!
[Kirin screams]
‐[Kirin gasps]
‐[Ayato] Look at that.
[roars]
[Kirin] A dragon, feels
just like the smaller ones
from before.
In that case, we'd better not
stay around here much longer.
Haaaaa!
Ayato, did it hurt you?
Nah, I'm all right,
except that...
we're kind of in a sticky
situation here, huh?
Listen, if I'm holding you back
in any way,
‐then just let go of me, please.
‐Huh?
If you should get hurt
because of me, then I...
I couldn't...
What's wrong? Are you OK?
[Kirin] I couldn't
bear it again,
somebody else having
to pay the price
for the likes of me.
[Ayato] It's gonna be fine.
You don't have anything
to worry about.
But, please, I just...
Come on. Any other time,
I know you could totally
annihilate a monster like this,
so it's only fair
to give me a shot.
I put up a good fight
against you, didn't I?
Have a little faith in me.
‐But that was...
‐[Ayato] And another thing.
[Ayato] Don't ever say
"the likes of me" again.
You should give yourself
more credit.
You really are a special girl.
I am?
Thank you.
OK.
[water ripples]
[energy pulses]
[grunts]
‐[Ayato] Up you go.
‐[Kirin] OK.
[creature roars]
She's right,
it is like the smaller ones.
Hey, Kirin, you got a read
on the location of its core?
[Kirin] Well, yes, I do, but...
It's hard to pin down.
It's constantly moving
inside him.
I gotcha. In that case,
time to give it a try.
Try what?
See, I haven't ever had
an Ogre Lux
that could withstand my Prana,
until now!
No way.
[roar]
Aaaah!
That was amazing.
Thanks, I...
Uggh!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Ayato, what's wrong?
Are you gonna be all right?
Ayato, please,
please stay with me!
[Kirin] So, you can only
fight at your full strength
for about five minutes?
‐[Kirin] That's all?
‐[Ayato] Yeah.
But if I really pushed it,
I bet I could go
a little longer.
But why would you want
to do that?
Why would you go
to such lengths just to fight?
Well, there's somebody
that I'm trying to help out.
You mean Miss Riessfeld,
don't you?
[Ayato] Uh... yeah.
I think I understand.
You and, uh,
Miss Riessfeld, uh...
you're in love with her, right?
[Ayato] Uh, I admire her, sure,
as a person and all that, but...
So you're not together, then?
Never mind,
that's none of my business.
I'm sorry.
[Ayato] Uh... no problem.
[Kirin] Then maybe there's
still a chance.
‐What did you say?
‐Nothing! I didn't say anything.
The rescue squad sure is taking
a long time to get here.
[Ayato] So... mind if I ask
you something now?
[Kirin] No, go ahead.
[Ayato] Why exactly are you
fighting here at Asterisk?
To save my father.
He's being detained
as a criminal,
so I fight to try and get him
released from prison.
[Ayato] Huh?
[Kirin] Five years ago,
a man held up a cafe
my father and I were in.
I was held at knife point,
and in the struggle to save me,
my father ended up taking
the man's life.
Normally, this would
have been excused as
a case of self‐defense,
except my father's
a Genestella.
I see. So the charges
against him were more serious.
[Kirin] Yes. Looking back,
even though I was only eight,
I could have easily
taken that man down myself.
But I was a coward
and I just stood where I was,
frozen and terrified.
That's why I must do something,
or it will be decades
before father gets out.
And my uncle told me there was
only one way to save him.
‐So you came here to Asterisk.
‐[Kirin] Mm‐hmm.
I had no choice.
I'm at the mercy of my uncle.
I do what he tells me.
I have to.
‐You don't have to.
‐What do you mean?
There must be some other option.
You didn't really choose
this path.
If you continue, then you're not
going to last very long.
And trust me, this is a lesson
I'm only just now starting
to learn for myself.
But without my uncle,
I couldn't possibly...
There's no way.
[Ayato] You'll be fine.
Because you're not alone, Kirin.
If no one else,
at least you've got my help.
Well, just so long as it's
a path you've chosen
for yourself, that is.
Do you really mean it, Ayato?
‐[Ayato] Uhh!
‐[Kirin] Huh?
‐Oh, jeez!
‐What?
‐[Kirin shrieks]
‐[Ayato] I'm so sorry!
No, it's not your fault.
I wasn't paying attention.
Let's change the subject.
Anyway, I hope you don't mind
my asking,
but I couldn't help noticing
you like to pat me
on the head a lot.
Oh, uh, sorry.
Does it make you uncomfortable?
No. It reminds me of my father.
He used to do that all the time.
I see.
‐[man] Someone down there?
‐[man 2] See anything?
[man 3] Look, there they are!
[men shouting]
[Koichiro] For the love of God,
Kirin, stop making me
worry so much.
Please forgive me, Uncle.
Hmm. Never mind about that.
Let's talk about
your next opponent.
Yes, sir, but first there's
something I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
Just now you said that you
were worried about me,
but were you worried about
Kirin Toudou your niece
or about the Kirin Toudou
you use as your tool?
Hmm. All I'm interested in
is your power,
nothing more, nothing less.
Of course, I understand.
And speaking of power, you were
just with that Ser Versta
wielder, weren't you?
‐[gasp]
‐[Koichiro] I hear he had
something to do
with that recent incident
with Arlequint.
I don't need him dragging you
into any of his messes.
You're not to see him anymore.
‐I'm not going to agree to that.
‐What did you say?
In the short time
I've known him,
Ayato's taught me
a very valuable lesson,
and I believe that there's
still a lot more that I
can learn from him
if given the opportunity.
Come on,
gimme a break, Kirin.
You wanna learn something,
all you need to do is exactly
what I tell you, understand?
‐No, I...
‐[Koichiro] Ugggh!
How dare you defy me, girl!
Do I have to remind you
that I made you Rank One?
You think Asterisk
is some kind of a joke
or that you could actually
win a Festa?
You can't do anything
without me.
Well, I know that it won't
be easy.
Then shut your mouth
and do exactly as I say.
You do want your father
released, don't you?
Of course, but I don't think
your methods are the best way
for me to accomplish that.
Grr. You got a smart mouth
on you, you little brat.
I am terribly sorry, Uncle.
[Koichiro groaning]
I am grateful
for all of your help.
However, I've made up my mind
to start fighting my own way,
from this moment on.
Because I know if I don't,
I'll only live
to regret it someday.
Come back here! How do you think
you're gonna make it?
First things first.
I'm gonna challenge someone
to a duel.
And I will pick
the opponent myself.
That's right.
This time,
I choose my own path.
Ayato, thank you so much
for agreeing to duel with me.
I'm very grateful.
Yeah, sure, but why pick me?
I mean, we just fought
each other the other day.
I chose you because I feel
this is the best way for me
to take my first true step
on my own, like you said.
‐You've chosen your own path?
‐That's right.
Good for you.
But if we're really gonna
do this,
then I'm going all out,
all right?
[Kirin] I expect nothing less.
[Ayato] Of course, it's not
like I didn't go all out
the last time we fought.
What about your Ogre Lux?
You're not going to use it?
The Ser Versta slows me down.
I can't keep up with that
speed of yours if I use it.
And I can't lose to you
the same way.
Julis will never let it go.
‐[energy pulses]
‐I'll use my brain instead.
Looking forward to it.
Seriously. Was providing
a stage this elaborate
really all that necessary?
Of course.
Why wouldn't they?
It's a must‐see match
with the Rank One student.
But even still...
Look, you gotta chill out,
Riessfeld.
Kirin is tough.
Her sword skills are probably
better than Ayato's.
‐Exactly.
‐[Saya] Ah, don't
worry about it.
[Saya] He's fought a way tougher
opponent before.
What opponent?
Who are you talking about?
‐Haruka, his older sister.
‐Sister?
Well, the dude definitely has
some kind of plan figured out.
Wait, what do you know about it?
Not much, but he did ask me
to loan him an Ogre Lux earlier.
Yeah? He asked me for one, too.
What does he want them for?
Ah, who knows? But I bet
we're about to find out.
‐[buzzer sounds]
‐[announcer] Let the duel begin!
[crowd cheers]
Here I come!
It's exactly as I expected.
When I hit you,
it felt like thick steel.
[Ayato] Well, it's nice to know
my Prana's doing its job.
[Kirin] That was also
the first time anyone has
evaded my Conjoined Cranes.
So that was
the infamous technique, huh?
Nesting State,
Citrus Bloom,
Side‐by‐side Wings,
Blue Sea Wave.
In the Toudou style, there are
49 of these conjoined skills.
When they're all combined,
it results in an unbeatable
multi‐hit attack:
Conjoined Cranes.
With this move, I am invincible.
There's no doubt,
I'll be victorious.
Then if you're so sure about it,
I better not hold anything back.
Haaaa!
[Kirin] I've got him.
[gasp]
[Kirin thinking]
Did his Météo arts fail?
Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
Spear Skill.
Ninth Cloud Wasp.
Spear Skills?
That's right!
Did I catch you off guard?
[Kirin] Yes, but that was
nothing but a cheap trick.
No way.
Well, bring 'em on.
More where these came from.
[Kirin] Haaaa!
Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
Short Sword Technique.
Reaper!
This is it!
Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
Grappling Technique Skill!
Purifying Sweep!
[gasps]
You doing OK?
Those were some nice moves.
You really fooled me.
Both the spear and
the short sword were decoys.
I concede defeat.
I've been beaten.
[announcer] End of duel.
Winner: Ayato Amagiri.
[crowd cheers]
[sighs]
Amazing. Who could have guessed
that you'd win?
Congrats, Ayato.
You looked cool out there.
Well, that's good to know.
[screen blips]
Ayato, may I come in
for a moment?
Sure.
Forgive the intrusion.
I brought a guest.
Now, don't be shy.
Um, hello. Pardon me.
Hey, Kirin.
What are you doing here?
[Claudia] Yes, well,
apparently, she has
some business with you.
[Kirin] Oh, um...
if I may be so bold,
I was wondering if
the offer still stands
to join in
on your practice sessions.
[all] What?
[Kirin] Oh, uh, well,
Ayato had invited me
to join him before,
but unfortunately, at the time,
I had to decline his offer.
Well, that's news to me.
Sorry, but just think
about how much better
our practices could be
if somebody of her caliber
joined us.
You make a valid point, but...
Yeah. Iron sharpens iron.
Bring it on.
It's not your call.
And while we're on the subject
of practice, who invited you
to start joining our sessions
every single day?
Oh, would you like to file
a formal complaint?
Because I'm not going anywhere.
Get over it.
I will not be undermined,
you little weasel!
They're like this all the time,
but are you still interested?
Yes, absolutely.
That's great. You're in.
Kirin, I know you're in there.
Come here right now!
Open up the door, damn it!
What kind of idiot are you,
you brainless girl?
You duel without my permission,
and not only do you lose,
but you're humiliated, too,
so is it clear to you now?
You can't do anything
without me helping you!
‐Ugh!
‐I'm sorry, Uncle, I really am,
but I've made up my mind to
fight my own way from now on.
‐I've decided.
‐Shut up, just shut up!
How many times do I have
to tell you to obey me!
[thwap!]
I hate to break it to you,
but she's on her own path now
of her own choosing.
She doesn't have to obey
anyone, not anymore.
Who the hell do you think
you are, raising a hand to me?
I'm not a Genestella.
You sure about this, Kirin?
Don't forget, I'm the one
who covered up the truth
about your father.
If you refuse to leave
this room with me right now,
I'm gonna tell everybody
the whole story!
You don't say?
What an interesting
choice of words.
What the...
Why, you're Enfield's daughter.
Of course, it isn't my intention
to interfere in matters
between you and Miss Toudou.
That said, she is a student
of Seidoukan Academy,
making her an asset
to this school
and to the Integrated
Enterprise Foundation.
Any intention to corrupt her
for your personal gain
simply cannot be overlooked.
And I'm sure that,
were she here,
my mother would make
the same judgment.
[Kirin] Wait, Uncle!
I appreciate everything
you've done for me,
and I truly mean that.
If it hadn't been for you,
I never would have come
to Asterisk
and I never would have met
anyone here.
And so I'm very... grateful...
for everything.
Thank you from the bottom
of my heart.
Uncle.
See you at training tomorrow.
OK, Kirin?
OK.
I wouldn't miss it.
‐Oh, um, before I get going...
‐Yeah? What's on your mind?
Well, there are a couple
of things I've been
meaning to ask you.
Actually, they're more like
two favors.
Like what?
If it would be all right
with you,
apart from our being
training partners,
would it be OK if I called you
my friend, too, maybe?
Is that all? Sure, no problem.
Of course you can.
So, what's the second favor?
[Kirin] Oh, right.
Well, Ayato, um... I...
What's up?
I was just wondering if maybe
you wouldn't mind considering me
as your friend also.
Sure, Kirin, no problem.
Thanks!
[Ayato] Well, we've got
some training to do.
[Kirin] Right,
let's get started.
‐[boom!]
‐[student] Damn it!
I only came along
because he said this
was just a puppet test.
I didn't know the two of us
were going to have to fight
something like this.
[explosion, screams, static]
And that, my friend,
is how you get it done.
Victory may not be
a pipe dream after all.
Course not. You had to know
that I wouldn't have settled
for anything less.
And I was able to collect
some data on our "red flag"
of a swordsman.
[Ernesta giggles]
Oh, I love this part.
Just look at him go!
I think I'm drooling.
[Camilla] Tenorio have
certainly lost face now,
and the fact that you've
acquired this data
simply by watching
their failures,
that's icing on the cake.
[sighs] Now then,
ladies and gentlemen of Tenorio,
and Seidoukan Academy as well,
I humbly thank you
for your efforts,
all for my sake!
I couldn't have done it
without you.
Now, please, sit back, relax,
and enjoy the main event.
I'm sure you'll each be glued to
your seats until the bitter end!
[Maaya Sakamoto]
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪
♪ I'm bracing
for the thunder ♪
♪ A twig that
wouldn't sway ♪
♪ In the wind ♪
♪ Hear my yearning ♪
♪ See the crimson flame ♪
♪ Like a ruby ♪
♪ It's the hope ♪
♪ In my eye ♪
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ And I don't see you anymore ♪
♪ I still wouldn't sway ♪
♪ But I'd be missing you ♪
♪ Now don't be afraid ♪
♪ You're the flower
couldn't sting ♪
♪ You can hide in my shade ♪
♪ Or maybe I ♪
♪ Could I be safe ♪
♪ In yours? ♪
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪
[gasp]
Oh, it's just you.
You startled me, Sasamiya.
I didn't see you there.
‐Hey, Toudou.
‐What is it?
[Saya] I heard you're here
fighting for your father's sake.
Is that true?
Why, yes it is.
That's admirable of you,
very admirable.
[Kirin] It is?
Actually, my father
is the reason why
I'm fighting also.
What? Really? You are, too?
‐I've got a proposal for you.
‐What kind of proposal?
If you want to...
let's team up for the Festa.
Huh?!