Hey, everybody, my name's Flora.
I'm from Lieseltania!
Hi there.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[Ayato, Saya and Kirin] Ahh!
Honestly, Flora, you should
have at least let me know
that you were planning
on coming out here.
[giggles]
But that's not my fault.
His Majesty said
if I kept quiet,
I could get some tickets
to the Phoenix Festa matches.
It sounds like he's
as mischievous as ever.
Bet my older brother also put
you up to wearing this outfit.
Yes. He said if I did,
you'd be able to spot me
right away.
[Julis] He's really
unbelievable.
It's fine. This is what
I normally have on.
But why would you wear
a maid's uniform?
Back home, Flora's been working
as one of our maids‐in‐waiting
around the palace.
Well, actually, she's still
going through training
right now.
[giggles]
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"The Asterisk War" in Japanese]
♪ This is the Asterisk War ♪
[Kirin] I would have never even
guessed that.
This entire time,
the reason you've been fighting
was to help save
an orphanage?
Uh, I really don't think
it's a big deal.
‐So, Flora, I wanted
to ask you something.
‐Yes.
What was Julis like when
she was back in Lieseltania?
Where'd that come from
all of a sudden?
Oh, I don't know.
Just wondering.
Hmm. Let me see.
What was she like?
She's pretty much the same
as she was then.
She was always so kind
and made us feel special.
Then, at the palace,
she was regal and cool.
So she hasn't changed at all.
[giggles]
Now then,
take a look at this!
Here are some of my memories
with her highness.
[Kirin] Wow!
Just look at all of these.
[Julis] A nun at the orphanage
said pictures were the best way
to preserve old memories.
And thanks to her,
all the kids there
started getting in the habit
of taking them, too.
Hey, Flora, what's this?
[Flora] Oh, that's when we went
to the bath
and her highness said
she'd help me wash my hair.
Ugggh!
There. Did you see that?
You saw it, didn't you?!
No, I didn't see anything!
Now, look, Flora,
I have told you repeatedly
that I want that photo deleted.
Oh, sorry.
That's one of my favorite
pictures of you, your highness.
Julis must be somebody who's
really special to you,
isn't she?
Yes! Her highness is
the best role model ever.
And hopefully I can come here
and be a student myself someday.
That way, I'll be able to help
everybody at the orphanage
like she did.
[Ayato] Sounds awesome, Flora.
We've already talked about
this before; there's no need
for you to do that.
But I know if I try,
I can make a difference
in their lives, too.
You're a child, Flora.
Don't worry about those things.
You should‐‐
I heard that the Student Council
president at Jie Long
is even younger
than I am now!
If she can do it,
then why can't I?
It'll be at least two years
before you're even old enough
to enroll at this academy.
And by that time,
I will have helped everybody
at the orphanage already.
I told you last time,
don't you remember?
I'm going to save each of you,
no matter what,
and change that country myself.
In order to do that, I'm going
to win every single Festa.
Or are you starting to doubt
I can deliver on my promises?
No, never in a million years.
Now, that's better.
That's our Riessfeld, all right.
Your goals are epic as usual.
But I'm afraid
you're out of luck,
because my teammate and I are
gonna take the Phoenix Festa.
‐Aren't we, Kirin?
‐Huh?
Oh, that's right, Saya.
And I'm never going
to back down,
cos I'm not giving up
on my wish.
Ahh! I see Lady Sasamiya
and Lady Toudou
must be her highness's rivals.
‐[Julis] Rivals?
‐[Saya] Huh?
[group muttering]
[Ayato] What's going on?
Got a point, I guess.
Huh?
Hey, I'm home. Huh.
Yabuki still hasn't
come back yet?
What about your older sister?
Why don't you have them
find her?
[Ayato sighs]
You're not the first person
he's ever seen wielding
that very same weapon.
Oh, hi, Amagiri.
Hey, how's it going, Priscilla?
Sorry to bug you.
Not at all.
Good to hear from you.
Actually, I wanted a chance
for us to talk,
but with the Phoenix Festa
still going on and everything,
I was kind of worried
I might end up bothering you.
Anyway, I can't thank you
enough for the other day.
Hey, come on, don't mention it.
I haven't done anything
you should be thanking me for.
Thought I'd lost her,
but you were able to bring
my sister back to me.
And I don't know how I could
ever repay you.
Oh, wait, would you like
to come over and maybe have
some dinner with us again?
‐That's enough, let me talk.
‐Hey!
Yo, Amagiri.
How's everything with you,
Irene?
OK. You wanted to talk to me,
not Priscilla, right?
No, you weren't looking
for me, either.
Cos the one who you were really
hoping to talk to tonight
is that bastard Dirk.
What? How did you guess?
I'm only repeating what I heard
that pathetic idiot say.
He told me you'd be calling
here sooner or later
and that you'd probably wanna
try getting in touch with him
about something.
In that case, could you
give him a message?
Tell him I want the two of us
to meet up sometime.
I need to ask him about
Haruka Amagiri.
Yeah, sure. It's just
another part of my job.
[Ayato] I owe you one.
Thanks a lot.
But remember to watch
your back, all right?
Cos Priscilla and I aren't
the only ones
he's got working for him.
Rumor has it Erenshkigal
herself does, too.
[Ayato] Erenshkigal?
[Irene] And I heard
he's got Grimalkin
wrapped around his finger.
Never heard of it.
[Irene] That's ReWolf's
intelligence organization.
Those guys are hardcore,
believe me.
And when they get an order,
they'll do the dirty work
without ever even giving it
a moment's thought.
[Ayato] OK, then,
I'll try and be careful.
[Irene] Yeah, you should.
None of this is worth losing
your life over.
Oh, by the way, I was watching
that last match of yours.
Damn, you were really
struggling out there,
weren't ya?
‐Yeah, no thanks to you.
‐[giggles] And don't forget it.
Hey, excuse me, Amagiri.
Would you mind waiting
for just a second, please?
‐Huh?
‐[Irene] Hey,
what the hell's going on?
[Priscilla] Thank him properly,
remember?
[Irene] I was getting there.
Hey, Amagiri...
[Ayato] Uh...
is something wrong?
No. Uh, how can I put this?
I just thought
I should tell you
how much I really appreciate
what you did for me, OK?
But don't let it go
to your head, got it?
What do you mean?
[Irene] Well, you know, for
that whole Gravi‐Sheath thing.
Listen, I don't want
to admit it,
and, frankly,
since you busted it,
I'm barely even scraping by
these days.
In fact, the whole thing's
driving me crazy.
But if it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be here.
Oh, really?
That's what this is about?
You saved me.
Thanks a lot.
[Ayato thinking]
The ball's in his court now.
So all I can do is wait.
Haruka.
I'm back, Ayato!
Ah, man, feels like I haven't
been here in forever.
Hey, Yabuki.
Oh, my bad.
Did I wake you up, man?
Oh, no, that's OK.
So how have you been, anyway?
Long time, no see.
[Eishirou]
Well, the Phoenix Festa is
a profitable time for me.
Oh, by the way,
I saw your match yesterday.
Looks like you're in
the quarterfinals now, huh?
Congratulations.
Well, thanks, though we almost
lost that last one.
[Eishirou] Come on,
the important thing is
you guys won either way.
It's all good, bro.
Ahh!
So you're probably gonna go up
against the Jie Long twins next,
aren't ya?
Those two really seem
like a handful.
Seriously, their personalities
alone couldn't be worse.
Yeah, I know.
I've looked over
their match data,
and from what I can tell,
those are some fighters who can
hit you where it hurts.
Oh, yeah, because nobody's taken
advantage of Star Senjutsu
like they have.
I bet most of their opponents
have ended up begging
for mercy.
What do you mean
by "Star Senjutsu"?
Wait, that's right.
You haven't had to go up against
a Taoist yet.
Here.
The short answer is,
Star Senjutsu takes the power
of a Strega or a Dante
and focuses on generalizing it
as a technique.
Stregas and Dantes each have
their own distinctive powers,
but they lack stability,
making it a lot easier
to launch a counterattack.
Huh?
[Eishirou]
Fully trained Taoists aren't
vulnerable to things like that.
Hey, thanks. Good to know.
‐[monitor beeps]
‐Huh?
Ayato, I see you're awake.
[Ayato] Yeah. So, what's up?
Um, nothing, um...
I'm actually calling you
about Flora.
She wants to take you
out to lunch.
Apparently, she has
some questions to ask you.
Seriously?
Now, this is only if you
wouldn't mind going, of course.
No. It's totally fine with me.
Really? Then do you think
you could meet us
in the business district?
The thing is,
it's really crowded
around Main Street
right now.
So I think it might be better
to try somewhere else.
So, you guys looking
for a place to eat?
That's cool. I'd be happy
to recommend one for you.
This is a date, right?
D‐D‐Date?
Not even close, moron!
‐Flora wanted to see him!
‐Okay, then.
‐This has nothing to do
with Ayato and me whatsoever!
‐See? Here it is.
[Eishirou] Not too many
tourists, good food.
Nice atmosphere.
Cool place.
[Ayato] Oh, wow, I gotta admit,
I'm pretty impressed.
What do you think, Julis?
You wanna give it a try?
Uh, I, uh... I guess so.
Though I am annoyed that it was
Yabuki who made the suggestion.
[Ayato] All right.
Sounds like it's settled.
Wanna meet up in, say,
two hours?
Fine.
Hey, thanks again.
I owe you one.
Come on, it was
the least I could do.
Besides, having you owe me one
could come in pretty handy
someday, you know.
[Ayato] Just hope it won't cost
too much when the time comes.
[Flora sighs]
That was so delicious, guys!
Just look at you, Flora.
There's ketchup
all over your face.
All right, I think I got it.
[Flora] Thank you,
your highness.
Well, it seems the food
and the atmosphere
really are good here.
As much as I hate to admit it,
guess Yabuki was right.
You should tell him yourself.
It would make his day.
I'll do no such thing.
Cos that guy has managed
to irritate me
more times than I even
care to count.
He's got a long way to go
before we talk.
So, what were
some of those questions
you wanted to ask me, Flora?
Oh, right!
Hold on just a second, please.
Uh... now, let's see.
‐Huh?
‐[waitress] Thanks so much
for waiting.
[kids] Awesome! Wow!
[waitress] Here's
your jumbo parfait!
What is it? You want one
of those, too, Flora?
Yes.
[waitress] Here's your
jumbo parfait!
[Flora] Whoa!
‐Why are you staring at me?
‐Huh? Oh, uh...
I'm just surprised at what
a softie you are around kids.
Well, I can't help it.
After all, kids like her don't
get a chance to be spoiled
too often.
And besides, at the orphanage,
treats like this
are a pretty rare thing.
Once in a while
shouldn't hurt, right?
Oh, but do you know what?
Since you've been sending
some money back home for us,
things have gotten
a lot easier lately.
Even the sisters said so.
Wow! You send money home, huh?
It's really no big deal, OK?
I just give them
my Page One bonus money.
And it's not like there's
something here I really need
to spend it on.
[Flora] Your highness,
your highness!
Yes?
Now open up and say "Ahh."
Ready?
Ahh.
No wonder you wanted this.
It is pretty tasty.
See? It's the most
amazing thing ever.
Oh, right.
Would you like to taste
my parfait, Mr. Amagiri?
‐[Julis] Huh?
‐What? You mean I can
have some, too?
Course you can.
At the orphanage,
the nuns and her highness
always taught us that food
tastes even better
when you can share it
with friends.
Right, your highness?
Well, yes, of course,
that's true, but...
but that sp‐spoon
was just...
Well, what I mean is,
I, uh...
Say "Ahh," Mr. Amagiri. Ahh!
Ahh...
Whoa! This is great!
You guys weren't kidding,
were you?
‐Nope.
‐[Ayato] Thanks for letting me
try it, Flora.
[Flora] Aww! [giggles]
[Ayato] Hey, uh, Julis,
is something wrong?
What do you mean?
I'm perfectly fine.
Now, anyway, Flora,
what about those questions
you wanted to ask?
It's time to get them
over with.
OK.
[Julis sighs]
All right, finally getting down
to business.
Um, where is it?
Where is it?
Oh, great! I found it!
OK. Here's my first question.
Um, I'm sure you two are growing
closer every day,
so how far has your relationship
with her highness gotten?
‐Huh?
‐[Julis] Wait a minute!
[Julis] What kind of question
is that, anyway?
You didn't honestly think that
one up by yourself, did you?
Nope. His Majesty told me
he wanted me to learn more
about the boy who might become
a future member of the family.
Uhhh! Curse you, brother,
enough of this!
Hmm?
‐You won't be needing that!
‐[Kirin] Aaaah!
[Kirin] Hold on!
He's counting on me.
Please put it down!
I don't wanna go back
empty handed.
You'll be fine.
[Korona] Excuse me.
I hope I'm not intruding, but...
could I talk to you
for a minute?
Hello, uh.
Your name's Ayato Amagiri,
isn't that right?
‐It is, but...
‐I hate to bother you like this,
but I was wondering
if you could come with me.
Oh, that's right. So sorry.
I haven't introduced myself yet.
I serve as secretary
to the Student Council president
at ReWolf.
My name is Korona Kashimaru.
And actually he's outside now,
wanting to speak with you.
You've gotta be kidding me.
What in the world could
the tyrant possibly want
with Ayato?
‐[Korona squeals]
‐Hey, it's OK, Julis.
Actually, I asked
for this meeting.
[Julis] Why would you do
something like that?
I can explain later.
Everyone just wait here, OK?
Oh, no, if you're doing this,
I'll go, too.
I mean, we are partners,
aren't we?
What? But he only wishes
to see Mr. Amagiri.
I'm going,
got a problem with that?
[Dirk] Fine.
Bring them over, Korona.
After all, it will give me
a chance to finally see
the Glühen Rose in person.
Of course.
Then, I'll bring them both, sir.
Hey, Flora, I'm sorry,
but I have to do this.
You can get to the hotel
on your own, right?
Sure! I'll be just fine.
‐[Korona] This way, please.
‐[door opens]
Now, get in.
So, you're Murakumo, huh?
Huh. You don't look
so impressive to me.
If someone like you
is ranked number one,
Seidoukan must be
nothing special.
I wonder who could have possibly
given the order
to destroy
such an unimpressive opponent.
Strange, isn't it?
[Dirk] Don't know what
you're talking about.
You're a lying bastard!
Irene Urzaiz already told us
all about it.
‐Give it up, now!
‐Look, it's no use.
Only reason she told us that is
cos she felt like she had to.
‐We don't have any proof.
‐Come on!
Besides, if we don't drop it,
we might make trouble for her
in the long run.
Ahh. I see your wits are
reasonably quick at least.
Well, none of that has anything
to do with what I'm needing
to ask you.
[Dirk] Oh, yeah, that's right.
But let me warn you
before we start.
Just cos you ask a question
doesn't mean I have to answer.
So just be sure
to keep that in mind.
Fine then, but if that's
the case, why are you here?
I don't know.
Let's call it a whim
and leave it at that.
With all you've got going on
as Student Council president,
you're meeting me on a whim?
I kind of doubt it.
[Dirk groans]
[Ayato] We're sitting
in this car
because you want something
from me, too, don't you?
You catch on fast, huh?
To get something,
you have to give.
Without some kind of exchange,
there's just no way
a deal can be made.
All right, fine, guess you pass.
What is it you want?
OK. My sister is missing.
Tell me what you know
about Haruka.
[Dirk] The truth is, I'm not
gonna be able to give you much.
I've only ever seen her
once before.
[Ayato] Where was that?
Eclipse.
[Julis grunts]
Hold on, you've heard
of it, Julis?
Well... yes.
The Eclipse Festa was created
by scumbags
who weren't satisfied
with the other games
and wanted something
more violent,
illegal tournaments
with no rules.
Unbelievable.
The matches were decided
when one of the players
would either lose consciousness
or worse.
Sometimes they died, too.
Apparently it had a strong
following among some wealthy
patrons and managed to thrive,
but that was years ago.
Yeah. Eventually they put an end
to the Eclipse Festa,
because the captain of the guard
just couldn't stand it anymore.
When I saw Haruka Amagiri,
it was as a contestant
in one of the matches.
Wait a minute, are you saying
she took part in it?
[Dirk] Yeah. I remember it well
cos she was using
that damn Ser Versta.
[Ayato] So, uh...
how did the match end?
[Dirk] She was defeated
by her opponent.
[Ayato gasps]
Hey, Ayato, are you all right?
Uh... yeah.
I'm fine.
[Dirk] Well, I heard
she didn't die that day.
Not that I know what became
of her afterward,
but that was the first
and last time I ever saw her.
Oh. I see.
[Dirk] I held up my end
of the bargain.
Now, it's your turn.
Tell me, what does the name
Madiath Mesa mean to you?
Huh?
[Ayato thinking] Madiath Mesa?
Chairman of the Festa
Steering Committee?
Hmm.
Fair enough.
Doesn't seem like
you're playing dumb,
so you can just forget it.
Right here. [snaps fingers]
Now get out of my sight.
We're done.
Hold it. There's just one thing
I can't figure out.
How did you find us?
Cos you knew exactly
where we were.
[Dirk] Huh?
We only decided to go
to that restaurant
a couple of hours
before we left.
I mean, I could understand
if we'd made a reservation,
but how did you track us
with such short notice?
Idiot.
What the hell makes you
think I have to give you
an answer to that?
[Korona]
Uh, come to think of it,
when I went
to pick up Mr. Amagiri
and Ms. Riessfeld before,
there was an adorable
little girl who was sitting
at the table with them.
Seriously, she looked
like a doll.
I wonder who she was, anyway.
Wait, what did you say?
[Korona] I didn't see her listed
in any of the data you gave me,
but she seemed pretty tiny.
And I don't remember seeing
a school emblem anywhere,
so I doubt if she's
a student at Asterisk.
[Dirk] Hmm.
One more thing.
That girl was even wearing
a little maid's uniform.
I couldn't believe
she really had one on!
But I have to admit,
she looked so cute!
[Korona giggles]
[Dirk] Interesting.
Tell me more about her.
[Haruka Chisuga singing
"Words of Love" in Japanese]