[Aldy] I've been waiting
a long time for this,
Ayato Amagiri.
You have no clue how much
I've been looking forward
to this day.
I've heard astounding things
about you from my master
and have high expectations
for this battle to be
quite the challenge.
Kirin Toudou left an impression
and I was inspired.
Can you do the same?
Show me you're a true warrior!
Unfortunately, that's not
something I can guarantee.
But just know this.
We will be victorious.
That's a promise.
[Aldy] Hah hah!
We'll see about that.
I only hope that you two
live up to my expectations
and are worthy
of my respect as‐‐
‐[Aldy] Uggh!
‐[Rimsy] You walking scrapyard.
[Rimsy] Your body is inefficient
enough as it is without you
running your mouth like that.
Stop the inane chatter, already.
And if you don't, I'll make sure
you never open that mouth
of yours again.
[Aldy] Ugggh!
Why must I stop talking
when you're obviously speaking
far more than I am?
And not only that but my mouth
doesn't even open!
[Rimsy] That's just what I'm
talking about, you and that
insolent mouth of yours.
Who do those two
think they are, comedians?
[Ayato chuckles]
You know, the way I see it,
the two of us are actually
pretty lucky to be
facing them in the finals.
Why is that?
Because we can
attack those things
without holding back at all.
Guess you're right.
They truly are worthy opponents,
aren't they?
Whoa! Amagiri's ready
for battle!
And it looks like
he's not using the Ser Versta
in this match, either.
[Tram] Well, if the rumors
are true, then it's more like
he can't use it.
[Meeko] That's right, Tram.
Word on the street is,
he's applied for an emergency
freezing process.
[Tram] There's no doubt
how hard the Ser Versta
can be on its wielder.
There may also be some issues
we just don't know about.
I just assumed he didn't have it
during the semifinal
because he'd sent it in
for routine maintenance.
I have a souvenir
you can take home.
You can make your decision
after seeing it.
But seriously?
Can you even believe it?
What a tacky souvenir.
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"The Asterisk War" in Japanese]
♪ This is the Asterisk War ♪
[Meeko] Is everybody ready?
Believe it or not, it's time
for the very last match
of the Phoenix Festa!
Now, which of our teams
will make it out as champions?
Phoenix Festa final match.
Battle...
[crowd cheers]
...begin!
‐[Ayato] OK, let's go!
‐[Julis] Right.
[Aldy] Oho!
[Meeko] Oho! What a bold move
by the Amagiri‐Riessfeld team!
[Tram] It looks like they're
both planning to go after Aldy,
thinking they can crush him
right out of the gate.
Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
Second Sword!
Nine‐Fanged Sword!
[Aldy chuckles]
Unfortunately for you, I've
collected data on that move.
I thought you would.
‐[Julis] Primrose!
‐[Aldy groans]
[Ayato] Amagiri Shinmei...
[Rimsy] You must think you have
this under control,
to leave me by the wayside.
[Ayato] Don't worry,
we haven't forgotten about you.
[Ayato]
So, assuming we're going
after Aldy together,
what about Rimsy?
What do you think we should
do about her?
[Julis] We're going
to have to use
your state of Vijñana.
Yeah, good idea.
It might actually work out.
I should be able to get a read
on the whole arena that way.
That's what I thought.
Since you can pick up on Rimsy
and my movement simultaneously,
we can focus on Aldy.
[Ayato] Julis!
[Ayato thinking] Now we have
a much better chance
of fighting two against one.
Whoa! That just can't
be possible.
What can't be possible?
[Tram] Their evasion technique.
It looked almost as if
Amagiri was maneuvering
Riessfeld away.
[Meeko] Oh, wow!
[Tram] But he'd only be able
to do something like that
if he's somehow predicting
every last one
of Rimsy's moves.
Now burst into bloom!
Livingstone Daisy!
Ayato, it's time to bombard him!
‐Let's get to work!
‐Go!
[Aldy groans]
This is such a waste of time.
[Ayato] Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
Second Sword.
Ten Linked Thistles!
‐[Aldy] Huh?
‐[Julis] Got him!
[Julis] I've been waiting
for this moment.
Come out...
Gloriosa!
[Aldy groans]
[Aldy] Is that all you've got?
‐[crowd cheers]
‐[Julis] Wow! That armor's
pretty incredible.
It didn't work.
We'll have to regroup.
[Julis] We need a plan.
They're not going to fall
for the same trick twice.
[Ayato] We really needed to
take him out with that attack.
[Ayato thinking] If I had
the Ser Versta...
[Rimsy] I understand.
Their plan was to attack me.
By doing so,
they drew away your barrier
to create an opening.
[Aldy] What?
You mean they went through
all of that trouble
as part of their strategy?
[Rimsy thinking] However,
because of this tin brain's
durable armor,
their approach
completely fell apart.
[Aldy chuckles]
[Aldy] Wonderful!
That was a truly
wonderful combination,
Ayato Amagiri,
and Julis‐Alexia von Riessfeld
as well, of course.
Today more than yesterday,
and with every passing moment,
without question we've grown
stronger and we've evolved.
But even so, you two have
somehow managed to surpass us.
You have even forced us
to show our hand and reveal
the ace up our sleeve
much sooner than we had
expected.
There it is, ladies and gents.
Sounds like Aldy's ready
to go full throttle.
Could this possibly mean
we're about to see
Aldy and Rimsy's fusion
in part of this epic battle?
[Aldy] I thought
we should have started out
with our special move,
but as usual, you just had
to veto me, didn't you?
Of course, I did.
After all, our master did
tell us to make sure to choose
the opportune moment to attack.
[sighs]
Although using that technique
looks like our best choice,
if we truly wish to win
this battle.
Good luck using
that fusion thing of yours.
It takes forever to prepare
and we don't plan
on passing up this shot.
You believe we're not prepared?
You really think our master
wouldn't have planned for this?
Ruin‐Sharif.
Mode: Wolkenwurf.
[Julis] Not this time!
Now maximum...
We've gotta get moving, Julis!
[Aldy laughs]
Let's get this started!
[Rimsy] ACM Unit.
First External Armor.
Preparing to purge
all Luxes.
Ceding Limit Control.
[Aldy] Ahh! It's time!
Here we go!
Start linking!
We can't let them finish!
[Meeko] Amagiri's charging in
with a courageous
last‐ditch effort.
[Tram] It's a desperate move
to prevent the fusion
from completing.
How unfortunate, Ayato Amagiri.
[Ayato] Hyaaa!
[Meeko] Camilla Pareto,
badge broken!
‐[boom!]
‐[crowd cheers]
[Aldy] Looks like you were just
a moment too late.
The fusion has completed.
[Rimsy] Seriously?
I'll leave it up to you
to finish this.
[Aldy] Right.
I'll take care of them.
OK, now show me what kind
of warrior you truly are.
Are you ready?
[whimpering]
All right, let me go first.
[Kirin gasps]
[Kirin] Flora!
[muffled shouting]
Let's get you out of here.
[muffled scream]
[Kirin thinking] Judging from
the Shadows on the first floor,
it must be someone
who uses them as a weapon.
If so, this place is perfect
for our enemy.
It's so dark,
he could use his power
to strike from anywhere.
Now, where is he?
‐Interesting.
‐[Kirin gasps]
Kirin Toudou, huh?
They must be taking this
pretty seriously
if they sent you.
[Kirin] You're the kidnapper,
aren't you?
[kidnapper] Hmm.
‐[muffled scream]
‐Please, you don't
have to do this!
[kidnapper] If you get
in my way, this girl
may never see tomorrow.
If you hurt her, then we're
going to take you down.
[kidnapper] Give it your
best shot, but there's one thing
you really should know.
You can go ahead and threaten me
all you want,
because it doesn't matter
what happens to me.
[muffled scream]
First, toss away your weapon.
[Saya] Kirin!
[whimpers]
[kidnapper] Who's the sniper?
Saya Sasamiya, huh?
Hurry up and take Flora!
Got it!
You won't touch her!
Thanks for the backup.
That was a close one.
Come on, we'll get you out.
‐[Kirin groans]
‐[Flora] Lady Toudou!
‐[Saya] You OK?
‐[Kirin] Don't worry, I'm fine.
Now we just have to get Flora
out of here.
But, Lady Toudou, you're...
I need you to run through
that door for me, OK?
Hmm... yes.
[gasp]
[Kirin thinking] He's strong.
[kidnapper thinking]
This game's over.
‐[Kirin gasps]
‐Watch out!
[screams]
[Saya] Kirin!
[kidnapper] Don't move
another muscle.
You're bleeding out.
If you don't have that
treated immediately,
it'll be a slow death.
‐[Kirin] I'm not... finished.
‐[kidnapper scoffs]
[kidnapper] What else
could you possibly do?
[Kirin] You'll find out.
[kidnapper]
What's this technique?
[Kirin] Toudou‐style
art of sword drawing.
[kidnapper gasps]
[kidnapper groans]
The Folded Wing.
[kidnapper] What the hell?!
Get ready.
[kidnapper] Impossible!
That illusion showed me...
my death?!
[Kirin sighs]
[kidnapper] Remarkable skill,
but it's still not good enough.
[Saya] Oh, really?
How about this?
[whimpering, panting]
[Saya] Kirin! Hang in there.
[Flora] Lady Toudou!
Lady Toudou!
Are you OK? Say something!
[Kirin thinking] Wait a minute.
Ayato and Julis
have a match right now.
I wonder how that's going.
[boom!]
Hyaaa!
[Aldy chuckles]
[Aldy] Is this your best?!
I expect more from you.
Ayato!
Burst into bloom! Primrose!
‐[Aldy] Hmm!
‐What the hell?
How can this even be happening?
He's definitely more powerful
than before.
Seriously,
it doesn't make sense.
Since the semifinals,
he's on a whole different level.
[Julis] I know.
He hasn't even had to use
multiple defense barriers
like he did
in previous matches.
[Aldy chuckles]
This surging power,
it has become mine to harness.
And now that I have learned
to control it, I will use it
to crush any opponent.
I've never felt so free!
I've never felt so energized!
My master granted me this power
and with it I have reached
my true potential!
His true potential, huh?
Hey, Julis, this might
sound crazy,
but what if this is just Aldy
without all of his powers
being sealed away?
Like how your powers
were sealed away?
It's not entirely impossible,
but...
why would he go through
so much...?
[Aldy] All right, are you ready?
Let's see how you fare
against my...
[Ayato] Not good!
[Aldy] ... Wolnir Hammer!
Here it comes,
now get ready to move.
Seems his hammer's power's
been increased, too.
[Aldy chuckles]
[Aldy] Come on!
I'm not even close
to finished with you.
Hyaaa!
‐There's no cool‐down period?
‐Don't just stand there, run!
[Aldy] Hyaaa!
You think you can just keep
running from all my attacks?
[energy pulses]
[Julis] What the hell?
[Ayato] Oh, crap!
[Aldy chuckles]
[Aldy] You won't be escaping
my next attack so easily.
Wolnir Hammer!
Fire!
Burst into bloom!
Anthurium!
[Ayato] Julis,
are you all right?
Yeah, but that was a close one.
[Aldy] Impressive.
You were able to find a way
to survive a direct hit.
Now, that's the spirit.
[Ayato] He's got us trapped.
We've gotta find a way
out of this box.
[Meeko] Incredible!
What an amazing showing
of Aldy's overwhelming power.
Question is, will this be
the moment
that decides the outcome
of the final match or... Huh?
‐[static]
‐[Meeko] Hey, come on.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute!
What's going on?
[Claudia] Um... Ahem.
[Julis] Claudia?
Oh, Ayato, Julis, can you two
hear me down there?
I'm glad to say Flora is safe.
You have nothing to worry about.
Well, anyway, go show them
what you're made of.
[Aldy] Wait! What's going on?
[Claudia] Thank you.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Wait. Correct me if I'm wrong,
but that was Seidoukan
Student Council President,
right?
[Tram] Uh, yeah.
Pretty sure that was her.
[Julis giggles]
Can you believe that girl?
I mean, really, she went
way too far this time.
[Ayato] You said it.
Who would have expected
that she'd barge into the studio
like that just to deliver
a message to us?
She's done so much for us.
We can't lose now.
For Saya and Kirin's sake
as well, right?
[Aldy groans]
I have no idea
what that was about.
But it doesn't matter.
You're going to witness
the full extent of my abilities!
Wolnir Hammer!
OK, let's do this.
Ser Versta!
[Aldy] You're finished!
[Aldy] What the...?
[giggles]
[Dirk] Shit.
[energy pulses]
It's time for a counterattack.
[Haruka Chisuga singing
"Words of Love" in Japanese]