Greetings, Madam Enfield.
You're as punctual as ever.
[Claudia giggles]
Good afternoon.
It's a pleasure.
I'm glad to see
everyone looking so well.
Yes, indeed. And now that we've
finally all gathered here,
we can begin.
‐[Claudia] Where is‐‐
‐[Ernest] Oh, yes.
She's currently in the middle
of her European tour.
That diva songstress
doesn't rest, does she?
Though it's par for the course.
[Dirk] If you ask me,
it doesn't make a difference
whether that little brat
is here or not.
Please refrain from insulting
the other academy's delegates,
if you'd be so kind,
Double Sword Overlord.
Hah! All depends
on that bitch from Queenvail.
I mean, how many times
has she been...
[thud!]
I asked you not
to speak that way.
[Dirk] Well, well.
Wanna take me on,
Lord Holy Knight?
[energy pulses]
[scoffs] And what is that
kiddie toy supposed to do?
So sweet.
It seems like you two kids
are as chummy as ever.
Really adorable.
But a piece of advice.
Give the childish horse playing
a rest.
Otherwise, I'll start itching
to join the fray.
[Ernest scoffs]
I believe it's
in our best interest
to not upset the princess.
‐[Dirk] By the way, Claudia.
‐[Claudia] Yes, what is it?
[Dirk] I keep hearing rumors
that Seidoukan and Arlequint
have joined forces
to develop a new type of Lux.
Is that true?
‐Interesting.
‐Really?
Goodness, it would appear
news travels fast.
It's true, we will indeed
be sending some of our
finest engineers to Arlequint.
Are you trying
to pull a fast one?
Secret deals between schools
are prohibited under
the Stella Carta.
And besides that, how would
the collaboration even work?
Arlequint is light‐years
ahead of Seidoukan
in terms of technology.
It's almost as if
they're saying,
"Help yourselves to as much of
our technology as you'd like."
What are your feelings
about this, Mr. Arlequint?
Uh... well, actually...
all I did was press
an approval button,
so I don't really know
all the particulars.
[Claudia] There seems to be
some kind of misunderstanding.
This project isn't
some clandestine deal
or anything of the sort.
Rather, it's an official
agreement between Seidoukan
and Arlequint Academy.
We'll eventually go public
with the details.
[Shuma sighs]
So you're saying that it's
an equal partnership, huh?
One‐hundred percent.
Since Arlequint has
graciously allowed us
to use their facility,
Seidoukan will cover 70%
of the R and D budget.
That reminds me.
Seems Seidoukan had
some internal strife recently
and they were forced to send in
the Shadow Stars.
Could that incident have
anything to do with this?
I've no clue what you mean.
Right.
You scheming little shrew.
I do believe this topic
has worn out its welcome.
Quite. With that, we will wait
for the official announcement.
All right, moving on.
Let's begin the meeting.
[Shuma] Uh, excuse me.
I'm sorry.
It's a bit sudden,
but I need to say this.
There's something that I'd like
to add to our discussion,
if it's OK with you.
Really? Well, whatever
could it be?
[Xinglou] Seriously,
what is there to add?
Well, uh, I want to propose
the use of artificial
intelligence in Asterisk.
And I'd also like for us
to grant their usage
in the Festas.
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"Brand‐new World" in Japanese]
[panting]
[Ayato thinking] This is bad.
Julis is gonna kill me.
[both gasp]
Huh?
[crash!]
[sobs]
Oh no. Are you...?
Yes, I'm OK. I just...
Huh?
[shrieks]
It's my fault. Sorry.
I should pay attention.
No, I'm the one who should be
apologizing to you.
Hang on. There's something
stuck in your hair.
Huh? Where is it?
I can't see!
Hey, just hold still.
Tha...
Thank you very much.
Sure, but I...
Kirin! What are you doing?
Hurry up!
Nothing. Sorry.
I'll be right there.
See you later.
See ya... later.
Uhh! No, Julis.
Burst into bloom! Now!
Livingstone Daisy!
And go!
I see that you're still
relying on cheap tricks.
All right, can you dodge
this one?
Bring it on.
I'll take whatever you dish out!
Show yourself.
Lily Gloriosa!
[Ayato]Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
Second Sword!
Ten Linked Thistles!
[buzzer sounds]
[sighs] I was sure I'd be
the victor this time.
Well, to tell you the truth,
you almost were.
You've got a whole arsenal
of moves, don't ya?
I, uh, suppose so.
Anyway, are you holding up
all right?
I'm fine. I can manage
for about three minutes.
Good to know.
Assuming you can maintain
full strength for that long,
finding a way to deal
with opponents at my level
should be easy.
[Ayato] Wait a sec.
There can't be that many
students who are stronger
than you, right?
Thank you for the vote
of confidence,
but to be honest, I can name
quite a few students who are
more powerful than I am.
Who are they?
[Julis] Well, the Gallardworth
Student Council president,
for one.
His swordsmanship is unmatched.
Not to mention
Jie Long's president
and her monstrous power.
That being said,
she's still a bit too young
to take part in the Festas.
Oh, yeah.
Speaking of contestants,
there is one
that's pretty well known.
Last year, she became
the second person in history
to win the Lindwurs Festas.
I think she was from ReWolf.
[Julis]
She was Ereshkigal Ophélia.
Ophélia, that's her.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Anyway, it's good that we have
at least one thing
in our favor.
You're new at Asterisk
and no one knows about
your skills yet.
Your wielding the Ser Versta
may be public knowledge,
but even if someone has
that info, no one knows
how to deal with it.
It would be best if you could
try using the sword's power
without unsealing your own.
True, but unless I'm using
my full power,
this thing won't acknowledge me
as its wielder.
At any rate, the Phoenix Festa
is a month away.
So don't go revealing your hand
in any meaningless duels.
[Ayato] You got it.
[monitor rings]
[Saya mutters]
No fair. Listen up, Riessfeld,
you're totally monopolizing
Ayato.
I caught you red‐handed.
Just admit it.
I'm fully aware that you've been
stealing away to a secret room
with him after school
and engaging in all kinds
of unspeakable acts.
Don't hurl slanderous
accusations at me.
All we're doing is training
for the upcoming Phoenix Festa.
So, Lester, glad you're out
of the hospital.
Uh, yeah, thanks.
[Ayato] Come to think of it,
what brings you here?
And of all people,
how did you end up with Saya?
I just picked up the little
squirt on the way over here.
Hey, who are you calling
a little squirt?
But I owe you for
getting me here, so thanks.
You're welcome, I guess.
So about that thing with Silas,
there's no denying that you
saved my hide back there.
And, well, you know,
you... you did me
a solid, all right?
‐There you go.
‐[Ayato] Uh, OK.
[Claudia] My, my!
I'm happy that the four of you
have arrived.
Amazing! So this is
the Seidoukan training room
I've heard so much about.
Oh, squeaky clean!
Ernesta, please calm down.
We're guests here.
Oh! Oh!
[Ernesta giggles]
Allow me to introduce you all.
On my right is
Ms. Camilla Pareto
of Arlequint Academy.
And accompanying her
is Ms. Ernesta Kuhne.
‐[Ernesta giggles]
‐So, why are they here?
It's simple.
Our schools have joined forces.
We hope this partnership
results in the development
of a new type of Lux.
And today, these ladies have
come here to sign the contract.
‐Greetings.
‐Clever, Claudia.
Whaddya mean?
In return for not
charging Arlequint for
the incident with Silas,
Seidoukan secured
this collaboration.
‐[Lester] What?
‐[Claudia] Dear me,
where is this coming from?
Deny it all you want,
but first,
tell me the real reason
for bringing these two here.
[Claudia] Well, it's
as I explained earlier.
I know! We came here because
I told everyone I needed
to see it to believe it.
And to be perfectly honest,
I just had to see him
with my own two eyes!
[giggles] The young swordsman
who shredded all those puppets
created by...
‐...me!
‐[both] Huh?
You little brat.
Step away from Ayato
right this minute.
Yes, I see.
This is very promising, indeed.
Hmm. No, not too shabby
at all.
I like what I'm seeing here.
What are you...?
[Ernesta] But don't expect
the same outcome next time.
What's that supposed...?
[gasp] What the hell
did you just do
‐to Ayato, you bitch?!
‐That's not good.
Uh...
[Saya] Thieving hussies
must be destroyed!
[Ernesta] So scary!
It was nothing more
than a little hello.
I apologize.
What you've just witnessed
is the real Ernesta.
Excuse her rudeness.
This isn't something you see
every day.
Three Manadites
forcefully linked in the core
to boost output.
Haven't run across
that design in a while.
Correct.
How could you know that?
Because I'm a specialist
in this field.
Fact is, it's not really
a practical weapon.
First off, the tech was
shelved over a decade ago
for being incomplete.
To maintain its effects,
you'd have to constantly use
the Meteor Arts
to boost Lux output by pouring
Prana into the Manadites.
[Ayato thinking]
Jeez, he did it again, huh?
What's more, due to this,
an interval is required
between every attack.
And from the looks of it,
your model hasn't improved
on that flaw.
Well, I hate to admit it,
but you're right.
That said, I won't stand by
while you sling insults
at my father's gun,
so you'd better take it back.
Hold on. You wouldn't be
Dr. Sasamiya's daughter,
would you?
And what's it to you?
If you are, then that's one more
reason why I can't take it back.
Because of Dr. Sasamiya's
renegade tendencies,
he was cast out of Arlequint.
He was also ousted from
our faction, Ferrovius.
Speaking as the representative
of that faction,
I cannot acknowledge
your father's perverse notions.
‐[clears throat]
‐Now that you've all
been acquainted,
I think we should get back
to business, don't you?
Good idea. Pardon me.
[Saya] Wait. I insist
you retract your statement.
You're not gonna get through
to her, you know.
Although, if you're that
hell‐bent on it,
there's just one way:
you'll have to try and make her.
[Saya] You mean we should
start dueling?
[laughs] Please! She'd never
accept a challenge here.
But just so you know,
we will be taking part
in the upcoming Phoenix Festa.
[Camilla] Ernesta,
we're leaving.
Yeah, I'm coming!
Catch ya later! Bye!
[giggles]
‐[Saya] Ayato.
‐[Ayato] Something wrong, Saya?
I'm fighting in
the Phoenix Festa,
it's settled.
Huh? Well, you know it's
a tag‐team tournament, don't ya?
Do you have somebody
to team up with?
‐That would be you, of course.
‐No, he's my partner!
I've had it with
these ridiculous assertions!
[Saya] Stop monopolizing him.
What are you talking about?
I am the one who
asked him first!
[arguing continues,
Lester groans]
[Lester] What could go wrong?
What's up?
It was pretty rare
to see you lose your cool.
I wasn't expecting you to go
and provoke that blue‐haired
chick like that.
I did nothing of the sort.
I just gave her
my frank opinion.
Anyway, what are your thoughts
on him?
Hmm. Honestly, I think I'm gonna
need a little more data first.
The prez has done his part.
Because of his help, we're ready
for the Phoenix Festa.
Now the only thing we have
to worry about is that boy.
You're not planning
another stunt, are you?
[giggles] You know the lengths
I'm willing to go to.
I'll do anything in order
to realize my dream.
[Eishirou] At Arlequint,
the students are in two groups.
The research class develops
the Luxes,
and the practical skills class
uses them in Festas.
Apparently the research class
has way more clout.
‐Really?
‐Yeah. Get a load of this.
There are factions
within the research class.
They're always fighting
over R and D facilities
and top‐tier students.
Right now the group
with the most influence
of all is Ferrovius.
I had no idea.
[slap!]
Kirin, how many times
do I have to tell you,
it's none of your concern,
stupid girl?
But... but, Uncle, I just...
I don't recall giving you
permission to talk back.
Now, that's enough.
[gasp]
[Koichiro] Who the hell
are you, brat?
[Ayato] I'm not sure
what this is about,
but I don't approve
of raising a hand to a girl.
Outsiders should stay out
of our family affairs.
Disciplining my niece
is well within my rights.
[Ayato] Your niece?
That's right.
I'm Koichiro Toudou.
I'm Kirin Toudou's
beloved uncle.
Now you know, so beat it.
Besides, if I'm not mistaken,
you Genestella freaks
are basically immune
to taps like that, right?
Even if we're Genestella,
it doesn't mean
that we don't feel pain.
I see.
Now tell me,
what's your name, boy?
‐[Ayato] Ayato Amagiri.
‐[Koichiro] Amagiri.
Well now, a rank‐and‐filer
who's not even in
the Named Cults, huh?
Hmm. Ah.
Very well.
Since you have a problem
with the way I do things,
what would you have me change?
You have but to say the word
and I shall comply.
So, whatever I say, huh?
Then would you promise me that
you'll never get violent
with Kirin again?
Sure, no more.
But only on the condition
that you win a duel. Deal?
Seriously?
And your opponent will be
my niece.
[Ayato] What?
‐But, Uncle, no, I can't!
Kirin, you're not
disobeying me, are you?
No, sir.
Of course I'm not.
[Koichiro] Bear in mind,
if you defeat the Ser Versta,
it'll bolster your resume
even further.
I'm so sorry about this.
I, Kirin Toudou, challenge you,
Ayato Amagiri, to a duel.
Please, don't do this!
There's no reason for us
to start fighting each other.
There's only one way to avoid
all of this: refuse to duel me.
Tell me something.
If I do, what happens to you?
It doesn't matter.
I honestly don't care
what happens to me.
I couldn't change
my fate anyway.
If that's the case, then I can't
afford to say no.
You're really a kind‐hearted
person, Ayato.
However, you leave me
with no choice.
Cos like you, I also cannot
afford to lose.
I accept your challenge.
[energy pulses]
Hmph!
Kirin, avoid parrying
that Ogre Lux of his
at all costs.
It'll slice you
along with your sword.
Here I come!
You're very powerful.
I have to admit,
I wasn't expecting that.
Right back at ya.
You're incredible.
[Julis thinking]
Didn't I tell that imbecile
not to get involved
in any meaningless duels?
Ayato is on the defensive?
[Eishirou] Well, well,
if it isn't her highness.
‐Eishirou.
‐Quite the spectacle,
wouldn't you say?
That bastard's been keeping
his moves under wraps
this whole time.
I know, but at this rate,
it's not looking too good.
Well, of course not.
He's up against the notorious
Lightning Blade Speed.
Not only that, it seems like
Ayato still has a hard time
controlling the Ser Versta.
Plus, Kirin's been able to dodge
every blow without taking
a single scratch.
[Julis thinking] How could he
possibly be following
the duel at this speed?
Never mind that.
I need to know how long
this has been going on.
Chill out. I don't know, maybe
around four or five minutes.
[Kirin thinking]
Amazing! I never thought
it would be like this.
[Ayato thinking] Damn it!
I'm almost out of time.
[weapon pulses]
Come on,
you can read her movements.
Dodge at the last second
and strike her out!
[Kirin thinking]
He's panicking, but why?
[Ayato thinking]
I'll dodge this one, too!
[buzzer sounds]
[announcer] End of duel.
Winner: Kirin Toudou.
[crowd gasps]
Uh...
Rookie mistake.
Forgot the rules and got
his badge sliced in two.
Kirin, we'll be taking
our leave. Come.
OK. Um...
Again, I'm really sorry.
Uh...
Come on, we need to get going
right now.
It won't be much longer
until you reach your limit.
[Ayato] Oh, right.
You have some explaining to do.
Why would you take her on?
That girl is ranked
the number‐one duelist
at Seidoukan Academy.
Uh...
You're kidding.
Kirin Toudou
is the school's top duelist?
[Maaya Sakamoto]
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪
♪ I'm bracing
for the thunder ♪
♪ A twig that
wouldn't sway ♪
♪ In the wind ♪
♪ Hear my yearning ♪
♪ See the crimson flame ♪
♪ Like a ruby ♪
♪ It's the hope ♪
♪ In my eye ♪
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ And I don't see you anymore ♪
♪ I still wouldn't sway ♪
♪ But I'd be missing you ♪
♪ Now don't be afraid ♪
♪ You're the flower
couldn't sting ♪
♪ You can hide in my shade ♪
♪ Or maybe I ♪
♪ Could I be safe ♪
♪ In yours? ♪
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪