[Koichiro] That took you
much longer than I expected.
I'm very sorry, Uncle.
You're a timid, incompetent
little brat,
good for nothing
but your swordsmanship.
But in my hands, you'll become
the top‐ranked student
and go down
in Seidoukan history.
Making my perfect planning
a reality requires
your complete obedience.
[Kirin] Yes, Uncle.
Of course.
And don't you ever forget that.
That is, if you want
your dreams to come true.
I understand.
I understand perfectly.
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"Brand‐new World" in Japanese]
So, uh, you are mad at me
after all, am I right?
Yes, very perceptive.
And do you have an idea
as to why that might be?
Yeah. Probably because
of my duel with that girl.
No, that's not it.
You did the right thing.
‐[Ayato] Huh?
‐No one should be used
as a tool, not by anyone,
especially a member
of their own family.
‐Julis.
‐In fact, if you turned
a blind eye
to what that bastard was doing,
I would have been
disappointed in you.
If I'd seen what you saw,
I'm sure I would have done
exactly the same thing.
Thanks a lot.
I'm glad to hear that.
[gasp]
It's nothing, not anything you
need to thank me for, anyway.
I mean, well, uh, look,
I'm still angry.
It's just about more than Kirin
and her horrid uncle.
What is it, then?
‐It's cos you lost, all right?
‐What? But you told me‐‐
I know. It's my selfish ego
getting in the way.
I just thought that...
if anybody stood
a chance against her,
it would have been you!
Though I suppose Kirin Toudou
should be commended.
She's only 13, after all,
just a first‐year
in junior high.
[Ayato] What? Thirteen?
She could have fooled me.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you've taken
an interest in her.
Um, no.
[Julis] Oh, never mind.
With my current ranking
at Seidoukan,
there are still three students
that I can't defeat yet:
you, Claudia, and Kirin Toudou.
[Ayato] Claudia?
She's ranked number two.
Looks can be deceiving,
can't they?
Whoa! I had no idea.
She's known as Parca Morta
and wields the Ogre Lux
called Pan Dora.
With it, she can see the future.
Do you mean, like,
precognition or something?
Exactly. And rumor has it,
she can see up to ten seconds
ahead of time.
Wow!
[Julis] Claudia has
remained undefeated
since she started here,
an accomplishment she shares
with Kirin Toudou,
though one important fact
sets them apart.
Unlike her, Kirin neither fights
with an Ogre Lux
nor is she a Strega.
Even if it's only been
three months,
to have defended
her first‐place ranking
armed only with a Japanese sword
is extraordinary.
So now we'll have to rethink
our Phoenix Festa
battle strategy.
With your abilities
out in the open and exposed,
our current game plan
is pretty useless.
Uh... sorry.
[Julis] Ha.
But strategy can wait.
First we need to get you
a new badge.
Oh, hey, this is, uh...
[Claudia giggles]
Bigger than you were expecting?
These are the Student Council's
recreational facilities.
[Ayato] Um, uh...
So I was sent down here
to get a new school badge
to replace my broken one.
Yes, I have it right here.
Will this do the trick?
Yeah, looks great.
Thanks a lot.
Wait a second, where exactly
were you keeping this, anyway?
[giggles] That's a secret.
[Claudia] You know, when I heard
about your duel with Ms. Toudou,
I must admit,
I was rather surprised.
Well, a lot happened
leading up to it.
[Claudia] With her uncle
Koichiro, you mean?
Yeah. You know him?
He's quite a handful
so it's hard not to.
He is an employee
of the Integrated Enterprise
Foundation Galaxy,
which runs Seidoukan Academy.
He oversees practically all
the student scouting operations
for the school,
giving him considerable clout.
[Ayato] So he's
the top brass, huh?
[Claudia] Hmm, "a candidate
for top brass" would be
a better description.
Mr. Toudou's quite eager
for a position on
the administrative board.
To that end,
he'll stop at nothing,
even taking advantage
of his own niece's talents.
Guess it's just as bad
as I thought.
She is being forced
to duel by that guy.
I wouldn't say "forced,"
because she appears to be
running her own agenda as well.
[Ayato] Hmm?
[Claudia] At any rate,
it should be difficult
for Mr. Toudou to secure
an executive position.
Anyone as self‐serving
and ruthless as he is
can't hope to advance,
not in the IEF.
Only those who've undergone
many treatment levels
of the psychological
adjustment program,
eradicating all
their personal ambitions,
are suited for the job.
You sure know a lot about it.
Yes, well, my mother
happens to be one of them.
[Ayato] Huh?
[Claudia] So, Ayato, what
are you going to do about
little Miss Toudou?
That is a very good question.
‐[students laughing]
‐[Ayato] Huh?
[Eishirou] Yo, over here!
Look who came to see you.
Oh, my. Hello, Ayato.
Um... so what can I do
for you?
I wanted...
to say thank you so much.
Huh? For what?
Well, even though I was
a total stranger,
you still protected me
from my uncle
and I feel very grateful.
And although the duel didn't
really end in your favor,
I... well, I'm glad we fought,
so thank you.
No worries.
I mean, it's not like
I actually helped at all.
That's not true.
[Ayato thinking] It's hard
to believe she's so strong.
[gasps] Ayato!
Shh!
[groans]
You sure are
a dedicated journalist,
aren't you, Eishirou?
[Eishirou, awkwardly]
Yeah, thanks.
[Ayato] So, Kirin, are you
a little nervous?
[Kirin] Huh? Yes, I am.
A little. I'm sorry.
It's just that I've never
walked alone before,
not with a man who wasn't
a relative, anyway.
Really?
Dad was, um...
My father was very strict,
you see?
I get it,
and from what I've heard,
the Toudou‐style training
regimen is also strict.
Wait, you mean you know
about our fighting style?
Well, yeah, sure.
What kind of a swordsman
would I be if I didn't?
Of course I've heard
of the Toudou‐style philosophy.
Like folding
a paper crane, right?
Huh? Actually, the Amagiri
style's an ancient one, too.
[Ayato] That's right.
I'm impressed.
Oh. Well, I couldn't help
noticing that when we fought,
you would drop down
in your stance on occasion
and you slid your feet
when moving into
a defensive position.
You also held the point
of your sword quite high,
aimed at my eyes,
all characteristics
of the ancient styles.
If I'd gotten to cross swords
with you, I'd have learned more.
I... I'm so sorry.
‐I'll be quiet now.
‐[Ayato chuckles]
You don't have to.
You're all about
swordplay, huh?
[Kirin] Uh, yeah.
But that's because I don't have
a talent for anything else.
I don't believe you.
No, it's true.
I'm not smart.
I'm a big klutz
and a coward, too.
But regardless, I know,
as long as I hold a sword,
I can be useful
to someone else.
That's the reason why I love it
so much, Ayato.
Is that right?
Cos like you, I also
cannot afford to lose.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah, sure.
What is it you're
fighting for, Kirin?
Uh...
I fight... to save my father.
Your father? That why you do
everything your uncle tells you?
[Kirin] My uncle has shown me
a path that is most suitable
and efficient to achieve
my goal.
I'm very grateful to him
for that.
[Ayato] Even if he's using you
to further his career?
[Kirin] He's showing me how
to turn my dream into a reality
and he should be compensated
for that.
It's only fair.
The arrangement's
perfectly reasonable.
Well, it sure doesn't
seem that way to me.
I guess not.
My uncle hates the Genestella.
[Ayato] Uh...
[Kirin] So...
I have a question too.
If you don't mind my asking.
‐Ask away.
‐It's about your training.
I was wondering what kind
you normally do.
Since I started at this school,
I've been training
all on my own,
but that's a little difficult.
I mean, I can't exactly spar
by myself.
No problem. You can always join
our training sessions
if you want to.
Huh? I can really do that?
[Ayato] Well, I should check
with Julis first,
but I bet she'll be cool
with it.
That's OK, never mind.
My uncle made it clear I'm not
to fight those on the list.
More importantly,
I'm to stay away from those
with a Page One ranking.
I understand.
Then why don't you come
to my early morning
training sessions instead?
To your sessions, Ayato?
[Ayato] Training with me
shouldn't be a problem, right?
You mean just the two of us
training together alone,
without anybody else around?
Yeah. It's fine,
I'm not on the list.
What's the matter?
[Kirin] Nothing. Uh...
Um... I'll do it.
I'll take you up on your offer.
[leaves rustle]
Whoa! Hey! Saya!
Are you trying to give me
a heart attack or something?
Who was she? Tell me.
Ugh! Come on.
Let go of me, would ya?
‐I can't breathe!
‐So what? Spit it out.
Who were you talking to?
[Ayato] How can I answer
when you're choking me?
Sorry. I guess I got a little
carried away and couldn't
control myself.
[Ayato] All right,
it's all good.
But what were you even doing
up there in the first place?
‐[Saya] Looking for you.
‐What for?
[Saya] I want to know
your answer about being
my tag‐team partner.
[Ayato] Oh, that.
Sorry, Saya, but I've already
teamed up with Julis,
and I can't just go back
on my word.
Gotcha.
Oh, well.
Back to my other question.
Who was that girl?
Her name's Kirin Toudou.
She's from
the junior high school.
Oh. She's the Rank One girl that
you had a duel with yesterday.
‐Yeah, that's her.
‐Unbelievable.
How do you get such
a banging body in junior high?
Life can be so unfair sometimes.
Hey, come on. Now, don't be
so hard on yourself.
You two actually have
some things in common.
‐Like what?
‐Like you're here
for the same reason.
Her dad needs help, too.
I don't know any more
of the details, though.
Her dad, huh?
[Ayato sighs]
[Julis] Ayato!
There's something I want
to ask you.
[Ayato] Sure.
Are you about to eat lunch?
Since you're here,
we could eat together.
Oh, really?
Well, if you insist,
I suppose I am a bit hungry.
Wait, that's not why I'm here.
I wanted to ask you
about Kirin Toudou!
[beep]
Hey, are you sure?
It looks pretty hot.
I said I was fine with it.
And stop dodging the question.
What's up with you and Kirin?
Hmm. There's not much to say.
We started training together
in the mornings,
and that's about it.
Oh, I get it now.
You're still worried that
someone might find out
about my skills.
What? No, that's not it at all.
Oh, never mind.
As long as you keep acting
like this, I'm sure everything
should be just fine.
By the way, I noticed you
haven't touched your curry
at all.
Are you gonna eat it?
Look, if it's too spicy for you,
go order something else.
Are you insane?
And waste all this food?
I'd never!
No, wait!
That's a huge bite, be careful!
[Julis] I'm fine.
This is nothing.
Look, how about I trade you
for mine, OK?
What?
[Ayato] I mean,
mine's pretty hot, too,
but no way is it as bad
as what you ordered.
Oh, wait, you probably
don't want a plate of food
I've already eaten from, huh?
What?
No, that's not the problem.
I don't care about eating
after someone, don't be absurd.
But I do care about consuming
everything I've ordered.
It's my responsibility.
I can't very well
hand it off to you.
Julis, we have to be able to
talk straight with each other,
even about trivial stuff,
or how can we work as partners?
Yes, I... suppose you're right.
Then...
will you please trade
your plate for mine?
Ayato?
Oh, right, sure, here.
Thank you.
[Ayato screams]
[Camilla] Time to wake up,
Ernesta.
‐[Camilla] They're on the move.
‐[Ernesta] Wha...?
[Ernesta] How can I wake up?
I wasn't even sleeping.
I was just deep in thought.
I think better
with my eyes closed.
Right. Then I'm sure that you're
fully capable of telling me
the reason I came here, too.
[Ernesta] Hmm? Let me guess.
The Tenorio guys
are on the move.
We must have stirred them up
pretty good, then. [sighs]
Yes, well, they've already
gotten started.
You'd better hop to it
or you'll miss them.
Quit dawdling.
[Ernesta] Right, copy that.
Coming in loud and clear.
[gasp] Check it!
There's someone else
besides little sword boy.
[Camilla] You're never
going to believe this,
but that Seidoukan's
Rank Number One.
Ho‐ho!
And you're still cool with
launching the maneuver, anyway?
Somebody's
pretty pumped up, huh?
Oh, hey, how's fishing going?
Did you get lucky?
Tell you one thing,
dragging out the Magnum Opus
won't be easy.
That's the understatement
of the century.
Hey, you can't blame them
for being cautious.
But who cares, anyway?
I mean, if they fail,
it's not like we can't
handle everything ourselves.
Am I right?
[Camilla] Seriously.
You sure love gambling,
don't you?
‐I what?
‐[Camilla] You take
too many risks.
[Ernesta giggles] Sorry,
but I can't help myself.
It's lots more fun this way.
[Ayato] Man, this fog
is intense, huh?
Yeah, it's pretty thick.
Though I've heard that
in the wintertime around here,
it can get even worse.
Yeah? The two of us could
probably get lost in this stuff.
Maybe we should just hold hands
the rest of the morning.
Huh? Well, 'K. Uh...
Um, my bad. I was just kidding.
I didn't really mean
that we should hold hands.
I'm so sorry!
I should have known better.
It's fine.
Under construction?
[Kirin] Ayato, I think‐‐
Yeah. There's more than one
of them.
Right. But I don't think
that it's a person.
This presence,
it feels more like...
[both gasp]
[roars]
They're kind of cute,
aren't they?
Yeah.
[creature snarling]
Whoa!
Be careful.
Are you all right, Ayato?
[Ayato groans]
What the hell?
Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
First Sword!
Four Wasps!
Aaaah!
All right, there's gotta be some
way to get rid of these things.
The usual slashing
and thrusting attacks
aren't getting us anywhere.
But I have an idea.
Would you mind if I
took a swing or two?
I'm sorry.
You're finished!
Thought so. It was controlled
by some kind of core.
[Ayato] Whoa, you've got
a good eye.
But I didn't see it,
I felt its Prana.
I could tell that it was
a little off.
I guess I've always been
sensitive like that.
I think you might be a lot more
powerful than you realized.
It's synthetic.
Could this be more
of Arlequint's technology?
Maybe they're behind...
[creatures snarling]
Jeez, I thought
those things took off!
I'll catch you, Ayato!
Are you all right?
Just hang on.
OK. You saved me.
[Kirin] Here.
Let me pull you up.
[both scream]
[Maaya Sakamoto]
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪
♪ I'm bracing
for the thunder ♪
♪ A twig that
wouldn't sway ♪
♪ In the wind ♪
♪ Hear my yearning ♪
♪ See the crimson flame ♪
♪ Like a ruby ♪
♪ It's the hope ♪
♪ In my eye ♪
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ And I don't see you anymore ♪
♪ I still wouldn't sway ♪
♪ But I'd be missing you ♪
♪ Now don't be afraid ♪
♪ You're the flower
couldn't sting ♪
♪ You can hide in my shade ♪
♪ Or maybe I ♪
♪ Could I be safe ♪
♪ In yours? ♪
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪