Sorry to have kept you
waiting, Ayato.
Close one, wasn't it?
[Ayato] Claudia!
Julis!
Erenshkigal.
Orphelia!
[gasp]
What happened?
I guess I must have
lost consciousness.
‐OK...
‐[door opens]
Hey, it looks like
you're finally up.
Hi, Julis.
[Julis] Thank goodness.
You were out for three days
straight, you know.
I was getting worried about you.
Wait, three days?
[Julis] These two were
pretty worried about you also.
They haven't left your side
since you got here.
You should be sure
and thank them later.
Speaking of that,
I haven't had a chance
to thank you myself.
[Ayato] What for?
[Julis] It wasn't only
Orphelia you dealt with.
I hear you had to battle
Gustave as well.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for saving me.
Really?
So, what are you gonna say next,
that you owe me?
I'm pretty sure
we're past that point.
Yeah, well, just wanted you
to know I appreciate it.
OK, then, so could you
tell me about it?
You know, about her.
What's the story with you
and Orphelia Landlufen?
[Julis] You remember this,
don't you?
Of course.
That's the handkerchief that
everyone at the orphanage
decorated.
And then your best friend
sewed it together
for you, right?
That's...
[Therese] The mere idea
of fighting disgusted her.
She was truly
a kindhearted girl.
[Ayato] You don't mean...?
That's right.
This was a gift from...
Orphelia.
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"The Asterisk War" in Japanese]
♪ This is the Asterisk War ♪
[Julis]What's so fun
about playing with plants
and getting your hands dirty?
[Orphelia] I'm not
playing with them,
I'm showing them that I care.
If you show plants
that you love them,
they'll love you back.
But if you don't,
they'll leave you.
[Julis] I don't understand.
How could they leave people?
[Orphelia] Sometimes plants that
aren't even sick just die.
It's cos they get tired
of dealing with humans.
[giggles]
[Julis] Caring for plants
brought her more joy
than anything else
in the world,
and she couldn't even
kill an insect.
When her flowers
would start blooming,
she'd always get so excited.
[Ayato] Then...
what happened the other day?
[Julis] Remember
that ruined building?
It was the result of Orphelia
going berserk one day.
It used to be a lab
for the Integrated
Enterprise Foundation,
called Frauenlob
at the time.
The lab was run
by an Arlequint student
called Magnum Opus.
Her research was ghastly.
Especially her research into
manufacturing Genestella.
[Ayato gasps]
[Julis] They had a guinea pig
for their experiments,
a child taken from
the orphanage as collateral
for their staggering debt.
Orphelia!
As a result, Orphelia,
who was never a Genestella,
is now known as the most
powerful Strega in the world.
Wait a sec, you mean
the experiment was successful?
[Julis] Not really.
The ground below
the abandoned lab is rotten.
Not even one blade of grass
will grow there.
It's the price she had to pay
for her powers.
She can't even get close
to the flowers
that she loved
to watch bloom.
I saw her again
when I came to Asterisk
and she'd become
completely different.
She'd already given up
on her past and herself,
abandoning everything.
You know just how powerful
she is.
But that strength
is a double‐edged sword.
The more she uses her
abilities,
the more of her life
gets taken away.
I tried to stop her
from being so reckless, but...
Hyaaaaa!
...it didn't work.
You know the rest.
I'm really sorry.
I never intended for you to get
dragged into all of this.
But I'm going to finish it,
and I'm doing it on my own.
Orphelia wouldn't accept
the defeat otherwise.
Understood.
As for you two
playing possum over there,
I'm counting on you
to follow through as well.
Looks like we're busted.
[giggles]
Sorry for eavesdropping.
Forget about it.
All right, back to business.
We need to make Gustave Marlow
our top priority.
[Kirin] Absolutely.
Has he made any attack
since the last time he appeared?
No. We've got that part
under control.
The threat level's been raised
throughout the capital
and we've boosted
our police presence.
I've also had some of our
forces sent to the orphanage
for good measure.
He could show up anywhere,
so we have to be vigilant.
Princess! Princess!
It's so horrible!
Flora, what's wrong?
Why are you panicking?
Oh, Your Highness,
the whole city is in chaos.
There are creatures
attacking us!
They're these
giant lizard things
with wings about this big!
They appeared out of nowhere!
[Julis] OK.
Are they attacking people?
[Flora]
No, not really attacking,
but that's cos our entire
police force has been sent
into the city to deal with them.
So far they've stopped
a lot of the damage.
Wait. The entire police force?
That means...
What about the unit
guarding the orphanage?
[Flora] Well,
from what I've been told,
they've all been reassigned
to protect the city.
[Julis] Damn!
Please, Julis,
you've gotta calm down!
This is exactly
how Gustave planned it.
He knew Lieseltania's police
would abandon the orphanage.
And he knew
if it was left unguarded,
that would be the perfect
diversionary tactic
to draw us out.
There's no doubt in my mind
that he's lying in wait
somewhere in the slums.
If I don't go out there
and face him right now,
the orphanage will be
completely destroyed.
[gasp]
[Julis] This isn't
anyone's problem but mine.
I'll handle it on my own.
Do you expect us to sit here
and do nothing?
‐[Ayato] Come on.
‐[Kirin] He's right, you know.
You're not alone in this.
He's coming after each of us,
remember?
We all have to stay together
on this one.
Very well then.
If that's the case,
I have an idea.
You'll need
to follow my plan exactly.
Gustave Marlow!
[Gustave] Ha ha!
[energy pulses]
[Gustave] Well, well,
if it isn't Princess Julis.
Your Highness.
I am beyond humbled that you
would come all this way
just to meet
with little old me.
If you've done anything
to that orphanage,
you'll regret it!
[Gustave] You may rest assured
the orphanage will remain safe,
as long as it helps me catch
my prey, that is.
So, without further ado,
let's get your friends
to join our party.
‐Hah!
‐[snaps fingers]
[energy pulses]
Hold on, is that a hydra?
[Gustave] Yes, Your Highness,
that is indeed a hydra.
Isn't he every bit as
frightening...
no, he's more frightening
than what you've read about
in mythology, don't you think?
Now then, having lured
in my prey, I've no use
for that orphanage.
All that's left is
to finish you off without delay.
It's been fun, but it's time
for me to be on my way.
Do enjoy your last moments.
[Julis] Get back here!
[Ayato] Julis!
‐[Julis] Sorry about that.
‐[Ayato] No, don't worry
about it.
[Julis] Damn it.
If I want to protect the city,
I've got to find a way
to stop this thing.
[Ayato] The police
won't be coming.
We've got to do something
about it ourselves.
Julis, can you help
evacuate the civilians?
Are you crazy?
You can't stop it
all by yourself.
I'll do what I can.
Besides, Saya should be done
with her preparations
pretty soon.
You can't do this!
[Ayato] You're more familiar
with this area than I am,
and everyone here would
listen to you, wouldn't they?
All right, fine.
Just try and be careful
out here, OK?
So there's no doubt
about it, huh?
[Eishirou] None.
I can also send you
the evidence I've gathered
if you need me to.
Thank you, but right now
that won't be necessary.
[Ayato thinking] That's as far
as you're gonna go!
Time to stop this!
Arrrgh!
Heh!
Yeah!
[Ayato thinking]
Its head regenerates,
just like in the myth!
[Saya] Hey, Ayato.
Let's kick some butt.
Thanks for the save.
That was a close one.
‐We're taking down that dragon
with all the heads, right?
‐Yeah.
[Saya] So what's the plan?
[Ayato] Gustave really
went all out when he
made this monster.
Just like in ancient mythology.
All of the Hydra's heads
will keep on growing back
until we manage to chop off
the one in the middle.
So we'd better
take him out fast.
Exactly, and we can
both stay in contact
through this monitor.
OK, then, let's go.
Time to bring it!
Hyaaaa!
[roar]
All right, that's two.
Hey, four o'clock!
Now it's four down!
[Saya] There's one on your tail!
I've got it.
That makes six.
Saya, let's finish it off.
[Saya] Understood.
[energy pulses]
Amagiri Shinmei‐style...
Twin Dragons!
Aaaaah!
[Ayato thinking]
One more head to go.
This ends now.
Ayato, incoming, three o'clock!
[Ayato thinking] Did it speed up
its regeneration by
focusing on one head?
We're not done!
Hyaa!
Great job keeping
that thing distracted
cos I just finished
setting up my attack!
Come out!
Rafflesia Duoflores!
[creature roars]
Hyaaaa!
Yaaaa!
[Gustave] How unexpected.
What do I have left
to throw at them?
Hmm?
Well, how did you manage
to find me?
You're the type
to keep your distance,
but you still want
to see what happens,
so you would find somewhere safe
to watch the battle that isn't
too close to the action.
[clang!]
Looks like Julis had you pegged.
[Gustave laughs]
So that's it.
You girls truly are
an annoying bunch.
A little too smart
for your own good.
[thwack!]
[monitor chirps]
Kirin here.
Gustave's been captured.
[clang]
[Claudia] Hello, father.
It's my understanding that
Gustave Marlow's been captured.
[father] It feels like ages
since I last saw your face,
Claudia.
[Claudia] So a member of Galaxy
hired a criminal to assault
a Seidoukan student
and that student happens to be
a princess no less.
Galaxy had nothing
to do with it.
I acted completely
of my own accord.
[Claudia] Surely,
such subterfuge
wouldn't do a single thing
to help a man stuck
in your position.
My mother would agree,
or do you think she'd
judge you differently?
[father] She'd agree.
Your mother wouldn't hesitate
a second to throw me
under the bus
if she thought it was necessary.
That being said,
anything you may have uncovered
won't be of any use to you
whatsoever.
Probably.
And yet you insist on competing
in the Gryps Festa.
Just let it go.
You already know what will
happen if you do this,
don't you?
Please, think about it!
At least change your wish.
There's still enough time,
Claudia.
I've already told you,
nothing will change my mind.
I won't go back on my word.
I love you, I love you
more than anything.
You know that, don't you?
Please!
[Claudia] I do appreciate
everything that you've done
for me.
I'm truly grateful, father.
That's all.
Have a good night.
[father sobbing]
[Jolbert] I really do
have to thank you all.
You've helped to restore peace
in our fragile nation.
Our citizens are just
as grateful.
By the way, Julis,
the people in the old city
are so fired up,
they just might go and throw you
another parade.
Does this mean you're actually
starting to lose the support
of our citizens? Well?
Cos if that's the case,
there's something really
important I need you to know.
Yeah, what would that be?
I'm going to win
the next Gryps Festa.
Then I'll expand the powers
of Lieseltania's king.
The attacks over the last
few days have convinced me.
I want to change this country.
Doing something more fundamental
may be the only way
to do that.
Hah. We could use
the Festa money to increase
the king's influence.
It would be quite doable.
If I do win, you're going
to have to become a more
responsible leader.
I know it's a burden,
but please, for my sake.
I need your support.
Will you help me change
this country?
Hah. Oh, Julis.
You've grown so much
since I last saw you.
I never dreamed
the day would come
that you'd ask for my help.
Thank you.
You've done so much.
I'm glad my sister found
such great friends.
Whatever you need,
count me in.
I promise, Julis,
if you really manage to come out
on top at the Gryps Festa,
I give you my word
I'll try harder.
I won't be
such a carefree king.
Thanks so much.
We can shape this country.
Those two really love
each other, don't they?
They really do.
[monitor chirps]
The Committee Chairman?
[Madiath] Mr. Amagiri.
I have news.
Your sister's been found.
[Ayato thinking] Haruka.
[Madiath] Haruka Amagiri
was brought to this hospital
around five years ago.
She's been in a deep coma
ever since she was admitted.
Despite her condition,
she hasn't aged at all
since that day.
I believe it's
the effect of some kind
of unidentified power.
According to the doctors,
there's nothing they can do
at this time.
This looks like the work
of Haruka's ability.
Her Imprisonment Power
allows her to bind all things.
I just don't understand why.
Why would she ever decide
to cast it on herself?
If she doesn't come out
of her coma soon,
how long before
her life is in danger?
[Madiath] If there's no change
in her current condition,
the doctors say that she'll
outlive all of us,
if you can actually
call this living, that is.
[Hilda giggles]
[Hilda] So I understand
they found your sister.
Ayato Amagiri.
I can cure your sister
and wake her from
that awful coma if you'd like.
All right, now, who are you,
and how do you know
about my sister?
[laughing]
My name's Hilda Jane Rowlands.
Nice to meet ya.
I'm the chairman
of the Arlequint Academy
Research Institute.
But I'm also known as...
Magnum Opus.
Once again, I apologize.
My father's caused
so much trouble for you.
But why would your father
willingly try to stage
an attack like that?
Probably because it would
inconvenience him if I win
the Gryps Festa.
Inconvenience Galaxy,
I should say, not my father.
[Kirin] Yeah, but wasn't there
any other way he could
have done it?
[Claudia] Most likely,
he was desperate to convince me
to drop out of the Festa
before Galaxy
could ever make a move,
cos if they came looking for me,
my father knew
what would happen.
They would have taken
very drastic measures.
Do you realize
everything you risk
if you go through with this?
If you're making
an enemy of Galaxy,
you're making yourself an enemy
of Seidoukan as well.
I know, but I don't intend
on conceding my wish.
And it doesn't matter what
enemies I make along the way.
All of you, wouldn't you feel
the same in my position?
Now, if you decide
to follow me,
it could mean making
Galaxy your enemy.
I know it's a lot of me to ask,
but I'd still like you
to join me in the Gryps Festa.
And when you think about it,
isn't being a part of this team
worth it to you?
Everyone in this lineup is
someone I would trust with
my life, no questions asked.
So count me in.
Yeah, me too!
I won't back down either.
When I saw you
in the last Gryps Festa,
I knew right away that I wanted
to fight by your side,
Ms. President.
I'll only do it
if Ayato does it, too.
[Claudia] So, what do you say,
Ayato?
What'll it be?
[Ayato thinking] I have
no intention of asking
Magnum Opus for help.
But if there's a way to wake
Haruka from her coma...
I've decided, you can
count on me to join you
as well, Claudia.
And by working together,
we can win this.
No matter what!
[Haruka Chisuga singing
"Words of Love" in Japanese]