[Xinglou humming]
[sighs] So all of you have
finally made it here.
[warriors yelling]
Well, what's the holdup?
[giggles]
How delightful!
Master, I believe we need
to begin our scheduled
debriefing.
[Xinglou sighs]
[Xinglou] Time certainly flies,
doesn't it?
Boys, good job, each of you.
Come back any time to try again.
Master, while sparring with
all those prospective students,
I was rather curious
as to what you were watching.
Oh! A match from the Festa.
And I saw a new fighter who was
truly amazing, Hu Feng.
Seidoukan's Ayato Amagiri
or something.
In terms of raw talent,
that kid was the best.
Really exciting to watch.
Think it's too late for him
to play for us now?
That's easier said than done.
Besides, from what I've heard,
his powers are somewhat
limited, right?
[Xinglou] That's precisely
what makes him so intriguing.
[Hu Feng] I believe he is going
up against Song and Luo next.
[Xinglou] He is?
I must admit, I'm envious.
[Shenyun] Master, we've both
been looking for you.
[Shenhua] Oh, you're here, too,
Brother Zhao.
[Shenyun and Shenhua]
It's been a long time.
Well, well, look,
it's the twins.
Yes, Shenyun and Shenhua.
[Xinglou]
So, what's this all about?
Well, it appears that
we're headed for a clash
with Song and Luo
coming up in the sixth round.
As members
of the Water Faction,
we don't see eye to eye
with the Wood Faction.
[Shenyun] So when it's
our turn to fight...
[Shenhua] ...the two of us
might go a little overboard.
[both] Thought it'd be something
you'd like to know.
You brats!
‐[Xinglou giggles]
‐You both can do as you please.
From the beginning,
my only goal was
to endow you with power.
But what you do with it
is none of my concern.
‐[Hu Feng] Master!
‐[Shenyun] I see why you've
been given
the title Divine Revelations.
[Shenhua] You're so open‐minded!
[both] Very impressive, Master.
[Xinglou] That said,
are you certain
everything will go
as planned?
[Shenyun] Are you saying
my sister and I don't measure up
to Song and Luo?
[Xinglou] Oh, no, but it's not
as if they're a lock
to move on to the next round.
Guess we'll have to wait
and see.
[Xinglou giggles]
[Hu Feng] Master,
with that Seidoukan team's
weakness exposed,
do you still think
Song and Luo could lose?
[Xinglou giggles]
I only care about one thing,
and that's having a good time.
Honestly, that's really
all I'm in it for.
If Amagiri and his teammate
win tomorrow,
it will just increase
his capabilities even further.
That's what I'm looking forward
to the most.
After all, that would make it...
so much more exciting!
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"The Asterisk War" in Japanese]
♪ This is the Asterisk War ♪
[Julis]
Seriously.
I can't believe how quickly
this rumor spread
in a single day.
And something tells me
the players must have gotten
even more details.
So how much do you think
they already know?
[Julis] Well, for starters,
it's safe to assume
the match against Irene
gave them a rough idea about
that time limit of yours.
Yeah, I guess so.
But the real issue now is
they're aware
of the toll it takes on you
after releasing your powers.
"To make a complete recovery
from the kind of physical damage
incurred while at full strength,
Amagiri must stand by
for a certain interval."
‐[crash!]
‐I keep hearing these rumors
can be traced back to ReWolf.
Wretched tyrant!
[Ayato sighs]
So, how have you
been holding up, anyway?
Truth is, I still have
a few aches and pains,
but it's gonna take
a lot more than that
to keep me from fighting.
Still too soon for you
to go all out, though, isn't it?
Mm‐hmm. I don't think
that's gonna happen.
[Julis] All right.
Then in that case,
I just need to find out
two things:
How can you still have such
formidable defensive skills
when your powers
have been sealed away?
Oh, well, if it's just defense,
I can get by using experience
alone, up to a point.
OK.
And as for the other thing,
think there's any chance
you'd be able
to release your full power,
even if it's for a split second?
I could probably pull it off
at least one more time.
Very well then,
these are our opponents,
Jie Long's Rank Number 20
and Number 23.
They're disciples of
their Student Council president,
Divine Revelations,
and masters of close combat.
If you could fight
at your full strength,
then defeating those two
would be fairly simple.
But now it would be too much
to ask in the state you're in.
And while I know that I could
take them on one‐on‐one,
I'm not so sure
about both at the same time.
Which brings us back
to my plan.
What do you mean?
How about this strategy?
[crowd cheers]
[Meeko] Here we are, everyone!
It's the last match
of the Phoenix Festa's
round five.
Which team has what it takes
to join the others
in the quarterfinals?
With the quality
of the competitors this year,
I'd say that any one of them
has a shot at winning it all.
All right then.
Now let's introduce
the quarterfinalists to watch
in the upcoming matches.
First, we have this year's
front runners,
Arlequint's all‐powerful
cutting‐edge puppets,
Aldy and Rimsy.
They'll be competing
as Ernesta and
Camilla's alternates.
[Tram] After allowing
their opponents
to attack at full force
for a whole minute,
their win
was pretty surprising.
[Meeko] And here are
Jie Long's Li Shenyun,
aka Mirage Genesis,
and Li Shenhua,
aka Mirage Dispersion.
[Tram]
With their massive arsenal
of Star Senjutsu combo moves,
they're almost impossible
to beat.
So far, they've brought down
each of their opponents
and gone on to victory.
[Meeko] But we are just
getting started, folks,
waiting for the pride
and honor of Life Rhodes,
Elliot Forster
and Doroteo Lemus
of Galahadworth.
[Tram] Doroteo's a real beast,
and with two Festas
under his belt,
a seasoned veteran,
while Elliot
is a young prodigy
who joined Life Rhodes
despite only being
in junior high school.
[Meeko] Seidoukan's been
dominating this Festa,
but can they stand
their ground?
Here's Kirin Toudou
and Saya Sasamiya.
[Tram] Toudou,
with her close‐combat skills,
and Sasamiya,
with her sheer firepower,
are out to prove
they're in the zone.
But up next,
also representing Seidoukan,
is the seemingly unstoppable
duo known
as the Amagiri‐Riessfeld team.
Right.
They handed Irene, armed with
her Ogre Lux Gravi‐Sheath,
and her teammate Priscilla,
a resounding defeat.
[Meeko] Although recently,
some rumors have been
swirling around about Amagiri.
[Tram] That's right,
and if what we heard is true,
the disadvantage to his team
could be huge.
[Meeko] Has he recovered
from the damage he sustained
after releasing his powers?
And will he be ready to go out
and fight again today?
‐[crowd cheers]
‐[Meeko] OK, this is the match
we've been waiting for.
Here's Seidoukan Academy's
Ayato Amagiri
and Julis‐Alexia von Riessfeld!
And now their challengers
have arrived.
It's Jie Long's Seventh
Institute's Song and Luo.
Hey, Amagiri, whether
those rumors about you
are true or not,
Luo and I aren't gonna
hold anything back.
Truth be told, we would have
preferred to go head‐to‐head
with you when you were 100%.
But we must follow the rules
of the Phoenix Festa.
‐So don't take it personally.
‐Huh? You don't have to...
[Song] We just wanted to let you
know that before the match.
[Ayato] Uh... right.
[Julis] Whaddya know?
Sounds like they really are
true warriors.
Yeah, I didn't know
those still existed.
[crowd cheers]
[Meeko] Both teams have now
taken their places.
More than likely, they're
going to start off
by testing you
to find out if you're
at full strength again.
And they'll know right away.
There's no getting around that.
I suppose so.
[Julis] OK, listen up, Ayato.
This is your mark here.
You need to remember it.
[Ayato] Uh, yeah.
Now, the signal's still
the fireworks, right?
Make sure you've met
all the conditions by then, OK?
[Ayato] Got it.
[Meeko] All right,
which team is going to feel
the sweet thrill of victory
here in the fifth round
and head to the quarterfinals?
It's match eight, round five,
of the Phoenix Festa.
Battle...
begin!
Let's go!
[battle cry]
As I thought.
The rumors were true.
You're not at full strength.
[battle cry]
Burst into bloom!
Primrose! Hah!
[battle cry]
Aaah!
Ayato, he got past me!
[crowd cheers]
[chuckles] Do you think
you can take this?
Come on.
[Meeko]
Whoa, I can't believe this.
Amagiri is under siege.
Didn't see that one coming.
That Song and Luo team's
coordinated attack was
masterfully done.
[Tram] And it looks
like Amagiri's using
quite a bit less Prana than
we've seen in earlier matches.
So, maybe those rumors
are true after all.
Come out!
Loropetalum!
[Meeko] Aaah! Is this yet
another one of Riessfeld's
incredible skills?
A gigantic wall of flames
has appeared out of nowhere.
And it's divided
the stage in two.
I see, you're trying to keep me
separated from Luo.
Now, let's fight one‐on‐one.
[Song] Do you truly believe this
is going to make a difference?
[Ayato] I don't think it's
gonna be easy,
but even so, that doesn't mean
I should give up, does it?
Rather impressive.
Guess I was wrong.
Do forgive me.
What's wrong?
I see you've been overhyped,
Glühen Rose.
[Julis thinking] This is someone
who's ranked 23?
At Seidoukan,
he'd easily be a Page One.
Haaaaa!
[Julis] Livingstone Daisy!
I get it.
So that's what's going on here.
You're expending your power
to keep the flames going.
But you could have turned this
into a one‐on‐one battle
without any of this.
Why use these elaborate tricks?
I had no choice.
It's the only way
Ayato and I have a shot
at winning this match.
[Luo] Ahh.
Then that can only mean
you have something else
up your sleeve, don't you?
‐[crowd cheers]
‐[Ayato panting]
[Song] I have to admit,
I admire you.
Even though you've been
focusing on defense,
you've been able to withstand
all my attacks.
And I'm also aware that if you
were fighting at full strength,
then our roles
might well have been reversed.
No, I don't think I could have
held out as long as you have.
Well, I'm not sure...
that's necessarily true.
But I simply couldn't live
with myself
if I went on battering you
in this way.
So, out of my great respect
for you,
my next move will finish this.
Well, you'd better hurry...
or the battle just beyond
this wall will be over soon.
[Julis] Are you implying my
team partner is about to lose?
[Luo] In his current state,
Murakumo has no chance,
now does he?
I suppose not.
For Ayato to defeat you
in his current condition,
he would have to try and
catch you off guard somehow.
Hah. Well, Song and I would
never be foolish enough
to leave ourselves open.
[Julis thinking]
So it's that side.
Try protecting yourself
all you want,
but my fist is lethal.
I would advise you dodge it
rather than trying to block.
[Ayato thinking] Julis.
This is it!
Burst into bloom!
Oh, no, you don't!
[Julis] Amaryllis Duo Flos!
Aaah!
[Ayato] The signal!
[snaps fingers]
[battle cry]
[blade clangs]
‐[crowd cheers, buzzer sounds]
‐[virtual ref] Badge broken.
[Meeko] End of match!
The winners are
Ayato Amagiri
and Julis‐Alexia von Riessfeld!
Catching
their opponents off‐guard,
they showed some
stunning teamwork.
Amazing!
Actually, what they just pulled
off wasn't quite so simple.
What do you mean by that?
[Tram] Song and Amagiri
were battling each other
in some close‐quarter combat.
Meanwhile, Luo was busy
countering Riessfeld's
long‐distance assault.
By switching places,
the Seidoukan team messed up
their opponents' timing
and were able to catch
each of them off guard.
Pretty incredible!
[footsteps, Ayato sighs]
I guess we pulled it off, huh?
The fact that we even
got through the match
is the real victory.
So after you get a full day's
rest in tomorrow,
you should be able
to go all out when it's time
for the next one, right?
Oh, yeah, that won't be
a problem at all.
But I've been wondering
about you, Julis.
Are you gonna be OK?
[Julis] Well, nothing seems
to be broken, so I'm sure
I can handle it.
Now, about our next match.
Even if you get
all your strength back soon,
our next opponent should be
a handful.
Yeah, that's what I've heard.
[Julis] Huh.
I'm sure you didn't come here
to offer your congratulations,
so what do you two want
with us?
[Song] Actually, you're wrong.
You were the one who came up
with that strategy,
weren't you, Glühen Rose?
Yes, that's right.
The combination you pulled
was astounding.
You must really trust
each other.
You both wiped the floor
with us today.
Amazing job.
Well...
But there's something
you both should know.
That strategy of yours
won't have any effect
on your upcoming opponents.
[Julis] And what does that mean?
It's simply a warning,
nothing more, nothing less.
That's funny.
The next team we're up against
just so happen to be
friends of yours.
How am I supposed
to trust you?
[Song] We might
go to the same school,
but that doesn't mean
we're friends.
[Luo] Neither of us sees
eye to eye with Li Shenyun
and Li Shenhua.
Never have.
That said, we're not about
to clue you in
on their weak points.
But quite frankly, we feel
more an affinity for you
than for those twins.
Just want you to know,
you both have our full support.
All right, then let me
ask you again,
why did you say our strategy
isn't going to work?
[Song] Because, when it comes
to deception, trickery
and surprise attacks,
those two are highly skilled.
They'll see right through
any plan that you can devise
and then one‐up you
at every turn.
In battle, you see
your opponents as equals
and are willing to face whatever
challenges may come your way.
But those twins
are much different.
They constantly look down
on their opponents
and never expose themselves
to danger.
It's how the Li twins
have always been.
And it's the thing we can't
stomach about them.
[Shenyun] Well, well, well.
First you go down
in a pitiful defeat...
[Shenhua] And now you're
trash‐talking other people
with the same ones
who crushed you.
Damn you!
[Shenyun] It's nice to meet you,
Glühen Rose, Murakumo.
My name is Li Shenyun.
And mine is Li Shenhua.
[both]
Hi. It's truly a pleasure.
What is it you want?
Oh, we just wanted
to offer you an apology.
A what?
You see, unfortunately,
it appears our friends here
put up quite a lame fight.
[both] As students
of the same master,
we couldn't be more mortified.
Well, I didn't think there was
anything lame about it.
It simply won't do for disciples
of the Divine Revelations
to be seen as weak.
So we'll do everything
in our power
to show you a world
our elder brothers couldn't.
[both] The depths
of Star Senjutsu, soon...
[Julis] Pretty annoying duo,
weren't they?
But, including the two of them,
three more victories
and we stand to win
this entire tournament.
Three times, huh?
That's a lot more demanding
than it sounds.
Well, at least you know
what we can expect.
So, have you thought about
what you're going to ask for
if we pull this off?
Uh, hmm. I can't really
come up with anything.
Kind of had a feeling you might
say something like that.
Now look, I'm so grateful
to you for fighting with me,
and honestly, it, uh,
makes me happy.
But, Ayato,
it's time for you to think
about what you really
want for yourself.
[Ayato] Hmm.
Yeah, I guess, but...
What about your older sister?
Why don't you
have them find her?
[Ayato] I'm sure she must
have had her reasons
for leaving home.
So I won't go out of my way
to look for her.
[Julis] But finding your sister
would be the fastest way
to do something about
your seal, wouldn't it?
Yeah, well, that's true,
but I...
‐Don't tell me you're...
‐[monitor blips]
Yoo‐hoo.
Hello, you two.
You came here
just to see us?
We're sure you're both
completely exhausted,
so we wanted to congratulate
you as soon as possible.
[Ayato] Then I'll open the door
right now.
Uh, before you do, I thought
I should let you know
that there's
another guest with us.
Think it would be OK
if we brought her in, too?
[Ayato] A guest?
Yeah. To see Riessfeld.
[Julis] To see me?
‐Hello, your highness!
‐[Julis] But you're...
Long time, no see!
I've missed you!
[Flora giggles]
[Julis] F‐FLora!
[Haruka Chisuga singing
"Words of Love" in Japanese]