[footsteps approaching]
Burst into bloom!
Red Crown!
Surely, you don't think that
cowardly move sufficient enough
to dispatch me?
Come out here and show yourself!
Hello, Silas Norman.
[chuckles maniacally]
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"Brand‐new World" in Japanese]
[Silas] I'm impressed you
realized I was the one
behind the attacks.
Your slip of the tongue
helped significantly.
Afraid I don't know
what you're talking about.
The commercial district
yesterday.
You said something when you were
trying to stop Lester.
I believe you said you would
never do anything as cowardly
as watching a duel
for a chance to attack.
Yeah, so what if I did?
A telling statement.
The media only reported
that I'd repelled my attackers.
There wasn't a single mention
of my having fought Sasamiya.
Watching a duel
for a chance to attack?
Only a person who'd actually
seen it happen
or had been told about it
could say that,
which means it must have been
the perpetrator,
or one in league with him.
Congratulations.
You're a quick one.
So in other words,
Ayato deliberately
provoked Lester yesterday.
[Julis] Most likely.
He's smarter than you think.
I wouldn't underestimate him
if I were you.
Well then, if that's the case,
I see I made the right call
in targeting him instead.
I don't need him interfering
when you're the one
I'm really after.
How dare you!
Oh, a little sensitive, are we?
Wait, don't tell me.
You came here in an attempt
to either convince or force me
to leave Ayato out of this.
Let's bargain.
I'm not unreasonable.
I've but one condition,
that you withdraw yourself
from the Phoenix Festa.
Now, why would I do that
when I could simply annihilate
you right here and now?
[Silas] Huh.
[Lester] Is what you just said
true, Silas?
[Julis] Lester!
Oh, I was wondering when you'd
grace us with your presence.
I came right over when I heard
Julis had accepted a challenge.
Only to find out that you're
the one who attacked her.
[Julis] He's been hired
by some academy or another
to take out
the front‐running competitors
for the Phoenix Festa.
Surely you knew that.
How could you sell out
your fellow students like that?
[Silas] My fellow students?
You can't be serious.
"My fellow enemies"
would be a better description.
We're all here
for one reason alone
and that's to take
each other down in pursuit
of our own desires.
And since there's nothing
we can do about it,
we might as well make
some money in the process.
I gotta know before
I kick your ass.
Why did you make a point
of bringing me out here?
So I could have someone
to blame all those attacks on.
It was almost too easy.
You would duel each other
and fall by your own hands.
Seems legit, doesn't it?
[growls]
You go to hell!
What the...
OK, I get it now.
They're buddies from
whatever school hired you.
[chuckles] Oh, you don't know
the half of it.
[snaps fingers]
Allow me to introduce you
to my little friends.
My precious dolls.
Puppets!
[Silas] You know, "puppet"
is a rather crude title,
don't you agree?
They're much more than
mere machines, or even robots.
Well, Silas, now I see
where your true talent lies.
[Lester] Huhhh!
[battle cry]
You're going down!
Blast Nemea!
Yaaaa!
[joints crack]
Great.
[screaming]
[Julis] Lester!
[Silas] Don't go.
I've made an adjustment
just for you.
Why don't you test the new
threshold for heat tolerance,
Princess?
So, is that the best you've got,
a dirty sucker punch?
[Silas] Oh my, you're
in better shape than I thought.
[Lester] It doesn't matter
how many
of your stupid little dollies
you attack me with.
[Silas] It doesn't matter
how many, you say?
Very well, as you wish.
How does 128 sound to you, then?
[laughs maniacally]
The look on your face
is priceless.
Goodbye, now.
‐[Lester screams]
‐[Julis] Lester!
Silas, that's enough!
Burst into bloom!
Antirrhinum majus!
Hah!
Well, that was quite impressive,
‐but at the end of the day...
‐[snaps fingers]
you're still outnumbered!
[laughs manically]
[shrieks]
[Silas] Your skills are
certainly prodigious,
but the way they prevent you
from viewing your opponent
is a real flaw.
Well, they haven't prevented me
from discovering something.
[Silas] Oh? And what's that?
[Julis] I know who's pulling
your strings.
And it's Arlequint!
There's no other academy
that can mass‐produce armor
capable of withstanding attacks
as strong as mine and Lester's.
[footsteps approach]
[Silas] Quite perceptive.
But I'm afraid
now that you know,
there's no way I can afford
to let you out of here alive.
[shrieks]
You know, I can think
of few things more pleasurable
than inflicting pain on you,
but let's just get this
over with.
Been nice knowing you,
your highness.
[Ayato] I'm sorry I got here
so late.
[Julis] Ayato!
[Julis] Hold on. I...
What are you doing here?
I came here to rescue you.
I don't recall asking
for your help.
This is my problem, not yours.
What sort of fool
goes out of his way
to put himself in danger?
You don't get it, huh?
OK, you said you were fighting
of your own volition.
No one made you, right?
You have an objective,
and that's to make sure the kids
in the orphanage are OK.
It's been your plan
since the beginning, hasn't it?
Yes. So what's your point?
Well then, if you're out
fighting to protect them,
who's gonna protect you?
Protect me?
[Ayato] I've been searching
for a long time now,
trying to figure out what I can
do with this power of mine,
and what I'm supposed to do
with it.
But coming here and meeting you,
I finally understand.
You see, there is something
that I want to do,
and I'm just hoping I've got
what it takes to do it.
Because now I know that
it's my true purpose.
And what do you want to do?
I want to be the one
who protects you.
You imbecile. How could you
say a thing like that?
[boom!]
If you two are done
with your little chat,
we have unfinished business.
The power of the Ser Versta
is remarkable,
and also a bit of a pain.
However, just because
your surprise attack
happened to work out,
that doesn't mean you can expect
the same results against
so many of my dolls.
Doesn't it?
Cos don't forget, I learned
the surprise attack from you.
What else have you got?
I beg your pardon?
Perhaps you would care
for a test.
[snaps fingers]
With my soul's sword, I break
these celestial bonds...
that my savage force
may be seen!
Ayato.
[groans]
Impossible! How? Where?
Right behind you.
[energy pulses]
Who in the world are you,
anyway?
You better put me down
this instant!
I couldn't bear
being a burden to you!
Well, sorry, but you're gonna
have to bear it a little bit
longer, OK?
All right, this time I'm not
gonna hold anything back!
[puppets' joints creak,
footsteps echo]
Behold! This is the power
of my Maelzel Corps!
You can try fending them off
if you dare!
[Ayato] I see.
At most, you can only move
six puppet types at once.
[Silas] Huh?
[Ayato] And there are 16 of them
who can just follow
a certain pattern of moves.
All the rest can only execute
simple actions.
Wait.
Six types, 16 pieces.
It's just like a game of chess.
[groans]
Damn you, Amagiri!
I'll destroy you!
I will end you!
Wait. No way.
His sword can't be blocked
no matter what?
This can't be real.
How is this even happening?
It's game over, Silas.
Give up now.
No! It's not.
Not until I say it's over!
[Silas laughs hysterically]
The time has come, my queen.
Take him down!
[steel clangs, feet pound floor]
I shall sever the limbs
and the five viscera.
Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
Second Sword!
Nine Fangs!
[gasps]
Man, this guy doesn't know
when to quit.
Sorry, Julis, but I'm gonna
have to go after him.
Would you mind waiting
back here for just a minute?
Sure, but do you think
you can make it?
Honestly, I don't really know.
One way to find out.
[Julis] In that case,
it's my move now.
I told you before,
I've no intention
of burdening you.
Burst into bloom!
Strelitzia!
‐Whoa!
‐Let's go.
And don't worry, I'll pilot you.
Aaah!
This time, don't you let up
until you've kicked
his sorry ass!
His what?
Not what I'd expect to hear
from a princess.
[gasp]
Checkmate, Silas!
You've got nowhere to go.
No wait,
you can't do this to me!
Aaaaaah!
It's OK, Silas is a Genestella.
I'm sure the fall
won't kill him.
Pretty sure.
Anyway, Claudia and her crew
should be waiting down there.
Let's leave the rest to them.
[gasp]
Good idea.
The view is awesome up here.
Indeed. It is quite spectacular.
[low pounding]
‐Hey, what is it?
‐[Ayato groans]
Tell me what's going on!
[Ayato screams]
[chains rattle]
[Julis] Ayato! Hey! You OK?
No, come on!
Stay with me.
Ayato!
‐[Haruka] I'm sorry, Ayato.
‐[Ayato] Haruka?
[screams]
With these celestial shackles,
I bind your savage force.
[weakly] Why, Haruka?
You mean you don't remember?
I swore that I'd protect you
no matter what.
That's why.
But I said that I was gonna
protect you, too.
Please don't go!
[Haruka] I must, Ayato.
I love you.
So, you've finally come to.
Oh, thank goodness.
I was beginning to worry.
[groans]
[Ayato] Oh, man.
So I did pass out after all.
Just take it easy.
I've already contacted Claudia.
I'm sure she's on her way.
Thank you, Julis.
Don't thank me!
I'm the one who needed
to be rescued, remember?
Hey, you need to keep still.
[Ayato] Whoa! My bad.[groans]
[Julis] Oh, grow up, you idiot.
But I can't just lie here.
Well... you can if I tell you
it's fine, and it's fine,
all right?
Uh... Did you hear me?
Yeah, sure.
[Julis clears throat]
[Julis] Anyway, listen.
About that power
that's restraining you.
Can you tell me who cast it?
Uh... cast what?
Don't know what you mean.
It was my sister.
Imprisonment power.
It gave her the ability to bind
anything that she wanted to.
Impressive. So what you
unleashed back there
were your true powers,
what you're really capable of.
Yeah. That's one way
of looking at it.
Can't you give a straight answer
for anything?
Ha. Well, I can only use them
for so long.
That's the first time ever...
I've gone more
than five minutes.
Guess I shouldn't brag.
Look at the state I'm in.
But why would your sister
do that to you?
I'd ask her myself if I could,
but she's been missing
for about five years now.
No, it's all right.
Wherever she's gone,
she had her reasons.
Just like she had a reason
for binding my powers.
Mind if I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
Your partner for
the Phoenix Festa, picked one?
[Julis] Uh...
[Ayato] Just cos I know
a guy who'd be interested.
Really?
Now, you set the bar high,
but I'd say I'm pretty decisive
and determined.
Though you'll have
to give me a pass
on the noble dedication,
knightly thing...
I appreciate your offer,
but don't push yourself.
At the Festa level,
your normal strength
simply can't compete with that
of the other fighters.
And you wouldn't want
to end up like this
after unsealing your powers
at every match.
Oh, I don't know,
this isn't so bad.
I told you before, what I'm
supposed to be doing right now,
like it or not, is trying
to protect you, Julis.
Well, thank you, but this is
all rather informal, so I, uh...
Hang on, are you embarrassed?
You're turning bright red.
Don't be ridiculous. I am not!
And stop looking at me!
[Ayato] My eye!
Julis?
[Julis] Do you really...
mean that?
Of course.
Ayato, you're
a pretty strange one.
But thank you.
[Maaya Sakamoto]
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪
[Silas gasping]
[footsteps approaching]
[Claudia] Now, now.
You don't expect me to believe
you were ignorant
of his power, do you?
[Silas gasps]
Aaaaah!
[Eishirou] Man! Now, what did
you go and do that for, anyway?
Oh, there's nothing
to worry about.
I didn't kill him.
After all, he can still be
of some use.
I see. So instead of going
public for the sake
of diplomacy,
you'll just handle
the entire incident internally
so that Arlequint
will owe us one.
I'm going to leave it up to you,
so use your best discretion.
Just be sure to get
some information out of him.
[Eishirou] You can count on it.
Cos it's what
we Shadow Stars do.
Oh, yeah, so how did it go
with those two?
Rather well, I do believe.
[Eishirou] OK, then what's
with the forced smile?
That's good news, right?
[Claudia] Well...
most certainly,
and why wouldn't it be?
[Ernesta] Okie‐dokie,
that should do it.
I gathered plenty of data.
Silas performed better
than I could have hoped.
I mean, did you see
those sneak attacks
on the front runners?
Come on. [laughs]
They're proficient little guys,
if nothing else.
Of course,
they were designed by me.
[giggles, sighs]
Thankfully,
that half‐baked nut job
was even easier to manipulate
than these dolls.
[sighs]