Mr. MacPhail has chosen
the Ser Versta, too.
[Lester]
Why won't you obey me?!
[Lester groans, chains rattle]
Be careful!
[Ayato groans]
[sighs]
As I expected.
Ayato, I feel I can trust you,
so I have a favor
I would like to ask.
[Ayato] What?
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"Brand‐new World" in Japanese]
Why'd she even ask me here?
Claudia, you there?
I'm coming in.
Uh...
Ayato, I'm so glad you made it.
[gasps]
Please, have a seat.
[Ayato] It's so spacious.
Must be nice to be
Student Council president.
[Claudia] It's not that.
The presidency does have
its advantages,
but this is a privilege
for top‐tier students.
The Page Ones are granted
private quarters, you see.
If you advance in rank,
you'll have one, too.
Incredible. I had no idea
you were a Page One.
Oh, dear, how could you not
have known that, Ayato?
If it's not asking too much,
I'd like for you to take more
of a personal interest in me.
‐Oh, my bad.
‐[Claudia giggles]
[Claudia] Don't worry about it.
To be perfectly honest with you,
being Student Council president
is more trouble
than you might think.
If it sucks so much, then why
do it in the first place?
Well, the truth
of the matter is,
I like trouble.
[groans]
So, is that what this
is about, to ask me a favor
regarding that trouble?
That's precisely why
I called you here.
Kindly take a look at this.
It's a list of students who are
supposed to enter the upcoming
Phoenix Festa.
They've all recently sustained
debilitating injuries
and were forced to withdraw
from the competition.
At this point,
we're suspecting foul play.
But we'll see.
So you're saying
they were attacked?
Just like with Julis.
That's what we're basing
our investigation on.
[Ayato] Have you found
any proof?
We haven't. Not yet, anyway.
That being said,
the Disciplinary Committee
is currently investigating
Lester MacPhail
as a likely suspect.
Neither he nor Randy Hook
have an alibi
for yesterday's attack.
Although,
without solid evidence,
aren't your hands kind of tied?
They are, but this time
we have an ace in the hole.
The committee has obtained
an interesting tidbit.
We know the name
of the next target.
Julis, right?
Bingo. Which brings me
to that favor we were
speaking about.
For the time being, I'd like you
to stay close by her side.
I fear she'll be attacked again
in the near future.
When that happens, I don't think
she'll be able to deal
with them herself.
Can someone else guard her?
I mean, why me?
As you may know, she tends
to distance herself from others.
Fortunately, however, she seems
to be comfortable with you.
Well, I don't know.
Though, come to think it,
she is gonna show me around
the city sometime this weekend.
[giggling] You really are
oblivious, aren't you, Ayato?
[sighs] I'll do it.
But first, mind if I ask why
you're so worried about Julis?
If that's OK.
It's simple, really.
I wouldn't be a good
Student Council president
if I didn't do everything
in my power to keep
the students secure.
That's all there is to it?
Ayato, I'm just trying
to fulfill my purpose,
as is every student
who attends Seidoukan.
I assure you,
that's all it is.
To that end, I'm only doing
what I feel is my duty.
Before I forget,
I believe you're owed
a reward for taking on
such a dangerous request.
Wha...?
It's fine,
I don't really need one!
Claudia?
[Claudia giggles]
Aaah!
Since you're here,
you might as well act
on your primal urges.
Don't you agree?
Be just as rough as you like.
I can take it.
There.
[Ayato gasps]
Hey, take it easy!
So we're all good, right?
‐Sorry to run out like this!
‐[Ayato grunts]
Dear me.
What a shame.
[sighs]
[Ayato] Fulfill my purpose, huh?
[gasp]
Now, why are you standing there
with your mouth open?
Does something about my face
amuse you?
[Ayato] No, that's not it.
You just look different today.
[Julis] You think so?
Yeah, but I'd say
it's a good different.
Wha...? What are...?
Just what are you playing at?
This is nothing more
than an ordinary outfit
that I randomly picked from
clothes sent from my country.
[Ayato giggles]
Anyway, follow me.
And this is the main stage,
the largest arena
in all of Asterisk.
Oh, wow!
This is the building where all
of our Festa finals take place.
Additionally, there are
three large‐scale stages
and seven mid‐size ones.
And there are far too many
smaller outdoor stages
to count.
[Ayato] That's amazing!
[Julis] It's considered
proper etiquette to use
those smaller ones for duels
instead of doing them
in the street.
However, very few adhere
to those rules.
[Ayato] Wait, you're saying
people have duels
in the middle of the city?
[Julis] Unfortunately.
Sounds intense.
Wouldn't want to live here.
Me either.
Looks like a good area
to grab some lunch.
What do you say, huh?
Uh...
Ayato, how about having
lunch here?
[Ayato] At this place?
You sure you really want
to do this?
‐It's cool with me, but...
‐Of course.
[Julis] Shall we?
Are you absolutely sure
you're a princess?
Hmm. What's that
supposed to mean?
Well, it's just
sort of weird for royalty
to go to a burger joint.
Only if you buy into
that nonsense, but since
you're sitting with one,
‐I'd say it's perfectly normal.
‐[Ayato laughs]
Actually, some of my friends
told me about this place.
[gulp] Your friends?
Do you have to sound
so surprised?
[Ayato] Uh, sorry.
Though, they're not here.
My friends are back home.
Julis, there's something that
I need to discuss with you.
‐Go ahead.
‐I'm not sure how much you know
about the attack on you,
but Claudia gave me
some details.
Now that I filled you in,
you can see why maybe
you shouldn't go out alone,
or duel anyone for a while.
Thank you.
But it's absolutely ludicrous
that I'd be expected to alter
my routine due to these cowards.
I hear ya.
I shall be the one
to decide my path.
And I won't allow anybody
to choose it for me.
[Ayato chuckles,
footsteps approach]
Look, guys, the brave princess.
It sounds like she doesn't mind
if she's attacked again.
I've always wanted
to be spied on, Lester.
Thank you for that.
But you should know that I'll
battle anyone worthy
of dueling me.
Huh? That a fact?
Then let's settle our score
right here and now.
Did you not hear a word I said?
I'm only dueling
worthy challengers.
I don't care what you say,
we're gonna do this!
[crowd murmuring]
Come on, don't you think you've
taken this far enough, Lester?
Shut your hole,
you little punk.
‐[Ayato] No, I can't do that.
‐Say what?
Picking a fight with Julis is
the worst thing you could do
right now.
If you want to look guilty,
then be my guest,
but doing this makes you seem
just like the kind of coward
that attacked her the other day.
[Lester] Oh, yeah?
Don't gimme that crap!
So you're sayin' I'm no better
than the creep sneaking around
in the shadows, huh?
Fine, then let me show you
how much we're alike
by ripping you apart!
A second ago, you were
all high and mighty, and now
you're just gonna stand there?
Who's the real coward?
Sticks and stones.
Meaningless duels
aren't my thing, dude.
‐Bastard!
‐[Randy] Hey, calm down, Lester!
Everyone knows you've always
been a fair fighter.
You don't have
to prove that here.
Yeah, that's true.
You would never do anything
as cowardly
as watching a duel
for a chance to attack.
[Lester snarls]
We're gonna let you guys
off easy today.
[Ayato sighs, Julis giggles]
So you are a tough one,
aren't you?
I don't know what you mean.
Anyway, more importantly,
you've got some ketchup on you.
Oh, dear, whatever are we going
to do with you, Ayato?
[Ayato] Thanks for today.
I really learned a lot
and had some fun, too.
Did you?
I mean, as I've said before,
I was merely squaring away
my debt with you.
‐So there's no need for you
to thank me‐‐
‐[punk] Bastard!
[student] Just shut up
and bring it!
[Julis] They're from
ReWolf Black Institute.
[Ayato] Looks like they're
about to fight.
Here we go.
‐You want some?
‐[student] Bring it on!
[both grunting]
‐This isn't good.
‐[Ayato] Huh?
[Julis] It's a setup.
[student] Hyah!
[Julis] Typical strategy.
Surround the target
during a fake brawl.
Then strike
while they're distracted.
Does this mean ReWolf
was behind the attack
on you all along?
No, not necessarily.
If you throw enough money
their way,
these miscreants will take on
just about anything.
[punk] Shit.
I'm gonna go and get
some answers out of them.
We'll call it self‐defense.
Just go easy on them,
and hold off at medium‐rare, OK?
[punk screams]
[Julis] Huh.
That wasn't even a warmup.
You there.
Stand up, or else
I'll burn off the rest
of that bizarre hairstyle
of yours, roots and all.
‐[punk screams]
‐Answer me, right now.
Who gave you the order
to attack me?
[punk] Some dude
we didn't know.
He said he'd pay us pretty good
if we roughed you up a little.
What exactly did
this person look like?
He was dressed all in black,
kind of tall, big guy.
Hey, there he is!
That's the one who hired us!
‐Get back here!
‐Julis, hold up a minute!
Julis! Where are you?
Look out! Behind you!
Ayato!
‐Hey, are you all right?
‐[Ayato] I'm fine.
Basically. Think my clothes
are a different story, though.
I can't believe you let
your guard down like that.
Dodging those attacks
should have been easy for you.
And you managed
to destroy your Lux, too.
Hey, gimme a break.
That's all I could handle
with my current skills.
Guess you can't take on
more than one at a time, huh?
No matter.
Security should be
arriving shortly,
so it would be best
if we take our leave.
[Ayato] Good idea.
‐Oh, by the way...
‐[Ayato] Huh?
You wouldn't still be
available later, would you?
I'm coming in.
Jeez, I hate that this has
become almost normal for me.
There you are. Now...
Let's get this over with,
shall we?
‐Take off your clothes.
‐Say what?!
[Ayato] Why would I...? Julis!
Why are you getting
so bent out of shape?
Just take off
your clothes and...
That's not what I...
Get your mind out of the gutter!
You idiot, I merely wanted
to repair the clothing
that was ripped in the fight!
You did? Hang on.
You can sew, Julis?
I'm not the best,
but I have done it before.
And since I'm partly
to blame for what happened,
I'm preemptively canceling out
any additional debt to you.
All right, have it your way.
Here.
[beep]
So, is sewing another thing
you picked up from
your friends back home?
‐Yes, how did you know?
‐It was just a hunch, really.
Hey, Julis, these kids
that are in the picture here,
they're your friends,
aren't they?
Hmm. Why are...
Why are you looking at that?
Who gave you permission?
And that girl who's sitting
in the middle of everyone,
that's you, right?
Indeed.
The ones in that photograph
are definitely my friends,
without question.
I may not look it now,
but I used to be
quite the tomboy back then.
I would sneak way
from the palace more times
than I can remember.
On one of my expeditions,
I lost my way
and I found myself
in the slums,
trapped in an alley
by a group of ruffians.
All I could do in that moment
was sob helplessly.
Then the children
in the picture appeared
and rescued me.
After returning to the palace,
I learned that the girls
who'd saved me
were from the orphanage
in those slums,
and I began sneaking out
of the palace whenever I could,
to spend as much time
with them as possible.
[Ayato] Did they know
you were a princess?
Did you ever end up
telling them?
[Julis] No. I kept that part
of my life a secret,
though I'm certain
the nuns knew who I was.
[Ayato] Oh, I see.
The orphanage was built with
money raised by my late mother,
but those funds
have long since run dry.
And we need them so.
Without them,
they can't stay open.
That's the reason
I came to Seidoukan.
It's sad, but what the children
of my country need
more than anything else
right now is money.
But wait, you're the crown
princess of the country,
aren't you?
Wasn't there an easier way
to find the funds you needed
besides coming out here?
I don't have money lying around
that I can use at my disposal.
Who in their right mind
would authorize
a welfare endeavor
with no hope for revenue,
especially in
a figurehead regime
of the Integrated Enterprise
Foundation?
I'll do it, trust me.
I'll earn the money myself.
Fortunately, I have my talent
as a Strega to rely on.
It's fitting, don't you think?
What better title for a freak
than "princess"?
Julis.
This city is vile
and insignificant.
[crowd applauds]
Students are made
to battle one another
for nothing more than
the sheer amusement of a crowd.
Their greed is a maelstrom
that sucks in anything
that gets in its way,
and left unchecked,
the chaos will
only continue to grow.
But it's precisely due
to this reason
that the city is
the nucleus of all desire.
That said, I too will obtain
everything that I desire,
not because someone asked me
to do it, but because
I know in my heart
that I have something
worth fighting for.
That is my reason
for going into battle.
There!
Your shirt's mended,
so it's time for you to be
on your way, all right?
Uh, sure, thanks a lot.
My debt has officially
been paid.
It looks that way.
‐Oh.
‐Huh?
[Julis] Oh.
It's from my friends.
They gave this to me
years ago as a birthday present.
Even took turns embroidering it.
Do you see this especially
heinous part?
It was done by my best friend.
It's my special treasure.
Good morning, Julis.
‐Julis?
‐Oh, sorry!
[Julis] Good morning.
[Ayato] Hey,
where are you going?
To take care of something.
[Ayato] What's with her?
[Eishirou] Looks like she's gone
back to her old self
for some reason,
and right when she was beginning
to thaw out, too.
[Claudia] Ayato?
Is there something
troubling you?
[Eishirou] Just the ice princess
reading some letter,
getting pale and running off.
The usual stuff.
Oh, no. If she's going off
to do what I think she is...
‐No way!
‐She's going after
her assailant!
If she is, then why'd
she run off without
telling me anything?
I thought she was starting
to trust me.
Are you saying that she doesn't?
My, how soon we forget.
It's everything she can do
to protect what she has now,
so she has to hold on tight.
Most likely she wanted
to protect you from the danger
that lies ahead.
Wait a minute,
she wanted to protect me?
Oh, man, you're right.
Yeah, of course.
My purpose in life
is to protect you, forever.
I swear.
I'm gonna have
to protect you, too.
I'm sure that's what I'm...
I didn't fully understand it
back then, but...
‐I'm going after her!
‐[Claudia] Hey, wait!
Uggh!
[Ayato] Haruka's sword!
[Ayato thinking]
I finally get it now!
I know what my true purpose is!
And you're the one
who taught me!
I'll always be there for her,
and I won't fail.
I'll protect Julis!
[Maaya Sakamoto]
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪
♪ I'm bracing
for the thunder ♪
♪ A twig that
wouldn't sway ♪
♪ In the wind ♪
♪ Hear my yearning ♪
♪ See the crimson flame ♪
♪ Like a ruby ♪
♪ It's the hope ♪
♪ In my eye ♪
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ And I don't see you anymore ♪
♪ I still wouldn't sway ♪
♪ But I'd be missing you ♪
♪ Now don't be afraid ♪
♪ You're the flower
couldn't sting ♪
♪ You can hide in my shade ♪
♪ Or maybe I ♪
♪ Could I be safe ♪
♪ In yours? ♪
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪