Sorry to suddenly
change the subject,
but have any of you already made
plans for the winter vacation?
Well, for me,
since I learned so much
during the Phoenix Festa,
I decided that I should
use this opportunity
to do some intensive training.
I'll probably just go through
my usual regimen during break.
[Claudia] Since we're finally
getting some time off,
I thought I'd take it easy.
[Ayato] Really?
A quiet New Year's holiday
does sound pretty good.
You could always sleep through
New Year's with me, Aya...
[thud!]
Actually, there's something
that I'd like to discuss
with everyone.
What's up?
Huh?
[giggles] Hello, everyone.
I'm here with your ride
to the palace.
[crowd cheering]
‐Welcome home, Princess Julis.
We're glad you're here!
‐Awesome!
‐[girl 1] Mr. Amagiri!
‐[girl 2] Over here, Ayato!
[girls cheer]
[Ayato] How did we get
to this point anyway?
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"The Asterisk War" in Japanese]
♪ This is the Asterisk War ♪
[footsteps]
All right, brother,
what were you thinking, huh?
Oh, hey there, Julis.
Welcome home.
Oh, my, well, if it isn't
Julis and Claudia.
It feels like it's been ages.
It has been a while, yes.
If you'll please excuse me,
Maria,
would you mind giving
the two of us a moment?
‐I'd like a quick word
with my brother.
‐Not at all.
I know you all helped Flora out
during the Phoenix Festa.
I invited you here so that
I could thank you in person.
I'm happy to see you've
accepted my invitation.
I'm Julis's older brother
Jolbert.
You may know me best
as the king of Lieseltania.
And this is my wife, Maria.
It's such a pleasure
to meet all of you.
‐R‐Really nice to meet you.
‐It's a pleasure.
‐He's the king?
‐Never mind the introductions.
You didn't tell me
anything about there being
a victory parade.
If I had told you, would you
have agreed to the idea?
Of course not.
Making me go through it
is one thing,
but why did you have to drag
everyone else into it?
At least have the courtesy
to ask us about it first.
All right, all right,
I get it, I apologize.
Sorry for the deception,
everyone.
Please understand, Julis,
the people aren't intrigued
by you alone
but also by your partner,
Mr. Amagiri, as well.
After all, their princess did
handpick him, didn't she?
‐[Saya sighs]
‐[Claudia] Really?
The citizens are the only ones
who are intrigued by him?
Well, well, well.
You're just as perceptive
as ever, aren't you,
my dear Ms. Enfield?
[Julis] What's this about?
Do you think we could save
that discussion
for another time?
There are so many other things
I'd love to talk to you
and Mr. Amagiri about.
I guess we can save it
for later, then.
Yeah, sure, sounds good.
[Jolbert] One more thing.
I've gone and made arrangements
for a welcome banquet to be held
in your honor tomorrow night.
Hope I'll see all of you there.
Wow! It's so beautiful!
Uh‐huh. In the springtime,
all of the flowers
begin to bloom,
so it looks
even more beautiful.
All I wanted was for you
to see my country,
and all this happens.
I'm sorry it's become
such an ordeal.
Well, this place
is pretty incredible.
Everything's so majestic.
[Julis] Yeah. Both this garden
and the villa
were built during the time
of the Holy Roman Empire.
It later gained its independence
as the Kingdom of Lieseltania
and was wiped out
during the German Revolution.
[Ayato] No way.
[Julis] But after
the Invertia happened,
an extremely unique meteorite,
a high‐degree Grade‐A Beltis,
was discovered in the borders
of one of Lieseltania's
former lands.
And that's when the Integrated
Enterprise Foundation
began fighting over it
amongst themselves,
but there was no way they would
risk going to war over it.
So the foundation
signed an agreement
to share the wealth.
[Julis] From there, they thought
they might as well make
a small paradise for themselves
that they could
have their way with
and resurrected the country
that existed there before,
Lieseltania.
So it's basically
a puppet state.
I couldn't have
said it better myself.
Which is why the Integrated
Enterprise Foundation
keeps such a tight grip
on my homeland.
While we do receive some
financial aid and benefits,
many never see it
and a lot of our people
are silently suffering.
I want...
I need to change this country.
[Claudia]
I really must apologize.
No matter how many times
you ask, the answer is no.
Yes, of course,
I'm entirely aware.
Goodbye.
[sighs]
‐[knock on door]
‐Yes? Come in.
Excuse me, Mr. Amagiri.
What's going on?
Is everything OK?
The thing is, I can't find
Ms. Sasamiya anywhere.
She's not in her room,
and it's almost time for dinner.
Saya's directionally challenged,
so she probably just got lost.
Oh, wait, I think I might know
where she could be hiding,
so I'll help you look.
Saya, are you getting hungry?
Cos dinner's almost ready.
Ayato.
You OK?
Ayato...
I... I've always wanted to...
I've always wanted to tell you
that I'm sorry.
Not sure I know what you mean.
What could you be sorry about?
[Saya] After I moved away,
you and I somehow managed
to still keep in touch.
remember?
[Ayato] Yeah, of course.
[Saya] But then it got
too painful
and I felt like I couldn't
talk to you anymore.
Is that what really happened?
Because we used to play together
every day no matter what,
but after I moved,
all I could do was talk to you.
And then it wouldn't even be
for very long.
I looked forward to
our conversations so much.
But after a while,
it just hurt me,
so I decided it was best
if I stopped talking to you,
until we met again.
[Ayato] OK, I understand.
[Saya] But that's not all.
If I just kept in touch
with you the whole time,
I might have been able to be
there to support you when
your sister disappeared, Ayato.
Even if I couldn't have helped,
I still could have
cheered you up.
I would have found a way
to be there for you.
It makes me...
feel so frustrated.
[Ayato] Saya.
[Saya] I never should have
stopped talking to you.
Because even when...
when I wasn't there,
I was by your side.
So you should know,
you can lean on me, Ayato.
And from this moment on,
I'll make sure
I'm there for you.
Saya.
[Ayato] What I'm supposed to be
doing right now,
like it or not, is trying
to protect you, Julis.
That really means a lot.
And if that day ever comes,
just know I'm counting on you.
Come on, let's go.
Everyone's probably hungry
and waiting for us inside.
[Saya] OK.
Now then, I'd like to take
this opportunity
to discuss something.
It's about next year's Festa.
I have a request to make.
I want you all to join me
as teammates
and enter next year's
Gryps Festa.
I've already invited
Ayato to participate,
but he has one condition.
Julis has to join, too.
And you aren't going to change
your mind about this,
are you?
No. She goes, I go.
[Claudia] What are your thoughts
on this, Julis?
Before I answer, there's just
one thing I need to know
from you.
[Claudia] All right.
And that is?
Why enter the Gryps Festa?
In the Phoenix
or Lindwurs Festas,
you could easily advance.
[Claudia] Yes, that's true.
I would definitely be able
to advance,
but there's no guarantee
I'd be able to make it
through the finals.
And that would be unacceptable.
So your best chance
is the Gryps Festa?
[Claudia] Well, yes, as long as
I have dependable teammates,
of course.
I'll be able to go into further
detail of what I have planned
after you've all agreed
to partner with me,
since it has to do
with my Achilles' heel
and this one's.
Precognition
has an Achilles' heel?
Mm‐hmm. There's no such thing
as a perfect weapon.
But, President, you're
a really powerful opponent
even without your Pan‐Dora,
aren't you?
[Claudia] Oh, no, not at all.
My abilities are
fairly pedestrian without it,
which is precisely why
I need a powerful team
to join me.
Remember, anyone who hopes
to become the champion
of the Gryps Festa
needs to be able to defeat
the Life Rhodes.
Then there's
Zhao Hufeng and Cecily Wong,
former Festa runner‐ups.
They'll likely be competing
for Jie Long's team.
The Divine Revelation's
number one disciple
is rumored to be
a member of their team as well.
Right. Celestial Monarch.
They're Rank Number 2.
I hear he has
terrifying dexterity.
[Claudia] We also can't
underestimate Rusalka
of Queenvail,
or any of the other teams
standing in our way.
Sounds like the next Gryps Festa
will be quite the challenge,
doesn't it?
You read my mind.
Which brings me back
to my point.
If we enter the Festa together,
I just know we'll have a chance.
[Julis] It's settled then.
I'll join you in the Festa.
After all,
what do I have to lose?
[giggles]
‐[chuckles]
Mr. Amagiri, that looks nice.
Are you sure?
I've never had to dress up
like this before
so I'm kind of nervous.
Sorry, Mr. Amagiri.
You're not allowed to carry
weapons or things like that
during parties,
but I can hold onto it
for you.
Oh, OK, that's fine by me.
Hey, Julis, can I come in?
[Julis] Y‐Yeah, of course.
[gasp]
Why are you standing there
staring at us like that?
She does have a point, Ayato.
This is when you're supposed
to be showering us ladies
with compliments.
Yep, agreed.
Oh, no, well, I'm not, um...
I'm sure I don't look good
in this.
You don't have to say anything.
Well, let's see.
I think you all look
really beautiful.
[Claudia] Why,
thank you so much.
And you're looking
quite handsome as well.
Now then, as much as I'd really
like to be escorted by you,
Ayato,
Julis is the guest of honor,
which means you're all hers.
Just remember you still
have to spend time
with us later as well.
All right, go on!
[Julis] Uhh!
Well, I suppose I have
no choice then.
Here.
Now, let me help you.
Just bend your elbow a little.
That's it.
[Ayato] Uh... so sorry.
Don't worry about it.
If push comes to shove,
I can take the lead.
‐[Ayato chuckles]
‐[door opens]
[Flora] Excuse me,
is everyone ready yet?
Time for your appearance
at the banquet.
[laughter]
[sighs]
You look like you're
pretty exhausted.
It's that obvious?
I guess I had no idea there'd be
this many people here.
And don't take this
the wrong way,
but I thought you said
your family didn't have
any money left.
[Julis] Well, the country may
have plenty of money to spend,
but I don't have any
to use myself.
Besides, my brother isn't
anything like me.
[Ayato] What do you mean?
[Julis] He never speaks out
politically,
and he has no enthusiasm
at all for his job.
I guess you could say
he's the quintessential puppet.
That's why the Integrated
Enterprise Foundation
is so fond of him
as the country's leader
and why they willingly
turn a blind eye when he wants
to have his way.
Oh, and all those women,
they're my brother's lovers.
Uhh! His lovers?
He's pretty bold, isn't he?
[Julis] Just like
my sister‐in‐law,
they were also sent here
by the Integrated Enterprise
Foundation.
‐They aren't
exactly spies, but...
‐What about Maria?
[Julis] Well, my sister‐in‐law's
a genuine airhead.
As the saying goes,
"ignorance is bliss,"
especially in her case.
Although it's not as if
I dislike her.
As for Claudia,
her father's in charge
of this region
on behalf of the Galaxy.
She's visited Lieseltania
with him numerous times
since childhood,
which is why she and my brother
get along so well.
Is Claudia's father
an Integrated Enterprise
Foundation executive, too?
Not at all. I think he's
more like her mother's
own personal whipping dog.
‐He'd never make it
as an executive.
‐Why's that?
Because he's managed
to maintain his humanity.
The only way to become
an executive
is to lose whatever part of you
that makes you human.
That's why, for me personally,
her father made a much more
favorable impression
than her mother ever did.
At the very least,
it became clear to me
that he cared for his daughter
more than anything.
‐[Ayato] Hmm.
‐[Jolbert] Hey, Julis.
Damn my brother.
I don't want to drag you into
a situation like yesterday.
‐Can you...?
‐Mm‐hmm.
I think I'll go refresh my drink
and get some air.
[man] You're captivating
in that dress.
[Kirin, nervous] Oh, well,
thank you very much.
[man 2] Your Phoenix Festa
performance was magnificent!
Oh, uh, thank you for your‐‐
[woman] Do you happen to have
your sword on you?
Well, uh, no, you see, I, uh...
[Ayato] Hey, Kirin,
do you have a second?
[Kirin laughs]
Yes, of course.
I'm sorry. If you'll excuse me.
Ayato, thank you so much
for getting me out of there.
‐You saved me.
‐Oh. No problem at all.
It's just that, it can be
so hard for me to talk to people
that I don't know.
Besides, I'm not as pretty
as Julis or the president.
Huh? I don't think that's even
close to being true.
But, uh, what I'm saying is,
I think a dress like this
just isn't meant to be worn
by a child like me.
Huh?
I really did mean it
when I said that before.
You do look great in that dress,
like a true lady,
gorgeous and refined.
Huh? Thank you, Ayato,
for your compliment.
Sure thing.
Um, see you later, then.
[Kirin] Wait, um, I have
a favor to ask of you.
‐Is that OK?
‐A favor?
Yes. Well, um, if it isn't
too much to ask,
I'd like to link arms with you,
if you wouldn't mind.
It just looked so lovely when
you did it with Julis earlier,
so I would really
like to try it.
Well, I don't see why not,
but I don't know if I can be
a proper escort.
That's no problem at all.
If you're OK with this,
then that's enough for me, so...
If that's the case, then...
here.
Uh, wait a minute, Kirin,
I don't think you have to
hold onto me so tightly.
Oh, sorry, I'm really sorry.
Hey, stop hogging Ayato.
Arrgh! Whoa, Saya, what
in the heck's gotten into you?
I want to be able
to link arms with you, too.
[man] Now that's what I call
having a pretty girl
on each arm.
And I must say, that's the kind
of spirit I like to see.
Just the kind of behavior
I'd expect from one who made
his mark in the Phoenix Festa.
Right, thanks a lot, sir.
By the way, would you happen
to be planning to take part
in the Gryps Festa as well?
If the rumors are true,
you're thinking of joining
Ms. Enfield's team, yes?
[Ayato] Well, I haven't
quite decided.
[softly] Hmm.
Haven't decided, huh?
In that case...
a word of advice.
I believe it would be
in your best interest
not to join her team.
Just what are you trying to say?
What do you mean?
Was that not clear enough?
It wouldn't bode well
for a certain someone you know
should you decide
to join her team.
My job is to simply find
a way to stop you,
using whatever means possible.
And so I've decided
to give you this warning.
What if we decided to ignore it?
Now, that would be
so very unfortunate.
Never have I taken
pleasure in doing away
with an innocent youth.
So instead, I'll let my friend
here take care of that job
for me.
[energy pulses]
[roars]
[screaming]
If you'll excuse me,
please accept my condolences.
Come back!
Kirin, wait!
[roars]
Thirty‐Eight‐type
Lux Grenade Launcher.
Hernekraume!
Burst!
What did I say?
Didn't I tell you I'd be there
for you, Ayato?
‐Thanks, Saya.
‐[Julis] What's going on?
[gasp]
[creature roars]
Kirin, let me handle this.
OK.
[Julis] Ayato!
[roar]
Ayato, watch out!
Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
Grappling Technique.
Coffin Drill!
Amagiri Shinmei‐style,
Thunder!
Hyaaaa!
Saya, Julis!
[Julis] We can take it
from here.
Burst into bloom! Hernekraume!
‐Amaryllis!
‐[Saya] Kaboom.
[man] Who would have thought,
even a beast like that chimera's
no match for him.
And taking it down
without a weapon as well.
He's going to be
a bothersome one.
[snaps fingers]
I'd rather not get too involved
at this level of work,
but sometimes...
[chuckles]
[sinister chuckling]
[Haruka Chisuga singing
"Words of Love" in Japanese]