[crowd cheers]
[Meeko] Was that unexpected
or what?
The winner has been decided
in less than a minute!
With a fearsome display
of power,
Aldy and Rimsy
have shown everyone
that they're a force
to be reckoned with.
Those guys never stood
a chance, did they?
[Saya] Unless we get past that,
neither will we.
[Julis] Getting through
that wall of light will
take everything we've got.
‐[monitor rings]
‐[Saya] Huh?
Just a sec.
[Souichi] Did you
see that match just now?
‐I did.
‐Those puppets are controlling
over 5 Manadites concurrently.
That's far beyond
a human's ability.
But an artificial intelligence
could handle it, no problem.
Dad, wait,
you're going way too fast.
Hang on a minute,
is that Uncle Souichi?
[Souichi]
Well, if it isn't Ayato.
‐It's been quite a while.
‐Yeah, no kidding.
‐So, Dad, what's up?
‐Right.
I took the liberty
of sending you a new gun.
‐Has it arrived yet?
‐No, not yet.
Unfortunately, that means
it won't get there in time
for your first match.
Would you mind heading over
to Customs to double‐check?
[Saya] OK, but it won't
be a problem.
‐[Souichi] Hmm?
‐I've got the Arcwandels
so I'll be fine, trust me.
Of course I trust you, darling.
As long as you're
wielding one of my guns,
you're unstoppable.
All right, I await news
of your victory!
He hasn't changed much, huh?
[Saya] Nah. I'm heading
over to Customs now.
Oh, if you don't mind,
I'll come with you.
As for me, I'm gonna
see if I can sneak into
the press conference.
Wish me luck.
So what should we do
in the meantime?
We could celebrate
our first victory,
but we can't afford
to just rest on our laurels.
So maybe we should get
some practice in?
Sounds good.
Whoo‐hoo! Nice job, you two!
That was a spectacular
performance!
[Rimsy] You are too kind,
master.
[Aldy laughs]
[Aldy] Honestly, were you
expecting anything less?
‐Ohh! Aaah!
‐[thud!]
[Rimsy] How dare you present
that sort of attitude
before our master!
Have you no shame?
[Aldy] Rimsy,
quit joking around.
It's no joke.
If you continue showing
our master disrespect,
you'll be punished
just like any other.
Now, Rimsy, why don't we let him
off the hook just this once?
If that is your wish.
[Aldy] Master,
I have a question.
Very well, speak your mind.
[Aldy] As far as our specs
are concerned,
Rimsy and I are
more or less equal,
so why am I helpless
against her?
Well, that's just
the way it is.
Listen, it's like
that old saying:
"Woman is nature's contrivance
for perpetuating
its highest achievement,
whereas man,
man is woman's contrivance
for fulfilling nature's behest
in the most economical way."
People had such a way with words
in the olden days.
[Aldy] So what you're saying is
a male type like myself
will never be able to defeat
a female type like Rimsy?
It would appear so.
But anyway, we should probably
start heading back to our room,
don't you think?
We don't want to keep
Camilla waiting.
[Aldy sighs]
[Aldy] Then that's the way
it's to be.
[Ernesta thinking] Poor Aldy,
I can't tell you that Rimsy
is your limiter,
so for now, that explanation
will have to do.
[Shiena Nishizawa singing
"Brand‐new World" in Japanese]
‐Hurry up!
‐Julis! Hey, hold on a minute!
It's not like we're gonna
make it for the start
of the match anyway.
I'll just let them know
we're running
a little bit late.
All right, fine.
Come on, don't look so sad.
We both wanted to practice
till the last second.
[Irene] Take that!
[Julis] What's that? A fight?
[Julis] Wait.
That's Irene Urzaiz.
[Ayato] You know her?
[Julis] She's a Page One
from ReWolf.
[Irene] Jeez. Don't you dumb
asses know settling scores
is so played out?
Uggh! Shut up!
If we don't go through
with this, we'll lose face!
[Irene] Hyaaah!
Buzz off, it's not a sideshow.
Huh?
Just as I thought.
How's it going, Murakumo?
Huh?
What exactly
would the likes of you
want with my partner,
Lamirexia?
If it isn't the Glühen Rose.
This doesn't concern you,
so take a hike.
I can't do that.
Do you realize how many people
you put in danger
by dueling
in the middle of a crowd?
They're the ones who started
that free‐for‐all,
so don't go blaming me.
Regardless,
remember where you are.
One wrong move
and you're disqualified.
Hey, take it easy.
Then by all means, Glühen Rose,
why don't you teach me
proper dueling etiquette?
[energy pulses]
[Irene] Nice.
Pretty good reaction time.
Enough!
Oh, no!
[Priscilla] You've gotta be
kidding me, sis.
You're fighting
without permission again?
[Irene] Priscilla.
Apologies. Please forgive
my sister for causing
all this trouble.
Oh, there's no need.
All right, you apologize,
too, sis.
You want me to say
I'm sorry. Why?
Because.
I'm so sorry
for my sister's behavior.
[Irene] Come on, knock it off!
I'll be sure to give her
an earful.
OK, then,
let's get going now, sis.
Fine. Let's go.
[Ayato] I wonder if they're
really sisters.
I think there may be an entry
in the data Claudia sent.
Pricilla Urzaiz.
She's unranked, and there isn't
a shred of data on her
except that she's
Irene's partner.
I see.
By the way, why did you provoke
Irene back there?
That's not like you at all.
You heard what she said.
Her business didn't concern me.
I find that strange considering
I called her out.
Which means, for some reason,
her target was you.
But I don't even know her.
Knowing ReWolf, this could all
be part of some sinister scheme.
I wish I had more than just
a hunch to go on.
[Ayato] Yeah.
‐Uh!
‐What's wrong?
Saya and Kirin's match
has already started!
[Nanna] Holy cow, just listen
to that crowd roar!
And it's no wonder
why they're so excited.
She might have lost
her title the other day,
but don't let that fool you.
Ms. Toudou's still
the super rookie
who reached Seidoukan Academy's
Number One Rank when she
was just a junior high student!
And now that I'm
seeing her in the flesh,
despite her slight stature,
I can tell that she's
the real deal.
[Chitose] Nanna, Nanna,
the other one is Ms. Toudou!
The small one with the blue hair
is Saya Sasamiya.
Huh? For real?
No way she's in senior high!
Whoops. Looks like we made
a small mistake.
[Saya] That's putting it mildly.
[Kirin giggles]
[Saya] And where the heck
is Ayato?
They said they were
on their way, so I'm sure
they'll show up soon.
But for now...
[Kirin] They seem
pretty competent, don't they?
[Saya] Well, we're about
to find out.
Thirty‐four‐type
Wave Motion Heavy Gun...
Modified Arcwandels!
Which one do you want?
Huh? Oh, uh,
I'll just take whichever.
Gotcha. Then I'll take
the bigger guy.
Sounds like a plan.
[Nanna] Block L,
round one, match two.
Let the battle begin!
[crowd cheers]
Hyaah!
[virtual ref]
Badge broken.
[Nanna] Well, that was
certainly over quickly.
[sighs]
And the winner
of this short‐lived battle
is none other than Ms. Toudou!
Look, Nanna, the little one's
putting on a good show herself,
wouldn't you agree?
Oh, wow, she's unbelievable!
[opponent grunting]
[snarls]
Now burst...
[screams]
[buzzer sounds]
[Nanna] And it's over!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you your winners,
Saya Sasamiya
and Kirin Toudou
of Seidoukan Academy!
[crowd cheers]
‐Cool!
‐[Kirin giggles]
Hey, Saya, your gun,
it seems to be more than just
a hard surface from what I saw.
Mm‐hmm. In order to suppress
some of the excess output,
it's been modified to function
as an energy field.
So is that the reason
you were able to tolerate
all that close‐combat fighting
during our match today?
[Saya] Yeah.
[Kirin] From the way you were
handling yourself,
I would have guessed
that you were a student
of the Amagiri Shinmei style.
[Saya] I got most of my moves
from watching,
but Ayato did teach me
a few things.
I'm gonna head out.
Saya, wait! You'll catch
a cold if you don't
dry yourself properly!
Ahh.
[Saya] Hmm.
Uh, is there something wrong?
[Kirin gasps]
[Kirin] What are you doing?
[Saya] Since ancient times,
it's been said that massaging
can increase the size
of your breasts.
[Kirin] I don't know
where you heard that,
but it couldn't be more wrong.
No fair.
Sorry. But what can I do
about it?
[monitor blips]
Sorry, we lost track of time.
[gasp] If it's not too much
trouble, could you wait
just a minute?
‐It took you long enough.
‐Hey!
I hate that we missed
your match.
Uggh!
We won.
[gasp]
[Kirin screams]
[Meeko] It's Phoenix Festa,
day five!
Now let's get round two
started!
[Julis] All right then,
I let you handle
all the fighting during
our duel in round one.
‐Now it's my turn.
‐[Ayato] Gotcha.
[Yanon and Yosuga]
Hi, everybody!
It's a pleasure to meet ya!
We're from Queenvail,
the school for goddesses.
We're ranked number 37 and 54.
They call us "Non‐sugar"!
[crowd cheers]
Thanks so much for your support,
everybody!
We're gonna do our very best!
[energy pulses]
[Meeko] Without further ado,
let the battle begin!
And here we go!
Aaaaah!
Flame of the Torokia.
Scale the castle walls!
And burn down
the Nine Scourges!
Burst into bloom!
Scatter, Primrose!
[virtual ref] Badge broken.
That the best you've got?
‐Try not to underestimate me.
‐[crash!]
Now release... Semiserrata!
[screams]
‐[buzzer sounds]
‐[Meeko] End of match!
Ms. Riessfeld snatched victory
away from her opponents
through her rock‐solid
tactical strategy!
[Tram] While Yanon was focused
on the flurry of attacks,
Julis lured her target
into a flawless trap.
[sighs] Well,
that takes care of that.
You were great out there, Julis.
I don't feel like I did
very much, but thanks anyway.
[Julis] By the way,
what are your plans
for the rest of the day?
Let's see.
I'd like to make it
to Saya and Kirin's match
to cheer them on if I can.
Don't you think it will probably
be over by the time
we get down there?
And besides, we haven't had
a chance to have any lunch yet.
OK, why don't we grab
some food around here?
‐[Julis coughs]
‐You all right?
Uh... actually...
I, um...
Huh?
Hey, sandwiches, huh?
[Julis] Don't get your hopes up.
They're not super fancy
or anything.
Well, how is it?
To be honest,
it's really delicious.
You think so?
Huh?
I had no idea
that you cooked, too.
Impressive.
Give me some credit,
it's not hard.
Aren't you gonna have any?
Yes. It's just that
I don't like being...
Hmm?
I just don't like being treated
differently, you know?
What do you mean?
I just mean that...
you do this thing all the time
for Sasamiya and Toudou,
but never for me.
I'm not saying you
have to do it or anything.
I guess I just find it
kind of strange
that you've been excluding me.
Uh...
You aren't talking about...
that, are you, Julis?
Uh, OK.
Here goes nothing.
‐Aah!
‐Hey, here's an idea.
Why don't we take a look
and see how the other match
has turned out?
[Lester] Get moving, Randy!
[Julis] Oh, I didn't realize
their match was today, too.
[crowd cheers]
[Domitila] There you have it,
folks.
Team Lester‐Randy
is the first to strike!
Even though Lester and Randy
made the first move,
for some reason they're keeping
their distance from Irene.
What could they be planning?
[Maeve] Irene's weapon,
the Gravi‐Sheath,
is a powerful Ogre Lux
with the ability
to control gravity.
Since the weapon
is most effective when
an opponent has been targeted,
I believe the duo is trying
to stay on the move
to avoid being locked onto
by the deadly scythe.
[Lester] We're also trying
to take advantage of
that thing's tragic flaw.
It's an energy waster
They say no wielder has ever
been able to withstand
its side effects.
So, the longer we drag out
this fight,
the better our chances
of winning.
[Randy] We might as well
have some fun
while we're buying time.
So let's find out
what this girl's made of!
Hmm. When will you people learn,
this strategy isn't
gonna work on me?
Randy!
Ugggh!
Didn't you hear me before?
I told you
that's not gonna work!
Hyaaa!
I'll deal with you
a little later.
Get back here, damn it!
So, what's it gonna be?
Give up?
Yeah, right, keep dreamin'.
Feisty.
[energy pulses]
[virtual ref] Randy Hook
rendered unconscious.
That's one down.
Oh, looks like you're
as tough as I thought,
Raging Axe.
You know who
you're dealing with?!
Take this, you bitch!
Blast Nemea!
Arrrggh!
[Irene groaning]
Oh, Irene!
What do you think?
[Irene] Damn it.
That wasn't bad.
I guess I don't have
a choice, then.
Out of respect for your power,
I'll go all out.
[Lester] What the hell?
Are you hurt?
[Irene] Sorry, but I need
a little.
[Ayato] What's she doing?
[Julis] Unless I'm mistaken,
that kid sister of hers
must be a regenerative.
[Ayato] Hold on, a regenerative?
You don't mean she can use
her powers to heal wounds,
do you?
[Julis] Yes.
And if she's capable
of replenishing lost blood,
she's even more elite
than I thought.
That's an insane trump card.
My Gravi‐Sheath.
In return for its powers,
it yearns for the taste
of blood.
If you don't keep feeding it,
this baby gets all dried up
before you know it.
So to keep the blood coming,
it alters its wielder's body
and allows said body
to absorb more blood.
So you really are
a vampire, aren't you, lady?
‐Arrrggh!
‐Good. Bring it.
Cos now we're playing
for keeps!
Go!
Uhh! What the...
Don't worry, I just gave
the gravity a little boost.
Didn't want you escaping.
[Lester groans]
[chuckles] You'll probably need
an Ogre Lux if you're gonna
try blocking my gravity balls
head‐on again.
Piss off!
[screaming]
[Irene] Now then, Raging Axe
of the Distant Thunder,
still wanna fight?
[Lester] Enough!
I give up.
‐[buzzer sounds]
‐[Domitila] The match is over!
[applause]
[Maaya Sakamoto]
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪
♪ I'm bracing
for the thunder ♪
♪ A twig that
wouldn't sway ♪
♪ In the wind ♪
♪ Hear my yearning ♪
♪ See the crimson flame ♪
♪ Like a ruby ♪
♪ It's the hope ♪
♪ In my eye ♪
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ And I don't see you anymore ♪
♪ I still wouldn't sway ♪
♪ But I'd be missing you ♪
♪ Now don't be afraid ♪
♪ You're the flower
couldn't sting ♪
♪ You can hide in my shade ♪
♪ Or maybe I ♪
♪ Could I be safe ♪
♪ In yours? ♪
♪ I'm waiting for the rain ♪