[YAYA] You're amazing, Raishin!
That feels so--!
[YAYA moans]
[RAISHIN]
Quit yelling and moaning.
If anybody hears,
they'll think I'm doing
something untoward to you.
Well you don't
see that every day.
You've got a girl
hanging from a net?
What kinda sick
fetishes are you into?
I've been with
you all morning.
[YAYA] Yaya looked away
for point-three seconds
in the changing room!
And you think in less than half
a second I could've done this?
[RAISHIN] All right, what
are you doing in my room?
Easy, puppy.
He's an automaton, right?
[RAISHIN] Don't tell me you
got caught in your own net.
Honeytrap! Honeytrap!
[RAISHIN] Oh yeah?
Then where's the honey?
Are you blind?
She dangled herself
in the air like that
to give you a look
at her undergarments!
If you want to see
knickers so badly,
then you look at Yaya's!
I don't wanna see that!
Pardon.
I appreciate your help.
That was so kind.
I have luncheon.
Please accept it as
a token of gratitude.
[YAYA] She brought you a meal?
You are dating this hussy!
She didn't make it to thank
me for something I just did.
Obviously it's a trap!
[FREY] It's quite tasty.
I am an excellent cook.
[RAISHIN] That seriously
isn't the issue here.
[sighs]
[RAISHIN] What's it spiked with?
Um. I'd wanted
sleeping potion,
but that proved rather
too difficult to obtain.
So instead just lots of salt.
That's a ridiculous
substitution!
What do you expect salt to...
a... ccom... plish...?
[YAYA]
Hmm?
[running shower]
[FREY] I have such a chill,
I shall catch my death!
Perhaps if you warm me
with your body heat.
Like Yaya said--
Honeytrap!
I give up.
Just tell me what
you're doing here.
Yeah. I'm here to...
...assass... inate you.
[CHARLOTTE] This is
beyond comprehension.
She was there to assassinate
you, and you let her go?
Anyways, the only
white-haired chit
with a pup at Walpurgis is Frey.
She's a third year.
Registration code: Silent Roar.
And she's ranked at ninety-nine.
Meaning she'll be
your first opponent.
Clearly she's decided
you're too much
of a threat, and wants
to eliminate you beforehand.
You may be
ranked one hundred.
But since defeating
Felix and Eliza,
people have gotten
nervous about you.
Well, speak of the devil
and he shall appear.
[RAISHIN] Frey again. What now?
[CHARLOTTE] I believe she's
building some sort of cage.
That must be the bait.
What's on that cover?
Wait. Is that what people here
actually think about me?
That I read that
sort of thing? Criminy.
[LOKI] What foolishness
are you up to now?
[CHARLOTTE] Blade Emperor Loki!
[RAISHIN] Huh. So that's the
guy they call Sacred Blaze?
[LOKI] Dammit, Frey.
Why are you still wearing those?
I told you:
you need to withdraw.
You'll be hurt.
Yes, but--
[CHARLOTTE] Loki is only
in his second year,
but he's already
one of the Rounds.
In fact, he's even seen
as a possible challenger
to the "Marshal."
[RAISHIN] He and
Frey kinda look alike.
Don'tcha think?
Yes, naturally.
They are siblings.
The weak shouldn't meddle
where they don't belong.
They should simply
obey the strong.
[growls]
[LOKI] Very well. Cherubim!
[CHERUBIM] Command.
He forgets I'm a
puppeteer, too.
Okay, Rabbi. Let's go.
Attack.
[CHERUBIM] Ready.
Rabbi!
Festival starts
tomorrow, "Emperor."
You should save your energy.
[LOKI] Get stuffed.
No, thank you.
[LOKI] I'll kill you.
No to that one, too.
[LOKI] I am a humble,
tolerant person.
However, there are three
things I simply cannot abide.
People who order me around.
People who stand
against me. And, lastly--
Cocky Orientals
who stick their noses
where they don't belong!
Hey, what a coincidence.
I hate arrogant Westerners who
start fights for no real reason.
[LOKI] You're a moron.
You shouldn't speak
to your betters like that.
[RAISHIN] I think
you're the moron.
People so quick to declare other
people morons usually are.
[LOKI] Absurd!
Do you even know
how high my marks are?
[RAISHIN] If you measure
your smarts by your marks,
that's further proof
you're a moron.
[LOKI] And you
preserve your pride
by insulting those
superior to you.
Now that is moronic.
[RAISHIN]
You're the moron, moron!
No, that's you!
Nuh-uh, you!
[CHARLOTTE] Oh, be quiet!
[CHARLOTTE] You're both morons.
If you keep this up any longer.
I'll be forced to
kill the two of you.
Back off, Tyrant Rex.
I suggest you withdraw from
the festival, Second Last.
And keep your distance
from me and my sister.
No chance.
Um. I must thank you again.
What were you
two fighting about?
Loki blames me.
Do excuse us;
it's hard to explain.
I must go.
Blames her?
[RAISHIN] Hey.
What department is she in?
History, if I'm not
mista--Wait, "hey"?
I'm not your wife, to be
addressed so familiarly!
Raishin's wife? His wife?
I think she might
be in trouble.
And you want to
come to her rescue.
Well, I am not helping you,
so don't even ask!
Raishin has one wife,
and that's Yaya!
Raishin has no wives!
[CHARLOTTE] Not so much as a
scrap of useful information!
Unless you wanna hear comments
on the size of her bosom.
Well, thanks anyway.
You were pretty adamant
about not helping before.
[CHARLOTTE]
Um... So... Uh...
Would you say that you
like a generous one, as well?
Generous what?
Are you kidding me?
Good lord, you're even stupider
than I thought you were.
[RAISHIN] Um?
[CHARLOTTE]
Bosom, you twit. Bosom!
Do you get it now,
or must I draw a picture?
[RAISHIN] If you really
care for someone,
that sort of thing
doesn't matter.
Hmm? You truly believe that?
[YAYA]
Of course not. He's lying!
Huh?
How naïve are you, Blondie?
Raishin likes an ample bosom,
one that bounces around,
like Frey's does.
Yaya.
"She's in trouble!
We need to help her!"
You're no gallant hero,
you want what's in her blouse!
You make me sick! Ugh!
How dare you treat women with
such little respect! You cad!
[slap]
[RAISHIN] Yaya.
[YAYA] Yes?
[RAISHIN] Guess what emotion
I'm feeling again.
Hint-hint:
it's bubbling out of control.
Once again, that little vixen
was clearly making eyes at you!
Now you're just being absurd!
She was only looking
for some friendly advice!
[YAYA] You're an idiot,
you know that?
A complete and utter idiot!
[KIMBERLEY] As you can see,
so long as a puppeteer
is unconscious,
he emits no magical power.
However, it is
possible to draw out
power using certain talismans.
Ow!
Are you okay?
I'm not tutoring
you for my benefit.
It would behoove you
to pay very close attention.
The festival starts tomorrow.
So why do I need the help?
We all fight on the
same terms anyway, right?
Not even a little bit.
Has nobody explained
the rules yet?
Your position is by
far the most difficult.
The festival is
essentially a melee.
Though it doesn't
start out as such.
On the first night,
those in the one hundredth
and ninety-ninth
slots do battle.
The contest is
suspended at midnight.
Anyone whose glove is taken
before then is eliminated.
The next day, number
ninety-eight takes the field,
even if ninety-nine and
one hundred are still standing.
[RAISHIN] Okay.
So at that point I relax
and watch the
rest of the fighting
until finally taking the
field against the Marshal.
Yes, that would
be easier, wouldn't it?
Too bad for you, only
those in the upper ranks
have the option
of sitting out a fight.
And worse, the
lower-ranked, like you,
must remain on
the field of battle
for the span of
at least one hour.
[KIMBERLEY] The textbook
approach would be...
[RAISHIN thinking] Is that
what Frey's after?
Does she want to be Wise Man
badly enough to kill for it?
Nothing ever changes.
This benighted
academy is exactly as
it was all those years ago.
So the festival
begins at last.
I hope you know,
I expect much of you.
Of me, sir?
You don't mean Loki?
Loki's situation differs a bit,
and don't be self-effacing.
Why bother when I understand
your particular talents
better than anyone else could?
I know how hard you apply
yourself to the task at hand.
Now then,
a small gift for you.
I-I'm sorry.
The promise you made.
You haven't forgotten?
No, child. I am
a man of my word.
Do your duty, and we shall
all live together again.
Yes, sir.
[MALE VOICE 5A] Amazing! Tenzen
is truly gifted at his craft.
[MALE VOICE 5B]
It is no exaggeration
to call the boy a prodigy!
[MALE VOICE 5C] Talent like his
you see once in a hundred years,
if you're lucky!
[MALE VOICE 5D]
There's no doubt about it.
He's going to make the Akabane
clan world-famous someday.
[MALE VOICE 5E] Raishin,
on the other hand.
He's a different story.
[NADESHIKO]
Raishin, wait! Don't go!
[NADESHIKO] You can't!
Please just say
this is a bad dream!
You'll become a great
puppet master, Nadeshiko.
Better than even Tenzen someday.
[RAISHIN] Yaya!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
[YAYA] What is it?
Are we being attacked?
[RAISHIN] You're not Yaya!
So, who--?
[YAYA] Would you care to
explain just what you're doing?
You won't even let
Yaya in your bed,
no matter how often she begs.
See?
It was an assassination
attempt, not--
[YAYA] Bouncy-bouncy!
[RAISHIN] No, don't look
there. Look here! Weapon!
[RAISHIN] Wait, please don't--!
Auuuughh!!
[RAISHIN]
Yeah. I need you
to dig into Frey's
background for me.
At this rate, I don't
know how many more
of these night
raids I'll survive.
[IRORI] I had no idea
she was so dangerous!
I'll tell Master
of this right away!
Actually, I meant--
[CHARLOTTE] It's awfully
early in the morning
to be looking so glum.
[CHARLOTTE] This business
with Frey reminded me
of something I'd heard before.
And I decided you would
benefit from knowing it.
You may express your gratitude.
[RAISHIN] Thank you so much.
[CHARLOTTE] Now, have you
heard of Divine Works?
[CHARLOTTE] They're a
machinart studio on the rise,
having received a
nomination to compete
for the English Army's next
generation weapons contract.
They hold the patent on
the "Sonic" magic circuit.
And, they sponsor
both Frey and Loki.
Which means what?
Well, Rabbi and
Cherubim might be
new prototypes they're
testing in the festival.
Thing is--
Divine Works has an
unsavory reputation.
Supposedly, they obtained some
of their patents
through outright bribery.
No need to hold back
with people like that.
Teach the bloomin'
prats a thing or two.
Oh yeah, tonight's when
the festival kicks off.
That's right.
I'm thrilled to see you're
taking this so seriously.
Whatever will be will be.
Idiot. Do one thing at least.
Don't forget the amulet.
Thanks for the reminder.
[RAISHIN] Sonic.
Down, boy! Rabbi! Heel!
Is his circuit
on the fritz?
Rabbi! Wake up!
[RAISHIN] Don't worry.
He'll be fine.
That was only meant to stun.
Thank goodness!
[RAISHIN] See?
[FREY] You're hurt. Hold on.
I appreciate it.
So, do you always
carry bandages with you?
Yes, I'm a bit accident prone.
I'm sure you've noticed.
Maybe a little clumsy.
[FREY] I know.
Um. What happened
with Rabbi?
Oh. I'm sorry about that.
Hey, no worries.
I'm not upset about it.
How could you not be?
Because I'm just not.
[RAISHIN] All right, come clean.
Why are you so desperately
trying to kill me?
[YAYA] She's had enough
chances. Let's kill her.
Please just give the order.
Tell Yaya to destroy her.
Yaya will crush her into
teeny tiny bouncy bits.
Ugh...
[YAYA] Do what needs
to be done, Raishin.
This situation is
growing dangerous.
Before long... Before long...
Her bosom will render
you completely powerless!
Hypnotized by
two big mounds of fat!
I don't think I'm
the one losing control.
Yaya will destroy
all the vixens!
How could you be
so cruel, Raishin?
Going behind Yaya's back.
Having a secret tryst with her!
In what way did that
look like a tryst to you?
I was nearly killed by
that dog of hers--
S'prise!
Long time no see!
[YAYA and RAISHIN]
Komurasaki!
[RAISHIN] You uh--look
like you've grown a little.
[KOMURASAKI] You noticed!
So, you wanna touch 'em?
[RAISHIN] Keep your shirt on!
I'm talking about your
height, not your chest.
[KOMURASAKI] Go on,
give 'em a li'l squeeze.
They might even be bigger
than my sister's now.
[RAISHIN] Let's just
change the subject.
I'm a grown up now.
So grown up in fact, you could
even marry me if you want to.
Hahahaha.
You always did like a
good joke, didn't you?
Now, come on over
and chat with your
big sister like a good girl.
Yaya even saved you a spot!
You can sit right here!
Careful, you might
hurt your hand.
You should be careful.
Raishin will stop liking you
if you behave so violently.
Raishin! You wouldn't!
Say it's not so!
So. If Shoko sent you,
I can probably guess the reason.
Time for some
reconnaissance work?
Clever as usual, I see!
The location we're infiltrating
should have many
secrets to reveal.
Let's go.
As an agent of the Army,
spywork is my official job.
So what will
Yaya be doing?
[KOMURASAKI]
Sorry, you're not invited.
Really, it's true.
My instructions explicitly say
to bring only Raishin with me.
But-- No fair!
I'm sure we won't be long.
Fine. Go then.
[RAISHIN] Komurasaki?
[KOMURASAKI] Okay!
I'm excited. Let's do it!
Give me your magic, Raishin.
Pour it all into me! I'm ready.
Be careful.
[RAISHIN] Even though
I get why it's happening.
It always feels strange to
have people looking through me.
[KOMURASAKI]
Turbid Haze is so helpful.
When activated, it works as
sort of an "invisibility cloak."
It neutralizes the
observer's senses,
effectively putting
the user in stealth mode.
We could have a romp right here
and no one would even know.
[RAISHIN] You're starting
to sound like Yaya.
[KOMURASAKI] Aw, look!
So many puppies!
[RAISHIN] Here we go.
[jangle of keys]
[door creaking open]
[KOMURASAKI] Is it empty?
[RAISHIN] No. It's not.
[SIGMUND] This is a surprise.
You don't often come
out alone. Now then.
What did you wish
to speak with me about?
[YAYA] Yaya is
sorry to bother you.
But she wanted to know.
Have... Have you ever
wished you were human?
[SIGMUND] Hm. Would I be
correct in assuming that you do?
[YAYA] Human girls
have everything.
It isn't fair! Yaya wants more!
If only--if only
Yaya were human!
[SIGMUND] If you were,
I doubt you'd be
very good at protecting Raishin.
Is that really something
you'd be willing to sacrifice?
You are an extraordinarily
gifted automaton, Yaya.
What Raishin needs in his life
isn't an ordinary human girl.
No. The truth is,
he needs someone like you.
Think about it again.
Do you truly still
wish to be human?
[YAYA] Maybe you're right.
Maybe it is good Yaya's a doll.
Even if Raishin
doesn't return
the affection
Yaya feels for him.
She can still be there to
help him when he needs her most.
Even if Raishin develops
a pointless infatuation
with some fragile,
weak-willed, human girl.
Even if he stops
paying attention
to Yaya no matter
how hard she tries.
Even if he keeps company
with little vixens,
if he holds them
and kisses them.
Yaya cannot accept this!
Hmmm...
You've got the appearance
and behavior of
a real girl down.
And Raishin doesn't
distinguish between human
and doll as so many others do.
As much as it pains
me to suggest this.
Perhaps the problem
isn't that you're a doll,
but that your approximation
of human nature is a bit dodgy--
Huh? HUH?!
[YAYA screams]