[YAYA] Raishin!
Please don't go!
Raishin! Please!
[RAISHIN] Wh-- Nadeshiko?
[NADESHIKO]
Please don't go, Raishin!
You know I don't
have any choice.
Dad's making me.
You can't!
You said we'd watch the
Ryogoku Bridge fireworks
together again next year,
or was that a lie?
You told me you
would stay right here
by my side until I find
a husband, remember?
You promised!
But you lied to me!
How can I forgive you?
It's time to grow up.
If you're so helpless without
your big brother around,
it's good that I'm going.
[sobs]
Just open your eyes!
Please, Raishin! Wake up!
Cherubim. We're done here.
[CHERUBIM]
Yes, sir. Why, sir?
Wouldn't want
him to die on me.
That'd result in
my disqualification.
[CHERUBIM] Yes, sir.
[YAYA sobs]
[BRONSON] Why did you not
take his glove when he was down?
I could have
made the attempt,
but the automaton would've
fought back most strenuously.
What should you
care if it did?
You think my Cherubim
would be bested
by a doll with an
unconscious puppeteer?
It was a Banned Doll, sir.
If we'd kept on, its puppeteer
would've died before long.
Contestants who
cause the death of
an opponent are disqualified--
regardless of the reason.
Very well.
You've one more thing
still to explain, boy.
Why did you forfeit seventh
place and drop to ninety-ninth?
I had to keep
Frey out of that fight.
There was no chance
that she would win.
We want to compare the Garms'
and Angels' performance.
To do that, we must
eliminate Second Las--
[BRONSON] That
won't be called for.
If you do not stop
acting without my leave,
I shall be forced
to stop your heart.
Now, when you
face Rabbi tomorrow,
endeavour to destroy it.
It will be best
for Frey, as well.
As you wish, Father.
I understand.
[YAYA] Yaya is his puppet!
Let her come in
with him! Please!
[CHARLOTTE thinking]
Idiot girl!
They'll find out she's
a Banned Doll for sure!
Sister, why are you here?
[CHARLOTTE thinking]
"Sister"?
You need to
calm down, Yaya.
But Raishin
won't wake up!
It was just like that other
time! He shielded Yaya!
All that blood!
It was Yaya's fault!
She's a bad doll! She--
Now, take a breath.
How do you think panicking
will help the situation?
[IRORI] You know
how strong Raishin is;
you need to believe in him.
Show him some patience.
If nothing else,
you know he'll refuse to die
until he's defeated Tenzen.
[CHARLOTTE]
Has there been any change?
[SIGMUND] None. He's still
unconscious, apparently.
Keep resting. I shall
alert you if he wakes.
[CHARLOTTE] Mm.
[CHARLOTTE] He is such an idiot.
A prize idiot.
A boundless idiot!
No human could
withstand an attack like
that without sustaining
life-threatening damage.
[SIGMUND]
About that...
Huh?
It sounds strange,
but I think Loki
may have held back.
I don't see how
that would be possible.
Cherubim was in the
middle of his attack,
and Loki could only ease
off at that point if--
Wait, could there
be a magic circuit
that allows for
such precise control?
I cannot be certain,
but the answer to
that may hold the key
to the Blade Emperor's defeat.
We must be
sure to tell the idiot
about this when
he awakens.
Must we?
The more Raishin wins,
the stronger he'll become.
Imagine just how powerful
he'll be once he's worked
his way through the ranks
and he finally has to face you.
Don't get carried
away, Sigmund.
I am still Charlotte
of the House of Belew!
No matter how
powerful he becomes,
I shall face him on the
battlefield and crush him.
[thinking] You had
better not die, Raishin.
After all, you
should be honored just
to have me worrying about you!
[YAYA] If there are any
gods out there listening,
please save Raishin's life.
Yaya begs you.
She promises not to
be selfish anymore.
Even if Raishin flirts
with a human girl,
Yaya will not be
angry or jealous.
Even if he rejects
Yaya's attention
and comes home
smelling of another girl.
Or spurns Yaya for
one of those vixens.
Even if one day
he suddenly declares
he's found a girlfriend.
[rumbling]
N-n-no wait!
That was an accident!
Yaya will be good! She promises!
Yaya won't be jealous or
obsessive or violent ever again!
[KIMBERLEY] So. How is he?
[CRUEL] Lucky, that's how.
He was slashed
with a giant sword
and he's still breathing.
That's a good start.
A couple more millimeters
and it would have
punctured a lung.
A centimeter would've
hit his heart.
[KIMBERLEY] It is likely he'll
survive, though?
[CRUEL] As far as this
wound, yeh. However.
His vital forces are
still being drained.
He could drop dead,
without any warning.
Thanks, Doc.
So, lad, do you
have enough fight left
in you to return
to the festival?
[MALE STUDENT 7A] See!
Blade Emperor's keen
for the fight to start.
[MALE STUDENT 7B]
Well, I dunno why.
The bottom fifty together
couldn't match him.
This fight'll be a bore.
[MALE STUDENT 7C] Shh! Look!
Here comes Silent Roar!
[LOKI] I'm surprised
you're here, Frey.
Disappointed as well,
I might add.
I expected you to
back out of this bout.
No. I would never
run away from this, Loki.
[LOKI] Ever since
we were children,
you've been slow and
clumsy at everything.
Always so eager to give up
when things got hard.
How many hundreds
of times did you
get frightened and
run to me for protection?
Yet here you are now.
You don't actually
intend to fight me?
You don't get it.
My entire life,
I've always thought
you could do anything.
So bright and
brilliant and strong.
Good at everything you try.
Never letting fear take over.
Just calm and steady.
And that made
things easy for me.
All I had to do was stay near
you and keep out of sight.
Now here we are.
You may despise me,
but it doesn't matter.
I am going to
fight you tonight!
I can't keep cowering
in your shadow.
I can't protect
anyone from there!
You foolish girl.
Who are you protecting?
Rabbi!
Feeble attempt.
Evade!
Go, Rabbi! Attack again!
You didn't learn
the first time?
Rabbi!
Rabbi. No!
You'll want to
close your eyes.
This will be its end.
[CHARLOTTE] Such strong magic!
How can a human even
put out that much power?
Rabbi? Are you--?
Something is wrong over there.
That's not Frey's magic
controlling him anymore.
[growls]
[FREY] Wha--?
[screams]
What the devil is going on?
[SIGMUND] Looks as
if Frey's magical power
is being forcibly
drained out of her.
What do you mean
"forcibly"? That shouldn't--!
If it doesn't stop,
she'll die!
[CHARLOTTE]
What's that around them?
Looks like some
kind of force field.
Her blood is being
transformed into magic.
Cherubim. Halt.
[CHERUBIM] Yes, sir.
No! Rabbi! Stop it!
We have to help them!
You will do no such thing!
Students may enter the festival
arena by invitation only.
Setting foot in there now
would be the very
definition of poor form!
[CHARLOTTE] Now is not the
time to worry about form!
Stand down, Tyrant Rex.
Someone is already on the job.
Huh?
That bloody idiot!
[RAISHIN] Mind if I cut in?
Think I'd like to
give this dance a try.
Now, Yaya!
Whistle Twenty-f--
Ugh! Wha'd you do that for?
[LOKI] For sticking
your nose in again!
Now buzz off and
annoy someone else.
Cherub--
What was that for?
For bein' an
arrogant ass!
Do you even know
what you're gonna do?
You are a complete
and total idiot.
Obviously, I'm going to
stop Rabbi from killing me.
No, you're the
idiot here.
Don't you see
what's going on?
If you attack now, you're
putting Frey's life in danger!
You don't
understand anything.
Now shut up and watch, while
I do what needs to be done.
[RAISHIN]
You shut up and watch me!
[LOKI] Not a chance, idiot!
You are determined
to interfere!
Sure am! I won't
let you kill Rabbi!
[LOKI] If he isn't put down,
spectators might get hurt,
and Frey will likely die.
[RAISHIN]
If that's your only plan,
back off and let me do this.
I'll stop him,
without killing him!
[thud]
Augh! Uhnn...
[LOKI] Give up.
You can barely stand as it is.
This is the only way
left to save my sister.
[LOKI] I'll destroy
its heart in one blow.
The monster must die,
so Frey may live.
[RAISHIN]
That's not good enough.
If this ends with Frey
alive and Rabbi dead,
do you think she'll thank you?
You'll still be
killing a part of her!
So what's your solution?
Save the dog and watch her die?
No, idiot.
I plan to save them both!
Yaya! Whistle 24 Sho!
Right!
[RAISHIN] Good job!
Now hold him back for me!
Don't hurt him!
[RAISHIN] Loki?
I am a humble,
tolerant person.
However, what I cannot abide
is someone who is all talk.
You say you can handle this,
so hurry and do it
so I can kill you.
Dream on, pretty boy.
I'm gonna kill you first!
All talk!
[RAISHIN] Sorry for this.
Behold: a goddess!
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry.
It's just that-- I have
no one else to turn to.
Now's not the time, boy,
but there will be a lecture.
I wouldn't want to intrude
without your permission.
Granted, of course.
In fact, I'd be honored.
It's not often I get to see
the great Karyusai at work.
I'll need insulated forceps
and a conductance catheter.
Ethanol and
distilled water, too.
Plus salt, and plenty of it;
the last thing
I want is to run out.
Irori, go and fetch
me a washbasin
full of ice, won't you?
[IRORI] Yes, ma'am.
[SHOKO] If it's not too
much trouble, Professor.
Would you locate
a pair of shears,
and snip a lock
of the girl's hair?
About Rabbi.
[SHOKO] Save it.
You owe me dearly, boy.
A magic circuit.
You just removed
it from him?
[SHOKO] The Army will receive
the specimen they requested.
They should have
no reason to complain
that I left the
poor dog alive.
Thank you, ma'am.
You're getting
ahead of yourself.
Don't thank me yet.
His chances of survival
are still quite slim.
So, what exactly
happened out there?
Why did Rabbi
suddenly lose control?
Silly boy, you
have it backwards.
Frey was the one
who lost control.
What?
[SHOKO] The amount of power Frey
sent Rahbi exceeded safe levels.
It overwhelmed his reason,
turning him into a monster.
Clearly you didn't know there's
a magic circuit
installed in Frey's heart.
In her heart?
[SHOKO] Like a parasite designed
to forcibly extract
power from its host.
While it increases
her magical affinity,
it will, eventually,
reconfigure her entire body.
[SHOKO] Have you heard
of "White Mediums"?
In this country,
I understand they are
known as "Promised Children."
Young people born
incredibly rich in magic.
Can you imagine the benefits
if these kids could
be mass produced?
You're saying you
think Frey and Loki are--?
[SHOKO]
Synthetic White Mediums, yes.
Divine Works' most
important laboratory rats.
Frey's power is unnatural.
Its flow has been
artificially divided.
There can be no doubt,
her heart has definitely
been mechanized.
[RAISHIN] Divine Works installed
machines inside of humans?
[SHOKO]
The change in their coloring
is the most visible side effect.
The load on their bodies must
cause a breakdown in melanin.
[RAISHIN] That sort of
procedure can't be easy?
[SHOKO] Of course not.
Did you not see what
happened to those children
whose surgeries were
less than successful?
Not another step.
I forbid you from setting
one foot off campus.
Ugh! But, ma'am!
Do you remember our
discussion about arrogance?
You can do nothing about
this situation, boy.
How much more plainly
must I phrase it?
Any way you slice it,
you're simply no match for him.
Try as you might,
you would accomplish nothing.
[RAISHIN]
"Him," who?
The head of Divine
Works, naturally.
Named Bronson.
He was a student
here twenty years ago.
Even earned the Wise Man title.
Now, I hope you haven't
forgotten our agreement.
You don't get to
die a pointless death.
Are you sure
you're allowed out of bed?
Just so y'know,
Shoko's the
world's best doll maker.
So, uh, I'm sayin' there's
a good chance he'll make it.
When he's feeling up to it,
you should think about
letting Char visit.
She kinda has a
soft spot for dogs.
Doesn't sound
like Tyrant Rex.
Yeah, an intimidating nickname,
but not a bad person.
Tough to get to know, maybe.
She's not really unfriendly
though, just misunderstood.
She's kind of
like me in some ways.
I don't have many friends
either, but I wasn't lonely.
I had my family, and,
of course, I always had Rabbi.
And Yomi?
Was she like family, too?
Absolutely.
We were very close.
In fact, she was almost
like a second mother to me.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Don't blame yourself.
It was me. It was
because I was so weak.
When my parents died,
I was supposed to
be the one on stage,
but I was too scared.
So my mom--
she went instead.
Loki, my own
brother, hates me,
because I'm weak and
frightened and worthless.
But he's strong, strong enough
to be Cherubim's operator.
[FREY] I'm sorry, Rabbi.
I'm sorry I didn't protect you.
I'm sorry everyone dies
because I'm so weak!
[RAISHIN] Don't say that.
It's not true!
None of it's your fault.
Understand? Not one bit.
[RAISHIN] Yaya.
[YAYA] Yes?
[RAISHIN] I'm an idiot, right?
Yes!
[CHARLOTTE]
And where do you think
you're off to at this hour?
[RAISHIN] Taking a stroll.
To the orphanage, I'd guess?
You're gonna steal
Rabbi's automaton siblings
before they're
demolished, aren't you?
[RAISHIN]
Nice girls don't eavesdrop.
And here I thought
you were a lady.
You can barely even walk,
and you want to put
your body through more?
Think this through.
You're half-dead already!
Are you hoping
to finish the job?
There's nothing
to worry about, Char.
I have the world's
best automaton at my side.
No one can touch me.
Besides, I thought this was the
kind of thing you'd understand.
Because family is sacred.
And you don't let it
go without a fight.
[CHARLOTTE]
I'll have to stop you, then.
You want to get yourself killed?
You'll have to fight
me for the privilege.
[RAISHIN] What are you
getting so worked up for?
So what if I die?
No loss to you, right?
[CHARLOTTE] It isn't about that!
Look, I owe you a
debt for saving me.
Well, assisting me, a little.
And as a proper English lady,
it is only right I return
the favor in kind by
rendering you assistance.
So there.
I shall do what's necessary.
Including protecting
you from yourself.
Even if it means you'll hate me
when all is said and done.
I think you're forgetting
about the amulet.
It's defensive
power saved my life.
So you owe me nothing.
We're even-steven, Char.
[CHARLOTTE] That was a
gift. It doesn't count.
[RAISHIN]
I'm asking for your trust.
You don't hafta trust in me.
But at least trust in the
magic strength of the amulet.
That is not fair.
It's downright tacky.
Using my gift
against me like that.
Hmph! Fine, you twit,
go die in a ditch somewhere!
And may wild dogs eat your body!
I can always
count on your stupidity.
It's as reliable as Big Ben!
[RAISHIN] Thanks to Komurasaki,
getting off campus
was simple enough.
But getting in there will
be a different matter.
[YAYA] They sure
have a lot of guards.
[RAISHIN]
What happened yesterday
must have made
them extra cautious.
You flirting
with Komurasaki?
Yaya's surprised it
didn't make them vomit.
Let it go Yaya, that's
not what happened.
And show some respect.
I almost died.
[YAYA]
They've already been scrapped?
[RAISHIN]
Dammit, I smell an ambush.
Time to get rowdy. Ready?
[YAYA] Yes. Yaya's always ready.
[RAISHIN] Flare 12 Ketsu!
[YAYA] Right!
[LOKI] I am a humble,
tolerant person.
However, there are three
things I simply cannot abide.
Those who order me around,
those who stand against me,
and, of course,
foolhardy idiots like you.