Just stay close.
You'll be fine.
[RAISHIN] Look out!
[RAISHIN] Yaya!
Concentrate.
Sense his movements.
Use fighter's
intuition to track him.
[YAYA cries out]
No!
[gasps]
[gags]
Rai... shin.
Augh!
Stop it!
Whatever am I thinking?
I nearly forgot my young
master's explicit orders.
[SHIN] While the
Granville's deserve a butler
with enormous talent,
I am not without my failings.
If I had to name
one flaw it would be--
The slightest tendency
toward absentmindedness.
I remember now, though.
My orders, Master Akabane,
were to bring him your head.
Stop it! Please,
I'm begging you!
[LOKI] I am a humble,
tolerant person.
However, there are three
things I simply cannot abide.
People who order me around.
People who stand
against me. And...
...bastards who
go after my prey.
Second Last isn't yours to kill!
[LOKI] Cherubim!
[CHERUBIM] Ready.
Spin! Cherubim!
[thinking] That didn't
even touch him.
[barking dogs]
[FREY] Rabbi!
[LOKI] You should
stay out of this, Frey.
If you interfere,
you'll only be in the way.
[LOKI] Look, what
I'm trying to say is,
it's difficult for me
to protect somebody
in the middle of a fight.
It can be a bit distracting.
I-- uh. Okay,
wait a minute.
What was that for?
[FREY] A way to
thank you. That's all.
I appreciate you
protecting Raishin.
Professor Kimberley
is forcing me to do it.
I don't need anyone's gratitude.
[LOKI] Why are you
lookin' at me like that?
Was there something
you wanted to say?
[CHERUBIM] No. No, sir. Ready.
[CEDRIC] Chilly. These late
nights are murder on my skin.
You've something to report?
My most abject apologies.
I failed to recapture
Henriette as ordered.
[CEDRIC]
There was no helping it.
What with Sacred Blaze
making a surprise appearance.
[SHIN] Master. I have
also failed to bring you
the head of Second Last.
[CEDRIC] You still have much to
learn about my sense of humor.
I didn't want him beheaded.
I was putting on an act
for the Belew tramp.
Forgive me, Master,
I am not quite
certain I believe that.
It would have its uses.
[CEDRIC] Indeed.
I would still love to
have it, were it feasible.
Akabane's head would make
rather superb magic material.
But if we're to succeed,
we must not be too greedy.
The Granvilles'
objective is to assist
the Kingsforts in
their time of need.
However, you and
I have a different goal.
To reveal your existence to
highly-placed academy faculty.
With that in mind,
preparations are
proceeding according to plan.
We've even confirmed
the existence of the
Cathedral of Fools.
I'm most satisfied.
Now then, what have you
discovered about Magnus?
To be perfectly honest,
I'm outmatched.
It would simply not be possible
to defeat all six of his
automatons on my own.
[CEDRIC] Put your findings
in a detailed report.
After all, one rarely
gets a chance to face off
with his 'Squadron' directly.
Oh, and, investigate
the Cathedral.
My understanding
is that another team
is exploring the
site at present.
[CEDRIC] Not anymore.
They've been eliminated.
The vaunted
headmaster of Walpurgis,
old Edward Rutherford, is a
formidable opponent indeed.
He wasn't hailed as
the most powerful mage
of the nineteenth century
without reason.
[SHIN] The deadline
swiftly approaches.
Will Tyrant Rex succeed
in her assignment
to assassinate
Headmaster Rutherford?
[CEDRIC] Not a chance.
Magnus is practically glued
to Rutherford's side.
Killing him now
will be impossible.
I could send an entire division
and they wouldn't succeed.
Then why ever did you task
Charlotte with his murder?
In order to placate
the Kingsforts' wishes.
They'd be thrilled
if she succeeded.
But if she failed, they
would quite obviously plan
to pin the blame
on the Granvilles.
They have plots within plots.
As we speak, they're
even covertly trying
to seal an accord
with the academy.
[SHIN] Interesting. What sort
of accord are they seeking?
[CEDRIC] What else would it be?
Joint research into
"god replication."
[SHIN] Ah. I see.
Then if the Granville butler
were to appear involved.
[CEDRIC] Fear and
suspicion abound.
Of course, the adults' agendas
are only part of my motivation.
I'm also doing this
because I want to.
After all, the pursuit
which gives me the
greatest pleasure is witnessing
the misfortune of others.
As always, young master,
there can be no doubt you
are rotten to your very soul.
Thank you, Shin.
Now. I have a thirst.
Make me some tea before
we begin your punishment.
Something that'll
pep me up a bit.
As you wish.
[distant howling]
Oh, wow.
You really do
despise dogs, don't you?
[HENRIETTE] You're awake!
I don't though.
I like them, really.
[RAISHIN] You do? Then why're
you so afraid of 'em?
[HENRIETTE] Because of Alfred,
our canine automaton.
My sister gave me care of him
while she was away at school.
If only I had been able
to control him properly!
The prince never would
have come to any harm.
Now everything
that's going wrong
is my fault again.
I simply don't care anymore!
[RAISHIN] What do you mean?
Don't care about what?
[HENRIETTE]
We were given a deadline.
They said if Charlotte failed
to kill the headmaster
before dawn, they would kill us.
So, you see,
our time is nearly up.
[RAISHIN] You shoulda
told me that sooner!
No, please! Don't go!
You have to help me kill myself!
Charlotte might
have a decent chance
of escaping if she
were on her own.
Without me holding her back.
[RAISHIN] Don't say that!
Why the hell do you
think Char's doing all this?
It's because she
wants you to live!
[HENRIETTE] You know.
I've always been
so envious of Char.
She's my big sister; so smart,
beautiful, and brave.
Everyone always liked her.
But I was there, too.
Always stuck in her shadow.
No matter what,
I could never be as good as her.
I'm nothing like her at all.
The truth is... I hate her!
My own sister!
I could have taken the
blame for our family's fall,
but instead, I made it
seem like Alfred's fault.
Charlotte's fault.
Don't you see?
I'm a wicked,
horrible girl. So, I--
You're wrong!
Everyone gets
jealous sometimes.
You don't really hate your
sister, you're just scared.
[RAISHIN] You gotta
stop running away, Henri!
It's time to face
your true feelings!
I'm afraid!
[RAISHIN] It's your choice.
What do you want me to do?
I want you-- I want
you to save my sister!
Of course.
I'd be happy to.
Yaya! What's wrong?
Yaya is sorry. She
failed to protect Raishin.
Because of Yaya,
you were hurt.
[RAISHIN] Don't be silly.
I'm the one who's sorry.
When this pretty
face got hurt today,
all I could do was watch.
You deserve far better than
that from your puppeteer.
Yaya's fine.
Even so, I am sorry.
It seems I'm always
causing you pain,
even when I try not to.
Anyway.
There'll be plenty time
to beat myself up more
after we bring
Dinosaur Girl back.
What about Henri?
[yawns]
I can look after her.
Can you?
That'd be great.
Mhmm. It's no trouble.
We'll stay here and
keep her company.
[RAISHIN]
Thanks, Frey.
Oh. I could probably
track Char down faster
if I had one of
your dogs with me.
Would that be okay?
You won't do
anything dirty?
[RAISHIN] Of course not!
You really think I'm some
kind of deviant, don't you?
Here, Riviera.
Nothing to be scared of,
girl. I think.
Thanks for
the help, Riviera.
Are ya ready?
It's Shoko.
I find myself in
an unpleasant mood.
Wanna help?
[RAISHIN] Sure.
I'll say this only once,
boy, so listen good.
You're at a crossroads
and you gotta take
one of two paths.
Go on back to bed and
sleep like a good child.
Or continue, and I'll put
you to sleep right here.
And what if I choose
neither of those paths?
You cannot honestly
mean to defy me.
Nothing in this world is
more tragically worthless
than a dog who's
forgotten his master.
Well, that's me.
[SHOKO] Yaya.
Come here right now.
But Raishin...
[SHOKO]
I said now.
Yaya's sorry.
She can't leave.
She wants to stay by Raishin's
side. Whatever happens.
I never want to see your
face again, boy, understand?
It's okay.
Shoko's scared.
She'd only react that way with
someone she truly cared for.
Yeah, I know.
And I don't enjoy
worrying her, but still.
I can't abandon the
"Awkward Sisters."
Not when they need my help.
[CHARLOTTE] Let's go.
It's not too late to
reconsider your plan.
Stop and think, Char.
[CHARLOTTE] I'm sorry! But if
I disobey, Henri will die.
[SIGMUND] That may be true,
but what guarantee
have they given us that
she'll live if we succeed?
[CHARLOTTE] Sigmund!
[SIGMUND] If you do this, you'll
never be able to go back to him.
Remember how
lonely you were?
How the other
students avoided you?
It was beginning to
look like you'd never
develop any real
friendships here.
And then you
finally found someone
who was willing to take
the time to understand you.
Giving Raishin up
means sacrificing
the happiness it took
you so long to find.
Is that what you want?
Doesn't matter. It's too late.
I am an assassin,
out to kill the headmaster.
There's no turning back.
Happiness isn't
an option for me!
[SIGMUND] I've failed.
If I'd only been stronger,
I would have been able to save
you and Henri from this fate.
[CHARLOTTE] No! That's not true!
I've been hurt and
depressed and alone.
I've been frightened and unsure,
but through it all,
you were always there.
You've never left my side!
So thank you.
Now, I can't just sit
here bawling forever.
It'll be dawn before long.
[SIGMUND] That's right.
And while I have nothing
against the headmaster,
we do as we must.
[RAISHIN] If you got nothing
against him, don't kill him.
Heya, Dinosaur Girl.
How's about that second date?
[CHARLOTTE] Raishin.
Just forget this
stupid plan of yours
and go back to the dorm.
Catch up on your beauty rest,
apologize to the
board of trustees,
get a good stern talking-to.
Then go into town
with me to celebrate.
Instead. You could
celebrate here on campus
where Yaya can chaperone.
Don't stand in my way.
[RAISHIN] Now which
one of us is the twit?
Have you honestly forgotten
what you came here for?
Kill the headmaster today,
and you will never restore
the Belew family name.
Your dream will die with him!
You think
I don't know that?
I'm doing this because
I have no choice!
[SIGMUND] Stand aside, laddie.
Please don't force us
to hurt you, as well.
And what
makes you so sure
you two would get
the best of us?
[SIGMUND] It is a dangerous
fancy to believe your power
is equal to that of the Rounds.
You think far too highly
of your own abilities.
Char will do what
she believes necessary.
Whether you can understand
it or not, the fact remains.
There is only so much
one human can do.
No matter how talented
a puppeteer she may be.
No see, I think you're the
one who doesn't understand.
It doesn't matter how weak I am.
Or how strong you and Char are.
Regardless of our
enemy's strength,
Yaya and I refuse to back down.
Ever. You know why?
Go, Sigmund!
As I was saying,
it's 'cause Yaya's the
best automaton in the world!
[loud crash]
Now, Yaya. Fall back!
[CHARLOTTE] Lustre Cannon!
Flare! 36 Sho!
Right!
[CHARLOTTE] Lustre Flare!
Whistle 36--no wait!
Forty-eight Sho!
Stronghold!
Come on, Sigmund!
You're stronger!
Good Yaya!
Push him back!
Now, Flare! 48 Sho!
[RAISHIN] Come on,
Dinosaur Girl!
You're fighting
the wrong person!
Why wouldn't someone
with your power unleash
it on the real enemy?
There'd be no point.
I would never be able
to stand up to them!
So you come to me for help!
Your friend!
[CHARLOTTE]
No! I have come too far!
It's too late to turn back now!
Believe in me.
Please, Char.
I want to, but this
is my fight, not yours.
So? We'll face it together.
Ahhh!
[CH ARLOTTE] Oh, no.
What's wrong?
You're burning up.
[SHIN]
Your concern is misplaced.
You've far more pressing
worries at the moment;
like the headmaster,
for example.
My mind's changed.
I won't do your dirty work.
[SHIN] Such a pity.
[SHIN] Still conscious,
Master Akabane?
You took quite a tumble.
[SHIN] Despite my past actions,
Granville butlers abhor
physical confrontation.
Settling matters with one's
fists is so primitive.
Perhaps you'll simply
allow me to kill you?
Please do. I should consider
it a personal favor.
[RAISHIN] Go to hell.
[RAISHIN] Silence 48 Sho!
[SHIN] Now, then.
I believe it's your turn.
[CHARLOTTE] Sigmund!
Lustre Cannon!
Impossible!
The Belew's prized Gram has
a well-deserved reputation.
No point in looking.
So sorry.
Search all you want,
you'll find no one there.
[CHARLOTTE] Your puppeteer!
He must be nearby.
[SHIN] Automatons don't
create magical energy.
Even in the case
of a Banned Doll.
It isn't the doll who
produces the magic.
It's the human parts that have
been combined
with the mechanical.
How then do you explain the
fact that I'm fighting alone?
You're being ridiculous.
I should really believe
you're here on your own?
While blessed
with enormous talent,
I'm not without my failings.
If I had to name one flaw,
it would be that on occasion
I have a rather loose tongue.
Therefore I shall
enlighten you.
I am something
truly extraordinary.
A divine instrument--
a Machine-Doll!