[explosion]
[YAYA] Raishin!
[panting]
Raishin. Raishin!
[KIMBERLEY] Wait, Yaya.
You should know
you're being watched.
Yaya has to help him!
[GUARD 10A] What happened?
[GUARD 10B] Our priority
is finding the headmaster!
[KIMBERLEY] If you
make a wrong move,
they'll have Second Last
in their sights as well.
Yes, but--
Hmph. Besides,
I imagine he's fine.
You know his unholy
luck better than anyone.
[KIMBERLEY] Now, follow me.
Where are we going?
[KIMBERLEY] There is
a decision to be made.
One I cannot make alone.
I must consult my comrades.
It's awful. I actually
killed someone.
[SIGMUND] You need
to collect yourself.
[CHARLOTTE] I'm collected.
[SIGMUND] Then let's go.
We're being pursued.
Yes. Of course.
Automaton sentries!
[SHIN] You are
a troublesome one.
We're withdrawing.
[knock, knock]
I'm disappointed, Lavenna.
You're not demonstrating
the commitment I'd hoped for.
But I assassinated
the headmaster
just as you instructed!
Your roundabout methods are
what have given me pause.
Using Sigmund, you could have
killed Headmahster Rutherford
and his guards in a
much more direct fashion.
I still held up my
end of the bargain.
No, you haven't.
The target's death
has yet to be confirmed.
Now look here.
I've something
entertaining to show you.
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
Henri!
[CEDRIC] You nearly
killed her, you know.
Your own sister.
It's lucky for little Henriette
you chose the less
precise attack, isn't it?
She fell into an
underground cavern
when the earth collapsed.
Oh, my! And Second Last is
making an appearance, too.
[gasps]
[RAISHIN] Come on! Wake up!
Henri! Open your eyes!
Are you all right?
You're not hurt, are you?
Ah! Dirty boy! No! No!
[RAISHIN] Hey!
Will you stop that?
No! No!
[RAISHIN] Stop! Haven't
you noticed where we are?
The ground's
beginning to crumble.
We need to find an exit fast.
Do as you will,
just leave me be.
[sighs]
Yep, you're a
Belew girl all right.
What? Did I hear
the buzzing of a fly?
Believe me now?
[RAISHIN] This area used to be a
testing ground for taboo magic.
The story I heard's
pretty grisly.
Thousands buried
alive right below us.
The few who
survived had no choice
but to start eating each other.
Ripping out organs, drinking
blood, gnawing on bones.
They say there was
only a single survivor,
who still wanders
the maze to this day.
Bah! A ghost story!
I won't believe a
crib tale like that.
It's pure fiction!
[HENRIETTE]
Wh-What's the matter?
[RAISHIN] Listen.
Do you hear something?
[HENRIETTE]
What? No! Don't do this to me!
Ahh! He's here!
[HENRIETTE] No!
Don't kill me! Don't kill me!
Don't kill me!
[RAISHIN] You can get up.
I was joking. Sorry.
So, no one's there?
[RAISHIN] I was borrowing from
an old Japanese ghost story.
I'm still pretty new here, too.
How would I know
anything about this place?
You cruel josser!
Really, how could you?
I thought I would
die of sheer terror!
I have no idea
if there's a world
beyond the grave.
But if there is,
I bet it has a lot in
common with this place.
Dark, moldy n' damp;
the perfect spot for the
dead to wander 'round.
I'm just trying to say,
if you're really
so afraid of ghosts,
maybe you shouldn't be
in such a hurry to die.
You don't understand.
It's not as though
I yearn for death.
We shouldn't be down
here too much longer.
Once my partner knows
I'm with another woman,
nothing will stop
her from finding me.
So it's gonna be okay.
Help will come.
[GUARD 10C] We still don't know
whether the headmaster is safe.
[GUARD 10D] Apparently
there were some students
who got mixed up in this, too.
[GUARD 10C] Yes, a girl
and some Oriental boy.
They're down in all
that rubble somewhere.
Ow, that one's
gonna leave a bruise.
"Oriental boy"?
[MALE DISCIPLINARY 10A]
This area's strictly off-limits.
Um, sorry 'bout that,
but if I could maybe
just take a quick peek?
[MALE DISCIPLINARY 10A] Sorry.
[MALE DISCIPLINARY 10A]
Crying won't help.
[FREY] Loki.
[LOKI]
Fresh out of the infirmary,
and already he's in trouble.
I swear, that imbecile
must have a curse on him.
Stay out of this, understand?
It's his mess, not yours.
[thinking] Raishin.
[BROTHER TURTLEDOVE]
So. Sister Warbler.
What do you suggest we do?
[KIMBERLEY] I'm pondering that,
as well, Brother Turtledove.
It's why I came to you.
[BROTHER CROW] It's obvious
what the enemy's objective is.
Our best option is to go
and guard the headmaster.
It's also a fine chance to get
to the bottom of this
"Cathedral of Fools" business.
Although, should we
make a wrong move,
the Cathedral may be
destroyed along with him.
Our primary objective here
is limited to containment.
Therefore, we shall
only observe and monitor.
We must be careful not
to overstep ourselves.
[BROTHER TURTLEDOVE]
Naturally.
Now, I believe you reported
Second Last is also missing?
Correct.
He's a quick-witted child,
and perceptive.
And thus inevitably at
the center of any hubbub.
[BROTHER TURTLEDOVE] A surviving
Akabane in our midst.
Is it possible that he is the
one foreseen by Father Time?
[KIMBERLEY] That is
certainly a possibility.
[BROTHER TURTLEDOVE] Very well.
We shall seek the
Father's instructions.
[sighs]
[YAYA] What now?
What do we do about
saving Raishin?
Nothing at the moment,
but I can assure you
he is still safe.
Listen.
If it's true, and he is
indeed the one Father foresaw,
then I highly doubt
a little fall
is going to be the end of him.
But we'll see.
Hm?
[RAISHIN] Whoa.
This chamber's
enormous, isn't it?
[screams]
[breathing heavily]
[RAISHIN] Are you all right?
No!
Don't you touch me!
[sighs]
What is it about me
that bothers you so much?
[HENRIETTE] It's not you;
I hate all men.
They're scary and mean
and violent and cruel.
And stupid, and really smelly.
[RAISHIN] Well, I'm still
glad you're not hurt.
Watch your step better
from now on, okay?
I... I will.
[cries in pain]
What's the matter?
Can I have a look?
[HENRIETTE] Careful, that hurts!
[thinking] Well, I guess
we'll need to rest for a while.
[RAISHIN] Here.
[RAISHIN] They're a little
smushed, but they're edible.
[RAISHIN] Yeah, you're
Char's sister, all right.
I know what
you're implying:
that she's
prettier than I am.
Everyone thinks so.
[laughs]
That's rude,
even for you!
You're just mocking me.
Calm down,
you got it all wrong.
Meanie!
Ow! The rock throwing
is really not necessary!
I wasn't laughing at you
or mocking you, I promise!
Stop it!
See, I had a talented
older sibling, too.
People compared us
all the time. Thing is...
...we really
couldn't have
been more different
from each other.
Unfortunately,
I was the lesser of the two.
When we were younger,
Charlotte had far
more friends than I.
Somehow I have a
difficult time imagining that.
Something about her just
drew everyone to her side.
Everyone here avoids
her like the plague.
And she was so kind
to everyone in return.
Now she's always
cross with everyone.
[FIREFLY]
Make your answer swift.
Are you my master's enemy?
[thinking] Nadeshiko?
[RAISHIN] Tenzen? You did this?
[TENZEN] I did.
[RAISHIN] And Nadeshiko?
[TENZEN] I had to dissect her.
[RAISHIN] But why?
It was an unfortunate necessity.
A necessity for what?
[TENZEN] For the
creation of a god.
[RAISHIN] I didn't expect
to run into you down here.
[RAISHIN] Hello, Magnus.
[HEADMASTER] Raishin Akabane,
if I'm not mistaken.
[RAISHIN] Headmaster!
[HEADMASTER]
Apologies if I startled you.
My bodyguard Magnus
can be quite protective.
Seems we're all in
the same predicament.
Best we wait for
rescue together, then.
And Raishin, lad.
I do fully expect you
to behave yourself.
Understood?
[FIREFLY] Master.
If it pleases you, I can
break through the ceiling
and locate assistance for us.
Don't interfere.
We have a job to do.
Keep your focus
on our protectee.
[FIREFLY] As you wish, Master.
In all things, I obey.
[exasperated noise]
[HENRIETTE] You all right?
I'm sorry. I was
too angry to stay.
Why does he
vex you so?
Magnus killed my family.
He killed my little sister.
He what?
He's the reason
I came to Walpurgis.
I fully intend to kill him.
Don't look at
me like that.
I'm not gonna do
it now or anything.
But do me a favor.
Keep it to yourself.
Even Char doesn't
all of this.
So, why tell me?
I hardly know you.
Sounds weird, but, I kinda
feel like I know you.
[HENRIETTE] Anyways.
Despite the uniform.
I'm not actually
enrolled at the academy.
You're not really...
Wait, what do you mean?
[HENRIETTE]
It's hard to explain, I--
[KIMBERLEY] Well hello,
Sacred Blaze.
You look lonely
without Second Last
here keeping you company.
Did you want
something, Professor?
As a matter of fact,
I have a proposal.
There is someone in
need of protection.
What makes you
think I'd help you?
All due respect.
[chuckles] Because I shall
reward you, silly boy.
Handsomely. Play along
and I'll give you
what you long for
most in this world.
That's De Organum !
Nice try.
Don't promise
what you can't deliver.
You'd never hand over
a work of such importance.
[KIMBERLEY] I'm certainly not
suggesting I'd let you keep it.
However, there
has been discussion
about making a copy of
it in the near future.
A task for which I'd require
a trustworthy assistant.
Heh.
Cunning, Professor.
Heh heh.
Good, Firefly.
Now restrain him.
[FIREFLY] As you wish, Master.
[thinking] No human
moves like that.
But I don't sense a
puppeteer anywhere.
[HEADMASTER] One of
the rebels out to get me?
[RAISHIN thinking] No, not
this time. He tried to kill me.
[GUARD 10E] There they are!
[AVRIL] Headmaster.
Are you all right?
Avril. It's good
to see you.
And, yes,
I'm safe and sound.
[AVRIL] What a shame.
Guards, take the brats up.
[YAYA] Raishin!
[sobs]
Yaya, calm down!
Yaya was so worried, Raishin!
She thought you were gone!
Never leave Yaya!
Sorry 'bout that.
You can stop crying.
It'll take more'n a
little fall to kill me.
[YAYA] Yaya knows.
She was just afraid
that you had run
off with that vixen!
[RAISHIN]
Okay, you coulda worried
about my life a tiny bit.
[YAYA] But Raishin!
[YAYA] Take off your underpants!
[RAISHIN] Not gonna do that.
[YAYA] Fine. Just pull out
what's inside, then.
[RAISHIN]
Not doing that, either.
Uh...
[YAYA] Why won't you
ever make love to Yaya?
[RAISHIN] Whoa, stop!
Keep your clothes on!
[YAYA] So, it's true.
You hate Yaya so much
you won't even touch her!
[RAISHIN] I don't hate you,
okay? Now get dressed!
[YAYA wails] Not even a
twitch in reaction!
[RAISHIN]
Where were you looking?
Clothes! Now! I mean it!
[YAYA] Raishin really
doesn't love Yaya!
WAAHHHH!
[RAISHIN] Hey! Take it easy!
You'll break right
through the floor!
You're the last person
I wanted to tell this to,
but I'm betrothed.
Raishin is betrothed?
\You liar!
That can't be true.
You've been with Yaya two years.
Why'd you never tell her?
It just never felt like the
right time, and truthfully?
I was scared to.
[YAYA] Because you didn't want
to hurt your
relationship with Yaya?
No, 'cause I didn't want
you to hurt my skull.
[YAYA] How could you? You
tricked Yaya for so long!
I am going to kill you!
Wait, Yaya listen!
There's more to the story.
I'm not really
gonna... marry her!
You're not
going to marry her?
Please explain to Yaya.
It was an
arranged marriage.
Our parents set
it up without us.
But they're gone now,
along with the rest
of my family, so...
So...
Wait.
It's never been officially
cancelled though.
Which means,
even if I wanted to,
I can't see other people.
[YAYA] Shit. Always so proper.
[RAISHIN]
I heard that! Language!
Raishin is
already betrothed.
[FREY] T... Tyrant Rex!
Our opponents
didn't show.
Yaya wonders why.
Me, too. It's
weird, isn't it?
No 87 two days in a
row. And now tonight.
Number 86 didn't
show up either.
[YAYA]
Are they working together?
I couldn't say.
But there's something going
on here, that's for sure.
Going home, then?
[RAISHIN] No. We're not.
No, we're going
fishing for sharks.
[CEDRIC] Well, look at that.
[CEDRIC] Things are becoming
quite interesting, indeed.
Second Last took it upon
himself to kidnap Henriette.
[CHARLOTTE]
So, how did that feel, Cedric?
Being outwitted by
the very man you mocked.
[CEDRIC] I admit I'm rather
impressed by how fickle you are.
Opening your legs
for that yellow mongrel
so soon after
opening them for Felix.
You--
Don't be so vulgar!
[CEDRIC] You surprise me.
Don't tell me
you're still untouched?
In that case,
I might enjoy tossing
you naked into a den of rogues.
No, it would be far more fun
if I saved that for your sister.
If you do anything
to harm Henri,
I swear to God your
family line will end with y--
I hope you'll
pardon my presumption.
Consider it pardoned.
Now retrieve
Henriette for me.
I shall see to it at
once, and Second Last?
[CEDRIC] He need not survive.
In fact, you may take his head,
and we shall make it
a gift to this harlot.
Not the most
refined of tactics,
but if you wish it,
young master.
[CHARLOTTE] What foul
plot are you hatching?
Why use me and my sister?
[CEDRIC]
Well, that's a silly question.
Because it amuses me.
[CEDRIC] And I believe
tormenting you will give Felix
a certain amount
of satisfaction.
After all, we are cousins
and the dearest of friends.
[CHARLOTTE] I don't believe
you're Cedric Granville at all!
You're disguising
yourself with magic!
[CHARLOTTE]
But then who are you?
[CEDRIC] I am but a shadow.
A formless shadow,
and nothing more.
Help! Please!
I've been kidnapped
by a bad, bad man
who wants to have
his way with me!
Keep it down wouldja?
We're gonna get caught!
I'm not try'na hurt you.
I'm try'na help you!
Before, when you said
you were afraid of death.
You don't want to die. Right?
You just feel like you have to?
[RAISHIN]
Lemme venture a guess here.
Someone's threatening Char.
Saying unless she kills the
headmaster, they'll kill you.
[HENRIETTE]
It's hopeless, though!
I keep running away,
but they bring me back!
And when I try to just die,
someone always saves me!
It does me no good
to run and hide.
They'll find me!
[RAISHIN]
That's why I'm not hiding.
Huh?
In fact, I'm hoping
they'll notice me.
It's why I kidnapped
their hostage.
Real soon. They are
gonna take the bait.
[RAISHIN] And sooner
than I expected.
What a good hunting dog.
[SHIN]
I do possess certain skills.
My master deserves a
butler with enormous talent.
Loyalty, too.
Bet it'll take
more'n a few bruises
before you spill
your master's secrets.
Naturally.
What will you do?
"Naturally" whatever
I have to.
And then, I'll expose
your depraved master
for the monster he is.
[SHIN] You question
my master's sanity?
It's hard not to.
Anyone who'd dream up
this plan must be mad!
Not mad.
Although, I admit he is a
somewhat twisted individual
who schemes as
easily as he breathes.
Sad but true--'tis a
curse of the Granville line.
After boasting about being
such a talented butler,
I really didn't expect you
to give up your master's name.
Yes, well.
Talented as I am,
I'm not without my failings.
But if I had to name one flaw,
it would be my
incredibly short temper.
Yaya!
After we crush this man,
we save Char n' Henri.
Let's go!
Right!