[YAYA screams]
[SIGMUND] Yaya!
Ah, Ms. Karyusai!
Impeccable timing.
Care to patch her up?
And hello to you, Professor.
I hope you're well.
That brat of yours is
proving quite the handful.
I hope he had good reason
for sneaking off
academy grounds like that.
Really. It's no wonder
she wound up in a bad way.
It sounds like you might know
who was responsible for
the attack on his doll.
Even if I did,
that would be a
discussion for another time.
For now...
Well, you wouldn't want
to lose her, would you?
[SHOKO] Your concern
is noted, Professor.
But don't worry.
You'll find she's quite
tougher than she looks.
[KIMBERLEY] That covers
the automaton, then.
But what of Second Last?
He's playing a dangerous game.
Don't underestimate him, either.
No boy of mine
would die so easily.
It has been lovely catching up.
Give my regards to
Father Time, won't you?
That woman practically
bathes in intrigue.
Loves her secrets.
Though, I suppose
it's not my place to judge.
[YOMI] Something I can
do for you, young fellow?
Whoa, a talking dog!
[YOMI] Both my thought processes
and vocal chords are on par
with that of any of you humans.
For better or for worse.
[RAISHIN] You shouldn't
be able to detect us.
And yet, as should
be clear, I can.
You are well
concealed, though.
A passive sensor wouldn't
even know you were here.
[KOMURASAKI]
So you're active!
Hmph. Well, we have a
clever one on our hands.
Now then, it's only
polite say 'hello'
when sneaking into someone's
home without permission.
Of course. Sorry.
I'm Raishin Akabane.
Pleasure to meet you.
We're undercover!
How refreshing!
It's not every day you meet
such well-mannered intruders!
Those other dog
automatons out there.
Are they your pups by chance?
[YOMI] In a way
I suppose they are.
I am the prototype
for the Garm Series,
the line to which
my son Rabbi belongs.
[RAISHIN] With the
Sonic magic circuit!
Indeed. So you've
heard of it, then.
Since you're so smart,
do you know how it functions?
We emit sound
and it bounces back;
seeing and hearing the world
via changes in wavelength.
It's rather impressive, really.
Like a bat.
So you're a Banned Doll?
What led you
to that conclusion?
[RAISHIN] Far as I can tell,
there's no puppeteer nearby.
Yet you're still using magic.
Well spotted.
Clearly you're more intelligent
than you first appear.
Gee thanks. So why are
you locked up in here?
I near the end of the
great road we all travel.
I'll soon be disposed of.
Happens to us all eventually.
They're putting you down?
But why?
They no longer have
need of a prototype.
Which means there's nothing to
justify the cost of my upkeep.
How can they do that?
Sorry for yelling.
It just makes me sick to see
a living creature's
worth reduced to numbers.
[RAISHIN] Wait, why
don't you come with us?
And why would I do that?
Because where's
the fun in living out
your final days in a dismal
hellhole like this place?
[chuckles] I'll say this:
you are a most amusing chap.
Why'd you break in here, anyway?
[RAISHIN]
For information on a girl
who keeps trying to
kill me, named Frey.
That's ridiculous!
What on Earth would compel
her to do such a thing?
That's exactly what
I'm trying to find out.
If you're interested,
I could really use
a guide to help
show me around.
Then follow me, son.
I'll share the secrets
entombed within these walls.
But beware: you're about
to see a glimpse
of hell on earth.
Hold up. You never
did tell us your name.
It's Yomi.
[SIGMUND] Yaya!
Yaya! Stay with me!
[YAYA] Wh-what happened?
Are you all right?
Yaya should be fine.
She's still functional.
You were lucky;
surviving an abdominal
blow like that is rare.
Yaya is not lucky;
she is the best
automaton in the world.
She's strong.
[SIGMUND] Steady now, child.
I'll go an' fetch a technician.
No, that won't do.
Not Yaya. Normal
repairs won't be enough.
[SIGMUND]
Then what will help you?
[YAYA] Raishin.
Yaya needs Raishin.
[SIGMUND] His magic
is our only hope, is it?
[CHARLOTTE] Good lord!
What is all this ruckus?
[SIGMUND] Char! Thank goodness.
You're just in time.
Lend me a hand!
No! We need to leave
this to the technicians!
How could those bastards
have built her like this?
She's made up of even more
fragile parts than you are!
I'm afraid only her
designer would be able
to repair something this severe.
I'm not sure it'll help,
but I can give her
some of my magic.
What is this? I can't--
Aaaaa!!
[SIGMUND] Are you all right?
[YAYA] Please don't
endanger yourself for Yaya.
This is nothing!
I've got this!
[YAYA] But...
You're the ene--
I am Charlotte of
the House of Belew,
who were granted
the noble unicorn crest
and northern earldom
by Her Majesty the Queen!
Whatever enmity you
and I might share
can be settled
on festival grounds.
[YAYA] No. Yaya doesn't want
to be indebted to a vixen.
You don't know
when to shut up!
[door opening]
[sighs]
[KIMBERLEY] Haven't changed
a bit, have you, Doctor?
All part of the
treatment. My word.
Just makin' sure the
stethoscope was properly placed.
[KIMBERLEY] Ugh. Spare me
the details, won't you?
So, what tears you away
from your busy schedule
to come bother me?
A stomach ache, perhaps?
Menstrual cramps?
Not menopause already?
Actually, I'd like your thoughts
on a certain student.
What's your opinion
of Raishin Akabane?
[CRUEL] Wondered when
you'd ask after 'im.
[KIMBERLEY] So, something
has caught your eye.
[CRUEL] Well, first, his wounds
are terribly slow to heal.
He suffers from
poor blood formation
and cell division as well as
inefficient nutrient intake.
All of which
suggests he's having
the life sucked out of him.
[KIMBERLEY] Is it
possible it's being used
to repair an automaton?
Certainly.
Provided he is in
possession of a Banned Doll.
I want him very
closely monitored.
Naturally you'll be under
exclusive contract with us.
Your life's about
to change, Doctor.
Both Academy and English
government are your enemies.
I am a reasonable
woman, though.
You have a choice.
Between the cash
or a sniper bullet.
[YOMI] Here we are; Frey's room.
[RAISHIN] Is Frey her real name?
[YOMI] More of a codename.
[RAISHIN] And her parents?
Such a tragic story;
they were in a traveling puppet
show in the United States.
Halfway through
one of their shows,
an automaton malfunctioned,
and they were both killed.
Now. I know Frey well
and can't hazard a guess as
to why she'd try to kill you.
She's always been such
a sweet little dear.
Everyone loves her.
It's impossible not to.
That's why she was chosen;
she was the obvious choice.
To command Rabbi, you mean?
The world can
punish the kindhearted.
I fear her innate
goodness may have
led her down a
most unfortunate path.
[RAISHIN] Whatever
misfortune's befallen her,
her life doesn't seem all bad.
I mean, she has loving
family like you around.
[RAISHIN]
Are these all siblings?
No, that wouldn't be possible.
[YOMI] Those are
"Promised Children."
Rare individuals who
possess an affinity
for magic that goes
beyond that of most humans.
Each of the children
in that room
is literally one in a million.
[RAISHIN] Why are they here?
They all just happened
to be orphaned?
[YOMI] What would you say
if I told you they
aren't entirely human?
Come.
I've something even more
horrifying to show you.
What the hell?
What is this?
[alarm siren]
They're headed our way!
How many of them can see
through our cloaking spell?
Every Garm doll
has that ability.
Although I am uncertain
whether any of the
guards puppeteer one.
Then we'll
have to break through
and hope for the best.
[YOMI] Short-sightedness like
that will be the death of you.
[RAISHIN] Is there another exit?
[YOMI] Quickly. Open this.
A secret passage?
[YOMI]
No, it's only a rubbish bin.
[GUARD 6A] There they are!
They're fleein' down the sewer!
[splashes]
Argh!
Your shoulder!
It's just a scratch.
Where's this tunnel lead?
Into the town's sewer system.
You should make
it out before long.
Assuming of course,
that your pursuers are
as incompetent as ever.
[RAISHIN]
That's not as reassuring
as you probably think.
[KOMURASAKI] Ugh.
I'm positively
soaked in this muck!
[YOMI] I believe
I may have an idea
why Frey has been
attempting to eliminate you.
A loss for her at the
festival would effectively
end plans for the mass
production of the Garm Series.
[RAISHIN] And if that
happened, then all of you...
[YOMI]
...would be disposed of, yes.
And then, of course,
they would have to
introduce a different model.
Like Cherubim!
[YOMI] Correct. They would
launch the Angel Series,
to which Cherubim belongs.
Their individual battle
capabilities exceed any Garm's.
However, they are
costly to produce,
and are difficult to manage.
We Garms are different.
We are easy to control by even
the greenest of puppeteers.
Which makes a good deal
of sense. We are dogs.
Raishin, look out!
Yaya was quite rude before.
Thank you; she should be all
right until Raishin returns.
[CHARLOTTE] That artillery
shell is enormous.
But from where was it fired?
[SIGMUND] I don't see
any barrel marks on it.
The absence of
such scoring indicates
that it was launched
without the use of a gun.
If a weapon wasn't required,
the attack could have
come from anywhere!
This bodes ill.
If someone tried
to eliminate Yaya
as a way to force Raishin
out of the competition--
They'll target him next!
[YAYA] Raishin!
[RAISHIN] Aw, hang on, Yomi!
You'll be okay!
[RAISHIN]
Why did you block that?
If I die, Frey beats
me by default.
Here, Raishin!
I think I've found us
a way out of here!
Hurry up!
[RAISHIN] Great, more troops.
[YOMI] Don't die
playing the hero, son.
Leave me;
get your fool self out.
I can't just abandon you!
[YOMI] It's what I want.
These old bones are so tired.
I'd like to sleep now...
...here, with my children.
[YOMI] You did provide me
with a little bit of fun
in my final hours.
For that, you have my thanks.
Argh!!
[RAISHIN] Yomi!
[KOMURASAKI shrieks]
No! Damn them all!
[LOKI] What are you
staring at the gates for?
I'm waiting for
Raishin to come back.
You're going to be
waiting forever, then.
[FREY] Why?
What happened to him?
I know his automaton was
attacked and badly injured.
Was that you?
And if I told you it was?
What would you do, Frey?
Second Last
became a nuisance.
Uncovering secrets
best left undisturbed.
Our secrets.
So Father took care of him.
Guess I'm not quite
as dead as you think I am.
That one's got
ice in his veins.
[sniffs]
[FREY] You must smell like
someone Rabbi recognizes.
He does, and I owe
you an apology, Frey.
Yomi died today.
[RAISHIN] I dragged
her into this. I'm sorry.
It sounds weird but thank you.
Why?
[FREY] You let her out of
her pen before she died, right?
Yes, but--
She'd been locked
away like a prisoner
in that awful place for
more years than you know.
She must have been happy.
Given even that small
measure of freedom at last.
Just be mad at me.
Something!
Raishin!
You were gone so long!
Wait, what happened to you?
Were you hurt?
Oh, Yaya is fine. Unlike you!
Look at all those bandages!
What happened?
[RAISHIN] I uh--I messed up.
And Komurasaki?
I left her at an Army safe
house on the way back here.
That's not what Yaya meant!
Her sister was with
you the whole time!
Wait. Was that it?
Did you get hurt
because someone attacked
the two of you mid-tryst?
[RAISHIN] You're being
ridiculous. Let it go.
That girl is a lot more
dangerous than she seems.
Yaya must know!
Now remove
your underpants!
Yaya must inspect
them for evidence!
Made it back in
one piece, did you, boy?
I hope you found the
experience educational.
[RAISHIN] Yeah.
[SHOKO] Then you
understand why I sent you
to explore the orphanage?
Why it was necessary?
You sent me there as a decoy,
so you could spy on
Divine Works in the meantime.
[SHOKO chuckles]
That's my clever boy.
[RAISHIN] And did the
Army learn anything useful?
I'd like to know if
our mission was worth it.
A life was lost.
I'm sorry, that sounds
like a complaint.
And I know I have
no right to do so.
So you blame yourself
for what went wrong.
Well, that is just
downright arrogant!
S'cuse me?
[SHOKO]
You may have talent, boy,
but you're not omnipotent.
You can't heal the dying,
even with Yaya.
Do not fret over things
beyond your control.
I expect far better of you.
[SHOKO] Frey will be
entering the festival using
a Banned Doll.
With human parts
alongside the mechanical,
it's exceedingly
difficult to keep
such an automaton
alive for long.
But there is a way to do so,
provided you aren't burdened
with an overabundance of morals.
Yeah, by using a living
being as a vessel.
[SHOKO] Precisely.
You then need to simply provide
the nourishment necessary
to bring the parts
harmoniously to life.
Unfortunately it works
for a relatively
short amount of time.
The parts last only
as long as the vessel.
The "Sonic" is an
excellent magic circuit,
though too "heavy"
for everyday use.
If it could be activated
using less magic,
it would reduce the
strain on the puppeteer.
So that room I saw
in the orphanage.
[SHOKO] If that's what
the English Army is using
to maintain its supremacy,
how can Japan stay silent?
I'm confused.
I thought we were allies.
[SHOKO] For now we are.
[RAISHIN] Don't tell
me the Army's thinking
about turning on England!
[SHOKO] You're one
of the Army's dogs, boy.
Your only concern is to
follow your master's orders.
And speaking of which,
I want you to appropriate
Rahbi's magic circuit.
However, you must do
so at the festival
without arousing suspicion.
[RAISHIN] Whoa, wait!
Magic circuits are attached
directly to a doll's heart.
I can't remove it
without killing him!
You foolish boy.
Surely you haven't forgotten
who you're speaking to.
[RAISHIN] Are you
ordering me to kill Rabbi?
[SHOKO] Do not make
me say it again.
[SHOKO] Run along.
It's nearly time.
[HEADMASTER]
I look forward to the results
of your hard work
and diligent study.
My fellow Walpurgis competitors,
we have a sacred duty.
Today we honor the
source-spark of magic.
Today blood answers to blood!
Today we shall be kings
or we shall be nothing!
Today, we pledge a battle true!
Attention students and faculty.
The moment is upon us!
Walpurgis Night begins!
[cheering crowd]
[MALE ANNOUNCER 6A] In 100th
place. Second Last. Approach!
[MALE ANNOUNCER 6A] In 99th
place. Sacred Blaze. Approach!
[LOKI] I told you to
withdraw from the festival.
You should've.
[RAISHIN] And I chose to
ignore you, so, here we are.
Time for a little payback.
Yaya! Whistle 24 Sho!
On it!
Stronghold 48 Ketsu!
Now, Yaya!
Flare 24 Sho!
Hmph! Impressive armor.
I'll concede that.
Even the sharpest
blades can't cut Yaya!
Oh, but they will.
As you're about to see, there's
nothing Cherubim can't cut.
Cherubim. Attack!
[CHERUBIM] Ready!
[RAISHIN] Move it!
Excellent reflexes.
Why are you
hesitating, Raishin?
Give Yaya magic! Don't worry.
Yaya won't get hurt.
You know she can hold her own!
Then let's do it! 24 Sho!
This is it!
Yaya can't go any further!
[RAISHIN] Stronghold 96 Sho!
[YAYA] Raishin!