Hnmph...
[gasps]
[RAISHIN] Nadeshiko!
Where are you? Nadeshiko!
[RAISHIN] Dad, no!
[RAISHIN] Nadeshiko!
[screams]
Can't be her.
[RAISHIN] Wait right there,
Mask Boy. Sorry. Magnus.
"The Great One?" Y'really
make people call you that?
[MAGNUS] Who are you?
Well, that's a
rather icy greeting.
Considering I traveled
across half the globe
for the express
purpose of seeing you.
[MAGNUS] I believe you've
mistaken me for someone else.
[RAISHIN] Very well.
I won't keep you much longer.
But before you go,
I want you to have this!
Raishin!
[CHARLOTTE] Magnus is the
highest-ranked
student at Walpurgis.
He's the most
brilliant puppeteer
the school has ever seen.
One bloke who deploys
six automatons at one time.
It's unheard of!
He is the obvious favorite
to win the title of
Wise Man this year.
These young ladies
of yours are so touchy.
I only wanted to give you
a token of our acquaintance.
They surely wouldn't
object to that.
What'd he give him? A jar?
[MAGNUS] I accept your
token with gratitude.
Yaya let you down!
She is sorry!
Yaya should have
fought those dolls off!
[RAISHIN] Much as I hate to
admit it, Charlotte was right.
At my current level,
I couldn't defeat him.
[RAISHIN] Will I be
strong enough? Ever?
[YAYA] Raishin! Yaya is
happy to wash your back.
You've had such
a long, tiring day.
And it is a wife's duty
to soothe her husband's
tension and weariness.
Ah! Yaya!
Hands off! Stop!
[YAYA] It'll be all right.
[RAISHIN] What are you
even talking about?
[YAYA] You will win. Yaya knows.
[YAYA] Don't doubt yourself.
Today doesn't matter.
The festival does.
[RAISHIN] Yeah, you're right.
Thank you.
I needed to hear that.
[YAYA] You're welcome!
But there is a better way
to thank Yaya. Yes, yes!
[RAISHIN] Stop rubbing
yourself on me like that!
[YAYA] Right this way!
Yaya loves it when you squirm!
[RAISHIN]
I mean it, Yaya! Get off of me!
[FELIX] Cheers! Good morning.
[RAISHIN]
Hmm?
You're confused.
Sorry. Introductions first.
I'm Feli--
Felix Kingsfort.
One of the Rounds, and the
head of the Disciplinary Board.
Which is the linchpin of the
academy's student government.
So what do you want with me?
[FELIX] I believe we
can strike a bargain.
There's an important matter
I'd like to discuss.
[RAISHIN] Don't care.
You haven't heard
what I'm offering yet.
A guaranteed festival entry.
[gasps]
[FELIX] Thought as much.
Shall we speak later?
A magic circuit
is an alternative
to performing a magic ritual.
Think of it as a type of engine.
Just as we use
steam to turn gears,
so, too, can we use magic power
to produce a magical effect.
[RAISHIN] I don't know how I can
trust that one, but his offer.
[YAYA] What happened?
Are you okay?
[KIMBERLEY] The fact
you're ignoring my lecture,
Second Last, makes clear
how little you value your life.
Why do you suppose I'm
spending my precious time
on such basic material?
For new students
like me, I s'pose?
And others who might
be failing the course.
[KIMBERLEY] Or for a student
who is both new and failing.
Now, answer this, if you can.
Which magic circuit is
currently the most widely used?
Mm. Heat, right?
No, wait. Power, isn't it?
Light maybe?
[KIMBERLEY] Charlotte,
enlighten your classmate.
The answer is Eve's Heart.
[KIMBERLEY] Correct.
All automatons contain magic
circuits known as Eve's Hearts,
which are responsible
for their animation.
These circuits are
what allow automatons
to function independently.
The Eve's Heart is vital,
giving a doll its intelligence.
With it, skilled craftsmen
can do great work.
Even producing automatons nearly
identical to human beings.
Though, if you ask me,
imitating humans is a
rather pointless endeavor.
I have no idea what would
make you say something
like that, Professor.
But Yaya is the best
automaton in the world!
Aw, Raishin!
She was built by Shoko,
after all!
[YAYA] Shoko? Shoko again?
It's always her, isn't it?
[bell tolling]
What's Felix up to?
He's talking to that new twit.
[SIGMUND]
Interested in him, are we?
[CHARLOTTE] No!
That's rubbish! Pure drivel!
One more word and
you're on a green pea diet!
I'll admit.
He has always behaved
in a most gentlemanly way.
[SIGMUND] No. It's not Felix
I was speaking about.
I meant the new lad, Raishin.
He may be worth getting
better acquainted with.
[SIGMUND]
I'm certainly impressed.
We were having lunch,
and he inquired as
to how I was feeling.
Do you not recall that, Char?
Yes. Your point?
He treated me
as an individual,
an entity separate from you.
Most puppeteers would have
spoken quite differently.
The question would be directed
at you, rather than me.
"How is your puppet?" is what
anyone else would have asked.
[CHARLOTTE] I-I suppose
I see what you're gettin' at.
[SIGMUND] Char.
I want to ask you something.
Raishin and Yaya fought for
you when you were outnumbered.
Are you prepared to face 'em
in battle when the time comes?
[CHARLOTTE] I am Charlotte,
of the House of Belew.
Her Majesty granted my family
the noble unicorn crest.
She bestowed upon us
the northern earldom.
I shall eliminate anyone
who stands in my path.
Anyone at all.
[FELIX] Now, then.
Shall we discuss our
bargain in greater detail?
Well, I know what
you're offering;
so what do you want from me?
Take a look at
these photographs.
I doubt you're aware, but
twenty-six academy students
have gone missing
since October last.
If that weren't bad enough,
we've also discovered twelve
gruesomely destroyed automatons.
The methods,
as you can see,
are reminiscent
of Jack the Ripper.
[RAISHIN]
Who would do such a thing?
A fellow student.
One we are calling
Cannibal Candy.
I would like you to identify
him, and then defeat him.
Okay, so why me?
[FELIX] I have two reasons.
First, I don't
consider you a suspect.
Given you only just
arrived at the academy.
As for the second,
I saw you sparring yesterday.
You're quite strong.
Gives you a sporting chance.
[LISETTE] There you are!
Pardon the intrusion.
I'm Lisette Norden,
Disciplinary Board Vice-Chief.
[FELIX] My goodness, love.
You're not easily flustered.
What's wrong?
Has there been another
Cannibal Candy incident?
Aye. Another doll was found.
The crime scene's behind
the Technology Department.
[RAISHIN] Hi, Charlotte.
Hello, Sigmund.
[FELIX] Didn't expect
to see you here. 'lo, Char.
[CHARLOTTE] I was curious
what the commotion was about.
[RAISHIN]
Oh, you know each other?
Rather well, in fact.
I've been trying
to call on her for ages.
Alas, she turns me
down every time.
[FELIX] Excuse me,
I need to see to this mess.
Perhaps we'll speak again later.
[FELIX] Raishin, come along.
Her magic circuit is missing.
[FELIX] That's his
modus operandi.
The automatons always look
as if he's eaten out
their Eve's Hearts.
Do you know
yet whose it is?
We're still investigatin'.
From what we've been
able to determine so far,
the automaton was a boule user.
[RAISHIN] Yes, that's right.
We fought her
yesterday. Except--
[RAISHIN]
Is something wrong, Char?
[RAISHIN] Hold on a second.
[CHARLOTTE] Let me go.
[FELIX]
I can certainly empathize.
Seeing that must've made
her itch for immediate action.
My blood's boiling, too.
We must apprehend
this monster, and soon.
You'll help me track
him down, won't you?
Yes, I'll help.
But just be forewarned,
I'll be doing it my way.
[LISETTE] Sorry!
If I could have one more
moment of your time?
I'd appreciate it if
we might speak in private.
Shan't take long.
In private, huh?
Sounds like it's serious.
Very.
Nothing of a
romantic nature, I hope?
Please, I am Vice-Chief
of the Disciplinary Board.
I've a solemn duty
to this academy.
And no time for such thoughts.
[RAISHIN] All right, all right,
I was only busting your chops.
How can you even say
such lecherous things?
You ought to be ashamed!
That's the pot callin'
the kettle black!
Yaya will stay
to make sure
this girl doesn't try anythi--
I'm fine on my own.
Go back to the room.
[whines]
Come back as soon as
your "conversation" is done.
Unless you want the
dorm reduced to rubble.
[RAISHIN] Don't you dare!
No rubble! You hear me?
[RAISHIN] Well? What did
you want to talk about?
[LISETTE] I regret the
necessity of doin' this,
but I'm afraid I must
warn you 'bout somethin'.
Charlotte may be your friend,
but please be wary of her.
Her automaton is
not what he seems.
He is a Banned Doll.
Hm?
[LISETTE] I'm sure you know
what constitutes a Banned Doll.
Their parts include
livin' tissue.
Their existence violates
the Mage Code of Ethics.
According to
Belew family tradition,
Sigmund has committed countless
atrocities for generations.
Burning entire villages.
Devouring innocent people.
I hear even now he
can't maintain his form
unless he feasts on
a steady diet of meat.
[RAISHIN] What are
you trying to say?
[LISETTE] To get right to it,
we suspect Cannibal Candy has
been usin' a Banned Doll
to commit these murders.
[YAYA] Raishin.
You're thinking about
that pink-haired vixen
right now, aren't you?
I am.
How do you always
know these things?
Hand over your undergarments
right this minute!
Yaya will thoroughly
inspect them to ascertain
whether you had
relations this afternoon!
Like hell you will!
Seriously, Yaya; you have no
concept of how people work!
[YAYA] But-- but that vixen!
At any rate,
tomorrow I plan to start
really looking into this case.
Given everything I've seen and
heard about Cannibal Candy, I--
No, we have
to find this killer.
Are you with me?
Yes!
[RAISHIN] Charlotte?
What're you doing
over here so late?
Guh--!
[RAISHIN] Yes?
Go out with me!
[CHARLOTTE] Rather,
I'll allow you to take me out.
Tomorrow perhaps.
After lessons are finished.
Huh?
[YAYA]
Wha--? Nuh-- No!
Thank you for the lovely offer,
but no, no, no, no!
[RAISHIN] Yeah sure.
Sounds good. I'll see you then.
Excellent, I shall
hold you to it.
[YAYA] How could you?
You're so cruel to Yaya
after all she's done for you!
Interesting spot
to choose for a date.
Hmph!
Poor, blind fool.
This isn't a date. It's a trap.
[RAISHIN] Actually,
I had assumed as much.
Don't be alarmed.
You're perfectly safe,
I assure you.
Should the villain appear,
I'll handle it.
You just stand there
looking helpless.
Now I see.
You don't have any
friends, do you?
[CHARLOTTE]
Why would you say that?
[RAISHIN] You needed help
with this plan of yours,
and you came to me.
The guy you just met.
I-- No! Y-You've
misread the situation!
I'm helping you!
Ungrateful lout that you are.
Okay, I get it.
You heard Felix offered
me a festival entry
if I could solve this case.
Which means you must've
been eavesdropping.
[CHARLOTTE] Wha--
and if I was? What of it?
I think I'm done with this.
Enough of playing detective.
Let's go on that date instead.
Wha-- What?
How unbelievably forward of you!
[RAISHIN] You're the
one who asked me out.
Or does the daughter
of the great Belew family
not keep her word?
How dare you, sir!
Fine then; name the place,
and I shall take you there.
No, sirree!
Absolutely not!
Yaya will chaperone you!
I know.
Let's go into town.
Into town?
Then Sigmund can't come.
Correct.
It's considered normal practice
to not bring one's
automaton on dates.
Ah... I wouldn't be so
boorish as to ruin your fun.
Have a good time.
What're you--?
That's my hand!
And this is a date.
[CHARLOTTE]
Let me go this instant!
[RAISHIN] Quit flailing.
Y'might try having a bit
more faith in your master.
Does he even deserve it?
Trust me when I say
I am an accurate judge
of a person's character.
I have had a hundred-fifty years
on this earth to figure it out.
There was no lust in
his eyes when they left.
None? Really?
[SIGMUND] Really.
Though I must admit,
boys his age are
unpredictable at best.
No denyin' that.
So I suppose
it's always possible
something may
happen between 'em.
[YAYA] Yaya knew it!
[SIGMUND] We are not
human, you and I.
You may be more or less
human both in appearance
and functionality,
but you mustn't forget
that you will never
actually be one of them.
Yaya knows
that already too!
Automatons operate
on magical power supplied
to us by our puppeteers.
Given that, it's natural to feel
great affection for your master,
but I do not understand how
you came to be so obsessed.
Yaya cares for
Raishin, that's all.
Yaya won't say more out loud.
[SIGMUND] At any rate, our
masters aren't here right now,
and Cannibal Candy
is still on the loose.
We must be careful.
[CHARLOTTE] I don't know
about you, but I'm famished.
Let's go back.
Why? We can eat here.
Come on, I'll even treat.
[CHARLOTTE] I don't take
charity from lechers!
[stomach growls]
[CHARLOTTE] Oh, fine, let's eat!
But I'll have you know,
I will never forgive you
for this embarrassment!
[CHARLOTTE]
It looks divine.
Out of curiosity,
the other day,
why did you eat
lunch at my table?
Just seemed like the
natural progression.
Of what?
We were hardly friends.
First, I yelled at you,
then you challenged
me to a duel,
then you insist
we dine together?
That could only make
sense to a blithering idiot.
I believe I'll take
that as a compliment.
[CHARLOTTE] But why so
intent on my entry, anyway?
There are a hundred of us
who qualified to compete.
You could easily have picked
a lower-ranked target.
[RAISHIN] Victory against
easy prey wouldn't mean as much.
I tried to take
an entry by force,
but at the expense
of another person.
That'd be inexcusable without
also taking a personal risk.
And even then it's
still inexcusable. Sorry.
Yeah. I'm not explaining
myself very well.
When we first met,
my impression was you were
a tough person to read.
But I've come to
realize you're just daft.
So, any more
questions for me?
Only one for now, I think.
About your fighting style.
What is it called?
I noticed you were fighting
alongside your puppet.
Technically, that
was me cheating.
I was creating a formation.
It's my family's fighting
specialty, using group tactics.
That's us.
Pulling the strings
of a team of dolls.
However, my training
was kind of rushed.
I got my hands full
with just Yaya.
The other day, I was
just using my own body
in place of another doll.
So it's a good thing I know
a little something
about martial arts.
What do you mean,
your training was "rushed"?
[RAISHIN] Well,
I didn't start really studying
until just over two years ago.
[CHARLOTTE] Huh? What?
And you already want
to compete for Wise Man?
I have my reasons.
Let's leave it at that.
[RAISHIN] My turn.
Do you have a crush on Felix?
[CHARLOTTE] Wha--? You--!
Don't make me sound so common!
My relationship with Felix
is nothing so vulgar as that!
[RAISHIN] I don't see
anything vulgar about it.
It's no big deal.
That sort of thing
is human nature.
[CHARLOTTE] I'm telling
you to drop it right now.
Or I shall be forced to
cause you grievous bodily harm.
Only sometimes, I make enemies
without realizing or meaning to.
So, as head of the disciplinary
board, Felix worries about me.
That's all.
[RAISHIN] He's asked you
to go out with him, hasn't he?
Why not accept?
I can't do that!
Don't you know how
popular Felix is?
With girls, I mean.
The chits are practically
rabid about him.
[RAISHIN] So you'd wind up
with even more enemies.
Is that it?
[CHARLOTTE] Precisely.
[RAISHIN] What about you?
Why do you want
to be the Wise Man?
[CHARLOTTE] I have a dream.
Something important.
Something I'm willing to
get blood on my hands for.
[RAISHIN] Fair enough.
[RAISHIN] Thank you for
coming shopping with me.
You were a big help.
[CHARLOTTE]
To be honest,
I'm surprised buying her
a gift even occurred to you.
What is it?
Is she so terrifying you have
to buy her presents
to placate her?
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
Not where she can hear me.
You're pitiful.
You know that?
Ordered around by
your own automaton.
That's plain backwards.
[CHARLOTTE] Look, about
what you said before,
the reason you chose
to challenge my entry.
[RAISHIN] Yeah?
[CHARLOTTE] I want you
to know, I get it.
You're still daft,
but I understand
wanting to be punished.
There are things in my past
I'm not proud of, either.
Huh?
No.
Cannibal Candy!
[RAISHIN] Didn't think
he'd strike again so soon!
[RAISHIN] Yaya!
[CHARLOTTE] Raishin!