[bell tolling]
[ANNOUNCER 9A]
Hello and welcome.
Today's celebration
marks one hundred years
since the completion of the
Walpurgis Royal Academy
of Machinart's clock tower.
To begin the festivities,
we have a few opening remarks.
Headmaster Edward Rutherford.
[clapping]
[frightened screams]
[grumbles]
[FREY] She just jumped?
[RAISHIN] Yeah, right off
the roof, earlier today.
[FREY] Wow.
What did she look like?
[RAISHIN] She had
light-colored hair.
And was wearing a floppy hat.
[FREY] Um. Raishin?
Oh, sorry.
Got distracted.
It's weird, though.
The girl actually kind
of looked like Char.
I think I know who that is.
It's Henri. You hadn't
met Henriette Belew?
[RAISHIN] Belew?
[FREY] Yes. Tyrant Rex's
younger sister.
She transferred here.
[RAISHIN]
Oh. Well, that explains it.
[FREY] So sad.
That makes six suicide
attempts since she arrived.
Obviously, she's
never been successful.
The rope would break or
someone would find her.
[RAISHIN] Huh.
Wonder if that makes
her lucky or unlucky.
Oh. And speaking
of Tyrant Rex.
It seems she may
have gone missing.
She never came back to
the dormitory last night.
[RAISHIN] She didn't?
[door opening]
So. You've gotten dressed.
I hope you're not gonna tell me
you're planning to leave
the infirmary today.
[RAISHIN] I'm sorry
to be so predictable.
Are you quite certain
you've thought this through?
You are aware what'll happen
once I've discharged you?
Yeah, I'll have to
rejoin the festival.
[sighs] By the way, I heard
something interesting
about the clock tower explosion.
Hm?
Rumor has it, Tyrant Rex
was the responsible party.
[gasps]
Your face
betrays you, lad.
So, you and Dinosaur Girl
are something of an item, yeah?
[gasps]
And if I told you we were?
Ah!!
Would you be more
likely to discharge me?
We're not, but if it
helps me get out of here.
Do whatever you please.
It's your neck.
[door opening]
[YAYA] Yaya doesn't understand
why you're so insistent.
What's the matter?
[YAYA] You know you'll
have to face Charlotte
as an enemy one day.
Yaya doesn't want you
losing sight of your goal,
or your position, either.
[barking and growling]
You're going
to look for her.
For Tyrant Rex, aren't you?
[RAISHIN] That's my plan, yes.
[FREY] Then please, let me help.
They can help, too. Dogs are
excellent at tracking people.
That would be great.
Thank you.
[opening door]
Lavenna, excellent,
you've returned.
I've news that might be
of some interest to you.
Despite his injuries,
it seems Second Last
is determined to search
for Charlotte Belew.
A noble gesture, certainly,
but I never knew
Tyrant Rex was so popular.
I'd like you to visit him.
I don't fancy him
and his rag-tag search
party nosing about,
and I should think you
would feel the same.
You've less
than forty hours
until the appointed time.
Do make haste.
[YAYA] Raishin, why are
we at the girls' dormitory?
[RAISHIN] Because we need
to question Char's sister.
You saw how strangely
she was acting.
There must be a reason.
I'm guessing she
knows something.
We're too late.
Seems Henriette has
disappeared again.
We know she's
a danger to herself.
Let's find her quickly.
[FREY] Also, look at these.
Pant--Why do you--?
Where did you get those?
Henri's room, obviously.
And just what do you
intend to do with them?
[sniffing]
[barks]
[loud whistle]
[barking dogs]
[YAYA] Raishin!
If you really want
to smell underpants
so badly, you smell Yaya's!
[RAISHIN] Not what
I was thinking about!
You're the only one
here who's that perverted!
[dog howling in distance]
[FREY] Hear that?
They found Henriette.
[RAISHIN] Already?
[HENRIETTE] No! Bad dogs!
Shoo! All of you!
Somebody help me!
[HENRIETTE] Bugger off! Shoo!
[screams]
Get off!
Listen. I know who
you are, Henriette.
Now, where's Char?
Is it true she didn't return
to the dorm last night?
Does her disappearance
have something
to do with the clock tower?
And why are you
so eager to die?
Well, what are you waiting for?
You know something, don't you?
Maybe try to not ask her a
million questions at once.
We're sorry about
this, Henriette,
but would you please
tell us the truth?
These suicide
attempts of yours.
They're your pathetic way
of getting Raishin's
attention, aren't they?
Yeah, this isn't working.
Maybe you can try, Frey.
[FREY] Henri. Are you staging
these suicide attempts
just to get
Raishin's attent-- Ah!
Oh, dear! This cad is
clearly a barbarian!
[RAISHIN] Just hurry and tell
me where Char is, all right?
If you don't,
I'll have no choice
but to set the dogs on you.
[woof]
Aaaa!!
You'll have the dogs
do what to me?
You deviant!
You're absolutely despicable!
What would my mother say
if she knew her
daughter was set upon
by beasts and
their beastly master?
She would be horrified!
[YAYA] How horrible!
Yaya knew nothing
of this fetish.
[sighs]
[YAYA] You won't
even kiss Yaya,
but you will participate
in an unholy union
with that trollop
and an animal?
Yaya would sooner
kill you and herself
than allow another
woman to have you!
Is that what you want?
Damn! She's gettin' away.
Frey, will you follow her?
You're terrible.
The absolute worst
pervert I know.
[RAISHIN] For cryin' out loud,
Frey, not you, too!
[RAISHIN]
Are we on the same page?
This was all just
a misunderstanding.
[FREY] I never doubted you.
[RAISHIN] You liar!
You just finished
calling me a pervert.
[FREY] Yeah.
The festival
starts back up soon.
You should head
back to the field.
[FREY] What are
you gonna do?
Well, I'm gonna see
if I can't track Char down.
I'll get there in time,
though, don't worry.
Are you sure?
[RAISHIN] Yeah, it's fine.
I'm sorry I dragged
you along with me.
[panting]
Back to the beginning.
Let's try the
girls' dorm again.
[YAYA] Yaya assumes
you'll be stealing
Charlotte's knickers now?
[RAISHIN] I'm real tired
of these insinuations.
I just want to see what
I can find out about Henri.
Hold up!
Bad enough
you're playing hooky,
but now you're skulking
around the grounds at night?
Boy, do I have some
questions for you.
That's a pity.
I've no answers for you.
Only a warning.
Leave Henri be or there
will be consequences.
Sorry, no can do.
Although, if you
come along quietly,
I will give it some thought.
You twit. Foolish,
hopeless twit.
I see you're still as
wonderfully obtuse as ever.
I'll say it one more time:
Stay away from my sister.
If you don't,
I shall have to kill you.
Okay, I'm confused.
Just the other day you
promised to protect me.
Quiet! I will kill you.
I mean it!
Please, Raishin,
just keep out of this!
[RAISHIN] You're the
twit this time, Char.
That look on your face
means something's wrong,
and I won't give up
'til I find out what.
If you're that worried,
the solution's simple enough:
go to the infirmary
and visit him.
I am not
going to visit him.
I'm not worried in
the slightest about
that great bumbling buffoon.
His noggin's as
thick as a tree trunk,
so I'm sure he'll be fine.
[SIGMUND] The lady
doth protest too much.
The more obstinate you are,
the clearer your
true feelings become.
What feelings?
[SIGMUND]
For Raishin, of course.
You are attracted to him, yes?
I am nothing of the sort!
How could you even think of
something so absurd as that?
Instead of chicken for lunch,
you get herring from a tin.
Really smelly herring.
You seem to be trying a
bit too hard to deny it, Char.
Why is that, now?
I'm not denying a thing!
What I mean is I can't let
myself have feelings for him.
It would be inconvenient.
Emotions make
things too complicated.
[sighs]
You humans seem to
live for "complicated."
But, if you want
my advice, I--
[knock, knock]
Who's there?
[CHARLOTTE] Henri?
I can't believe it's really you!
Are you all right?
Where have you
been all this time?
Where's Mother?
What are you doing
at the academy?
Enough questions.
You'll have ample chance to
interrogate your sister later.
[SIGMUND] It's been
a long time, Henri.
Well, as you humans
mark it, anyhow.
It's good to
see you, Sigmund.
I hope you're well.
[SIGMUND] I'm glad
to know you're safe.
As you can imagine, Char's
been quite worried about you.
[HENRIETTE] I'm sorry, Char.
Please don't cry.
[CHARLOTTE] Why shouldn't
I have a good cry?
Seems perfectly natural to me!
[CHARLOTTE]
What's happened, Henri?
Please. You can tell me.
[HENRIETTE] I've been
given a dreadful task.
[CHARLOTTE] I'm confused.
What sort of task?
And what does it have
to do with the academy?
I'm so sorry, sister!
I've come here to hurt you!
[gasps]
[YAYA] It's getting late.
Shouldn't we stop?
[RAISHIN]
Are you tired?
No, of course not.
Yaya's tougher and
more tireless than you are!
[RAISHIN sighs]
Guess I should
head to the festival.
I'm sorry, but I have to
ask even more of you.
[YAYA] Don't worry!
Yaya lives to serve.
[YAYA] What is it, Raishin?
Is something wrong?
[RAISHIN] I could
have sworn I heard--
Never mind. Let's go.
[MALE STUDENT 9A]
Silent Roar left,
so I guess that's the end
of competition for tonight.
[MALE STUDENT 9B]
Doesn't seem like
number eighty-seven's
gonna show.
Frey's not here.
She must've gone home
for the night already, huh?
Yeah, looks like
she put her time
in first to avoid
having to face us.
But on the schedule
it says we're supposed
to battle number
eighty-seven tonight.
Do you know who that is?
You're thinking about her.
You're standing there right now,
thinking about Charlotte.
[RAISHIN] How did
you know that?
[ringing bell]
[CHARLOTTE] Don't you dare!
[HENRIETTE] Ch-- Charlotte!
[CHARLOTTE]
Don't do anything stupid!
[CHARLOTTE] Whatever you think,
it's not for the best!
I know you're
terrified of hurting me.
But seeing my sister again,
knowing our mother is
still alive somewhere,
that's worth any
amount of pain to me.
[HENRIETTE] I'm sorry,
Charlotte! So very sorry.
[CHARLOTTE] You don't need
to worry about it anymore.
Tomorrow, I shall put
an end to all of it.
[HENRIETTE] Please forgive me!
[CHARLOTTE] Don't apologize!
When all this is over, we'll
be together again. Understand?
[HENRIETTE] Yes.
[KIMBERLEY] Come.
Ah, Second Last;
I assumed you'd come
calling before long.
Yaya dear.
Make us a spot of tea.
Oh, of course!
So, what would
you like to know?
Since you're an
academy professor
and a part of Nectar,
I know you're well-connected.
That's how you were able to
hush it up when I snuck out.
And it's also the reason
Frey and Loki didn't have
their automatons
confiscated, isn't it?
[KIMBERLEY] At this point, I see
no reason to hide that from you.
However, it should not be
a matter of public knowledge.
Should anyone learn
of this from you--
The debt
I owe you is huge.
I promise I'll take
your secret to the grave.
[KIMBERLEY] How very noble.
See that you do.
But I'd like to know
who's manipulating Char.
Oh?
You're certain someone
behind the scenes
is pulling her strings?
That she isn't acting
of her own free will?
[RAISHIN]
Come on, you know Char.
She's not a violent person.
She would never use
Sigmund's power to kill.
[KIMBERLEY]
She destroyed the clock tower.
That seems awfully violent.
[RAISHIN] And how
many deaths were there?
Zero fatalities.
Several injuries, however.
[RAISHIN] Point made.
So who was she after?
[KIMBERLEY] You're unusually
sharp today, aren't you?
I'm still investigating,
but I do know the
most likely target.
I believe she is after
our esteemed headmaster,
Edward Rutherford.
[gasps]
[RAISHIN] Why? Does she have a
grudge against him or something?
Not that I'm aware.
I assume she's being used.
As you surmised, I don't think
she's acting on her own.
But by whom?
By whom do you think, lad?
Must be someone with reason
to be angry with the headmaster.
Only one I can think
who fits the bill is Felix.
Or, really any of
the Kingsfort family.
[KIMBERLEY]
What a compelling theory.
[RAISHIN] But that's stupid.
Why wouldn't they
be targeting me?
Oh, I'm sure they'd find
it highly satisfying
to kill you, as well.
But your death offers
no profit, so it's unlikely.
What do you suppose
the Kingsforts want more
than anything else right now?
Restored status?
Precisely.
Sir Walter wants to
reclaim their lost honor
and return the family
to political prominence.
The best way to do
that is to cast doubt
upon the situation that
resulted in their downfall.
That doesn't
make sense either.
Wouldn't assassinating
the headmaster
basically be an
admission of their guilt?
[KIMBERLEY] The point here
is to turn black and white
into shades of gray.
The Kingsforts are famous for
their philanthropic endeavors.
The Belews, however, well,
the Belews are famous
for the scandal which led
to their utter disgrace.
[RAISHIN] What scandal?
[KIMBERLEY] You don't know?
The Belews' prized dog
automaton went berserk during
the Prince of Wales'
hunting party
and began savagely
attacking Prince Edmund.
The young prince
was nearly mauled
to death before
anybody could stop it.
The house of Belew is
now an enemy of the Crown.
Public opinion will
follow Crown favor.
[RAISHIN] So if they
trick Char into killing
and make her their patsy.
[KIMBERLEY] How easy
will it be to let her take
the fall for the crimes
of which Felix is accused?
You should back out
of this before it's too late.
Not gonna happen!
Especially if the Kingsforts
are really behind all this.
[KIMBERLEY]
You don't get it, do you?
There's not so much
as a shred of proof.
All of what
I've shared with you is
pure speculation,
and nothing more.
If you let your emotions
get the better of you,
and cause an incident,
the Belew sisters
will be even worse off.
[RAISHIN] So what we
need is hard evidence.
That is correct.
Honest-to-God proof
would solve everything.
[YAYA] It's much too late
for you to be awake.
You should get some sleep.
[RAISHIN] Oh, I will.
Just as soon as
you get out of my bed.
Yaya. About the question
you asked this afternoon.
Why I'm so dead-set
on helping Char.
Why I refuse to abandon her even
after Shoko laid down the law.
Truth is, I don't know, either.
Despite what you think,
I'm not in love with Charlotte.
She and Sigmund are some of the
toughest competitors
in the festival,
so I might be better off
if they were gone.
But if they're in trouble,
I have to help them.
Yes, but why?
It's not about Char;
I'd help Frey, too.
And you, obviously.
Loki'd probably just get mad.
But what can I say?
I'd help him if
he needed it, too.
And now we have Henri
to worry about, as well.
Yaya understands.
She'll always do
whatever you say.
I really am sorry I'm always
causing trouble for you.
[YAYA] No, please.
Never apologize for that.
Yaya is happy just
to be by your side.
Tell you what.
One of these days,
I'll make it up to you.
Oh? Really, Raishin?
You promise?
So does that mean you're
going to marry Yaya?
[RAISHIN]
Why would it mean that?
[YAYA] Because!
You just said you promise
to do anything Yaya wanted,
no matter what!
That's not what I said at all!
I just told you
I'd make it up to you!
Fine. Yaya will settle
for being your wife!
[RAISHIN]
How is that settling?
You just said the same
thing a different way!
[YAYA] If you want to pay Yaya
back for causing her trouble,
then let her do things
to you right now!
[RAISHIN] I can't breathe!
Not sure how many more
sleepless nights I can take.
That must be
because you were
even more passionate
than usual last night.
Twisting the facts as always.
Let's be clear: I was
passionate in my resistance.
[MALE STUDENT 9C]
Hey, did you hear?
Rumor has it Tyrant Rex is the
one who destroyed the tower.
Hard to believe a noble
would attack a
school monument.
That's serious stuff.
Maybe they were wrong
to clear her name before.
Perhaps she is a bad seed.
Makes me wonder
about Cannibal Candy.
I never quite believed Felix
Kingsfort would kill anyone.
[MALE STUDENT 9E]
If Tyrant Rex is rotten,
that casts doubt on
Second Last as well.
[MALE STUDENT 9C]
He only just arrived,
and he slithered
right into the festival.
Seems awfully convenient to me--
[RAISHIN]
Don't let 'em get to you.
Anyway, lessons are
suspended for the day.
Let's start by
looking for Henri,
then we'll see
if we can find Char...
Why did you stop?
Is something the matter?
Henri's right there.
And she's in a hurry.
Sure wish I knew
what she was up to.
[YAYA] Raishin!
[RAISHIN] Headmaster Rutherford!
What's he doing down there?
Oh, I see.
He's inspecting the damage.
[KIMBERLEY] I assume
she's being used.
As you surmised, I don't
think she's acting on her own.
I believe she is after
our esteemed headmaster,
Edward Rutherford.
[RAISHIN] Oh no!
[YAYA] What?
[RAISHIN] I need you to
get ahold of Shoko, fast!
[YAYA]
No! Yaya's coming with you!
Hurry! I'm counting on you!
Oh man,
she's really gonna do it!
No, Char! Hold your fire!
Please listen to me!
Dammit! Henri's in
the line of fire!