[CHARLOTTE] If you're looking
for the twit, he's gone.
[FREY] Oh! Tyrant Rex, hi.
Sorry about your dog.
I hope he heals.
Thanks. He's all I have.
Without him I'd--
I'd be all alone.
From what I've seen,
that's not the case at all.
You've never been alone.
Huh?
[CHARLOTTE]
There's always been someone
in your life who puts you first.
That's how it
seems to me, anyhow.
Now then, back to the twit.
[FREY] Raishin? Where did he go?
[CHARLOTTE]
Unless his plan's changed,
he's most likely nickin' pooches
from a certain orphanage.
Huh?! Why would he do that?
'Cause he's
nobler than he is smart.
He cannot bear to stand idly by
when there's a damsel
in distress somewhere.
It's his greatest weakness.
I could just strangle the git.
Honestly, if Professor
Kimberley found out--
[KIMBERLEY] As it happens,
I am already aware.
[KIMBERLEY]
No need for hysterics.
I'm not going to interfere
with his big plan--
quite the opposite, in fact.
[KIMBERLEY] If you will
abide by a few conditions,
I shall take you to him.
[KIMBERLEY]
What do you say, Charlotte?
You are worried about
your good friend, yes?
Uh, don't be daft!
That knobhead and
I aren't friends!
Really, of all the nonsense.
[KIMBERLEY] Not coming, then?
[CHARLOTTE]
He can handle this. I trust him.
Frey? How about you then?
Yes, I'll come.
What the bloody hell?
[GUARD 8A] Stop this!
We're on your side!
Okay, what are you doing here?
It doesn't make sense!
Make up your mind.
Are you my enemy or ally?
Does your stupidity
know no bounds?
The penalty for academy students
who attack civilians is death.
Yes, I'm well
aware of that, thank you;
but it doesn't matter.
I can prove they've been
doing illegal experiments.
So we can add naïvety
to your list of flaws.
Your so-called proof will
never see a courtroom!
The Church'll
hold a witch trial,
and you'll be
burned at the stake!
Y'think so?
Only a moron would
underestimate me.
Whatever happens,
I'll never stop fighting.
Even if they do kill me.
Heh. Ever the noble fool.
Makes me sick.
[RAISHIN] Who the hell are
you to lecture me, anyway?
How many guards did
you just take out?
Police, quick!
A vicious criminal's
lurking over here!
[LOKI] Oh, that's how
you want to play it?
Inspector!
You'll wanna see this!
I've found their ringleader!
[RAISHIN] You're one
of the almighty Rounds.
Isn't aiding and abetting
a criminal beneath you?
[LOKI] Sod the Rounds.
I'd much rather vent my spleen
on these bastards in our way.
[BOTH] Well, I guess
we're both idiots!
[YAYA] Something wrong?
[RAISHIN] Looks like--
[LOKI] Lucifer.
[BRONSON]
This would seem my lucky day.
Procuring parts of your
calibre. And so easily.
I didn't even have
to lift a finger.
[BRONSON] Good god, son.
Have you taken
leave of your senses?
[RAISHIN] "Son?"
Then that must be Bronson.
[LOKI]
No, I've returned to them.
I've spent so long
licking your boots.
Obeying you without
so much as a question.
[LOKI] But all that
ends here and now!
[RAISHIN] Havin' some trouble?
You almost died there.
[LOKI] I'm fine.
Just thought I'd
leave you an opening,
should you wish to attack.
I'm considerate.
It repelled her kick?
This series of automatons
are very powerful.
Lucifer has a Jet
magic circuit, like Cherubim.
[KIMBERLEY] Ah.
So it hit her with a
high-density blast of hot air.
Cherubim! Spin!
You are an utter fool.
To ensure a win
in a real battle,
one must target the mage.
[RAISHIN]
So true!
Haha!
[RAISHIN screams in pain]
Ah! Raishin!
I am gravely disappointed.
Is there any beast more wretched
than the dog who
bites its master?
[LOKI] I obeyed. We obeyed.
We always did as we were told.
Even when our friends began
disappearing out of the blue.
Even after you made us
your test subjects.
Therefore I don't understand
why you've betrayed me now.
Have I not rewarded
you both amply
for services performed?
I am a humble,
tolerant person, Father.
However, there are three things
in this world I'm
afraid I cannot forgive.
People who think they
can order me around.
People who stand against me.
And, of course,
bastards who dare
betray my sister!
[CHARLOTTE]
There's always been someone
in your life who puts you first.
That's how it
seems to me, anyhow.
[BRONSON] It's a shame, really.
I went to some
trouble acquiring you
and your sister
for my experiments.
[BRONSON] I journeyed
all the way to the States.
And even then,
spiriting you away required
more than one cheap trick.
Just lie here quietly.
I won't kill you.
Not here--I'd much rather
disassemble you alive.
So. Still up
and about, are you?
Remarkable,
for an Oriental specimen.
Are you a special model?
You still strong
enough to fight?
Do you truly have to ask?
Give me a hand then?
Suppose I can.
Don't get used
to it, though.
[BRONSON]
Come up
with some ridiculous
little trick, have you?
[RAISHIN] Yeah.
A ridiculous little
trick that will end you.
But first things first;
I want to know why
you lied to Frey.
You never planned
to let the Garms live.
So why did you
force her to fight?
Why did you try to make
her something she's not?
Why did you pollute her heart?
[BRONSON] Because that
is the way of the world.
[RAISHIN]
What are you talking about?
[BRONSON] Scientific
advancement occurs only
when there is
continual progress.
Forward motion.
We can allow neither
stasis nor regression.
For mankind, the absence
of progress leads
to only one thing--
Rapid decline and extinction.
Probing life's mysteries,
seeking its truths.
That is what humans
were created to do.
It is our proper path.
Because of our gifts,
we magi are
especially responsible.
That is the academy's purpose,
and the entire reason the
title of Wise Man exists.
It's a fact of life.
Oft times the ends
do justify the means.
[thinking] "Advancement?"
"Progress?" That's why?
That's the reason?
Why my mother and father,
and Loki, and I...?
[RAISHIN]
If murdering children's families
is considered progress.
Then mankind can
go straight to hell!
Their combined
heat welded them together?
Not good enough.
What was--?
[KIMBERLEY thinking]
She repelled the blast
of hot air with a shockwave.
Did Second Last know the
Jet Circuit's secret all along?
In order to block
Lucifer's blow,
he would need to dispel its heat
with a jet of the
same temperature.
He must have deduced as much,
hid explosives
in Yaya's sleeves,
and then saved them
for this very moment.
The lad has nerves of steel.
Well, look who's
not all talk.
I'd originally
planned to use
that as my trump
card against you.
Yaya, Final Whistle.
Hisagi Sword Glint!
Hey, Second Last,
you still alive over there?
[RAISHIN] You're not looking
so good yourself, Blade Emperor.
Think you can even stand up?
Don't be absurd.
I'm only taking a short
break to catch my breath.
You're the one who looks
like he'll never walk again.
[RAISHIN] I'll be fine.
I'm just looking at the stars.
They're nice tonight.
Stargazing happens
to be a hobby of mine.
You do a lot of
face-down stargazing?
Because I'd think it would be
rather tough in that position.
Why not simply admit
that you're half-dead?
I promise I won't
mock you for it.
[RAISHIN] Like I said, I'm fine.
You must be in pretty
terrible shape, though.
You oughtta get to a hospital
and have the doctors see to
your scrapes and scratches.
I can carry you there
if you need me to.
[LOKI] You're the one
who should be there,
having nurses hand-feeding you
and giving you blanket-baths
while you regain your strength.
[RAISHIN] How stupid are you?
That would be
awful for my health!
You know why?
Because Yaya would murder me!
[YAYA] No talking, Raishin.
Please, take it easy.
[LOKI] You are a
complete imbecile.
[RAISHIN] Am not! You are!
[BRONSON thinking]
A shame to sacrifice Lucifer,
but at least Cherubim survived.
I'll still have something
to showcase in the festival.
Raishin! Raishin!
This infuriating one, however.
I think I shall have to
put down. Then I still win.
Though I'd prefer
a less dull ending.
[gunshot]
[KIMBERLEY]
Dreadfully sorry, Bronson.
Does this liven it up?
[BRONSON] What is the
meaning of this intrusion?
Explain yourselves at once!
[KIMBERLEY] We are Crusaders.
You may know us better
as the Brotherhood
of the Magi's Watchdogs.
So you're with Nectar.
Doing background checks on
your students now, are you?
[KIMBERLEY] Sort of.
There's a bit of trouble over
this year's festival.
Leading us to this
enlightening home visit.
Divine Works.
Arrogant enough to claim
you're touched by God's hand.
Now you're under arrest
for practicing forbidden arts.
[BRONSON] Beg pardon?
[KIMBERLEY]
I have evidence: Modification,
experimentation, and
abandonment of human subjects.
Additional charges will
now be filed, of course,
for the heinous crimes
of kidnapping and murder.
From what I observed,
your automaton seemed more
high-precision than Loki's.
Yet you couldn't even manage
to beat a pair of teenaged boys.
So the former pretty boy,
once hailed as an angel,
crashes into middle age.
Instead of wielding
swords with telekinesis,
you rely on a machine.
Calling it Lucifer only made
your bitterness more apparent.
You were "Sword Angel."
And now look at you.
I've regrets, perhaps.
But I harbor no bitterness.
[KIMBERLEY] No?
I should have been
Wise Man all those years ago.
I would not now
be facing charges
for a few little experiments.
Your ignorance surprises me.
I truly believed you
were more intelligent.
And what does that mean?
While the Wise Man is not bound
by the Mage Code of Ethics,
as the rest of us are.
He or she is still
bound by the law.
All human experimentation
requires consent of the subject.
[KIMBERLEY] Children, like
those who you preyed upon,
cannot give their consent.
Even the Wise Man
is not allowed to do that.
[sighs]
[KIMBERLEY thinking]
Blind fool.
So consumed by the
idea of playing God,
and in the end, God played you.
The gallows suit you far better
than the Wise Man's throne.
Good Lord.
These children will turn
my hair gray before its time.
[bells tolling]
Tee hee! Be a good boy!
Time to undress!
If you don't
remove your underpants,
Yaya won't be able
to make you better!
This is not how a
nurse is supposed to behave!
It's unprofessional!
I am a humble, tolerant person.
However, there are three
things I simply cannot abide.
People who order me around.
People who stand against me.
And no-good foreigners
who take advantage of
nurses in the infirmary!
If you hate it so much,
help me make her stop!
Why do you need my help?
She's your automaton!
That's right,
Yaya is Raishin's beloved doll.
Now ignore him and pet
Yaya like you always do.
[LOKI] Unbelievable!
[RAISHIN]
Nothing she says is true!
She's lying, I swear!
[RAISHIN] Uh, Frey!
Good to see you!
I hear you've won
all your battles so far.
Yes, thanks to
Rabbi and Riviera.
Oh, and Ruby, too.
And Reveena and Robin.
They all work so hard.
I'm quite proud of them.
[RAISHIN] Riviera.
Ruby. Reveen--Um.
Can I just call 'em the Five Rs?
Huh?
Loki.
It's because of you that
they're still here with me.
Please, I didn't
do anything.
You should be thanking
this idiot instead.
Yeah, don't believe
a word he says.
You shoulda seen
the look on his face
when you almost died.
Do you want to die?
Think you can defeat me?
Let's go. I'll rip
that pretty face off.
[FREY] Stop it!
Loki! No fighting!
C'mon, Raishin might be
part of our family soon!
[FREY]
Uh... um... eh...
[FREY shrieks]
[RAISHIN] Yeah um,
what did she say?
I must not have heard her right.
So you are in a
relationship with that vixen?
Just when did you
start dating my sister?
Never, that's when!
You two are nuts!
[YAYA] Where did that coward go?
Coward.
[sighs]
[RAISHIN] Oh, it's you. Hi.
[FREY] Sorry about all this.
Loki's temper gets out
of control sometimes.
[RAISHIN] Don't worry.
He and I will settle things
eventually, at the festival.
[FREY] You could report
him to administration.
Well, I don't want to
get him expelled or anything.
He beat me once.
I just want a chance
to even the score.
So, are you gonna
continue competing?
Yeah.
I need to be Wise Man
so I can use forbidden arts.
What for?
[FREY] So I can put Loki's and
my hearts back to normal again.
[RAISHIN] Hell of a plan.
Though Loki's probably intending
to try the same thing, you know.
I've never done the things
for him that a
big sister's supposed to.
So it has to be me.
I won't even lose
to you, Raishin.
Yeah, we'll see.
Sigmund?
No, just a dove.
[thinking] I haven't
seen Char in a while.
Not since that night.
I can always count
on your stupidity.
It's as reliable as Big Ben!
Didn't realize I'd made
her that angry with me.
Char? No, that's not her.
Hey.
Yaya!
Great timing, Yaya!
If it wasn't for you--
[YAYA] You're an idiot.
You scared Yaya!
How could you?
She just jumped;
I didn't exactly
have time to think.
Hey, are you all right?
You're not hurt too badly?
Ahhh!!
A man touched me!
I just saved
your life here!
Hmph! That's
exactly the problem!
Did I look like
I wanted help?
Did I ask to be rescued?
Why did you
save me, you cad?
As recompense, I ask
that you now kill me.
Or, at the very least, you
must give me a sound beating.
What the hell
are you saying?
Ravage my body
in whatever way
your basest instincts desire.
Do with me what you will.
I shan't object.
Make me an outlet for
your animal passions.
Disgusting!
What kind of freak
do you think I am?
Since the vixen asked so
nicely, Yaya will beat her.
No, Yaya, you will not.
[RAISHIN] Hey! Come back!
[YAYA] You want to
have your way with her!
And use her for your
carnal animal passions!
For once, could you
read the social cues here?
You deny Yaya when
she throws herself at you.
So tell me what makes
this vixen so special!
[YAYA] What is that?
[RAISHIN] Char!