We have another victim.
[FELIX] Hello, Char.
You two were in town together?
[CHARLOTTE] Oh. Yes.
[murmuring crowd]
[sobbing]
[RAISHIN] I remember her,
from before. From the fight.
[FELIX] My dear.
You seem to have a keen
interest in this case.
However, I think
it would be best
if you were to stay away
from it going forward.
[CHARLOTTE] But!
[FELIX] Please, leave it
to the Disciplinary Board.
Also, I see with
whom your heart lies.
While I am disappointed,
I shan't interfere.
You've made your decision.
And it was in Raishin's favor.
I shall respect your choice.
It isn't like that!
Now if you will excuse
me, I have work to do.
And I think I should
not see you for a while.
[RAISHIN] Char!
What the hell
was that about?
[FELIX] Harsh, I know.
But I had to be.
Otherwise she will keep
risking her own safety.
Understand?
I guess, but that doesn't
mean I like to see her hurt.
[FELIX] I shall endeavor make
it up to her when this is over.
Yaya's love has
returned after a long day!
Welcome home!
Great timing, too!
Supper is ready and waiting.
Come see!
Yaya has outdone herself!
I think I'm missing
something here.
[YAYA] Don't be silly, Raishin.
Come to the table!
Something's bothering you!
Not at all, Yaya is fine.
No need to worry about her.
[RAISHIN] I was thoughtless.
I cannot apologize enough.
[YAYA] That was so cruel!
You know quite well
how Yaya feels.
[sobs]
Do you know how much
that hurt, Raishin?
I'm so sorry.
Please don't cry.
'Kay.
Almost forgot.
I brought back a
little present for you.
Present for Yaya?
[RAISHIN] Yep.
[RAISHIN] I noticed yours were
looking a little worse for wear.
[RAISHIN] I figured these
might hold up better.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
Perfect fit!
That other thing. Yaya?
What's that?
As far as Char goes, I don't
have feelings for her.
Of course you don't.
She is nice. And I
consider her a friend.
But to be honest,
I really just don't go for
girls who pad their brassieres.
Who does?
I prefer more curves.
Bountiful, goddess-like
cleavage. Like Shoko's.
Totally reasonable!
[YAYA] Shoko. Again.
It's always Shoko!
I am so sick of Shoko!
[RAISHIN] You're missing
the point, Yaya.
I had my own reasons
for going out with Char.
I wanted to confirm something.
[RAISHIN] What distinguishes
Cannibal Candy
is the wound it leaves behind.
Like a half-melted
chocolate bar.
It's very distinctive.
Sigmund's magic is light-based.
It could produce
that kind of effect.
But if I went
out with Char,
took her away from the academy,
and Cannibal Candy made a move.
[YAYA] Then she'd
have a solid alibi.
Exactly. And the
killer did strike again.
So, that means Charlotte
is innocent, right?
I dunno. It seems
awfully convenient to me.
The timing of the attack seemed
to perfectly coincide with
when she and I were gone.
Charlotte may
not have been here,
but Sigmund was.
Were you with
him the whole time?
Well, no.
But he wouldn't have been able
to use magic anyway, would he?
At least not without
his puppeteer nearby.
Yeah, except that
he's a Banned Doll.
You know what that means.
He could provide a little
bit of magic by himself.
[telephone ringing]
Why're you calling?
[LISETTE] I'm attemptin'
to locate Charlotte, actually.
She ought t'have
been here by now.
Y'see, she and I both live
in the Griffin Hall dorm.
[RAISHIN]
Oh. And she isn't there?
No. I haven't set eyes on her,
and it's quite late.
I thought perhaps
she was off pursuin'
impure relations with you,
so I rang to see.
'Parently I was incorrect,
so ta. Useless git.
Lovely girl.
[RAISHIN] Char must be out
somewhere investigating again.
What a pain.
[YAYA] Oh, no.
[SHOKO] Such a beautiful night.
Don't you, think, boy?
The moon especially.
Shoko, ma'am, hello.
[SHOKO] Yaya, my dear,
you're looking well.
Yes ma'am. Yaya is in
excellent working order.
[IRORI] If you are operating
normally, as you say,
then why is it obvious
you have been crying?
[YAYA] Irori, hi!
You're here, too?
[IRORI]
Indeed. You're growing lax.
[SHOKO]
I hear you started a brawl
almost the moment
you arrived. Yes?
[RAISHIN]
Pretty much.
[SHOKO]
Interesting.
Would you care to explain why
you didn't destroy a
single one of your opponents?
Whatever, I did
plenty of damage.
[SHOKO] Don't play
the simpleton, boy.
I know you're not one.
An automaton won't die unless
you stop its Eve's Heart.
There is no point
in taking half measures.
Remember, dolls are not people.
Sorry, I don't buy into that.
To me, automatons are human.
I wouldn't stop a
doll's heart so lightly.
Far as I'm concerned,
it's murder.
That's my school of puppetry.
We need to talk
about Cannibal Candy.
Please understand,
he is a far greater
threat than you realize.
Even the Army's involved.
They're in the process
of trying to identify him.
But nothing yet, huh?
Not yet.
The academy is
concealing information
pertaining to the case.
Given their secrecy,
we've considered the possibility
British royalty is involved.
You don't have
to be part of this.
It's not too late yet
to back out, you know.
[RAISHIN] No.
This has become personal.
[RAISHIN]
There's someone involved
I don't want to abandon.
She's a brat,
but she's alone out there.
[RAISHIN] She's fixated
on Cannibal Candy.
I don't know why,
but she won't back off.
When it comes down to it,
I guess I feel like I owe her.
I feel guilty.
Damn it!
It's hard to explain!
I'm sayin' I wanna save her!
[SHOKO] Yaya.
[YAYA] Oh! Y-yes, ma'am!
[RAISHIN] Yaya!
[RAISHIN] What did you do?
For lack of a better term,
I "unbound" her.
See, boy. Yaya's
Diamond Strength circuit
is without peer.
[SHOKO] However,
one thing it cannot do
is defy the Law of Causality.
For example,
consider Tyrant Rex's
magic circuit, called Gräm.
[SHOKO] Yaya cannot withstand
a direct hit from that magic.
It would be the end of her.
One more thing you
should keep in mind.
Yaya's natural enemies
are water and wind.
No matter how much
power she may have,
she cannot subdue
that which has no form.
So do try to be
careful out there.
We will.
Yaya. Let's go.
[IRORI] Master. Are you sure
that was the right decision?
[SHOKO] Worried about Yaya?
[IRORI] No! I have no
personal feelings invested.
[SHOKO] Worry not, child.
All will be well.
Yaya is fine.
I did unbind her.
[IRORI] And what of Raishin?
Will he be all right?
Yaya won't inadvertently
drain him dry?
[SHOKO] Come, now,
the boy is not so weak as that.
[IRORI] No, Master.
But he has only been studying
puppetry for a few years.
[SHOKO] A short time.
That is true.
[SHOKO] You. Boy.
You are the only surviving
member of Clan Akabane, correct?
[RAISHIN] Who are you?
[SHOKO] Magnificent, isn't she?
[SHOKO] She is the second part
of my Seasonal
Treasures trilogy.
She is Yaya, the Moon.
Karyusai is the
greatest living doll
maker in the world.
Likes fine wine,
women, and parties.
Well known as the
biggest carouser around.
Oh-ho. I see
my reputation precedes me.
I will admit, I do like
my wine and my girls very much.
[RAISHIN] Then it was you.
You made the
Army's Veiled Fuji series.
[SHOKO]
I consider that a failure.
They weren't beautiful at all.
However, thanks to
my work on that series,
I am well known among
the military elite.
[SHOKO] In fact, with
my contacts and influence,
I am in a position
to grant your wish.
I can help you, boy.
I can find him for you,
the one you hate.
The one whose life
you long to take.
And I can lend
you the automaton
you'll need to
accomplish that goal.
[SHOKO] So, boy.
What do you say?
Are you mine now?
[SHOKO] He's simply unaware
of his natural gifts.
There is genius inside him.
Always has been.
His clan are Onmyoji,
blending cosmology and religion.
They at one time used
dharmapalas and shikigami
in their practice--truly
fearsome familiars.
[SHOKO] Doesn't it
sound magnificent?
Of course.
Their bloodline is
one of the reasons
such grave misfortune
befell the Akabane siblings.
[IRORI] When they finally meet,
what do you suppose
the outcome will be?
Can Raishin defeat Tenzen?
[SHOKO] Revenge.
Such rubbish, isn't it?
[IRORI] Master?
[SHOKO] I daresay he'll resent
me when he learns the truth.
No avoiding it at this point.
[YAYA] Up ahead!
[RAISHIN] It's me,
Lisette! Raishin!
[LISETTE] I didn't
expect you 'ere.
[RAISHIN] What's going on?
[LISETTE] The Disciplinary
Board has been mobilized.
We are all out here
searching for Charlotte.
[RAISHIN] Why are you so
desperate to find her tonight?
[LISETTE] We made
a startling discovery.
A store of magic circuits
was found in her room.
[RAISHIN] That can't be!
We are not
yet certain they
were the ones taken from
Cannibal Candy's victims.
Good night.
[RAISHIN] Wait a sec.
Technically, I'm affiliated
with the board
right now, right?
So, you're duty-bound
to help me.
[SIGMUND] You should
turn back, Char.
What's got your goat, anyhow?
[CHARLOTTE] It is unforgivable.
I cannot stand idly by
and do nothing.
[RAISHIN] This is
where the lockers are?
[LISETTE] Yes.
This is a repository
for important machines.
I've received
permission to enter.
However, a great many automatons
are kept inside this building.
[LISETTE] Your doll
could destroy them easily,
so you understand the concern.
[RAISHIN] But we
would never do that.
[LISETTE] Nevertheless,
I assume my meaning was clear.
[RAISHIN] Yeah, fine, I get it.
[RAISHIN] Yaya will remain here.
[YAYA] Raishin!
[RAISHIN] Lisette.
Can I ask something?
[LISETTE] You may.
[RAISHIN] I've never
met Felix's automaton.
I was hoping you could
tell me what it's like.
[LISETTE] I can't
vouch for this myself,
but I have heard that it
dates back to the Renaissance.
[RAISHIN] That
makes it an antique.
A doll that old,
I wonder what sort of
magic circuit it runs on.
Sorry. I wouldn't know.
Felix's locker
is right through here.
There's something I've
been wanting to ask you.
Huh?
[RAISHIN] When we were
at the crime scene,
you said the victimized
doll was a boule user.
How did you conclude that?
There wasn't much to suggest it.
[LISETTE] Well, it was
patently obvious, actually.
Boules leave very
distinctive injuries--
[RAISHIN] The doll's legs were
crushed, I know, I saw it.
Which is what
I'm asking about.
The natural conclusion would be
the attacker was a boule user.
It shouldn't occur to you
that she was attacked
with her own weapon,
unless you had
something else to go on.
Or unless you saw it happen.
[LISETTE] What're you
accusin' me of?
No need
to get defensive.
I just thought you might've
been an eyewitness.
It's a bad idea
to make assumptions!
[LISETTE] Raishin!
Where are you goin'?
Get back 'ere!
Oh, bollocks.
[RAISHIN]
How did it take so long
to figure out
something so obvious?
This is
Lisette Norden's corpse!
[RAISHIN] You're a Banned Doll!
I warned you 'bout makin'
assumptions, didn't I?
You shouldn'ta
stuck your nose in!
[alarm blaring]
[GUARD 3A] What happened here?
[LISETTE] You're just in time.
I'm Lisette Norden, Vice-Chief
of the Disciplinary Board.
Apprehend this lad:
Raishin Akabane.
I want him held on suspicion of
colluding with Cannibal Candy.
And as a precaution,
take the doll out front.
[GUARD 3B] Understood.
We'll bring her in.
[LISETTE] I shall go an'
report this to the board.
[GUARD 3C] Thank you, ma'am!
[CHARLOTTE] There it is,
at last. I want it alive.
[CHARLOTTE] Lustre Flare!
[CHARLOTTE] Smashing!
[FELIX] Stop at once!
[FELIX] The plan worked.
Hello, Char.
[CHARLOTTE] Felix!
[FELIX]
We set out that automaton
as bait for Cannibal Candy.
The dormitory warden alerted us
that you'd slipped
out of Griffin Hall.
That's when we found the proof--
quite a lot of it--in your room.
[CHARLOTTE] What?
[FELIX] It was a large
collection of magic circuits.
Eve's Hearts to be exact.
[CHARLOTTE] No, wait!
That isn't--!
[FELIX]
Charlotte of House Belew!
You are Cannibal Candy.
[CHARLOTTE] What?
[KIMBERLEY] Wait.
Several broken ribs, it seems.
[KIMBERLEY]
She's badly injured, too.
Been beaten half to death.
[KIMBERLEY] Stand back!
Get down!
[KIMBERLEY] What is this?
What's happening to her?
What manner of beast--?
[MALE DISCIPLINARY 3A]
Do you see that light?
[MALE DISCIPLINARY 3B]
It's off near the lockers!
[FELIX] We need to know
what's happening over there.
All board members,
dispatch at once.
[MALE DISCIPLINARY 3C] Sir,
you shouldn't stay here alone.
Tyrant Rex is a
formidable enemy.
[FELIX] I shall be fine.
In case you've forgotten,
I am one of the Rounds.
There, you see.
My automaton's arrived.
I won't require
further assistance.
[FELIX] Now.
Make haste, all of you!
[MALE DISCIPLINARY 3B] But, sir!
Exactly how
dense are you?
I'm telling you you'll
be in my way. Go!
[FELIX] There.
Now we can chat in private.
You don't
honestly believe
I'm Cannibal Candy, do you?
Can't you see how
ridiculous that is?
[FELIX] I don't need
to believe it.
I just need others to.
That was the
original plan, anyway.
To set the new chap,
Raishin, on your tail,
and have him destroy you.
[FELIX] But, unfortunately,
he dug too deeply.
[CHARLOTTE] Wait, what
have you done to Raishin?
[FELIX]
Hmph!
[CHARLOTTE] Where is he?
[FELIX] If you
find it comforting,
think of it as a
cruel twist of fate.
It's fate that we were both here
in the year of the festival--the
year of the magical eclipse.
Yes. And it is also fate
that your doll's Gräm is
like my doll's Predator.
[CHARLOTTE] I see now.
You set me up! Which means--
You're a murderer!
You're Cannibal Candy!
Felix! How could you--?
Why would you--
do something so cruel?
[FELIX] Because I want to
be named the Wise Man.
Obviously. I will be
king of the magical world!
[FELIX] Now, Char,
this is goodbye.
[SIGMUND]
Why are you sitting there?
Quickly! I cannot
defeat him on my own!
[CHARLOTTE] Raishin. I'm sorry.
[RAISHIN] Don't be an idiot,
Char. It's not you.
You have nothing to
apologize for. He does.