- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ryomou:
THAT LIGHT.
WHY?
DID THE GHOST FROM THE PAST
TAKE OVER EVERYTHING?
IS THERE NOTHING ELSE LEFT?
SO, THAT'S IT?
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS
TO FIGHTERS WITH SACRED BEADS.
IS THAT WHAT WE ALL WILL
EVENTUALLY BECOME?
- Ryofu:
RYOMOU.
- RYOFU?
- WHY ARE YOU HERE?
YOU DON'T BELONG HERE.
YOU HAVE A LIFE AND A SCHOOL
TO GO HOME TO.
THERE ARE PEOPLE
WAITING FOR YOU.
- BUT YOU'RE--
- YOU KNOW, RYOMOU,
IF WE HAD MET
FOR THE FIRST TIME
A LITTLE EARLIER
THAN WE DID,
AND MAYBE UNDER SLIGHTLY
DIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCES,
I THINK YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN
MY BEST FRIEND.
THOUGH I DOUBT YOU BELIEVE THAT.
YOU MEANT MORE TO ME
THAN YOU KNEW.
I LOVED YOU, RYOMOU.
I USED TO BOAST
I WOULD CHANGE MY FATE,
NO MATTER WHAT IT COST ME.
BUT IN THE END, I WAS AFRAID.
I DIDN'T WANT TO DIE, RYOMOU.
- THAT SAME FATE
THAT I CARRIED WITH ME, RYOFU.
FOR ALL I KNOW, IT MAY HAVE
BEEN THE VERY SAME AS YOURS.
- ( gasps )
- Ryomou:
KAN'U!
WAIT, THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE.
SHIRYUU CHOU'UN?
- DAMN IT ALL.
CURSED SHIRYUU.
- Chou'un KANU, OUR LEADER'S
LIFE IS IN GRAVE DANGER.
WE NEED TO SAVE HER
AT ANY COST.
THAT'S WHY I NEED YOU
TO TRY AND LISTEN TO ME.
WHY I NEED TO GET YOU
BACK TO SEITO
AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
BUT RIGHT NOW, YOU'RE IN
NO POSITION TO HEED MY WORDS.
YOUR FIGHTING SPIRIT IS FILLED
WITH A FRIGHTENING AMOUNT
OF EVIL.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
KNOW THAT IF YOU TRY
TO STOP ME, YOU WILL REGRET IT.
I PROMISE YOU,
I WILL SHOW NO MERCY.
- WELL THEN, KAN'U, IT SEEMS
THAT TAKING YOU BACK
TO YOUR LEADER WILL TAKE
LONGER THAN I HOPED.
I SUPPOSE I'LL HAVE TO DO THIS
THE HARD WAY.
- OH, VERY INTERESTING.
I'D BE LYING TO YOU
IF I SAID
I NEVER WANTED AN EXCUSE
TO TAKE YOU ON.
- KAN'U ISN'T EVEN IN CONTROL
OF HER OWN MIND.
THESE TWO ARE THE TOP FIGHTERS
OF SEITO ACADEMY.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN
WHEN THEY CLASH?
- LET'S BEGIN.
- Ekitoku:
TOO BAD, BITCH!
YOU'VE USED UP YOUR DISKS,
THERE'S NO ESCAPE.
YOU'VE ALREADY LOST, SO GIVE UP
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
- ( screams )
- Moukaku: DON'T ACT
LIKE YOU'VE ALREADY WON!
DON'T GO DOWN YET.
I'M NOT THROUGH WITH YOU.
- HA, IF YOU WANT THE PRIVILEGE
OF BEING A FIGHTER
SAVE YOUR BOASTING UNTIL
AFTER YOU'VE WON, FUCKWIT!
- Ekitoku:
KAN'U, NOW THAT I THINK OF IT,
YOU NEVER LET GO
OF YOUR GREEN DRAGON BLADE,
DO YOU?
THE UNCHO KAN'U
OF 1800 YEARS AGO
PROBABLY DID
THE EXACT SAME THING.
- HE VERY WELL MIGHT HAVE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY,
EKITOKU CHOUHI HAD A WEAPON
AS WELL, DIDN'T HE?
- NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
HE DID.
IT WAS A LONG SPEAR
WITH A CRAZY SHARP BLADE
THAT RIPPLED LIKE A SERPENT.
- YOU KNOW, EVEN IF YOU
DON'T HAVE THAT LANCE
RIGHT NOW IN THIS LIFE,
YOUR BODY IS STILL ENDOWED
WITH AN INNATE SENSE
AND ABILITY
TO WIELD THAT WEAPON.
TO WIELD EKITOKU CHOUHI'S
SERPENT SPEAR.
- I'M NOT...
GIVING UP YET!
- YOU CAN'T HANDLE IT!
HANDLE THIS, BITCH!
- Hakufu:
ALRIGHT, SO YOU TWO MAKE...
97 AND 98.
- 99!
- 100!
- AND INCLUDING THIS GUY,
103!
NOW THEN...
THAT JUST ABOUT DOES IT.
WHOA, STILL FIGHTING, ARE WE?
- MASTER, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE ALL FINALLY DONE HERE.
BUT THERE ISN'T MUCH TIME LEFT,
SO YOU SHOULD HURRY ON AHEAD
AND GET TO KAN'U.
- Hakufu:
RIGHT, THANK YOU.
TRY TO BE CAREFUL, BACHIN!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING
STANDING THERE?
AREN'T YOU WORRIED ABOUT MASTER?
YOU'RE HER BOYFRIEND
AND ALL,
ACT LIKE IT AND PROTECT HER!
- BOYFRIEND?!
WAIT, HANG ON.
I THINK YOU GOT IT WRONG.
- HURRY UP AND GET GOING,
GOLDFISH POOP.
- I UNDERSTAND, THANKS BACHOU.
- Soujin: TRY AND GRAB
MY ASS WILL YOU...
- GOOD GRIEF, WHAT A HANDFUL
THAT BOYFRIEND OF HERS IS.
- HUH, WERE YOU
SAYING SOMETHING?
- Koukin:
HAKUFU!
- KOUKIN!
- WHAT THE HELL JUST HAPPENED?
- THIS CAN'T HAPPEN!
MASTER!
ARE YOU ALRIGHT DOWN THERE?
YOU HAVE TO SAY SOMETHING!
- Ten'i:
FORGET ABOUT HER.
- IT IS THE END
FOR ALL OF YOU.
WHILE I STILL BREATHE,
I WON'T ALLOW ANYONE
TO DEFY MOTHER MARY.
- Soujin:
HEY, YOU!
YOU'RE TEN'I,
ONE OF OUR
MIDDLE SCHOOL KIDS, AREN'T YOU?
JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING WAY OUT HERE?
- ONLY THROUGH
THE MERCIFUL GRACE
OF MOTHER MARY
HAVE I BEEN LED HERE.
AND AS SUCH, ONLY ON BEHALF
OF MOTHER MARY DO I FIGHT.
- WHO'S THIS MOTHER MARY
SHE KEEPS TALKING ABOUT?
- DAMN, YOU!
I DON'T REALLY GIVE A DAMN
WHO MOTHER MARY IS
OR EVEN WHO YOU ARE.
BUT SHE'S NOT GOING TO STOP ME
FROM KICKING YOUR ASS!
- THAT FREAKING IDIOT.
JUST HOW RECKLESS
CAN THAT GIRL GET?
- SOUJIN, COME GIVE ME A HAND.
WE HAVE TO TRY
AND PULL HER OUT.
- RIGHT, I'M ON IT!
- Kentei:
I WILL MAKE YOU PAY.
YOU USURPED ME.
SEIZED FROM ME MY IMPERIAL RANK.
AND TOOK THE NAME EMPEROR WEI.
YOU, MOUTOKU SOUSOU.
- Shibai: AND THEN THERE'S
KOUMEI SHOKATSURYO.
THE DESPICABLE ONE WHO STOOD
IN MY WAY NUMEROUS TIMES.
- REGARDLESS OF HOW GREAT
THE PASSAGE OF TIME MAY BE,
- I REFUSE TO ALLOW
YOU TO COMPLETE
YOUR AMBITIONS IN THIS WORLD.
I WILL SEE THAT YOU FAIL.
- ( both )
THE SOULS OF WARRIORS
WHO SERVED GREAT EMPERORS
AND CLANS
WILL RISE AGAIN SOON
TO DESTROY EVERY LAST FIGHTER
IN THIS WORLD.
LOYAL FOLLOWERS SHALL RETURN
AND WILL JOIN ME
IN MY TRIUMPHANT REIGN OF POWER.
WE WILL PROCEED TO UNLEASH
NEVER-ENDING PAIN AND DESPAIR
TO EVERY ONE OF YOU
WHO STOOD AGAINST ME.
- Bashoku: THE BAMBOO
TUBES WE SCATTERED AROUND
ARE LOADED
WITH POWERFUL EXPLOSIVES.
WHEN LIT, THEY WILL CAUSE
AN INFERNO
THAT WILL BURN AWAY
THE GIANT TREE.
IT LOOKS LIKE
EVERYTHING'S READY TO GO.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO AT THIS POINT,
IS LIGHT IT.
- GOOD.  SADLY, THESE LIVES
WE ARE ABOUT TO TAKE
CAN NEVER BE REBORN.
BUT WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO DESTROY THEM.
- Rikuson
STRATEGIST KOUMEI,
WHILE YOU'RE HERE, WE'RE
GOING TO SEARCH
FOR THE FIGHTERS WHO ARE
BEING HELD PRISONER.
- Koumei PLEASE KEEP
IN MIND THAT THIS PLACE
IS UNDER THE CONTROL OF A FORCE
THAT TRANSCENDS TIME.
SO YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL.
- I DON'T CARE HOW POWERFUL
OR HOW RUTHLESS
KENTEI TRULY IS.
I'LL TELL YOU THIS RIGHT NOW,
HE WON'T TURN NANBAN
INTO A DEN OF MONSTERS.
- Koumei:
VERY SOON THIS PLACE
WILL TURN INTO A SEA OF FLAMES.
YOU MUST HURRY.
- Student 1: WHAT'S GOING ON?
LOOK AT THE CLOUDS!
- Student 2: THAT'S REALLY
SCARY, WHAT IS THAT THING?
- THE DRAGON'S CHI ISN'T
DIMINISHING AT ALL.
IN FACT, IT'S GROWING
MORE POWERFUL!
BE PREPARED, BECAUSE WHEN
GENTOKU'S SPIRIT
IS NO LONGER ABLE TO CONTROL
THE FORCE OF THE DRAGON,
THE TWO OF US WILL HAVE
TO STEP IN AND STOP HER RAMPAGE.
EVEN AT THE COST
OF OUR OWN LIVES.
KAN'U, CHOUHI, CHOU'UN--
YOU ARE CONNECTED
TO THE THREE OF THEM
BY THE UNBREAKABLE BONDS
OF DESTINY.
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO SEE
THEIR BLOODSHED
AND HEAR THEIR CRIES.
GENTOKU RYUUBI'S LIFE
ON THIS EARTH
HAS NOT YET
REACHED ITS END.
PLEASE, HANG IN THERE.
- DAMN.
LOOKS LIKE I'M GETTING
MY BUTT KICKED AGAIN.
WHY?  WHAT IS THE MATTER
WITH ME?
I'M AM EMBARRASSMENT.
A SHAME TO THE NAME
OF EKITOKU CHOUHI.
I DON'T DESERVE THE NAME.
NO, THIS HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THE NAME.
IT HAS TO DO WITH ME!
I'VE GOT TO FIGHT HER
WITH EVERYTHING I HAVE.
I CAN'T LET MYSELF HOLD BACK.
THIS IS MY POWER.
THIS IS MY ART.
WATCH ME, EKITOKU CHOUHI!
HERE, TASTE MY SERPENT SPEAR!
SERPENT SPEAR
LINKED THUNDER STRIKE!
- THIS CAN'T BE.
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE,
FUCKWIT.
- SHIRYUU, DON'T YOU DARE
HOLD BACK ON ME!
- TELL ME WHY.
WHY DO WE HAVE TO KEEP ON
FIGHTING LIKE THIS?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT A FIGHTER IS ANYMORE.
ARE WE ALL JUST DESTINED
TO KEEP ON FIGHTING EACH OTHER?
FIGHT UNTIL WE SUCCUMB
TO OUR FATE, OR PERISH?
STOP THIS ALREADY!
WHAT ON EARTH CAN
POSSIBLY BE GAINED
BY CAUSING ANY MORE
NEEDLESS BLOODSHED?
- LISTEN, RYOMOU.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
IT MAY ALL BE TRUE.
BUT EVEN IF WE ARE DESTINED
TO FIGHT UNTIL WE
DESTROY EACH OTHER,
YOU MUST NOT BE AFRAID TO KEEP
ON FIGHTING FOR OUR FUTURE.
ALL OF US FIGHTING
RIGHT HERE AND NOW,
THIS IS WHAT WILL BUILD
OUR FUTURE.
FOR THE PEOPLE
WHO BELIEVE IN US.
FOR ALL THE LIVES
WE HOLD MOST DEAR.
WE MUST FIGHT
TO DEFEAT OUR DESTINY.
- ( screams )
- Chou'un
MAYBE I'M WRONG.
MAYBE ALL OF US ARE NOTHING
BUT PAWNS OF THE SACRED BEADS.
AS SAD AS IT IS,
PERHAPS US KILLING EACH OTHER
IS INEVITABLE.
YET THROUGH IT ALL,
I STILL WANT TO BELIEVE IN US.
THAT WE ALL GREW
TO LOVE EACH OTHER
OF OUR OWN FREE WILL.
TRY TO REMEMBER, KAN'U.
TRY TO REMEMBER YOUR FEELINGS
FOR OUR LEADER.
JUST ONCE MORE!
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER HER, KAN'U!
PLEASE!
- A FORCE FIELD!
IS THAT FROM THEIR CHI?
THEIR INCREDIBLE CHI
CREATED A FORCE FIELD!
IT'S UNREAL!
- Soujin:
OH, YOU'VE FINALLY COME TO.
SHE WAS BURIED UNDER THE RUBBLE.
TRYING TO PROTECT YOU.
- Kyocho: I TRIED CALLING
OUT TO HER MANY TIMES.
BUT SHE STILL
REMAINED UNCONSCIOUS.
- Koukin:
HAKUFU.
- Koukin: IT CHANGES COLOR
THE MORE FIGHTERS YOU DEFEAT.
- Hakufu: DOES THAT MEAN THAT
YOU'RE STRONGER THAN I AM,
KOUKIN?
- Hakufu:
HOW DARE YOU?
HOW DARE YOU
DO THIS TO KOUKIN?
YOU BASTARD!
SOUSOU, GET READY TO LOSE!
WOW, THOSE PEOPLE
WERE REALLY UNLUCKY.
THAT SOUNDS AWFUL.
KOUKIN AND I HAVE KNOWN
EACH OTHER SINCE WE WERE KIDS.
AND NOW WE BOTH LIVE TOGETHER
IN THE SAME HOUSE.
WHEN WE WERE LITTLE,
HE USED TO GET PICKED ON.
HE WOULD CRY
AND THEN I WOULD HAVE
TO RESCUE HIM.
SURE, BACHIN FOR BACHOU.
WHAT SHOULD BE MY FIRST ORDER...
AN EYE FOR AN EYE, A TOOTH
FOR A TOOTH, A HEAD FOR A HEAD.
THAT'S HOW IT'S DONE!
SO MUCH FUN BEING MASTER
AND SLAVE.
GOING UP AGAINST A REALLY STRONG
OPPONENT MAKES YOU BETTER.
YOU GAIN EXPERIENCE
AND GROW STRONGER.
- ( laughing )
LET'S DO THIS!
YOU GOT ME ALL FIRED UP.
- Bachou:
YOU'RE HER BOYFRIEND AND ALL.
ACT LIKE IT AND PROTECT HER.
- Hakufu:
KOUKIN!
- WHAT ARE YOU--
- YOU NEED TO HOLD HER.
SO THAT SHE KNOWS YOU'RE HERE.
- Kyocho:
MR. MOU, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- I DIDN'T REALIZE UNTIL NOW.
I WAS HOLDING IT ALL THIS TIME.
- Ryomou:
YES.
I ACTED LIKE I DIDN'T CARE.
BUT I WAS AFRAID.
JUST AS RYOFU WAS.
I WAS AFRAID OF MY DESTINY
AS A FIGHTER.
AND OF MY OWN FUTURE.
BUT RYOFU AND SAJI
FOUGHT THEIR FATE.
AND CHOSE THEIR OWN DESTINIES.
WHAT THEY DID WAS LIVE
THEIR LIVES AS FIGHTERS
TO THE FULLEST!
UNCHO KAN'U
OF 1800 YEARS AGO,
IF THE DRAGON
IN MY LEFT EYE
IS YOUR BITTER GRUDGE
AGAINST ME AS A FIGHTER,
I WILL RETURN IT
AND YOUR DESPICABLE CURSE.
HERE AND NOW!
SAJI, RYOFU, PLEASE HELP ME!
HELP ME TO DESTROY
THE DESTINY OF THE SACRED BEAD!
HEAVEN AND EARTH,
WHITE WAVE SHOCK!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Rikuson: WHEN YOUR LEADER'S
SUCH A SCATTERBRAIN,
THERE'S NO END
TO A TACTICIAN'S PROBLEMS.
- Koumei: YOU CAN'T JUDGE
A BOOK BY ITS COVER.
GENTOKU IS
USUALLY VERY GENTLE.
BUT WHEN
SHE LOSES IT,
SHE'S
UNCONTROLLABLE.
- Rikuson: PLEASE TELL ME
THAT SOMEWHERE OUT THERE
THERE'S A
CONSUMMATE LEADER
WHO'S STRONG, GENTLE,
SMART, AND PROPER.
- Koumei:
NO.
NEXT TIME ON "IKKI
TOUSEN XTREME XECUTOR,"
"FIERY CASTLE."
- Rikuson:
GUESS IT'S TOO MUCH TO ASK.