- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( phone ringing )
- HI, SAJI?
UH, DO YOU HAVE A MINUTE
TO TALK TO ME?
- Housen:
SORRY?
- A WOMAN'S VOICE?
SORRY, I MUST HAVE
DIALED WRONG.
I THOUGHT
THIS WAS SAJI'S NUMBER.
- WHO'S CALLING?
HE'S NOT HERE.
OR TO PUT IT ANOTHER WAY,
HE LEFT WHILE I WAS
STILL ASLEEP.
BY ANY CHANCE,
ARE YOU THE GIRL I SAW BEFORE?
THE ONE WHO ALMOST GOT
A PIPE TO THE BACK OF THE HEAD.
MOU-CHAN WAS IT?
- EXCUSE ME?
- SAJI WAS COMPLAINING
ABOUT YOU BEFORE WE WENT TO BED.
HE CALLED YOU CARELESS, SAID YOU
COULDN'T FINISH A FIGHT.
- ( phone hangs up )
- OH.
- YOU'RE AN ASS, SAJI.
HOW COULD MAKE FUN OF ME
LIKE THAT?
- ( phone ringing )
- IDIOT.
- Saji:
A LITTLE TOO CARELESS,
JUST LIKE ALWAYS,
EH, MOU-CHAN?
HERE, YOU CAN HAVE THE REST.
I'LL TAKE OVER FROM HERE.
CLEANING UP
IS A MAN'S JOB.
- WAIT, SAJI!
THAT WAS HER.
- WHAT'S THIS?
HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN OUT HERE WAITING?
- IT WAS YOU ON THE PHONE,
WHY DID YOU COME OUT HERE?
- GUESS, WHY DO YOU THINK?
HERE.
YOU'RE IN LOVE.
YOU LOVE SAJI.
- WHAT?!
I DON'T LOVE HIM.
HE'S A JERK.
- YOU'RE SO OBVIOUS.
BUT, I WAS JUST FOLLOWING ORDERS
TO KEEP SAJI
UNDER SURVEILLANCE.
AND I ENDED UP FALLING FOR HIM.
SO WHO AM I TO JUDGE
HOW YOU FEEL?
- SURVEILLANCE?
WHAT'S THAT FOR?
- YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW,
YOU HAVE NO CLUE
WHO THE MAN YOU LOVE REALLY IS.
A MEETING IS BEING HELD TODAY
AT YOSHU ACADEMY TO FORM
AN ANTI-TOTAKU ALLIANCE.
KAKU OF RAKUYO HIGH SCHOOL
IS SCHEMING TO PREVENT
THAT FROM HAPPENING.
BUT SHE'S NOT THE MASTERMIND
BEHIND THE CURTAIN
WHO'S SECRETLY PULLING
ALL THE STRINGS.
- IT SHOULD BE
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
- ( people running )
- WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( screaming )
- Kentei: AN 1800 YEAR OLD
VENDETTA MANIFESTED AS A DRAGON.
IT ENTERED RYOMOU
AND SETTLED BEHIND HER LEFT EYE.
THE DRAGON MAY NOT HAVE
KILLED HER IMMEDIATELY
BUT IT IS MERELY DORMANT.
ONE DAY IT WILL BURST OUT
FROM WITHIN HER,
AND RYOMOU WILL DIE
IN A RAIN OF HER OWN BLOOD.
JUST AS HER FOREBEAR DID.
- I REMEMBER.
I FELT A THROBBING PAIN
INSIDE MY LEFT EYE THAT DAY.
AND EVERY DAY SINCE!
AND ALL BECAUSE OF KAN'U!
- Yougai:
THIS FRIGGIN' SUCKS.
I CAN'T TAKE IT, HOW LONG
ARE THEY GOING TO KEEP US
COOPED UP?
- JUST CALM DOWN.
WE'LL BE RELEASED
ONCE THE SOUTHERN SCHOOLS
REACH AN AGREEMENT.
THEY'LL SURRENDER TO NANBAN
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
BUT THOSE GUYS, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO THEM.
KYOSHO, SEITO, AND NANYO
ARE THE THREE SCHOOLS
THAT CONTROL KANTO. THEY'VE
FOUGHT SOME SERIOUS BATTLES
FOR THE POWER THEY HAVE,
THEY WON'T JUST SUBMIT.
- I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE ALSO HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING ON
BEHIND THE SCENES.
THERE COULD BE SECRET ALLIANCES.
- HUH?
HEY, WAIT.
JUST WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- Yougai:
I DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
I WAS JUST THINKING OUT LOUD.
- IF THERE WERE A CONNECTION,
WE WOULDN'T BE HERE NOW,
WOULD WE?
- A CONNECTION?
THAT GIRL WHO WAS
WITH THE NANBAN FIGHTERS
WHEN THEY ATTACKED US
ON THE SHIP--
I'M PRETTY SURE
SHE'S THE ARCHER TEN'I.
FROM KYOSHO.
- COME TO THINK OF IT,
I THOUGHT SHE LOOKED
SOMEWHAT FAMILIAR.
HUH?
HEY, I HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT!
I'M A PRISONER
JUST LIKE YOU GUYS!
- THEN EXPLAIN ABOUT THE GIRL.
- Soujin: SHE'S NOT
REALLY A KYOSHO FIGHTER.
ACTUALLY, SHE NEVER WAS.
SHE DIDN'T ANSWER TO SOUSOU.
SHE WAS A LACKEY
OF OUR OLD STRATEGIST, SHIBAI.
- Koukin:
CHUUTATSU SHIBAI.
FORMER STRATEGIST
OF KYOSHO ACADEMY.
DURING THE BATTLE OF RED CLIFFS
SHE FOUGHT KAN'U
AND WAS DEFEATED. THEN SHE
DISAPPEARED. DIDN'T SHE?
IS IT POSSIBLE
SHE COULD BE KENTEI?
- ANYWAY, WE SHOULD BE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET OUT OF HERE.
WE COULD PLAY DEAD.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
GOT ANY GOOD IDEAS?
- HM... HEY, I KNOW!
- JUST GREAT!
YOU COMPLETELY KNOCKED
THE GUY OUT COLD.
NOW WE CAN'T GET
ANY INFO FROM HIM
ABOUT WHERE KOUKIN
AND THE OTHERS ARE!
- I'M SORRY, I THOUGHT
HE HAD FIGURED IT OUT
SO I KICKED REALLY HARD.
- I MADE THE DISGUISE PERFECTLY.
NO ONE CAN TELL.
- Bachou:
MASTER!
IT LOOKS LIKE THERE ARE STAIRS
UP AHEAD OF US.
- WHAT?  YOU MEAN THERE'S
NO ESCALATOR?
- YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
IT'S JUST A FEW STAIRS.
- BACHIN, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- THIS LOOKS LIKE
JUST A STOREROOM, NO ONE'S HERE.
OH, WAIT!
I SEE ANOTHER ROOM IN THE BACK.
THAT BELONGS TO KAN'U.
- NOW, BACHIN!
- ( fighting )
- I CAN RETURN THIS TO KAN'U.
- Hakufu:
THIS IS TERRIBLE, BACHIN!
YOU KNOCKED THEM UNCONSCIOUS
THIS TIME, TOO.
- MASTER, AMBUSHING THEM
FROM ABOVE WAS YOUR IDEA.
PLUS, YOUR GUY'S
ALSO OUT COLD.
- FOCUS, DON'T OVERDO IT
THIS TIME.
- NO PROBLEM.
HEY, SOMEONE'S COMING.
OH, WOW.
HE SEEMS AWFULLY BIG.
- Hakufu: GOOD,
HOPEFULLY HE WON'T GO DOWN
FOR THE COUNT SO EASILY.
- WAIT, MASTER!
- 'KAY, SO THIS IS
YOUR FRIEND, THEN?
- YES, MASTER.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
- IN THAT CASE, THAT MAKES
YOU AND ME FRIENDS, TOO.
NICE TO MEET YOU!
- I'M KYOCHO.
- Bachou: HANG ON A SEC,
SOMETHING JUST OCCURRED TO ME.
KYOCHO'S FRIEND
AND GOLDFISH POOP
ARE PROBABLY IN THE SAME PLACE.
- THAT MAKES SENSE,
BUT WHERE ARE THEY?
WE THINK THEY'RE
SOMEWHERE TOGETHER,
BUT HOW DO WE FIGURE OUT
WHERE THAT PLACE IS?
HM...
- MASTER!
I HEARD SOMETHING ONCE ABOUT
FIGHTERS WITH SHARED FATES.
THEIR SACRED BEADS CAN CONNECT
THEM TO ONE ANOTHER.
WHAT IF YOU USE THE POWER
OF THE SACRED BEAD
TO TRY AND FIND GOLDFISH POOP?
- GREAT IDEA, I'LL TRY THAT!
'KAY, HERE IT GOES.
- ( humming )
- ( humming continues )
- Hakufu:
I SENSE SOMETHING!
- DID YOU FIGURE OUT
WHERE THEY ARE?!
- OVER THERE...
IT SMELLS LIKE CURRY!
- GREAT.
- I'M HUNGRY.
GIRL'S GOT TO EAT, RIGHT?
- YOU'RE RIGHT!
- IT SURE DOES SMELL DELICIOUS.
- HOW'S FOOD GOING TO HELP US
FIND KOUKIN AND THE OTHERS?
- EVERYONE'S GOT TO EAT.
THAT'S A FACT.
SO NANBAN HAS TO FEED
THEIR PRISONERS.
- NICE THINKING, BACHIN!
- YOU READY?
JUST LIKE WE ALL PLANNED IT.
- Soujin:
OW-WW!  IT HURTS!
IT HURTS SO MUCH!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU, SOUJIN?
- OH, MY STOMACH!
- IT SOUNDS LIKE THEY ALL
HAVE FOOD POISONING.
HEY, YOU MORONS, DO SOMETHING!
- Koukin:
DO YOU HAVE ANY MEDICINE?
THEY'RE REALLY SICK,
THEY COULD DIE!
- GET 'EM!
- ( screams )
- I FOUND KOUKIN!
- HAKUFU?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- Bachou:
AND MOUKI BACHOU, I'M HERE, TOO!
- YOU'RE NOT DEAD!
WAY TO STAY ALIVE, BACHOU!
- THANK YOU, GLAD TO SEE
YOU'RE ALIVE TOO, CHOUHI.
- Kyocho:
ARE YOU ALRIGHT, SOUJIN?
- Soujin:
WELL, SORT OF.
- Koukin:
THANKS FOR SAVING US, HAKUFU.
- SURE, ANYTIME.
- Yougai: OKAY, WE HELPED YOU
ESCAPE. NOW YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
- Shuhou:
SEE YOU.
- THEY COULD HAVE
AT LEAST STAYED FOR THE MEAL.
- Ekitoku: I SEE, SO GENTOKU'S
DRAGON HAS BEEN AWAKENED AGAIN.
- YES IT HAS.
MASTER SUIKYOU SAYS SHE'S SICK.
KAN'U MAY BE HER ONLY HOPE.
BY THE WAY, WHERE IS SHE?
- I'M NOT SURE.
I SENSE SOMETHING BAD. SHE'S
DEFINITELY IN SOME TROUBLE.
- WE THINK SHE MIGHT BE FIGHTING
NO HOLDS BARRED WITH RYOMOU.
- YOU MEAN, TO THE DEATH?
BUT THEY'RE FRIENDS,
WHY WOULD THEY FIGHT LIKE THAT?
- Soujin:
I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT THOSE TWO
HAVE BAD KARMA BETWEEN THEM.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
THIS PLACE IS WAY TOO BIG
TO SEARCH EVERYWHERE.
- I WANTED TO RETURN THIS
BACK TO KAN'U.
BUT HOW WILL WE FIND HER?
- HOLD ON A SEC, IS THAT
WHAT I THINK IT IS?
- I FOUND IT ON THE WALL
IN THE STOREROOM.
- Ekitoku:
THE GREEN DRAGON BLADE.
I CAN HEAR IT,
THIS BLADE IS CRYING OUT
TO BE RETURNED TO KAN'U.
- Mouyuu: WE'RE JUST ABOUT
AT THE CENTER OF THE BASEMENT.
- WHAT IS THAT THING?
IT'S ENORMOUS.
- IT'S WHAT ALL THE ROOTS
THAT ARE GROWING
ALL OVER THESE CATACOMBS
SEEM TO BE FEEDING.
- Bashoku:
IS THIS REALLY NANBAN HIGH?
- Mouyuu:
GOOD QUESTION.
I'VE BEEN WONDERING THAT MYSELF.
- THIS ISN'T
JUST A GIGANTIC TREE.
- Bashoku: MISS KOUMEI, WHAT
ARE THESE STRINGS OF BULBS?
- Koumei:
THIS IS...
- Chou'un:
STRATEGIST, TELL US
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- Koumei:
SOMETHING UNSPEAKABLY EVIL.
DARK SOUL RESURRECTION.
- Chou'un:
WHAT IS THAT?  IS IT A SPELL?
- Rikuson:
MORE LIKE ALCHEMY.
IT'S A SCIENTIFIC METHOD
FOR RAISING THE DEAD.
- Koumei:
IT'S A TABOO PRACTICE
THAT HAS NONETHELESS
BEEN ATTEMPTED MORE THAN ONCE
SINCE ANCIENT TIMES.
IT IS A GHASTLY
AND DEPLORABLE METHOD
OF RESTORING LIFE
TO THE DECEASED.
HOST BODIES ARE GROWN
ARTIFICIALLY
TO ACCOMMODATE WANDERING SOULS
THAT MAY BE BITTER OR VENGEFUL.
THE ONLY WAY
FOR THESE GRUESOME CREATIONS
TO FULLY MATURE IS TO SPILL
BLOOD OF FIGHTERS
AND FEED IT TO THEM.
THIS IS THE HORROR
THAT WAS KENTEI'S TRUE PLAN.
- Rikuson:
SO THOSE GLOWING PODS
ARE ALIVE?
- Mouyuu: NANBAN HIGH SCHOOL
HAS BECOME A DEN OF MONSTERS.
- Ryomou:
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
IT'S EITHER KILL
OR BE KILLED!
- MY SACRED BEAD IS PULSING
WITH ENERGY.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE
I CAN HEAR SOMETHING.
THERE'S NO MISTAKING IT,
WHAT I'M HEARING
IS DEFINITELY A FIGHT.
- Kan'u:
RYOMOU!
- Ryomou:
KAN'U!
- I FEEL HER.
STRATEGIST.
- YES, CHOU'UN,
WHAT'S WRONG?
- THERE IS A FEROCIOUS BATTLE
GOING ON RIGHT ABOVE THIS TREE.
- IS KAN'U THERE?
CAN YOU SENSE HER?
- I BELIEVE SO.
MAY I HAVE YOUR PERMISSION
TO GO INVESTIGATE?
- Soujin:
WHAT HAPPENED TO THOSE TWO?
THEY BOTH LOOK DEAD.
- Hakufu:
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- Soujin: IT'S A TRAP!
THE NANBAN GUYS
WERE WAITING FOR US!
- I DIDN'T EXPECT
NANYO'S LEADER
TO COME RESCUE
HER FIGHTERS PERSONALLY.
YOU'VE SAVED ME THE TROUBLE
OF HAVING TO HUNT YOU DOWN.
- THAT'S THE MAN I SAW BEFORE!
- WHICH MEANS YOU MUST BE...
- YOU'RE KENTEI!
- YEAH, THAT GUY!
- CORRECT.
I AM UNEQUIVOCALLY
THE ONE AND ONLY
TRUE BEARER OF THE TITLE
KENTEI EMPEROR
OF THE LATER HAN.
- Koukin:
BUT IF YOU REALLY ARE KENTEI,
WHY BOTHER PRETENDING
THIS WAS A TOURNAMENT?
YOU COULD HAVE JUST AS EASILY
ISSUED AN IMPERIAL ORDER
FOR US TO COME
AND PAY HOMAGE TO YOU.
- FIGHTERS ARE SIMPLE
AND STUPID.
YOU KNOW NOTHING EXCEPT
THE INSTINCT TO FIGHT.
I REQUIRE THIS PRIMAL ENERGY
TO FULFILL MY MASTER PLAN.
AND RIGHT NOW, KAN'U
AND RYOMOU ARE SUPPLYING IT.
- YOU EVIL MONSTER!
- WHAT HAVE YOU DONE WITH KAN'U?
- Kentei: SHE AND RYOMOU
ARE FIGHTING IT OUT.
SETTLING AN ANCIENT BLOOD FEUD
IN THE ARENA BELOW US.
THEY'RE FIGHTING TO THE DEATH.
IT WILL BE OVER SOON.
- NEVER!  WE'LL STOP YOU.
THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE
GOING TO LET THEM DIE.
- IT'S TOO LATE.
BESIDES, IN A FEW MINUTES
YOU'LL ALL BE DEAD, TOO.
EVERY NANBAN FIGHTER
IS HERE TO MAKE SURE OF IT.
YOU CAN'T DEFEAT ALL OF THEM.
BUT YOU'RE WELCOME TO TRY.
- NO!  WE DON'T HAVE THE TIME.
- SO MANY OF THEM,
DEFINITELY MORE THAN A HUNDRED.
- HEY, CHOUHI!
- WHAT IS IT?
- Bachou: HERE!
HURRY, GO FIND KAN'U.
THESE PATHETIC NANBAN MORONS
ARE ALL MINE.
- HANG ON,
DON'T GO HOGGING THEM ALL.
KENTEI MESSED WITH US TOO.
AND I'M MAD AS HELL.
HE WANTS A FIGHT, HE'LL GET ONE!
I'M GOING TO KICK SOME ASS
AND THEN SOME!
- LET'S DO THIS!
YOU GOT ME ALL FIRED UP!
ONE!
- AND TWO!
- THAT'S THREE!
- Bachou: CHOUHI!
WHEN YOU GIVE THAT TO KAN'U,
PLEASE TELL HER I SAID HI.
- THANKS BACHOU, I WILL.
- KAN'U...
- WHAT'S ALL THE BIG RUSH,
SPEED RACER?
YOU REALIZE THEY'RE BOTH
PROBABLY DEAD ALREADY, RIGHT?
- OUT OF THE WAY,
I HAVE TO SAVE MY FRIEND!
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS!
- DON'T GET YOUR PANTIES
IN A BUNCH.
FRIENDS, FAMILY, NONE OF IT
REALLY MATTERS IN THE END.
WHEN PUSH COMES TO SHOVE
AND IT'S ALL ON THE LINE,
YOUR OWN LIFE'S THE ONE
YOU'RE GOING TO SAVE.
- YOU BITCH.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I PITY YOU.
- PITY ME?
- YOU OBVIOUSLY DON'T LOVE
OR TRUST ANYONE.
IF YOU DID, YOU'D UNDERSTAND
HOW I FEEL.
FOR KAN'U AND FOR THE ONES
I LOVE,
I WOULD GLADLY PUT MY LIFE
ON THE LINE.
- THAT'S ALL BULLSHIT!
FUCK YOU!
- PATHETIC BITCH!
- WHAT THE HELL?!
- HANG ON, KAN'U.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
I'LL BRING
YOUR GREEN DRAGON BLADE,
I SWEAR.
BUT BEFORE THAT, I'M GOING
TO KICK SOME SERIOUS NANBAN ASS!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Soujin: I'M SICK
OF THIS ALREADY.
WHEN DO WE GET TO GO HOME?
- Kyocho:
NO IDEA.
I DON'T KNOW ANY
MORE THAN YOU DO.
- THERE'S
NO TV HERE.
I MISSED MY SOAPS THIS WEEK.
NOW I'LL BE BEHIND
ON THE STORIES.
- I THINK STAYING ALIVE
IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN KEEPING UP ON YOUR
FAVORITE SOAP OPERAS.
WATCH OUT, IT'S COMING
AT YOU. - UH-OH!
NEXT TIME ON "IKKI TOUSEN
XTREME XECUTOR--"
"SHREDDED
DARKNESS."
COULD SOMEONE MAYBE RECORD
THIS WEEK'S SOAPS FOR ME,
PLEASE?