- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( Goei laughing )
I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN THAT
YOU WERE MY IDIOT DAUGHTER,
BUT I NEVER KNEW TILL NOW
HOW DOWNRIGHT STUPID YOU WERE.
- OKAY, NOW ISN'T THAT
A BIT TOO HARSH?
- Goei: SO YOU LEFT THE HOUSE
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING
AND BOARDED THE TRAIN.
YOU THEN WENT AND FELL ASLEEP
ON THE YAMANOTE LINE
AND JUST KEPT RIDING
IN CIRCLES UNTIL
YOU WOKE UP.
SERIOUSLY, HOW DEVASTATINGLY
STUPID CAN YOU GET?
- OKAY, I GET IT!
THAT'S ENOUGH.
- YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD
CONSIDER YOURSELF FORTUNATE
THAT KOUKIN WAS ABLE
TO TAKE YOUR PLACE
AT THE BIG FIGHTER'S
TOURNAMENT.
- WHAT?  BUT IT'S NO GOOD
IF KOUKIN FIGHTS.
MOU-CHAN AND I WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE THE ONES
GOING OUT THERE
AND WINNING.
AND AFTER OUR GREAT VICTORY,
WE WERE GOING TO
TURN INTO A HIGH SCHOOL
SINGING AND DANCING
FIGHTER DUO.
AND THEN WE'D MAKE
OUR WORLD DEBUT
AS IDOLS!
- Man: MOU-CHAN!
MOU-CHAN, I LOVE YOU!
( cheering )
- YAY!
AND THEN I COULD FINALLY
SAY GOOD-BYE
TO THE AWFUL OLD HAG I'VE
BEEN STUCK WITH FOR SO LONG
AND LIVE THE GOOD LIFE
IN A LUXURIOUS CONDO--
- WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?!
- ( yelps )
- Goei: HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT
ABOUT YOUR ONE AND ONLY MOTHER?!
- Hakufu: I'M SORRY.
THE TRUTH JUST SLIPPED OUT!
- WHAT?!
- UHH... NO, I WAS KIDDING.
THE TRUTH DIDN'T
SLIP OUT AT ALL.
OH?  WHERE'D THIS COME FROM?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
A POSTCARD JUST CAME
IN THE MAIL FOR YOU.
- AWW. I WONDER HOW
CHUBO'S BEEN DOING LATELY.
- Chubo: "GREETINGS.
WHILE THE SUN CONTINUES
ITS MERCILESS STROKE OF HEAT
ACROSS THE LAND,
I HOPE THAT EVERYONE
HAS BEEN DOING WELL.
GRANDMOTHER, GENPOU, AND I
ARE ALL KEEPING VERY WELL.
EVERY DAY THAT
WE SPEND HERE
IS FULL OF TRANQUILITY.
AND THE DAYS I SPENT
WITH YOU AT NANYO ACADEMY
NOW SEEM LIKE
THE DISTANT PAST,
AS IF THEY WERE
MANY LIFETIMES AGO.
IF YOU HAPPEN TO
FIND THE TIME,
PLEASE CONSIDER
COMING TO VISIT US HERE.
I LOOK FORWARD TO THE DAY
WHEN I CAN SEE YOU,
YOUR MOTHER,
AND KOUKIN AGAIN.
AND I HOPE WITH
ALL MY HEART
THAT DAY WILL BE
VERY SOON.
I HAVE TO GO,
BUT PLEASE CONTINUE
TO TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF
AND ALL YOUR FRIENDS.
SINCERELY,
CHUBO."
- I UNDERSTAND.
WELL, THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR YOUR HELP.
- ( cell phone beeps )
- ( sighs )
- WE SHOULDN'T HAVE
EXPECTED ANY LESS OF HER.
WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE
IT'S THE FIRST TIME
SHE'S DONE SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
- Yougai: YEAH, BUT DO YOU THINK
WE CAN REALLY TRUST THEM?
- HMM?
- WHAT ARE THE CHANCES
THAT THE REAL KENTEI
SENT THE IMPERIAL LETTER?
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
IF HE GOT TOGETHER
WITH THOSE GUYS AT NANBAN,
THEN CHANCES ARE IT MEANS--
- THOSE RABID SISTERS ARE
NO DOUBT BOUND TO SHOW UP,
RIGHT? SO AFTER THEY GO
AND SEVER TIES WITH US,
THEY HAVE THE ARROGANCE
TO SEND A LETTER LIKE THIS.
- IF NOTHING ELSE,
I CAN PAY THEM BACK
FOR PUTTING A SCAR ON THIS
BEAUTIFUL HEAD OF MINE.
- ANYWAY YOU LOOK AT IT,
THIS TOURNAMENT IS STILL
A PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
FOR THE FEDERATION.
- Men: YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT?
- Koukin:
THE SOUTHERN KANTO FEDERATION.
I HEAR THEY HAVEN'T ALLIED
WITH ANY LEADER OR SCHOOL,
BUT HAVE COME TOGETHER FOR
SOVEREIGNTY IN ALL OF KANTO.
AND NOW THAT THERE'S
A THREE-WAY STALEMATE,
JUST AS KOUMEI SHOUKATSURYO
OF THE THREE KINGDOMS
ERA PREDICTED,
THEY'RE BECOMING
A RISING NEW POWER.
REPRESENTING KYOSHO ARE...
KYOCHO CHUUKOU,
A SUPER A-RANK HEAVY HITTER.
SHE REFUSES TO LET ANYONE
NEAR THEIR LEADER SOUSOU.
AND SHIKOU SOUJIN,
A B-RANK OFFENSIVE COMMANDER,
AND LEADER OF
MANY SUBORDINATES.
- ( yawns )
- AND OF COURSE,
SEITO'S REPRESENTATIVES ARE...
KAN'U,
AND HER GOOD FRIEND
CHOUHI.
I WONDER IF THE POWER
OF THE SACRED BEADS
IS TRYING TO CREATE
YET ANOTHER EPIC BATTLE.
SHIMEI RYOMOU DIED
AS A RESULT OF A CURSE
FOR HAVING BEHEADED
UNCHO KAN'U.
SUCH INTERTWINING DESTINIES.
- Ryomou: I FEEL IT.
IT'S FAINT.
BUT I CAN FEEL
THE CHI OF BATTLE
SLOWLY PULLING ME IN.
- Ekitoku: HEY, KAN'U? WHAT'S
UP WITH THE GRIM EXPRESSION
YOU'VE GOT GOING ON THERE?
- HMM?
- YOU'RE ABOUT TO GO
INTO BATTLE, YOU KNOW.
IF YOU DON'T GO IN
COMPLETELY FOCUSED,
YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO GIVE IT YOUR ALL.
- I'M FEELING FINE.
THE LAST TOURNAMENT
I WENT TO,
I HAD NO ONE ELSE
TO DEPEND ON,
BUT THIS TIME
I HAVE YOU WITH ME.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT
AS LONG AS THE TWO OF US
ARE TOGETHER.
YOU AND I ARE BOUND
BY UNBREAKABLE TIES
THAT HAVE US FIGHTING TOGETHER
THROUGHOUT ALL OF OUR LIVES.
- UNBREAKABLE TIES.
AND IF I RECALL CORRECTLY,
WE JUST FOUND ANOTHER ONE
TO ADD TO THE MANY THAT
BIND US TOGETHER, DIDN'T WE?
- OH, YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
THAT LOUDMOUTH BRATTY GIRL,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
I HADN'T SEEN HER IN AWHILE
AND THEN I'D HEARD
SHE'D GONE OVER
FOR SOME SPECIAL TRAINING
WITH SONSAKU
AT NANYO ACADEMY.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU MEAN HAKUFU SONSAKU?
- SHE'S REALLY QUITE
THE SLICK ONE, ISN'T SHE?
- IN THE WORLD OF COMBAT,
THERE ARE NO LIMITS
TO WHAT A PERSON SHOULD DO
IN ORDER TO BECOME
A STRONGER FIGHTER.
SHE MUST HAVE HER REASONS,
AND WE HAVE NO RIGHT
TO JUDGE HER FOR THAT.
- WELL, IN THAT CASE, I'LL BE
SURE TO DECIDE FOR MYSELF
HOW MUCH STRONGER
SHE'S BECOME
THE NEXT TIME I SEE HER.
- ( chuckles )
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
- KYOCHOU?
IT WAS SO EARLY I DIDN'T HAVE
TIME TO EAT THIS MORNING.
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING?
- NO, I DON'T.
- AWW, MAN.
( groans )
HUH?
OH, SO YOU DO HAVE SOMETHING.
- HMM?
- SO IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE HUMAN AFTER ALL.
THANKS FOR THE FOOD.
- HUH?  THAT'S FUNNY.
- Kyochou: SORRY,
BUT THAT FOODS NOT MINE.
- UH--
- HMM?
( screaming )
SO YOU HAVEN'T LEARNED
YOUR LESSON YET, HAVE YOU?
- HA!  DON'T GET THE IDEA
THAT I'M HERE BECAUSE OF YOU.
I CAME TO CHEER
FOR MY MASTER
WHO WILL BE COMPETING
IN THE BIG FIGHTERS TOURNAMENT.
- FOR YOUR MASTER?
- HOLD ONTO YOUR HAT.
MY MASTER IS NONE OTHER THAN
THE LEADER OF NANYO ACADEMY.
THE HAKUFU SONSAKU!
- WHO'S THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WHAT DOES THAT GIRL
THINK SHE'S DOING HERE?
- SONSAKU HAS A DISCIPLE?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- WELL...
WELL, YOU SEE...
IT'S A BIT COMPLICATED.
- OKAY, SO YOU'RE HERE.
BUT I NOTICE THAT YOUR MASTER
IS NOWHERE TO BE SEEN.
SHE'S NOT SWIMMING BEHIND
THE SHIP BY CHANCE, IS SHE?
- WH-- WHY YOU...
- Koukin: UH, BACHOU.
CAN I TALK TO YOU?
- OH, GOLDFISH POOP.
SO WHERE'S MASTER?
- WELL, YOU SEE,
IT'S ABOUT THAT.
- WHAT?! SHE GOT ON
THE YAMANOTE LINE
EARLY IN THE MORNING
AND THEN FELL ASLEEP?
AND WENT AROUND AND AROUND
AND AROUND IN CIRCLES
AND ONLY REALIZED
SHE WAS LATE
AFTER WAKING UP AT NOON?!
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO YELL
IT OUT SO LOUDLY LIKE THAT.
- ( men laughing )
- ( sighs )
- Koutei: I HEARD RUMORS THAT
THE HEAD OF NANYO WAS AN IDIOT,
BUT NEVER THOUGHT
SHE WAS THAT STUPID.
- Yougai: WHO CARES
HOW STRONG YOU ARE
IF YOU'RE TOO MUCH OF
AN IDIOT TO EVEN USE IT?
- Shuhou: WHAT A PERFECT MATCH
THOSE TWO MAKE.
A STUPID MASTER
FOR A STUPID DISCIPLE.
- DON'T YOU...
DARE LAUGH!
I WON'T FORGIVE YOU.
HOW DARE YOU LAUGH AT ME!
- BACHOU.  CHILL.
- HUH?
- YOU WANT TO HAVE IT
OUT HERE, DO YOU?
- YOU BET I DO.
I WON'T JUST STAND BY
WHILE YOU LAUGH
AND SMACK TALK ME AND MY MASTER.
- JUST LET IT GO.
- SHUT UP!
ANYONE WHO STANDS BY
WHILE THEIR MASTER IS INSULTED
IS NOT FIT TO CALL THEMSELVES
A TRUE FIGHTER!
- ( men murmur )
- ( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
- ( groans )
( whimpers )
- HEY.
- NO!
- SHE'S SEASICK?
- ( men laughing )
- WELL, THAT'S NO GOOD.
I GUESS SHE ISN'T ANY
STRONGER AFTER ALL.
- IT SEEMS SHE'S
QUITE A WAYS OFF
BEFORE SHE CAN JOIN THE RANKS OF
THE SEITO FIVE TIGER GENERALS.
- Ekitoku: HEY YOU! WHY DON'T
YOU GET A GRIP ALREADY?
- ( sighs, gags )
- ( chuckles ) SO WHAT DO
YOU WANT TO DO NOW, KYOCHO?
- NOTHING.
IT DOESN'T EVEN
CONCERN ME.
- WELL, OKAY THEN.
- MAN, THAT REALLY
RUINED THE MOMENT.
- OH, WELL.
THAT'S THAT.
- YOU KNOW, WHATEVER.
- SO THAT'S SONSAKU'S
APPRENTICE?
- ( Bachou groans )
- YOU KNOW,
I JUST DON'T LIKE HIM
ONE LITTLE BIT.
- PERHAPS.
BUT HE DOES HAVE
AN UNUSUAL POWER.
- Moukaku: YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT WHEN I LOOK UP
AT HIS UGLY FACE,
HE MAKES ME
WANT TO PUKE.
- SO WHAT'S THE LATEST
ON THE STATUS OF OUR PLANS?
- OF COURSE WE'RE GOING
THROUGH WITH THEM, IDIOT.
AND IT'S NOT BECAUSE
HE TOLD US.
TAKING OVER KANTO WAS SOMETHING
WE'VE ALWAYS BEEN PLANNING.
- I KNOW.
- JUST REMEMBER THAT
TAKING OVER NANBAN HIGH SCHOOL
IS JUST THE FIRST STEP,
GOT IT?
( chuckles )
WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
YOU READY TO DANCE,
FUCKWITS?
- ( girls laughing )
- SO I GUESS HER FATHER
AND HER TEACHERS
WEREN'T ENOUGH FOR HER.
- I HEARD THE GIRL TRIED
TO GET IN WITH SHIBAI AS WELL.
- SHE'S QUITE THE BRAT,
ISN'T SHE?
- LOOK AT YOU.
YOU POOR LITTLE THING.
YOU'RE SOAKING WET.
- YOU'LL CATCH A COLD.
- LET'S STRIP HER.
- ( laughs ) GOOD IDEA.
- Ten'i: STOP.
( gasping )
( grunts )
( panting )
- Shibai: TEN'I!
YOU NEED TO STOP, TEN'I.
YOU'VE DONE QUITE ENOUGH.
- ( screams )
- Shibai:
THERE.  I'VE GOT YOU.
YOU LITTLE TROUBLE MAKER.
- Ten'i: THAT MOMENT,
FROM THAT SECOND,
MY LIFE WAS YOURS,
MOTHER MARY.
NO MATTER THE COST,
I WILL GLADLY
GIVE MY LIFE TO YOU.
- Kentei: REMEMBER MY SOUL
WILL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
BECAUSE OF THAT,
NOBODY IN THIS WORLD
WILL EVER BE ABLE TO
HURT YOU AGAIN.
YOU WILL SOON BE
FULLY REBORN,
LIKE ME.
JUST AS I WAS REBORN.
- ( car horn honks )
- BIG SISTER HAKUFU!
- CHUBO.
( giggles )
IT'S BEEN TOO LONG.
- YOU LOOK JUST AS WELL
AS WHEN I LEFT YOU.
THAT MAKES ME SO HAPPY.
- AND THEN
BEFORE I KNEW IT
SHE BECAME MY DISCIPLE.
- THAT'S A BIG
RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOU.
BUT I'M REALLY GLAD THAT
EVERYONE ELSE IS DOING SO WELL.
- OH, YEAH.  MOM TOLD ME
TO TELL YOU SHE SAYS HI.
YOU KNOW HOW THAT OLD HAG
IS STILL RUNNING AROUND
CHASING AFTER YOUNG STUDS.
- OH? ( giggles )
- AND YET, NO MATTER
HOW IMMATURE SHE ACTS,
SHE STILL CALLS ME
HER STUPID DAUGHTER
EVERY TIME SHE SEES ME.
SHE'S RELENTLESS.
- HMM.
HEY, BIG SISTER?
- HMM?  WHAT'S UP?
- WELL, UH...
IT'S ABOUT--
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT!
CHIBI THE CAT IS GOOD TOO.
- ( meows )
- Chubo: OH, I SEE.
- AND AS FOR KOUKIN...
- YES?
- HE'S AT THE BIG
FIGHTERS TOURNAMENT.
- BIG FIGHTERS TOURNAMENT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WHERE YOU CAN DO BATTLE WITH
A BUNCH OF AWESOME STRONG GUYS.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO GO MYSELF,
BUT THERE WAS A BIT OF A PROBLEM
AND ONE THING LED TO ANOTHER,
AND WELL, YOU KNOW.
( laughs )
HUH?
DID I SAY SOMETHING WRONG,
CHUBO?
- JUST HOW DANGEROUS
OF A POSITION
IS BIG BROTHER KOUKIN
IN RIGHT NOW?
- OH?  OH, DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL BE OKAY.
FOR FIGHTERS LIKE US,
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
ISN'T A BIG DEAL AT ALL.
- I WISH I HAD BEEN RAISED
A FIGHTER LIKE YOU TWO.
IF I HAD BEEN
RAISED A FIGHTER,
NOT ONLY WOULD I BE ABLE
TO SPEND A LOT MORE
OF MY TIME WITH YOU,
BUT I COULD SPEND IT WITH
BIG BROTHER KOUKIN AS WELL.
( sighs )
- CHUBO!
I TOLD YOU.
DID YOU FORGET ALREADY
THAT YOU'RE MY DARLING
LITTLE SISTER
WHENEVER AND WHEREVER
EITHER OF US ARE.
- BIG SISTER HAKUFU.
- EVEN WHEN WE'RE
NOT TOGETHER, WE ARE.
I KNOW KOUKIN FEELS
THE SAME WAY TOO.
EVEN WHEN WE'RE NOT TOGETHER,
WE'RE ALL STILL
TOGETHER IN SPIRIT.
- YES.
- OKAY, NOW IT'S TIME
TO PLAY HARD!
- OH, BIG SISTER.
- ( sighs )
- Koukin: YOU SEEM LIKE
YOU'RE FEELING BETTER.
- ( sighs )
- I WANTED TO COME
AND THANK YOU FOR
STANDING FOR HAKUFU BEFORE.
- OH, LOOK.
IT'S THE GOLDFISH POOP.
DAMN IT.  IF I DIDN'T
GET SEASICK LIKE THIS,
I'D NEVER LET THOSE
STUPID JERKS GET AWAY WITH IT.
- ( sighs )
- SAY, KYOCHO,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THE CHANCES ARE
THAT SHE'S GOING TO BE IN
THE BIG FIGHTERS TOURNAMENT?
- DON'T KNOW.
- OH, YEAH.
WASN'T SHE SAYING ABOUT
MOUTOKU BEING AN ENEMY
OR SOMETHING?
CAN YOU THINK OF ANY
REASON WHY THAT IS?
- ( sighs )
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT STILL...
WHOEVER IT IS,
I REFUSE TO JUST STAND BY
AND LET THEM KILL MR. MOU.
- Kan'u: EKITOKU.
- Ekitoku: YEAH?
WHAT IS IT, KAN'U?
- DO YOU NOT FEEL IT?
THERE'S AN EVIL ENERGY.
- EVIL ENERGY?
- All: HUH?
- WHY DID THE SHIP JUST STOP?
- HUH?
- WHERE'D ALL THIS
FOG COME FROM?
- ( water splashes )
- ( gasping )
- Shuhou: SOMEBODY JUST
JUMPED OVERBOARD.
- HEY, RYOMOU.
- SHUYUU, STAY ON GUARD.
- HUH?
- WE'VE BEEN TRICKED.
THIS IS A TRAP.
- TRY NOT TO FREAK OUT,
KYOCHO.
( squeals, sighs )
- YOU MAY WANT TO
WATCH YOUR STEP.
- Kan'u: THE MALEVOLENCE...
IS GETTING CLOSER.
- ( grunts )
YOU...
WHICH SCHOOL
ARE YOU WITH?
( screams )
- I WONDER IF KAN'U AND ALL
THE OTHERS ARE DOING OKAY.
EVEN THOUGH ALL THREE OF US
MADE THE OATH OF THE
PEACH GARDEN ON THAT DAY,
IT SEEMS LIKE I'M
THE ONE LEFT BEHIND
WHEN THEY GO OFF AND FIGHT.
- ( door opens )
- HUH?
- MAY I HAVE THE NOBLE HONOR
OF JOINING YOU IN THE BATH?
- Ryuubi: SHIRYU?
YOU BROUGHT YOUR SWORD?
EVEN IN THE BATH?
( sighs )
- EXCUSE ME.
I FEEL ALIVE.
- UH, HEY...
UM, SHIRYU?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT THOSE TWO.
I PROMISE YOU THAT
THEY WILL BE JUST FINE.
- YEAH, BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE TOURNAMENT?
WASN'T KOUMEI SAYING THAT
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS TOURNAMENT
SEEMED REALLY SUSPICIOUS?
- Shiryu:
ALL THE MORE REASON.
IF THERE ARE SPARKS SHOWERING
SEITO BEHIND THIS TOURNAMENT,
THEN WE MUST DO ALL WE CAN
TO CALMLY BRUSH THEM AWAY.
AND IT'S NOT
JUST THOSE TWO,
BUT EVERY ONE OF YOUR
RETAINERS FEEL THIS WAY.
- ( sighs )
BECAUSE OF THAT...
IT ALWAYS SEEMS TO ME
THAT PEOPLE DO NOTHING BUT GET
THEMSELVES HURT ON MY BEHALF.
IT MAKES ME
SO VERY VERY SAD.
I CAN'T STAND IT.
( crying )
- A LEADER SHOULD NOT
BE PAINED BY SUCH THINGS.
THAT THEIR SUBORDINATES' BLOOD
IS SPILLED ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
- HUH?
- KAN'U AND CHOUHI,
AND EVERY WARRIOR OF SEITO,
IF IT'S SOMETHING
THEY RECEIVE AS A RESULT OF
FIGHTING FOR THE ONE
THEY BELIEVE IN...
THEN IT IS A BEAUTIFUL
AND BLISSFUL WOUND.
- BEAUTIFUL? BLISSFUL?
- ( water splashes )
- WHAT IS IT SHIRYU?
- A LARGE RAT.
OR RATHER,
A VICIOUS TIGER.
- ( gasps )
- ARE YOU ATTACKING
KNOWING FULL WELL
THAT THIS IS THE HOME
OF OUR HONORABLE LEADER?
SEITO ACADEMY'S
SECOND YEAR STUDENT,
SHIRYU CHOU'UN
WILL TAKE YOU ON.
- NANBAN HIGH SCHOOL
SECOND YEAR STUDENT MOUYUU.
MY ONLY PURPOSE HERE IS TO TAKE
THE HEAD OF GENTOKU RYUUBI.
( shouts )
( grunts )
- Kouchuu:
I'LL BE YOUR OPPONENT AS WELL.
KANCHOU KOUCHUU
IS HERE TO FIGHT.
- ( exhales )
- SHIRYU CHOU'UN,
THIS MATCH WILL BE
CONCLUDED AT A LATER DATE.
- HOLD IT!
- Ryuubi: SHIRYU.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
LEADER?
- ( gasps )
YOUR ARM.
- I SUPPOSE I'VE ADDED TO MY
BEAUTIFUL AND BLISSFUL WOUNDS.
- ( sighs )
( crying )
SHIRYU...
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE'RE GOING TO FIND
ONCE THIS BLANKET
OF FOG IS FINALLY CLEAR?
- HEY, ARE WE GONNA BE OKAY?
- I DON'T KNOW. BUT STOP
BEING SUCH A DAMN COWARD.
- LOOKS LIKE YOU DREW
THE SHORT STRAW
TAKING THE PLACE
OF SONSAKU.
- NO, I HAVEN'T BEEN
THIS EXCITED IN AWHILE.
- IT CAN'T BE.
I REALLY HOPE THIS DIDN'T TURN
FROM A BIG FIGHTERS
TOURNAMENT
INTO SOME HAUNTED
GHOST TOURNAMENT.
- ( Shoujin sneezes )
- ( screams )
( groans )
JEEZ.
- ( sniffles )
IT'S GOTTEN UNUSUALLY COOL, HUH?
- SHH.  STAY ALERT.
THEY'RE COMING.
- ( grunts )
- ( men gasp )
- LOOK AT THAT SPEAR.
IT CAN'T BE!
- ( men gasp )
( gasping )
- ( laughing )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Shiryu:
LEADER, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- Ryuubi: SHIRYU,
OF COURSE I AM. YOU SAVED ME.
- Shiryu: SINCE KAN'U
ISN'T AROUND TO RISK HER LIFE,
I WILL RISK MY LIFE
FOR YOUR SAFETY.
WHILE I HAVEN'T MADE
THE OATH OF THE PEACH GARDEN,
I HAVE DECIDED IN MY HEART
THAT I WILL FOLLOW YOU
TO THE GRAVE.
- Ryuubi: NO WAY.
IN THAT CASE,
WHY DON'T WE
JUST MAKE AN OATH RIGHT NOW.
I'LL CALL IT
"THE OATH OF THE BATH."
NEXT TIME ON
"IKKI TOUSEN XTREME XECUTOR,"
"BONDS OF A SOUL."
IT'S A PROMISE.
- Shiryu: LEADER.