- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ( footsteps )
- ( growling )
- ( gasps )
UNCHO KAN'U,
THERE'S SOMETHING
DIFFERENT ABOUT YOU.
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
WHO ARE YOU?
- WE'RE FRIENDS.
HAVE YOU REALLY FORGOTTEN?
- ( man laughs )
- ( gasps )
- KAN'U HAS LOST HER SIGHT.
SHE CANNOT TELL IF YOU
ARE FRIEND OR FOE.
BUT I SHALL ASSIST HER.
THE PERSON BEFORE YOU
IS YOUR ARCH-ENEMY.
FOLLOW THE DESTINY YOU ARE
BOUND TO FROM THE PAST:
FIGHT!
- ( gasps )
- Kan'u:
I HAVE NOT FORGOTTEN
THE ONE WHO
SET A TRAP FOR ME,
THE ONE WHO SEVERED
MY HEAD.
I MAY DIE BUT MY HATRED
FOR YOU WILL REMAIN
FOR ALL OF ETERNITY!
- WHAT TRAP?
- Man: THE TRAP SET
BY THE ONE
WHOSE DESTINY YOU INHERITED.
THE SACRED BEAD YOU WEAR
CAME WITH EVERYTHING
FROM THAT SOUL'S PAST,
INCLUDING VENDETTAS.
THE TIME HAS COME. OLD SCORES
MUST BE SETTLED HERE AND NOW.
WELCOME COMBATANTS
TO THE BIG FIGHTERS
TOURNAMENT!
- I GET IT NOW.
YOU MUST BE KENTEI.
CALL YOURSELF WHATEVER
THE HELL YOU WANT, I DON'T CARE,
BUT I WON'T FIGHT
LIKE A DOG. I WONT!
( grunts )
- ( screams )
- Kentei: WHAT NOW?
YOU MAY NOT WANT TO FIGHT,
BUT IT APPEARS THAT KAN'U
IS LOOKING FOR ONE.
- Kan'u:
ARE YOU AFRAID, RYOMOU?
- ( scoffs )
- ( engine humming )
- ( waves splashing )
- Chou'un: SHOULDN'T YOU
CONSIDER GETTING SOME SLEEP?
- UH.
THANKS.
BUT I'M ALL RIGHT.
I COULDN'T SLEEP ANYWAY.
MOU-CHAN IS AT NANBAN HIGH
AND KOUKIN WENT IN MY PLACE
AND NOW THEY'RE
IN TERRIBLE DANGER.
WHEN I THINK ABOUT THAT,
THERE'S NO WAY I
COULD GET ANY SLEEP.
AND AFTER HE SENT
THAT BIG NASTY GUY
TO TRY AND TAKE
RYUU-CHAN'S HEAD OFF--
IT'S TOTALLY UNFORGIVEABLE.
HE MUST PAY.
THAT GUY WHAT'S-HIS-FACE?
- YOU MEAN KENTEI?
- RIGHT!
THAT'S THE GUY--
"KENNY G" OR "CHIANTI" OR
WHATEVER THE HECK HIS NAME IS.
WHEN I MEET HIM I'M GONNA
GIVE HIM A PIECE OF MY MIND.
I WILL SAY TO HIM, "YOU LOSER.
PREPARE TO GET YOU BUTT KICKED!"
( laughs )
- ( scoffs )
( chuckles )
I ENVY YOU.
- HM? HOW COME?
- YOU'RE CHEERFUL AND YOU
HAVE A SENSE OF HUMOR,
EVEN WHEN THE SITUATION
IS SO SERIOUS.
- HUH?
- SONSAKU, WILL YOU LEND ME
YOUR JOY AND GOOD HUMOR
AND HELP ME TO SAVE MY LEADER?
- I WILL! HAKUFU SONSAKU
AT YOUR SERVICE!
- STRATEGIST KOUMEI,
WHAT'RE YOUR THOUGHTS?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHO KENTEI IS?
I MEAN HIS ACTUAL IDENTITY.
- STRATEGIST RIKUSON,
MY GUESS IS
HE HATES FIGHTERS.
PERHAPS THIS KENTEI PERSON
HAD A SACRED BEAD OF HIS OWN,
BUT HE DIDN'T LIKE HIS FATE
SO NOW HE'S LASHING OUT.
HE'S MAD. IT'S LIKE HE'S
CURSING EVERY ONE OF US
WHO BEARS A SACRED BEAD
AND HAS A DESTINY TO FULFILL.
THE BIG FIGHTERS TOURNAMENT
WAS A TRAP.
HE JUST WANTED TO LURE KAN'U
AND THE OTHERS TO HIM.
I DON'T THINK HE DID
ALL THIS JUST TO KILL THEM.
CLEARLY HE HAS SOME
ULTERIOR MOTIVE
AND THAT MAKES ME UNEASY.
- ( grunting )
- ( chuckles )
MORE... MORE BLOOD!
I REQUIRE EVERY LAST DROP
YOU SPILL WHILE IN BATTLE.
IT IS NECESSARY IN ORDER
TO ACHIEVE MY OBJECTIVE.
- ( gasping )
- ( roaring )
- WHAT'S THAT VOICE?
( groans )
MY EYE...
IT'S THROBBING!
- ( roars )
- MY GOD. WHAT IS IT?
- Ekitoku: KAN'U, NO!
STOP IT!
- HUH? CHOUHI?
SOMETHING WRONG?
- DON'T FIGHT HER!
YOU CAN'T!
YOU MUSTN'T FIGHT
SHIMEI RYOMOU!
NOT IN THE STATE YOU'RE IN!
- RYOMOU'S NOT HERE.
IS SHE FIGHTING?
- DID YOU NOT HEAR WHAT I SAID?
A DARK EVIL IS ENVELOPING
KAN'U'S FIGHTING SPIRIT
AND IT'S REACTING TO HER.
NOT AGAIN.
IT'S HAPPENING
ALL OVER AGAIN!!
- I STILL FEEL IT.
THE PAIN FROM WHEN YOU SEVERED
MY HEAD FROM MY BODY.
IT NEVER ENDS.
FOR 1800 YEARS I'VE SUFFERED
BECAUSE OF YOU.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
HAS THE SACRED BEAD
TAKEN YOU OVER?
WHERE'S KAN'U'S SOUL?
- AS LONG AS BATTLES
STILL EXIST IN THE WORLD,
MY SOUL WILL REMAIN
DOMINANT!
THIS IS DESTINY! THIS IS
WHAT IT IS TO BE A FIGHTER!
- YOU ARE WRONG!
I'M MORE THAN JUST
MY INHERITED FATE.
IT DOES NOT CONTROL ME!
I AM NANYO FIGHTER
SHIMEI RYOMOU!
- Ekitoku: LET ME OUT!
IT'S A MATTER OF LIFE AND DEATH!
IF I DON'T STOP THEM
THEY'LL DESTROY EACH OTHER!
AND LEVEL HALF THIS PLACE
IN THE PROCESS! ( grunts )
ASSHOLE!
YOU'LL REGRET THAT!
- COOL IT!
TRY TO KEEP CALM!
- DON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID!
- Ekitoku: NO.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
SOMEONE HAS TO STOP
THEM BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
- WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- BACK IN THE ERA OF
THE THREE KINGDOMS...
- ...THOSE TWO
WERE MORTAL ENEMIES.
SHIMEI RYOMOU SET A TRAP
FOR UNCHO KAN'U,
AND ONCE KAN'U WAS CAUGHT
RYOMOU DECAPITATED HIM.
BUT IN DEATH KAN'U
GOT REVENGE,
CURSING AND HAUNTING RYOMOU
UNTIL HE DIED AS WELL.
- Soujin: YUCK.
THAT'S FUCKED UP.
- Koukin: IF CHOUHI'S RIGHT,
IF RYOMOU AND KAN'U
REALLY ARE FIGHTING
NO HOLDS BARRED,
THERE'S NO TELLING HOW MUCH
WORSE THE POWER OF THEIR GRUDGES
IN THEIR SACRED BEADS
COULD MAKE THINGS.
- THAT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE NANBAN.
THAT'S WHY THEY OUSTED
THEIR OLD LEADERSHIP.
THEY'RE NOT CRUEL
AND THEY DON'T FIGHT DIRTY.
THEN AGAIN I HEARD THEY
RECRUITED A NEW STRATEGIST.
SO WHO KNOWS
ANYTHING ANYMORE?
- STRATEGIST?
- Woman: I KNOW YOU.
YOU ARE SHIBAI, ARE YOU NOT?
- ONCE YOU AND I LIVED
AND FOUGHT TOGETHER,
BUT I AM NO LONGER
THAT PERSON.
- ( gasps )
I WILL LIVE FOR YOU,
SERVE YOU.
I WILL GIVE
MY LIFE FOR YOU.
YOU HAVE BUT
TO SAY THE WORD.
I WOULD DO ANYTHING.
PLEASE TRUST ME.
PLEASE SHARE YOUR SECRETS.
PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO SEE YOUR FACE!
- REGRETFULLY
I CANNOT DO THAT.
- ( sighs )
- I HAVE MADE MANY PAINFUL
SACRIFICES INCLUDING MY BODY
IN ORDER TO ACHIEVE
MY DESIRED OBJECTIVE.
THE ONE STANDING BEFORE YOU
IS NOT THE CHUUTATSU SHIBAI
YOU ONCE KNEW.
- THAT'S FINE.
I CAN LIVE WITH THAT.
YOU REMAIN MY ONE,
MY ONLY...
YOU ARE STILL
MY MOTHER MARY.
- WATCH ME, I WILL
RE-MAKE THIS WORLD.
- WHAT YOU THOUGHT POSSIBLE
ONLY IN DREAMS WILL BECOME REAL.
THE FLAMES OF HELL
WILL RAIN DOWN
AND SHALL CONSUME
THE FOOLISH AND UNWORTHY.
WHILE THOSE OF A RIGHTEOUS HEART
WILL BE WELCOMED
THROUGH THE GATES
OF PARADISE.
WE WILL BEAR WITNESS
AS THIS COMES TO PASS.
WHAT RISES
WILL BE A NEW EDEN,
A TRUE KINGDOM
OF GOD ON EARTH.
- Bachou: MAN, HOW DEEP
DOES THIS PLACE GO?
IT'S LIKE A JUNGLE
MADE UP OF ROOTS
INSTEAD OF TREES.
( sighs )
MMM.
THAT DAY,
SHE TOTALLY KICKED MY BUTT.
IT WASN'T EVEN CLOSE.
YET NOW HERE WE ARE
WORKING TOGETHER.
STRANGE HOW THINGS
TURN OUT SOMETIMES.
- HM?
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
- OH.
- UH, CAN I ASK YOU
SOMETHING, KYOCHO?
COULD YOU TELL ME A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT MOUTOKU SOUSOU?
- AH.
- UM... DON'T WORRY.
IT'S NOTHING BAD.
I JUST REALIZED
I KNOW NOTHING ABOUT HIM.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD TELL ME
WHAT HE'S LIKE?
- MR. MOU IS... OF ALL
THE PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD,
HE'S THE ONE
I WANT TO PROTECT.
I WOULD GIVE MY LIFE
TO SAVE HIS.
- YOU WOULD LAY DOWN
YOUR LIFE...
FOR HIM?
- Kansui: LISTEN UP! I'M GONNA
TEACH YOU THE ONE THING
YOU NEED TO KNOW TO GET
OUT OF ANY KIND OF TROUBLE,
NO MATTER HOW BAD IT IS.
- OKAY.
- NEVER FORGET
HOW STRONG YOU REALLY ARE.
- MM-- BUT, BRO,
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- FIGURE IT OUT
FOR YOURSELF.
- DON'T BE A JERK!
C'MON, TELL ME!
- ALL RIGHT THEN,
I'LL GIVE YOU AN EXAMPLE.
SOMEDAY
SOMEONE WILL COME ALONG
YOU'D BE WILLING TO GIVE
YOUR LIFE TO PROTECT
AND YOU'LL BE STRONG ENOUGH
TO PROTECT THEM.
- I THINK I SEE
STAIRS BACK THERE.
- HUH?
- ( both grunt )
- UP AHEAD
I SENSE A FIGHT.
IT'S INTENSE,
AS IF THEIR SPIRITS ARE
DEVOURING EACH OTHER.
- WHAT?!
BUT THAT MEANS...
THE TOURNAMENT'S
STARTED ALREADY.
I HAVE TO HURRY AND GET THERE.
IF I DON'T I MIGHT MISS
MY CHANCE TO COMPETE!
- WAIT A SECOND!
- HOLD ON, KAN'U! I'M COMING.
CHOUHI!
I'M ALMOST THERE!!
( grunts, gasps )
- ( gasps )
YOU'RE THE DOUBLE SWORD FIGHTER
WHO ATTACKED US ON THE SHIP!
- ( gasps )
MOTHER MARY,
LEAVE HER TO ME.
- HEY!
WAIT A SECOND!
- ( both grunting )
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
SHE'S NOTHING,
LITTLE MORE THAN A MOUSE.
THE NANBAN FIGHTERS
CAN TAKE CARE OF HER.
- ( panting )
( yelps )
- ( muffled grunts )
- ( footsteps marching )
- WHEW! LET'S GO!
WE'LL MAKE A RUN FOR IT!
- YOU SHOULD GO HIDE IN THERE.
- ( gasps ) BUT THEN I--
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- I WON'T FIT.
IT'S TOO NARROW.
- WAIT HOLD ON A SECOND.
NO WAY!
NOT AGAIN!
- Koumei: WHERE DOES
THIS PATH LEAD TO?
- Mouyuu: IT GOES
TO NANBAN'S BASEMENT.
THE SCHOOL SITS
ATOP A MOUNTAIN.
IT'S ROCKY AND STEEP.
- SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
CAREFUL.
I SENSE A DARK AND BLOODTHIRSTY
AIR ABOUT THIS PLACE.
- LEADER, UMM...
WHAT IS IT THAT
YOU'RE DOING?
- I'M LEAVING MARKS ON THE PATH
SO WE DON'T GET LOST.
- ( sighs )
OF ALL THE SCHOOLS AND LEADERS
I COULD HAVE BEEN
STRATEGIST FOR,
I GOT STUCK WITH
THE IDIOT AT NANYO.
- Hakufu: HEY, RIKU-CHAN,
WANT ME TO CARRY THAT SWORD?
- Rikuson: SOUSOU ENTRUSTED YOU
WITH THIS VALUABLE WEAPON.
BUT YOU LOSE THINGS.
SO I'LL HOLD ONTO IT FOR NOW.
- Hakufu: WOW!
LOOK AT THAT BUDDHA!
- THAT'S NOT THE ONLY ONE,
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE HERE.
- IN ANCIENT CHINA, GREAT LORDS
AND EMPERORS WOULD BUILD
SIMILAR STONE STATUES OR TEMPLES
NEAR THE WALLS OF THEIR CASTLES.
- COOL! YOU KNOW
A LOT, RIKU-CHAN.
- Koumei: OH.
MOUYUU, CAN YOU TELL US
WHAT THESE ROOTS ARE?
- Hakufu: WHOA! THE PLACE
IS COVERED WITH THEM!
- THERE WEREN'T ROOTS
HERE BEFORE.
- Hakufu: IF THEY'RE
WEEDS OR SOMETHING,
LET'S CLEAR THEM AWAY!
- ( thumps )
- AH... MMM!
HA! WHAT WAS THAT?!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT FELT SO STRANGE.
WHEN I GRABBED IT
I THOUGHT I FELT A PULSE.
- ( faint moaning )
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
- IT'S COMING FROM BACK
WHERE THE THICK ROOTS ARE.
- HAI!
- IT CAN'T BE!
THAT LOOKS LIKE BLOOD.
- UH.
DO YOU RECOGNIZE THEM?
- THEY'RE THE SOUTHERN KANTO
FEDERATION.
- DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE STILL ALIVE?
- NO WAY.
COULD KOUKIN OR MOU-CHAN
HAVE ENDED UP
AS PLANT FOOD
LIKE THOSE GUYS DID?
KOUKIN! MOU-CHAN!
WHERE ARE YOU?
ANSWER ME.
KOUKIN!
- ( gasps )
HAKUFU?
- WHAT IS IT?
- HAKUFU!
( echoing )
- Rikuson: LEADER SONSAKU,
ARE YOU OKAY?
- I THINK I JUST HEARD KOUKIN.
THAT MEANS HE'S ALIVE!
- LOOK BEHIND YOU!
HURRY GET AWAY!
- AAH!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?!
- SONSAKU!
- DON'T! YOU'LL GET
CAUGHT IN IT YOURSELF!
- SHE NEEDS ME!
- Chou'un: HONESTLY,
I DON'T THINK SO.
- REMEMBER SONSAKU DOES
HAVE THE POWER OF A DRAGON.
I'M SURE SHE CAN
HANDLE A FEW PLANTS
WITHOUT GETTING SO
MUCH AS A SCRATCH.
GOING AFTER HER WILL
TAKE TIME WE DON'T HAVE.
SHE CAN TAKE CARE OF HERSELF.
- THIS IS WRONG.
THESE ROOTS ARE
FEEDING SOMETHING.
WE NEED TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S BEYOND THEM.
THERE'S A HIGH PROBABILITY
THAT WHATEVER IT IS
HAS SOME CONNECTION
TO KENTEI.
- Hakufu: STUPID PLANTS!
( panting )
MAN!
I HATE THOSE ROOTS!
I'M GONNA BUST UP
EVERY SINGLE ONE!
I'LL GIVE 'EM A RIGHT JAB
AND A LEFT HOOK AND-- HUH?
WAIT A SEC, WHERE AM I?
- ( rattles )
( beeps )
- ( whimpers )
WHAT IS THAT?
( yelps )
HA!
STOP FOLLOWING ME!
- MASTER!
DON'T RUN AWAY.
IT'S ME!
- I KNOW THAT VOICE.
IT'S YOU, RIGHT?
- YES! YAY!
YOU ACTUALLY REMEMBERED ME!
THANK YOU!
- WHO ARE YOU AGAIN?
- ( groans )
IT'S ME!
YOUR DISCIPLE MOUKI BACHOU!
- OH YEAH... BOCHIN!
- IT'S "BACHIN"!
IT MEANS PIPSQUEAK
AND YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO GAVE ME THE NICKNAME!
- COME TO THINK OF IT, I HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU AROUND LATELY.
WHERE'VE YOU BEEN?
- ARE YOU REALLY THAT DENSE?
I'VE BEEN AT THIS SCHOOL
THE ENTIRE TIME.
I STOWED AWAY ON THE SHIP
TO COME WITH YOU.
BUT ON THE DAY THE BOAT WAS
SUPPOSED TO LEAVE YOU MISSED IT.
WHAT HAPPENED? I HEARD YOU
FELL ASLEEP ON THE TRAIN!
- ( chuckles ) UH YEAH.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
BUT NOW
I'M HERE AND WITH YOU.
- YUP! I CAN'T REMEMBER THE
LAST TIME I WAS SO EXCITED!
- OH, AND ALSO
RYUU-CHAN'S IN BIG TROUBLE.
SHE'S SICK.
- MISS GENTOKU'S SICK?
- THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
AND IT'S ALL THAT WEIRD
HENTAI GUY'S FAULT!
- YOU MEAN KENTEI?
I BET THAT WAS HIM.
- WHAT?
YOU KNOW HIM, BACHIN?
- I THINK I SAW HIM.
HE HAD ON A HOODED CAPE
THAT, LIKE, COVERED HIS HEAD
AND HE WORE A MASK.
ARE YOU LISTENING
TO ME, MASTER?
HUH?
WHA...?
( groans )
- ( hisses )
- ( whimpers )
IT'S A SNAKE!
- ( hissing )
- ( sobbing )
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU, BACHIN?
GET UP AND FIGHT!
- I CAN'T!
I HATE SNAKES.
I'M MORE AFRAID OF THEM
THAN ANYTHING!
- YOU CAN'T BE SCARED!
YOU'VE WORKED TOO HARD
TO GIVE IN TO FEAR!
- EH... WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- FOCUS! REMEMBER THAT
SPECIAL TRAINING WE DID?
- OUR TRAINING?
- "DON'T THINK BUT STILL THINK,"
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
DON'T THINK!
- DON'T THINK ABOUT IT.
THINK ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE!
( grunting )
- ( groans )
HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- IF I STRIKE AN IRON
WHILE IT'S HOT
IT'LL BURN ME!
DON'T BURN BRIDGES!
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO GET HOME!
WHEN YOU CUT FLESH,
YOU MUST ALSO CUT BONE!
- FOCUS YOUR ATTACK AND HIT HIM
WHERE IT HURTS MOST!
- RIGHT!
- ( hisses )
- ( clanks )
- AN EYE FOR AN EYE.
A TOOTH FOR A TOOTH.
AND A KICK IN THE HEAD!
- ALL RIGHT!
SHALL WE GO FINISH THE JOB?
- YOU BET!
LET'S DO IT!
- ( both yelling )
- A ROLLING STONE...
- NEEDS TO GET OUTTA MY WAY!
- RIGHT! TIME TO GO
AND RESCUE EVERYBODY!
- YES, MASTER!
LET'S GO!
- BY THE WAY...
DO YOU KNOW THE WAY OUT?
- OY!
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Bachou: MASTER,
LET'S SLIP PAST
THE GUARDS
AND RESCUE EVERYONE!
- Hakufu:
HUH? HOW?
OUTSIDE THIS ROOM THERE'S
TONS OF ENEMY THUGS
CRAWLING ALL OVER
THE PLACE...
- LEAVE THAT TO ME!
SEE?
I CAN MAKE US A DISGUISE
OUT OF ALL OF THE STUFF
IN THIS TRASH BIN.
- OH! YOU MEAN WE'RE
DOING COSPLAY?
CAN YOU MAKE ME
A SEXY NURSE?
- MASTER! BE SERIOUS!
NEXT TIME ON "IKKI
TOUSEN XTREME XECUTOR":
"ANGRY LOVE."
- YOU'RE RIGHT. I'D
RATHER BE SANTA, ANYWAY!
- MASTER, ARE YOU
REALLY THAT STUPID?