- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Mouyuu: GENTOKU RYUUBI.
- BE HONEST WITH ME.
THIS IS ALL KENTEI'S DOING,
ISN'T IT?
- WITHOUT A DOUBT.
IT'S HIM.
HE CAN CONTROL ANIMALS
USING HIS MIND.
- Ryuubi:
WHAT HAPPENED, KOUMEI?
I'M CONFUSED.
HOW COME I'M HERE NOW?
- GENTOKU, I'M SORRY,
BUT THERE'S NO TIME
TO EXPLAIN ANYTHING.
WE HAVE TO LEAVE HERE
IMMEDIATELY.
- Shiryu: STRATEGIST.
- HUH?
I WILL REMAIN HERE AND KEEP
THAT PACK OF WOLVES AT BAY.
YOU AND KOUCHUU MUST
ESCAPE WITH OUR LEADER
BY FLEEING INTO
THE FOREST.
- ESCAPE?
ARE THE BATTLES
STARTING ALL OVER AGAIN?
I CAN'T RUN AWAY.
I'M THE ONE WHO
SHOULD BE FIGHTING.
- BUT YOU CANNOT.
I KNOW YOU WANT TO HELP,
BUT YOU MUSTN'T USE YOUR POWERS.
IF YOUR DRAGON AWAKENS,
THEN EVERYBODY WILL SUFFER.
- Ryuubi: BUT YOUR LIVES
ARE ALL IN DANGER.
I CAN'T JUST DO NOTHING.
- Mouyuu: I'LL HELP YOU.
I'LL ACCOMPANY YOU AS YOU
ESCAPE THROUGH THE FOREST.
IF WE MEET DAIOU BOKUROKU,
I'LL TELL HIM THE ATTACK
HAS BEEN CALLED OFF.
- WHY SHOULD WE TRUST YOU?
YOU TRIED TO KILL
OUR LEADER.
- YOU SPARED MY LIFE.
I OWE YOU A DEBT.
THIS IS MY CHANCE
TO REPAY IT.
AS A LEADER OF NANBAN
AND A FIGHTER,
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
- ( sighs )
OH, THANK YOU FOR HELPING US.
- LEADER,
PROTECT HER, MOUYUU,
FOR ALL OF OUR SAKES.
KOUCHUU!
- ( gasps )
- TAKE OUR LEADER
AND RUN FOR IT.
MOUYUU, I AM TRUSTING YOU,
ONE FIGHTER TO ANOTHER.
- ( wolves growl )
- ( gasps )
WAIT!  HOLD UP.
- THEY'RE GONE.
SOMETHING HIT ME
AND MY GLASSES FELL OFF.
- Kouchuu: LEADER,
DO YOU REMEMBER ABOUT
WHERE YOU LOST THEM?
- Ryuubi: UM, SOMEWHERE
BACK IN THE TREES I THINK.
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
- Kentei: WELL DONE, MOUYUU.
- ( all gasp )
- I WILL FORGIVE YOU FOR HAVING
PREVIOUSLY FAILED ME TWICE.
- WHAT IS THAT?
IS IT A GHOST?
- NO.  I THINK IT'S KENTEI.
- Kentei:
NOW TAKE RYUUBI'S HEAD.
DO IT.  THEN YOU WILL HAVE
CONQUERED KANTO FOR NANBAN HIGH.
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE.
TAKE IT.
BATHE IN THE LIMELIGHT
OF GLORY AND CONQUEST.
- SAY SOMETHING, MOUYUU.
- YOU LIED TO US.
YOU LED US INTO A TRAP.
- KOUMEI,
SHE GAVE US HER WORD.
SHE SWORE AS A FIGHTER AND AS
A LEADER OF A RIVAL HIGH SCHOOL.
SHE DIDN'T LIE.
I TRUST HER.
- Kentei: HOW NAIVE.
- ( gasps )
- Kentei: IN THE TIME
OF THE THREE KINGDOMS
1800 YEARS AGO,
MANY FORMIDABLE WARRIORS
UNITED TO SERVE UNDER
GENTOKU RYUUBI,
BUT IN THE END
THEY ALL FELL.
ALL OF IT WAS FOR NOTHING.
SURELY YOU HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
WHO ACTUALLY ENDED UP
WINNING IN THE END?
- IT CAN'T BE.
- WHAT USE IS A HUMAN HEART
TO A FIGHTER?
ALL A FIGHTER NEEDS TO TRUST
IS HIS OWN STRENGTH.
NOW KILL HER.
- LEADER, STAY BEHIND ME.
- GENTOKU RYUUBI,
I CHALLENGE YOU.
I WISH TO FACE YOU
AND THE CHAMPIONS OF SEITO
IN A FAIR FIGHT.
IN ORDER TO MEET MY CHALLENGE,
IT IS NECESSARY
FOR YOU TO REMAIN ALIVE.
- ( gasps )
BUT MOUYUU...
- I WILL NOW RETURN TO NANBAN
TO GATHER MY TROOPS.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
NO ONE KILLS HER.
- AS I PREDICTED.
FIGHTERS ARE INDEED
FOOLISH CREATURES.
- ( all gasp )
- ( murmurs )
- IT'S HIM.
- ( chuckles )
THESE TINY CUTE SPECS
MAKE EVERYTHING BIGGER.
- ( gasps )
THOSE ARE MY GLASSES.
EXCUSE ME--
BEGGING YOUR PARDON,
BUT COULD I PLEASE
HAVE THEM BACK?
- ( chuckles )
I THINK I'LL TRY THESE ON
AND SEE HOW THEY FIT.
- ( glasses crack )
- OOPS.
( chuckles )
THEY BROKE.
I GUESS THEY'RE TOO SMALL.
- HOW COULD YOU?
- YOU'VE ALWAYS
BEEN AN ASSHOLE.
- WHO IS THIS PERSON
AND HOW DO YOU KNOW HIM?
- HE'S A THIRD YEAR
STUDENT FROM NANBAN.
DAIOU BOKUROKU.
- ( chuckles )
KEEP OUT OF THIS, MOUYUU.
DON'T TRY TO CONVINCE ME
YOU'VE HAD SOME CHANGE OF HEART
AND BECOME A GOODY TWO-SHOES.
YOU'VE BEEN A BAD GIRL
UP TO THIS POINT.
YOU'RE BAD TO THE CORE.
- ( gasps )
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AM A BAD GIRL.
- HUH?
- BUT FIRST,
I'M A FIGHTER!
- ( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
( grunts )
- ( growls )
- Bashoku: ARE YOU OKAY?
- Shiryu: BASHOKU.
- SORRY I'M SO LATE.
- ( grunting )
- ( grunts )
- COME ON, WE SHOULD GO.
- I'LL HOLD HIM OFF.
- BUT--
- HURRY!
- BE CAREFUL.
- YOU KEEP SWITCHING SIDES
AND CHANGING TACTICS.
I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO PLAY YOUR STUPID GAMES.
FIRST I'LL TAKE DOWN
SEITO'S LEADER,
THEN I'LL HEAD TO NANYO
AND CRUSH THEIR SO-CALLED
LITTLE CONQUEROR,
HAKUFU SONSAKU.
ONCE I'VE BEATEN THAT BITCH,
KENTEI WILL MAKE ME THE LEADER
OF NANBAN HIGH,
AND ALL ITS FIGHTERS.
- NANBAN IS A STRONG SCHOOL.
THEY DON'T NEED KENTEI
TO FIGHT THEIR BATTLES.
CAN'T YOU SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( laughs )
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
NOT SEEING CLEARLY.
I DON'T CARE IF I LIE,
CHEAT, OR STEAL,
AS LONG AS I GET
WHAT I WANT,
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
THAT COUNTS...
THAT I WIN!
( grunts )
- ( shouts )
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- GENTOKU, YOU CAN'T STOP!
- KOUMEI, I CAN'T RUN.
I CAN'T JUST ABANDON THEM.
I'M A LEADER.
HOW CAN I SIT BACK
AND WATCH?
I CAN'T.
WHAT IF THEY DIED FOR ME?
( sighs )
- YOUR COMPASSION
IS ADMIRABLE, GENTOKU.
BUT YOU ARE A LEADER,
AND THAT MEANS YOU ARE
MORE THAN JUST YOURSELF.
- YOU ARE THE BANNER
FLYING IN THE WIND
OVER A BATTLEFIELD.
FIGHTERS LOOK TO YOU FOR HOPE.
KAN'U, CHOUHI,
CHOU'UN,
KOUCHUU, AND MOUKI BACHOU TOO.
THEY WERE ALL
UNITED BY YOU.
ACROSS TIME AND SPACE,
YOU SHOWED THEM THE WAY.
EVEN THAT FIGHTER
FROM NANBAN.
YOU INSPIRED HER,
GENTOKU.
DID YOU REALIZE THAT?
BECAUSE OF YOU,
SHE FINALLY UNDERSTANDS
THE REASON WHY SHE FIGHTS.
- ( chuckles )
- WELL...
READY TO SURRENDER?
- ( spits )
- ( gasps )
- THEY MAY DIE FOR YOU,
BUT YOU MUST LEARN
TO UNDERSTAND THAT.
BE STRONG. YOUR POWER
PROTECTS AND SERVES EVERYONE.
LET EVERYONE ALSO
PROTECT AND SERVE YOU.
- ( gasps )
UH-HUH.
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE BRIDGE?
- THE ENEMY ANTICIPATED
WE'D COME THIS WAY.
THEY CUT OFF OUR ESCAPE.
- WHAT DO WE DO?
SHOULD WE CLIMB DOWN
INTO THE CANYON?
- AT THE BOTTOM IS
A RIVER WITH RAPIDS.
EVEN IF WE MADE IT DOWN,
CROSSING WOULD BE
VERY DANGEROUS.
- WE CAN CROSS.
I'LL FIND A PLACE
WHERE THE WATER'S LOW.
- ( all gasp )
- ( wincing )
- Ryuubi: MOUYUU.
YOU SACRIFICED
YOURSELF FOR ME.
- GENTOKU, BACK AWAY.
- BUT SHE'S INJURED.
- ( all gasp )
- ( chuckles )
IT SEEMS WE MEET AGAIN,
LEADER OF SEITO ACADEMY.
- YOU'RE A MONSTER.
- YOU LOOK VERY HOT
WHEN YOU'RE ANGRY.
PITY I WON'T
GET TO ENJOY IT.
YOU'LL BE CRYING
BEFORE LONG.
YOU'LL BE BROKEN
AND BLEEDING
AND BEGGING ME TO KILL YOU
AND GET IT OVER WITH.
- ( gasps )
- MY TURN!
- WHO ARE YOU?
( grunts )
( chuckles )
- ( screams )
- STOP IT!
STOP HURTING HIM.
- KOUCHUU!
- ( grunts )
- ( Daiou chuckles )
PATHETIC.
- DON'T HURT HIM! I'M
BEGGING YOU. ( gasps )
- MORON.  DON'T BUTT IN.
NOW THEN...
( chuckles )
- Ryuubi: WHY?
WHY?
- ( chuckles )
- WHY?!
- GENTOKU!
NO, YOU MUSTN'T!
- ( laughing )
- ( screams )
- WHERE DID SHE GO?
I WAS GONNA
RIP HER HEAD OFF.
( gasps, grunts )
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
- DAMN IT.
WHO THE HELL IS
THIS CHICK IN THE WATER?
- YOU RAT BASTARD!
GUYS WHO PICK ON GIRLS
WHO'VE LOST THEIR GLASSES
ARE THE LOWEST SCUM!
I WON'T LET YOU DO THAT.
I'M THE SHOU HAOU OF NANYO!
( giggles )
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO SAY THAT.
- NO WAY.
YOU'RE SONSAKU?
HUH?
- HI THERE.
GUESS YOU DON'T LIKE
PICKING ON SOMEONE
YOUR OWN SIZE.
BUT MAYBE IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO LEARN WHY.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?!
( grunts )
( yells )
- TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION,
MY NAME IS...
GAKUSHU!
- UM, I THINK HE'S UNCONSCIOUS.
- HMM?
- RYUU-CHAN.
RYUU-CHAN,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- ( groans )
- WAKE UP.
IT'S HAKUFU.
OPEN YOUR EYES
AND LOOK AT ME.
- THAT'S THE ONE?
SHE'S THE LITTLE CONQUEROR?
- ( moans )
( gasps )
- THANK GOODNESS
YOU'RE AWAKE.
I'M SO RELIEVED.
YOU REALLY HAD ME GOING THERE.
I ONLY DROPPED BY TO ASK
IF YOU'D HEARD FROM THE FIGHTERS
AT THE TOURNAMENT,
AND SUDDENLY THERE YOU WERE
ABOUT TO FALL INTO A CANYON.
- ( panting )
- Kentei: AWAKEN.
I WILL GRANT YOU
THE ULTIMATE POWER
SO YOU CAN DESTROY THEM.
- ( growls )
( screams )
- ( sighs )
SONSAKU.
- ( giggles )
- ( yelling )
- ( gasps )
- ( shouts )
- ( crying )
YOU'RE SAFE NOW,
SONSAKU.
- I AM, RYUU-CHAN.
- I'M SO RELIEVED.
( shouts )
( grunts )
- ( all gasp )
- Hakufu:
WHAT'S WRONG WITH RYUU-CHAN?
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
- IT IS A PARADOX.
THE POWERFUL DRAGON THAT
SLEEPS INSIDE GENTOKU AWAKENED
TO PROTECT HER FRIENDS.
BUT HER KINDLY NATURE WAS
HORRIFIED BY THE VIOLENCE.
HER PURE HEART ATTEMPTED
TO RESTRAIN THE DRAGON,
AND THE OPPOSING FORCES
CLASHED INSIDE HER.
THE ENERGY FROM SUCH
AN INTENSE CONFLICT
RAGING INSIDE HER
HAS FORMED A PARADOX
IN GENTOKU
MAKING HER APPEAR
TO TURN TO STONE.
- Mouyuu: LAYING DOWN
YOUR LIFE FOR YOUR FRIENDS,
OR FOR WHAT YOU BELIEVE IN.
A BOND OF HONOR
AMONGST FIGHTERS.
VALUES LIKE THIS WERE TOTALLY
FOREIGN TO US AT NANBAN.
- Hakufu: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
WHAT MATTERS IS RYUU-CHAN.
HOW DO WE MAKE HER WELL AGAIN?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WHAT? YOU HAVE TO KNOW.
- I CAN'T KNOW
WHAT I DON'T KNOW.
BUT IF THERE IS
ANYONE AT ALL
WHO COULD POSSIBLY
SAVE GENTOKU--
- TELL ME,
WHO COULD SAVE HER?
- Suikyou:
HER BEST CHANCE WOULD BE--
- IT'S KAN'U, ISN'T IT?
- YES.
KAN'U HELPED ONCE BEFORE
WHEN GENTOKU'S DRAGON
AWAKENED.
SHE AND HER
GREEN DRAGON BLADE FOUGHT IT
AND PUT IT BACK TO SLEEP.
PERHAPS GENTOKU'S DRAGON
CAN ONLY BE QUIETED
BY ONE WHO IS
HER SWORN SISTER.
IT IS POSSIBLE
THEIR DESTINIES
MEANT FOR THEM
TO TAKE THAT OATH.
- PLEASE, MASTER SUIKYOU,
TELL ME WHAT I MUST DO. I WOULD
LAY DOWN MY LIFE FOR OUR LEADER.
- THERE'S NO NEED
TO BE HASTY, SHIRYU.
- ( gasps )
- I HAVE A TASK FOR YOU.
IT IS YOUR JOB
TO FIND KAN'U,
AND BRING HER BACK HERE.
THIS IS SOMETHING ONLY YOU
WILL BE ABLE TO ACCOMPLISH.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
AND DON'T FAIL ME.
- I WON'T.
- Mouyuu:
I'LL SHOW YOU THE WAY.
- ( gasps )
- ( door opens )
- I'LL TAKE YOU TO NANBAN.
- ( Bachou grunting )
( sighs )
OF ALL THE RIDICULOUS PLACES
THEY COULD PUT A SCHOOL.
WHOSE CRAZY IDEA WAS IT TO
BUILD IT ON THE TOP OF A CLIFF?
( panting )
( sighs )
STILL SUCH A LONG WAY
TO THE TOP.
WATCH ME, MASTER SONSAKU.
I'M GONNA PUT ALL THAT
YOU'VE TAUGHT ME TO GOOD USE.
I'LL RESCUE EVERYONE
AND MAKE NANBAN PAY THE PRICE
WHILE I'M AT IT.
( chuckles )
OHH?
- ( grunting )
- ( scoffs )
OH YEAH?
WELL, I'M GONNA
GET THERE FIRST.
( grunts )
( yelps )
( chuckles nervously )
( screams )
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
( cries )
( sighs )
- Kyocho: ARE YOU OKAY?
- I'M FINE.
I DIDN'T FALL THAT FAR.
THOUGH I DID GET
THE SHIT SCARED OUT OF ME,
AND MY LIFE SHORTENED
BY A COUPLE OF YEARS.
( screams )
- ( gasps )
WHAT HAPPENED NOW?
- KYOCHO, COME HERE!
YOU GOTTA COME DOWN
AND SEE THIS PLACE.
THESE STRANGE ROOTS ARE GROWING
EVERYWHERE IN THIS CAVE.
I BET IF WE FOLLOW THEM,
THEY'LL LEAD UP TO THE SCHOOL.
- Kyocho:
WHAT KIND OF PLANTS ARE THESE?
- Bachou:
SUPER GINORMOUS BEAN SPROUTS.
OR MAYBE NOT.
- Ryomou:
THE FIRE IS REACTING
TO A VERY POWERFUL
FIGHTING SPIRIT.
NOT A GOOD SIGN.
WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS GOING ON?
- ( clanging )
- ( gasps )
HUH?
LOOKS LIKE HE MEANS ME.
AM I GOING TO AT LAST MEET
THE SELF-PROCLAIMED KENTEI?
- ( creature growls )
- Ryomou: THAT ROAR.
NOT GOOD INDEED.
WHAT'S GOING ON UP THERE?
- Kan'u:
IS THAT ALL YOU'VE GOT?
GO AHEAD, DO YOUR WORST.
I MAY BE BLIND,
BUT YOU'RE STILL NOT GOING
TO GET THE BETTER OF ME.
I AM UNCHO KAN'U!
- WOW.
- HMM.
- THIS BOAT IS AWESOME.
IS THIS THE ONE WE'RE
GONNA USE TO GET THERE?
GAKU-CHAN, HOW'D YOU MANAGE
TO GET US THIS SWEET RIDE?
DID YOU FORGET TO TELL US THAT
YOUR DAD'S THE PRIME MINISTER?
- ( all sigh )
- SHE REALLY IS THAT DUMB.
- A GOOD SAMARITAN
HEARD ABOUT OUR PREDICAMENT
AND VOLUNTEERED TO HELP.
- OHH?
WHO OFFERED US HELP?
- SOMEONE'S COMING.
- HUH?
- ( footsteps approach )
- WHO ARE THEY?
( gasps )
- YO.
HOW'S IT HANGING,
SON-STUPID-KU?
- TON-CHAN!
HEY, DID YOU JUST CALL ME
"SON-STUPID-KU"?
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO CALL ME STUPID.
I'M SMARTER THAN YOU.
- LEADER SONSAKU,
KYOSHO ACADEMY GOT US THIS BOAT,
YOU MAY NOT WANT
TO INSULT THEM.
- OH?  YOU DID THIS FOR US?
- I WISH I WERE GOING,
BUT I HAVE TO SIT THIS ONE OUT.
WHEN YOU GET THERE, KICK SOME
EXTRA BUTT FOR ME, OKAY?
- YOU GOT IT!
- MOUTOKU COULDN'T COME,
BUT HE SENT THIS AS A GIFT.
HE TOLD ME TO PUT IT
IN YOUR HAND MYSELF.
- THIS IS FOR ME?
- THE DRAGON SWORD
OF A HUNDRED TEARS.
- 1800 YEARS AGO,
SOUSOU HAD THIS SWORD CRAFTED
WHICH TOOK THREE YEARS.
IT'S RUMORED TO BE
THE MOST POWERFUL
BEJEWELED BLADE EVER.
- OHH.
- Kakouton: WE'LL SET UP
A SECOND FRONT HERE
ON THE OFF CHANCE
YOU DON'T STOP KENTEI.
EVEN IF IT TAKES
EVERY LAST FIGHTER
THAT KYOSHO ACADEMY HAS,
WE'LL NEVER SURRENDER.
WE WON'T LET THAT
BASTARD KENTEI WIN.
WOULDN'T YOU DO
THE SAME FOR US?
( chuckles )
- TON-CHAN.
- Kakouton: HAKUFU SONAKU,
YOU ARE THE LEADER
OF NANYO ACADEMY.
GO TO NANBAN
AND KICK SOME ASS!
THOSE ARE THE BASICS!
YEAH!
- YEAH!
LET'S GO!
GET READY, KENTEI.
WE'RE COMING FOR YOU!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Gakushu: I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR YOU HELP GETTING THE BOAT.
- Kakouton: DON'T MENTION IT.
IT'S THE LEAST I COULD DO
SINCE I COULDN'T HELP
WITH THE FIGHT.
SONSAKU'S GOT
A LOT ON HER PLATE.
SEEMS LIKE SHE'S ALWAYS
BUSY WITH SOMETHING.
- Gakushu: YEAH,
SHE DOES TOO MUCH,
TO BE QUITE FRANK WITH YOU.
BUT I SUPPOSE
THAT'S THE DESTINY
OF THOSE WHO
POSSESS THE SACRED BEADS.
THEY'RE LIVING THEIR OWN LIVES
AND LIVING OUT THE FATE
OF SOMEONE ELSE.
NEXT TIME ON
"IKKI TOUSEN XTREME XECUTOR",
"REUNION OF THE FISTS."
- Kakouton:
THAT'S THE BASICS OF A REUNION.