- ( theme music playing )
- ( vocalizing )
( singing in Japanese )
- SHIRYUU CHOU'UN,
IF YOU TAKE ONE MORE STEP
TOWARDS US...
I'LL SEPARATE GENTOKU RYUUBI'S
HEAD FROM HER BODY.
- SO IF I PROMISE TO FIGHT YOU
UNDER YOUR TERMS,
DO YOU GUARANTEE THAT
YOU WON'T LAY A FINGER ON,
OR HARM OUR LEADER IN ANY WAY?
- PLEASE DON'T AGREE TO THIS,
SHIRYU!
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND,
I DIDN'T SURRENDER
WITHOUT REASON,
I DID AS SHE ASKED
BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANNA SEE
ANYMORE PEOPLE GET HURT.
- LEADER...
- YOU HAVE MY WORD.
HOWEVER, KEEP IN MIND
THAT IF YOU LOSE,
SEITO WILL CEASE TO EXIST
AS OF TODAY.
- A LITTLE TO THE RIGHT.
OKAY, A LITTLE MORE.
RIGHT THERE!
HOLD STEADY, AND...
ALL RIGHT!
FINALLY GOT IT!
OKAY, NOW LET'S GO MORE
TO THE LEFT.
AND SHIFT, SHIFT.
- WHAT KIND OF FRUIT IS THIS?
- WHO CARES WHAT IT IS.
I HAVEN'T EATEN IN FOREVER.
HERE GOES NOTHING!
( groans )
IT'S SOUR.
- DELICIOUS.
- HUH?
NO WAY!
( gasps )
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- I'M GUESSING
IT'S NANBAN HIGH.
- ( gasps )
SO THAT MEANS...
YOU AND I HAVE TO SNEAK IN THERE
AND RESCUE EVERYBODY ELSE,
AM I RIGHT?
- ( sighs, grunts )
- HEY, WHAT IS THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
- QUIET.
DOWN THERE.
- HUH?
KAN'U.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE THEY WERE
ABLE TO GET CHOUHI TOO.
KAN'U, ON MY HONOR
AS A FIGHTER,
I PROMISE
I WILL COME FIND YOU.
- THIS IS COMPLETELY OUTRAGEOUS!
WHAT ELSE DOES THE LETTER SAY?
- Rikuson: "SHIMEI RYOMOU
AND KOUKIN SHUYUU
ARE NOW OUR HOSTAGES.
WE DEMAND THAT NANYO'S LEADER
SURRENDER AND PLEDGE
HER UNDYING ALLEGIANCE
TO THE ALMIGHTY KENTEI.
IF SHE REFUSES TO COMPLY,
WE CANNOT GUARANTEE THE SAFETY
OF BOTH HOSTAGES."
I'D BET YOU ANYTHING THAT
AN IDENTICAL LETTER
WAS SENT TO BOTH
KYOSHO AND SEITO.
- SO THAT MEANS THE BIG
FIGHTERS' TOURNAMENT
WAS ALL A TRAP?
- IT ONLY MAKES SENSE,
SINCE THE ENEMY'S OBJECTIVE
WAS TO SPLIT EVERYONE UP.
THIS COULD BE BAD.
- YES, WE SHOULD
CONSIDER OURSELVES FORTUNATE
THAT SONSAKU'S NOT
WITH US NOW.
- ( bell dings )
- YAHOO!
THIS FEELS GREAT!
WHOO-HOO!
- WAIT FOR ME!
YOU'RE GOING TOO FAST FOR ME,
BIG SISTER!
- PEDAL FASTER, BIG SISTER!
FASTER!
- ARE YOU DOING OKAY UP THERE?!
- YOU HAVE TO COME UP HERE,
CHUUBO.
THE VIEW REALLY IS
SOMETHING ELSE.
- OH, DON'T BE SILLY.
I CAN'T CLIMB.
- AH!  AHH!  AHH!
AH-CHOO!
- OH, DID BIG SISTER
CATCH A SUMMER COLD?
BIG SISTER HAKUFU!
I HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY
BECAUSE IT'S TIME TO EAT LUNCH.
- ( giggles )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
AND YOU GOT GENPOU NAKED
AS WELL?
- WHY DON'T YOU
JOIN US, CHUUBO?
THE WATER'S COOL
AND FEELS GREAT.
- I CAN'T JUST--
WHAT IF SOMEONE WERE
TO SEE THE TWO OF YOU?
HOW SHAMELESS CAN YOU BE?
- OH, COME ON, NOBODY'S
WATCHING US THIS FAR OUT.
HA!  GUESS MISS MODESTY'S
TOO EMBARRASSED
TO COME IN, RIGHT?
- THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH ME
WANTING TO ACT LIKE A LADY.
- HUH?
( snickers )
OW OW OW OW OW!
IT HURTS!
OW!  MY POOR LEG'S CRAMPED!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
BIG SISTER?
- ( yells )
- NOW JUST TRY
AND GRAB MY HAND.
- HA!  SUCKER!
- AAH!
- GOTCHA!
- OH!
THAT WAS MEAN!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU TRICKED ME.
- AND OFF IT GOES!
AND NOW FOR THE FINAL
PIECE OF THE PUZZLE...
- NO!
- THERE!
NOW YOU CAN HAVE
AS MUCH FUN AS US TWO.
- BIG SISTER HAKUFU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
AAH!
AMAZING.
- AND BACK YOU GO.
- SO YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU'RE
ABLE TO CONTROL WATER AT WILL?
- AW, MAN.
I'M JUST LAYING HERE RELAXING
WHILE KOUKIN AND MOU-CHAN ARE
OFF DOING THEIR BEST
IN THE TOURNAMENT.
- Ryomou: THE WOUND HE SUFFERED
WHILE BATTLING RYOFU
SHOULD HAVE HEALED BY NOW.
SO WHY IS SAJI...
STILL--
SAJI!  WHAT'S WRONG?!
- LUCKILY THE DOCTOR SAYS
IT'S NOTHING TOO SERIOUS.
- BUT IT WAS STILL A SURPRISE.
AND TO SEE YOU
COLLAPSE LIKE THAT.
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE I WAS FEVERISH
FROM MY DATE WITH YOU,
MOU-CHAN.
- DON'T BE STUPID.
I WAS REALLY WORRIED!
- THANK YOU, MOU-CHAN.
- ALL THIS HAPPENED,
BECAUSE YOU TOLD ME TO GO.
NOW I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
- ( munching loudly )
HEY!  HOW LONG ARE YOU GOING
TO KEEP US COOPED UP IN HERE?!
WHATEVER HAPPENED
TO THE TOURNAMENT?!
I DEMAND TO SPEAK
TO YOUR LEADER!
DO YOU HEAR ME?!
( groans )
MORON.
FUCK YOU!
IF YOU WON'T TALK TO ME,
I'LL GIVE YOU SOMETHING ELSE
TO TALK--
- SAVE YOUR BREATH ALREADY.
NOTHING YOU SAY WILL
DO US ANY GOOD.
- AND WHY'S THAT?
- ONE THING I BET
YOU DIDN'T KNOW
IS THAT NANBAN HIGH IS
MADE UP OF REJECTS
FROM ALL THE OTHER SCHOOLS.
- HANG ON.
UNLESS I'M MISTAKEN,
I HEARD RUMORS THAT
YOU GUYS HAD AN ALLIANCE
WITH THEM AT ONE POINT.
- AT ONE POINT.
BUT EVEN BACK THEN,
WE COULDN'T ACTUALLY
TALK WITH THOSE GUYS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- BEFORE THEY STARTED TRYING
TO CONTROL EVERYTHING,
THEY HAD ENOUGH PROBLEMS
TRYING TO DECIDE WHO WAS
GONNA BE THEIR LEADER.
AND WHEN ALL WAS
SAID AND DONE,
THEIR LEADERS WERE
TWO SISTERS--
MOUKAKU AND MOUYUU.
- Shuhou:
AND THESE TWO ARE RUTHLESS.
THEY WEREN'T WILLING TO HELP
THEIR FRIENDS
OR COOPERATE WITH ANYONE.
BECAUSE OF THAT,
IT'S A WONDER THEY EVER GOT
TOGETHER LONG ENOUGH
TO TRAP ALL OF US
LIKE THEY DID.
- WHAT THEN?
YOU'RE SAYING IT'S KENTEI,
AND NOT THOSE TWO
WHO ARE LEADING THE SHOW?
- PROBABLY.
THEN AGAIN THAT DOESN'T
HELP US VERY MUCH.
SINCE WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHO KENTEI IS.
- ( door opens )
- HEY!
DON'T TOSS THE INJURED AROUND
LIKE THEY'RE SANDBAGS!
- CHOUHI, WAKE UP!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( groans )
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- WE'RE AT NANBAN HIGH.
WE'RE BEING KEPT IN A CELL.
HOLD ON, WASN'T KAN'U
WITH YOU EARLIER?
- DID YOU LOSE HER
WHEN YOU JUMPED OFF THE BOAT?
- KAN'U.
I REMEMBER NOW.
SHE CAN'T EVEN SEE.
I COULDN'T EVEN HELP HER.
DAMMIT!
- HA!
SO WHAT DUMB BASTARD WAS
STUPID ENOUGH
TO SEND US SOMETHING
LIKE THIS?
- PLEASE CALM DOWN, KAKOUTON.
WE HAVE TO REMEMBER
THAT KENTEI ISN'T THE ONLY ONE
TRYING TO GAIN SUPREMACY
OVER KANTO.
- NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
WE AREN'T EVEN SURE
WHO KILLED KAKUKA, EITHER.
I'D BE DISRESPECTING HIM
IF I LOST SIGHT
OF THE TRUE REASON
THAT WE FIGHT.
AND TO LOSE THAT WILL BE
TRULY DISGRACEFUL FOR US.
- I COULDN'T AGREE
WITH YOU MORE ON THAT ONE.
- MOUTOKU.
- HEY, TON.
COME TAKE A WALK WITH ME.
THERE'S SOMEPLACE
I WANT YOU TO SEE.
BACK IN THE DAY,
YOU, ME AND KAKUKA CAME HERE
ALL THE TIME, DIDN'T WE?
- YEAH, BUT THAT STUPID FOOL,
HE HAD THE ROTTEN NERVE TO DIE
BEFORE THE REST OF US.
- ( water splashes )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN THE WATER?
- TON.
KAKUKA IS STILL ALIVE.
- ( sharply gasps )
- YO.
YOU ALWAYS DID HAVE
TERRIBLE TASTE IN CLOTHES.
- BUT YOU--
AREN'T YOU DEAD?
- ( chuckles )
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT MATTERS IS
RIGHT NOW
THERE'S A CRAZY BASTARD LOOSE,
YOU UNDERSTAND?
- WHAT'S THAT?
COME ON, CAN'T YOU GIVE ME
A STRAIGHT ANSWER?!
- CORRECT ME IF I'M WRONG,
BUT KYOCHO AND SOUJIN ARE
AT THE TOURNAMENT?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT,
THEY ARE.
AND NOW WE HAVE TO HURRY UP
AND RESCUE THEM.
- SOMEONE WILL,
BUT IT WON'T BE US.
- WHO?
- IT'LL BE THOSE
FROM ACROSS THE HORIZON.
- WOW!
IT'S BEEN
PRACTICALLY FOREVER
SINCE I'VE HAD
A CHUUBO BOXED LUNCH!
- PLEASE FEEL FREE TO EAT
AS MUCH AS YOU'D LIKE.
- WELL, DON'T MIND IF I DO.
THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD!
AH, DELICIOUS!
HMM?
- HUH?
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- SOMEBODY'S WATCHING US.
- HUH?!
WHE-- WHERE ARE THEY?
- THEY'RE NOT HERE.
THEY'RE WAY...
WAY OVER THERE.
- ( birds squawking )
- YOU SEEM TO MISS THE THRILL
OF FIGHTING, HAKUFU SONSAKU.
- IS THAT SOUSOU FROM KYOSHO?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE IS THIS PLACE?
- WAY BACK WHEN,
AT THE BATTLE OF RED CLIFFS...
YOU SAVED MY LIFE
WITH THE POWER
OF YOUR LIFE FORCE.
- WITH WHAT?
THE POWER OF MY LIFE FORCE?
I DON'T QUITE UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- THEN ANSWER ME
THIS QUESTION.
WHAT IS IT THAT
WE FIGHTERS FIGHT FOR?
- HUH?
I DO IT BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING
MORE THRILLING TO ME
THAN FIGHTING STRONG OPPONENTS.
AND THE STRONGER
THE OPPONENT I FIGHT,
THE MUCH STRONGER I BECOME.
- SO, IS THAT ALL?
- HUH?
- YOU'RE A LEADER, AREN'T YOU?
- UH, YES?
- SO TELL ME WHY YOU WANT
TO BECOME STRONGER.
- UH, WELL, UH...
I WANT TO BECOME STRONGER,
BECAUSE...
BY BECOMING STRONGER,
I'M ABLE TO PROTECT PEOPLE.
( gasps )
WAS THAT IT?
- THERE'S AN ENEMY.
AN ENEMY WHO DESPISES
US FIGHTERS,
AN ENEMY WHO WANTS
TO DESTROY US.
- DESTROY?
- GO.
FULFILL YOUR MISSION
AS A FIGHTER
AND YOUR MISSION
AS A LEADER.
YOU MUST DO IT
FOR THE SAKE OF THOSE
WHO WILL TRUST
AND FOLLOW YOU.
THEREIN LIES
YOUR GREATEST STRENGTH.
- I'M SORRY, CHUUBO.
I GUESS I'LL HAVE TO ENJOY
YOUR BOXED LUNCH
SOME OTHER TIME.
- AS LONG AS IT'S
A PROMISE, BIG SISTER.
- PLEASE TAKE CARE,
BIG SISTER HAKUFU.
- I'LL SEE YOU TWO
AGAIN LATER.
- SEE YOU SOON!
POOR BIG SISTER.
EVERYONE IS WAITING FOR HER.
A GREAT BATTLE IS
SUMMONING BIG SISTER.
- Chuubo: BIG SISTER...
- WELCOME TO MY GREAT CASTLE,
UNCHO KAN'U.
- WHO ARE YOU?!
- MY NAME IS KENTEI.
I AM SUPREME RULER
AND EMPEROR.
- I SEE.
SO YOU'RE THE FOOL
WHO THINKS HE'S KENTEI.
- YOU'D BEST
WATCH YOUR TONGUE.
DO NOT FORGET THAT
YOUR FRIENDS ARE MY HOSTAGES.
- WHY DID YOU SO DEFILE
OUR SACRED TOURNAMENT?
ON WHAT GROUNDS DID YOU
BESMIRCH ITS NAME?
IF YOU WISHED FOR
ULTIMATE SOVEREIGNTY,
YOU NEEDED ONLY
TO FIGHT US FAIRLY!
- ( chuckles )
FIGHT, YOU SAY?
THAT IS THE ONLY THING
FOOLS LIKE YOU
EVER KNOW AND LIVE FOR.
YOUR DESTINY IS ONE OF
MUTUAL DEATH AND DESTRUCTION.
- YOU'RE WRONG!
WE FIGHTERS WORK HARD EVERY DAY
TO HONE OUR SKILLS,
AS WE DREAM OF ACHIEVING
COMPLETE DOMINANCE.
WE EACH SHARE THAT DREAM
AND FIGHT FOR THAT SINGLE BOND
BETWEEN US!
- YOU SPOUT SUCH NONSENSE.
ONLY THE FEW CHOSEN
SHALL WRITE HISTORY.
NO NUMBER OF YOU
LOWLY FOOT SOLDIERS
WILL MAKE ANY REAL DIFFERENCE
IN THIS WORLD.
AND YOU WILL AMOUNT TO
NOTHING MORE THAN MICE.
- FINE THEN.
WHY DON'T YOU COME DOWN
AND LEARN
HOW WEAK
THIS MOUSE REALLY IS.
COME DOWN HERE AND FIGHT ME
IN SINGLE COMBAT.
- ( chuckles )
DO NOT WORRY.
THE BIG FIGHTERS' TOURNAMENT
WILL BE HELD.
HOWEVER...
- ( growling )
- ...IT WILL BE
ACCORDING TO MY RULES.
( laughing )
- MY EYE.
- KAN'U...
( groaning )
I'M COMING NOW.  AAH.
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE MOVING AROUND
IN YOUR CONDITION.
- IF YOU FIGHT, YOU'LL JUST MAKE
YOUR INJURIES WORSE.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
IF I DON'T GO TO KAN'U,
WHO KNOWS WHAT'LL HAPPEN.
- QUIT YOUR BAWLING ALREADY,
YOU WHINY FUCKWIT.
- AAH!
- MOUKAKU!
- HEH HEH.  I JUST STOPPED BY
TO KILL SOME TIME,
BUT I DIDN'T REALIZE
YOU'D ALL BE SO SPUNKY.
- MOUKAKU.
YOU'RE NANBAN HIGH'S LEADER.
- DAMN YOU!
WHAT'VE YOU DONE WITH KAN'U?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU WERE PASSED OUT
THE ENTIRE TIME,
SO YOU WOULDN'T KNOW,
WOULD YOU?
- WOULDN'T KNOW WHAT?!
THAT THE FOOLISH WOMAN
GAVE HERSELF UP
IN ORDER TO SAVE YOUR LIFE.
SHE'S PROBABLY WITH KENTEI
RIGHT NOW, AS WE SPEAK.
- JUST WHO IN THE WORLD IS
KENTEI?
AND WHY IS HE WORKING WITH YOU?
- SO YOU WANNA KNOW
WHO KENTEI IS?
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'D KNOW?
THIS WAS NOTHING MORE THAN
A SITUATION
WHERE OUR OBJECTIVES
COINCIDED WITH EACH OTHER.
BOTH OF US WANTED
NOTHING MORE THAN TO SEE
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU
KANTO FIGHTERS DEAD!
- KAN'U IS SOMEWHERE CLOSE BY.
THAT EXTREME FIGHTING SPIRIT
I'VE BEEN SENSING...
IS NO DOUBT COMING FROM HER.
- ( sobbing )
KAN'U, WHY DID YOU DID THAT?
WHY DID YOU DO THAT FOR ME?
I'M A FOOL.
I'M NOTHING BUT A DAMN FOOL!
- ( shouts )
- ( roaring )
- ( groans )
- Kan'u: I COULDN'T JUDGE
ITS DISTANCE IN THE AIR.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
( shouts )
- ( laughs )
THAT'S MORE LIKE UNCHO KAN'U.
NOW LET IT ALL OUT.
FOR THE STRONGER YOU ARE,
THE BETTER IT IS FOR ME.
YOUR AMAZING STRENGTH
WILL ONLY BRING OUT THE EVIL
INSIDE OF YOU.
- HOW?
A BLOW LIKE THAT
SHOULD'VE SHATTERED ITS SKULL.
AAH.
UNTIL I BRING EKITOKU BACK
WITH ME TO SEITO,
I CAN'T GET KILLED...
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
I JUST CAN'T!
GENTOKU!
( echoing )
- ( grunts )
( shouts )
( grunts )
- DO YOU WISH TO KEEP GOING?
- SHIRYU...
IT IS VERY CLEAR
THAT THE MATCH IS OVER.
SO WILL YOU--
WILL YOU PLEASE
JUST LET HER GO?
- I WILL ADMIT MY TOTAL DEFEAT.
HOWEVER...
( running steps )
- ( sharply gasps )
- I WILL ATONE
FOR THIS DISGRACE
BY PUTTING AN END
TO MY PATHETIC EXISTENCE.
- ( sharply gasps )
ANSWER ME THIS:
WHY IS IT THAT WE FIGHT?
WHY WE HURT, AND WHY WE SPILL
EACH OTHERS' BLOOD?
- LEADER, YOU MUST STOP THIS.
- WE ALWAYS FIGHT FOR OUR
SCHOOLS AND FOR SACRED BEADS.
BUT IS IT WORTH IT?
WORTH ALL THE CASUALTIES?
I KNOW THAT IT MIGHT BE
OUR DESTINY,
BUT I DON'T--
I DON'T WANNA BE A FIGHTER
SO MUCH THAT I WANNA LOSE
THE ESSENCE OF MY HUMAN SOUL.
I BELIEVE...
THAT LIFE IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING IN THE WORLD.
IT'S SO IMPORTANT.
- Mouyuu: WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO WITH ME?
- FIRST, WE WILL TREAT
YOUR WOUNDS.
THAT IS THE WILL
OF OUR GREAT LEADER,
THE KINDHEARTED
GENTOKU RYUUBI.
- WHY DID YOU SPARE ME?
THERE IS NO POINT.
AS LONG AS HE CONTINUES TO SEEK
THE LIFE OF SEITO'S LEADER,
HE'LL CONTINUE TO MAKE
DIFFERENT PLANS.
- YOU'RE REFERRING TO KENTEI?
I WOULD LIKE YOU TO TELL US
EVERYTHING THAT YOU KNOW
ABOUT KENTEI.
PLEASE, FOR GENTOKU'S SAKE.
- VERY WELL.
WHEN I SAW THE FACE THAT WAS
HIDDEN UNDER THAT MASK--
- ( howling )
- ( gasps )
IT CAN'T BE.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- ( growling )
- IT SEEMS OUR TIME IS UP.
IT'S HERE.
THIS MUST BE THE NEXT PART
IN HIS PLAN.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Chuubo: GENPOU,
DO YOU THINK OUR BIG SISTER
WILL BE ALL RIGHT?
- BIG SISTER HAKUFU IS STRONG
WHEN IT COUNTS,
SO IT'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
- BUT WE CAN'T BE
TOO CERTAIN.
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES
TO BIG SISTER.
- SHE'S HAD SILLY SCREWUPS
FROM TIME TO TIME.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY GOOD ADVICE
YOU COULD GIVE HER?
- SUN TZU TEACHES,
"THE UNEXPECTED
WINS THE BATTLE."
NEXT TIME ON "IKKI TOUSEN:
XTREME XECUTOR"...
"SILENT TEARS."
- HOLD ON, GENPOU,
I THINK YOU MAY HAVE JUST
STOLEN MY LINE.