- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( Kan'u sighs )
SUCH FINE CRAFTSMANSHIP...
STOP IT! YOU DIDN'T COME HERE
TO STARE AT WEAPONRY.
( book closing )
- A PARTY FOR HER
NOW THAT SHE'S WELL?
I THINK GENTOKU
WILL LOVE IT!
- GLAD YOU THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
I WANTED TO PERHAPS
GET HER A PRESENT TOO.
WHAT... DO YOU
THINK SHE'D LIKE?
- BOOKS!
THEY'RE A SAFE BET.
BUT NOT THOSE THICK ONES...
LIKE THE ONES WE HAVE
TO READ FOR CLASS.
WHY NOT GET HER SOMETHING FUN,
LIKE A NOVEL OR MANGA?
- BOOK, HUH?
SUCH A CUTE LITTLE BOOK.
I HOPE GENTOKU WILL LIKE IT.
- OH WOW!
I LOVE IT, KAN'U!
IT'S PERFECT!
THANKS SO MUCH! I COULDN'T
HAVE ASKED FOR A BETTER GIFT.
I'M SO INCREDIBLY HAPPY!
- ( nervous chuckle )
- OH!
- GENTOKU...
- Woman: LOOK AT THAT GIRL!
- ( chuckling )
- DO YOU THINK
SHE'S ON DRUGS?
- Ekitoku: WOW, THAT
LOOKS EXPENSIVE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO WEAR IT!
- GENTOKU, SORRY I'M LATE.
- Ekitoku: THIS ONE'S COOL.
CHECK IT OUT!
- OH HI, KAN'U!
LOOK AT ALL OF THIS!
EVERYONE GAVE ME SO MANY FLOWERS
AND PRESENTS IT FEELS LIKE
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY AGAIN!
WANNA SEE WHAT SHIRYUU GAVE ME?
IT'S A GIANT TEDDY BEAR!
- I WANTED TO GET YOU
SOMETHING BIG... AND CUTE!
- AND KOUCHUU GAVE ME A T-SHIRT
HE MADE HIMSELF.  IT'S ME!
- THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE IT.
IT'S CUTE.
- HOW SWEET. THAT WILL LOOK
GREAT ON YOU. THERE'S ONE MORE--
- Gentoku: I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
IT'S JUST WHAT I WANTED!
- HUH?
- THANK YOU, KOUMEI.
I LOVE BIG THICK
ACADEMIC BOOKS.
I JUST CAN'T GET ENOUGH OF THEM.
I CAN'T WAIT TO READ IT!
- I THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE THE PERFECT GIFT.
I KNOW WHAT GENTOKU LIKES.
- DON'T FORGET TO THANK KAN'U.
TODAY'S PARTY WAS HER IDEA.
SHE PLANNED IT ALL.
YOU GOT HER A GIFT TOO.
ISN'T THAT WHAT
YOU TOLD ME?
- I DID?
WELL, I MEANT TO GET SOMETHING,
BUT I RAN OUT OF TIME.
- THERE'S NO NEED
TO GET ME A GIFT, KAN'U.
YOU'VE ALREADY DONE SO MUCH.
I'M HAPPY JUST TO BE
FEELING BETTER
AND HAVE ALL OF MY FRIENDS
WITH ME TO CELEBRATE!
- IF YOU'RE HAPPY,
THEN SO AM I.
- SO WHAT DID YOU THINK
OF THE BARBELL SET
I GAVE YOU FOR WEIGHTLIFTING?
PRETTY COOL, RIGHT?
- UH... IT'S GREAT.
IT WILL ALWAYS REMIND ME OF YOU!
- BECAUSE IT'S SOMETHING
YOU WOULD ENJOY,
NOT THAT GENTOKU WOULD LIKE.
- WHAT THE-- ?
IT'S AN AWESOME GIFT!
IT'S USEFUL!
GENTOKU CAN BUILD UP MUSCLE
STRENGTH AND BE TONED AND FIT
LIKE A LEADER SHOULD BE!
- Chou'un: IT'S AN
EXCELLENT GIFT, CHOUHI.
OUR LEADER'S HEALTH
AND FITNESS ARE IMPORTANT.
- Kouchuu: I AGREE. YOU CAN DO
IT, LEADER! TONE THOSE LATS!
- THAT LAST DAY...
KENTEI SAID
HE WOULD BE REINCARNATED
OVER AND OVER AGAIN,
UNTIL EVERY LAST FIGHTER
HAD BEEN WIPED FROM
THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
- KAN'U, CHOUHI!
MASTER!
- BACHIN!
- Bachou: I'M SO HAPPY
TO SEE YOU!
- Koukin: HAKUFU!
THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE OKAY!
- Hakufu: KOUKIN, I'M SORRY
FOR MAKING YOU WORRY.
- ( whimpering )
- LIGHTNING DRAGON THAT
LIVES WITHIN GENTOKU,
BE STILL
AND SLEEP ONCE MORE.
RELEASE YOUR ANGER!
GO BACK TO THE REALM OF SHADOWS
AND STAY HIDDEN THERE
FOREVER!
( screams )
- KAN'U!
( giggles )
- GENTOKU?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- ( sighs )
NOTHING'S WRONG.
I JUST NOTICED THE
WEATHER WAS NICE,
SO I THOUGHT I'D READ OUTSIDE.
IT'S SO PEACEFUL. BY THE WAY,
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
AFTER THE PARTY I FOUND A GIFT
THAT DIDN'T HAVE A NAME ON IT--
A CUTE LITTLE MANGA NOVEL.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHO
MIGHT HAVE LEFT IT?
- I-I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE IT'S
FROM ONE OF THE FRESHMEN.
- ARE YOU SURE?  'CAUSE
THAT ISN'T WHO I WOULD GUESS.
- IN THAT CASE,
I HAVE NO CLUE WHO IT'S FROM.
IS IT REALLY THAT
IMPORTANT TO YOU?
- NO WORRIES.  I THINK I KNOW
WHO THE BOOK IS FROM ANYWAY.
AND I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT I'M RIGHT.
- I SEE.  MYSTERY SOLVED.
GOOD FOR YOU, GENTOKU.
- ( giggles )
THANK YOU FOR THE BOOK, KAN'U.
- ( gasps )
- HOW DID YOU KNOW
THAT IT CAME FROM ME?!
- WE MAY NOT HAVE BEEN BORN
ON THE SAME DAY...
- BUT WE BOND AS SISTERS...
- AND SOLEMNLY VOW THAT
WE WILL DIE TOGETHER.
- Gentoku: EVEN THOUGH
I WAS UNCONSCIOUS
I FELT LIKE I COULD
STILL HEAR YOU.
IT WAS AS IF YOU WERE
CALLING OUT TO ME
FROM FAR AWAY.
YOU KEPT SAYING...
"HOLD ON, MY FRIEND!"
I'M SORRY FOR ALL
THE TROUBLE I GET INTO
THAT YOU ALWAYS HAVE
TO SAVE ME FROM.
- I REALLY DON'T MIND.
YOU'RE MY FRIEND
AND THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS DO.
OH!
- YOU'RE ALWAYS THERE FOR ME.
THANK YOU, KAN'U.
- MMM.
- THERE YOU ARE.
WHY DO YOU LOOK SO HAPPY?
WERE YOU GOSSIPING
ABOUT SOMETHING?
- Gentoku: HI, EKITOKU!
- I WAS THINKING WE COULD
KEEP THE PARTY GOING
AND HEAD INTO TOWN.
WHAT DO YOU SAY? YOU UP FOR IT?
- SURE!  I'D LIKE THAT.
COME ON, KAN'U! THERE'S A NEW
BAKERY I'VE BEEN WANTING TO TRY.
I HEAR THEIR CUPCAKES
ARE DELICIOUS!
- THAT SOUNDS NICE.
WHY DON'T WE GO?
- HERE.
- HUH?
- A FAREWELL PRESENT.
- GUMMY SNACKS!
- I BOUGHT OUT EVERY SINGLE
STORE IN THIS ENTIRE AREA.
- MASTER?!
( whimpers )
THIS IS THE BEST GIFT
I'VE EVER GOT!
- IF YOU EVER WANT
MORE TRAINING,
YOU'RE WELCOME
TO COME BACK AGAIN.
- I CAN HELP TEACH YOU
HOW TO WIN FIGHTS
WITH OPPONENTS WHO ARE
MUCH BIGGER THAN YOU.
- AWESOME, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
THANK YOU FOR
OFFERING TO TEACH ME.
MASTER, CAN I ASK A
REQUEST OF YOU?
- HUH?
- I'M GOING TO STUDY
AND TRAIN REALLY HARD
SO THAT ONE DAY
I CAN COME BACK
AND FACE YOU AS AN EQUAL.
WHEN THAT DAY COMES,
WILL YOU PROMISE
TO ACCEPT MY CHALLENGE?
- YEAH, SURE THING.
- WHOA, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE ASKING?
- DON'T INTERFERE.
A STUDENT SHOULD AIM
TO SURPASS HER TEACHER.
IT'S THE CIRCLE OF LIFE.
- INDEED.
THAT IS THE NATURAL
ORDER OF THINGS.
SINCE SONSAKU IS A FIGHTER,
SHE CANNOT BACK DOWN
FROM A CHALLENGE.
- THEN LET US MAKE
THIS PACT TOGETHER.
ONE DAY, WE WILL FIGHT.
- I'M AFRAID HE'S STILL
RECOVERING FROM HIS ILLNESS.
- I SEE.
THEN I'LL COME BACK
ON ANOTHER DAY.
- WHEN HE FIRST
RETURNED HOME...
- UH...
- HE GAVE ME
A MESSAGE TO PASS ON.
- WHAT DID HE SAY?
- Shisonzui:
THE FUTURE ON NANYO
DEPENDS ON YOU,
SHIMEI RYOMOU.
WORK WITH SONSAKU
TO BRING FORTH BRIGHTER DAYS.
- SAJI, NO MATTER WHAT
TRIALS MAY LIE AHEAD,
I DON'T INTEND
TO LOSE ANYTHING,
NOT MYSELF OR ANYONE
I CARE ABOUT.
SO KEEP ON FIGHTING, SAJI.
I WON'T LET YOU GIVE UP.
- ( man running, grunting )
HEY, WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?!
YOU'VE BEEN FOLLOWING ME
ALL THIS TIME.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?!
- ( man screaming )
- ( footsteps )
- HEY, YOU.
ARE YOU THE BASTARD
WHO'S BEEN KILLING OFF
ALL OF OUR FRIENDS?!
- SAY SOMETHING!
WHAT'S WITH THAT WEIRD MASK?
- ( blasting )
- STOP, WHAT IS
YOUR PURPOSE HERE?
WHY ARE YOU
TARGETING KYOSHO?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I WILL FIGHT YOU
IF I MUST.
SPEAK.
SHE'S GONE.
- Koukin: ANOTHER
ATTACK ON KYOSHO?
- Rikuson:
EARLY REPORTS ARE SAYING
THEY'VE SUFFERED
HEAVY CASUALTIES.
- Koukin:
NEITHER NANYO NOR SEITO
WOULD DO ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
SO WHO'S RESPONSIBLE?
- Rikuson: FACE IT, SHUUYU.
WE BOTH KNOW
WHO THE MOST
LIKELY SUSPECT IS.
- Koukin: WHO?
- Rikuson: MOUKI BACHOU!
SHE'S SWORN REVENGE
AGAINST SOUSOU.
SHE CLAIMS HE'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE DEATH OF HER BROTHER.
- Koukin: I WAS AWARE
OF HER PRIOR ATTACK,
BUT I DON'T
THINK IT'S HER.
- BACHOU ISN'T THE ONE
WHO ATTACKED KYOSHO.
- ( both gasps )
- IT'S SOMEONE UNKNOWN.
WHOEVER IT IS,
HE'S THREATENING NANYO AS WELL.
- Koukin:
WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN?
- Gakushu: WE FOUND IT LIKE THIS
JUST THIS MORNING.
THE PERSON WHO DID THIS
IS FRIGHTENINGLY SKILLED.
- THIS IS BAD.
WE MIGHT BE IN REAL DANGER.
- ( leaves rustle )
- WHO'S THERE?!
- ( meows )
- AH, CHIBI!
( giggles )
SO THIS IS WHERE YOU WERE.
- ( meows )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
OUT HERE ALONE?
BE CAREFUL.
THE BOOGEYMAN'LL GET YOU.
SCARY, SCARY.
- ( meows )
- ( distant chatter )
- SORRY I COULDN'T
KILL SOUSOU
AND AVENGE YOUR DEATH,
BIG BRO'.
I HOPE YOU WON'T
HOLD IT AGAINST ME.
- Man #1: THAT PUNK
WON'T GET AWAY WITH THIS!
- HUH?
- Man #2: DAMN RIGHT! I'M GONNA
BEAT HIS ASS INTO THE GROUND.
- LET'S TAKE HIM OUT!
- Both: YEAH!
- WHAT'S UP WITH THOSE GUYS?
THEY'RE ALL RILED UP
ABOUT SOMETHING.
COULD IT BE
ANOTHER BATTLE?!
COUNT ME IN!
( running footsteps )
- Man #2: ( in pain )
WHERE'RE YOU FROM?!
YOU PUT YOU UP TO THIS?!
WHY ARE YOU
TARGETING KYOSHO?
- ( thudding )
- ( grunting )
- OH, WOW.
IT'S A TOTAL MASSACRE.
- ( groans )
BEHIND YOU.
HEY, WHO ARE YOU?!
AND WHAT'S WITH
THE WEIRD GETUP?!
A FIGHTER WITH TWO SWORDS!
HEY, WAIT A SEC.
DAMN IT!  DON'T RUN AWAY!
- Kan'u: WHAT IS THE REASON
THAT WE FIGHT THE GOOD FIGHT?
WE FIGHT BECAUSE WE SHARE
A DREAM FOR THE FUTURE,
TO IMPROVE OUR WORLD.
WITHOUT SUCH PURPOSE,
FIGHTING IS WRONG.
AND YET THERE ARE TIMES
WHEN WE MUST FIGHT AND DIE
FOR THE SAKE
OF THAT DREAM.
BUT THERE ARE TIMES
WHEN WE SHOULD
SHEATH OUR WEAPONS
FOR THE GREATER GOOD.
THIS WAY--
THE WAY OF PEACE--
IS THE WILL
OF GENTOKU RYUUBI.
- Koumei: THE TIDE
OF ANY NATION TENDS
TO FLOW TOWARDS UNITY AFTER
PERIODS OF DEEP DIVISION,
AND TOWARDS DIVISION
WHEN THERE ARE
MOMENTS OF NATIONAL UNITY.
IT IS A NEVER-ENDING CYCLE
OF WARFARE AND PEACE
THAT HISTORY REPEATS
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
BUT SHE WOULD
BREAK THE CYCLE.
GENTOKU'S WISH IS THAT
WE WOULD FIGHT NO MORE.
- IF THE DAY SHOULD COME
WHEN WE ARE
NO LONGER FIGHTERS
AND THE SACRED BEADS
DON'T EXIST,
OUR BONDS OF SISTERHOOD
AND FRIENDSHIP WILL REMAIN.
THEY WILL CONNECT US FOREVER.
- Ekitoku: TAKE THAT!
- WHOA! ( grunts )
- WANT TO GIVE UP
AND CALL IT QUITS FOR THE DAY?
- ( strains ) NO!
I WANT TO KEEP GOING.
TODAY I'M GOING
TO KNOCK
YOU TO THE MAT FOR ONCE.
AND WE CAN'T STOP
UNTIL I DO.
- NICE!  THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
OKAY, THEN COME AT ME
WITH EVERYTHING YOU'VE GOT.
TOO SLOW!
- OWW!
I WASN'T READY YET.
- THIS ONE
AND THIS ONE TOO.
OH, AND HERE'S ANOTHER ONE
I HAVEN'T READ YET.
THERE'S NOTHING BETTER
ON A RAINY DAY
THAN CURLING UP
WITH A GOOD BOOK.
OH, WAIT A SEC.
I WONDER IF I SHOULD
GET ANOTHER BOOK
FOR KAN'U TO READ.
HUH?
( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- MA-CHAN, HOW--
- STAY BACK, MISS GENTOKU.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET HURT.
- ( both scream )
( groaning )
- OWW, THAT HURTS
MY BOTTOM.
- WHOA, THINK THAT
YOU CAN STAND UP?
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M FINE.
- ( gasping )
( screams )
- NO, RUN, MA-CHAN!
I CAN'T, MISS GENTOKU.
I HAVE TO PROTECT YOU.
HURRY, GO TO KAN'U!
I'VE BEEN TAILING
THIS MASKED FIGHTER
EVER SINCE I SAW HER
AMBUSH A GANG IN TOWN.
HER METHODS ARE
RUTHLESS AND CRUEL.
NO, GO! GET AWAY!
- BUT, MA-CHAN--
- DON'T WORRY.
I'LL STOP HER.
SHE WILL NOT
GET PAST ME!
- MA-CHAN...
- Kan'u: GENTOKU,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- KAN'U, EKITOKU, COME QUICK!
MA-CHAN'S LIFE
IS IN DANGER!
- Ekitoku: WHAT'S WRONG?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO HER?
- Kan'u: CALM DOWN.
TELL US WHAT WENT ON.
- SHE JUMPED IN
TO PROTECT ME.
AND NOW SHE'S FIGHTING
AND I'M SCARED FOR HER.
- ( grunts )
( screams )
( pants )
- I WILL NEVER DIE.
I AM IMMORTAL.
- THAT VOICE!
YOU'RE THAT MONSTER!
UNTIL I HAVE
MY DESIRED VENGEANCE,
I WILL COME BACK
AGAIN AND AGAIN.
- YOUR VENGEANCE?
- IT SEEMS I HAVE
FOUND A KINDRED SPIRIT.
- ( gasps )
- THE DESIRE FOR REVENGE
BURNS INSIDE YOU.
- WE ARE NOTHING ALIKE!
- BUT WE ARE.
I CAN PEER DEEP
INSIDE YOUR SOUL
TO WHERE IT SEETHES
WITH DESIRE
TO AVENGE YOUR
OLDER BROTHER'S DEATH.
IT STILL BURNS IN YOU.
- THAT'S A LIE.
YOU CAN'T READ MY SOUL.
- DOES THAT MEAN THAT
YOU'VE FORGOTTEN HIM?
THAT HE MEANT
SO LITTLE TO YOU
THAT YOU JUST ERASED HIM
FROM YOUR MEMORY?
EVER SINCE YOUR BROTHER
WAS MURDERED,
HIS SPIRIT HAS BEEN
UNABLE TO REST.
HE SUFFERS IN PURGATORY
AND CRIES OUT TO YOU
TO SAVE HIM!
"HELP ME, SISTER,"
HE WAILS.
"AVENGE MY DEATH."
- HE SAID THAT?
- YOU HAVE OFTEN WONDERED
HOW YOUR BROTHER DIED.
SHALL I SHOW YOU?
- ( gasping )
- WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED HERE?
WHO ARE Y-- WAIT, I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE SOUSOU.
STOP IT, SOUSOU!
PLEASE DON'T HURT ME!
( screams )
- KANSUI!  NO!
- GET JUSTICE
FOR YOUR BROTHER.
JOIN WITH ME.
AND I WILL HELP YOU ATTAIN
THE VENGEANCE YOU SEEK.
REVENGE IS POWERFUL.
USE IT WITH ME.
- Sousou: DON'T SUCCUMB
TO THE DARKNESS,
MOUKI BACHOU.
- ( screams )
- ( sighs )
IS SOMEONE THERE?
- YOU WERE
AS I WAS IN THE PAST.
RAGE SUMMONS NEGATIVE POWERS.
THE NIGHTMARES
GO ON FOREVER.
- ( strains )
- ALL THAT LIES BEYOND
IS A TRAGEDY THAT
LEADS YOU TO DESTRUCTION.
REMEMBER THAT WELL
UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN.
- YOU'RE FINALLY AWAKE.
THANK GOODNESS.
- HOW DID--
- THE MASKED SWORDSMAN
WAS GONE WHEN WE GOT THERE.
WE FOUND YOU PASSED OUT
AND BROUGHT YOU HERE.
SOUSOU SAVED ME.
- ( gasps ) SOUSOU
WAS THERE AS WELL?
- WELL, MAYBE I DREAMT IT.
- I SEE.
- Ryuubi: KAN'U!
- EVERYONE'S OUTSIDE
WAITING FOR YOU.
THEY'RE EXCITED TO GREET
THEIR NEW CLASSMATE.
- WELCOME HOME.
- Koumei: MOUKI BACHOU,
YOU ARE NOW
OFFICIALLY ENROLLED
AT SEITO ACADEMY.
- ( panting )
I'M SEITO ACADEMY
FIRST-YEAR STUDENT
MOUKI BACHOU.
I'VE COME HERE TODAY
TO CHALLENGE
THE SCHOOL'S LEADER
HAKUFU SONSAKU!
- SHE'S BACK.
- HUH?
- YOU'VE COME BACK.
- ( screams )
- WILL YOU FACE ME
IN A FAIR FIGHT?
- BACHIN, IF YOU WIN,
THEN YOU CAN BE THE LEADER
OF NANYO ACADEMY.
- REALLY?  IN THAT CASE,
I WON'T HOLD BACK.
- Narrator: THE HISTORY
OF HUMANKIND
IS A HISTORY OF BATTLES.
IT IS THE DESTINY THAT
ALL WHO LIVE MUST BEAR.
THERE IS AN ETERNAL KARMA
GOING BACK 1800 YEARS
INHERITED BY
DAUNTLESS WARRIORS
WITH A STRENGTH OF 1,000.
WE CALL THEM...
FIGHTERS.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )