- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kentei: I HEAR IT.
I CAN HEAR IT--
THE HATEFUL GRUDGES OF CARCASSES
STREWN ABOUT THE BADLANDS,
BLOODY, WOUNDED,
AND DEFEATED.
LISTEN, HEAR ME,
YOU LOST SOULS.
THIS IS THE GATEWAY TO HELL,
THE THRESHOLD TO DEATH.
AND WHAT IS MORE?
THE GRAVEYARD FOR FIGHTERS.
COME AND CONSUME
THEIR FLESH.
DRINK THEIR BLOOD
AND THEN RISE
ONCE AGAIN.
JOIN ME AND FIGHT BY MY SIDE
ON THE BATTLE FIELD.
- WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU PEOPLE?!
- YOU GUYS BETTER STAY BACK
UNLESS YOU LIKE PAIN.
- ( screams )
- WOW, THEY'RE SO COOL,
AND NOW IT'S MY TURN.
( yelps )
AHH!
( thuds )
- DAMN THEM! DAMN THOSE
FREAKING NANBAN SCUMBAGS.
- HEY!
- COME ON!
LET'S PUT AN END
TO THIS BULLSHIT.
- TO ALL OF THOSE
WHO ARE SERVANTS OF GOD
AND TO ALL THOSE WHO ARE
FEARFUL OF GOD...
- ( screams )
- I'VE HEARD THOSE WORDS.
I KNOW THEM.
- ( cackles )
- ( men grunt, scream )
- LOOK UP, YOU SCUM,
AND PRAISE GOD WITH ME.
- Yougai: STOP IT, PLEASE.
- ENOUGH!
THIS IS NO HONOR
TO BE HAD IN KILLING A MAN
WHO HAS LOST
ALL WILL TO FIGHT.
- KAN'U, WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
- HUH?
- ( strains, grunts )
LET GO OF ME,
YOU STUPID, BALD FREAK!
- MAN, YOU SUCK.  FIGURES
YOU'D GET CAUGHT FIRST.
- HMM, THIS NEVER
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED
IF I DIDN'T TRIP AND FALL
IN THE FIRST-- ( whimpers )
- GREAT, NOW THEY'VE
GOT THE UPPER HAND.
- KEEP STILL.
- SO WHAT'S
THE PLAN HERE, KAN'U?
THINK WE SHOULD GIVE IT UP
FOR NOW?
- ( chuckles )
- Kan'u: LISTEN TO ME,
MOUKI BACHOU.
SHOW SOME PRIDE.
IF YOU'RE INDEED A FIGHTER
WHO IS DESTINED
TO JOIN US IN BATTLE,
THEN PROVE IT TO US.
PROVE THAT YOU ARE WORTHY
BY GETTING OUT ALIVE
BY YOURSELF!
- KAN'U.
- OUR MISSION TO PROTECT
IS ONLY RESERVED
FOR THOSE WHO TRULY NEED
TO BE PROTECTED.
ARE YOU ONE WHO TRULY
NEEDS OUR PROTECTION?
LET'S JUST SEE!
THIS IS MY TEST FOR YOU!
- SHOW SOME PRIDE.
SHE'S RIGHT.
I CAN'T BE WEAK.
I CAME ON BOARD THIS SHIP
TO GET STRONGER.
AND I WILL BECOME STRONGER.
THEN I'LL AVENGE MY BROTHER
FOR THE SAKE OF MY PRIDE
AS A FIGHTER!
- ALL RIGHT, SHE DID IT.
WAY TO GO!
GOOD GOING, BACHOU!
- UH, HEY, KAN'U?
I...
- HMM.
- ( giggles )
- ( gasps )
- ( ragged breathing )
- ( panting )
KAN'U!
- CHOUHI!
HUH?
- TAKE A LOOK AROUND, KYOCHO.
THIS IS MESSED UP.
WHAT SORT OF FREAK SHOW
DID WE GET OURSELVES
INTO THIS TIME?
- LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
COMPLETELY SURROUNDED.
- IT'S ALMOST AS IF
WE JUST WANDERED
INTO THE ERA OF
THE THREE KINGDOMS.
- NO WAY.
KAN'U.
AND CHOUHI TOO.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- Ryomou: IT LOOKS LIKE THE
RUINS OF AN ANCIENT TEMPLE.
- MAN, WHAT IS
THIS CREEPY PLACE?
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE
ON THE SET OF "LOST."
HEY, WEIRDOES!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHO YOU'RE DEALING WITH?
YOU'RE DEAD MEAT!
I'M A THIRD-YEAR
A-RANKED FIGHTER
FROM KYOSHO ACADEMY,
YOU HEAR ME?!
- YOU REALIZE YOU'RE
JUST WASTING YOUR BREATH.
- SHIT.
DON'T TALK TO ME.
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT
THAT WE'RE IN THIS MESS.
TAKE SOME RESPONSIBILITY, HUH?
- ( growls )
- OH, COME ON.
I WAS JUST KIDDING.
DON'T TELL ME
YOU CAN'T TAKE A JOKE.
- GIVE ME BACK
MY GUMMY CHEWS.
- TOO BAD FOR YOU
I ALREADY ATE THEM ALL.
- TAKING SOMEONE ELSE'S CANDY,
YOU'RE SO UNBELIEVABLE.
- YOU STILL HAVE SOME?
I COULD GO FOR MORE.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
WHY DON'T YOU
BRING YOUR OWN SNACKS
FOR ONCE, HUH?
- YOU'RE A REAL CHEAPSKATE.
- LOOK WHO'S TALKING!
- CHEAP CHEAP!
- STUPID PIG!
- Kyocho:
THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU TWO.
THERE ARE OTHER
PRESSING MATTERS.
- Both: RIGHT.
- Shuhou: WHAT HAPPENED
TO KOUTEI AND THE OTHERS?
ARE THEY STILL
ON THE SHIP?
- WHO KNOWS?
HONESTLY,
I'D BE MORE WORRIED
ABOUT YOURSELF
THAN WHATEVER THEY'RE
GOING THROUGH RIGHT NOW.
DAMN, YOU KNOW,
NO MATTER HOW HARD I TRY,
I JUST CAN'T GET A READ
ON THESE GUYS.
- THAT GIRL WHO ATTACKED US
FROM THE DECK
OF THE SHIP EARLIER...
I'VE SEEN HER.
I'M POSITIVE THAT'S
THE GIRL WHO ATTACKED ME
WHEN I VISITED
RYOFU'S GRAVE.
- HALLELUJAH.
SALVATION, GLORY, AND POWER
BELONG TO THE ONE AND ONLY
ALMIGHTY GOD.
OUR JUDGMENT IS BOTH
TRUE AND RIGHTEOUS.
- Ryomou: SHE'S A KILLING
MACHINE TRAINED TO ELIMINATE
ENEMIES WITH
DEADLY CERTAINTY.
TEN'I FROM KYOSHO ACADEMY.
- TO ALL OF THOSE WHO
ARE SERVANTS OF GOD,
LOOK UP, YOU FOUL SCUM,
AND PRAISE GOD WITH ME.
- THOSE ARE THE SAME
WORDS SHE USED BEFORE.
- FROM THE LOOKS OF IT,
THIS CONTEST WAS A FAKE
TO BEGIN WITH.
AT ANY RATE,
UNTIL WE KNOW FOR SURE
WHO THIS KENTEI REALLY IS,
WE BETTER KEEP OUR EYES PEELED
AND OUR MOUTH SHUT.
- THIS KENTEI,
I'M REALLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO MEETING HIM
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
- SHIRYUU CHOU'UN...
THE WAY YOU FOUGHT
TO PROTECT YOUR LEADER
WAS A COMMENDABLE
FEAT INDEED.
THOUGH YOU ARE MY ENEMY,
I ADMIRE YOU.
- Kentei: I PUT A CURSE
ON THE SACRED BEADS
HELD BY THE FIGHTERS
IN ORDER TO LURE
THEM HERE.
I GUARANTEE THAT
IT WILL WORK WITHOUT FAIL.
AND NOW THE SOULS THAT
HAVE REMAINED DORMANT IN THEM
WILL BE RELEASED.
AND THE FIGHTERS WILL BE DRAWN
TO THEIR BLOODY DESTINY,
A DESTINY OF 1800 YEARS PAST.
HERE, IN THIS ARENA,
THEY WILL DO BATTLE
UNTIL THEIR BODIES
GIVE OUT AND EXPIRE.
- YOU CAN COUNT
ON ME FOR THIS.
NO ONE WILL BE GETTING AWAY
WITH ME AROUND.
- Kentei: IN THE COMMOTION,
I WILL TAKE THE HEAD
OF SEITO'S LEADER.
GENTOKU RYUUBI.
- HMM.
- RYUUBI'S DRAGON
IS THE POWER OF LIGHTNING.
HOWEVER, AT PRESENT, SHE IS
STILL UNABLE TO CONTROL IT.
ITS TRUE POWER CAN
ONLY BE DISPLAYED
WHEN HAKUFU SONSAKU'S
WATER DRAGON IS NEARBY.
- HAKUFU'S SONSAKU'S
WATER DRAGON?
- FIRST, WE NEED
TO KILL RYUUBI
BEFORE THE DRAGON
SHOWS ITS POWER.
THEN WE NEED
TO CAPTURE SONSAKU.
ONCE WE'VE DEFEATED
SEITO AND NANYO,
CONQUERING THE KANTO REGION
WILL BE EASY.
- WHAT ABOUT SOUSOU
OF KYOSHO ACADEMY?
- Kentei: SOUSOU
WON'T TAKE ACTION.
HE KNOWS HIS POWERS
WILL ONLY BRING ABOUT
HIS OWN DESTRUCTION.
AND HIS FEAR CONTROLS HIM.
- AND WHO THE HELL ARE YOU
TO TELL US WHAT DO TO, HUH?
DON'T TELL ME YOU BELIEVE
YOU'RE REALLY
THE REINCARNATED KENTEI?
- BUT I AM.
AND DON'T THINK
I AM SO INSIGNIFICANT
TO MERELY HAVE POWER
THROUGH SUCCESSION.
I ASSURE YOU,
I AM THE TRUE EMPEROR
OF THIS WORLD.
AND AS SUCH,
I HAVE USED MY POWERS
TO TRANSCEND TIME.
- ( laughs )
EMPEROR OR NOT,
YOU CAN'T EXPECT
US TO TRUST YOU
UNLESS YOU SHOW US
WHAT'S HIDDEN
UNDER THAT MASK OF YOURS.
- I HAVE NO FACE.
ONLY AN UNFATHOMABLE DARKNESS
LIES BENEATH THIS MASK.
IF YOU WISH TO SEE IT,
YOU MUST BE PREPARED
AND WILLING
TO ENTER THIS
DARKNESS YOURSELF.
- REGARDLESS OF WHO
KENTEI REALLY IS,
I WON'T FAIL IN TAKING
RYUUBI'S HEAD AGAIN.
- BE AWARE.
SEITO'S TACTICIAN
SHOULD ALREADY BE PLANNING
THEIR NEXT ATTACK.
THEREFORE,
HERE IS WHERE YOU COME IN.
- ( growls )
- Chou'un: NOW THAT IT'S CLEAR
THAT THE ENEMY IS NANBAN HIGH,
I'M ALMOST POSITIVE
THEY PLAN TO MAKE A MOVE
TO CONQUER ALL OF
THE KANTO REGION.
- YES, BUT I ONLY WISH
WE HAD A CLUE
AS TO WHO THIS
KENTEI REALLY IS.
THE NEXT TIME THAT FIGHTER
ATTACKS GENTOKU,
WE CAN'T LET HER GET AWAY.
THE COST WOULD
BE TOO GREAT.
- AND NO MATTER WHAT,
WE MUSTN'T UNDERESTIMATE
THE FIGHTER CALLED MOUYUU.
I SENSE THAT SHE IS
THE DANGEROUS TYPE
WHO ONLY BECOMES
MORE FIERCE AND DEADLY
AS THE BATTLE RAGES ON.
- IF THAT IS INDEED TRUE,
THEN THAT'S ALL
THE MORE REASON
TO AVOID A DIRECT
CONFRONTATION WITH THEM.
WITHOUT HAVING KAN'U AND CHOUHI
HERE AT HOME WITH US,
WE CANNOT HOPE TO COMPETE
ON THE MERITS
OF OUR STRENGTH ALONE.
- ( girl panting )
KAN'U, YOU WITH ME?
( continues panting )
DON'T LEAVE ME HANGING.
WE'RE NOT DEAD YET.
- Ekitoku: KAN'U! KAN'U!
HEY, ARE YOU AWAKE YET?
- ( gasps )
- HEARTLESS BASTARDS!
YOU GUYS LIKE TO
PLAY DIRTY, DON'T YOU?!
- DIRTY OR NOT, SWEETHEART,
IF IT HELPS ME WIN,
I DON'T GIVE A CRAP
WHAT YOU THINK.
- TOO BAD.
LOOKS LIKE RAKUYO'S KAYUU
IS GOING TO CRUSH THOSE TWO.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS SEITO THINKING ONLY
SENDING THOSE TWO AS BACKUP?
- YUP, KAYUU'S DEFINITELY
GONNA KILL THOSE TWO FOR SURE.
- ( chains clink )
- ( groans )
- Both: HI'YAH!
- ( grunts, groaning )
- EKITOKU!
IS THIS...
- KAN'U, TRY TO STAY BACK.
I'M OKAY.  THESE GUYS
ARE NO PROBLEM.
MY OPPONENT IS STILL
MY OPPONENT UNTIL I FALL.
AM I RIGHT?
- EKITOKU!
- WELL, THAT'S NOT GONNA BE
FOR MUCH LONGER,
YOU CRAZY BITCH!
- ( screams )
- Kayuu: "UNTIL SHE FALLS."
WELL, THERE YOU HAVE IT.
SHE'S DONE.
- NICE JOB, BOSS.
( laughs )
- KAN'U, I'M NOT DONE.
I CAN STILL FIGHT.
I PROMISE.
AFTER ALL, I AM UNCHO KAN'U'S
YOUNGER SISTER, RIGHT?
I REALLY CAN'T AFFORD
TO EMBARRASS YOU, YOU KNOW?
- YOU NEVER...
- ( strains )
WELL THEN, COME ON,
YOU STUPID BASTARDS!
EVEN IF I SPILL MY GUTS,
EKITOKU CHOUHI
WON'T BE LOSING
TO THE LIKES
OF SCUM LIKE YOU!
- WELL, IF YOU'RE
READY AND WILLING,
WHY DON'T I JUST SPILL 'EM
FOR YOU RIGHT NOW?
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- ( gasps )
- ( boys gasping )
- ( grunts )
DAMN IT.
- KAYUU, YOU'RE NOT
HURT TOO BAD, ARE YOU?
- All: ( gasping )
- UNFORGIVEABLE.
HOW DARE YOU
HURT MY SISTER.
MOCK MY SISTER.
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY
WITH YOUR LIFE!
- ( whimpering )
- Kan'u: TAKE THIS GIFT FROM ME
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
THE NAME OF THE GOD OF DEATH
WHO WILL BE YOUR DESTRUCTION.
MY NAME IS--
MY NAME IS...
- OH.
KAN'U.  OH, GOOD,
YOU'RE FINALLY AWAKE.
- IS THAT YOU, EKITOKU?
- WELL, YEAH.
WHO ELSE WOULD IT BE?
OH, WAIT A SECOND.
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOU, ISN'T THERE?
- I CAN'T SEE YOUR FACE.
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
- WELL, I'M RIGHT HERE.
I PROMISE I'M NOT
GOING ANYWHERE.
- AWW, GEEZ!
( squeaking )
- HEY, WHAT NOW?
- UH...
I CAN'T HOLD IT ANYMORE!
- HUH?
- AWW! HURRY! HURRY! HURRY!
I'M GONNA BURST!
HURRY UP! HURRY UP!
YES!
HUH?
( pants )
OKAY, YOU CAN LOOK AWAY NOW,
YOU PERVS.
( sighs )
( urinating )
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- ( trilling )
- HMM?
- ( Bachou screams )
- Both: HUH?
- SHE'S AT IT AGAIN.
- SO WHAT IS IT
THIS TIME?
- GO! GET AWAY FROM ME!
( whimpering )
( screaming )
HUH? OH!
WHOA! WHAT THE--
ARE YOU KIDNAPPING ME?!
- HUH? HEY!
YOU FORGOT TO
TAKE ME WITH YOU!
- ( boys sigh )
- Bachou: SO ITCHY!
THAT'S PROBABLY GONNA
LEAVE A SCAR TOO.
BUG BITES ALL OVER THE PLACE
AND A SNAKE WHEN
I'M TRYING TO PEE,
THIS REALLY ISN'T MY DAY.
( whines )
AND YOU.
SAY SOMETHING ALREADY.
WHY DON'T YOU
SAY SOMETHING LIKE
"THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT"
OR "YOU IDIOT"?
- YOU IDIOT.
- ( gasps )
( growls )
( screams )
OKAY, FINE,
I GOT BEAT DURING THE RAID
AND I GOT TAKEN HOSTAGE
WHILE ON THE SHIP
BACK THERE TOO,
BUT MASTER'S SPECIAL TRAINING
HAS TURNED ME INTO
A WHOLE NEW PERSON.
AND IF I FELT LIKE IT,
I BET I COULD EASILY
TAKE YOU ON
IN A ONE-ON-ONE FIGHT!
- OH, REALLY?
- ( huffs )
SO THEN WHY DID YOU
DECIDE TO SAVE ME?
- BECAUSE IF I HADN'T,
YOU WOULD'VE DIED.
- ARE YOU SAYING
THAT I'M A WEAKLING?
- WELL, NO.
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
- AND YOU DID
THE SAME EXACT THING
BACK WHEN WE FOUGHT
AT KYOSHO, DIDN'T YOU?
PUT 'EM UP!
WE'LL PICK BACK UP WHERE
WE LEFT OFF LAST TIME.
WELL, PUT 'EM UP!
I WON'T BE SATISFIED
UNTIL WE FIGHT
IT ALL OUT.
- I'M SORRY,
BUT THERE'S NO POINT.
- HUH?
D-- DON'T MOCK ME!
HI'YAH!
HEY, COME ON.
WHY DO YOU KEEP
RUNNING AWAY FROM ME?
ARE YOU TRYING TO TELL ME
THAT I'M NOT EVEN
WORTH THE EFFORT, HUH?!
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs )
- WELL, I GUESS
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU KEEP TRYING
TO RUN AWAY FROM ME.
SO DO YOU GIVE UP NOW?
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN STRUGGLE ALL YOU WANT,
BUT IT'LL JUST MAKE YOU
SINK DEEPER AND DEEPER.
UH, ( nervous laugh )
HEY, STOP PRETENDING.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE
REALLY SCARED.
WHY DON'T YOU SAY SOMETHING?!
UH...
OH, FOR CRYING OUT LOUD,
TAKE MY HAND.
- YOU GO.
ESCAPE ON YOUR OWN.
- HUH?
- IF YOU TRY TO HELP ME,
YOU'LL END UP
SINKING DOWN HERE AS WELL.
- WHAT THE--
YOU DO REALIZE
YOUR LIFE IS IN
REAL DANGER, DON'T YOU?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- OH, NEVER MIND WHY!
HURRY, GRAB MY HAND.
UH, I WON'T TELL YOU
TO FIGHT ME ANYMORE!
HERE.
NOW HOLD ON TIGHT, OKAY?
( strains )
COME ON!
( grunts )
( pants, sighs )
WELL, I THINK WE CAN SAY
WE'RE EVEN NOW.
I OWE YOU NOTHING.
HUH?
- THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
- THANK YOU TOO,
I GUESS.
- SO THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
- AFTER YOU FELL
INTO THE OCEAN,
I JUMPED IN
RIGHT AFTER YOU,
BUT THE CURRENT
WAS TOO POWERFUL.
AND THAT'S HOW THE TWO OF US
MANAGED TO WASH UP ON SHORE.
EVEN THOUGH THOUGH
WE'RE LOST ON SOME ISLAND,
WE'RE SURE LUCKY.
- THIS ISN'T FAIR.
YOU'RE ALWAYS
SAVING MY LIFE.
- DON'T BE LIKE THAT.
AFTER ALL,
YOU AND I ARE SWORN SISTERS,
AREN'T WE?
WE LIVE TOGETHER
AND WE DIE TOGETHER.
- ( chuckles )
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
- ( metal whirs )
- WHAT THE--
- ( metal clinks )
- EKITOKU!
- ( metal whirs )
( clinks )
- WHO'S OUT THERE?!
( grunts )
DAMN.  KAN'U, MAKE SURE
YOU STAY WHERE YOU ARE.
- WAIT, DON'T GO OUT THERE!
- ( screams )
( screaming echoes )
- Moukaku: HOW SAD.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR PARTNER'S
ABOUT TO BITE THE DUST.
IF SHE MEANS
ANYTHING TO YOU,
THEN GIVE YOURSELF UP
WITH OUT A STRUGGLE.
- EKITOKU, CAN YOU
STILL HEAR ME?
- OOH, THAT'S A DANGEROUS
LITTLE STICK
YOU'VE GOT THERE,
BUT YOU DON'T EVEN LOOK
LIKE YOU CAN STAND
ON YOUR OWN TWO FEET.
ARE YOU SURE YOU CAN FIGHT?
- Ekitoku: KAN'U!
DON'T FIGHT.
I CAN STILL--
( gasping )
I CAN STILL FIGHT HER.
- NO, NOT AGAIN.
YOU CAN'T FIGHT.
- Moukaku: WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU GONNA LET THIS
HALF-DEAD ONE FIGHT,
YOU FUCKING IDIOT?
- I WON'T FIGHT.
I SURRENDER.
I'LL DO AS YOU SAY.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS
TO MY PRIDE,
I CAN'T LET EKITOKU DIE.
- HUH? SO YOU GAVE UP
BECAUSE YOUR FRIEND'S LIFE
MEANS MORE THAN YOUR PRIDE.
- THIS ONE IS MY OPPONENT.
IT'S MY OPPONENT UNTIL I FALL
AND I WON'T FALL.
- Kan'u: EKITOKU CHOUHI,
YOU ARE
MY GREATEST PRIDE,
MY PRECIOUS SISTER,
FOR ALL ETERNITY,
UNTIL THE END OF TIME.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Koukin:
RYOMOU, NANBAN HIGH IS LIKE
SOME KINGDOM
DEEP IN THE JUNGLE.
ISN'T THAT A LITTLE WEIRD?
- YES, IT IS.
BUT YOU CAN THINK OF IT
AS TAKING OUR SCHOOL TRIP
A BIT EARLY THIS YEAR.
- HOW ARE YOU TAKING THIS
SO WELL?
WE DON'T EVEN GET
CELL PHONE RECEPTION HERE.
- WHAT?! YOU MEAN I CAN'T
EVEN SEND TEXT MESSAGES?!
WE SHOULD GO HOME!
RIGHT NOW!
- UM, IN CASE YOU FORGOT,
WE'RE BEING HELD CAPTIVE.
NEXT TIME ON "IKKI TOUSEN,
XTREME XECUTOR,"
"SWARMING FANGS."