- ( train approaching )
- ( punch landing )
- ( grunts )
- COME ON, LET'S GO!
LET'S KILL THESE PUNKS!
- COME ON, LET'S DO THIS!
- THEY'RE GONNA FIGHT.
- ( shouts )
- ( grunts )
- Koukin: RYOMOU!
- AAH!
- WHERE THE HELL HAS
OUR LEADER GONE?
- SHE GOT OFF THE TRAIN
TO GET SOME SWEET JELLY
AT NAGOYA STATION
AND THEN I LOST HER.
- THAT IDIOT!
- YOSHO ACADEMY,
RAKUYO HIGH, KYOSHO...
WHAT ARE THEY ALL DOING HERE?
- I GUESS THEY'RE PROBABLY HERE
FOR THE SAME REASON WE ARE.
WE CAN'T STAY HERE.
LET'S GO!
- RIGHT!
- QUITE SCHOOL TRIP
THIS HAS TURNED OUT TO BE.
- ( humming )
- HEY!
- HUH?
- WHATCHA READING, GENTOKU?
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS THING?
- I PUT IT TOGETHER
THIS MORNING.
- Koumei: INTERESTING.
- UH...
- SERIOUSLY.
- YOU GUYS ARE READING
THIS CRAP TOO?!
SHOULDN'T YOU BE TRAINING
INSTEAD OF DOING
CREATIVE WRITING PROJECTS?!
WHICH REMINDS ME,
WHERE IS KAN'U?
AAH!  THINKING MAKES
MY BRAIN HURT!
- CHOUHI, YOU HAVE NO BRAIN.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
- HERE, I MADE A COPY
FOR YOU TOO.
- KAN'U ISN'T HERE.
SHE'S OUT SEARCHING
THE SURROUNDING AREA.
- OH, I SEE.
SO HOW MANY OF THOSE
STUPID BOOKS DID YOU
DECIDE TO BRING WITH YOU?
WE'RE ONLY GOING TO BE HERE
FOR THREE DAYS.
- Announcer: ATTENTION
PATRONS OF KYOTO STATION...
- ( people screaming )
- ...A CONFLICT HAS BROKEN OUT
INSIDE THE STATION,
INVOLVING KANTO FIGHTERS.
THE SITUATION IS
EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
THE STATION STAFF
WILL DIRECT YOU TO SAFETY.
- WHAT THE--?!
- OH!
- NANYO, KYOSHO.
- WHY ARE THEY HERE?
- SEITO!
- Kyosho student:
SEITO STUDENTS!
- YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO, RIGHT?
- YEAH, I KNOW.
GET THEM!
- ( men shouting )
- ( chuckles )
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
- LOOKS LIKE
THEY REALLY WANNA FIGHT.
- LEADER, YOU AND KOUMEI
GO UPSTAIRS.
WE'LL HANDLE THINGS DOWN HERE.
- YOU CAN I CAN TAKE CARE
OF THEM MYSELF.
- ENGAGING THEM IN BATTLE
WOULD MAKE YOU MISS YOUR BUS.
- WELL, I'LL TAKE CARE OF
THOSE TWO UP THERE.
BEFORE THE REST
EVEN GET CLOSE.
- Rikuson: SEITO'S HERE TOO?
IT'S NO DIFFERENT
FROM BEING BACK IN KANTO.
- NO WAY THIS IS A COINCIDENCE.
FEELS LIKE A SETUP.
- Koukin: GAKUSHU!
- AH, YOU'RE OKAY.
- DID YOU HAPPEN TO SEE
OUR STUPID LEADER ANYWHERE?
- NO.
YOU HAVEN'T FOUND HER, EITHER?
- MAYBE SHE GOT LEFT BEHIND
IN NAGOYA STATION.
- IF SHE DID,
FORGET ABOUT HER.
- ( both gasp )
- AAH!
- KAKOUEN?
- ( groans )
- GOD ON HIGH IS ALMIGHTY.
IT'S HIS DIVINE JUDGMENT
THAT IS ABSOLUTE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
LEAVE AT ONCE.
- ( grunts )
- AAH!
- ANYONE HAVE A PLAN?
- GAKUSHU!
I'M ON MY WAY!
- THOSE WHO STAND IN MY WAY
SHALL BE JUDGED WITHOUT MERCY.
- ( groaning )
- ( slightly gasping )
- ( shouts )
- WE'LL SETTLE THIS IN KANTO.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- THAT WAS AWESOME.
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
IT'S NOT SAFE.
- All: MM.
- EKITOKU!
- HUH?
- Ryomou: SEITO ACADEMY?
- Soujin: HOLD IT!
I CAN'T ALLOW YOU
TO BEAT UP OUR CLASSMATES.
- Ekitoku:
WELL, YOU GUYS STARTED IT!
- UH... NO.
THIS ALL STARTED
BECAUSE NANYO CAME LOOKING
FOR TROUBLE.
- Ryomou: STOP YOUR BICKERING.
NONE OF US HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
WE ALL HAVE OTHER THINGS TO DO.
- Ekitoku: NO ARGUMENTS HERE.
I MEAN, WE'RE RIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF
OUR SHUUGAKU TRIP.
- WHAT'S A SHUUGAKU TRIP?
- UH... ( stammering )
- GENTOKU, OVER THERE.
KYOTO... FIGHTERS.
- GREETINGS, KANTO FIGHTERS!
WE JUST WANTED TO
WELCOME YOU TO KYOTO!
- All: HIP HIP, HOORAY!
- LET'S ALL TAKE CARE
OF THE WELCOME WAGON FIRST.
- COUNT ME IN!
- LIKE WE HAVE A CHOICE.
- ATTACK!
- ( men shouting )
- Announcer: A MAJOR CONFLICT
BETWEEN KANTO AND KYOTO FIGHTERS
HAS BROKEN OUT
NEAR THE MAIN STAIRWAY.
THE SITUATION IS
EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
STATION MANAGEMENT REQUESTS
YOU KEEP YOUR DISTANCE.
- THE SHUUGAKU CLASS TRIP.
A TRAINING JOURNEY
EMBARKED UPON
DURING THE BIG FIGHTERS'
TOURNAMENT
TO REPLENISH THE SPIRITUAL
ENERGY OF THE SACRED BEADS.
KYOTO, THE GREATEST CITY
OF SPIRITS IN ALL OF JAPAN--
IT'S HOME TO MANY FIGHTERS,
ALL WHO CARRY THE SPIRITS OF THE
GREATEST WARRIOR GENERALS.
THEY CARRY TSUBA,
OR SAMURAI SWORD HAND GUARDS,
WHICH ARE CONNECTED
TO OUR SACRED BEADS.
THE MORE FIGHTERS
THEY DEFEAT IN BATTLE,
THE MORE TSUBA
THEY COLLECT.
IT IS HOPED THAT
THE SHUUGAKU JOURNEY
WILL FOSTER IMMENSE GROWTH
AND ABUNDANT MEMORIES
TO ALL FIGHTERS
THAT PARTICIPATE.
( chuckles )
I WISH I COULD SAY
THAT I AGREE.
- THE TRAVEL AGENCY SCREWED UP.
THE RESERVATIONS FOR US ARE
ALL WRONG.
DON'T WORRY. I MADE SURE
THEY FIXED OUR ITINERARY.
BESIDES, YOU DON'T LOOK
QUITE YOURSELF.
- THANKS A LOT.
I PREFER TO SETTLE
OUR ISSUES WITH KANTO
IN KANTO.
- ( deeply sighs )
- HMM?
- BARELY MADE IT.
HMM?
HUH?
TON-CHAN.
AAH.
- HMM.
FOR YOU.
- ( screams )
- LET'S GO.
- UH, SURE.
LATER.
- Announcer:
WE REPEAT-- TO ALL PATRONS,
A FIGHT BETWEEN KANTO
AND KYOTO FIGHTERS
HAS BROKEN OUT
NEAR THE MAIN STAIRWAY.
THE SITUATION IS
EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
WE ASK YOU, PLEASE
KEEP YOUR DISTANCE.
- ( jingles )
- THESE ARE THE SOULS OF
SAMURAI WARRIOR GENERALS?
RYOMA SAKAMOTO WOULD CRY.
- RYOMA SAKAMOTO WASN'T
A WARRIOR GENERAL.
- FALL BACK!
- YOU GUYS ARE RUNNING AWAY?
I KNOW YOU'RE TERRIFIED
OF ME, BUT COME ON!
- I SMELL SMOKE.
- ( all gasp )
- PUSH!
- TAKE COVER!
- THIS IS BAD!
- Ryuubi: KAN'U!
- WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?!
WHERE WERE YOU?!
- KYOTO STATION...
IS VERY BIG.
- YOU GOT LOST?
- KAN'U!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- OH-- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- I THINK KAN'U IS EXCITED.
- IN MORE WAYS THAN ONE.
- SORRY FOR TAKING SO LONG.
HERE'S MY APOLOGY...
- ( jingles )
- Ryomou: A SINGLE STRIKE.
KAN'U REALLY IS THAT GOOD.
- HI!
- HAKUFU!
- HEY, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- I HAD TO PEE.
DID I JUST MISS SOMETHING?
WHERE'S THE FIGHT?
WHERE'S THE BATTLE?
- IT JUST ENDED.
- HUH?!
- 'CAUSE YOU'RE A STUPID LEADER!
- HEY!
YOU KNOW THE ONE WHO SAYS
STUPID FIRST IS REALLY STU--
- STUPID STUPID STUPID STUPID!
( echoing )
- SO THIS IS A TSUBA.
HOW MANY DID YOU COLLECT,
KOUKIN?
- I'D SAY ABOUT 15 MAYBE.
BUT GAKUSHU AND RYOMOU HAVE
COLLECTED A LOT MORE OF THEM
THAN I HAVE.
- BUT IT'S NOT WORTH THE TROUBLE
IF YOU GET KILLED REPLENISHING
YOUR SPIRITUAL ENERGY.
- MOU-CHAN, IT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU HAVE SO MANY TSUBA.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE
JUST ONE OF THEM YET.
- THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU GO OFF ON YOUR OWN.
- LET'S SING, MOU-CHAN.
IT'S OUR SCHOOL TRIP.
- WILL YOU PAY ATTENTION!
- IS THAT SEITO'S GUIDEBOOK?
- YEAH.  IT SEEMS WE BOTH USED
THE SAME TRAVEL AGENT,
SO OUR SCHEDULES OVERLAP
QUITE A BIT.
NEXT IS...
HUH?
THERE THEY ARE.
- IT'S RYU-CHAN.
HI, GUYS!
- MISS SONSAKU!  HI!
WE'LL WAIT FOR YOU!
- ( groans )
HEY, DRIVER!
GO FASTER!
- OH, NO.
THEY PASSED US.
- PLEASE, DON'T DISAPPOINT
OUR LEADER.
- YES.
- OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
COME ON, HURRY UP!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
- I FEEL SICK.
SLOW DOWN OR I'M GONNA THROW UP.
- DO NOT BACK DOWN.
THE FIRST OF US TO BACK DOWN
WILL LOSE THE FIGHT.
- KAN'U, WE'RE GOING TOO FAST.
IT'S WAY TOO DANGEROUS.
- EKITOKU, YOU WOULD DARE ACCEPT
DEFEAT FROM PATHETIC NANYO?
- NO, I WOULDN'T WANT THAT,
BUT--
- I DO NOT WISH TO SEE
OUR LEADER DISTRESSED OUR UPSET.
THAT WOULD AFFECT
OUR TEAM SPIRIT.
I HAVE SWORN UPON MY LIFE
NOT TO ALLOW ANYONE
OR ANYTHING TO HARM GENTOKU.
- UH, KAN'U?
- ( exhales )
- ( gasps )
WHY IS SHE SLEEPING?
- IT'S IN HER NATURE.
- Ekitoku: KAN'U!
- NEVER BACK DOWN!
- Koukin: HAKUFU, STOP IT!
- GO!
- NOW I'M REALLY SICK.
- AAH!
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
- OWWIE!
- PLEASE TRY TO CALM YOURSELF,
KAN'U.
WE'RE HERE TO COLLECT TSUBA.
WE CAN'T AFFORD THIS SORT
OF BEHAVIOR.
- THAT'S TRUE.
FORGIVE ME.
- BESIDES,
YOU'LL SOON ENOUGH HAVE YOUR
CHANCE TO FIGHT, I PROMISE.
- Hakufu: WOW!
A REAL SAMURAI TOWN!
- Ryomou:
TRY TO CONTROL YOURSELF.
- Koukin: LOOKS LIKE
NO ONE'S HERE.
- WE HAVE THE WHOLE PLACE
TO OURSELVES.
IT SAYS THAT UNTIL MIDNIGHT,
SPIRITS THAT WERE UNABLE
TO FIND FIGHTERS TO POSSESS
WILL ROAM THE STREETS.
- SPIRITS?
YOU MEAN GHOSTS, RIGHT?
- "DEFEATING A SPIRIT DOES NOT
EARN A TSUBA,
SO USE CAUTION.
HIDDEN SOMEWHERE IN TOWN IS
A GIANT TSUBA
THAT CONTROLS
ALL OF THE OTHERS.
AVOID THEIR ATTACKS
AS YOU SEARCH EVERY CORNER.
BE CAREFUL AND GOOD LUCK."
THIS GUIDEBOOK SURE IS HANDY.
- WELL, IT DOES POSSESS
A LEVEL OF DETAIL
THAT OUR LEADER CERTAINLY LACKS.
- YEAH, AND THAT'S NOT ALL
THAT SHE LACKS.
- ONE GIANT TSUBA.
WE SHOULD GET MOVING
BEFORE IT'S DARK.
YOU'RE STILL NOT HEALED.
STAY HERE AND REST.
- THANK YOU, RYOMOU.
- I PROMISE
TO TAKE CARE OF HIM.
- PLEASE DO.
WE CAN'T LET SEITO
GET THE JUMP ON US.
WE'LL SPLIT UP AND SEARCH.
- THAT'S A GREAT PLAN.
- WHEN DID MOU-CHAN
BECOME OUR LEADER?
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- INTERESTING.
IT SEEMS YOU REACT TO
THE PRESENCE OF FIGHTERS.
BUT YOU MUST KNOW
I'VE FOUGHT FISTS
MUCH SHARPER THAN YOUR BLADE!
- ( grunts ) -
YOU WON'T FIND A SUITABLE BODY!
HA!
- ( shouts )
- BACK WHERE YOU CAME FROM!
( gasps )
THE TSUBA MUST BE
THAT DIRECTION.
- I THOUGHT I RECOGNIZED
YOUR PRESENCE.
FOUND WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR?
- AAH!
- CHOU'UN, YOU PUT ON
QUITE A SHOW.
- THANK YOU. BUT THEY WERE
HARDLY WORTHY ADVERSARIES.
IT WAS DISAPPOINTING.
- MERELY WANDERING SPIRITS
WITHOUT BODIES.
THEY ARE NO MATCH FOR US.
- I CONCUR.
OUR COMMON ADVERSARY IS
ELSEWHERE.
- I'M GOING AFTER IT.
- I WON'T LET YOU.
- THE CONTROLLING TSUBA IS
PROBABLY BEYOND THERE.
RIGHT?  ISN'T THAT WHAT
YOU AND I ARE BOTH LOOKING FOR?
- WE ARE LOOKING FOR
THE CONTROLLING TSUBA,
BUT ALL THAT MATTERS IS
FOR ONE OF US TO FIND IT.
IF YOU TRUST IN YOUR FRIENDS,
YOUR PATH BECOMES CLEAR.
I'M SURE THAT YOU FEEL
THE SAME WAY.
- ( both grunting )
- YOU WILL REMAIN HERE,
QUIETLY UNTIL MIDNIGHT.
OR UNTIL ONE OF MY FRIENDS
COLLECTS THE CONTROLLING TSUBA.
- DO YOU REALLY PLACE
THAT MUCH TRUST IN YOUR FRIENDS?
- ( scoffs )
WHY, YOU DON'T
TRUST YOUR FRIENDS?
- I ABSOLUTELY DO NOT.
SONSAKU'S IRRESPONSIBLE,
CARELESS AND STUPID.
SHE'S UNRELIABLE,
INCREDIBLY GULLIBLE,
AND DID I SAY STUPID?
SHE'S A STUPID GIRL
WHO USES THE WORD STUPID
LIKE IT'S THE ONLY ONE
SHE KNOWS.
I'M ASHAMED TO
CALL HER LEADER.
- HMM.
- YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW MUCH TROUBLE
SHE'S CAUSED ME.
HOW CAN I TRUST HER
TO FIND THAT TSUBA?
SHE'S COMPLETELY HELPLESS
WITHOUT ME AND SHUYUU.
THAT'S WHY!
I CAN'T REMAIN HERE QUIETLY!
- QUITE A CHALLENGE.
- I LIKE A CHALLENGE.
- I WON'T GO EASY.
- I KNOW.
- ( both grunting )
- NINJA?!
- ( Koukin grunts )
- KOUKIN, YOU'RE AWESOME.
WHEN DID YOU LEARN TO BE
SUCH A STRONG FIGHTER?
- AW, COME ON!
THERE'S MORE THAN WE EXPECTED.
RYOMOU MIGHT BE IN DANGER.
- SHE'LL BE FINE.
MOU-CHAN WILL NEVER BE
DEFEATED BY THIS.
- LOOKS LIKE THIS IS THE PLACE.
- IT APPEARS SO.
THANKS TO YOUR IMPATIENCE,
WE SEEM TO BE
THE FIRST ONES HERE.
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasps )
- ( roars )
- FORWARD ATTACK?
- HER RIGHT ARM.
( grunts )
- ( grunts )
MY SHEATH.
- ( grunting, exhales )
JOINT LOCK.
( groans )
( groaning )
- ( both groaning )
- JUST GIVE UP.
- ( all gasp )
- Hakufu: MOU-CHAN!
- Ryuubi: SHIRYUU!
- ( traffic sounds )
- I'M AN "A"-RANKED FIGHTER.
WHY AM I DOING MANUAL LABOR?
- KEEP QUIET.
REPAIRING THE DAMAGE
WE'VE ALL DONE IS
THE LEAST WE CAN DO.
- I'M KIND OF ENJOYING THIS.
- HEY!  HOW COME OUR LEADER
ISN'T HELPING OUT WITH THIS?
HE SHOULD BE DOWN HERE.
- ( grumbles )
WELL, THEY--
HE'S RECUPERATING.
- Sousou:
KYOTO'S A PLACE THAT'S SEEN
CONTINUOUS BLOODSHED
FOR 1200 YEARS,
FROM THE HEIAN PERIOD
UNTIL THE FALL OF THE SHOGUNATE.
THIS CITY HAS BEEN INFESTED,
TEEMING WITH ALL SORTS
OF MONSTERS AND MURDERERS.
NO WONDER IT MAKES
OUR SACRED BEADS DANCE.
I WONDER-- THE FIGHTERS
I KILLED AT SEKIHEKI...
ARE THEIR SPIRITS
WANDERING ABOUT IN CHINA?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- IF IT'S GOD'S WILL,
THEN IT SHALL BE THEIR FATE.
- WELL THEN, SHALL WE GO
HAVE SOME FUN?
- HEY, YOU!
WE'RE HERE TO THANK
YOU FOR BEING SO GOOD
TO OUR YOUNGER BROTHERS.
- SO, DO YOU THINK TON WOULD
MIND TOO MUCH IF WE FOUGHT HERE?
- ( exhales )
- ( gasps )
YOU'RE AWAKE!
MOU-CHAN, WE FOUND YOU
AND SHI-CHAN FROM SEITO
LYING TOGETHER ON THE GROUND.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
- RYU-CHAN AND THE OTHERS
TOOK HER AWAY.
APPARENTLY SHE WAS
UNCONSCIOUS TOO.
- UNCONSCIOUS?
BOTH OF US WERE BADLY INJURED
IN THE BATTLE,
BUT BEFORE I PASSED OUT,
I SAW A DRAGON ON THE POND.
AND I REMEMBER THE BIG TSUBA.
WHAT HAPPENED TO IT?
DID YOU GET IT?
- IT WAS PAST MIDNIGHT.
SO THE SPIRIT WAS LONG GONE
BY THE TIME WE GOT THERE.
I THINK IT'S POSSIBLE
YOU WERE BOTH HEALED BY
THE EFFECTS OF
THE SPIRIT ENERGY.
I TALKED TO THE STRATEGIST
FROM SEITO ACADEMY
AND THAT'S WHAT SHE THOUGH
MIGHT HAVE HAPPENED.
- THAT'S KOU-CHAN.
- UM, YEAH, THAT'S HER.
SO THAT MEANS NOW
THE BOTH OF YOU HAVE
A LOT MORE SPIRITUAL ENERGY.
- SO I SEE.
- I'M SO JEALOUS OF YOU,
MOU-CHAN.
I HAVEN'T ACCUMULATED
ANY SPIRITUAL ENERGY YET.
- THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE LAZY,
SONSAKU.
- YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND NOW IT'S TIME FOR BED.
- HOLD ON.
WHY ARE BOTH YOU GUYS
ROLLING OUT YOUR FUTONS
IN HERE?
AREN'T YOU IN SEPARATE ROOMS?
- OH, COME ON, MOU-CHAN.
THIS IS OUR SCHOOL TRIP,
WHICH MEANS WE GET TO SPEND
ALL NIGHT TALKING ABOUT BOYS.
- TALK ABOUT B-BOYS?
- WE NEED TO KNOW, PLEASE.
- Both: PLEASE!
- ( sighs )
- Gakushu: I'M HEALED!
- SUCH A FAST RECOVERY.
KYOTO'S AMAZING.
THE OLD TOWN HAD MANY SPIRITS,
BUT THERE SHOULD BE EVEN MORE
SCATTERED THROUGHOUT THE CITY.
- INTERESTING.
ESPECIALLY SINCE KYOTO HAS
A LOT LESS PEOPLE THAN TOKYO.
THERE MIGHT EVEN BE MORE TSUBA
HIDING OUT THERE FOR US TO FIND.
- THE QUESTION IS:
HOW DO WE FIND THEM?
- WHAT DOES THE GUIDEBOOK SAY
ABOUT IT?
- IT SAYS...
- Ryuubi:
I THINK SHIRYUU FELL ASLEEP.
THAT'S GOOD.
- WE SHOULD GET TO SLEEP TOO.
WE HAD A REALLY LONG DAY.
- YES, WE DID.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYONE.
SLEEP TIGHT.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- MM.
- GOOD NIGHT, EVERYONE.
- I'M TURNING THE LIGHTS OFF.
- I'M TOO WORKED UP TO SLEEP.
( exhales )
GENTOKU.
SHE'S ALREADY ASLEEP.
- ( giggles )
I'M STILL AWAKE.
- OH, REALLY?
- IT'S SO WEIRD.
TURNING OFF THE LIGHTS
ALWAYS MAKES ME FEEL MORE AWAKE.
KAN'U, WOULD YOU MIND IF
WE TALKED FOR A WHILE?
MAYBE THAT WOULD HELP.
- SURE.  YOU AND I CAN TALK
IF YOU LIKE.
- THAT'S AWESOME!
IT JUST WOULDN'T FEEL
LIKE A REAL SCHOOL TRIP
WITHOUT A LITTLE GIRL TALK
UNDER THE COVERS.
- EKITOKU, STAYING UP LATE IS
BAD FOR YOUR COMPLEXION.
- HUH?
- ( moans )
I'M COLD.
- ( laughs )
- Ryuubi: KOUMEI...
( giggles )
THAT TICKLES.
- GENTOKU, YOU'RE SO WARM.
- KOUMEI, PLEASE.
THAT'S AGAINST SCHOOL RULES.
- UH...
- I WANNA GO SHOPPING
FOR SOUVENIRS.
WHAT'S KYOTO KNOWN FOR?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?!
DON'T YOU KNOW THAT SOUVENIRS
ARE JUST JUNK
THEY SELL TO STUPID TOURISTS?!
- ( sighs )
THEN WHAT SHOULD I BUY?
I'D BE HAPPY WITH
ANY GIFT FROM YOU.
I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
- WHY WOULD BE
EXPECTING A GIFT?
- YOU COULD TAKE ME HOME
AS A GIFT.
- KOUMEI!
WHY ARE THE TWO OF YOU
ACTING SO WEIRD?
- ( Shiryuu chuckling )
- SHIRYUU, DID WE WAKE YOU?
- OF COURSE.
WOULD ANYONE HERE MIND IF
I JOINED IN THE CONVERSATION?
- THIS FINALLY FEELS LIKE
A REAL SCHOOL TRIP.
EVEN THERE WE'RE ONLY HERE
TO COLLECT TSUBA.
- IT'S KINDA FUNNY, ISN'T IT?
HERE WE ARE, FELLOW FIGHTERS,
ENGAGING IN SOMETHING
AS ORDINARY AS GIRL TALK.
- KAN'U, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- ( sighs )
I WONDER...
WHAT IF I WAS BORN
AN ORDINARY GIRL?
STUDIED AND PLAYED
LIKE AN ORDINARY GIRL?
- ( all gasp )
- LIVED LIKE AN ORDINARY GIRL?
MY LIFE WOULD BE SIMPLE,
PEACEFUL AND FUN.
I WOULDN'T BE
CONSTANTLY IN DANGER
OR WORRYING ABOUT
COLLECTING TSUBA.
I COULD JUST LIVE MY LIFE
FOR ME.
BUT THEN, WOULD I
HAVE MET ALL OF YOU?
IF I HADN'T BEEN BORN
GENTOKU RYUUBI,
WOULD WE HAVE BECOME FRIENDS?
WOULD I HAVE MET YOU,
EKITOKU?
KOUMEI, SHIRYUU?
AND KAN'U?
DO YOU THINK WE WOULD HAVE?
- WHO KNOWS?
- DIFFICULT TO SAY.
- Kan'u: OF COURSE YOU WOULD.
- HMM?
- NO MATTER WHERE YOU WERE
BORN IN THIS WORLD,
MY PLACE IS AT YOUR SIDE.
IT'S JUST THAT AT THIS
PARTICULAR TIME,
WE HAPPENED TO BE BORN
AS KAN'U AND GENTOKU.
THIS SACRED BEADS
MAY INFLUENCE OUR LIVES,
BUT I WON'T ALLOW THEM
TO AFFECT OUR BOND.
NEVER.
WE MAY HAVE BEEN BORN
ON DIFFERENT DAYS,
BUT ON THE DAY THAT WE DIE,
WE WILL DIE TOGETHER.
- OH, KAN'U.
- CAN WE ALL TAKE THAT OATH?
- OF COURSE WE CAN, KOUMEI.
- ( gasps )
YES!
- All: ALL OF PRESENT HERE
DO SOLEMNLY SWEAR
WE MAY HAVE BEEN BORN
ON DIFFERENT DAYS,
BUT ON THE DAY WE DIE,
WE DIE TOGETHER.
- IT'S MORNING!
MOU-CHAN, RIKU-CHIN, WAKE UP!
COME ON, WAKE UP!
LET'S GO GET BREAKFAST!
- ( groans )
BE QUIET!
- ( door slams )
- MOU-CHAN IS SCARY
IN THE MORNING.
SHE'S SCARY
IN THE DAYTIME TOO.
BUT SHE'S SO CUTE
WHEN SHE'S SLEEPING.
OH, GOOD MORNING, KOUKIN.
- GOOD MORNING.
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
- THEY'RE STILL SLEEPING.
PROBABLY STILL EXHAUSTED
FROM YESTERDAY.
THEY'RE NOT TRAINING
HARD ENOUGH.  HMM!
- EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
SINCE YOU DIDN'T
FIGHT WITH THEM.
- I DIDN'T, DID I?
OH, WHATEVER.
I'LL MAKE IT UP TO THEM.
TODAY THEY'LL SEE
MY BEST MOVES.
( gasps )
A GIFT SHOP!
- HE BEST MOVES, HUH?
- WE'LL SEE.
- I NEED TO FIND
SOMETHING NICE FOR CHUUBO.
BUT I'M NOT SURE
WHAT SHE'D LIKE.
HMM?  UGLY.
WHO'D BUY THAT?
- ( grunts )
IT'S YOU AGAIN.
- HUH?  KAN-CHAN, SO YOU'VE
BEEN STAYING HERE TOO?
- DON'T CALL ME THAT.
- HUH?!  WHAT DO YOU MEAN?!
WHY NOT?!
- ( groans )
I'LL TAKE FIVE OF THESE.
- HUH?
YOU'RE BUYING FIVE?
WHAT HORRIBLE PERSON
WOULD WANT THAT AS A GIFT?
- ( grunts )
- AAH!
- HAKUFU!
- BEST TO KEEP HER ON A LEASH,
OR ELSE.
PROBLEM?
- DAMN YOU!
OKAY, THAT DIDN'T WORK.
I MUST BE LOSING
MY SPIRITUAL ENERGY.
- HAKUFU!
- NICE CATCH.
- ( groans )
WHERE'D THAT COME FROM?
- GOOD QUESTION.
I ALWAYS CARRY MY GREEN
DRAGON BLADE WITH ME.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I WAS
TALKING ABOUT AND YOU KNOW IT!
( grunts )
UH-OH.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- AAH!
- HEY, YOU BITCHES!
- ( gasps )
- OUR YOUNGER AND OLDER BROTHERS
WANNA GIVE SOME PAYBACK!
THE ONE WITH
THE GLASSES IS MINE.
- NO!  GENTOKU!
- COMING THROUGH!
- ( gasps )
- TAKE THIS!
- ( screams )
- WHOA!
THAT REALLY DOES FEEL FANTASTIC.
I CAN FEEL GREAT POWER
GROWING WITHIN ME.
IS THIS SPIRITUAL ENERGY?
- COME ON, SPIRITUAL ENERGY
DOESN'T WORK LIKE THAT.
- STUPID GIRL INDEED.
- WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR, HUH?
- TAKE THAT!
- ( groans )
- DID YOU LIKE IT?
HOW ABOUT THIS?
- SHAMEFUL.
SHE ENJOYS INFLICTING VIOLENCE.
SUCH DISGRACE.
- AAH!
- ( exhales, groans )
UNFORGIVEABLE.
- ( men yelling )
- UNFORGIVEABLE!
- KAN-CHAN!
THAT'S TOO MUCH!  STOP!
- DON'T CALL ME KAN-CHAN!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO STARTED THIS.
- ( murmurs )
- STOP!
- GOOD MORNING, EVERYONE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- KAN-CHAN, STOP!
- SILENCE!
- ( grunts, groans )
OKAY, I GET IT.
I DON'T WANNA CAUSE
ANYMORE TROUBLE.
LET'S STOP THE FIGHT
FOR TODAY.
THIS FIGHT HASN'T EVEN
STARTED YET!
HA!
- AAH!
( grunts )
- ( groans )
- OH, NO...
- I'LL KILL YOU.
- Ekitoku:
KAN'U'S GONE TOTALLY CRAZY.
- Ryuubi: WHERE IS SHE?
WE HAVE TO FIND HER.
- THAT WAY.
- WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE?
- ( car horn honking )
- YEP, THERE SHE IS.
- WHERE IS SHE?
- RYOMOU, LOOK AT THIS.
- Reporter:
THIS JUST IN-- A FIGHT
HAS BROKEN OUT IN KYOTO.
IT APPEARS TO HAVE BEEN
INSTIGATED BY FIGHTERS
FROM KANTO.
ACCORDING TO REPORTS...
- SONSAKU'S FAMOUS.
SHE'S ON TV.
- ( groans )
STUPID IDIOT.
- Hakufu:
I SAID I WAS SORRY!
- APOLOGIZE BY DYING!
- ENOUGH!
HA!
AAH!
- HA!
- ( shouts )
SORRY ABOUT THIS!
I'LL HAVE TO PAY YOU BACK.
- ( grunting )
- WELL, THAT DIDN'T WORK.
TAKE THIS!
HA!
( groans )
- YOU CALL THAT FIGHTING?
- ( pole clangs )
- ( gasps )
- YOU CALL YOURSELF
NANYO'S LEADER?
THEN WHY DO YOU REFUSE
TO ATTACK ME DIRECTLY?
- IF THIS IS HOW
NANYO ACADEMY FIGHTS,
THEN YOU ALL MUST BE NOTHING
BUT A BUNCH OF WEAK IDIOTS.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KNOW I'M PRETTY STUPID.
I DON'T HAVE THE STRENGTH OR
THE SKILL TO FIGHT LIKE YOU DO,
BUT I-- I CAN'T--
I CAN'T ALLOW YOU TO CALL
MOU-CHAN OR KOUKIN STUPID TOO!
HOW'S THIS FOR DIRECT?!
- ( groaning )
( shouts )
- ( gasps )
- TAKE THIS!
- ( shouts )
- ( groans )
- ( both grunting )
- ( giggles )
- HMM.
- ( both shouting, grunting )
- ( panting )
( grunts )
I DON'T WANT YOUR SYMPATHY.
- AND I WOULD NEVER GIVE IT.
I CAN BEAT YOU EVEN
WITH ONE EYE CLOSED.
- IS THAT A JOKE?
- UH, NO.
- WELL, IT SUCKED!
- I'M GOING TO KILL YOU.
( groans )
- AHH!
- ( both grunting, groaning )
- HA!
- Ekitoku: UGH.
WHY ARE YOU GUYS HERE?
- WE'RE LOOKING FOR HAKUFU.
- DO YOU THINK THEY'RE UP THERE?
- ( all gasp )
- Ryomou: SONSAKU!
- Koukin: HAKUFU!
- Ryuubi: KAN'U!
- Ekitoku: KAN'U!
- YOU STAY BACK!
- STAY AWAY!
DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE ALMOST DONE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( all murmur )
- ( both grunting )
- HA!
- ( whimpers )
- ( both groan softly )
- KAN'U!
- HAKUFU!
- WHAT IS THAT?
- THE TSUBA!
- BUT WHY?
- IT APPEARS THAT
THE TSUBA RAINED DOWN
IN REACTION TO
THEIR EPIC BATTLE.
I THINK.
- KAN'U.
- ( groans )
KOUKIN...
IS IT BREAKFAST TIME YET?
- ( all sigh )
- HEY.
- All: HUH?
- PLEASE TELL HAKUFU THAT--
THAT THE TWO OF US CAN
SETTLE THIS BACK IN KANTO.
- UNDERSTOOD.
- ( sighs )
- ( exhales )
- I MEAN THIS SINCERELY...
YOU HAVE A REALLY STUPID LEADER.
- Ryomou: YES, WE DO.
- ( traffic sounds )
- SO...
SHALL WE SAY THIS ONE
DOESN'T COUNT?
- SHUT UP.
- KAN'U SEEMS ANGRY.
- QUIET.
- HI, THERE.
I GOT YOU SOMETHING.
- HUH?
- HERE.
- OH.
- WHAT ARE THEY?
- I THOUGHT THEY'D MAKE
GOOD SOUVENIRS
OF OUR SHUUGAKU TRIP
IF WE ALL KEPT ONE.
DO YOU LIKE THEM?
- THEY LOOK PRETTY STUPID.
- THIS IS VERY KIND OF YOU.
I WOULD BE HONORED
TO HAVE ONE.
- ( giggles )
- KOUKIN, DO YOU THINK
THAT BATTLE
MIGHT HAVE MADE ME
STRONGER?
- NOT SURE.
I GUESS WE'LL FIND OUT
WHEN WE GET HOME.
- WHAT YOU REALLY NEED TO DO IS
STRENGTHEN YOUR MIND
AND STOP ACTING LIKE
A STUPID LEADER.
- WHY ARE YOU SO MEAN?
- ( jingling )
- SO NOW I CAN BUILD
MY MUSCLES IN SPIRITUAL POWER
AT THE SAME TIME.
TWO BIRDS, ONE STONE.
- Female announcer:
THE SHINKANSEN FROM HAKATA
AND BOUND FOR TOKYO
WILL BE ARRIVING SHORTLY.
PASSENGERS SHOULD PREPARE TO
BOARD ON THE PLATFORM.
- WE SHOULD GET GOING.
- OKAY.
LET'S GO HOME!
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Girl: LOOK, THE BULLET
TRAIN'S COMING!
- HELLO.
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
- Ekitoku:
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
- Soujin:
WOW, TALK ABOUT COINCIDENCE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I REALIZED I NEVER REPAID YOU
FOR TRYING TO TAKE MY LIFE.
- THAT'S NEWS TO ME.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- UH, YOU GUYS LEFT!
YOU LEFT US THERE ALONE TO FIX
THE DAMAGE OURSELVES!
- NO, NOT HERE.
WE SHOULDN'T FIGHT
ABOUT THIS HERE.
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
I'M COMPLETELY HEALED.
- I FEEL TOTALLY AWESOME!
- WELL, I FEEL MORE AWESOME
THAN YOU.
- HAKUFU!
RYOMOU, PLEASE STOP HER.
HUH?
- LET'S SETTLE OUR ISSUES
WITH KANTO IN KANTO.
- ( whimpering )
- WELL, AS THEY SAY,
HOME IS WHERE
THE BEST BATTLES ARE.
RIGHT?