- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY, BACHOU?
- WHAT IS IT, KANSUI?
- LISTEN UP, SIS.
FROM NOW ON,
REMEMBER TO COUNT
THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE
YOU'RE GOING TO
BE UP AGAINST
BEFORE YOU PICK A FIGHT?
- SORRY, BRO.
I HATE MATH.
- QUIT ACTING SO DUMB.
IF I HADN'T BEEN HERE,
THINGS WOULD'VE BEEN BAD.
REAL BAD.
- ( chuckles )
BUT BRO, YOU'RE ALWAYS HERE.
- ( groans )
IF YOU WANT TO
BECOME STRONGER,
FIGHT STRONGER
INDIVIDUAL FIGHTERS,
NOT HUGE HORDES OF THUGS.
- BUT I THOUGHT
ALL THE STRENGTH I NEEDED
CAME FROM MY SACRED BEAD?
- NOT ALL OF IT.
SOME POWER COMES FROM
THE SOUL YOU INHERITED,
BUT TRUE STRENGTH
REQUIRES TRAINING.
- THEN LIKE I SAID,
IF I GET INTO TROUBLE,
I ALWAYS HAVE YOU.
- I'M NOT GONNA
BE HERE FOREVER.
ONE DAY YOU'LL BE
ON YOUR OWN.
- WHAT?  YOU CAN'T LEAVE.
- ( chuckles )
THAT'S MY LITTLE SIS.
WHAT A BABY.
SHE STILL NEEDS ME
TO BE THERE
TO HOLD HER HAND.
SO HERE I AM.
- JEEZ.
I'M NOT HELPLESS.
IT'S NOT AS IF
I'M STILL IN DIAPERS.
- ( chuckles )
- ( groans )
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S WRONG, BRO?
YOU OKAY?
( gasps )
- BACHOU...
- KANSUI, HANG ON.
( gasps )
( screams )
( sighs )
KANSUI...
- ( knocks on door )
- ( gasps )
( yelps )
- Ryuubi: GOOD MORNING.
- UH, I'M UP.
JUST A SEC.
- YOUR CLOTHES ARE
BACK FROM THE LAUNDRY.
- UHH...
- YOU SURE YOU DON'T
HAVE A FEVER?
YOU WERE SOAKED.
POOR THING.
YOU LOOKED SO BEAT UP.
- ( sighs )
- Ryuubi: IT REALLY
DID A NUMBER ON YOU.
LISTEN TO THE WEATHER MAN,
FROM NOW ON
DON'T GO OUT IN STORMS.
IT'S DANGEROUS.
- OKAY.
- Ekitoku: SO THIS IS
WHERE YOU'VE BEEN HIDING?
- Ryuubi:
OH, HI, EKITOKU.
- HEY LOOK,
I KNOW YOU DON'T LIKE
SPEAKING IN FRONT
OF BIG CROWDS,
BUT YOU PROMISED.
NOW KAN'U'S PISSED.
- UHH... OH.
- HMM?
- ( gasps )
- COME ON.
WE'RE GOING.
- WAIT, EKITOKU.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
- AS YOU KNOW,
THERE HAS BEEN A CEASEFIRE
IN EFFECT BETWEEN
KYOSHO AND NANYO ACADEMIES
EVER SINCE THE BATTLE
OF RED CLIFFS.
BUT YESTERDAY
I RECEIVED A REPORT
THAT KYOSHO ACADEMY
WAS ATTACKED.
THE SCHOOL RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS ATTACK
REMAINS UNKNOWN.
UNTIL WE KNOW THE FACTS,
WE MUST BE ON HIGH ALERT.
BEFORE WE CONCLUDE,
OUR LEADER WILL ADDRESS YOU.
- ( girls gasp )
- LEADER, IF YOU PLEASE.
- UH--
- YOU CAN DO IT, LEADER.
COME ON, GO GET THEM.
- Ryuubi: OKAY.
- THAT WIMPY GIRL
IS A LEADER?
- UM... GOOD MORNING.
I'D LIKE TO THANK
EVERYONE FOR--
OW! OH, OW.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( laughing )
- ( chuckles nervously )
JUST A BIT LOWER.
UM, I WOULD LIKE TO SAY...
TO SAY...
- FELLOW STUDENTS
OF SEITO ACADEMY...
- "FELLOW STUDENTS
OF SEITO ACADEMY,"
UH...
- OUR GREAT ANCESTOR
ONCE SAID...
- "OUR GREAT ANCESTOR
ONCE SAID..."
- LISTEN TO ALL
POINTS OF VIEW,
REJECT WHAT IS DOUBTFUL,
SPEAK CAUTIOUSLY
ABOUT THE REST,
AND YOUR MISTAKES WILL BE
FEW AND FAR BETWEEN.
- UH... "LISTEN TO
ALL POINTS...
REJECT DOUBT."
- BE CAUTIOUS ABOUT THE REST.
- "BE CAUTIOUS ABOUT BREASTS."
- PERFECT.
- NO WAY.
SHE'S A TOTAL DUNDERHEAD.
- WOW, YOU'RE POPULAR,
KAN'U.
ANOTHER GREAT HAUL.
- PLEASE SAY YOU'LL SHARE
SOME OF YOUR DELICIOUS TREATS.
- FIRST I WANT ANSWERS.
YOU PROMISED WE WOULD
HAVE A MEETING THIS MORNING
SO YOU COULD GO OVER
YOUR SPEECH.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO REHEARSE.
- I DIDN'T MEAN TO MISS IT,
BUT I WAS DOING
SOME OTHER STUFF
AND I FORGOT.
- THERE'S NO EXCUSE.
YOU'RE THE LEADER.
- Bachou: HOLY CRAP!
THIS GUMMY CANDY
ONLY JUST WENT ON SALE.
AND THIS ONE'S THAT
PLUM FLAVORED GUMMY.
IT'S ONLY BEEN OUT
A FEW DAYS.
THESE ARE SOLD OUT
EVERYWHERE.
- WHO IS THAT?
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D
FIND THEM HERE.
I SEE.
SO YOU WENT OUT,
YOU GOT CAUGHT IN
THE STORM UNPREPARED,
GENTOKU FOUND YOU
AND BROUGHT YOU BACK HERE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- SHE WAS SOAKED TO THE BONE.
WE CAME BACK.
BOTH OF US NEEDED A BATH,
THEN I PUT HER TO BED.
- I DON'T APPROVE OF YOU
PICKING UP STRANGE GIRLS
AND BRINGING THEM BACK
TO SPEND THE NIGHT.
- HUH?
- THE TWO OF YOU,
PLEASE TELL ME YOU DIDN'T...
DO IT TOGETHER.
- Ryuubi:
DO WHAT TOGETHER?
- TAKE A BATH.
- OF COURSE WE DIDN'T.
I JUST LEANT HER
MY PANTIES.
- YOUR PANTIES?
- I HAD TO.
HER CLOTHES WERE ALL
WET AND DIRTY.
I PUT THEM IN THE WASH.
- Kan'u: YOU CAN'T JUST LET
RANDOM PEOPLE WEAR YOUR PANTIES.
- Ekitoku:
HEY, CAUGHT IN THE RAIN GIRL.
- HMM?
- YOUR NAME?
YOU STILL HAVEN'T TOLD US.
- MOUKI BACHOU.
I'M A FIRST YEAR STUDENT
AT RYOUSHUU HIGH.
- MOUKI!
- BACHOU!
- Kan'u: IN THE TIME
OF THE THREE KINGDOMS,
MOUKI BACHOU WAS
A COMMANDER OF GREAT SKILL.
BUT HE WAS ALSO
KNOWN FOR HIS BRUTALITY.
HE WAS ONE OF THE FIVE
TIGER GENERALS
AND DUBBED BY GENTOKU RYUUBI
"BACHOU THE SPLENDID."
A FIGHTER BEARING
BACHOU'S DESTINY
HAS FINALLY APPEARED.
- HUH.
- IF SHE REALLY IS
WHO YOU SAY,
THEN MAYBE I WAS
SUPPOSED TO FIND HER.
- Both: HUH?!
- JUST A MINUTE.
WERE YOU THE ONE WHO ATTACKED
KYOSHO ACADEMY YESTERDAY?
- UH-HUH.  I AM.
- DON'T JUDGE A BOOK
BY ITS COVER INDEED.
OKAY.  WHO DID YOU
GO THERE TO FIGHT WITH
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- SOUSOU.
- ( all gasp )
- YOU ATTACKED KYOSHO
AND THEN YOU PICKED A FIGHT
WITH ITS LEADER?
- Bachou: I DID.
- DID YOU ACTUALLY
TAKE ON SOUSOU
IN COMBAT?
- NO, I DIDN'T.
HE WASN'T AT THE SCHOOL
WHEN I WENT THERE.
- ( all sigh )
- DO YOU HAVE A DEATH WISH?
WHY THE HELL WOULD YOU
PICK A FIGHT WITH SOUSOU?
- THE REASON IS...
- SPIT IT OUT.
- EKITOKU, THAT'S ENOUGH.
DON'T BADGER HER.
- BUT I WANT TO KNOW.
- LEAVE HER ALONE.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO SAY.
EVERYONE HAS THINGS THEY
LIKE TO KEEP PRIVATE.
- I DON'T HAVE ANY SECRETS.
- YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
SO KAN'U KNOWS ABOUT
HOW YOU SNEAK OFF CAMPUS
SOME NIGHTS AND GO INTO
TOWN TO EAT BURGERS?
- NO I DON'T!
- Kan'u: EKITOKU,
HAVE YOU BEEN
CHEATING ON YOUR DIET?
- SOMETIMES I SLIP.
BUT NOT MUCH.
- Kan'u: SO THIS IS WHY
YOU'VE BEEN SO SLOW
AND WEAK LATELY
DURING PRACTICE.
YOU DISAPPOINT ME,
EKITOKU.
- AWW, KAN'U.
DON'T YOU THINK YOU'RE
BEING A BIT HARD ON ME?
- CALM DOWN NOW.
IT'S NOT THE END OF THE WORLD.
- SHUT YOUR FACE!
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT
FOR BLABBING ABOUT
MY FAST FOOD RUNS!
YOU AND YOUR BIG MOUTH,
HOW COULD YOU?
- I WAS ONLY
TELLING THE TRUTH!
- Ekitoku: YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO TELL ALL OF IT!
- Kan'u:
STOP THAT, EKITOKU.
GET YOUR FINGERS
OUT OF HER MOUTH.
GENTOKU IS OUR LEADER.
- Ekitoku:
YOU SURE IT'S NOT BECAUSE
YOU'D RATHER HAVE
YOUR OWN FINGERS IN HER MOUTH?
- Kan'u: SHUT UP, EKITOKU.
WAS IT REALLY NECESSARY
TO SAY THAT OUT LOUD?
- ( gasps )
OH, SORRY.
I SPACED OUT.
I WAS JUST REMEMBERING
SOMETHING FROM A LONG TIME AGO.
- ( sighs )
MAYBE...
- RIGHT, I'VE DECIDED.
MISS RYUUBI, I MEAN MISS
RYUUBI, OH MY GREAT LEADER.
- YOU MEAN ME?
- PLEASE ALLOW ME TO
STAY HERE WITH YOU.
- ( all gasp )
- I COULD LEARN SO MUCH
FROM MISS KAN'U
AND MISS CHOUHI'S STRENGTH.
AND FROM MISS RYUUBI'S
WISDOM AND KINDNESS AS WELL.
I WISH TO LEARN
FROM ALL OF YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONLY PEOPLE
I CAN SERVE WITH ALL MY HEART.
- WOW, THIS IS
ALL SO SUDDEN.
I'M NOT SURE
WHAT TO SAY.
( gasps )
- I CAN BE YOUR TIGER GENERAL
LIKE I WAS IN THE PAST.
KAN'U, CHOUHI,
LET'S ALL THREE US OF WORK
TOGETHER TO PROTECT AND SERVE
MISS GENTOKU.
- HOLD ON!
WHO THE HELL DO YOU
THINK YOU ARE?!
PROVE IT.  SHOW US.
IF YOU'RE SO CERTAIN
YOU'VE GOT WHAT IT TAKES.
- HMPH!
( shouts )
HMPH.
- YOUR ATTACK'S
NOT HALF BAD.
LET'S SEE HOW AGILE YOU ARE.
GO FETCH!
- ( giggles )
( grunts )
- WELL, THAT'S ONE WAY.
- ( grunts )
( chuckles )
- BE CAREFUL UP THERE,
OKAY?
- ( gasps, whimpers )
( screams )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- A SNAKE!
DON'T BIT ME.
( screams )
- YOU'VE GOT TO
BE KIDDING ME.
( laughing )
THIS IS HYSTERICAL.
ONE OF THE FAMOUS FIVE
TIGER GENERALS
IS TERRIFIED OF
A LITTLE SNAKE?
LOOKS LIKE THIS TIGER
IS REALLY JUST A FRAIDY CAT.
- KAN'U?
- ( sighs )
- ( gasps, screams )
( panting )
- KAN'U JUST SAVED
YOUR SORRY BUTT.
DON'T YOU THINK YOU SHOULD
BE THANKING HER?
- ( grunts )
- WHAT'S THAT?
YOU CALL THAT GRATITUDE?
- ( gasps )
YOU KNOW,
I WAS THINKING,
THE POWER OF
THE SACRED BEADS
MUST HAVE BROUGHT YOU AND
I TOGETHER FOR A REASON.
I'M SURE THAT MEANS
THERE WILL COME A TIME
WHEN THE TWO OF US
WILL NEED ONE ANOTHER.
- ( gasps )
- JUST LIKE THE EVENTS
THAT LED TO EKITOKU,
KAN'U, AND I
MAKING OUR OATH
UNDER THE PEACH TREES.
- Ekitoku: HELLO?  YEAH.
I JUST GOT HERE.
SO, HOW'S IT BEEN
GOING OVER THERE?
REALLY?  THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
I'M ITCHING TO JUMP IN
AND GET MY HANDS DIRTY.
WHAT'S THAT?  NO PROB.
TALK TO YOU LATER.
I CAN DO IT.
I CAN...
( straining )
...NOT DO IT.
( sighs )
- NEED HELP?
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THOSE BAGS WEIGHED A TON.
- ( sighs )
THEY SAY NO ROAD IS LONG
WITH GOOD COMPANY,
BUT THEY NEVER HAD TO
CARRY ALL THESE BAGS.
WHAT'S IN THEM ANYWAY?
WE ONLY NEEDED TO
BRING THE ESSENTIALS.
- THEY ARE MY ESSENTIALS.
I DON'T GO ANYWHERE
WITHOUT THEM.
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE PRACTICALLY
EXTENSIONS OF MY BODY.
LOSING THEM WOULD BE
LIKE LOSING AN ARM.
- IF THEY'RE SO PRECIOUS
TO YOU, FOUR-EYES,
WHY DON'T YOU
CARRY THEM YOURSELF?!
- Ryuubi: I'M SORRY.
- ( chuckles )
- THIS IS A NICE PLACE,
ISN'T IT?
THE COUNTRYSIDE
IS LOVELY,
AND THE COOL AIR
SMELLS SWEET.
- YOU'VE HEARD ABOUT HOW ROUGH
THIS SCHOOL IS, RIGHT?
SEITO ACADEMY HAS
A NASTY REPUTATION.
BUT DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
MY BEST FRIEND KAN'U
IS THERE ALREADY.
SHE CLEANED HOUSE
AND TOOK OUT THE TRASH.
- OH? KAN'U SOUNDS
LIKE A NEAT FREAK.
SHE REALLY MUST
LIKE THINGS CLEAN.
- WHAT?  YOU'RE JOKING,
FOUR-EYES.
I MEANT TRASH LIKE
RIFFRAFF AND SCUM.
- WHO ARE YOU CALLING
RIFFRAFF AND SCUM?
CHANGE OF PLANS, LADIES.
SORRY TO BREAK UP YOUR PARTY,
BUT NEW STUDENTS MUST PASS
ENTRANCE EXAMS.
- OH, YOU MUST BE MISTAKEN.
WE TOOK THOSE TESTS
A LONG TIME AGO.
- YOU IDIOT.  THAT'S NOT
WHAT SHE'S TALKING ABOUT.
THIS CHICK LOOKS DANGEROUS.
I'M SURE SHE'S BAD NEWS.
YOU WANT TO TEST ME, BITCH?
BRING IT ON.
ANYTHING YOU CAN DISH OUT
I CAN HANDLE.
- YOU'VE GOT
A LOT OF SPIRIT, GIRL.
BUT I DON'T RECOMMEND
DEFYING US
UNLESS YOU PREFER
DYING YOUNG.
- JUST TRY IT!
HEY, FOUR-EYES.
STICK CLOSE.
GET BEHIND ME
AND I'LL KEEP YOU SAFE.
WHAT THE--?
THEY GOT YOU ALREADY?
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
- ( grunts )
- ( screams, grunts )
- LET'S STRING HER UP IN
THE TREES FOR A NIGHT
SO SHE LEARNS WHO'S
BOSS AROUND HERE.
- OKAY.
- STOP. DON'T DO IT.
THERE'S NO NEED
FOR VIOLENCE.
- SO MAYBE YOU WANT TO
TAKE HER PLACE THEN?
( chuckles )
- ( yelps )
( gasps )
- JUST A BUNCH OF BOOKS.
- THEY'RE GOOD KINDLING.
WE COULD MAKE
A BIG BONFIRE
AND BURN THEM.
- GOOD IDEA.
- PLEASE, DON'T DO THAT.
- THOSE BOOKS MEAN
A LOT TO YOU, NERD?
I BET THEY'RE THE ONLY
FRIENDS YOU HAVE.
- ( crying )
- SEE, BOOKS CAN'T HELP YOU.
THEY'RE JUST PAPER.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW MANY OF THEM
YOU'VE READ,
'CAUSE YOU'RE STILL
SHAKING IN YOUR SHOES.
BOOKS ARE TOTALLY USELESS.
- REAL POWER DOESN'T COME
FROM WORDS ON A PAGE.
IT'S ABOUT PEOPLE
BEING AFRAID OF YOU.
- ( gasps )
- THOSE THINGS--
THE POSSESSIONS SHE LOVED MOST.
THEY WERE JUST
DUSTY OLD BOOKS?
( gasps )
- Ryuubi: YOU'RE WRONG.
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
BOOKS ARE VERY IMPORTANT.
BY READING BOOKS,
YOU CAN EXPAND YOUR KNOWLEDGE.
YOU WON'T NEED
FEAR TO RULE.
PEOPLE WILL LISTEN
BECAUSE YOU CAN HELP THEM.
THEY'LL RESPECT YOU.
CONTROL THROUGH VIOLENCE
LEADS TO NOTHING.
FEAR IS NOT POWER.
- ( gasps )
- IT CAN'T BE.
THAT STUPID FOUR-EYES.
SHE IS...
GENTOKU RYUUBI?
- ( gasping )
- IT'S HER.
- THERE YOU ARE.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU.
I CAUGHT THE REST OF
THE SCUM THAT RAN AWAY.
I FINALLY FOUND YOU AS WELL,
GENTOKU.
- WHO ARE YOU?
IS THAT YOU, KAN'U?
- ( screams )
-  ( groaning )
- AW, DAMN IT.
- THANK YOU FOR SAVING US.
- THERE'S NO NEED
TO THANK ME.
THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
WE WERE BROUGHT TOGETHER
BY THE DESTINIES
OF OUR SACRED BEADS.
- I WISH YOU COULD HAVE
HEARD HER, KAN'U.
FOUR-EYES-- I MEAN GENTOKU,
GAVE THE MOST INCREDIBLE SPEECH
JUST BEFORE YOU SHOWED UP.
- WE MAY NOT HAVE BEEN
BORN ON THE SAME DAY...
- BUT WE BOND AS SISTERS...
- AND SOLEMNLY VOW
THAT WE WILL DIE TOGETHER.
Ekitoku:
AND THAT'S HOW IT HAPPENED.
FATE BOUND US,
AND WE MADE OUR VOW.
IMPRESSIVE, RIGHT?
- WHAT AN INCREDIBLE STORY.
I WISH THAT COULD
HAPPEN TO ME.
- I MEAN IT'S SO TRUE.
WE THREE ARE BEST FRIENDS.
BEST OF ALL TIME.
- BEST FRIENDS OF ALL TIME?
I THINK THAT'S
AN EXAGGERATION.
- AND TO THINK,
IT ALL HAPPENED BECAUSE OF YOU,
MISS CHOUHI.
YOU'RE THE GLUE.
IT'S YOU WHO'S HOLDING
THE FRIENDSHIP TOGETHER.
YOUR STRENGTH MAKES ME REALIZE
I STILL HAVE A LOT TO LEARN.
- ( chuckles )
YOU'RE YOUNG,
BUT YOU UNDERSTAND
SOME THINGS ALREADY.
THAT SETTLES IT.
YOU'RE GOING TO STAY
HERE WITH US FOR AWHILE.
AND I WILL PERSONALLY
OVERSEE YOUR TRAINING.
- I CAN REALLY STAY?!
THAT'S FANTASTIC!
- Ryuubi: UH, EKITOKU?
SHOULDN'T WE DISCUSS THIS?
- Kan'u: THE TIGER GENERAL
BACHOU HAS APPEARED.
- ( laughing )
- Kan'u: IS THIS A SIGN
THAT A NEW BATTLE
IS IMMINENT?
GENTOKU'S DRAGON MUST
NEVER AWAKEN AGAIN.
I HAVE TO PREVENT IT.
- ( sighs )
- HUH?
KOUMEI, WAKE UP.
YOU'RE SLEEPING IN
THE LIBRARY AGAIN.
- GENTOKU,
LET'S TAKE A BATH TOGETHER.
- Ryuubi: WHERE DID THIS
SUDDENLY COME FROM?
- LET'S BATHE.
- THE SUN IS STILL UP.
IT'S TOO EARLY.
- LET'S BATHE.
- HMM.
BUT KOUMEI, YOU FOOL
AROUND SO MUCH
EVERY TIME WE TAKE A BATH.
YOU TICKLE ME AND I LAUGH,
AND THEN I CAN'T
WASH YOU PROPERLY.
- I WILL WASH YOU.
LET'S TAKE A BATH.
- HMM.
- ( giggles )
- UNTIE ME!
HURRY UP AND UNTIE ME
RIGHT NOW.
- JUST GREAT.
THAT SNEAKY LITTLE BRAT
ABDUCTED OUR LEADER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE DID
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- I'M MORE WORRIED
ABOUT GENTOKU.
I'M GOING AFTER
BOTH OF THEM.
- Koumei: UNTIE ME.
I'M YOUR STRATEGIST.
- EKITOKU, WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
- UH, DO SOMETHING
ABOUT WHAT, KAN'U?
- I SHOULDN'T HAVE LEFT
WITHOUT SAYING ANYTHING.
I BET KAN'U AND THE OTHERS
ARE REALLY WORRIED ABOUT ME.
( gasps )
- HEY.
IS IT TO TERRIBLE
TO HANG OUT WITH ME?
- UM, NO.  I'M FINE.
I MEAN, WE'RE HAVING FUN.
I LIKE YOU.
- Bachou:
GREAT.
THEN LET'S SPEND THE REST
OF THE DAY TOGETHER.
WE'LL GO ALL OUT.
- HEY. LOOK OVER THERE.
- IT'S GENTOKU RYUUBI,
LEADER OF SEITO ACADEMY.
I DON'T SEE HER GUARDS
CHOUHI AND KAN'U AROUND.
- WHAT A LUCKY BREAK.
LET'S GET EVERYONE DOWN HERE.
- SAY, MISS BACHOU?
- MY EARS HURT.
I WON'T LISTEN TO YOU IF
YOU'RE GOING TO BE SO FORMAL.
YOU HAVE TO CALL ME
SOMETHING ELSE.
- WHAT IF I CALLED YOU MOUKI?
- MM-MM.
- BACHOU?
- WELL THEN...
THE FIRST KANJI IN YOUR NAME
SOUNDS KIND OF LIKE HORSE,
SO...
MA-CHAN?
- ( gasps )
MM-HMM!
I KNOW A SHORTCUT!
COME ON!  IT'S THIS WAY.
- WAIT A SECOND, MA-CHAN.
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS ALLEY SEEMS
KIND OF DANGEROUS.
- FEAR NOT.  MA-CHAN IS HERE
TO PROTECT HER LEADER.
- YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T
BE SO CARELESS.
FIRST YOU WAGE A WAR
THAT LEFT HALF THE FIGHTERS
WITHOUT SCHOOLS TO
GO BACK TO,
AND NOW YOU'VE GONE AND
WANDERED INTO A TRAP.
- WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE?
- WE'RE RONIN FIGHTERS.
WE HAVE NO SCHOOL.
WE DO NOT SERVE A LEADER.
BUT IF WE CAPTURE RYUUBI
AND PRESENT HER AS A GIFT
TO ONE OF HER ENEMIES,
WE MIGHT JUST GET REWARDED
WITH A SCHOOL OF OUR OWN.
- HMPH.
- MA-CHAN, BE CAREFUL.
- YOU WON'T BE GETTING ANYTHING,
EXCEPT MAYBE THIS!
- ( grunts )
YOU KNOW, NOWADAYS
THEY HAVE THIS INVENTION
TO PROTECT OUR JUNK...
CALLED A CUP!
- ( grunts )
- MA-CHAN!
- ( all chuckling )
- Kansui: LISTEN UP, SIS.
FROM NOW ON, REMEMBER TO COUNT
THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
UP AGAINST BEFORE
YOU PICK A FIGHT.
- Bachou:
GREAT ADVICE, BRO.
BUT IT'S ALREADY TOO LATE.
BUT I'M NOT GIVING UP.
I WILL DEFEND RYUUBI
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES.
- Hakufu: HEY, LONG TIME NO SEE,
RYUU-CHAN.
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- MISS SONSAKU.
- THE SHOU HAOU...
HAKUFU SONSAKU?
THAT'S HER?
- THIS IS BAD.
REALLY BAD.
- I WAS OUT SHOPPING
WITH KOUKIN,
BUT THE TWO OF US
GOT SEPARATED.
HUH?  WHERE'S YOUR FRIEND
WITH THE BANGS
WHO SAYS "MY GREEN
DRAGON BLADE WEEPS"?
I THOUGHT SHE WAS
ALWAYS WITH YOU?
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
- THERE'S SEVEN OF US
AND ONLY ONE OF HER.
- RIGHT.
WE'RE NOT SCARED!
YOU'RE OUTNUMBERED, NANYO GIRL!
YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
- ( gasps )
- ( shouting )
( men grunting )
- AH, THAT FELT GOOD.
- Bachou: EVERY GUY SHE HIT
FLEW INTO THE AIR
AT LEAST 20 FEET.
SHE'S AMAZING.
- I SHOULDN'T HAVE EATEN
SO MUCH CAKE EARLIER.
BUT THE BEST METHOD
FOR LOSING WEIGHT
IS TO GET LOTS OF EXERCISE.
HMM?
WHO'S THIS?
- OH, THAT'S MA-CHAN.
- MASTER!
PLEASE LET ME BE
YOUR DISCIPLE?
- WHAT?
- HUH?
- ( sighs )
THEY DIDN'T NEED ME AT ALL.
( chuckles )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kan'u: HONESTLY,
SNEAKING OFF WITH GENTOKU
WHILE MY BACK WAS TURNED.
THIS IS THE WORST THING
SHE POSSIBLY COULD HAVE DONE.
- Ekitoku: I CAN THINK
OF A FEW THINGS
SHE COULD HAVE DONE
WITH GENTOKU
THAT YOU WOULD
HAVE HATED A LOT MORE.
- Kan'u: WHAT?
- Ekitoku: COME ON, KAN'U.
CUT BACHOU SOME SLACK.
- Kan'u: AND NOW SHE'S ASKING
HOW TO GET TO NANYO ACADEMY.
- Ekitoku: REALLY?
AFTER ATTACKING KYOSHO,
SHE'S GOT HER SIGHTS
SET ON NANYO?
WE'VE REALLY GOT A TIGER
BY THE TAIL, DON'T WE?
- Kan'u: NEXT TIME ON
"IKKI TOUSEN XTREME XECUTOR,"
"A TRAINED LION."