[BLUE-EYES grimaces]
I am extremely
disappointed in you...
Blue Eyes.
In order to capture Ellis...
those in our way must
be disposed of first.
That is our conclusion.
[CHAIRWOMAN] You are hereby
ordered to kill Nadie.
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
[CHAIRWOMAN] How you
accomplish this is up to you...
However, there is one
condition that must be met.
Condition?
Listen closely...
You are to execute
this mission personally.
[dial tone]
[BLUE-EYES] And thus...
I received the order...
to murder Nadie.
[gun cocks]
Ellis said it herself...
She wants it to be over.
Let's get this
over with... L.A.
I don't get it...
It just doesn't
make any sense...
What in the world could Ellis
possibly want to end...?
We haven't even begun
our ultimate journey!
Huh?
¿Está bien?
Do you not feel good?
I know what to do.
[GIRL gasps]
Hm. So uh...
Whatcha make of this?
I'm not real sure.
Don't you think it's
a little too "artistic"
to be You-Know-Who's handiwork?
[GIRL] Umm...
[ELLIS and NADIE] Hm?
You don't happen
to know the person
who put these
flowers here, do you?
Yeah, we might...
Sorry, we don't.
[NADIE] Uh--
Well if you ever happen
to run across him...
Will you do me a favor
and thank him for me?
[NADIE] Really?
He was kind enough to buy
every one of my flowers.
[NADIE] That guy?
Si!
[ELLIS] Hm?
He actually
pays for them?
Uhh...
Man, wish I could figure
out what L.A.'s up to...
Maybe he just went off the
deep end after all that crap
you said to him the other day.
So wait...
if a guy loses it,
but he's crazy to begin with,
does that bring him
back around to sane?
I don't want...
to talk about it...
Change the subject.
[NADIE] Hmm.
Yessir.
Any sniper
experience?
I've taken the standard
training courses,
so I think I should
be all right.
That being said, it has been
several years since then...
But I'm sure the training will
kick back in before too long.
[gunshot]
[BLUE-EYES] Do you know
why I was the one ordered
to be the shooter for this job?
[B-LADY A] I imagine
it has something to do
with our incompetence.
[BLUE-EYES] You're wrong...
I assume it has to do
with our superiors
being suspicious of me.
What's that
supposed to mean?
I think they believe
I'm prolonging the capture
of Ellis for my own purposes...
So they order me
to murder Nadie...
in an attempt to
test my loyalty.
[B-LADY A gasps]
[phone ringing]
Status report...
Target left the village on
foot early this morning...
Has since gone into hiding.
[B-LADY B]
Her motives are unknown...
Will continue surveillance.
[whispering]
Let's get as close as we can.
Yessir.
Ahh!
Um... Hey wait!
Come back!
[NADIE yelling]
[B-LADY B] Uhh...
Hold on...
They're actually trying to catch
a vulture with their bare hands?
[B-LADY B] It appears so...
What the hell are
they thinking?
[LIRIO gasps]
What do you see?
[VULTURE squack]
[LIRIO whimpers]
You stupid
little brat...
What have you done
with my prize vulture?!
[LIRIO giggles]
Only one way to
fix this, missy.
You owe me a new bird...
And if you're not
able to do that...
you better be ready to
pay me back--in cash!
[LIRIO giggles]
[LARCO sighs]
Listen kiddo, you got a mommy
or daddy around I can talk to?
Huh? Ah! Just my luck...
I was wondering who was
messing with my girl.
And if it isn't the
con man Bullshit Larco...
Kinda surprised to see you
still lookin' for rubes.
[LARCO sighs]
So where do you
find 'em...?
There anybody left
these days dumb enough
to fall for your
old-school scams?
[LARCO] Heh.
[ELLIS] It doesn't
want to come down.
[NADIE] We'll hafta
wait him out.
[footsteps]
[B-LADY B]
Has the situation changed?
No.
[B-LADY B] I believe
this is our best position.
Then we'll just have
to wait them out.
Come on,
land already...!
Stupid bird.
And you, why don't you quit
cat-napping and help me
think of something that
might actually work?
Something that
Yeah, as in a way to
catch the damn thing.
How 'bout...
We use our hands?
[NADIE sighs]
Oy vey.
[NADIE grunts]
[NADIE] There has to be
an easy way to do this.
Hey... Ellis.
[ELLIS chomping]
[NADIE] Gimme a bite.
Just a little.
Damn that's good.
That wasn't a little.
[ELLIS] Oh?
[NADIE] Hm?
I see movement.
What's she trying to do?
I don't think birds have
a taste for chocolate.
Here comes!
[NADIE] Shut up!
Yeah, that's sketchy...
There she is!
Dammit, I don't
have a clean shot.
So let's move.
[NADIE] I can't believe
we're doing this!
It's so dangerous!
Damn bird!
[NADIE] Ellis!
[ELLIS] Oof!
[ELLIS] That was scary.
[NADIE] Are you hurt anywhere?
[ELLIS] Nah, I'm fine.
[NADIE] Geez, talk
about frustrating.
Next time it swoops down
like that it's mine!
[BLUE-EYES exhales]
Little do you know
the real prey here is you...
Nadie.
[gunshot]
[gun shells clatter]
[MELISSA] Cute, aren't they?
[ROSENBERG chuckles]
These two are
a bonded pair ...
They should be laying
their eggs soon...
Once the chicks hatch you'll
take care of them with me,
won't you hon?
Of course I will. Heh.
C'mon bird,
I'm beggin' ya...
Just get down here!
Funny I was about to
say the same thing.
[NADIE] Hey...
you awake?
I dozed off.
Yeah, I noticed.
And the bird?
Lucky...
I wish I could fly like him...
It would be fun.
[NADIE] Yeah...
That would be nice...
After all, if you had wings,
you'd be totally free...
Free to go wherever
you felt like.
[ELLIS] Free.
Is there some place you
want to go someday, Nadie?
[NADIE] Hm?
Now that I think
about it, not really...
Even trying to be nice,
I wouldn't call that a
terribly constructive life.
[NADIE] I suppose the
destination doesn't matter...
Long as I don't
have to travel alone...
[BLUE-EYES sighs]
[NADIE] Long as
someone's by my side.
Someone, huh?
Does that mean Ellis?
Sorry kiddo, can't say.
[ELLIS] Come on...
[NADIE] I. don't. want. to.
[ELLIS] Why. Not?
[NADIE] Because.
I. Don't. Want. To.
[ELLIS] I. Don't. Think. It.
Would. Hurt. for you to tell me.
[NADIE] That was a long one!
[BLUE-EYES chuckles]
What's wrong, Nadie?
I'm bored up here...
Give me something
interesting to listen to.
[NADIE] Blue Eyes.
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
I'm not...
letting you take
Ellis away from me.
She's sleeping...
Jeez, don't scare me like that.
[NADIE] Mmm.
Did I... Did I fall
asleep or something?
Yeah, you sure did.
Sorry.
Nadie, who is Blue Eyes?
[NADIE gasps]
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
You were...
talking in your sleep...
I heard you say you wouldn't
let Blue Eyes take me away.
[NADIE]
Now that you mention it,
I think I was dreaming
somethin' like that.
[ELLIS] Is it that person who
tried to take me the other day?
Yeah...
it sure is.
What's she like?
You wanna know?
[ELLIS] Mm-hmm.
Okay, I'll tell
you everything...
Or at least as
much as I can...
I've only had dealings with
her on business matters,
so I don't really know her
on a personal level...
Are you cool with that?
[ELLIS] Mm-hmm.
[NADIE] Well,, in a word,
she's a robot...
A machine with a head
full of gears and cogs...
I mean, I'm sure she's
intelligent and all,
but how do I put this?
I think she's the type of woman
who'll go to her death
without ever
finding happiness.
How nice of you to say.
[NADIE] And on top of that,
she's got a mean streak...
Like when she closed off my
bank account, remember...?
I've known people like her,
and in my experience,
they never have many friends.
And now you're just
pissin' me off.
Tell me how
you really feel.
Well I can't help it...
I mean, the worlds
she and I come from
couldn't be any
more different...
She's a slave to the
organization she works for,
through and through...
I'm a free-spirited bounty
hunter, livin' in the now,
never knowin'
what tomorrow holds...
[ELLIS] Free, huh?
[ELLIS] Then you're
a bird, Nadie.
[NADIE] Huh?
[ELLIS] He's back.
[NADIE] You go 'round front.
[ELLIS] Yessir.
[NADIE] Let's go.
[BLUE-EYES] You're actually not
that wrong about me, Nadie...
I am merely a cog in
a much bigger machine.
But you're mistaken
about one thing...
Though I am a member
of the organization,
I do have my own dreams.
There is a place...
...I hope to arrive at someday.
[BLUE-EYES inhales]
So you see...
Freedom isn't a privilege
that's awarded to just you.
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
[ELLIS] Hey...
Does it feel good to fly around?
[NADIE] Get it!
Ellis, hold down its wings!
[ELLIS] Yessir!
[NADIE] It's okay birdie.
We're not gonna hurt
you or anything.
Don't worry, we're friendly.
That's a good boy. Good boy.
[BLUE-EYES] Come on, Ellis...!
Move the hell out of the way!
[NADIE] 'Least now
we're not gonna hafta pay
that old short dude back...
Thank god!
[NADIE] Wha... Ellis?
[ELLIS gasps]
[NADIE] Hey...!
What the hell you doin'?
[NADIE gasps]
[ELLIS and NADIE panting]
[NADIE panting]
[ELLIS] Hurry up!
[ELLIS] Go bird!
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
[ELLIS] Fly! Fly!
[B-LADY A] Take the shot.
[gunshot]
[ELLIS gasps]
[NADIE] Is that Blue Eyes?
[NADIE gasps]
[BLUE-EYES]
I've made up my mind.
[BLUE-EYES] I am...
descended from the Witches.
[BLUE-EYES] But unlike Ellis...
I'm not an artificial life form
created through genetic
engineering...
I'm a true witch.
[BLUE-EYES] However,
I'm unable to use the abilities
that are my birthright...
Do I not possess
these powers...?
or are they lying
dormant inside me...?
It's anyone's guess.
[BLUE-EYES] So if arriving at
that place allows Ellis to...
realize her ultimate
awakened state, then...
I assume there's
a high probability
the same will hold true for me.
[B-LADY A] So you're
saying that you
never intended
to capture Ellis?
[BLUE-EYES] I wasn't
sure at first...
Honestly... I wasn't sure
until this very moment.
But I've made my choice...
From now on I
follow my own path...
just like those
girls down there.
[B-LADY B] If you do that
they'll hunt you down.
I know...
So I can't drag you any further
into this than you are.
Thank you for all
you've done.
I can't believe that crotchety
old runt conned us...
Jus' thinkin' about it
still pisses me off.
[ELLIS] That Blue Eyes lady.
Say what?
Her eyes were real pretty.
[NADIE chuckles]
[MELISSA] Are you sure
you didn't let them out?
Melissa... I'd never.
[MELISSA] Of course...
I'm sorry.
[ROSENBERG sighs]
Are you wanting us to
come and get you...?
Little late for that
now, isn't it...?
As I recall, you are
the ones who left.
[BLUE-EYES] In the end...
a caged bird...
can only survive...
within its cage.