Can you even remember the
last time we had a shower?
I forgot.
[NADIE gasps]
[NADIE] Hi-iii!
[NADIE] Ugh.
Ellis?
I'm bored.
Huh?
Are we there yet?
Y'keep askin' that, and
we'll be campin' out again...
Wouldn't you prefer a bed
over the cold desert sand?
[ELLIS] Uhh...
[BLUE-EYES] Just as if they
were human themselves...
life forms created by the hands
of humankind will occasionally
develop strong attachments
to certain people.
[gun cocks]
[L.A. sighs]
Ellis.
[ROSENBERG] That's right.
The boy has no comprehension
of the position
he's put himself in.
Therefore, I've determined
he is in need of...
"re-education."
Any means necessary...
Correct...
Take him into
custody immediately.
Heh.
Huh?
I got a job.
Oohh...
I'll come right back for
you once I'm finished...
Promise me you'll wait
here 'til then...
Okay?
[LIRIO giggles]
Good girl.
[LIRIO sighs]
[NADIE] Ka-pow!
Come on...
[NADIE coughs]
What's with these people?
Why won't they stop?
That one sped up.
Do we look
like criminals?
You're gonna try?
No way that's happenin'.
You're way too young and you
don't know how to "work it."
You see...? Told ya...
[tires screech]
Uh?!
He stopped.
You're kiddin'...
Seriously, that's
just messed up.
Would you rather sleep on
the cold desert sand again?
Once we hit town,
why don't we splurge
and find a nice
hotel to stay at?
Do you have money?
I'll figure it out...
Oh, I can hardly wait--a long
hot shower and an actual bed.
Heeeyyy.
[ELLIS] It's big.
[NADIE] Not bad for
a place out in the sticks.
Oh that's why
this is here.
What?
It looks like there's
some ruins nearby...
See check it out.
[ELLIS] Hmm?
I'll get us a room...
Wait here 'kay?
Yes sir.
[ELLIS] Hm...
Huh?
[LIRIO laughs]
[LIRIO giggles]
That girl...?
[NADIE] Ya-hoo!
Hold it!
Uh--
We'll just get the bed dirty,
so we should probably
clean up first...
Now come on.
Shower time!
[ELLIS] Ya-hoo.
So soft.
[NADIE] Mmm.
I feel human again!
[NADIE hums]
[NADIE chuckles]
[ELLIS] Mmm. Feels nice.
Did you...
cut your hair?
[ELLIS] Huh-uh.
Oh... You sure
'bout that?
'Cause it looks a bit
shorter in the back.
Or am I crazy?
[ELLIS] Aww...
How careless to leave my
darling Ellis all alone.
Oh dear...
I can't help myself.
When falling in love...
One tends to lose sight
of everything else.
[L.A. chuckles]
I'm taking this
as a memento...
Until the day you and
I are bound together.
[L.A. sighs]
You're so sweet...
my darling Ellis.
Hey what you got
there... chico?
Some kind of magic?
[SCOUNDRELS laugh]
[RADIO COP]
The suspect's whereabouts
are unknown at this time...
and there are no witnesses...
There appear to be
five or six victims...
but it's unclear exactly
what kind of weapon was used.
Cancel that, there may
be more victims...
The scene's a mess,
it's kinda hard to tell...
Just get Homicide
down here ASAP...
[sirens blare]
I can't sleep.
[NADIE sleepily] Got any
last words... say 'em.
That girl...
She's waiting for someone.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
We barely have enough
to cover the room
so window
shopping only.
Yeah... you said
that earlier.
Uh?!
Still there.
What is?
That girl.
[NADIE] Huh?
Huh... She looks familiar.
[LIRIO giggles]
[NADIE] Hi... Heh.
Ho boy... Um...
H-Here.
[LIRIO] Ohh!
[LIRIO giggles]
Oh, yeah!
[LIRIO] Huh?
You know her?
I only met her once...
Her name was...
Didn't I give this to you
the last time we met...?
You haven't eaten it yet?
Why?
You don't want it?
Lemme guess.
Not much of a chocoholic?
Maybe she
wants to share.
[NADIE] Oh, okay...
That must be why it's
still in the wrapper.
Whoa hey...
What are you doing?!
Waiting...
for someone.
Huh?
That's not him.
[RICARDO] Did you
give her that?
Thank you.
[NADIE] Oh, it's nothing.
Come on, Lirio...
Let's go.
Mistaken identity?
Here...
We can all share.
[NADIE] Delicious.
Have it.
[ELLIS] Heh.
[LIRIO] Mmm!
So hey...
We got nothin' to do...
Anyone down for a nap?
Hm? Waitaminnit,
where ya going?
Wow. Talk about amenities...
Señorita...
What room are you in?
I'm in this one.
Ah, lo siento...
Unless you are
staying in a VIP room,
there is an additional charge
for the aquatic facilities.
We have to pay...?
Forget it.
We'll just look around.
Uh!
--[ELLIS] And, jump!
--[NADIE] No wait!
There's also a swimsuit
rental charge,
we'll put it
on your bill.
[NADIE] Heh, heh...
[NADIE] Cannonball!
I thought you said we
didn't have any money.
Who even cares?
Oh yeah...
This's the life...
She fell asleep.
[NADIE] Let's cover her up.
Doubt she wants her
tummy to get burned.
She's so cute...
Like a little angel.
[ELLIS chuckles]
[NADIE] U-U-Uh?
What's all this?!
Lirio ordered
us all dinner.
[LIRIO laughs]
Uhhh, yeah I can see that.
[STAFF MAN B clears throat]
[NADIE] Look, the point is I
don't have near enough money...
I'll explain everything
later, just do something...
Please... I'm beggin'!
[BLUE-EYES sighs]
[BLUE-EYES]
All right...
It'll have to be cash,
can you get out tonight?
A timeframe...?
You know I can't
be that specific...
Okay, do you have a pen ready?
Huh? Wait...
You guys, hold on!
[LIRIO and ELLIS] Huh?
Never mind.
You're leaving?
I won't be long.
[distant thunder]
Storm rollin' in...
Figures, that's just my luck.
[rainfall]
[thunder]
[lightning strikes]
[L.A. chuckles]
What is this freak?
[L.A.] You're lucky
it's raining...
You can actually
see my attacks...
Though ultimately, you'll find
that is to your detriment.
So I must know.
Who are you, sir...?
The silent type.
Well, not that it matters...
Anyone who gets in my way...
will end up dead.
[lightning strikes]
Uno... Dos... Tres.
Waiting again tonight?
[LIRIO] Hm.
You believe in 'im.
I think I'll wait too...
for Nadie.
This is ridiculous...
After I just had
that nice shower...
I'd love to stay and
play some more...
but I'll have to wrap this up...
I still have my rendezvous with
Ellis to get to this evening.
Uno... dos...
...tres!
[L.A. grunts]
[RICARDO grunts]
Don't underestimate me...
I can break a mere
human being with one hand.
Go ahead...
Try me.
[L.A.] H-Heh...
Ya think you're fast enough
to snap my neck...
Before I can pull
this trigger...?
I'll take that bet.
[L.A. chuckles]
Not bad...
In fact you're pretty good,
for a human...
Ah!
I'll buy you a drink
in hell... amigo.
Ah!
[RICARDO] Heh.
'Bout damn time.
Where did you go?
Nowhere...
Is she still waiting
for her friend?
[LIRIO gasps]
[LIRIO giggles]
Nuh-uh.
We meet again.
Coincidence...
...or is it?
Thank you for watching her.
It's obvious...
Just look at her face.
[LIRIO giggles]
Bye bye.
Okay?
Hm. Okay.