Found it.
Where?
How wonderfully
tasteful of him.
[L.A.] Oh, Ellis...
let's go together...
to our special
place of eternity...
Wiñay Marka.
[BLUE-EYES]
When dealing with L.A...
Caution is required.
[gun cocks]
Gracias.
[B-LADY A] Ciao.
[NADIE] Yo, Ellis.
[ELLIS] Hm?
Oh hey... huh...
You still have that thing?
Yup.
[NADIE] Cool.
Down!
[ELLIS gasps]
[NADIE] Huh?
[CONSTRUCTION WORKER]
U-Uh...
[NADIE] Sorry, mister!
My bad!
[CONSTRUCTION WORKER]
Yeah... sure.
[NADIE] Ellis?
[ELLIS whimpers]
[NADIE] What's wrong?
Aw crap...
Your charm got busted...
That sucks.
Hey, what's with the cold
shoulder treatment...?
It was an accident...
the only reason I pulled
my piece on that guy
was cuz I thought
he was after you.
But I knew he didn't
have a gun on him...
I knew it right away.
Huh...?
Then you should've
said something.
You shoved me
before I could.
[NADIE] Uh...
Ellis...
Look I...
Wait... no... stop!
Don't you dare!
[NADIE] Why I oughta'...
Wonderful...
Sounds like trouble.
[B-LADY A] I'll tail 'em.
Thank you, please do.
So... y'think tonight...
hotel...?
Cuz um...
it's a bit cold out
here for camping.
There's one.
Ohh...
Looks like a bed
and breakfast.
'Cause it is.
Heh.
Okay... Kokopelli... Huh...
[rustling]
Oh... Buenas tardes...
Need a room?
[ELLIS chuckles]
Heh. Yeah...
sure do.
[OLD MAN] So, you ladies
are traveling...?
Seeing the sights
all by yourselves?
[NADIE] It's kinda
complicated...
Hafta say Gramps, you gotta
crap-ton of books.
It's what I do...
Well, I don't write anymore.
[ELLIS]
"Miguel... My love..."
[OLD MAN] Hm?
"From the first moment
I laid eyes on you...
I have loved you with
all of my heart..."
Huh?
"And the incandescent flames...
of love burned deep within the
hearts of Miguel and Nadia,
until the end of time."
Hey, that's...
[OLD MAN] Ah... that
brings back memories.
What...? Did you write
that or something?
Yes... it was... Huh...
Back when I was with my
second, no, first ex-wife.
[ELLIS] Howard Heisman.
I don't believe it...
What's a famous author doing out
in the boonies running a B&amp;B?
Well I retired
ten years ago.
You're all alone?
Yes... You could say that...
How come...?
You wanna get married?
Yeah, no.
My, aren't you
direct, lil missy?
[knocking]
Oh... Sounds like we
have more guests.
Ricardo.
[door closes]
Hey there, bonita.
They friends of yours?
Yeah, sure.
Need one room
for the night.
That won't be a problem...
So then...
Missy and her friend
will be in Room One,
and you'll be right next door.
One more please.
What?
I would prefer
having my own room.
Oh yeah?
[RICARDO] Mm?
Yeah...
We're workin' through
somethin' right now.
I see...
This tends to happen...
on long journey's like yours.
So...
Missy you can take the
last room on the left.
Thank you.
[NADIE sighs]
[ELLIS chuckles]
[LIRIO whimpers]
[OLD MAN]
After-dinner herbal tea.
Oh, thank you...
You're a helluva cook, Gramps...
That was delicious.
[OLD MAN]
A ladies man like myself
needs to be good in the kitchen.
[NADIE chuckles]
[LIRIO playing flute]
Ah...
Kokopelli's flute.
That it is.
What's that?
He's the spirit
of harvest...
He's also known as a messenger
of peace who brings happiness.
Like... Did you see the
guy on the sign out front?
[RICARDO] Oh, the drawing.
You know quite
a bit about him.
[NADIE laughs]
[ELLIS playing flute]
You suck.
Here...
Gimme it a sec.
[ELLIS] Wha...
Whoa...
It's not wood.
It's llama bone.
Yeah?
Know what llama's are?
They've got long
necks like this...
and their ears stand
straight up...
And their eyes are
spaced real far apart.
Nadie.
Huh?
[NADIE sighs]
[NADIE] Ellis?
You in there?
I'm coming in.
[ELLIS] No.
[NADIE] Why not?
[ELLIS]
Because I suck... remember?
[NADIE] I was
only joking around.
[ELLIS] I'm going to bed.
[NADIE sighs]
I'm here... Ellis.
[OLD MAN] Buenas noches.
It's cold out here...
Why don't you come inside?
I did not come
here to see you.
Put that away...
It's not necessary here.
Come warm up inside.
[L.A. sighs]
Well?
Suit yourself...
And what about you
there, young lady?
I've got some
great herbal tea.
Who are you?
[OLD MAN] Just an old man,
as you can see.
I find that
hard to believe.
Well then...
You leave me no choice.
Honest to God truth is...
I'm a spirit.
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
That's ridiculous.
[OLD MAN chuckles]
When you feel like having
some tea, come on inside...
You're more than welcome here.
[door closes]
I need to get a
background check.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
I heard the stories about
Kokopelli from my mom
when I was
a little kid.
I always wanted
to meet him...
so I became obsessed
with practicing the flute.
I thought if I learned
how to play well...
he would visit me one day.
But... I never did
get very good at it.
Well, children
are innocent...
It's very easy to
hurt their feelings...
There are things adults can
rationalize matter-of-factly...
But children don't
have that capacity.
In many ways, children
see the world around them
in black and white,
or in other words...
In love... and hate.
Who'da thunk you'd ever
teach me somethin'?
You're tellin' me...
Y'get it from Lirio?
[RICARDO] No...
Long before her.
[RICARDO] Something
from so long ago...
I just wish I could forget...
but I never will.
[NADIE gasps]
[RICARDO] Look at
me all chatty...
Mus' be drunker'n I thought.
[NADIE] Nah, I'm good.
[RICARDO] All right.
[NADIE] Ricardo.
[RICARDO] Hm.
Thank you.
[RICARDO] You'll catch
your death out here.
[NADIE chuckles]
[NADIE] Yeah, it is
gettin' cold out.
Blue-Eyes, what--?
[BLUE-EYES] The man
inside's an imposter.
[NADIE] Huh?
[BLUE-EYES] I ran
a background check.
Howard Heisman, the author,
died over three years ago.
[OLD MAN] Ellis.
What's that?
I looked in a mirror.
A mirror?
And when I did...
I didn't...
like what I saw.
[OLD MAN] Are you sad?
Yeah.
I see...
Why don't you come
with me for a second.
Then... who is this guy?
[BLUE-EYES]
It's anyone's guess...
Probably a washed up con man...
or maybe...
A bounty hunter.
That is a
possibility.
Ellis.
[NADIE gasps]
My team's
already inside...
Our superiors want us to
take Ellis into custody.
[OLD MAN]
Just beyond this door.
[B-LADY B] Don't move.
[ELLIS gasps]
[OLD MAN] Hello ladies...
What's the meaning of this?
Hand over the girl,
right now.
[B-LADY B gasps]
[OLD MAN laughs]
Move it...
You're not taking her.
[BLUE-EYES] Ellis is missing
part of her memory...
the part from a very crucial
period in her life.
When you get to
your destination...
do you really think Ellis
will find happiness?
[NADIE sighs]
Hand Ellis over to us...
I promise you, it's the closest
to happiness she'll ever find...
Your journey ends here, Nadie...
For Ellis's sake, let her go.
Wiñay Marka means
'place of eternity.'
So where is it...?
And what's there...?
You do know...
so spill.
Now, Blue Eyes.
[L.A.] Do not be
deceived, Nadie.
[NADIE gasps]
[NADIE] L.A.!
What this woman is saying
is utter nonsense...
Arriving at Wiñay Marka
is exactly what's needed...
to bring happiness
to my dear Ellis.
[NADIE] So what's there?
[BLUE-EYES]
Think about this Nadie...
If L.A. thinks going
there is a good idea...
Then no happiness
awaits Ellis...
Only his sinister designs.
[L.A.] Sinister designs, huh?
Is it not true?
[L.A. laughs]
[L.A.] I believe the same
could be said of you.
[BLUE-EYES] All I am doing
is following orders.
[L.A.] I wonder...
[NADIE sighs]
What's there, damnit...?
Tell me.
Trust me, once you find out
you'll wish you never asked...
It will only bring
you suffering.
[NADIE gasps]
Well that much we
can agree upon...
The only thing you need to do
is safely deliver Ellis to me.
[BLUE-EYES] No.
I won't allow it.
You really mean that?
Yes, I do.
[L.A. laughs]
[NADIE gasps]
[RICARDO] Nadie!
[NADIE] Ricardo...
Did you just...
Ellis is gone.
[NADIE gasps]
[OLD MAN] Here.
Try opening it, Ellis.
[ELLIS]
'Kay.
Pretty.
It's glowing.
How do you feel... Ellis?
A bit different
than before...
When it was glowing the other
day my chest felt tight...
It really
hurt a lot.
But now though...
It doesn't.
Nadie.
[YOUNG NADIE] Hm?
[ELLIS gasps]
Nadie.
[YOUNG NADIE chuckles]
[YOUNG ELLIS chuckles]
[YOUNG NADIE laughs]
[OLD MAN] Mm-hmm...
[NADIE] Ellis...?!
Ellis...?!
Ellis!!
Ellis...
[ELLIS] Nadie.
[NADIE gasps]
There you are...!
Ellis!
[ELLIS] Nadie.
[NADIE] I'm sorry.
[ELLIS] I'm sorry.
[NADIE] No...
I'm the one who was wrong.
I don't really have any
happy memories of my own...
so even the little
things are important...
They're like...
everything to me.
Yeah...
You're right...
I'll remember that.
[ELLIS] Nadie. You know what?
[NADIE] Hm?
[ELLIS] I'm glad.
[NADIE] For what?
[ELLIS] You and I are friends...
aren't we?
[NADIE] Silly...
Of course we are.
[ELLIS] Let's go together...
to Wiñay Marka.
[NADIE sighs]
[NADIE] I'm in.
[NADIE] I don't know
what awaits us there...
but... if Ellis
wants to go...
we'll go.
No matter what we find...
I will stand by her side...
and protect her...
'til the end.
[MELISSA] Doug.
[ROSENBERG] Hmm?
[ROSENBERG] Hello Melissa.
Hello.
Let's head into town
and do some shopping.
That sounds great.
[ROSENBERG sighs]
What a gorgeous day.
So... We're
goin' on ahead.
Huh...? Already?
[LIRIO giggles]
Bye bye, bonita!
You find Gramps?
No, huh-uh.
Well shoot...
Wonder where he could've gone
so early in the morning...
I wanted to say goodbye.
He probably went home...
Ready?
What's that mean...?
Whatever...
We can try droppin'
by on the way back.
[NADIE] See ya!
[ELLIS] Bye bye, old guy!
[L.A.] Oof.
Ellis!
[L.A.] Ellis...
Where are you?
[group gasps]
What does this mean?
[BLUE-EYES] I am not
a believer in ghosts...
However... It is certain
there are truths stranger
than fiction out there...
apparently.