[ROSENBERG] Yes, I'm here...
Today's report, please.
[ROSENBERG] I understand.
A mantle of rainbow-colored
light soars through the heavens.
Gallant is the dance of flames
that rends the land asunder...
The roar of the spray in
frenzied, spastic tumult.
They are the culmination
of all deviltry...
Where the crimson essence
ultimately leads.
It ends soon.
Melissa.
That's a pretty gun...
Does it work?
Try shooting it... At me.
You shouldn't make
jokes like that.
Yes, I'm terrible.
"An unusual place"?
Yeah... Somewhere that's...
known for being mysterious...?
Ring any bells?
No idea...
Lo siento, hon.
Oh... damn.
But... I'll tell ya who's full
of weird stories like that...
Who, the old guy?
[STORE OWNER]
Yeah, go ask him.
But he ain't right in the head.
Don't say I didn't warn ya.
[OLD MAN]
"Unusual," huh?
[NADIE] Yeah, know
any 'round here?
[OLD MAN] Every place
around here is unusual...
Well... compared to
the city, that is.
[NADIE] Uh, yeah... not quite
what I was gettin' at.
[OLD MAN] So,
on vacation, are ya?
Sure...
You are greatly
mistaken, my dear,
if you believe you will
always get what you seek...
You mustn't seek.
Yeah, thanks, Pops...
That's deep n' stuff...
You take care now... Maybe I'll
catch ya on the flipside.
There is a place called
the Witches' Village.
[NADIE] Waitaminnit...
Witches?!
That's totally what I'm after!
So, uh, where is this village?
[OLD MAN]
Hey... easy...
[NADIE] Uh... Sorry.
[NADIE] That way...?
In those mountains?
Three mountain peaks over...
then maybe five days
by horse and carriage.
Three mountains, five days
by horse and carriage...?
Seriously? That's pretty far...
What's this place like?
It's not there anymore.
What?
It fell to ruin... 'bout ten
years ago, if I recall.
Fell to ruin...?
How come?
[OLD MAN] There was
a terrible fire.
So, what about
the people there?
Ohh... Died or fled...
Don't quite know...
These witches...
They really existed?
Sure... A couple of them
even lived in this town...
They came from that
village in the hills.
No way!
[OLD MAN] They kept their
identities hidden...
so very few people knew
about them... That's because
their village did not approve
of contact with outsiders.
[NADIE] Where are
those people now?
[OLD MAN sighs]
[L.A. giggles]
Aw... 'Zat your daughter?
No, it's my wife.
[NADIE] Hm?
That's Zaida... She fell ill
when she was very young...
She was such a beautiful woman.
She sure was.
[OLD MAN]
She was also a witch.
[NADIE gasps]
[L.A. giggles]
[OLD MAN] Zaida didn't have much
in the way of magic powers...
Lighting candles, heating up
water and the like...
And you'd never want to go near
her with a deck of cards...
But the Witches of old...
Water, land... sky...
It was almost as if
they could control
anything they imagined...
Supposedly they
could bring about
abundant harvests with
their amazing powers.
They were Gods,
if you will... Goddesses.
[NADIE] Well, yeah, if they
used their powers for good...
Uh...?
But if they chose to use their
powers for evil purposes...
they weren't Goddesses.
'Cause in the Old Testament...
There are stories about a
great beast with evil powers...
It's called... Leviathan.
[OLD MAN] It seems the
witches who left the village
gradually lost their powers...
Perhaps this world
sullied them...
or maybe the power is
in the village itself.
[OLD MAN] If it's
mere curiosity,
I'd advise against going...
Life isn't always
about forging ahead...
Sometimes you need
the courage to turn back.
Did you find anything?
[NADIE] Huh?
Yeah, sorta...
Buy that?
Not yet.
But you like it, right?
"The incandescent flames of
love burn deep within my heart."
"However... We no
longer have enough money
to fill our gas tank."
We don't?
Yeah, not so much.
Then I won't get it...
Should we get jobs?
Guess so... We're real close
to Wiñay Marka, y'know.
[ELLIS gasps]
[NADIE] I found out where it is.
Really?
[NADIE] Mm hmm.
[ELLIS] Nadie!
[NADIE] Easy...
Too hot for hugs.
[NADIE] Thanks again, Pops...
But I have to go...
For her sake...
Because I'm sure we'll
find some answers there.
[MELISSA] Is there something
you're wanting to get?
You buy me more than enough of
the things I want, darling...
So, I thought... for once,
why don't we just go out
with no real
purpose in mind.
Suppose it'll
rain on us, then.
Did you notice? Inca rose...
Remember, Doug? The first
present you ever gave me.
They look great
on you, Melissa.
[MELISSA] You told me the
power these stones have...
They make you forget
past unpleasantries...
and awaken passions
left lying dormant...
[ROSENBERG] I'm surprised
you remember.
[MELISSA] Well, it's exactly
how things turned out, Doug...
I'm so much happier now...
Let's have a fabulous day.
Yes... One we
will never forget.
[NADIE] Man,
we're strikin' out...
[ELLIS] There's no work here.
[NADIE] Yeah, findin' day
labor in a town this small
is gonna be rough... Figures.
We can try this.
That won't even buy bread.
[NADIE's stomach rumbles]
Damn it... Even the mention
of food is makin' me hungry.
That's kinda obvious.
Well, excuse me.
[ELLIS's stomach rumbles]
Uh-huh... Sounds
like you are too.
Well, excuse me.
[ELLIS] Bread.
Lirio... What...
You're giving us that?
[LIRIO giggles]
Wow, thank you!
[RICARDO] Broke again, huh?
What can ya do, right?
There's always somethin'
to spend it on...
I hear ya, we're in
the same boat...
So I found a way to
make a little cash.
Really?
You got a bounty?
[RICARDO] Wanna team up on it?
Yeah?
[RICARDO] It was Lirio's idea.
[LIRIO giggles]
Hey, thanks, guys...
but right now...
we've got some other
things cookin'...
'Kay, your loss...
[LIRIO coos]
--[NADIE] Oh.
--[ELLIS] Kitty.
[NADIE] It's a puma.
[RICARDO] How 'bout it?
Carries a hefty bounty.
Wow, you aren't kidding.
Cha-ching!
What did the cat
do to get wanted?
[RICARDO] It's killed
eight people so far.
Aha... a real man-eater.
We'll split it
fifty-fifty... You in?
Hell, yeah!
[LIRIO giggles]
Thank you, Lirio.
Uh, sorry... just noticed you've
become so well-mannered.
I am well-mannered.
You're on my foot.
[ELLIS] Oh, I am.
[NADIE] No apology?
[ELLIS] What for?
[NADIE] I take back
what I just said.
Where am I?
Ellis?
What is happening... to me?
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
[NADIE] First a vulture
and now a big kitty, huh?
[NADIE] Not sure that'll be
the most effective weapon...
Weapon...? It's a kitty.
Yeah, he's a bit more
dangerous than you realize.
Dead or alive, right?
I'm bettin "dead" is
gonna be more likely.
I getcha.
Maybe that's him...
[ELLIS] Kitty!
[NADIE] Ellis...!
What did I just say to you?!
Uh, Lirio...?
What the hell...?
Were you hiding?
[LIRIO] Mm hmm.
So then...
[ELLIS] There!
Big cat!
[LIRIO gasps]
Ricardo!
You better stay still...
Leave the rest to me.
Lirio, no!
Ellis! Stop her!
You can't...
It's too dangerous.
[NADIE] Lirio.
I understand how you feel...
but you need to
let me handle this...
Besides, I need you to take
Ricardo to a hospital.
Okay...?
Can I count on you?
Good.
I want you to stay back too.
I'm coming with.
Ellis...
No.
Okay, fine, partner.
Okay.
Nadie... It's a real
wild one... Be careful.
[NADIE] I'll be cool!
[ELLIS] Nadie's more wild
than a silly kitty cat any day.
[NADIE] What, really?
That's what matters in life...
the people you meet.
[L.A. giggles]
[L.A. gasps]
[phone rings]
Here's what you'll do...
[L.A.] Yessir.
[ROSENBERG] Sorry about that.
Did you find what you
were looking for, hon?
Yes... They had fallen
in between the seats.
Ah.
[MELISSA] Pretty, isn't it?
[ROSENBERG] Not as
gorgeous as you, dear.
[MELISSA] Now that's
going too far.
[ROSENBERG laughs]
[MELISSA laughs]
[NADIE] I was sure it
came back this way...
[NADIE] Hmm...
[CAT roars]
[NADIE] Yah!
[CAT growls]
[ELLIS] Take this!
Yeah, shoulda known better...
Thank you very much.
You are very welcome.
He's gone.
Well, damn it...
I was hopin' to
finish this by dark.
[crashing noise]
Whoa... Let's go!
Yes sir!
Looks like he's hurt.
Here's our chance.
[dull ringing]
What a nice surprise,
Ellis... You came.
L.A... What's the
meaning of this?!
[ringing]
[ringing grows stronger]
The Inca Rose!
[NADIE gasps]
[L.A. giggles]
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
[ELLIS pants]
Ellis...!
Ellis?
What's going on?
Ellis!
[NADIE] Ellis...
[ELLIS] A mantle of
rainbow-colored light
soars through the heavens.
Gallant is the
dance of flames
that rends the land asunder...
The roar of the spray in
frenzied, spastic tumult...
They are the culmination
of all deviltry...
Where the crimson essence
ultimately leads.
Can't be...!
[NADIE] Ellis?
Oh, my...! Lovely!
[L.A. shivers]
Ellis! Oh, Ellis...!
You are my Goddess!
[L.A.] Ellis!
[L.A. yells]
[NADIE] Ellis!
It's no use!
With the state she's in, she'll
have no idea who you are.
She's being subjected
to immense power...
Her soul is being released.
[NADIE and BLUE-EYES gasp]
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
Look out!
[BLUE-EYES and NADIE grunt]
What the frig is that?
[ELLIS pants]
What happened?
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
Nadie?
[ELLIS] Nadie!
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a quick announcement.
The Captain would like me to
inform you that the hurricane
which appeared this
evening has died out
and we will be moving
into calmer air shortly...
It should be a smooth
ride the rest of the way,
so please enjoy the flight.
[ROSENBERG] Hm.
[AIRPLANE CAPTAIN gasps]
[MELISSA] Doug...
Doug...
[BLUE-EYES]
Rosenberg, it seems...
has finally made his move.