[NADIE] Oh, man... what to do?
[ELLIS] Hmm...
[NADIE] Well yeah,
I mean we're still heading
that way eventually...
but there's something we
need to take care of first.
[ELLIS] Um...
Those dogs are fine
for us to eat...
The problem
is feeding him.
Besides, I'm sick of
camping all the time...
I'd do anything for a shower...
But, where's the money
gonna come from?
You are a bounty hunter,
aren't you?
[ELLIS] Hm?
Yeah, but it's
not that simple.
[BLUE-EYES]
Nadie is a bounty hunter...
It's a fact that
is as true today...
as it was yesterday.
[gun cocks]
[NADIE] All targets
are called bounties,
but each scenario is unique.
Most of the time though...
it's a suspected
criminal who skipped out
on a court date or paying
back his bail bondsman...
We call it going on the lam.
Or sometimes a victim's family
puts a price on
the assailant's head.
Occasionally, with bigger
crimes like terrorism,
a government will set
a price themselves.
[BOUNTY SALESMAN] Hm?
[NADIE] Course, the easiest
gigs are usually
the criminal-underworld
type stuff.
How come?
Bang.
[ELLIS gasps]
[ELLIS] I'm a "bang" too.
We're lookin' for some
quick and easy cash.
[BOUNTY SALESMAN] How much?
The more the better,
old timer.
[BOUNTY SALESMAN sighs]
[BOUNTY SALESMAN]
Here's one that's close.
His general location
is already known
and he has the highest price
on his head of the whole lot.
That's him.
The fee for the intel
is five percent.
Hmm... Yeah, cool.
[BOUNTY SALESMAN chuckles]
Five percent for
a job like this?
What a rip.
'Kay, we're in the clear.
No more camping or
runnin' outta gas...
let's find this guy.
Yes sir.
[RESTAURANT WALLA]
[BLUE-EYES] I see...
So they've resurfaced...
I'm heading your way now.
[BLUE-EYES sighs]
Aren't you tired
of this slop yet?
Supposedly it's good
for your diet.
[BLUE-EYES sighs]
[BOUNTY SALESMAN] Hm?
[LIRIO giggles]
Best of luck to
the both of you.
It'll be fine...
No more camping out, promise.
[NADIE] The target's
name is Guerrero.
Stole money that belonged
to a big organization.
As the story goes...
About a month ago,
he was shoppin' for
a house in this area...
Not a whole lot to go on...
But it's not a completely
useless lead, either...
If he was looking
to buy a house here...
it means he prob'ly
thought the town was safe.
Thing is...
with fugitives...
when they find a place
under the radar...
they'll usually try'n stay put
'til they're forced otherwise.
Which means he may
still be around.
[ELLIS] Hm?
What's up?
It's just...
You've given this
a lot of thought.
Well I am kind of a pro.
Oh right.
[NADIE gasps]
[NADIE] If crap hits
the fan, you run.
[engine starts]
[NADIE] Got it?
[YOUNG CLERK] Huh?
[YOUNG CLERK groans]
Wha--What the hell?!
[NADIE] You're gonna take me to
whoever it is you answer to.
Last thing these
scumbags want...
is a couple of bounty
hunters snoopin' around
their turf askin' questions.
So this is where he got
his face rearranged, huh?
You could use some
plastic surgery yourself.
Oof!
[NADIE] Right back at ya.
We did what you asked
now will you let us go?
We need to work.
[NADIE] You boys've
been a big help...
And I'm sure you
know the drill...
you never saw either
one of us, got it...?
you were out taking a walk.
[YOUNG CLERK]
How do we explain this?
[NADIE] Say... you fell
down a flight of stairs.
Who'll believe that?
[NADIE] Hello, anybody home?
[NADIE and RICARDO gasp]
Nadie.
Mm? What the...
[DIRECTOR]
I-I don't know anything...
I swear...! Please,
you gotta believe me.
If I had a peso every
time I heard that...
Well, when you're
a plastic surgeon
in this part of the world...
pryin' into the private
lives of your patients
often ends up
costin' your own life.
So you learn to not
ask questions...
Y'stay quiet...
You just do the work
and forget about 'em.
We're all aware of how
your business works, doc...
Which is why we only
have one question for ya.
What does Guerrero's
face look like now?
I...
[sighs]
I don't remember.
[RICARDO] Want me to change
your face around too?
Now my friend here's got steady
hands, but he's no surgeon...
So, y'got any last words...
...say 'em.
[DIRECTOR]
[CROWD WALLA]
[NADIE] Right, his eyes kinda
look like that one actor's
and he's got a sharp-ish nose.
[NADIE] What?
Three percent?
[RICARDO] Yeah.
[NADIE] That dirty
old bastard...
He charged me five percent
for the same intel...
Pisses me off.
Difference in experience.
Yeah, whatever...
You know I used to be
a pretty well-known
bounty hunter myself up north...
Say fifty-fifty...?
We both need the cash,
so why don't we just
split it down the middle?
Sixty-forty.
Fifty-fifty.
Lirio... Let's go.
[LIRIO sighs]
Lirio?
[RICARDO] Fifty-fifty.
[MELISSA] How's it going, honey?
Catch anything?
[MELISSA chuckles]
[ROSENBERG]
The secret to fishing...
Oh, you're awake?
...is to be patient and
allow the prey to come to you.
[MELISSA] Is that right?
[ROSENBERG] It is.
See?
I caught you.
[MELISSA] Heh. Oh Dougy.
Livin' like a king in a luxury
condo with stolen money...
This guy's got some cojones.
I'm thinkin' our best bet's
to stake 'im out here.
We have to?
Security looks pretty
tight in this place...
so much for gettin' a hotel.
[NADIE] Wiñay Marka.
[ELLIS] Hm?
If something happened to me,
could you make it
there on your own?
I just want to make sure that
you're prepared for the worst.
[RICARDO]
[shower runs]
[GUERRERO hums]
[GUERRERO] Hm?
Ah!
[ELLIS gasps]
You hear that...?
Ricardo!
I'm taking Ellis
into custody.
Hold up.
[gasps]
Who are you,
a bounty hunter?
[NADIE] Gotta be coming from
Guerrero's room.
[ELLIS gasps]
[LIRIO claps]
[RICARDO] I'll go in from above.
[NADIE] Good, then I'll come in
low.
[L.A.]
[GUERRERO]
[ELLIS] No.
Ellis.
Heh. You are in need of
this man, am I correct...?
Allow me to take
him down for you.
No way.
[L.A.] Mm?
Please Ellis?
[NADIE gasps]
[GUERRERO gasps]
[GUERRERO]
[NADIE]
[NADIE] Guerrero!
[ELLIS]
[LIRIO]
[NADIE] Ellis!
Move it!
[ELLIS panting]
[NADIE] You guys all right?!
Ellis! Lirio!
[ELLIS gasps]
[gunshot]
[NADIE groans]
Nadie.
[GUERRERO] Hand over...
the car...
Do it!
[LIRIO gasps]
[GUERRERO grunts]
[gunshot]
[ELLIS] Nadie!
[ELLIS] Nadie.
[NADIE groans]
Sonuva bitch that hurt...
Must'a slipped.
[RICARDO] Uhh...
Is it...
over already...?
Is that ice...?
What the...
[ELLIS laughs]
[NADIE chuckles]
Oh dear...
I was scolded by Ellis again.
Look forward to doing
business with you again.
[RICARDO] Here's your cut.
Oh hell yeah.
Lets see...
One, two, three, four, five...
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Wait I thought we agreed on
splitting this fifty-fifty?
Don't forget, if you'd
collected on the bounty,
the old guy would have
taken five percent.
You cheap ass.
[RICARDO]
Neither of us can afford to
throw money to the wind.
Well yeah, that's true, but...
From Lirio.
[ELLIS]
[NADIE] Ricardo.
[RICARDO] Heh.
Sweet...
Gotta love a full tank...
Let's do this again sometime.
You got it.
Do they worry you?
Yeah, me too...
No one can cheat
destiny forever.
Nadie.
[NADIE] Hm?
Is this...
Is this what...
your life was like...?
Before you
came across me?
Guess so.
[ELLIS sighs]
Then...
I'll...
I'll never suggest it again.
Well yessir.
[BLUE-EYES] For bounty hunters,
danger is a constant
companion...
And Nadie...
is no exception.