[KID ELLIS] No.
[HEINZ] It's the same
examination we always do.
Nothing to be scared of.
It's never hurt before, has it?
[KID ELLIS] No.
[HEINZ sighs]
[ROSENBERG] You seem
to be in a foul mood.
[HEINZ sighs]
[HEINZ] Rosenberg.
Did she...
refuse to go along with
the examination again?
What's that?
[ROSENBERG] Today is
Thanksgiving, I'm giving thanks.
Sorry, would you have preferred
a turkey and stuffing?
I prefer not to pander
to social norms.
My dear Dr. Heinz Schneider...
How very like you to say so...
But that is why I chose
to place her in your care.
I'll complete the exam
in the next day or two.
[ROSENBERG]
Will you be all right?
This has happened, what...?
At least three
times now, right...?
Or is it four?
The subject is
strong-willed...
It cannot be easily manipulated.
I see, then here...
Use this.
[HEINZ] Huh?
Fight the heart...
with the heart.
Okay... Shall we begin?
Ellis?
[HEINZ] "Man's destiny
is within himself."
[gun cocks]
[KID ELLIS gasps]
[KID ELLIS]
That one is my favorite.
[HEINZ gasps]
Ellis, hi... Sorry I
came in without asking.
I don't mind...
it's fine.
It's finished.
[HEINZ] Huh?
[KID ELLIS] You.
It is you... You see?
[KID ELLIS] Achoo!
Ellis, you must
be freezing...
Change out of those clothes...
I'll put another log
on the fire for you...
Come warm up once
you're dressed, ok?
[KID ELLIS] Hmm?
[HEINZ] Quickly.
[KID ELLIS]
'Kay... I got it.
[HEINZ] How are you doing?
[KID ELLIS] With what?
[HEINZ] Are you warm enough?
[KID ELLIS] Yes.
[HEINZ] Good.
[KID ELLIS] Why?
[HEINZ]
"Time does not exist...
There is only
the current moment."
Hello birdie.
[ROSENBERG] I looked
through your report...
it appears we have a problem...
Ellis has shown no recent
signs of progress.
Your point...?
My job is to collect data based
on her periodic examinations...
I only analyze my data and
report the findings...
It's not my concern
if the results
are not what you'd hoped for.
I'm sorry?
[HEINZ] Hm?
[ROSENBERG] You just
referred to Ellis as "her."
I did.
Is that a problem?
[ROSENBERG] Hm. No, no...
Not at all...
I'm simply reflecting on
how people change over time.
[HEINZ] What are
you talking about?
The subject...
That's how you've always
referred to Ellis,
if you recall...
In the past, I attributed
your use of the term
to your clinical nature.
So what happened...?
Change of heart perhaps?
[HEINZ sighs]
Who knows?
It wasn't my
intention to pry...
Guess my curiosity
got the better of me.
One can often be surprised by
what one is concerned about...
Regardless...
what's important is Ellis has
been here nearly ten years now.
Judging from my analysis
of the results thus far...
perhaps Ellis is no different
than the others after all.
So, not a witch... Yes?
[HEINZ] Her physical
abilities are far superior
to normal humans...
and while minute,
I have detected the occasional
unique emanation.
But never enough
that she's actually
caused something to happen.
Welcome back.
[HEINZ] Never mind
Maxwell's Demon...
she hasn't shown enough
supernatural power
to bend a spoon.
[ROSENBERG] Those abilities
may yet surface.
[HEINZ] I am inclined
to disagree.
[ROSENBERG] Do you wish
to part with Ellis?
[HEINZ] Once the
study concludes...
there will be no reason
for her to be here.
And you are
okay with that?
What does that mean?
[ROSENBERG] How should
I put this...?
It seems you're running away
from your own feelings, Doctor.
[HEINZ] I don't understand
what you're getting at.
[ROSENBERG] Of course you don't.
Please leave now...
The paper I'm submitting
to a conference next week
still needs finalizing.
Hm. I'll be on my way...
I will discuss the matter
of Ellis with my superiors.
It appears...
a glint of light has begun
to shine into the void...
Just a glint.
Ellis... Would you
like a cup coffee?
Ellis?
Ellis...
What did...?
[KID ELLIS] He went missing
so I looked for him...
and I found him here.
Who did this?
It wasn't me.
[KID ELLIS] He was...
my favorite.
[HEINZ] Did Rosenberg
do this...?
But, why?
Awful.
Ellis?
[KID ELLIS panting]
Are you alright?
[KID ELLIS gasps]
[HEINZ grunts]
Ellis...
Stop this now... Ellis!
[KID ELLIS panting]
You have to stop!
What a gorgeous sunset.
So it was all true...
Demons really do exist.
But then...
[KID ELLIS moans]
[HEINZ sighs]
[HEINZ] "Self discovery comes
when a man measures himself
against an obstacle."
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
[KID ELLIS panting]
That's good Ellis...
Very good. In fact
in the last month
you've dramatically reduced
your time to activation.
[KID ELLIS panting]
[ROSENBERG]
Is this data accurate?
[HEINZ] Facts are facts,
whether you like them or not.
Strange, Doctor...
Your report for the
past three months...
is identical to the one
submitted for the
same time last year.
[ROSENBERG sighs]
Look Heinz...
the study is financed
with taxpayer money...
This sort of conduct
is unacceptable.
[HEINZ] Don't try to
bait me, Rosenberg.
That data has not
been fabricated.
That's your story?
[HEINZ] If you want to
fire me, then do it.
[ROSENBERG sighs]
All right then...
I believe you...
You know...
it is gorgeous outside...
Take the rest of the day off,
maybe an excursion
out to the lake.
I'm sure Ellis would
love the fresh air.
[HEINZ] I have no intention
taking the subject anywhere.
Or have you forgotten Cartagena
Protocol on Biosafety?
Subject?
[HEINZ] Is that all?
Yes... I'll let myself out.
Keeping her
to yourself...?
Doctor...
You will regret it.
Are you alright?
So high.
[HEINZ] Hm?
[KID ELLIS] The sky...
It's way up there.
[HEINZ] Heh.
How about...
a little trip?
It's so big.
Yes, it sure is...
In fact, it has a surface area
of 28,568 square kilometers.
It's about the tenth
largest lake in the world.
But I suppose...
you don't care.
[KID ELLIS] Waves.
That's right.
[KID ELLIS] Pretty, isn't it?
Yes, very.
[KID ELLIS] It's cold.
Ellis.
Doctor...
Check it out... it's cold.
[KID ELLIS giggles]
[KID ELLIS] Mmm...
You feeling tired?
[KID ELLIS] I'm okay.
It was a day full
of firsts, wasn't it?
Yes.
[HEINZ] Did you have fun?
[HEINZ] Why don't
you get some sleep?
We still have the examination
when we get back.
Do we... have to?
Yes, we do.
[HEINZ] "In love...
there is only one law...
That is to bring happiness
to the one you love."
Just bread to eat, huh?
G'morning.
Ah good morning, Ellis...
I see you got things ready...
Why don't you relax here for
a bit while I make some soup.
Will do.
[KID ELLIS] No...
[HEINZ] Ellis...!
Ellis, calm down...!
Please Ellis, don't struggle.
[KID ELLIS] No... I don't
wanna do that anymore!
I don't wanna!
[HEINZ] Ellis...
[KID ELLIS] Don't wanna.
All right then...
No more examinations...
We won't do them anymore...
I promise.
I cross my heart...
Deal?
Ellis...
[KID ELLIS] You really promise?
Yeah... I promise.
Doctor...
[HEINZ]
"Life is not complex...
We are complex...
Life is simple...
and the simple thing
is the right thing."
Well... It looks all right...
considering it's my first
attempt at roasting a turkey...
Now... I only hope
it's cooked through.
Which one?
Hm? Wear whichever
you like most.
I like both.
[HEINZ] Oh...
quite a dilemma...
Pick the one best
suited for a party.
Party...?
There's a party?
Well, today is
Thanksgiving...
[KID ELLIS] Thanksgiving?
We've never done that.
Guess not...
Now head up and get changed.
'Kay.
So... How do I tell
when it's perfectly done?
Ellis.
[HEINZ] What's going on?
[KID ELLIS] A present.
A present...? For me...?
What's the occasion?
Ellis?
[KID ELLIS]
Because I love you.
[HEINZ gasps]
Oh, Ellis... thank you.
[KID ELLIS sighs]
I've decided...
We're leaving, Ellis.
We'll go somewhere far
away from this place.
You sure?
Yes, I'm sure...
Nothing else matters now.
Doctor.
[HEINZ] Ellis.
[gunshot]