Bienvenidos...!
Enjoy your meal at Amigo Tacos!
[BLUE-EYES] Food,
clothing, and shelter
are important to the human race.
[gun cocks]
[stomach growls]
[car door opens]
So, how'd it go?
I hate people...
So not well then?
Yeah, hey...
How much've you got?
Heh...
We can't even buy
bread with this.
[stomach growls]
Damn robotic bitch...
She's just playin' dirty.
Did you handle that...
assignment I gave you?
[B-LADY B] For your
verification...
All of the bank accounts
have been suspended...
Nadie won't be able to
withdraw a single peso
from here on out...
My next assignment?
Nothing, we're finished now.
Huh?
[BLUE-EYES]
Is that a problem?
No... I was just
under the assumption
you would begin
negotiations at this point.
Hitting her in the
pocketbook will only serve
to slow her down...
and it certainly won't
induce her to part with Ellis.
[B-LADY B] Then why bother?
Put nicely,
to educate her...
But if you want
an honest answer...
revenge.
[NADIE] What's this?
[BLUE-EYES]
Payment in full.
Your fee plus expenses,
as agreed upon...
With a fifteen percent
bonus for your efforts.
What the hell?
Your contract ends
effective today.
Hold on a minute...!
This is all comin'
outta nowhere!
[BLUE-EYES]
I'm grateful to you...
You've protected Ellis
well to this point.
What's gonna
happen to her?
[BLUE-EYES] I have no
reason to tell you that.
Again...
The girl no longer concerns you.
[NADIE sighs]
[NADIE] Keep it...
I don't want your money.
Hold on!
[NADIE] My mind's made up.
I'm stayin' here...
by Ellis's side.
I want her to understand
how naïve her decision was...
So very naïve.
Yeah not so much...
The idea is to
make some quick cash
without expending
too much effort.
Oh, I can do that.
Hm? Explain please?
The end.
[NADIE gasps]
Wow...!
I've never seen such an amazing
illusion in my whole life...!
'Kay...
Tips are welcome.
I'm miserable.
Crispy gooey nachos.
So stupid...
Why didn't I just take
the money back there
instead of tryin' to look cool?
[ELLIS] Piping hot enchiladas.
No no, if I accepted that
money I'da just regretted it
for the rest of my life
and then some.
[ELLIS] Tender cochinita pibil.
Ooh, chimichangas...
With sweet bananas...
Ellis...
While I appreciate
the sentiment,
aren't you hungry enough?
Tacos.
So you're gonna
keep at it, huh?
No the sign...
Right there.
[NADIE] Huh?
Another Amigo Tacos,
so what?
They have a poster up...
And lucky for us,
it says they're hiring.
It does...? Show me.
Just look.
Blows me away you
can read that far.
Oh yeah...
cuz I'm not normal.
Yeah, um...
You might not want to
share that too much.
Heh. Yessir.
[ELLIS and NADIE]
[STORE OWNER] Yum...
Sorry for eating in
front of you like this
but I didn't get a chance
to have lunch today.
Sure.
Let's see...
Which one is Nadie?
That's me sir.
[STORE OWNER]
And I take it you're Ellis?
Yep.
Hey, those are mine.
[ELLIS] Huh?
Ah!
Mmm. Tasty!
I've never tasted
such a delicious taco
in my entire life.
[STORE OWNER gasps]
I'm... sorry
about that...
She may not look it, but she
hasn't had the best upbringing.
[STORE OWNER] You're hired!
Huh?
Our tacos are
delicious, aren't they?
Yes.
Well not to toot
my own horn...
But between you
and me, chicas...
I put a little something extra
in the sauce the
company sends me...
It's the only way I can truly
have pride in what I serve.
[NADIE chuckles]
[crunch]
[NADIE] No kiddin'!
Mmm...!
[gulp]
This rules!
I know...
Can you taste the honey?
That's my secret ingredient.
Honey, huh...?
Oh yeah, I guess that
is what that is...
I can totally taste it!
Mmm. It makes all
the difference!
Consider yourself
hired too.
Bienvenidos...!
Enjoy your meal at Amigo Tacos!
Nadie, your smile
is too big.
[NADIE] Uh, right.
And Ellis, your smile
isn't big enough.
[ELLIS] Hmm.
[NADIE] Uh.
[ELLIS] Right.
Buenos noches, señor...
Ready to order?
How am I supposed to know what
to order if I don't have a menu?
Oh! Sorry 'bout that.
Now place the
glass on the table...
Be cheerful and energetic.
Agua!
Try it again but a
little more gently.
[whispers] Agua.
That's... not quite
what I meant.
[ELLIS] Okay let me
read back your order...
That's two
Amigo combos...
With a coffee for you sir, and
an orange juice for the lady...
Great, and I'll be right
back with your drinks.
Looks like she's finally
startin' to get the hang of it.
[ELLIS gasps]
Heh. Sorry...
My hand's got a mind of its own.
[laughs creepily]
You okay?
Okay with what?
You serious...?
That guy totally just
touched your butt.
Yeah...
He totally did.
You didn't like it,
did you?
No... Not at all.
Listen, if someone does
something you don't like...
you hafta be tough and
stand up for yourself.
[ELLIS] Umm...
Here... Let me show you
the way I would handle it.
[STORE OWNER] Hold up a sec.
[NADIE] Uh...
Those guys... I'm warnin' you,
they're pretty notorious
thugs 'round these parts...
If you start trouble with them,
there's no telling
how they'll retaliate.
No worries boss, I got it.
[STORE OWNER]
Wait... Nadie!
[THUG C laughs]
[THUG A and THUG B] Huh?
You guys need a refill?
[THUG A] Sure.
We'd love one.
[THUG A laughs]
[THUG A] Ahh!
Bitch!
Got any last words...
say 'em.
[THUG C whimpers]
So that's standing
up for yourself.
I got it!
Boss-man's sure got
some wild ideas...
Hiring us to guard the
joint at night, too...?
But... Guess I can't
complain, right?
I mean, crash space
is crash space...
[ELLIS] A lot happened today.
You sleepy?
Yes...
Because there's so many
things to remember...
Like all the different
combos and drinks
and what to say to customers.
Ain't that the truth.
[ELLIS] And also being tough.
Heh.
Standing up for myself when
someone does me wrong...
Just like you taught me today...
Nadie?
[ELLIS sighs]
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
[door chimes]
Bienvenidos...
Uh--
Sorry about the wait
there, folks...
What are you two
doing here, Ricardo?
Funny, that was
my line, Nadie.
Kinda obvious, isn't it...?
I'm working.
Yeah, same with us
more or less...
Wait, back up...
I thought you told me last time
you'd just lost your gig.
[ROSENBERG] Correct...
Buy three thousand
shares of Albright...
and to offset that,
sell off the shares I
have in Pylon Corporation.
I'll leave the rest to you.
How about some
lunch, Doug...?
This new taco place
just opened...
It's supposed to
be pretty authentic.
Amigo Tacos.
Are you not a fan
of Mexican food?
Oh no...
It's my favorite.
Be a good girl,
wait for me here.
[LIRIO] Mm.
Okay, what's this for?
You know how our little
jingle goes, don't you?
[NADIE] Yeah.
[STORE OWNER]
Go outside and sing it
while you pass these out.
Wha--?
[STORE OWNER]
I've gotta run to the bank.
Watch over the place
for me, will ya?
Sure.
[door chimes]
[ELLIS] Hmm? Ah!
Oh hi, do you want to help?
You're good at this.
[LIRIO laughs]
[door chimes]
Bienve--...
Go and hide.
♪ Taco taco taco... ♪
♪ Su-uper tasty tacos too... ♪
The yummiest tacos in the
world, Amigo Tacos - ooh!
[NADIE giggles]
Someone gonna
take my order here?
Where's our food?
Sorry.
[CUSTOMER C (M)]
Una cerveza más!
Sure.
Miss, I would love a refill.
Come on, I ain't
got all day.
This is the worst service
I've had in awhile.
[ELLIS] Thanks for waiting.
Humans can be such
selfish creatures.
Wouldn't you agree, darling?
They know you're the only one
working here at the moment...
But it's not good enough.
Please enjoy.
Not just yet...
Here's your tip.
I've made up my mind...
I'm going to show you firsthand
just how foolish
human beings can be.
You don't need
to do that.
[L.A.] Heh...
[gunshots]
[THUG A grunts]
Wait! Please don't shoot us!
I'll buy you a drink in hell...
amigo.
Waitress.
What can I get for you?
You know what
I'd really love...
You.
From the menu.
Let me see.
What do you think
I should have?
So many choices,
I can't make up my mind.
[NADIE] Amigo Tacos...!
Great specials goin' on!
Here you go.
There you are.
Uh?
[over loudspeaker]
What the hell?
I thought you were
at the restaurant!
[feedback]
Yeah, and I thought
that's where you were.
[ELLIS] Thank you.
Come back soon.
[L.A. giggles]
[ELLIS gasps]
Finally you and
I are alone...
Ellis.
I love the uniform...
You're simply ravishing.
Heh! And now...
...you're mine.
I want to create an
entire new world with you...
A place where foolish beings
like humans don't exist...
A world that belongs to just us.
Humor me for awhile,
won't you my darling...?
Just for a little while...
Please...? Ellis?
[ELLIS gasps]
[NADIE gasps]
Ellis!
You'll just hit a car.
Give it back.
Is it that precious to you?
[ELLIS] Give it back!
Now that expression is
nowhere near as lovely...
Take a look...
At your precious treasure.
Stop it.
[NADIE] Listen, if someone does
something you don't like...
you hafta be tough and
stand up for yourself.
[L.A.] Huh?
[L.A. grunts]
[door chimes]
Hell yeah!
[L.A. groans]
Ellis.
[L.A. grunts]
[L.A.] W-Wait.
Holy...
That hurts.
That really hurts... Ellis.
[ELLIS gasps]
You've... done enough.
Nadie.
I'll handle it from here.
[RICARDO] Where's Lirio?
She's in the backroom.
[RICARDO] Gotcha.
[gun cocks]
Got any last
words, say 'em.
[L.A. chuckles]
You can't kill me,
even if you want to.
I'll take that bet.
[L.A.] Ellis...
You don't actually know
where Wiñay Marka is...
do you?
Just wandering south...
driven onward by
some vague urge...
Hoping to find answers.
But I know...
And if I die...
your one link to
Wiñay Marka's location...
will be gone...
And you will never find it.
We both know you
don't want that.
[NADIE] Ellis.
[L.A. grunts]
Don't shoot!
E-Ellis.
Thank you, Ellis...!
I love you.
If you ladies
will follow me...
I will lead you
straight to Wiñay Marka.
[L.A. chuckles]
Ellis...
To think that you would
treat me in such a manner.
[L.A. laughs]
It's fine though...
Simply a part of who we are...
Ah, love...
Isn't it wonderful?!
Isn't it?
[STORE OWNER] Here...
a little thank you gift.
[NADIE gasps]
[NADIE] This is...?
[STORE OWNER] The special sauce
with the honey added in.
[NADIE] Uh... Thank you, sir.
Ellis...
It's okay to get angry...
just pull your
punches a little, kay?
Angry...?
I see...
So that's what angry feels like.
[BLUE-EYES] On that day,
for the first time...
Ellis became aware
of the emotion...
...anger.