[CHAIRWOMAN] How long
has it been now...?
There is no one alive who
can say for certain...
When early civilizations
were beginning to form
on this planet...
there was a true
need for our powers.
However...
as time passed
through the ages...
we became ostracized...
and persecuted.
Thus, in order to
avoid repeating
this unfortunate history...
we decided our only option
was to hide the entirety
of our existence
deep in the shadows of
legend and folklore.
There can be
no exceptions...
even for a being...
created by humankind.
[CHAIRWOMAN] Now that Project
Leviathan has been suspended...
there are no longer any benefits
to allowing Ellis
to remain at large.
[CHAIRWOMAN] And it goes
without saying...
that allowing her to set
foot in that place...
is out of the question.
If the legend were
to become reality...
it would place the existence of
our people in grave danger...
I'm sure you remember
the "incident"
ten years ago as well as I.
We no longer have the time
to be acting deliberately...
I'll instruct you once again...
Capture Ellis at once...
That is the collective
will of our people.
[phone call ending beep]
[BLUE-EYES] And I obey.
Because I am just
one of the flock.
[gun cocks]
Another tasteless
taco billboard.
[ELLIS gasps]
What?
[ELLIS] There.
[NADIE] Hmm?
[NADIE gasps]
[LIRIO giggles]
[RICARDO groans]
It just died on ya, huh...?
Well... I gotta say
I'm surprised ya made
it as far as ya did.
[indistinct audio]
[MECHANIC] groans
It's not looking good...
It's gonna be tomorrow
morning at the earliest.
I'll give you a call
when I'm done...
Where can I reach you?
Not too sure yet.
I see...
Y'folks travelin'
in this thing...?
Be happy to recommend
a nice hotel in town.
Ah... I could
use a room too.
Wha...? Aren't you two...
like a couple?
Uh?!
Well, you do look a
little young for him...
But how do I say this...?
You two seem like a match.
Am I wrong?
What the...?
That's none of your--
Señor...
Give us a break.
[MECHANIC] Huh?
Ooooohhh...
[NADIE grunts]
[ELLIS grunts]
I getcha...
I'll go ahead and reserve
separate rooms for all of ya.
[RICARDO sighs]
Really...! That guy's
got alotta nerve!
Look it's fer the best...
Tryin' ta explain how we know
each other would just be...
I know...
But geez... Us married?
That's crazy.
[ELLIS scoffs]
[MECHANIC] Hey!
Almost forgot!
Some coupons for
a special dinner...
It's the fanciest
restaurant in town.
Sweet...
You sure?
Yeah I don't have
any use for them...
'Specially since I buried
my wife three years ago.
Oh...
Thank you.
Your wife comes across as
a bit of a simple sort...
Treat her to a nice meal,
I'm sure she'll cheer right up.
Yeah sure.
[MECHANIC] Good luck!
[NADIE] Whoa...
What a posh room!
We'll come knock
in a little while.
Right on.
Now... Time for a
nice hot shower.
[ELLIS] We're going to
have dinner with them?
What...? Yeah...
We're not payin for it...
plus...
[ELLIS] Because you're married.
[NADIE sigh]
No, that's not why...
You like to eat somewhere
nice once in awhile, right?
[ELLIS] Is that why
you're showering?
No, it's 'cause
I wanna be clean...
You coming with?
Yessir.
Yeah...
To dinner, not the shower.
Um... Miss...?
There's only two seats here.
We have a special
kids table.
Right this way.
[LIRIO giggles]
[ELLIS sighs]
[MELISSA] Doug, I see a nice
bottle of wine here.
Care to share?
Sure.
A decanter?
[ROSENBERG] Oh, absolutely.
With wines... they can only
reach their true potential...
when given the chance to
breathe the outside air.
Just... like human beings.
[NADIE] Hm. Pretty.
You know the least you
could do is agree with me.
Why's that?
[LIRIO] Mmm...
[ELLIS exhales]
[ELLIS] Nadie.
[ELLIS gasps]
[YOUNG NADIE giggles]
[YOUNG ELLIS giggles]
[RESTAURANT WALLA]
[MAN] I love you.
I don't wanna let
go of you tonight.
[WOMAN] Me neither.
[MAN and WOMAN chuckle]
[ELLIS exhales]
Wiñay Marka.
[NADIE] Huh?
[RICARDO] You have
any idea where it is?
Huh-uh...
But we do have an
excellent guide...
He's little weird though.
You watch your back.
Well thanks...
It's nice to know you care.
[WOMAN] The only thing is...
I still need to
take care of the girl.
[MAN] Oh I'm sure she can
manage fine on her own.
It'll be okay.
[ELLIS sighs]
[RESTAURANT WALLA]
[NADIE gasps]
What the hell?
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
[RESTAURANT WALLA]
Ellis?
[NADIE] Ellis?!
[ELLIS] I'm here.
[RESTAURANT WALLA]
I apologize for
the inconvenience...
Please rest assured that
everything is now back in order.
[LIRIO giggles]
Nadie.
Ellis...
Taking a detour?
Oh man...!
This is fantastic!
[RICARDO sighs]
Oh... the coupons
don't cover booze...
Don't drink too much.
[RICARDO] I'll pay
for whatever I drink.
Okay... That's fine.
So when you run
out of money...
What will you do?
[NADIE] Hmm, what will I do...?
Back to hunting bounties?
No way...
I'll come up with
something else...
Besides Ellis doesn't dig.
I see...
That's good.
How come...?
Do you maybe not like me being
a bounty hunter, Ricardo...?
'cause I'm a woman?
Relying on your
wits and a pistol
is no way to live
your life Nadie...
That's the pot callin'
the kettle black, isn't it?
Difference with me is
it's all I know how to do.
[RICARDO] You don't need guns
to make a life for yourself...
Somethin' I didn't
realize until too late.
[NADIE] What kinda
grandpa talk is that?
You still have plenty
o' years ahead of ya...
Don't forget, you were just
mistaken for being my husband.
Heh.
Heh. Ignore me, fine.
[RESTAURANT WALLA]
Again?
[MAITRE D'] I am so sorry.
Please stay at your tables,
we're looking into it.
[RESTAURANT WALLA]
Hell-ooo!
She won't come for me.
Ricardo being
there's a problem.
The general idea is to keep him
from getting too close to Ellis.
There are ways to do it...
Get back inside.
Right.
Is there something you want
to get off your chest?
[B-LADY A] No.
Tell me...
Have you ever seen a
witch's powers at work?
Like the power
Ellis invoked?
[BLUE-EYES]
That was nothing compared
to a real witch's abilities.
They'd be far more impressive.
I assume.
Maybe... there's
some bad wiring.
[B-LADY B] Pardon me.
Would you like to go sit
with Mommy and Daddy?
[LIRIO giggles]
[ELLIS sighs]
[NADIE] What's goin' on?
Why'd they just
bring Lirio over?
[NADIE chuckles]
[RICARDO] Nadie.
[NADIE] Huh?
[ELLIS gasps]
[RESTAURANT WALLA]
[RICARDO gasps]
[NADIE] Ellis!
[NADIE] Gracias.
[NADIE] 'Scuse me!
Pardon me! Sorry 'bout that!
[NADIE] Hiyah!
[B-LADY C] Oof!
Ellis!
Once we deliver the girl to
the designated drop off point...
our mission will be completed.
It was too easy.
Uh!
Oh... Ellis.
Take the side road.
Yeah.
[tires screech]
Ellis.
[L.A.] Ahh!
He's not following.
[L.A.] Ellis...
How odd.
[B-LADY A] Incoming!
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
Nadie.
Give her back!
No can do.
Damn it, Blue Eyes!
Nadie...
Just back off...!
You're in way over your head!
Ellis...!
Are you okay?!
[ELLIS sleeping heavily]
[NADIE] Ellis!
Nadie!
[ELLIS breathing heavily]
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
[ELLIS gasps]
[BLUE-EYES whimpers]
Ellis!
[NADIE grunts]
[NADIE] Oof!
You all right?
You came for me.
Duh...
Of course I did.
They won that one.
[beeping]
[L.A. sighs]
Ellis.
[MECHANIC] I, I was
asked to do it...
They told me to say the repairs
would take until tomorrow...
so you would stay overnight...
here in town.
[NADIE] And the
restaurant coupons...
Did they give you those as well?
They did.
[RICARDO grunts]
Uh... listen...
I won't charge you
for the repairs...
That make us even?
[ELLIS and LIRIO] Hm?
Wh-What is it?
Is something wrong Ellis?
[LIRIO laughs]
[RICARDO chuckles]
[ELLIS sighs contentedly]
Um... What's up?
Do we look married?
What?
Like we're a
happy couple?
Couples are usually
a man and a woman.
[ELLIS] Hmm.
So what?
Ellis...
I can't really drive
with you right there.
Ahh...
Who cares?
[L.A. growls]
Careful...
Don't get too close.
[horn honks]
Hey... Tell me...
Be honest...
Are you acting like this...
'cause Ricardo and I spent
so much time together?
Nuh-uh.
"Nuh-uh"...
Okay... Let's go.
[BLUE-EYES] Ellis,
the artificial witch,
has no capacity for
human emotion...
That report is already...
a thing of the past.