[L.A.]
Ellis... Help me...
I was... I was tricked...
I realize that now.
I will demolish that
bastard... Oh, yes...!
With my own hands!!
[L.A.] So... I have to keep my
composure... remain myself...
no matter what.
[L.A.] It's...
It's this thing...
[L.A.] Damn you!!
[L.A. grunts]
[L.A.] Get out...
Get out from inside me...
Rosenberg...
[L.A. laughs maniacally]
[BLUE-EYES]
The heart... is frail.
Was it... me...?
I did... this?
[ELLIS] So I did do this...
I did this... to Nadie.
You did.
[ELLIS] I see.
[ELLIS] I'm sorry, Nadie...
I'm so sorry.
[RICARDO] Was that for the best?
You could have just lied to her.
[BLUE-EYES] Do you really
think she'd have been
satisfied with that...?
She isn't stupid... Besides...
Lying won't help
the situation.
[BLUE-EYES] You see... there
was once a group of people
known as Witches...
But as time passed...
they lost their powers... and
became beings of mere legend.
Recently, science roused the
legend from its slumber...
Ellis is a witch made
by the hands of man...
She is not a child of God...
However, she was endowed
with amazing powers...
[BLUE-EYES] The same
powers the witches lost.
Thanks, Lirio.
[LIRIO giggles]
[BLUE-EYES] It has begun.
[NADIE] Uhh...
So I guess I'm not dead?
Nadie!
How 'bout...
some water?
Nadie...
[NADIE gasps]
She'll be fine...
I'm sure she's just relieved.
Thirsty?
'Preciate it.
Not to sound mean,
but why are you here?
To thank you... I mean,
you did save my life.
[NADIE] Hm.
Would you stop looking
at me like that...?
I promise it's not drugged.
[NADIE groans]
Ugh... Bitter.
It's coffee, Nadie.
If it's not strong,
what's the point?
[NADIE] I feel like
an invalid here.
You're fine now,
aren't you...?
Ellis should have healed
all your injuries.
A witch... huh?
Yes... The same as me.
Here I thought you had
something important to say.
I see... That's why you
told me that story before.
Right.
So what's your objective?
Which one?
Official? Or personal?
Wait... Hold on...
So you're actually a witch?
I told you I am, didn't I?
Do you believe me?
Try turning this into iced
coffee... Then maybe I will.
Yeah, fine.
Wha... For real?
Um... Yeah, not so much.
[BLUE-EYES] I'm descended
from the witches...
But... I don't have
their powers...
The powers known as magic...
I yearned for them...
researched them...
I tried every way imaginable...
But to no avail...
I was left with nothing...
Almost nothing...
There was the overwhelming
feeling of desolation...
But my sense of yearning
never subsided...
In fact, it continued to grow
stronger and stronger.
[RICARDO] So that's why...
[BLUE-EYES] I wanted to
see one... a real witch...
I thought if I could
touch her powers...
maybe it would spark
something in me too.
That was my personal mission.
And the official?
[BLUE-EYES]
To protect our people...
There was a government
project that tried
to recreate the witches
under the guise
of helping the nation...
That part you know.
[BLUE-EYES] Our people did not
look kindly upon the project...
The Witches were beings
who were laid to rest
by the passage of time...
Their slumber should not have
been disturbed so casually...
Nor should Man have ever been
given control over our kind.
[BLUE-EYES] That's why our
people set out to do everything
within our means... and
though it took some time...
We drove the project into
the ground... But then...
[BLUE-EYES] One man...
One man relit the candle that
was supposed to be extinguished.
[BLUE-EYES]
Rosenberg...
And it is my job to put a
stop to his sinister designs.
[BLUE-EYES] But I abandoned
the job before I could finish.
[NADIE] Abandoned?
[BLUE-EYES]
It's like I told you...
I wanted to see a
witch in person...
So, when I was ordered to
bring Ellis into custody...
[RICARDO] I had no idea
that's what you were up to.
[BLUE-EYES] Considering no
one's shown up to replace me...
I assume they must have
scrapped that plan, though...
Honestly, I'm just glad I
didn't follow through with it.
[NADIE] What was
up with Ellis...?
It's like she was
possessed... Or...
[ELLIS pants]
[ELLIS] A mantle of
rainbow-colored light
soars through the heavens.
Gallant is the dance of flames
that rends the land asunder...
The roar of the spray in
frenzied, spastic tumult...
They are the culmination
of all deviltry...
Where the crimson essence
ultimately leads.
It's a passage from the
legends of our people...
It celebrates
the great powers...
that only the true
witches possess.
The true... witches...
Earth, water, the sky...
You're sayin' they're capable
of manipulating all
things under the sun?
[BLUE-EYES] Yes.
They're gods.
Well... They have...
the power of gods.
And that power...
is what Rosenberg seeks...
There's no way to be certain how
much of the text he's read...
but without a doubt...
Ellis was found to have
that same capacity.
[ELLIS] I get it.
[NADIE gasps]
[ELLIS] Finally, the truth.
Ellis.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
Still no luck?
She won't even say
one word to me...
I'm sure it's because
of what you said.
In time, she would
have found out...
Besides...
It's not too late for you.
[NADIE] What?
I mean, there's still time
for you to turn back...
I never could figure her out...
She's just so pure...
so innocent.
Yeah, same goes for me...
I spent so much time tryin'
to keep up with her...
I couldn't just let her go.
We have that in common.
Well, whaddaya know...
That's why... I want to let
Ellis choose for herself...
to discover her
own path in life.
After all... staying
true to one's own heart...
That's what's most
important, right?
Oh, my... Another hot day...
Yesterday's storm
was your doing, yes?
Wait a sec...
How'd you know?
Of course I know...
I know everything about
the power of the witches.
Well, I don't want...
any of that.
It's a power...
that only the noble chosen
are permitted to possess...
Wanting has very
little to do with it.
Don't want it.
Why not?
Because it hurts the
people I care about.
That all depends
on you, dear...
Power can be used for
good or evil... And while
it may have overwhelmed
you a bit yesterday...
in due time, you will learn
to impose your will on it...
Once you have, you'll
never hurt anyone again.
[ELLIS] I don't want it.
[OLD MAN] Hm?
[NADIE] Uh oh.
[OLD MAN sighs]
[NADIE] Ellis.
Where're you going?
Talk to me.
[ELLIS] Bye bye...
Nadie.
Hold on!
[BLUE-EYES] Nadie...
You can't go after her.
[NADIE] But...
she was crying.
[BLUE-EYES] I know...
But Ellis needs to try to
find the answers on her own.
[NADIE] No... you just
don't get it, do you?
For her sake,
let her be...
That is what it means
to be free, right?
[NADIE] Not even a little bit...
Ellis is lost...
and she's suffering...
How am I supposed
to leave her alone?
That's called
being a meddler.
[NADIE] I thought I was
free for a long time...
'cause I was alone...
It's not that I wouldn't
depend on anyone...
It's that I couldn't. Even when
I went down the wrong path,
I had no one to
steer me right again.
[NADIE] You think freedom
is such a good thing...
But you'll find out
soon enough...
Being free's actually harder...
and more painful.
Nadie...
[NADIE] Guess I
wanted someone...
who would be there
for me... Always have.
She's got a good soul...
That's why Ellis
opened her heart to Nadie
in the first place...
I don't think those two
should ever be apart.
[ELLIS] You wanna come with me?
Ellis...
[ELLIS] Do you wanna...
come with?
[L.A.] To Wiñay Marka?
[ELLIS] Not there.
How 'bout...
somewhere... far away?
Thanks, lemme know
if you happen to see her.
[BLUE-EYES] Nadie,
get in... I found Ellis.
[ELLIS] You like it?
[L.A.] Well, you bought it
for me, didn't you...?
So of course, it's
delicious... Thank you.
[ELLIS] Let's get
moving once we finish.
[L.A.] Sounds good to me...
My darling.
[phone rings]
[L.A. gasps]
[L.A. screams]
L.A.?
Hey, Blue-Eyes.
[BLUE-EYES] Hm?
I was out of line
earlier... Sorry...
You're actually a pretty
good person, aren't you?
Now I see.
I think I understand...
what he was saying back there.
"He" who?
[BLUE-EYES] Ricardo.
He said something...?
About me?
Well, it really
wasn't anything big.
I didn't have any particular
reason when I picked you...
so I guess I just got lucky.
Odd choice of words for
the person who betrayed you.
Remember, though,
I'm a traitor too.
Um... Oh, yeah, right.
[L.A. cries]
What's the matter...?
L.A. Are you okay?
[L.A.] But I broke it...
that bastard...
Damn you, Rosenberg!
[ELLIS gasps]
[L.A.] Damn it! Damn it!
I'm somebody...! I'm me!!
[L.A. yells]
Ahh... That's much better...
He's gone now... Thank goodness.
[L.A.] Everything's
okay now... Ellis.
[L.A.] Ellis?
[L.A.] Where are
you going...? Wait...
We're together now... Ellis!
Ellis.
I won't let go...
No matter what.
[ELLIS] Why wouldn't you...?
I don't want to
hurt you anymore...
That's why I said goodbye.
[NADIE] Dummy...
Say something
like that again...
and I promise I'll
never forgive you.
[NADIE] You're so
little, and yet...
you're thinking about such
big things all by yourself.
[ELLIS] Yeah, but...
[NADIE] Try putting
yourself in my shoes...
We want to get to
Wiñay Marka, right...?
Isn't that why we've
come all this way...?
I've made up my mind,
you know...
I'm going to protect you
with everything I've got.
So you don't
have to worry...
I don't care about
some witch's powers...
If we make it to Wiñay Marka...
we may find the answers we've
been looking for all this time.
It'll be fine...
I'll be by your side no
matter what happens...
and I will never
let you suffer alone.
Okay...? Partner?
Yes sir.
[BLUE-EYES] The heart
is frail... But...
when two hearts are
there for one another,
they are stronger... than steel.
Feel anything?
No, I don't feel a thing.
What is this place?
Ladies, I have been waiting...
for both of you.
Oh, yeah...?
Who are you?
[ROSENBERG chuckles]
I know him.
[NADIE] What?
I do... I know him.
It has been a
long time... Ellis.