♪ Mariachi music ♪
[dissonant note]
Way to go, Miguel.
[dissonant notes]
[MIGUEL chuckles]
[MAN A] Wow, two
screw-ups in one song.
Just something I do
for the fans...
Gives the show a
little edge, you know?
If only you could play
guitar as slick as you talk.
So the girl's
a pro?
She's friggin' lucky
is what she is, man.
Yeah... But luck
is prob'ly all it is.
[MIGUEL] Sorry this
took so long.
Uh!
Hey.
Uh... Yes?
[BOUNTY HUNTER C]
You see either o' them,
you give us a call, all right?
We're stayin' at the
hotel on the corner.
Look at that
photo on the left...
That there's the bounty we want.
And the girl on the right
is the bounty hunter
that's runnin' her.
Everything goes as planned
we'll give you a cut.
Heh, heh, heh.
Thanks guys. Sounds good.
[MIGUEL] Don't know
the little girl...
But that other picture...
...was Nadie.
[gun cocks]
[ELLIS] Miguel... My love...
From the first moment
I laid eyes on you,
I have loved you
with all of my heart.
[ELLIS (deeper voice)] Oh Nadia,
I feel the same way...
Life without you is
a life not worth living.
And the incandescent
flames of love burned deep
within the hearts of Miguel and
Nadia, until the end of time.
Nadie...
These flames of love...
How hot are they?
Beats me.
[ELLIS] You really don't know?
[NADIE sighs]
That stupid story
is just fiction...
Love is nothing
more than a myth...
And relationships
are nothing more than
a game of Fool-Or-Be-Fooled.
Do you... hate men?
No, I don't.
I swear, I don't.
[NADIE] I'll admit, I was the
one who suggested you buy a book
to give you something to
do on the long bus ride...
But why'd you pick one
that was so trashy?
Because the name
was like yours.
Funny 'cause that's the part
that pissed me off most...
Even more so with
the guy's name.
Miguel?
[NADIE grunts]
[MIGUEL]
'Ey Nadie!
Nadie, is that you?!
[NADIE] No... can't be.
Thought I
recognized you!
Gosh, how long has it been?
Come give your old pal a...
[MIGUEL] Ahh!
[MIGUEL groans]
[NADIE] Heh.
The incandescent
flames of love...
burned deep within their hearts.
[MIGUEL laughs]
I see your punches
haven't lost their sting...
And I see your face still
makes an awesome punching bag.
Y'have to admit,
it's quite a coincidence...
Who'da thought we'd be
reunited in a town like this?
Sounds like destiny at work.
Sounds like bullcrap.
Oh yeah...?
Then maybe I'm destined
for someone else.
Like perhaps
your friend here.
Just ignore the idiot, Ellis...
Remember what I said.
Never trust a man,
for any reason.
Nadie, you're awful...
That's crazy talk...
Wait, don't tell me you're
still mad about that thing?
[NADIE] What? I don't know
what you're talking about.
Since you seem to have
removed it from your memory...
I'll go ahead and
tell the story...
Our relationship was a...
So Miguel... Are you
asking to get hit again?
[MIGUEL whimpers]
How much longer you
gonna be on your break...?
We're expecting
customers any minute.
Not long... I'll hurry.
Don't forget you were
hired out of charity...
Start pulling your weight
around here or you're gone!
[acoustic guitar plays]
[YOUNG MIGUEL] Miss Ruiz...
the manager is looking for you.
What the hell
does he want?
Okay, I lied. Manager's
not even here today.
Knowing these people
they're probably making you
do all the crappy jobs, huh?
Go ahead and take
your time eating.
Gracias... Miguel.
♪ Mariachi music ♪
[dissonant note]
[YOUNG MIGUEL] You need
a solid instrument
to be a good Mariachi...
And my guitar's about
the cheapest you can buy.
Unfortunately, there's only
so much I can do with it.
If there was a way to
get some extra cash...
the first thing I'd do
is go buy a better one.
I don't improve...
My ass is fired.
[YOUNG NADIE] Here.
It's not much but
it should help.
That's your week's pay...
I couldn't take that.
[YOUNG NADIE] I insist...
Don't worry, I have
more tucked away.
Got nothin' else
to spend it on...
I want to hear you
at your best...!
Okay?
Nadie.
I promise I'll
spend it wisely.
[YOUNG MIGUEL] Absolutely
stunning, my dear.
Your beauty shines even
brighter than before.
Are you sure I
can have this...?
Miguel...
I just happened to receive
a windfall yesterday...
And who better to share
my fortune with than you?
Nadie, hey...
You must be heading
back from shopping...
I was hoping you'd be
free later this week...
There are a few things I
wanted to talk to you about.
Uh--
Aahh!
[YOUNG MIGUEL groans]
To hell with men.
[MIGUEL] I feel horrible
about what I did...
I really do.
But I... I've changed,
Nadie. I've matured.
Heck I've even become a
halfway decent Mariachi.
Thanks for paying the bill.
Please let me buy you
dinner and apologize...
I want to pay back
the money you gave me.
No, the tacos were
more than enough...
Let's get moving, Ellis.
Yes sir.
Tonight...
I'll be in front of the clock
tower in the town square.
I'll wait as
long as it takes.
[NADIE sighs]
I'm beat...
We should take a nap...
Or sump'm.
Aren't you going?
What'd I tell you...?
You can never trust men
where love is involved...
Especially not him.
He says he's an
accomplished mariachi now?
Please, what a crock...
If I run to him like
some lovesick fool...
I'm sure he'll just
end up bamboozlin' me
out of more money anyway.
I am friggin' done with
bein' screwed over by men.
[NADIE] Like he actually
plans to pay me back...
How careless to leave my
darling Ellis all alone.
Oh dear...
I can't help myself.
When falling in love...
One tends to lose sight
of everything else.
[L.A. chuckles]
[clock dongs]
Guess Nadie's smartened
up a bit, oh well.
Miguel.
Glad you could make it, Nadie.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
I can't stay...
My friend is waiting.
If you worried why don't
you give her a call...?
Tell her you'll be
out late tonight.
[NADIE] Quit jerkin' me around
and just give back
the money you owe me.
You know, 'cause of you
I was able to become
an honest man...
I could spend the whole
night thanking you
and it wouldn't be enough.
Let us thank the good
Lord for reuniting us.
Salud.
[NADIE sighs]
What are you doing?
Idiot...
He's playing you again...
He's a lying liar...
and a rat...
and a cheat.
[NADIE] Is he in
the john or something?
Hey...
either of you happen to see
where my friend got off to?
Can't help.
You know the guy
I sat down with?
Did you see where he went?
Sorry, no.
'Scuse me...
Anyone seen my friend...?
He was wearin'
a Mariachi suit...
The man who was
at your table...?
He left earlier by himself.
That dirty snake!
Awright, who's got the
crappiest Mariachi band in town?
[MANAGER] Sure, Miguel's been
playing here for a long time.
Well, until three days ago.
What was three days ago?
That's when we'd
finally had enough
of his crappy performances...
Loser was chasin'
customers away.
I don't know what your business
with the guy is so forgive me...
but if I can offer
some advice...
Stay away from Miguel.
He's nothin' but trouble.
[BARTENDER] Nothin' but
a smooth talking womanizer.
Yeah, thanks buddy...
Don't need to tell me.
Can't tell you where he is now
but I'm sure it's not far...
Think he was hatching
another scheme.
Thought I overheard
him say somethin' about
his cash cow comin' in...
some old friend in town.
An old friend in town...?
Aw crap.
[knocking]
Who's there?
[MIGUEL] It's Miguel.
We met this afternoon.
Nadie asked me to come get you.
Nadie?
That's right.
Here's our stop.
[LIRIO] Heh!
[NADIE] Ellis!
[phone rings]
[DESK CLERK] You mean your
friend with the blond hair?
She left with a man
just a minute ago.
[NADIE] Where'd they go?
Sorry...
They didn't say.
[DESK CLERK] Um... Miss?
Uhh...
Where's Nadie?
Close...
Should be here any minute now.
[approaching footsteps]
Lourdes. It's about
time you showed up.
[BOUNTY HUNTER A] Heh.
Oh it's you guys...
What's going on?
I recall a conversation where
you promised to contact us
as soon as they got to town.
No worries,
I hadn't forgotten...
I was planning to bringing
her right to your hotel,
I just had to take care of
a few other things first.
But hey, if you're willing
to give me my cut right now,
I'll hand her over to you,
no questions asked.
I just need the money...
How much is my cut?
[BOUNTY HUNTERS laugh]
[MIGUEL] Heh, heh, heh.
[BOUNTY HUNTER B]
We're feelin' generous today.
Why don't we just give
you everything we got?
Yeah, that's cool.
You sure? 'Cause we'd just
be gettin' it right back.
[MIGUEL] Uhh...
[gunshot]
[MIGUEL] Wh-What is this?
[BOUNTY HUNTER A] Apparently
you got trouble keepin'
your hands off the ladies.
[MIGUEL] What?
[BOUNTY HUNTER B] The boss
of a certain little town
is pissed at you...
He's telling everyone 'bout
how you "ruined his daughter."
See...?
He's real pissed.
[BOUNTY HUNTER B] That got sent
to every hotel in the area
just a minute ago.
[BOUNTY HUNTER A] Y'got a pretty
sweet price on your head, boy.
Here we were
waiting for our goose...
when all of a sudden
our golden egg
came rolling in
right at our feet.
Who, that guy again...?!
People always mix us up...
You're not the first...
Come on man,
you gotta believe me.
I'm just a poor
struggling Mariachi...
I'd never even consider
putting my hands
on the daughter of some boss!
"A Mariachi who
talks too much."
Oh yeah, this is you.
The guy you're looking
for is a Mariachi too...
I know where he is,
you want I can take you to him.
[BOUNTY HUNTER C]
Says here to watch out
for your silver tongue.
And too bad for you,
also says "dead or alive."
[BOUNTY HUNTER A laughs]
Listen, I've got some
money coming in...
Let's talk...
[BOUNTY HUNTER A groans]
[NADIE] He may be a no good,
womanizing liar...
but he and I still
have some history.
[MIGUEL] Nadie?!
Ellis... Come out.
Okay.
[NADIE] Get back inside,
kill the lights and don't move.
Yes sir.
Awright, you got
two choices here...
Either walk away or fight me...
I'd go with the first one.
Got any last words...
say 'em.
[gunshots]
[MAN D] 'member hearin' about
those bounty hunters in town?
How much you want to bet
that's them shooting?
[MAN E] Geez. This town
is getting too dangerous.
[gunshot]
[LOURDES gasps]
Hey Ellis... Still alive?
Still alive.
Miguel... It's over...
But I got a crap-ton of
questions I gotta ask you...
Come on out.
Miguel... I said,
the coast is clear.
Miguel?
[LOURDES] Ah! Miguel!
[LOURDES] Oh God no!
Miguel, stay with me!
Why did this happen...?
You promised you'd take me
away from this town forever!
[LOURDES sobs]
[NADIE] Ellis... Let's go.
[NADIE] Ellis.
[ROSENBERG] Good morning,
Miss Hayward.
Good morning,
Mister Rosenberg.
How are you today?
Could I have a brief
word with you?
I was planning to come speak
with you about this later...
But recently your
reports have been
coming in
consistently late.
Just wanted to make
you aware of it.
Yes, of course...
I'll issue a stern warning
to my underlings...
Good day.
Heh. "Underlings"... nice.
[ROSENBERG chuckles]
[ROSENBERG] Interesting...
Seems a stern
warning is in order.
Did it not turn out
just like I said...?
Men are a breed that
simply cannot be trusted.
That's why you never
blindly follow a man
who says he has
feelings for you.
But you followed
after Miguel.
And then that other lady
said she was planning on
going with him too.
That's true...
And you know what...?
I'm sure the list of women he's
deceived over the years is long.
[ELLIS] Was he a bad man?
Yep...
Real bad man.
Thing is...
Even when you know it...
sometimes you just can't
bring yourself to hate 'em.
And that's especially true
between men and women.
So why...?
So why what?
[ELLIS] The incandescent
flames of love.
It doesn't work that way--Eh!
[NADIE tearfully] Stop it,
there's nothing to cry about!
[ELLIS sobs]
[NADIE] What are you
crying for anyway?
[ELLIS tearfully] What?
[NADIE] Forget it...
Just... stop crying.
[ELLIS] Yes sir.