Man tends to fear and yearn for
any power he does
not understand...
This facility was built
for that very reason...
To monitor the Witches' village.
So you're... Rosenberg.
Ellis... You have
traveled a great distance
in search of the truth,
have you not?
You wish to know
if it was indeed you
who killed Doctor Schneider.
Only one person in the world
knows the answer you seek...
And that is me.
Tell me... I want
to know the truth.
The answer...
is right here...
[ROSENBERG cocks gun]
[NADIE gasps]
[ROSENBERG] Hmph.
[NADIE] Ellis.
[BLUE-EYES] Artificial life
forms react in extreme ways
to fragments of their memory.
[ROSENBERG] You two have a
truly close relationship...
As someone who has watched
over your progress...
it brings me a
great deal of joy.
[NADIE] Watched over us?
Truth be told, you ladies could
show me a bit of gratitude...
I'm the one who orchestrated
this journey of yours.
What do you mean?
[ROSENBERG] If I set Ellis
loose with her memory wiped...
and created a critical situation
by placing a bounty
on her head...
it was a simple deduction that
the descendants of the witches
would assign her an escort...
And the bounty hunter who
just happened to be chosen...
was you... Nadie...
In time, a camaraderie was
bound to develop between you...
That part also turned out
just as I anticipated.
[NADIE] So you've been
pullin' everyone's strings
this whole time.
Oh, yes, and that's not all...
I fanned the flames of
that boy's obsession...
in hopes of bringing your
two hearts together as one.
Ellis... Yes, my dear,
that's the name you were given.
[L.A.] Open your eyes...
my Ellis.
I don't understand... Why
would you go to such lengths?
What do you hope
to accomplish...?
What's your goal here?
The Witches' powers,
of course.
[NADIE gasps]
Everything I have
done to this point...
has been to awaken
the powers within Ellis.
But in order to activate
those dormant abilities...
Ellis must be driven to
the brink... Only then...
when her powers have been
enhanced by her emotions,
will the person she cherishes
most be taken from her.
[NADIE gasps]
Yes, Nadie, that's right...
You see what I'm saying...
I've prepared a role for you
in Ellis' awakening as well...
as a sacrifice.
[RICARDO] That's enough.
Oh, look...
[ROSENBERG chuckles]
It's the bounty
hunter I hired...
Don't feel bad...
All I asked of him...
was to keep an eye on you two...
and to retrieve L.A. whenever
he got out of control.
This is actually our
first face-to-face...
We always communicate by phone.
You're the one who
scrapped our contract
without any explanation...
Now lose the gun.
If I must... Suppose
there's no rush...
I can wait until the
Witches' Village...
Before I have to kill you.
[RICARDO] How naïve...
I don't recall saying
I'd let you live.
It's not a job anymore...
I've made it my mission to
protect these girls.
You don't say...
I'll buy ya a drink
in hell... amigo.
[NADIE] Don't shoot!
Why shouldn't I?
Because... we still
don't have an answer.
Well, you're not as
stupid as you look.
So then... We'll meet at the
Witches' Village, shall we?
Why are you here?
[ELLIS pants]
[NADIE] You're awake.
You okay?
I'm okay.
Where the hell
have you been?
I managed to obtain some new
information regarding Rosenberg.
[NADIE] He showed up earlier.
Yeah, um...
He's got some issues.
So... he's making his move.
Who's there?
Rosen... berg?
Your time has come, L.A.
But I... But I despise you!
I'll demolish you... Bastard!
[L.A. yells]
[L.A.] Wha...? Why?
Like Man prostrating
himself before God...
You, too, are incapable
of defying me.
Stay away from me...
Stay away...! Please, no!
Get out... get out...
Get out of my head!
There's no need
for you to suffer...
Even your feelings for Ellis...
are no more than a part of your
personality I manufactured.
You're lying... Stop it...!
I love her... My Ellis.
[L.A. shudders]
The "love" you feel...
is something that I gave to you.
Liar... No...
[L.A. weeps]
Now... cast aside your emotions.
[ROSENBERG chuckles]
[BLUE-EYES] "Maxwell's
Demon" was a theory
proposed during the
nineteenth century.
Rosenberg's father,
one of its key researchers,
put considerable effort
into making it a reality...
which led him to
the "witches' powers."
What's Maxwell's demon?
[BLUE-EYES] You don't know?
[NADIE] Yeah, no.
It's a theoretical model
created in an attempt
to halt the
increase of entropy,
breaking the Second Law
of Thermodynamics...
Entropy refers to the movement
of molecules exciting
surrounding molecules, causing
them to begin moving as well.
It assumes the existence
of an entity, or "demon,"
capable of preventing the
natural movement of molecules,
an exchange of energy
which completely negates
Newton's Second Law.
Should I continue?
[NADIE] Can you explain
it more simply?
[BLUE-EYES] There's a scientific
theory called Maxwell's Demon...
And if it were a reality...
whole bunches of power
could be produced with no
real limitations... Better?
[NADIE] Don't hafta be a bitch!
[BLUE-EYES] Shall I try one
more time with smaller words?
[ELLIS] Go on.
To prove his hypothesis...
Rosenberg's father moved
his family from Berlin...
which was still behind the
Iron Curtain at the time...
and sought political
asylum overseas.
[BLUE-EYES] When the
U.S. Government obtained
samples of Witch DNA...
his research was approved
as an official defense
project... But soon afterward...
The elder Rosenberg was
cut from the team altogether.
[NADIE] Why?
[BLUE-EYES] That's the
government for you...
The Feds took his research away
and left him with nothing...
In despair,
Rosenberg's father...
[gunshot]
[YOUNG ROSENBERG shudders]
The Feds drove him
to his death...
and Rosenberg has
not forgotten that...
Surely he's plotting revenge.
And you think... he's
trying to use Ellis' power
to make that happen?
[BLUE-EYES] Most likely.
That's crazy...
There's no way in Hell
I'm lettin' him use
Ellis like that!
[ELLIS] I have to go.
Because he...
has the answer I need.
Ellis.
[ROSENBERG] I have to say,
it's a good look for you.
[ROSENBERG] Here...
I have a job.
[ROSENBERG] If you would...
dispose of this man for me.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
Poor kid, she tuckered
out so early.
I'm getting sleepy too.
Guess you're
still a kid then.
'Kay, then I'm not tired.
[NADIE chuckles]
[BLUE-EYES] You sure
about this intel?
We just confirmed it.
L.A. is completely
under Rosenberg's control...
It would appear his
obsession with Ellis
has been wiped clean
from his memory.
He's an artificial life form...
Without a shred
of emotion left, he's become
a virtual killing machine.
He will do Rosenberg's
bidding, no questions asked.
Great, so now...
he's comin' after me, huh?
Do you have a plan?
[RICARDO] Yeah...
Look after Lirio for me.
[NADIE] Wait.
I'm coming with you.
[RICARDO] You'll be in the way.
Not listening.
[RICARDO] I'm the
one he's after.
That doesn't mean you have
to go in there all by yourself.
But if something were
to happen to you...
then who would
take care of Ellis?
Yeah, but...
letting you risk your life
without backup just seems...
[RICARDO] So pay me.
[NADIE] Huh?
Hire me and it
becomes a real job...
That way it's not for you...
it's for the reward.
Greedy much...?
[NADIE] Ooh, ouch!
This is all I got.
Keep the change, amigo.
You better come back...
Lirio will be waiting for you.
I know.
I'll be waiting... as well.
[L.A.] Hmm.
Ricardo.
[LIRIO gasps]
Out of ammo, huh?
That... is... mine.
Something... that's
precious... to me...
It's... disappearing.
No, wait... this is not it...
What's truly... precious is...
[L.A. gasps]
Wait, where am I...?
What am I doing out here in
the middle of the desert...?
I have to go...
I have to go to my Ellis.
Ellis... I'm coming
for you, Ellis.
[gunshot]
[L.A.] Mm?
You are...?
I'm not letting you
anywhere near her.
Anyone who gets
in my way, sir...
[L.A. giggles]
...will die.
As it should be.
When we find her...
we'll call you.
I should... go with you.
No, I think you two
should stay here.
[L.A. grunts intensely]
Where are you...?!
Where the hell are you?!
[L.A. grunts intensely]
[L.A. pants]
[L.A.] Where are you...
Tell me where you are...!
Show yourself!
[L.A. grunts intensely]
[RICARDO] Nadie.
[L.A.] Where are you?
Where are you?!
[L.A.] Huh?
[L.A.] There you are!!
I'll buy ya a drink
in hell... amigo.
Ellis... You're here...
I'm so glad you came for me...
[L.A. grunts weakly]
Now I know why... I fell...
in love with you, Ellis...
I know.
It wasn't the man who gave
me the... capacity to feel...
It was you.
My dear... Ellis...
Ellis... To me... you are...
...everything.
Ahh... I'm starting
to feel... sleepy...
Ellis... Smile for me
one last time...
I want it to be the last
thing that... I see.
You're so wonderful...
my... Ellis.
Lirio.
Thank God... So they're
both doing all right?
[BLUE-EYES] Yes...
The job is finished.
So then... L.A. is...?
[BLUE-EYES] Dead.
Um... Blue-Eyes...?
Why do you suppose Lirio ran off
to go looking for Ricardo...?
She always used to
wait so patiently.
Perhaps... Lirio's no
different from me.
Maybe as she watched
over you two...
something...
changed inside of her.
We'll head back right away.
Wait until we--
Well, this journey began
with just the two of us...
What do you say we go the rest
of the way without them...?
You in?
Yessir... Partner.
[NADIE] Hm.
All right... Let's move.