[ELLIS gasps]
[ELLIS laughs]
Oops.
[POLICEMAN A] You're s'posed to
keep it on the stick, bonita.
My name's not
Bonita... It's Ellis.
[POLICEMAN A] Don't think I've
seen you around town before...
You on a trip or something?
We are going south.
[POLICEMAN A] South?
South where?
I don't know.
[POLICEMAN A] How could you
not know where you're going?
[ELLIS] Uhh...
Hold on... that face...
Do I know you...?
Ya look familiar...
Huh?
Thanks for
waiting, Ellis...
Oh... My friend givin'
you trouble officer?
Trust me, whatever it was,
she's too naïve to know it.
You're that bounty
hunter, aren't ya...?
C'mon... let's go.
[POLICEMAN A grunts]
[engine starts]
Ellis... Hang on tight.
Look!
Bitches!
Phew! We cut it close there.
Mine now.
Good for you.
[BLUE-EYES] Ellis is pure...
...and innocent.
[gun cocks]
Ahh, damn it.
[ELLIS] We're stuck.
Yeah, thanks.
Anything you can do?
Like what?
Um... You know
like Moses.
Part the rocks and make a path,
like he did with the Red Sea.
What's a Moses?
Just forget it...
Never mind.
Guess we just have
to turn around.
Rain.
[NADIE] Huh?
Oh great...
This sucks.
We have no roof.
Come on...
Let's go find some
shelter 'til this lets up.
Yes sir.
[siren blares]
Name... Josha Clreosky...
Male, aged forty-five...
Got an employee ID from
Kilroi Medicine Manufacturing
but it's three years old.
[phone rings]
[ROSENBERG] Rosenberg here.
[ASSASSIN] It's done.
That's good news,
thank you.
Let's try that house.
Yes sir.
Huh?
[NADIE] What's wrong...? Ellis?
[splash]
Ah! What the hell?!
Dummy...
What were you doing?
He was in the river.
Okay... You jumped
in to save a lizard?
[ELLIS] Mm-hm.
[NADIE] I do not
get you sometimes.
[door squeaks open]
[NADIE sighs]
Much better... I wonder
if anyone lives here.
Like him?
[NADIE] Hm?
Um, hey sorry...
This was the only place we could
find to get out of the rain.
Uhh... Hello...?
You there...? Asleep?
Asleep.
For the rest
of eternity.
Achoo!
Oh... Get those
clothes off...
You'll catch a cold.
[ELLIS] Yes sir.
And we better get that
"jewelry" off while we're at it.
Or you'll catch a cold.
[NADIE] Here.
Huh?
Coffee...
It'll warm you up.
Any cream?
I couldn't find any but
there is some sugar...
One?
Two.
[NADIE] You got it.
Is there enough for him?
[NADIE] Lizards don't
drink coffee, Ellis.
Oh right...
What about the man?
[NADIE] Hm?
You know, I honestly can't tell
if you're joking or serious.
Guess this guy
had a family.
Yet somehow he ended up in
this house all by himself...
Wonder what happened.
Did his family die too?
Who can say...?
What do you think
happened to them?
I have no idea.
Well, if the rest of
his family were dead...
...it might've been
easier for him...
He wouldn't've had any regrets.
But then...
if they are still alive...
and for whatever reason,
his family was living somewhere
far away from here...
[NADIE sighs]
"Someday...
the people I love...
will walk through
that door once again...
Somed... Someday, surely."
I couldn't imagine a
more horrible death...
...than that.
Nadie?
I'm fine...
See I'm one of the lucky ones...
Mine are already dead.
[ELLIS] Mine too.
[NADIE] Huh?
I'm one of the
lucky ones too...
because...
the Doctor's dead.
Ellis.
Hey... Do that thing.
[ELLIS] Umm...
You know that thing you
were doing when we first met.
Okay.
[NADIE laughs]
C'mon lizard, clap.
[NADIE] You have such
a strange power.
[ELLIS] Nadie, do you
know the truth about me?
[NADIE] Nuh-uh...
I caught you because you
were a bounty, that's all.
[ELLIS] Am I... weird?
[NADIE] Well...
You're not normal...
doesn't make you weird though...
It's just you have
this power that...
...no one understands.
Okay...
Because I used to think everyone
thought I was a weirdo.
There's always gonna
be negative people...
That's just the way
of the world...
The way to handle it...
is to ignore all that negative
stuff that comes your way...
Keep the pain and heartache
from taking over...
That's really the trick
to makin' it out alive.
Oh...
So... um...
How exactly do you get your
special powers to work...?
If I try really hard and
practice can I do it too?
I don't know.
How could you not...?
Sometimes I'm a bit
surprised at how little
you seem to know
about yourself.
I know.
But I'm pretty sure...
this will tell me.
The Inca Rose.
Wiñay Ma... Achoo!
[NADIE] Heh.
C'mon naked girl,
before you catch cold.
[ELLIS] Yes sir.
[BLUE-EYES sighs]
Can't be far
from here.
Then let's get 'em.
Hm. Too bad the weather
doesn't want to cooperate.
[TRANSVESTITE B] I know.
Depressing, isn't it?
[L.A.] Heh.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
[LIRIO chuckles]
[POLICEMAN A] Thought you walked
away from the game ages ago.
[RICARDO] Well...
lot's happened since then.
[POLICEMAN A] Who's the niña?
Sure as hell ain't
one of yours, is she?
Seriously, how many bounty
hunters drag a kid around
with 'em everywhere...?
What, y'think you're in some
Japanese samurai show?
You quit, huh...?
What's that s'posed to be,
some weak attempt at
cleaning up your act?
Well, I got a family now,
gotta take care of them.
[RICARDO] "Champion of
justice" now, are ya?
Wish I could say it's
made life any easier...
Kinda how the world
tends to work...
So hey...
[POLICEMAN A] Oh yeah...
...the bounty I mentioned
to you earlier...?
They're headed south.
South where?
Not sure, the girl doesn't seem
to know much more than that...
Though I'm willing to bet the
bounty hunter who was with her
would prob'ly know.
Your target, it's a little
blonde girl named Ellis?
[RICARDO]
Don't actually know yet.
Some friendly
advice, Ricardo...
Wash your hands of this
business while you can.
[LIRIO giggles]
[RICARDO] Lirio.
[LIRIO] Huh?
[LIRIO giggles]
The days of putting your
life on the line are over.
Take it easy.
[NADIE] Hm. Could stand
to be a bit spicier.
[ELLIS] Open.
Did you get 'em...?
Ellis?!
I'm cut.
Aw damn...
Put pressure on it...
Here.
[NADIE] Let's see, bandage...
Wonder if there's a first
aid kit here somewhere.
[NADIE] Ellis!
[ELLIS gasps]
What are you doing...?
You're bleeding all over.
[NADIE] Has it stopped?
Taste good?
Your blood...? No...
Wait, if I say yes...
does that make me a vampire?
[NADIE] There.
That should do it.
Be careful...
You may have
superhuman powers...
but you are still
human, all right?
Human?
Yeah, human...
You bleed red don'tcha?
Guess so.
You are one odd bird, Ellis.
I'm a human-bird.
That's them.
Duh...
What am I, blind?
[gasps]
[L.A.] Heh.
The hell?
Out of the way
or we shoot!
[gasps]
Bastard!
Get back here
right now!
Damn it...
We'll never
get across now.
Wanna go back
to the car...?
We can hide and
set a trap for them.
Fine with me...
It's all we can do.
But still... who
the hell was that?
Sorry, this may
taste like crap...
but it's a whole hell of
a lot better than starvin'...
Cool... It's ready.
Ellis.
[ELLIS] Hm?
Put it down.
[ELLIS] I was just
looking at it.
Right now.
'Kay.
That is not a toy.
[ELLIS] Are you mad?
[NADIE] Huh?
[NADIE sighs]
No Ellis, I'm not mad...
Just don't touch it again okay?
Yeah, okay...
Time to eat.
What is that?
[ELLIS] He's pretending
to be a bounty.
[NADIE] Thank you
Lord for this meal.
[ELLIS mumbles]
Thank you for the meal.
[LIZARD belches]
Your turn to say it.
[NADIE] "I'm not
gonna say 'thank you'
if it didn't even taste good."
That's the
look on his face.
At least he was
being honest.
It was that bad?
[ELLIS] Well...
Better than not eating at all.
Wow, no mercy, huh...?
Not, that I really care...
'Kay Ellis...
you clean up.
Why me?
I cooked, so you
get to clean.
That's just
the way it works.
[ELLIS] Hm?
Go on, it won't
take long.
Yes sir.
[clattering]
I heard something.
Stay where you are.
[door closes]
[ELLIS] Find 'em?
No one there.
Nadie!
[L.A.] She's fine...
just taking a little nap.
Ellis.
Who're you?
As of now...
it doesn't quite matter...
But soon enough...
You'll find I will be a very
important part of your life.
No you won't.
[L.A. laughs]
Who are you...?
A bounty hunter?
I am... always watching...
I just wanted to
tell you in person.
[NADIE groans]
[LIZARD belches]
Aaahh!
Don't scare me... Bugger.
Ellis?
He just left.
[NADIE] Huh?
He said he'll
be watching me.
Okay...
[ROSENBERG] Heh.
I hope you don't find the nerve
to act at your own discretion...
I'd like to be able to
trust you in the coming weeks.
[ROSENBERG] I am the one who
gave you the capacity to feel...
Do not forget that.
[ELLIS] Are you okay
sleeping in the chair?
Yeah...
I sleep sitting up
all the time...
In fact I actually
sleep better this way.
If you say so.
All right then,
Ellis... G'night.
'Kay...
Good night...
Sweet dreams.
[TRANSVESTITE A] Uh...
Hey, rise and shine, hooker!
The rain stopped... Finally.
Thank God...
Wanna party?
Sorry...
but my dear Ellis
needs her rest.
Okay, time to
say goodbye.
Really?
Uh-huh.
O-kay.
Buh-bye...
Take care now.
Oh yeah...
Thank you, sir...
You were a big help.
Buh-bye...
Take care now.
[door squeaks closed]
[engine starts]
Cool...
Southward bound!
Let's go!
I'm watching... Ellis.
[BLUE-EYES] His name is L.A...
But his background...
is unknown.