[NADIE yawns]
[door opens]
[NADIE]
'Ey... You two look nice.
[NINA] You sure
this is okay, Nadie?
[NADIE] Yeah, course it is...
Go see a movie...
Do some shopping...
Take your time and have fun.
Gracias.
I'm the one who should
be thanking you...
Roberto, Nina...
I'm just glad you hired us...
It really means a lot.
Hasta luego!
[PEDRO] Nadie.
Hey... Pedro.
They going out?
Yep, off to town
for a little date...
Well... Quite the antagonistic
stare you got there.
[JOAQUIN] You're a she-man.
What was that?
Joaquin...
Ah, jeez... Sorry.
It's no big deal...
I'm used to dealing
with twisted little kids...
That reminds me...
Would you mind watching
the store for a bit?
[NADIE] Got any
last words... say 'em.
A meat pie and
some cold lemonade.
Then go and make it
your damn self...
It's about time you did
some work around here.
Yessir!
The sky...
It's so high.
[NADIE] Sure is.
I can't reach it.
It'd be freaky if you could.
[PEDRO]
Nadie... is this it?
[NADIE] That's the one...
Thanks a bunch, Pedro.
She-man.
[NADIE] Heh...
You brought that for us...?
Aw, thank you, Joaquin.
[JOAQUIN giggles]
[NADIE] Sure, he's
sweet with you...
[ELLIS] Doesn't he
remind you of Lirio?
[NADIE] Yeah, no,
not seein' it.
[JOAQUIN]
You she-man.
[NADIE] Say it again,
I'll shoot you.
[NADIE] So Pedro...
You ever gonna
get married again?
[PEDRO] What?
[NADIE] Don't get me wrong,
I think it's great
you're still committed
to your late wife...
But don't you think,
for Joaquin's sake,
it'd be better if
you found someone?
Yeah, maybe...
Guess you've got a point.
[NADIE] Hey, Ellis, maybe
you should marry him.
[PEDRO gasps]
I'm pretty sure
Joaquin would like it.
I'm fine with it
if you are, Nadie.
[PEDRO] Whoa, hold up a sec.
[NADIE] What?
She's too young?
No, that's not what I meant...
If you're serious... I mean...
Nadie... The truth is...
[NADIE] Hola.
What's your business here?
Y'passing through?
[MAN] Hmm?
[MAN laughs]
[door slams]
What was that?
[PEDRO] Nadie.
[NADIE] Huh?
[PEDRO] If those guys show up
here again, give me a call.
Ooh, impressive!
[JOAQUIN] She-man.
[NADIE] Bang.
Thanks for dinner.
It was awesome.
So... I was thinking.
Next time we go out, you two
should come along with us...
They have an amusement park.
Cool... But really,
you should go alone...
Honest, we don't mind
looking after the store.
We'd have more fun
if you came too.
You girls would
have a blast...
Ellis, ever been to
an amusement park?
[ELLIS] Nuh-uh.
Then you're in
for a surprise...
They have a gigantic
Ferris Wheel there...
Does next Sunday sound good?
Any time is fine with us.
Then it's settled.
Ah! I can't wait!
[NADIE stretches]
An amusement park, huh...?
Got no worries about tomorrow...
Time's passin' nice an' slow...
This must be what
they call happiness.
All that...
seems so long ago...
What do you have
your gun out for?
Yeah... I, uh, didn't
want it to get rusty...
You said you wouldn't
take it out anymore.
[ELLIS] It's warm.
Hey, now...
Y'can't do that.
[ELLIS] Hm?
We agreed you wouldn't
use your powers anymore.
But no one's around to see.
Well, you still can't...
A female bounty hunter and a
girl with mysterious powers...?
If we were found out,
we'd have to leave again.
You think so?
[NADIE] People who
don't know any better
would look at us as
dangerous or creepy.
People think bounty
hunters are creepy?
Oy vey...
Yeah... No, I...
Let's just be careful, okay...?
I promise I won't take
out my gun again...
But you gotta promise
to lay off the powers.
Yessir.
We've found the
perfect life here,
no sense pushin' our luck...
Farewell... sweet prince.
[NADIE] Now then, I think
I'll go take a shower too.
Nadie... Are you all right?
[NADIE]
What...? Who, me?
[ELLIS] Um... Never mind.
You're so weird...
What is it?
[ELLIS] Taco taco taco!
[BLUE-EYES] There you are...
I've finally found you.
[ELLIS and NADIE gasp]
[NADIE] Blue-Eyes?!
You girls look like
you're doing well.
[NADIE] Wow...
District Manager?
I've been put in charge
of this entire area.
And you've only been with
the company a few months?
Guess this whole bossin' people
around thing really suits ya.
So it would seem.
There you are.
Thank you.
I'll be inside,
holler if you need me...
Hope you enjoy.
Thanks so much, Nina.
[BLUE-EYES] She's nice.
Yeah... She really is.
Oh... That's right.
An old cassette tape?
Someone asked me to
deliver this to you.
♪ Taco taco taco... ♪
What the heck is--?
Lirio.
Huh? Oh yeah, it is...
What's she singing?
The Taco-Taco-Taco song.
Okay, now that you said
somethin', I guess I hear it...
So waitaminit, Blue-Eyes...
you've seen Lirio lately?
By pure coincidence.
Oh, yeah?
Is she doing well?
Yes... And so is Ricardo.
Yeah, him I'm not
so concerned with.
They're still traveling,
same as ever.
Yeah?
You don't say...
Get this... Ricardo is
actually teaching Lirio
how to throw a boomerang.
There ya go, nice toss.
Heads up.
Gotta keep your eye on it.
[LIRIO giggles]
Cool.
Apparently she was
adamant that he teach her...
I guess, in her own way, she
just wants to help him out.
Well, they've been though
a lot... T'say the least.
[ELLIS] Nadie...
What's up?
Do you... wanna
travel again?
Jeez, what are you,
outta your gourd...?
Don't be ridiculous...
All that drama is behind us now,
and we're practically
living in paradise here.
Really?
Trust me, I've had my
fill of life on the road...
We have a home now...
You get me, don'tcha?
Yep... I love
living here too.
You see? You're just
being silly, Ellis.
Yeah...? Come in.
No way!
Hm.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
Rosenberg!
Uh...?
--[NADIE] Huh?
--[ELLIS] Not quite.
This is my new assistant...
Let me introduce you...
My name's Steve Beckman...
Pleased to meet you.
[NADIE laughs weakly]
Did you pass out the fliers?
Sure did, ma'am...
I canvassed every corner.
[BLUE-EYES] Good...
Wait in the car for me.
I'll be there soon.
Right... Excuse me.
Whoa, spittin' image.
He's a good honest kid.
You're deranged.
If you say so.
Seems awful Freudian...
Sure you didn't have a secret
crush on Rosenberg...?
Just kiddin'.
Maybe.
Uh-- Huh?
Just kidding.
Yeah, you're killin'
me over here.
[knock on door]
[NADIE] Huh?
Um, hi...
Something wrong...?
Why aren't you in the car?
Yeah... about that...
Shut up and
come with me.
There you are.
--[ROBERTO] Nadie!
--[NINA] Ellis!
I take it we're
the ones you want.
[MAN A] That's right.
So that means
these other people
have nothing to do
with it... Let 'em go.
[MAN A] No can do.
And why not?
[MAN B] 'Cause the last time
we underestimated you girls,
we paid dearly for it.
Last time?
[NADIE] Mmm...
Have we met?
They're the
transvestites.
Don't know ya.
Yeah, that's right, it's us!
And this is all
your fault, bitches...!
I can't believe you
don't remember us!!
Got any last words, say 'em.
We were in the
hospital for weeks!
Our injuries were
pretty serious,
and we wanted to heal
as quickly as possible
so we could hunt
you down again...
So we took in all the
nutrients we could
and this is how we
ended up...! Got it?!
That's great!
[NADIE stifles a laugh]
Whoa... Sorry,
you're right, not funny.
Well, this time,
your head is ours.
And with the bounty,
we can both go on a diet.
Oh, with the bounty, huh?
Better let them in
on the bad news.
Good idea. Ellis?
I'm not a bounty anymore.
I'm worth nothing.
[BOTH] Ehh...?
Yeah, guys, she was
taken off the wanted list
like forever ago...
You didn't know that?
[BOTH groan]
Talk about outta touch...
But there you go, case closed.
[TRANSVESTITE A] Not yet!
[NADIE] Say what?
Shut up...! Look at all
this weight we put on!
We can't just walk away now,
we're too hot to be fatties!
[NADIE] But we're
ordinary citizens now.
Do you really wanna
become low-life murderers?
Shut it!
[BLUE-EYES] Would you calm down?
Boss... You're not
gonna talk to them?!
Don't let your
emotions rule you...
Believe me, you will
regret it later.
Nobody asked you!
Don't lecture us like you're
all high and mighty...
Jus' stay out of it,
you old hag.
Okay, then.
[TRANSVESTITE B]
W-What the--?!
Stay back!
Boss!
If you value your job,
Beckman, shut it.
Now... Go ahead, shoot.
[NADIE sneezes]
[TRANSVESTITE B] Huh?
[TRANSVESTITE B] Yah!
Damn it!
I'm in love!
Now give it up,
nice and quiet.
We're not gonna let you
get away this time...
Hands up, jerkface.
Damn, that hurt.
[door opening]
Ahh... Talk about brute force.
Nadie... You okay?
--[NADIE] Ellis!
--[TRANSVESTITE A] Don't move!
Toss away the piece.
[TRANSVESTITE A] Do it!
Let go of me!
[TRANSVESTITE B laughs]
[BECKMAN] Boss!
I'll turn you
into Swiss cheese.
Joaquin!
Move, brat!
No!
[ringing noise]
Ouchie!
Got any last words,
say 'em... Again.
So you used to be
a bounty hunter?
[NADIE] Mm hmm.
And I'm a witch.
[NINA and ROBERTO] What?
Uh, yeah... Trying to give
you a full explanation
about Ellis would only
make it more confusing...
Jus' don't ask.
At any rate,
thanks for everything...
Wish I had some way to
show my appreciation.
[NINA] Please don't go.
[NADIE] What?
Nina and I have
talked it over...
And neither of us saw a thing...
In fact, we didn't
even hear anything.
You've been in this situation
before, haven't you...?
So what, you'll just
start all over again,
trying to hide your identities?
That can't be easy.
Why don't you stay here?
Nadie... Ellis...
We want you to stay.
If you don't want
to live with us,
it's okay, we'll find
a house for you...
We'll come up with
the money somehow...
As long as you pay us back,
we'll be fine... 'Kay?
So what do you say...?
Are you in?
Thanks, you guys.
Nadie?
Then I guess we should
take that as a yes?
You hear that...?
Isn't it great... Ellis?
Thank you both...
It warms my heart...
But we're... going.
[NADIE gasps]
Ellis...
But how come?
How come?
Because I love that
sparkle in her eye...
Love.
Ellis...
Good point...
I have to agree.
[ELLIS] Let's go, Nadie.
[NADIE] Ellis?
Time to hit the road.
All right... Let's go.
Cool. So, where're
we headin'... partner?
Lirio, duh...
Let's go an' see her.
Yeah?
[ELLIS chuckles]
[ELLIS and NADIE]
Yessir!
[BLUE-EYES] And their uncharted
journey... continues...