No way!
The coin's giving
us the same answer.
[NADIE grunts]
[NADIE] Do we really have to
take the road in that direction?
[ELLIS] Yes.
[NADIE] But why?
I don't know.
[NADIE] Ugh.
Talkin' to you sometimes,
I swear my brain's
turning to tacos.
Taco Taco Taco,
su-uper tasty--
Please, you're gonna
make my ears bleed.
...tacos, too...
The yummiest tacos
in the world...
[NADIE laughs]
[ELLIS giggles]
[BLUE-EYES] The two
continued on their journey...
just as they had before...
Nadie, it's shining.
[BLUE-EYES] However...
something was
beginning to change.
[gun cocks]
Through Blue-Eyes'
tireless efforts...
we now know the full extent
of Douglas Rosenberg's
clandestine project,
codenamed Leviathan.
[murmuring]
It is dangerous to let
Ellis remain at large...
We should dispose
of her immediately.
Correct...
But let us not forget
they are working under
the assumption that we already
have this information...
If we act too hastily
in this matter,
they could use that
to their advantage.
Unless we devise a plan,
we are simply inviting
the worst to occur.
[BLUE-EYES]
I believe I've answered
that question for you before.
[NADIE] "Who she is,
is need-to know,
and you don't need to know...
Just continue to protect her
until you receive
further instructions."
I've heard the spiel...
Y'know, you're really
startin' to sound like
a friggin' emotionless
robot here...
[BLUE-EYES] The last part
was unnecessary, but true.
Still haven't heard
an answer I like.
[BLUE-EYES] It matters?
[NADIE] What?
[BLUE-EYES] If you remain
in the dark about Ellis...
will it keep you from
doing your job effectively?
[NADIE] Well...
[BLUE-EYES] Your mission
is your top priority...
Is that understood?
[NADIE] Yeah, but...
[NADIE] Oy vey...
You chicas wouldn't happen ta be
heading southward, would ya...?
A word of friendly advice,
I'd go back the way
you came if I were you.
How come?
Folks livin' in the town
down the road there
have been a little
on edge... they're loco.
What're we talkin' here...?
'Cuz if it's scoundrels
and bounty hunters,
I'm cool with that.
Because Nadie is
a scoundrel herself.
[STORE OWNER] Huh?
Watch it.
Anyway, if you
insist on going south,
I recommend you take the
bypass road north of here.
It'll make
the trip longer,
but you'll be safer
than going through town.
We can't...
We're only going south.
Why so stubborn?
Better to not
ask questions...
It'll just turn your
brain into taco meat.
[STORE OWNER stammers]
What's that?
[NADIE] Ellis... Be careful.
[ELLIS] Yessir.
[LOOKOUT A]
Where are you two headed?
[LOOKOUT B] What's your
business in our village?
We're not
in business.
[NADIE] We're, uh,
just passing through.
[LOOKOUT A] Huh?
[LOOKOUT B] Mmhmm.
[LOOKOUT A ] Fine...
The thing is our village is in
the middle of a sacred festival.
[LOOKOUT B] So if you
want to pass through,
you'll have to do it
under our conditions.
Huh?
[LOOKOUT A ] Choose one of 'em.
I'd love to but...
I just did my hair...
[LOOKOUT B] It's what
our customs dictate.
[NADIE] It's heavy.
[ELLIS] And stinky.
[ELLIS] You look weird.
Speak for yourself.
Lookit, they're all
dressed the same.
Pro'bly just part of
their silly ritual.
[VILLAGER A (M)]
Guardian Goddess Chappy!
[VILLAGERS]
Guardian Goddess Chappy.
[VILLAGER A] Please Goddess,
bless our village with
wealth and good fortune.
[VILLAGERS] Please Goddess,
bless our village with
wealth and good fortune.
Goddess Chappy!
Goddess Chappy.
Great, now you're
turning into a parrot.
But it's cute though.
[NADIE] Meh.
Wait... Ellis.
[VILLAGER WALLA]
Very cute.
[VILLAGER A] Lady Natalya!
[VILLAGER WALLA]
[NADIE sighs]
Why do I get the feeling
I've seen her before?
[ELLIS gasps]
Behold my
witch powers!
[VILLAGER WALLA]
[YOUTH A (M)] Don't be
fooled by that liar!
Her miracles
are just a sham!
[NATALYA (WITCH)]
Foolish children...
You'd be best to
watch your tongues.
[YOUTH A (M)]
Can it, you charlatan!
[YOUTH B (M)] Give back the
money you conned us out of!
Oh yeah, that's it!
[VILLAGER WALLA]
Behold...!
That glowing child
is another of my kind,
whom I have summoned
here with my witch powers.
[NADIE] Ellis!
[VILLAGERS murmur worriedly]
[L.A. chuckles]
[ELLIS] Where am I?
How much d'you remember
of what happened earlier?
Up to where a weird lady
showed up and that's it.
Well right now you're in
that weird lady's bed.
Ahem. I welcome you
to The Witches Manor.
What a formal greeting,
thanks so much.
You are non-believers, yes...?
However, you are travelers...
So I shall forgive you...
Originally my thought was...
[clattering]
Ah! Wait!
Don't touch that!
[NATALYA sighs]
You can drop the shtick,
I've seen it.
I know what you're doing.
[NATALYA] What?
You're the psychic who
had the world buzzin'
a few years back with
your wild claims...
Nastarsha, wasn't it?
[NATALYA laughs]
You knew...
I wish you would have
told me that beforehand!
Huh?
[ELLIS] Cute.
Yes, her name
was Chappy...
She passed on last
year... diabetes.
[ELLIS] Aww...
You had a cat
with diabetes...?
Jus' what kind of
life do you lead?
Nothing wrong with
living extravagantly...
I have more money than I
could ever hope to spend.
And all you had
to do was fleece
a bunch of innocent
people, right?
You know you don't have to
make it sound so negative...
They donated it to me.
[NATALYA] Those are
from my childhood.
[ELLIS] Huh?
China, Japan,
Great Britain, America...
Back in those days I was raking
it in all over the world...
I even had a palatial estate
built for me in Beverly Hills.
But of course, they
found out the truth...
that I was just faking it...
The whole thing went
to hell after that.
The entire world was talking
about what a fraud I was.
Oh yeah,
I remember all that...
[NATALYA] In the end,
I'd lost everything...
I wandered for awhile
until I came here.
I believe fate is what brought
me to this little village.
The entire region is
filled with old legends
concerning witchcraft
and the dark arts.
I knew I could use
those legends...
for a new endeavor.
[EXTREMIST REP] The Council
is leaning towards a decision
that would be disastrous for us.
[EXTREMIST SUBORDINATE] So...
they intend to allow
Ellis to live?
[EXTREMIST REP] She was
created by the hands of man...
If this creature born of
nothing is allowed to thrive,
she will sow the seeds
of our destruction.
[EXTREMIST SUBORDINATE] I agree.
Worst-case scenario...
we may ignore the Council's
decision outright
and invoke the Laws
of the Night.
[EXTREMIST SUBORDINATE]
Preparations...
have already been made.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
Please believe me...!
I honestly do possess
psychic abilities!
[MEDIA D] Don't listen to her!
She's just playing
us all for fools!
How many times
must I tell you...?
I will admit, I did
lie to you all, but...
I really am a genuine psychic.
[CHILD A (F)] Stay away from us!
[CHILD B (M)]
Yeah, get outta here, witch!
But I'm... I'm not
a witch, I'm not...
...a witch.
[NATALYA gasps]
[RICARDO] Okay, just once.
Meow.
[LIRIO laughs]
[NADIE] Can'tcha sleep?
[ELLIS] Huh-uh.
[NADIE] Go'n take
a walk or somethin'...
Good idea.
So...
I'm curious, were you
bullied as a child?
'Scuse me?
Well, like me
you seem to have
abilities that most normal
people don't have...
Yeah, I was bullied
a whole bunch...
They called me "witch,"
sometimes worse.
[ELLIS] Even though
you're a fake?
[ELLIS] That tickles.
[NATALYA] Just hold still.
I feel it.
[ELLIS] Taco, taco, taco...
Su-uper tasty tacos, too!
What is that, your new
favorite song now?
You don't want to
sing with Ellis?
[ELLIS gasps]
[NATALYA] Get it now...?
My psychic abilities allow me to
read other people's memories...
The power is very
strong and very real.
Hey everyone!
We found the impostor's
true identity!
[YOUTH B] She's no psychic...!
A few years back,
she was all over the media
when they proved she
was nothing but a fraud!
[YOUTH B] Wake up, people!
The Goddess Chappy is
smoke and mirrors...!
Natalya's a fake! A phony!
--[VILLAGER] Oh my gosh!
--[VILLAGER] We've been lied to.
[RICARDO] Him again...
[L.A.] I remember you.
[LIRIO] Ah!
[RICARDO] Are you alright?
[L.A.] Maybe I'm... mistaken.
Are you happy, Ellis...?
'Cause nothing's ever
quite worked out for me...
Now for the most part,
money has never really
been the problem...
But my parents relied on
my income and they were
constantly fighting with
each other because of it.
The moment my
secret was out...
my parents stole every
penny and disappeared.
If I didn't have these
psychic abilities
and grew up like
a normal girl...
I could've been
like anyone else...
Gone to school, goofed
around with friends...
I'd have found a boyfriend
and gotten married,
had a few kids, ya know...
Wha--Hold on...!
What are you doing?
That's Chappy's food!
Just a little taste.
No, that's cat food.
[ELLIS] It's yummy.
Ahhhh!
[NATALYA] Heh, ha, ha!
You're kinda weird, Ellis...
Why don't you stay awhile?
We could hang out.
[ELLIS] Huh?
We're alike, you and I.
We could be friends.
I'm on my way somewhere.
I'll make sure you have
plenty of real food everyday...
Clothes, purses,
jewelry, you name it...
I can buy you whatever
you can imagine...
Forget happiness, money buys
all the good stuff, right...?
So come on... You in...?
Stay here, we'll be BFF's.
[glass shatters]
[NATALYA gasps]
My followers, what is
the meaning of this...?
You are trespassing on the
grounds of Witches Manor.
We're done
listening to you!
We already know the truth
about you and your act...
And all you are is a phony!
[VILLAGER A] How dare
you deceive us like that.
Give us back the money
you stole from us.
[VILLAGER WALLA]
[VILLAGER B] You took
from my family...!
We trusted you and
look how you treated us!
[VILLAGER D] Let's string her up
and teach her a lesson!
[VILLAGER F] We're not leavin'
'til you give back our money!
[NATALYA] You people...
You could never
understand how I feel.
[VILLAGER H] Who cares!
[NADIE] Aah!
Uh. Who turned out the lights?!
[NATALYA gasps]
[VILLAGER WALLA]
[NATALYA whimpers]
[ELLIS panting]
She... She just did witchcraft!
[VILLAGER WALLA]
[NATALYA gasps]
Ellis... You saved
me didn't you?!
[NATALYA] This is...
your past...
Wait... I don't get it.
Ellis, no...
Is that true...?
It, it can't be.
[NADIE] You guys all right?!
[NATALYA] Take care you two.
[NADIE] Same to you...
Don't forget to
apologize to the village.
I hope our paths
cross again soon.
[ELLIS] Mmm.
[NATALYA] Be careful
out there...!
Now...
[phone rings]
[NATALYA] Hello, is this
the White House...?
I don't care who I talk to
as long as they're
really high up...
I have some...
...information you all
might be interested in.
Yeah yeah, that's right...
I'm talking secrets vital
to national security...
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Can you give me any...
...details?
[NATALYA] It's concerning
a girl named Ellis...
but before that, you and
I need to talk business.
[SQUAD MEMBER] What business?
[NATALYA] This information does
not come free, you understand...
Once funds are secure, I'll
set up a meeting with Ellis.
And there's one
more condition...
I want your guarantee
you'll let us all live.
That's me, Ellis and
her companion, Nadie...
All three of us.
All right...
I'll be in touch.
[NATALYA] Ah!
That was nerve-wracking.
But it was worth it.
Everything should
work out now...
I'll even be able to move
back into my mansion
in Beverly Hills. Heh.
Just like the old days.
Hm?
[gunshot]
[ELLIS] Hm?
Is somethin' wrong?
No, it's nothing.
As for the
immediate future...
we shall merely observe...
We shall wait to see
how Rosenberg proceeds.
Any objections?
Correct, I am en route
to the location now.
[ROSENBERG] Hm?
Coming to get me...?
No, even she would
not be so bold.
The heat is unbearable
where you are heading...
Limit yourself,
lest it proves fatal.
Wonder if she's okay...
What?
It's nothing, really.