[ROSENBERG] Such errant
behavior is a serious problem.
[L.A. chuckles weakly]
[ROSENBERG] I did not give
you the capacity for emotion
so you could abuse it, L.A...
I'm disappointed in you...
An agent falling for his
target is unacceptable.
Ellis...
[ROSENBERG] Do you love her?
Ellis.
My darling...
My...
...Ellis.
You are a troublesome child.
Re-education it is...
A bit sooner than I expected...
Oh well, so be it.
[BLUE-EYES] Rosenberg...
does not approve of blue skies.
[gun cocks]
[LIRIO gasps]
[RICARDO] Lirio.
[MAN A] Say that again, pendejo!
Trouble waitin' ta happen.
Pre-vert.
[NADIE] You like that one?
The incandescent
flames of love
burn deep within my heart.
It's a keychain,
don't get too worked up.
[SHOP LADY] Here you go.
[NADIE] Ah, thank you.
He's still there.
Ah, Señor Sanchez...
Hello there...
I didn't even see you come in.
Okay...
No wonder he ran.
I take it you're
not scared.
I'm sorry, would
you rather I was?
Well, it would
have been cute.
[ELLIS] Hi-iii.
[SANCHEZ] Hm?
Yeah, no.
Am I cute?
[SANCHEZ sighs]
[ELLIS] Hi-iii.
Seriously...
Just give it up.
Just this.
I don't need the change.
Oh...
thank you.
You shouldn't accept
gifts from strangers.
[SANCHEZ]
It's nothing. Keep it.
No thanks.
It's a souvenir.
'Scuse me?
Just take the damn thing
and get out of here.
I do not appreciate
your tone.
You're an honest girl.
Hm. Just how I
was raised, I guess.
You're a bounty hunter...
Are you in town
looking for someone?
No... not here...
I caught a big bounty
the other day...
So my sister and I
are out celebrating...
Right, Ellis?
I see...
Then all the more reason
you leave town immediately...
Deep pockets make
for easy targets.
[NADIE sighs]
So this is your
little sister...?
You don't look alike at all.
Nadie's wrong...
We're not sisters.
What...?
But she just said...
Oh... Uh, yeah, see,
what I meant was...
It's wrong to lie,
you know.
The Doctor said
so himself...
He said
lying's bad.
I didn't have much
choice in this case.
No lies ever.
Yes sir.
[HOODLUM A] What's new
with the, uh... "thing"?
[HOODLUM B] About that...
[HOODLUM A]
You haven't done it yet?
[HOODLUM B] Sorry...
[HOODLUM A]
Just get it taken care of!
[HOODLUMS gasp]
So... Who was
Mr. Tough-Guy there?
Oh, his name is Sanchez...
He's the Candela
family's number-two.
The Mafia, huh?
Something must have
happened with the family...
He's really been getting
his face out there lately.
Huh.
What's a number-two?
It just means he's
second in command.
Just like it sounds.
Hm. Sorry it's not
more exciting than that.
Come on...
Let's get movin'.
Oh, wait!
Your change!
We don't need
the change.
Yeah, we do.
You be careful now...
Pretty girls like you are
not very safe in this town.
Thanks...
Then you'd best
be careful yourself.
Ah! Oh... Go on!
[HOODLUMS pant]
Ellis... Can you
hold this a sec?
[NADIE chuckles]
[NADIE gasps]
Nadie?
[SANCHEZ]
You can't help her now?
Sorry, there's nothing
we can do, Señor.
The operating room
is this way, sí?
[HEAD NURSE] Señor,
please, come back here!
Señor!
[ELLIS] Does it hurt?
You want some... water?
[ELLIS] Nadie.
[ELLIS pants]
Hey, the doctor'll
be here in a sec...
[SANCHEZ gasps]
Díos.
[dogs bark]
[dogs growl]
Hola, Sanchez.
Pops...
Lemme introduce you.
Paulina.
I can't believe
you came back.
No, Pops, it's not--
This girl is...
Welcome home, Paulina.
You're wrong, sir...
I'm not Paulina...
My name is Ellis.
Your hair is so soft...
Just like when you were a baby.
[SANCHEZ sighs]
[ENRIQUE chuckles]
[WOMAN A] He's on
a business trip, huh?
Where to?
[WOMAN B] No idea.
Out of the country
was all I heard.
[WOMAN A] His department's
budget must be ridiculous.
Shouldn't have had
that cake with lunch.
Plan B it is...
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
I'm sorry about that.
[ELLIS] That old man...
he's sick?
Doctors have given up hope.
[ELLIS] He's going to die?
I won't let him...
I don't really understand
this power you have...
But please...
I know you can use
it to save him...
I'm asking you...
as a favor to me
and my family.
[ELLIS] Is he your father?
No...
His name is Enrique Candela...
He's our family's boss.
[ELLIS] And you want
me to make him better?
I do.
[ELLIS] I can't.
I'll pay any
price you ask.
If you don't care
about money...
Then what...?
Name it and it's yours.
Doggies.
What?
They're watching.
You're upset about your friend
being shot; I apologize...
I do feel bad.
Ever since the
old man fell ill...
Everyone hoping to succeed him
has been rubbing each other out.
It'll take some time for this
infighting to die down...
I just hope he can last...
until... a suitable
replacement can be chosen.
Otherwise... the town
he loved will become...
Loved?
Please help.
I told you
I can't do it.
[SANCHEZ sighs]
So be it.
[SANCHEZ] I'm not letting
you leave this compound
until you've treated him...
If you continue
insisting you can't...
You will die here...
Understand, Miss Bounty?
[NADIE] Waitaminnit, back up...
What do you mean, "gone"?
I'm sorry.
Security and I
looked everywhere.
Ellis.
Where'd that come from?
"La Villa Candela."
How do I get to
the Candela estate?
[LIRIO giggles]
Draw me a map...
and quick.
Excuse me?
Run that by us again.
Hi-iii!
♪ Taco taco taco. ♪
♪ Su-uper tasty
tacos too...! ♪
♪ The yummiest tacos in the
world, Amigo Tacos--ooh! ♪
[NADIE laughs]
Um... We get that
your delivering tacos.
But why the hell're
you dressed like that?
Best service...?
Call Amigo Tacos!
[NADIE laughs]
Get lost.
We didn't order any.
Uhh!
Now maybe if a sexy
girl came up here
with a bag o' tacos,
we'd let her in...
Yeah, a sexy girl.
[GUARDS laugh]
[cracking knuckles]
Got any last words?
Say 'em.
A beautiful moon.
Yeah.
Come sit with Papi... Paulina.
But I'm Ellis...
Not Paulina.
[NADIE] Jerks.
I'll show them "sexy"!
[NADIE winces]
Crap. Hope my wound
didn't open up.
[dogs growl]
Uh oh.
Ah! Want some tacos...?
Super tasty... Prob'ly.
[loud footstep]
They actually don't
care for tacos.
Maybe for the best.
Your friend is inside.
[NADIE] Wow...
So Ellis was able to get
the bullet out of me.
[SANCHEZ] I couldn't believe
what I was seeing.
Yeah...
Well, I'm sorry, but what
you want is impossible...
The thing is, about Ellis...
I don't think she really even
understands her abilities.
[SANCHEZ] What's that mean?
See... If she could
use 'em at will...
I think it might just
be too much for her.
[SANCHEZ sighs]
[door opens]
[NADIE] Ellis!
We'll see.
Nadie... Should you
really be up yet?
Didn't really have time
to worry about it...
You disappeared on me.
I didn't disappear...
I'm here.
Uh--Yep...
So you are.
How's he doin'?
He wants...
some water.
[KID SANCHEZ] Let go!
I said, let go!
[THUG A]
Think you're funny, kid?
Pulling a stunt like that!
[THUG B] We're gonna
make an example out of ya.
[YOUNG ENRIQUE]
What's going on here?
[THUGS] Uh?!
[THUG A] Boss!
[THUG B] This punk tried to
steal some loot out of our car!
So? That money was dirty
in the first place!
[THUG B] Shut your
friggin' mouth, you!
[THUG B grunts]
[THUG B] But Boss...?
So it's money
you're after.
Come with me...
We'll get that
wound taken care of.
And that's how
you got here.
Though he never showed
me any true affection...
I was allowed to
stay by his side...
But that was enough for me...
At the time,
three meals a day...
was heaven.
[NADIE] So are you
gonna take his place?
No one will accept me
as their leader...
because to all of them...
I'm just not a member
of the Family.
Only a stray dog who wandered
in with an empty stomach.
[ENRIQUE] Thank you, Paulina.
Who's Paulina?
[SANCHEZ] His daughter.
Where is she?
[SANCHEZ] She's dead.
Along with her mother...
They were killed.
[glass shatters]
[ENRIQUE groans]
Pops!
It looks like my time...
...has finally come.
Don't give up yet.
[ENRIQUE sighs]
[ENRIQUE groans]
[NADIE gasps]
[ENRIQUE grunts]
It's going to
be all right...
Papá.
It's okay.
[ENRIQUE sighs]
Paulina...
He looks happy...
Thank you, Ellis.
I'm glad he could...
be with family in the end.
This is...
Ellis?
Same as mine.
[SANCHEZ] Can't believe
he still had it.
[NADIE and ELLIS] Huh?
Back when
I was a kid...
I got it for the
old man's birthday.
[SANCHEZ] He acted like
he didn't like it...
so I assumed he threw
it away years ago.
[NADIE sighs]
'Cause you ... were family too.
[SANCHEZ cries softly]
Enrique never
told him he cared...
Guess it's just
complicated in their world.
I told a lie.
Huh?
Even though lying's bad.
Yeah...
the thing is...
There's good lies and
there's bad lies...
That one was a good lie.
A good lie?
Yeah... a good lie.
Oh... Okay.
Cool...
Now let's make tracks!
[NADIE] ♪ Taco taco taco.
Su-uper tasty tacos too...! ♪
[ELLIS] I hate that song.
[NADIE] Oh, please.
[BLUE-EYES]
Several days later...
Sanchez vanished from sight...
His current whereabouts...
unknown.