[dog barks in distance]
[glass shatters]
It's no use...
I don't feel any better.
It's just...
unforgiveable...
That anyone else could be
closer to Ellis than me.
[L.A. chuckles]
Achoo!
Are you catching a cold?
[NADIE] Nah, somebody's
probably just talking about me.
"Hey, did you hear about that
sexy bounty hunter chick?"
"Oh yeah, I hear
she's smoking hot!
She's got a killer figure and
a mind as sharp as a tack."
"Whoo... What I wouldn't give
to run into a woman like
that just once in my life."
Then why don't
you chop these?
[NADIE] Wha...?
With your
sharp mind.
[POLICEMAN A grunts]
What the hell...?
What happened here?
[L.A.] Unforgiveable.
[L.A. sighs]
[POLICEMAN A gasps]
[BLUE-EYES] And then...
L.A. let his libido...
overtake his psyche.
[L.A. chuckles]
[gun cocks]
[ELLIS] What'd they say?
He's here... L.A...
I guess he caused some
trouble last night.
Ooh. What did he do?
[NADIE] Yeah, please
don't make me repeat it.
'kay I won't.
So... Wanna find a motel?
[POLICEMAN A] Don't bother
looking for a place to stay.
We'd like you
to come with us.
What...?
How come?
[POLICEMAN B] Just stay quiet,
do as we say and you'll be fine.
What if I say no?
Then we'll arrest
you for obstruction.
[NADIE] Umm...
Heh.
[POLICEMAN B] Oof!
[POLICEMAN A] Ugh!
Hold it...!
Nadie!
Keep going!
Move it!
[NADIE] Ahh!
[POLICEMAN A chuckles]
--[ELLIS] Nadie.
--[NADIE] Damn that hurt.
Ellis.
[ELLIS pants]
[NADIE]
Ellis, no! Run!
[ELLIS gasps]
[POLICEMAN B]
Damn, that girl is quick.
[NADIE] Oof!
Easy...
You don't have to be
so friggin' rough...
I am a lady.
Heh! Don't make
me laugh...
Your gun is filthy...
Don't you ever
clean it the thing?
Give it...
We were told if you turned up
dead no one would miss you.
You were "told?"
[POLICEMAN A] Heh.
Listen...
Believe it or not
I am a gentleman...
Thank your stars for that...
Besides, the last thing I'm
looking for is more trouble.
Someone's playin' 'em.
[POLICEMAN A gasps]
[L.A.] What a letdown.
You didn't kill her.
[POLICEMAN A] Well I'm not you.
Such weak creatures.
[POLICEMAN A]
Once we capture the girl
we'll hand her
over to you...
But then you leave town--
just like you promised.
Playing the
Champion of Justice?
[POLICEMAN A] Long as
you don't come back,
we'll forget about your
incident at the bar...
Then this town can
get back to normal.
Do I frighten you?
[POLICEMAN A] Uh...
[L.A. giggles]
Hey... Status?
[POLICEMAN B]
Sorry, nothing yet.
I'll let you know
if she turns up here.
[POLICEMAN B] Copy that.
Why us?
[POLICEMAN A] Seriously...
Ellis is mine
and mine alone.
Don't run off.
Where're you going?
To rescue Nadie.
[RICARDO] How...?
She got herself locked up.
I'll find a way.
[RICARDO]
It's impossible right now.
No.
Just wait a bit...
Once the sun sets I'll help you.
[LIRIO gasps]
Ellis.
I have to.
Because she's
always saving me.
[RICARDO] I know
how you feel but...
[ELLIS] And I've never done
anything to help her.
[RICARDO] Remember,
you're the one they want.
[ELLIS] I'm going.
Lirio...
All right...
I'll wait for a bit.
[B-LADY A] Should we move in?
No... Let's wait
them out and see.
Seems she's... growing.
[ROSENBERG] Melissa.
Have you seen
my keys?
[MELISSA]
Keys...? For the car?
I could have sworn
I'd left them right here.
Look what I got.
Ah-ha.
I know...
I have magical powers.
[ROSENBERG chuckles]
[ROSENBERG] Truth is, so do I.
[MELISSA] Heh. That is true...
For some reason,
I'm never able to lie to you.
[ROSENBERG]
That's the way it should be.
[MELISSA] I love you, Doug.
[ROSENBERG] Melissa.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
[NADIE] Hey, jerks...!
Dinner?!
Dumb bastards...
My stomach is seconds
away from eating itself.
I want dinner!
Oh!
Hey... doesn't hurt.
[NADIE] Warrr-dennn...!
[RICARDO] Nadie.
[NADIE gasps]
[NADIE] Ricardo?
We're bustin' you out.
[NADIE] What about Ellis?
Is she okay?
Yeah, she's fine.
[NADIE sighs]
Thank God.
[RICARDO] She wants to save you.
[NADIE gasps]
[RICARDO] That's what she said.
[NADIE] Don't let her be stupid.
I won't.
[NADIE] That girl is
honest to a fault.
Well so are you.
[NADIE] Uh...
[RICARDO] You make a good pair.
Wait is that
a compliment...
...or an insult?
[RICARDO] Kinda both.
Heh. We're a good pair, huh?
Funny.
[L.A. whimpers]
With my Ellis...
"A good pair?!"
No leads yet, huh?
[POLICEMAN B] Nada.
[POLICEMAN B gasps]
Stupid humans.
[POLICEMEN gasp]
[L.A.] So very dull.
[ELLIS pants]
[B-LADY A] Now's our chance.
Not yet.
[B-LADY A] But ma'am...
'kay... Let's move.
Ellis?
It's hot.
Without Nadie with me...
It's hot...
It's hot.
L.A. is here.
What?
[L.A. chuckles]
[L.A.] Nadie.
L.A...
[L.A. chuckles]
The hell...?
I thought we agreed
you'd leave Ellis to me.
[L.A.] Hm...
So I changed my mind.
[NADIE sighs]
[L.A.] Heh.
[RICARDO gasps]
Ellis.
Ellis?!
[ELLIS] Nadie.
I shouldn't have
left things...
in your hands...
or those cops.
Humans are such
weak creatures...
So they lean on each other...
Rubbish...
Pathetic!
[L.A. laughs]
Oh yeah...?
Why'd you leave her with me...
if I'm so weak?
[L.A.] Ah. Well...
I suppose I thought it
would be interesting.
Sure y'did...
Or maybe the truth
is you were scared.
[L.A. gasps]
You didn't want to upset Ellis
to the point where
she hates you.
I'm right... aren't I?
[L.A. giggles]
How human of you.
[L.A.] Heh.
I won't miss this time.
Anger...
Very good, that's
even more human.
[L.A. laughs]
[ELLIS panting]
[NADIE] Ellis!
[L.A. gasps]
[RICARDO] Nadie!
[ELLIS growls]
[NADIE] Ellis!
[L.A. whimpers]
Hm. Ellis.
Hurt her 'n' I won't
forgive you...
Not ever.
[L.A. gasps]
Ellis.
Even when you find out
who she really is?
[NADIE gasps]
[ELLIS] Who she--?
You see...
Nadie... is not who
she says she is.
She's lying to you.
Don't!
[L.A.] I'll tell you
the truth, Ellis...
[L.A.] Nadie was...
hired by an organization...
Which is how she crossed
your path in the first place.
She was...
hired to watch you.
[ELLIS] Watch me?
Would you like to go sit
with Mommy and Daddy?
[LIRIO giggles]
[RICARDO] Nadie.
[NADIE] Huh?
[ELLIS panting]
[L.A. giggles]
Ellis.
[BLUE-EYES gasps]
[ELLIS panting]
Ellis...
That's good...
[L.A. whimpering]
[NADIE] Whoa!
L.A...
Hey there.
Nadie.
Ellis.
You're safe...
I'm here.
[ELLIS] Thank you.
Ellis.
[L.A. whimpers]
[L.A. sighs]
[ELLIS] Wait.
I'm sorry...
I am, but Nadie is Nadie...
And for me, that's enough...
You see?
[L.A.] A deal's a deal.
I'll take you as
far as Wiñay Marka.
Let's get this over with...
L.A...
Let's end it.
[L.A.] Until then...
Ellis.
We missed our
opportunity, ma'am...
You have my apologies...
Won't happen again.
[phone rings]
Yes, I'm here...
Today's report, if you please.
[NADIE exhales]
[ELLIS sleeping]
[NADIE gasps]
Nadie.
You saved me...
Thank you.
It's okay now...
It's... gonna be all right.
[L.A. crying]
[BLUE-EYES]
Even artificial life forms
develop the capacity
for emotion...
In this regard...
there are no exceptions...
None.