[BLUE-EYES sighs]
[gun cocks]
Through Blue-Eyes'
tireless efforts...
we now know the full extent
of Douglas Rosenberg's
clandestine project,
code named Leviathan.
It is dangerous to let
Ellis remain at large...
We should dispose
of her immediately.
Correct...
but let us not forget that
they are working under
the assumption that we have
already have this information...
If we act too hastily
in this matter,
they could use that
to their advantage.
[EXTREMIST REP] The Council
is leaning towards a decision
that would be disastrous for us.
[EXTREMIST SUBORDINATE] So they
intend to allow Ellis to live?
[EXTREMIST REP] She was
created by the hands of man.
If this creature born out of
nothing is allowed to thrive,
she will sow the seeds
of our destruction.
[EXTREMIST SUBORDINATE] I agree.
Worse case
scenario...
we may ignore the
Council's decision outright
and invoke the Laws
of the Night.
[EXTREMIST SUBORDINATE]
Preparations...
have already been made.
[phone rings]
Ah.
[phone beeps]
[busy]
[phone rings]
[phone beeps]
[BLUE-EYES] Nadie!
What is going on?
[NADIE] I was gonna ask you...
[gunfire]
...the same thing.
[NADIE] Soon as we hit
town we got ambushed
by a squad o' weird
alien-ninja-lookin' dudes.
[BLUE-EYES] What did you do?
Nothin', I swear.
[NADIE] How many?
I don't know, a lot...!
I don't need you
to tell me to run,
I will when I am
damn well--Hello?!
Ellis... Let's run.
Yessir.
[phone rings]
[BLUE-EYES] Looks like
we're in for a long night...
Hey Ortega!
You hear me?!
[GAYA] This is our
land, not yours!
How many times I gotta say it?!
[ORTEGA] It's only yours
'cause you cozied up
to some
politicians.
[GAYA] Look, I don't
want any trouble!
Just get this thing outta here!
Target...
and... lock.
Bang!
[GAYA sighs]
[GAYA] Jerk...
How'd his broke ass
even pay for this?
[ORTEGA sighs]
Heh.
Hi...! Helluva ride!
Oh... Thanks.
[ELLIS] Hm?
[BLUE-EYES giggles]
[door opens]
[B-LADY A] That was a mistake.
[BLUE-EYES chuckles]
Let's talk.
[B-LADY A] One of the
factions overreacted
to the news of
Project Leviathan...
They have since taken action.
Yes, I'm aware.
[NADIE sighs]
My pops started
this collection...
Though I've added so many,
mine outnumber his now...
Got the entire arsenal
catalogued on my computer here.
Why don't I just
fire it up for ya.
Uhh...
You got a phone?
Oh, yeah...
Right over there.
[NADIE] Huh?
Ah, thanks.
Now I don't want you two
to get the wrong idea...
I'm no right-wing wack-job...
No way... I simply
provide a service,
delivering the iron hammer
of justice to the world.
And there's some
guy around here
who's in bed with
the local politicians.
[NADIE] Would'ya keep it down?
I'm tryin' ta use the phone.
Your friend there...
Got a bit of a temper...
Calcium deficiency?
What's calcium?
I'll call in five.
[ORTEGA] That there's
a government issue Colt
"M Nineteen-Eleven A-One."
Takes forty-five caliber
rounds, seven to a clip.
Adopted in 1911, it's been
the Standard-Issue sidearm
for the US Army for
almost a century now.
It's a highly accurate and
dependable piece of weaponry.
European "nine millimeters"
pack more rounds,
so they're the gun
of choice these days.
But with all the terrorist
attacks lately,
the Colt's gained
renewed respect
for its close range
stopping power. Heh.
I'm sorry...
I guess this must be pretty
boring for a girl, huh...?
Anyway... The Colt uses
Browning's short-recoil action.
Nadie has one.
Huh?
Hmm...
You gonna need a hand?
Huh?
You're bein' chased
by bounty hunters,
got nowhere to turn, right...?
I may not look like much but
I'm a damn good marksman...
Besides, and don't take
this the wrong way,
I doubt you can handle that
piece strapped to your leg.
All I need from
you is your phone.
[ORTEGA] Yeah sure,
you say that now...
Nadie.
[NADIE gasps]
'Kay I take it back...
Gimme some ammo.
[ORTEGA] Huh?
[gunfire]
And your van!
[ORTEGA] Who the hell
are these people?
Are they outta their minds?!
[explosion]
Hang onto somethin'...!
This faction is clearly
acting in defiance
of the Council's
official decision...
Listen...
Chairwoman, the council
needs to convene right away
so appropriate
steps can be taken.
[CHAIRWOMAN] I understand
what you're saying.
Unfortunately it is
currently nighttime over there.
[BLUE-EYES] You don't mean...
they're using that
to shield themselves?
To us...
...that is our greatest
governing principle.
[BLUE-EYES] The night
belongs to the witches...
Under darkness...
there is nothing
to hold them back.
[phone rings]
[ORTEGA gasps]
Take the wheel!
Cheese
and rice...
Why me?
I'm not even the
one they're after!
[NADIE] Fine! Ellis then!
Yessir.
[ORTEGA] No, wait!
I simply can't allow you
to endanger yourself...
Besides, this is my vehicle...
So I'm the only one who can get
maximum performance from her.
Whatever, just get up here!
The true form of the
legendary Silver Wolf...
Prepare to engage.
What does that mean?
[BLUE-EYES] It means for
the next several hours,
you'll be plagued by
intermittent showers of bullets.
A weather report? Nice.
[BLUE-EYES] I can
tell you one thing...
and it's far more reliable
than any weather forecast
you'll ever hear.
So listen...
It'll pass with the
first light of day...
I guarantee you that.
So find a way to stay
alive until daybreak...
Do you underst--
[NADIE gasps]
[phone busy signal]
Until daybreak?
[gunfire]
[NADIE] How many hours
is that gonna be?
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
[ROSENBERG] Yes,
that is a problem...
Well, it is certainly provided
for in the contract but...
this is quite urgent...
Can't something be done?
'Fraid not...
I'm... kinda busy now.
Hang in there.
[ROSENBERG sighs]
Well I suppose I will
leave it up to him then...
He's remained fairly
hands-on so far.
[phone busy signal]
[POLICEMAN] A-According to
eyewitness accounts...
the women who were
being attacked...
fled town in a van.
Ah yes...
I've finally caught up, Ellis.
[POLICEMAN] I swear,
that's all I know!
Ple-ease!
Ellis...
I'll be right there.
[POLICEMAN screams]
[L.A. chuckles]
[NADIE]
Gettin' a bit of a break.
[ORTEGA] Heh, heh, heh.
[NADIE] Hey pre-vert!
[ORTEGA] Oh!
You got a map?
[ORTEGA] I got a
killer setup in here.
There's a satellite
uplink to the internet
with real-time imaging
for anywhere in the world.
[ORTEGA] Huh?
It didn't work?
Oh, my God!
We're screwed...!
What the frak do I do...?
The uplink's fried!
And that's a problem?
Got paper maps?
[ORTEGA] Um... Nuh-uh.
Now that's a problem.
So that's it then...
We're all gonna die.
Oh I dunno, for as much as we've
been gettin' shot up tonight...
Nothin's really gotten
through the armor so far...
Van's pretty rugged...
It's a beast.
[ORTEGA] Huh?
And it's reinforced
in front...
You didn't mod this puppy
all by yourself, did you?
Sure did...
Basically transformed a normal
RV into an armored car.
Wow, that's incredible.
[ELLIS] Huh?
Incredible.
In this thing,
we'll be fine.
We'll be fine.
Ha! You really think so?
If we go right we'll end up
in a town that was quarantined
a few years ago because
of some weird epidemic.
Then I suppose we
better go left...
though it'll prob'ly
mean another ambush.
[ELLIS] Go right.
[ORTEGA] Huh?
Right.
Ellis?
Okay...
Right it is.
Whaa?
We need to stall
until dawn, huh...?
Well let's try
outsmarting them...
Why don't we take the route
that'll buy us some extra time.
[ORTEGA] Uh!
They're... here.
Why're they just
standing there?!
U-turn...
Back to the fork.
Go straight.
What's with you, Ellis?
Got it...
Plow right thru 'em.
Ortega!
It fell.
One plate won't hurt us.
Ah!
[ORTEGA grunts]
My face... my face!
It's just a scratch!
[ORTEGA] A half-inch to the left
and it woulda been
instant death!
Not even half...!
A centimeter!
Chill out, wuss.
Let's surrender...!
If we just give up now maybe
they'll let us all live!
Not with these people...
Ellis, take the wheel.
Yessir.
[ORTEGA] Huh?
[ELLIS] Two more fell.
[NADIE] Whaddaya expect
from an amateur mod job.
[ORTEGA] Amateur?
[ORTEGA gasps]
[ORTEGA whimpers]
[NADIE grunts]
Piece of junk!
That's no good.
Uhh...
Ahhhh!
Suck on my bullets...
...of rage!
[ORTEGA laughs]
He's nuts.
The ridge!
Ellis...
I'm here.
Almost...
It'll be dawn soon.
[NADIE gasps]
What happened?
[NADIE] Engine must'a
crapped out!
What?!
An' we're so close.
[ELLIS gasps]
[ORTEGA] Come on Silver Wolf,
Daddy needs you to
start for me...!
Please God give us a miracle.
Oh please, Lord!
[ELLIS panting]
Uh? They stopped.
[BLUE-EYES] Good.
So they're safe.
[ELLIS gasps]
[NADIE] Ellis!
[ELLIS] Hmm?
Thank you, Ortega...
I wish I had enough on me to
help cover your repairs but...
I don't care
about money...
Got my old man's inheritance...
Um... instead
of that could I...
could I get a kiss?
[NADIE] Ehh?!
Not from you.
[ELLIS] Hmm?
Just a little peck?
Ah, go ahead...
It's no big whoop.
If you... insist.
Wow, a girl's lips...
Rougher than I thought.
[giggling]
[NADIE] Where to now?
[ELLIS] Go straight.
[BLUE-EYES] And so the pair...
will come to learn the truth.