[gunfire]
Ah!
Bastards...
[TRANSVESTITE A]
Nowhere left to run...!
Bounty's as good as ours now!
[TRANSVESTITE B]
That's right, girlie-girl!
And since you stole our
jeep out from under us...
we do this the ugly way!
Reverend Mother!
Be calm, Sisters...
We are under the
protection of the Lord...
We will be fine.
Well, I feel better now.
We won't be protected.
[gasps]
No one... no one
can protect us.
[NADIE sighs]
Ellis...
[gunfire]
[gunfire continues]
Ow.
What?!
I got hit.
Wh-Where?!
Right here.
Ehh...
What?
[BLUE-EYES] Ellis is...
a unique life form,
crafted by human hands.
[gun cocks]
[BLUE-EYES]
R-Three-Three-Nine...
The unassuming home of a top
secret government project...
The man at its head
has a reputation
in the Agency as
a top performer...
Douglas Rosenberg.
Rosenberg here.
[BLUE-EYES]
This is Miss Hayward
in the Audit Department.
Ah...
Yes, Miss Hayward.
[BLUE-EYES] Um,
I've called repeatedly,
regarding these excessive
investigative expenses...
I apologize again...
But you've caught me
in another meeting...
[knocking]
Ah... And it seems a new
report is coming in now...
I'll have to call you back...
Bye now!
Come in.
[BLUE-EYES chuckles]
Well, you got me.
Do you often conduct
meetings with yourself sir?
If the situation
demands it, yes.
This is a detailed list
of the expenses you filed...
The entries in question
have been clearly marked...
Do please look it over.
You know, I think you'd
look much more beautiful
without those glasses. Heh.
When you've finished
reviewing it...
Please let me know...
Pardon.
[ROSENBERG sighs]
Such a shame to be so
stubborn in nature...
One misses out on so
many "opportunities."
Isn't that right... Ellis?
[clattering]
[ELLIS] Dropped it.
Shush... Be quiet.
[ELLIS] Yes sir.
Sorry we got you
into this...
We never should've
taken refuge here...
Child...
Do not be sorry, the Lord
is merely testing our faith.
Yes.
Oh... Is that all?
Well I'm glad one of us
isn't too worried.
[door opens]
[thud]
[NADIE gasps]
Huh?
--Shhh.
--I got hit again.
[TRANSVESTITE A] Hmm...
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[NADIE sighs]
Man, that was close.
God has kept
us safe.
Praise to you...
Lord Jesus Christ!
Yeah, yeah.
Ho-kay...
Now then, what to do...?
Not the windows...
That's for sure, so...
A'right... Ellis and I'll go and
draw these guys' attention...
You three run out the front
while they're distracted.
Amen!
No... We are not
going anywhere.
[NUN A and NUN B] Huh?
[NADIE] Why not?
This is a convent...
Our mission is to protect
the lost sheep...
So this is where we'll stay.
Amen!!
[NADIE] What are you saying?
These are armed
bounty hunters here!
Are you all trying
to get killed?
God is with us
in all that we do.
Oy vey...
Um... Has anyone seen Ellis?
She's asleep.
[BLUE-EYES] Following the murder
of a prominent physicist,
a young girl was made
the prime suspect,
and a bounty placed on her head.
[BLUE-EYES] This physicist
was a man named
Dr. Heinz Schneider...
He had been entrusted with
the long-term research
and observation of the girl.
[BLUE-EYES] And this
girl... is Ellis.
This girl is hopeless.
No way.
We will run those
miscreants off with these.
[NUN A and NUN B grunt]
Yeah... um...
You do know "those
miscreants" have guns...
[thud]
Really?
[BLUE-EYES] According to her
traveling companion's reports...
Ellis is currently missing
portions of her memory
concerning the incident.
[BLUE-EYES] Why was
Dr. Schneider killed...?
Was Ellis truly
the perpetrator...?
If we cannot restore
her lost memory,
these questions will
remain unanswered.
I'm gonna go
scope it out...
You stay here.
Right.
If they dare come in here,
we will smite them.
Oh great, isn't
that reassuring...
Now...
[ELLIS] I'm coming with you.
[NADIE] Ellis?
What's that?
Weapon.
[NADIE] Yeah, that's
not really gonna work.
Two?
Y'know, ya might wanna pick
something a little bigger.
[BLUE-EYES] The project
operating out of
R-Three-Three-Nine is
called "Leviathan"...
named for the
infamous sea serpent
which appears in
the Old Testament.
You are 3
minutes late.
[ASSASSIN] Your watch
must be running fast.
There was one person
still left alive.
Hm. I guess those academic
types are good at hiding.
[ROSENBERG] I'm counting on you.
To eliminate them...
There's no better
way to handle it?
[ROSENBERG] What the
government wants...
Government...
Figures...
[BLUE-EYES] Besides tracking
Ellis's whereabouts,
Rosenberg is involved
in numerous other
clandestine activities.
[ELLIS] Found 'em.
We're gonna lure
them outside...
I don't want the nuns to get
any more caught up in this.
Yes sir.
[NADIE] Yoo-hoo!
Lady boys!
Ah!
[grunts angrily]
Come back here!
Just a little further, Ellis...
Ellis?!
[TRANSVESTITE A]
Don't even flinch.
[TRANSVESTITE A chuckles]
Hi.
Well, this sucks.
[TRANSVESTITE B]
Drop your gun, girl.
Oops, sorry
about that...
Finger slipped.
Ow!
Damn!
Ah!
Nadie!
[NADIE groans]
Oh my, how dreadful.
Heh.
So... where do you want it...?
The gut...?
The boobs...? Or maybe...
...that smart-assed
little face of yours?
[TRANSVESTITE A laughs]
[ELLIS breathes heavily]
[BLUE-EYES] There once
was a group of people,
who were referred to as witches.
[ELLIS breathes heavily]
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
[ELLIS breathes heavily]
[BLUE-EYES] The "magic" these
legendary witches possessed,
was the complete control
over physical mass
at the molecular level.
[ELLIS gasps]
[BLUE-EYES] A power described
by later scientists,
as "Maxwell's Demon."
Ahhh!
[NADIE gasps]
[TRANSVESTITE B]
Wh-What the--?!
[TRANSVESTITE B groans]
[grunts]
You... damn penguins...!
O Lord...! Hear us!
Please... forgive us...
these transgressions!
Sisters...
[NUNS chuckle]
You all right?
Yeah.
What in the
world was that?
[NADIE] Call it
divine intervention.
Huh?
[NADIE] Heh.
Child...
[TRANSVESTITE A groans]
[TRANSVESTITE B groans]
Ellis, can you walk?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[NADIE] Good.
Nadie...
Pretty sure I'll go to hell if
I hafta kill 'em here, right?
[NADIE chuckles]
Mother?
[MOTHER SUPERIOR] Hm.
[engine revs]
Dammit!
Ach! Oh no they di'int...!
[Jeep drives away]
May God be with you.
[BLUE-EYES]
Over the course of time...
the witches died out.
[BLUE-EYES] However...
Roughly a thousand
years later...
today's brand of magic,
called genetic engineering...
brought that legend,
back into reality.
[BLUE-EYES] The modern-day witch
that Project Leviathan
gave birth to...
...is the girl known as Ellis.
[BLUE-EYES]
It is as yet unknown,
just how powerful,
she truly is...
[gunfire]
Ah jeez...
What a waste of
perfectly good bullets...
'Course I guess they
are pretty ticked off.
'Kay... there's
no one else around.
Oh yeah...
I think it's time...
Awright Ellis...
ease off the gas.
[ELLIS] Check.
[gasps]
And, go!
Yes sir!
Bitches're crazy!
Takin' us head-on?!
How dare they?!
Whoa...!
It's okay.
Not that'chu can
hear me, but...
Got any last words, say 'em!
Oh... Aaahhh!
[crash]
[BLUE-EYES] It's unclear why
Rosenberg hasn't taken Ellis
into protective custody...
But it's my belief the
reasons for his inaction,
are quite personal.
[GOVERNOR] Hm?
[GOVERNOR] Ah, there
you are, Doug!
Please forgive
my tardiness, sir.
Look at you,
Mr. Big Shot...
Keeping the
Governor waiting...!
Ha, ha, ha.
Kiddin' of course.
Nah... We got here
a bit early...
At my age, if you don't come
early, you don't get served!
[GOVERNOR laughs]
This is Douglas Rosenberg...
Real go-getter.
Doug... meet
Senator Ritgen.
It's an honor.
I like that look
in your eye...
Must be the German blood.
How kind of you.
Please, have a seat.
[BLUE-EYES] It's possible...
that in discovering
why Rosenberg hasn't
brought Ellis in...
I may finally discover a
weakness to be exploited.
[phone rings]
[BLUE-EYES] Nadie?
[BLUE-EYES] As an
escort for Ellis,
I hired a bounty hunter...
One with a questionable
background. My wild card...
Things will not go as
Rosenberg would like...
And his plans will
surely crumble...
In time, Rosenberg will
show his true colors...
And when he does...
[phone beeps]
[BLUE-EYES] I will
be ready for him...
And I will drive Project
Leviathan to dissolution.
[NADIE chuckles]
Thank you again.
[MOTHER SUPERIOR]
Think nothing of it...
I'm the one who should
be thanking you, Nadie.
[NADIE] Huh?
Thanks to you
and Ellis...
we were able to overcome
a great test from the Lord.
Mother...
[MOTHER SUPERIOR] And besides...
It was kinda fun!
Eh?
[MOTHER SUPERIOR chuckles]
[NADIE laughs]
[creaking]
[BLUE-EYES] Huh?
[ROSENBERG] Heh.
A new detailed
expense report...
I believe everything
is in order this time.
Thank you for bringing it
all the way down here.
Ciao.
Oh, by the way...
How was your meal?
Huh?
Their head chef
is from Japan...
His sauces are like no other...
Gotta run.
Watch out, Jody Hayward... Heh.
[phone rings]
Rosenberg here...
Ah it's you, good...
Where are you now?
[horn honks]
[HEINZ] Ellis...!
Ellis, calm down...!
[KID ELLIS] No...
[HEINZ]
Please Ellis, don't struggle.
No!
No... I don't wanna
do that anymore!
I don't wanna!
[HEINZ sighs]
Ellis...
[KID ELLIS] Don't wanna.
All right then...
No more examinations...
We won't do them anymore...
I promise.
I cross my heart... Deal?
Ellis...
[KID ELLIS] You really promise?
Yeah... I promise.
Doctor...
Ready to hit the road...?
Aaand still asleep.
[NADIE chuckles]
Doctor...
[NADIE gasps]
[BLUE-EYES] One thing
Ellis is not...
...is a child of God.