[WOMEN chattering]
[engine accelerates]
One two!
[NADIE grunts]
[NADIE] One two!
Gah!
Would it kill you
to give me a hand?
What for?
[NADIE] You have to ask?
Until we get this guy's
van unstuck and moving,
we don't go any further.
Oh, come on...!
Today, Ellis...
Alright... Now we'll
push when I say...
Appreciate it,
beautiful ladies...
You're stronger than you look.
[NADIE] Heh, heh...
[gun cocks]
[jeep accelerates]
He's here!
[jeep engine slows]
Ah!
What the hell...?!
I just filled up this morning!
I wanted to get through the
mountains before nightfall.
[chuckles]
Ah!
Gracias...
Saved our skins.
De nada...
I couldn't let two chicas spend
the night up there on their own.
If it hadn't been for you I'd
still be stuck up there myself.
[NADIE] Uh?
[ELLIS] Hm?
Hey...
Happen to know anyone around
here who's good with cars?
Huh?
[BUCHO] Ahh, there it is.
Looks like you've got
a hole in your tank.
[NADIE] Yeah? Great...
Rock musta popped up there.
Can'ya fixit?
[BUCHO] Hmmm...
You're from
the city?
Not that I'm
trying to pry...
But well are you...
from the big city or what?
Um...
'Kay how
about this?
Where are you from?
A laboratory.
A laboratory...?
Funny, you don't look
much like a scientist...
Oh... You must
be on vacation.
Uh... Where ya headed?
The south.
The south...?
Ahh... forget it.
What's wrong?
I have no idea.
[JOSE] Ladies, check out the
newest fashions from the city!
Straight from the manufacturer.
None of that second hand garbage
you see getting
hawked around here.
So what do you think?
Aren't these patterns lovely?
And the stitching is some best
you can find, very durable.
Feel free to try on any of
these that catch your eye.
[RITA] You got a pretty
nice selection this time.
Oh hi there. Uh...
Is it okay if I
take a look around?
Uhh... Make yourself at home.
[RITA chuckles]
Ooh...
I love that one!
No that!
Yeah... It's mine.
Here'ya go.
So... I wonder if you can
help me with something.
[JOSE] Hmm?
[NADIE] Thanks for
your help earlier.
What's her deal?
Rita's a sick
little girl.
What?
But don't let
it bother you...
Just one of
those things...
Like the measles,
everyone gets it at that age.
Huh? Nice, looks like
you got her fixed.
We're testin' it...
How are you?
[JOSE] I've been better.
I put up a lot of dough to get
all those designer items...
People want to do a whole lot of
looking and not enough buying.
Any sales?
Just one...
Some girl wanted me to sell her
a jacket but she couldn't pay...
"'til she struck it rich."
'Til she what now?
She said if I gave her
a ride to the city...
she would make a bunch
of money and pay me back.
Rita, right?
Huh?
[JOSE] She must be thinking
the streets in the city
are paved with gold,
which of course couldn't be
any further from the truth.
[NADIE] Tell ya what, I'll pray
that you make at least one sale.
[JOSE] Heh. Gracias, amiga...
Adios!
What's wrong?
Uh... nothing.
[clattering]
[BUCHO grunts]
[BUCHO] Alright.
That should about do it for now.
[NADIE] Heh.
It's a temporary
patch job at best...
You're gonna wanna take it
to an actual repair shop
when you get to the city.
Thanks Bucho...
So, how much do I owe you?
Forget about it...
Do unta others and
all that, right?
[NADIE] Aww...
You're the best...
'Kay girl... You ready?
[ELLIS] Mm-Hm.
Hold on...
You're plannin' to cross
the pass tonight...?
No way...
Too dangerous.
But there's nowhere to
stay in this village.
[BUCHO] If ya don't mind keeping
a boring old couple company,
my wife and I'd be happy
to put you up for the night.
[NADIE] Comin' in
with the water!
Aw. Thank you girls...
When you're my age,
drawing water tends
to be quite the chore.
[NADIE grunts]
Like Bucho said,
"do unta others"...
Am I right?
[BUCHO chuckles]
[knocking at door]
[BUCHO] Huh?
Wonder who that could be?
Where you want us
to put these?
[CAROLINA] Just over there
to the side would be great.
Sure!
Nadie...
There's someone at
the door for you.
[NADIE gasps]
A guide, huh?
The roads up in the
mountains are tricky...
lotsa cars and horses go
tumbling down those cliffs...
If you wanna get through
the pass in one piece,
you'll need a guide
who knows the terrain
like the back of her hand.
Izzat right?
I don't even want to
get paid for it...
Honestly...
All I ask is a ride to
the nearest big city...
Any big city will do.
Any big city...?
Doesn't matter which?
I couldn't care less...
I just want the heck out
of this boring village.
There goes Rita...
Spouting off again.
No family...? No job...?
Won't you be stuck?
[RITA] Nah, I can work all
that out when I get there.
[NADIE] Huh?
[RITA] My only goal
in life is to avoid
rotting in some
podunk mountain town.
I want to live the big life.
Like cool people!
Yeah, sorry...
Oh come on...
Giving me a lift
would be nothin'...
Unless there's some
reason you don't want to
take me that you're not
to tellin' me about.
There is.
[ELLIS] Huh?
We can't take you 'cause
bein' with us is dangerous.
Oh?
See her...?
Wouldja believe she's my bounty?
Yep...
Ellis is
a bounty.
Me? I'm what you call
a bounty hunter...
With a target on my back and
enemies 'round every corner...
Run with us and you'll just
get dragged down into all that.
You're mocking me 'cause you
think I'm just mountain trash.
Wha...?
No, it's not like that.
If you're gonna lie to my face,
at least do a better
job with it.
What was I thinking?
I don't need your help...
Good luck drivin' those cliffs.
[NADIE] Ah!
[door closes]
[NADIE chuckles]
Did I hear you say
you're a bounty hunter?
Wha...
Uh... Yeah.
She's not kidding.
Huh?
--See?
--Ah!
Put it back.
Yes sir.
Then, what you said about
her being a bounty...?
[NADIE and ELLIS]
Mm-Hmm.
[BUCHO] So I have to ask.
What's a bounty hunter
and her prize
doing in a little
town like this?
Well... You see it's
sort of complicated.
[L.A. chuckles]
[L.A.] Ahh... Ellis...
I've finally found you.
And I will never take
my eyes off you again.
[L.A. chuckles]
Never.
[gunshot]
[bullet shells clatter]
Yes... This should do.
Yes sir... I should
get back to my desk.
Thank you for your work.
[MALE AGENT]
Mm-Hm.
[door closes]
I'm gonna go
scope it out...
You stay here.
Right.
If they dare come in here,
we will smite them.
Oh great, isn't
that reassuring...
Now...
[ELLIS] I'm coming with you.
[NADIE] Ellis?
What's that?
Weapon.
[NADIE] Yeah, that's
not really gonna work.
Two?
Y'know, ya might wanna pick
something a little bigger.
What the hell... is this?
[FEMALE AGENT] See ya, Jody.
I'm heading home.
[BLUE-EYES] Okay.
Have a good night.
[BLUE-EYES sighs]
Repairs to a convent,
what is this about?
Where did this stack
of invoices come from?
That stupid child... Heh.
That stupid girl...
[ROSENBERG and BLUE-EYES] What
in the world is she thinking?
You like...?
They'd look
good on you.
Thing is...
we don't have any luggage
to carry any o' this...
I'll have to pass.
[JOSE] Oh okay.
I'll take this.
[JOSE] Excellent choice.
It really suits you.
[ELLIS laughs]
It's perfect.
[BUCHO] Still got another
spare room if you want it.
[JOSE] Nah, I'm good.
It's a bit of a quirk but
I prefer sleeping in my car.
[RITA chuckles]
I'll pay you back the
day I strike it rich...
I promise.
[JOSE] Hey chica.
You got money?
What poor manners...
Trying to go after my Ellis
while she is asleep.
[JOSE gasps]
Got any last words,
say 'em...
On the mountain, I only
told you we ran out of gas.
Then when you saw it running you
commented about it being fixed.
You're the one who put
the hole in my tank.
You a bounty hunter?
Peddlin' women's clothes
don't put food in my belly.
Put the gun down and back
away from the window...
Do it quietly...
Rather not wake the whole house.
If you to hand over
the little girl...
I have no problem
backing away.
You really think I'd go
for a deal like that?
Yes, I do.
[RITA] Take this!
[splash]
[NADIE] Wha... Is that--?
[JOSE] You know
what will happen
if you fire that gun
of yours, right?
This could have been avoided
if you'd just given me a ride.
[NADIE sighs]
[RITA] Come on, wake up already.
We're going on a little trip.
I said wake up...!
[JOSE] Don't follow us...
Rita go.
Damn.
[jeep ignition starts]
[JOSE] See ya.
What's goin' on?
What's the fastest
car you got?
That was easier than
I thought it'd be!
I'll head straight to the
city if that's okay with you.
Yeah...!
Tell you what.
You get us there in one piece
and I'll buy you
any outfit you want.
You got it...
I'm just glad that
crappy town's behind us!
[engine falters]
[RITA] Huh?!
[JOSE] What is it?
[RITA] I think...
we're leaking gas!
[JOSE] What?!
He said not to
drive it too fast.
[RITA] Why not?
Because the patch
was only temporary
and it might break again.
Now you tell us!
[RITA] Why didn't you
say something before?!
I see...
You still think
I'm just some hick.
[RITA gasps]
Nadie.
[NADIE] Ellis!
[gasps]
[NADIE] I'm comin'...
A-Aaahh!
Ahhh!
[JOSE and RITA scream]
[NADIE] Ellis!
[crashing sound]
[NADIE] You all right?!
Wonderful!
That's my dear darling Ellis.
[ELLIS] Saved.
[NADIE] Huh?
Rita.
[BUCHO] Hey...!
Everyone okay?!
[MEN]
Heave! Heave!
[BUCHO] Get her to
a doctor, rápido!
Looks too late for him...
[RITA] No thanks...
I don't want it.
I did my best trying to pick
the stuff I thought you'd like.
Yeah...
Pretty.
Maybe so but I want more out of
life than just cute clothes.
Not like you can understand
how I feel anyway...
Growing up in nowheresville
is a death sentence
for someone like me.
[RITA sobs]
[BUCHO] Rita wants to see the
world, like any other child.
[CAROLINA] When you live as far
off the beaten path as we do...
it's only a matter of
time before you start
dreaming about the bright
lights of the big city.
[CAROLINA]
Especially at Rita's age.
Right...
Is that the illness
you mentioned?
Huh?
Mm-hmm. Sure is...
Wanderlust hits
us all that age...
But hey...
How else are you gonna find out
what kinda life suits you best?
[CAROLINA] Here, girls.
For the road.
Wow...!
There's so much!
Looks yummy.
They are...
It's what our village
is known for!
Muchas gracias!
See ya! Take care!
--[BUCHO] Be safe you two!
--[CAROLINA] We'll miss you!
[NADIE and ELLIS]
Bye-bye!
I'll get to the city...
someday for sure.
[grunting]
Damn...
Those putas stole my van!
[RICARDO] You all right?
Huh?
You uh, know your
head is bleeding?
[JOSE] Uh--
It's um... tomatoes...
[NADIE chuckles]
Y'like that one, huh?
Yeah.
[ELLIS] How do I look?
[NADIE] Mm...! It is totally
see-through, though.