We're having a soccer match!
Finally lost your moffin' marbles, huh?
No!
Check this out.
You know that stadium to the south?
We'll hold a soccer match there.
That's our only shot at getting
100,000 people in only ten days.
You mean we're hosting a professional match?
That's right... That stadium can hold 50,000 people.
This is the perfect chance to use it.
As I'm sure some of you have already surmised,
going by the current rate, it's impossible
to reach half a million visitors by July 31st.
But if we account for the projected
number of soccer spectators...
Triken!
SIR! As per the acting manager's orders...
secretly I might add...
... I've been conducting research for quite some time now.
I followed the few leads I had all across Japan,
to the north, south, east, and west.
Oh yes, I went to such great
pains during this whole process...
that I only wish I could bow to myself in recogniti...
Hurry and get to the point.
But Miss Isuzu, I was up all night preparing...
What's that?
Basically, I wanted an event that would make
use of the stadium and bring in more guests...
I was actually on the lookout for a long time until now.
I had no idea you were up to something.
I didn't think there was much chance of finding anything.
However...!
Last night I received a positive
response from one of my contacts.
This is the home stadium of
Division One team Grandira Tokyo.
The turf is ragged, so it's scheduled for refurbishing...
but it's taking them too long which means
that the venue won't be ready in time...
for the commemorative match on July 31st.
July 31st, huh?
That's the date the team was founded, so
they were hoping to hold the match on that day.
From what we understand, the
annual match between the current...
and retired champion teams
tends to attract about 50,000 fans.
As you might've guessed, they're
in a hurry to find another venue.
So we'll invite them to come here.
But, sir...
I assume we would need to have some kind of special
license to host a professional match, wouldn't we?
I don't think it's going to be an official game.
I'm sure it'll work out if we negotiate properly.
We'll tell you more after we discuss it with them.
We're gonna be busy if it happens.
So you'd better be ready!
Are you sure you'd like ME to act
as Amabri's main representative, sir?
They won't take us seriously with
a high school student in charge.
Hey, Triken. Did you bring that Rarapazzi thing?
Of course. As long as I have this
they won't even care that I'm a dinosaur.
One question.
Hm?
Tell me honestly please...
How much of a chance do you think we have?
I just don't know.
It looks like it's the right size.
We'll have to see the turf.
What do you think, sirs?
I'm confident that the capacity of the
stadium will be enough to meet your needs.
From the looks of it, the building
was established quite a long time ago.
Ah yes...
I‐it's about 20 years old.
I understand the space hasn't been used much but...
what kind of regular maintenance have you been doing?
Um... Well, let me consult my notes here...
What about access from the train station?
How will you manage 50,000 patrons?
Um, I‐I was thinking hard work
and determination would suffice...
But the most crucial issue here is the turf...
It has to be all‐natural and perfectly maintained...
Without that, there can be no match.
But I'm sure you know that.
Yes of course I know that...
The turf is very important... I know.
No, you didn't.
My concern is that it's a multipurpose
stadium instead of a sports stadium.
Could you tell us more about the turf maintenance?
Ah, actually I'm only the Chief of Sales,
so I wouldn't know the details, sir...
Well then, I appreciate you all taking
the time to come speak with us today.
I think we've heard enough for now.
We'll get back to you with a final decision in a few days.
Wait! Please wait a moment!
I urge you to look over our
proposal one more time, please!
It would mean a lot!
First off... you asked us about maintenance?
The park employees are very dedicated to
keeping the stadium in top-notch condition.
We could do it tomorrow if you wanted.
Oh?
Then the matter of accessibility.
We'd be glad to ask a local bus
company to allocate some shuttle buses.
And our parking lot has enough space for 5,000 cars.
And we actually have a specialist
on site who takes care of the turf.
It's immaculately kept and 100%
natural, so there's no need to worry.
I'm not so sure.
I invite you to come see for yourselves...
You won't be disappointed.
Huh...
That's all well and good, but...
We'd rather not work with a venue with no experience.
Honestly, the main issue is how much this'll cost us.
With all the salary increases,
we're struggling to stay afloat.
We can't afford this.
We couldn't even afford to finish the turf replacement.
I'm starting to doubt that we'll be
able to pay all the bills this month.
We need to talk the price down as much as
possible without divulging our financial problem.
Oh, that's right. I forgot to mention something.
I've discussed this with the rest of our team...
and we've decided we'd like to waive the fees
and allow you to use the stadium free of charge.
No charge?!
That's not all, either...
We recognize bus rentals, security personnel,
advertising, and ticket printing can be expensive,
so we're prepared to cover a portion of
those costs as well if that's alright with you.
Y‐you're offering to pay US money?!
That's right...
In other words, Amagi Brilliant Park is
asking to participate as a sort of sponsor.
A‐are you sure we can promise that, Mr. Kanie?
Well, then we'd be interested in hearing what
kind of numbers you have in mind specifically.
Hm...
I think this is reasonable.
That sound about right?
W‐wait a minute, are you sure that
isn't some kind of gross miscalculation?
Absolutely positive...
These instructions come directly from the manager herself.
It still seems a little high...
Of course it's extremely appealing to us, but...
Aren't you going to suffer a serious loss?
I assure you gentlemen, our manager
is in full support of the sponsorship...
as long as it serves to bring in some new customers.
She'd like us to host these soccer fans
regardless of how much it costs the park.
That's exactly what she said.
We do have one small request, though.
And what's that?
We'd like all the spectators to
go in through the park's main gate.
Of course, if they have a soccer ticket, they'll
be granted the free admission to the park as well.
Why would you want to do that?
It looks like the stadium has its
own separate entrance, doesn't it?
It's too complicated to explain that...
but I'm afraid this particular
request is absolutely nonnegotiable.
Well, I don't see any reason to take issue with that.
What do you say, gentlemen?
Why don't you come pay us a visit soon?
That way you can approve the facility for yourselves.
Are you sure that was wise?
Promising to pay the expenses as well?
You must be well aware of
Amabri's financial situation, yes?
I have a plan.
Trust me.
What about the turf maintenance?
I'm not familiar with any "specialist".
What better landscaper than a flower fairy?
He's got quite the green thumb.
Alright!
Just leave everything to mii!
Mii!
Killer plaaant!
I was expecting something like that.
Are you guys ready?
Take it down!
Crisis averted, boss!
That's wonderful.
Yeah.
This oughta do the trick.
The turf is what really sold us!
I only wish I could convince
you all to tell us your secret.
Everything's not exactly perfect...
but we can iron out the details later on.
There's not much time to prepare, but working together,
I think we'll be able to pull this off quite nicely.
I do appreciate that, sir...
We'll do everything we can to help out.
We respectfully bow to you fine gentlemen.
Thank you so much...
We look forward to working with you as well.
That was nerve‐wracking.
Sento... tell everybody to gather on the roof of
Maple Castle as soon as the park closes tonight...
I'm breaking the news.
I'll do that.
What news is that?
Attention!
I have something I need to tell you.
It's important.
We're selling off the south area!
Y‐you say the south area's gonna be sold‐mii?
Right.
It's not up for discussion.
I was looking for a buyer for a while...
...and the other day I finally found one.
The money we make from that should
take care of our financial issue...
I'm sure you all understand.
Heh, there ya go droppin' another bomb on us.
But Mr. Kanie, the southern area's
almost as big as the main section!
You can't...
I can and I will.
I always thought Amabri would
get back on its feet one day...
and maybe we could build some
nice attractions over in that area.
Me too, I figured that was the plan.
Yeah, if we could've expanded, it would've
really put Amabri on the map once and for all.
None of that stuff is ever gonna happen!
Not before this park runs itself into the ground!
If we have to cut off a limb to
survive, then that's exactly what we'll do!
We can't afford to think about what happens after this.
Okay.
Huh?
Maybe it's not such a bad idea‐ y'know?
Mr. Moffle...
That's true, maybe hanging onto land
we're not using is kind of a waste‐ron.
Fair enough...
Guess I'm on board‐mii.
It does make a lot of sense from
an accounting perspective as well...
It's better if we can solve everything at once.
Maybe you're right... I just think it'll
be sad to give up half of the property.
I know, but it's for the good of the park.
Sounds like the best way for
us to keep working together...
so I can't really complain.
You can't make an omelet without breaking eggs!
Right! Lose the battle, win the war!
Good!
That's all I needed to tell you.
We've got 9 days left, and there's still a lot to do!
Starting tonight, nobody's going home or taking days off!
Now get to work, everyone!
YEAH!
How are the preparations going?
Well, I can't say it's a walk in
the park, but I think we can manage it.
That's wonderful to hear, Sir Kanie.
I'm uh... sorry.
About what?
About my decision I made to sell
almost half of the park property.
I know I discussed it with you before hand...
but I'm sorry it had to happen.
How many times must I say it?
You are the manager of our precious park, Sir Kanie.
We trust you to serve its best interest.
More importantly, isn't there something I can do to help?
I feel terrible sitting here doing nothing
while you're all working so diligently.
For now, your job is to get some rest...
So don't worry about anything else.
I don't know...
What? Now you can't follow the acting manager's orders?
Very well then.
Just sit back and relax.
I mean... think about how much better
this place is doing lately all because of me.
And once we get to August, it'll be even bet...
Oh wait... the first of August...
That's when you're gonna lose
all your memories again, isn't it?
Even if the park stays open.
Please don't let it trouble you.
It's just something that happens every year.
I can't believe you've been living your
life this way for such a long time now.
Yes... At the stroke of midnight
on the first day of August...
my physical body as well as my
memories are set back by a year.
My uncle explained the situation
to me when it happened the last time.
The reason I'm here... and what's happened up until now.
I'm sure I must have met the Digerry
Clan and Sir Rubrum at some point as well...
but I don't have any memory of that.
Oh.
But I know that as long as this park exists,
I'll always be here.
Always and forever.
So please...
Come back and visit me whenever you
can, even after you finish working here.
For some odd reason I never forget how to make croquettes.
Okay... I do like your croquettes.
Right! We can ride the Ferris wheel again too!
Ah! Uh, maybe not that.
Oh, I forgot!
I'm sorry.
Hey there, it's been a while.
You know, you're always barging in.
I just came to check the old visitor counter.
Not giving up, that's sweet.
Yeah, I think we'll just barely make 500,000.
Just to make this clear... the contract
deadline is at closing time on the last day,
which is 9 o'clock sharp.
No extensions allowed... Please remember that.
Well the soccer match kicks off at 6 PM...
So there's nothing to worry about.
I'll send one of my staff the day of...
July 31st at 9 P. M.
I'll be looking forward to it.
Kanie... It's time to go.
Right.
Unlock the gate!
We're open!
Oh my, they're lovely!
How did he do that?
Ro‐Ron! Ron ron...
Keep our planet clean!
Over here. Look at me so I can
take your picture with the ferret guy!
Hey guys!
Ready?
That's awesome!
We sure hope all of you enjoy the show today!
The numbers really are climbing up.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure we'll get even more.
We have to get more.
Current wait time is 20 minutes!
I repeat, the current wait time is 20 minutes!
Miii!!!
Aw, he's so cute!
Mii! Mii! Mii‐heehee!
Jeez, when's it gonna be over...
Mommy! It's Tiramy!
Another one?!
ENCORE ENCORE...
How many encores do they want from me‐ron?
Moff! All units follow me!
Hyahhhh!
I'm sorry, we're full!
but please feel free to wait for the next showtime!
I need 2 carbonaras, an order of hotcakes, 3 udon
bowls, and what was that other thing... 2 bowls of ramen!
W‐w‐wait a minute, there's
no way I can remember all thaaat!
Hey Shiina! We're running low on meat again!
Go pick some up from that store pronto!
Not again!
Go ahead and get as much as you can carry!
We're gonna need at least 200 pounds of it this time!
We don't have enough personnel!
Send some backup to the Lost Child Center ASAP!
Ugh, I'm so exhausted.
I've never even seen this many
people at comic conventions.
This has gotta be some kind of park record.
I can't feel my feet, mii.
Sure wish a nice girl would give me a massage.
Sorry! That's never gonna happen.
It's only gonna get busier in the afternoon.
We'll just have to stick it out.
It's time for the special event...
All cast members please be on standby.
Already?!
Come on dad!
It's almost time!
Slow down buddy, we'll get there.
Someday we'll be this crowded
without the help of some soccer match.
Yeah.
It's over there!
Sweet, let's go!
The people who came in on the
last bus just went through the gate.
Kanie!
We fell short.
Time for the attractions spotlight.
Today's feature is Fisherman's Dive.
Is this really necessary?
The park might be about to shut down.
That's exactly why it's important.
Fine.
So, what's Fisherman's Dive?
A coaster ride in Splash Ocean,
based on Hemingway's famous masterpiece.
Visitors struggle desperately to catch an
impressive marlin only to be thwarted by sharks.
That's not fun!