What? But we made sure...
It's the ticket utilization rate.
Utilization?
I was expecting a couple of the tickets
they sold to end up being no‐shows...
but I didn't think the number would be so high!
I miscalculated! Damn it!
We'll never get 252 people by 9 o'clock!
Princess... I think this may be the end!
Please help!
C'mon... we're not asking for much here!
It'll only take a second!
Just come in for a minuet.
We beseech you, sir!
You'll be doing our world a service!
How about you ladies?
Would you and your little ones please
come visit AmaBri for just a quick second?
Sorry... we're about to be late for dinner!
It won't take long!
We're desperate!
Sorry!
Yes, immediately.
We're inviting you to Amagi Brilliant Park.
Absolutely free!
Yes... yes...
That's right sir...
it won't cost you anything.
Of course not... That's not my intention.
Sorry to bother you.
No good.
I got turned down again.
No luck here either.
Wanipee and the girls are advertising at
the station right now, but... we'll see.
There's gotta be something we can do!
Come on now! Don't you kids think it's
about time for you to throw in the towel?
It's not over yet!
We've still got a moffin' chance at this!
Let's fight 'til the end!
But...
Hey Takami, sorry to call you at work.
Yeah it's me. Listen.
Could you bring every single customer
you have over to AmaBri right now?
It's really important.
Huh? Hey!
Tell 'em I'll pay their tabs if they come.
We came up short on visitors.
I'll never ask you for moffin' else!
Uh‐huh... Thanks a lot... See ya.
Don't just stand there!
Start calling!
Everyone you know!
You're serious? Cold‐calling?
Hey... Pachinko Parlor?
Shizue? Is that you‐mii?
Hello Grandma‐this is Muse.
Sorry to bother you. Is the con over yet?
Most people scroll right past stuff like this, but... eh.
Tally ho!
Hello there.
I know it's been a while,
but I actually have a bit of a favor to ask of you.
It's 252 people...
I highly doubt this'll make enough difference.
Sento, you're in on this too?
I'm telling the cast to help out.
Hey buddy, long time no see.
There's a little somethin' I need from ya...
Good evening!
No, I don't need to order supplies today.
Thank you very much!
I do appreciate your support.
Arr, if ye refuse it's the gallows fer ya!
Come on, pops! I'm only askin' for two or three head!
Yeah, I'll take a medium Margherita pizza.
Oh and make sure you bring it
through the main gate please.
Ecological emergency... mhm.
Hello? Hellooo?
Fine, I'll do it!
Uh... hey... is this Terano? It's Kanie.
I was wondering if... What? No, it's not that.
Listen. I still don't really understand
what happened but... I'm so sorry.
A‐anyway, I need to ask a favor of
you and it has to be done right NOW, okay?
Moff!
Takami!
Hey. sorry it took us so long!
Sorry to put you out.
Don't mention it.
I could never say no to a regular in trouble!
Look! It's them‐ron!
What's up?
Who are they‐mii?
They work at my favorite pachinko place!
What the moff is this?
Heh. I told all their husbands they were cheating on 'em.
You really went all out...
Oh no. This isn't the half of it‐mii!
That bastard messed with my wife!
See? Double the numbers‐mii!
Look mommy. They're having a grownup discussion!
Shush. Just pretend you don't see anything.
That's my grandma!
Sorry dear... none of my friends could make it.
Mm‐mm... I'm just glad you're here, Grandma!
Gang's all here, Salama!
Oh wow! my followers!
Sorry we're late, Kobory.
You brought the whole club!
Shirukooooo!
Huh?!
Shiruko is taking the stage!
Do I wanna know?
Apparently she's an internet celebrity‐ron.
A million hits?!
We just need 8 more people.
We might make it!
Kanie!
Okay we're here, now what?
Terano!
I‐I'm sorry. I could only get so many people to come.
No... this is great!
What the heck kinda goofy outfits are those?
Don't worry about that.
Moff! Only three more!
What is it?
They were the last people...
That's everyone we contacted.
But I don't have anyone else to call!
Neither do I-ron!
I'll try posting again!
But we can't lose now!
Somebody please!
No, it's all over...!
I'm gonna disappear forever!
Moff!
Just three more!
Someone! Anyone!
Again... I failed her again!
Mommy, I'm tired...
We'll be home soon, okay?
Huh?
IT'S A GIRLLLL!
Wahoo!
Don't you move.
Hah!
Yahoo!
Yeahhh!
We... we won...
Moffin' barely...
500,000! The park is saved!
That was awesome‐mii!
Hmph...
All tuckered out?
No I'm not...
Seiya.
I gotta admit...
We have you to thank for saving us.
Mr. Kanie!
Thank-you-thank-you-thank-you!
It's... it's a miracle!
I'm practically hunched over in tears...
Hey! get off of me ya bunch of goofballs!
Sir Kanie... Thank you...
Thank you so much for all you've done!
Alright!
Here's to pulling together to save
the earth from total destruction! Cheers!
Cheers!
Everything's settled.
Yes, sir! the park will be open tomorrow as normal.
Now, about selling the land...
Oh that's excellent, thank you so much!
We'll send someone over in a few days.
Okay, say moff!
Moff!
Thank you so much, Princess Latifah!
It's my pleasure.
Th‐thank you for t‐taking it, M‐Mr. Moffle!
Moff, no trouble at all.
We'll see you later!
Can I get everyone's attention?
We have today's guest count.
Turns out we had 54976 people.
As I told everybody when this whole thing started,
I'll be stepping down as manager from this day forward.
Huh?
I remember I was so shocked
when I saw how bad this place was.
Well it's still pretty bad!
Seriously, you losers had better be glad I'm a genius!
What a stuck‐up jerk‐ron!
Ehh, we'll let it slide today!
But...
But when the chips were down...
I was totally powerless to carry you guys through it.
But because of all of you...
we came out on the other side.
So... I wanna thank you...
Wha‐?!
Huh?!
B‐be quiet!
Anyway, I have another big announcement!
Earlier this evening, we officially closed the
deal to sell off the secondary park to the south!
The property was purchased by Moll Mart.
Wait a minute, there's no way you're talking about
that supermarket chain that's famous around the world‐mii!
Yep.
It won't be any time soon, but eventually they're
gonna build a giant shopping mall right next to AmaBri.
That should lead to a nice
customer spillover on both sides.
It'll be perfect synergy!
So when that happens, you clowns are
gonna be so busy you won't have time to think!
Oh boy, this is my chance to really be popular!
Something wrong?
It's nothing.
What do you want?
Very impressive.
It looks like that prophecy was right about you after all.
So how do you know about that?
You tell me, Champ.
Oops. I guess you can't read my mind anymore.
You may have gotten lucky this time, my
friend, but you can't rest on your laurels forever.
No matter how many visitors the park may
get, the princess will still be losing Animus.
In less than half an hour the date will change over.
And a brand new year will start from page one.
Glimpsing an ember of hope only
to have it dashed before your eyes.
I can practically taste your despair.
And I intend to savor every morsel!
Kanie!
Moff!
So all this time! It was him!
Moff my words, I'll crush that bastard!
What the...?
He's the one who cast the curse...
The sorcerer I told you about.
It's almost time.
Yeah.
I should say...
Y‐yes?
Thank you for everything, Lady Isuzu.
I'm not certain who I'm going to be when
tomorrow comes but... I hope you'll support me.
Yes... upon my life.
And Uncle?
Moff...
Try not to drink so much.
Okay, I'll try.
Please take care, you three.
Lord Moffle...
Sir Kanie.
I don't think I can ever thank you enough.
Uh‐huh...
You seem a little upset.
You think so?
Yes! You haven't even boasted
about your "supreme intellect" yet.
The truth is...
This isn't what I want at all!
Not after I met you... not
after the happy days we all shared!
And not after the wonderful miracle I witnessed tonight!
I just can't bear the fact
that I'm about to forget it all!
It's not much... but this is all I can do.
It helps.
That tree...
I don't think it's ever bloomed that much.
I failed her again... I couldn't...
Sir Kanie...?
Moff?!
You know who I am?!
Well of course I do...
I DO remember!
Latifah...
That tree is called Elpis. It
thrives on Animus for energy.
The amount it consumed in these three
months was enough to make it bloom.
Animus also alleviates Her Majesty's curse...
so I can only imagine the combined happy thoughts of
all the park visitors were what saved her in the end.
Kanie!
Sento... What's up?
Are you... leaving now?
Yep! Good riddance!
Look... Sento...
Ah! Wh‐what?
Here's the thing...
Yes?
It's nothing! Bye!
Agh, dammit!
Hey, sorry it's so late.
How'd things go at work?
Good, we delivered ahead of schedule.
Ohh.
Guess YOU had a rough day.
I quit.
You quit?! Already?!
Well, that's a shame.
Why's that?
You just looked like you were having fun.
Huh?
Yeah. you seemed excited!
Ever since you first started.
And you've never been excited about anything.
Does that surprise you?
I'm gonna puke‐mii...
Oh good morning, you two!
You don't look well...
Are you hungover?
Here comes the miracle dribble past 11 opponents!
Ah, youth‐ron...
I'm not doin' squat today...
Hey, no lying down on the job!
Kanie!
I thought you quit yesterday!
I changed my mind.
Without me, you'll go back to slacking off all the time...
I'll be keeping an eye on you from now on.
Seriously?
He's gone full Big Brother!
Quiet! It's almost time to open.
Moff?
We've got work to do, you lousy rat.
Get busy.
Well, I'll be moffed.
Perfect... Not that I'm surprised.
You came back...
Sento... Late, I see.
Did I miss something?
Yeah, this place is a disaster.
If we let our guard down just because we
reached the goal, it'll ruin everything.
You mean... you're...?
Yeah yeah... Enough chit‐chat! How's the schedule today?
Ah... first we have a pre‐shift
meeting with all the cast members.
Then let's go.
Sir Kanie!
I'm here to stay.
Well, at least until everyone finally
gets their sorry selves together.
Great!
I hope you're grateful!
I'm going out of my way to bless you with my skills!
Is everything ready to go?!
Yeah!
I want you to give it all you've got!
Open the gates!
Come on in!
Enjoy your day at Amagi Brilliant Park!
Attractions Spotlight!
The park is still open! You wanna do the honors, Sento?
Of course. Today's feature is Space Captain
a thrilling retro sci‐fi adventure ride.
The hero embarks on an epic
quest to the far ends of the galaxy.
Let me guess, you're about to tell me
something lame that ruins the whole thing.
How did you know?
The ride is currently shut down because
the Captain is suffering from lower back pain.
I knew it.