We're out of money.
I told you the 30 yen plan was a bad idea.
Look, the point is, I'm really sorry,
but we're not gonna be able to
pay anybody for this past month.
You're not giving us a paycheck?!
What's with that, mii?!
Forget it! We can't give you money we don't have!
But I have to go to the bars
and pick up all the loose women!
No, you don't.
And I have to play pachinko!
Again, no, you don't!
Listen up! I need you to help me brainstorm
some ideas to help bring in some quick revenue.
Betting on horses!
No gambling!
Ooh! Adults-only attractions!
That's probably illegal.
Moffle Punching Bag!
You're just gonna punch right back.
I have the solution here.
Uh, I'm not sure what that is...
Come on, think! There's gotta be another way!
Hmm...
Ron! Here's an idea!
Let's pay a visit to Dornell's Cave!
Dornell's Cave?
You know about the secondary park, don't you?
Yeah, I did read a little bit about it.
So, what's the big deal?
Dornell's Cave is inside that park!
Moff! A while back, there was a flower
fairy working here by the name of Dornell.
But one dark night, he got drunk, and set off
on a test of courage with some of his buddies.
I don't have time for the whole novel.
Anyway, they found some treasure in that cave.
Hey, there... Could we get two crepes please?
Uh, hello?
Huh? Didn't think it would be this grand.
The southern region was supposed to
be a second park with a focus on sports.
This stadium was the first element they built.
But after the bubble burst, the plan fell
apart and they just kinda left the building here.
It was quite disappointing.
Ever since that happened, the entire
southern area's been completely untouched.
And rumor has it Dornell never came
out of the cave again after that night?
That's right.
Wait, you never told us what happened
to the friends who came in here with him.
They looked pretty beat-up when they were found.
One guy said:
"There's a frickin' huge labyrinth in there, dude."
Does that mean they ended up finding the treasure?
If that's true, we're gonna be rich, mii!
Don't get too excited.
It's a dead end.
But what about the moolah?!
Tiramy, this is embarrassing.
I can't believe I wasted all this time
on that ridiculous story you guys told me.
Come on, let's go.
Check it out!
I found a secret switch, mii!
You call that secret?!
Now, let's see what happens when we push it!
No! Wait a second!
Whoa!
Moff! Seems legit.
I feel like a bad-ass, ron!
Aw, yeah! That's what I'm talkin' about, mii!
Shall we go?
Wait, Sento! Shouldn't we check
the place out before we just...
We locked ourselves iiiiiin!
We're gonna die in here!
It was a trap, mii!
I told you idiots!
No way to go but forward, I guess.
Can we come in? Mr. Kanie, we were just
hoping we could talk to you about a new show...
Huh?
Woohoooooo!
Miss Isuzu and Mr. Kanie must've stepped away.
Maybe you should try texting them real quick.
Let's see here...
I'm surprised we have a signal.
Super Sylphy is at the top of her game today!
Does that say "hole"?
What kinda weird emoji is that?
Skeletooooon!
What the...
Whoa!
I am the guardian of this accursed realm.
Come, adventurers, enter the Forsaken Labyrinth of Doom!
Did he just talk?!
Oh my, ron!
Such a thing defies scientific possibility, mii!
Oh, yeah, sure! This coming from the talking pink cat!
Wow!
Choose one of these coffins.
You will be granted a weapon of ultimate power!
Is he seriously just handing out weapons, mii?!
I hope we don't get eternally cursed or something.
A shovel?
And I got a stun gun.
Check out this huge metal bat!
Molotov cocktails! That's awesome!
Mine had a chain.
This stuff seems oddly violent for a family theme park.
Proceed into the darkness, fearless heroes!
You may go!
I feel like something's gonna jump up out of nowhere.
Don't let your guard down.
What'd I step on?
Oh man, that was close! I thought we were goners, ron!
Y-yeah, I don't wanna be rich after all!
Let's just go home now, mii!
Go home?! How?!
Calm the moff down.
First, we need to come up with a survival strategy.
Isuzu!
I'm ready!
Tiramy, we'll take the front!
Macaron, bring up the rear and keep an eye out for traps.
Isuzu, protect the kid!
Roger that, Captain Moffle!
Do you guys hear how dumb you sound?
Now, let's get a moff on!
I think I just moffed up.
You what?!
Huh?
At 12 o' clock!
All units retreat!
Whoo, Super Sylphy takes the lead again!
Like I said, I don't get her choice of emoji.
Kanie!
Sento!
You're more of a jerk than I thought.
Moff! Let's get outta here!
They got her...
No time to cry about that.
We have to find a way out of this crazy place first.
I know, I just...
Wait, mii!
Sounds like we got company.
What are those things?
They're about to get their butts kicked.
Let's moff 'em up!
Why would you pick a fight with them?!
Let the men handle this, chicken boy.
Here they come!
Eat this!
NOW, DANCE!
Heh-heh-heh...
Let the bloodbath begin!
I'm gonna make you punks beg
for the sweet release of death!
Can we just go?
Where are we?
Some kind of holding cell.
I need a nice long bath.
Not till we get out of here.
Now, how do we open this?
Do you have like a hairpin or something to...
I've got something much better.
I always liked you, ron.
That's odd. Why is it so quiet?
You'd think an alarm would go off or something like that.
This picture is priceless!
What kind of place is this?
Huh? Food's here already?
Dornell-Ron!
You're still alive?!
I'm so exhausted...
I can't dig anymore.
I'm all out of Molotov cocktails.
If only there was some chemical fertilizer lying around...
I could whip up some sick explosives
and wipe this place out, mii.
Great, the giant, pink kitten makes bombs.
There's more of them!
Are you moffin' serious?!
And now here I am.
So, you're telling us no one ever came here to rescue you?
And you've spent all this time
collecting figures and watching anime,
even getting them to set up
internet so you could play games?
And you've been down here for ten years.
Uh-huh! It's so comfy down here.
Hey, would you mind bringing me something to snack on?
I'm in the mood for some potato chips today.
Oh, and some oolong tea and three cups.
Thanks a bunch!
Listen... Don't you have a problem with the fact that...
everybody in the park thought you
were dead for the past ten years?
Why didn't you tell anyone you were alive?
At first I just wanted it to be a long vacation.
But after a while, it was too awkward to tell anyone.
Plus, that was around the same time I got hooked on MMOs.
What's an MMO?
You know, online games.
For a while there, I was logging
in for like 20 hours every day.
That's pretty disgusting, ron.
But how did you live your life in solitude for
all these years Without interacting with anyone?
Well, I play as a girl, so I'm kinda popular.
I'm not sure how to respond to that...
Pardon me.
Huh?
I brought you the chips and oolong tea you asked for.
Oh, perfect, thank you so much!
He's even got a servant?
I can't believe we almost died over some stupid treasure!
A-A-A dragon?!
Moff, it's just one thing after another today.
We're dead, mii!
I am known as Rubrum.
My wisdom surpasses that of man.
Tell me, why have you disturbed my slumber?
Oh God, what do we do now?! He's gonna eat us!
Just calm down.
Man up and look him right in the eye!
If you're so brave, stop using me as a meat shield!
We're sorry for bothering you, Mr. Rubrum, sir.
I promise you we're not here to make trouble.
You see, the thing is we kinda lost our way.
So all we're trying to do is
get back to our friends safely.
As I told you, I surpass human wisdom.
How can you hope to fool me with lies?
You have only come here to obtain the hidden treasure!
No, sir! I'm the acting manager of this park.
I'm just here to do a routine
inspection of all the attractions!
Ha! I have lived in this world for eons now,
and my intelligenceis far greater than your own.
You cannot deceive me!
Yeah, yeah, we get it! You're
smart or whatever. Can we move on now?
Tiramy!
You dare insult me?
Then, you will pay for your impertinence with your lives!
We're in trouble now, mii!
If I'm goin' down, I'm takin'
all these jokers down with me!
Wait, I've got an idea.
Hey, Rubrum! You keep telling us you're more
intelligent than all of mankind, isn't that right?
Don't make me laugh! I can tell you're a liar!
What did you say, human?
I'm a hell of a lot smarter
than you are, you overgrown lizard!
I'd certainly like to see you prove it.
You bet! Ask me any question you want.
But if I get the right answer,
then you have to let us go free.
Deal? Very well.
But if you cannot answer correctly, you
had better be prepared to face my wrath.
You got it. Let's go!
Then answer me this, you pitiful fool of a mortal.
It has to do with an ancient legend.
Back in the olden days, Illimo the
First from the land of Legnum Sonim...
This little whelp couldn't possibly know the Holy
Grail of Noitomorp Runostargnoc the Wise, still...
The Holy Grail of Noitomorp Runostargnoc the Wise.
What?! B-but I haven't even finished
asking you the full question yet.
But I was correct, wasn't I?
Uh, well, uh...
Was I right or not?
You were.
Moff!
That was absolutely incredible!
How did you know the answer to that?!
Ha! Trade secret.
Th-there must be some mistake! That question is taken...
from the elite Schuvert Agricultural University's
entrance exam for the Livestock Alchemy department!
There was no way you could have known that!
It's an exam question?
Nerd.
Ah, don't make fun of me!
Regardless, I cannot allow you to leave alive!
You know, he's not that intimidating anymore.
That's a good point!
I feel like I can actually take this guy now.
You're tougher than I thought. Fine!
Stop, Moffle.
Get ready for some pain!
Dragon Slayer Technique!
I said stop!
What's your problem?!
You're wasting your breath.
I'm really sorry, all right? I just
got a little too carried away, that's all!
But still, you didn't have to hit me like that!
I mean, to be fair, I shouldn't
have let myself get all worked up
just because you're the first
guests I've had in several years.
Wait, "guests"?
Yes, you're only the second group of
adventurers to visit Rubrum's Chamber of Trials...
since this attraction came into existence.
It wasn't real?!
Rubrum's telling the truth.
Sento! I'm so glad you guys are alive, mii!
Hey, wait, that's... that's Dornell!
Why are you guys so obsessed with me?
Whew, boy!
An attraction that never opened?
Let me explain everything in detail.
Name's Taramo. Nice to meet ya!
I happen to be the leader of the Digerry clan.
So you're the one in charge here? All right, I'm all ears.
But I don't have all day, so
keep it to 20 seconds or less.
O-kay!
While my people have a great talent for construction,
we've always been kinda pushed
around by the powers that be.
Just when things were gettin' rough, the park
authorities agreed to let us take refuge here.
But we had to make it appear on paper as an "attraction".
There ya go, with time to spare.
I'm lost.
The Digerry clan was starting to get a lot of crap from
a bunch of bullies who call themselves the Polytia Empire.
From what I understand, it was supposed to be a secret...
that Amabri helped get the clan out of trouble with them.
Something suspicious was happening with money as well.
You mean the park spent money on this?
They gave us some construction
funds to live on at the beginning,
but when that was gone we had to dip into our assets.
Assets? Are you referring to...
Oh yeah, our treasure used to
fill up this entire main hall,
but we spent every last bit of it.
Whaaaat?!
That's no fair, mii!
So we came all the way down here
for nothing and risked our lives?!
Rah, rah, rah! Whoo!
Do you think she's really okay?
Bobsled!
I hear you all had quite the adventure today.
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you about that actually.
That's about it.
Oh my goodness, that's quite a story.
To tell you the truth, well, I...
Hey!
Miss Manager!
Whoa, there!
'Scuse me, coming through, sorry everybody!
Please forgive me, friends. You see, I
wasn't able to fit through the staff corridor...
Did you just fly your giant
dragon self over a public road?!
Evening, Miss Manager.
It's a pleasure to get to speak with you.
Oh, no, the pleasure's all mine.
Kanie, mii!
We need to make an announcement.
Did something bad happen?
We did some digging, and it turns out the Polytia
Empire fell apart after a pretty nasty uprising.
Which means the Digerry clan's got
nothing to be afraid of anymore, mii!
Well, that's convenient, isn't it?
Really? Are you sure that's true?!
Yup!
So, we're finally free.
In that case, would you please
consider giving all of us a job?
A job?!
I'd like to be employed here as well.
I promise I'll do my VERY best to scare the visitors!
Interesting...
What do you say to that, Sir Kanie?
Sure, I can put you guys to work.
Gosh, you mean it?
Yeah, but fair warning,
I'm gonna work you to the bone every day.
Hurray! Way to go!
But, Kanie, what'll we do about the money?
Oh! Just leave everything to yours truly, ron.
Did they really build that thing overnight?!
Yep, that's the total.
Stop! Stop! Stop! Come back!
Selling off Dornell's collection ought
to get us through the month at least.
Good.
But that doesn't exactly take care of our biggest problem.
What are you going to do now?
I got the goods right here, mii!
Sweet, I can't wait to try these babies out!
This is gonna be killer...
Time for the attractions spotlight.
Today's feature is Planet Dinosaur,
a prehistoric adventure where
dinosaurs still roam the Earth.
I hear Triken makes an appearance here sometimes.
Oh, I thought he was just Chief of Sales.
Kids and parents alike can't get
enough of this educational thrill ride
from the Triassic to the Cretaceous Period.
I see. Is there like a grand finale, too?
Yes, they go extinct.
That's not fun at all!