I want some ice cream!
Hope you enjoy it! Strawberry's the best kind!
Moff!
Moff! Moff, moff, moff!
Wow, did you hear that, boys and girls?
Moffle wants to thank every one of
you for coming out to Amabri today!
Ron, ron, rooooon!
Macaron wants to play!
Mii, mii, miiiiii!
Tiramy's happy too!
Here we go!
Still not enough turnout.
Okay, then we're just gonna have to kick
the entertainment factor up another notch.
That's what we're here for, isn't it?
Definitely.
Don't screw up.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Look! I see Moffle!
Moff! Moff...
Wow!
I wanna go get a closer look at him!
A shark?
I wonder if he's part of the show too?
Why would you do that, Jaw?
I thought I told you to always stay behind the scenes!
I apologize, sir!
Really, I do! But I am a man of the sea!
And so I assumed that the pool was the
most appropriate place for me to greet...
Well, yeah, it wouldn't be a problem if
you could be tiny and adorable all the time,
But whenever you get wet...
You've never seen yourself?!
Ah, just go hide in the machine room!
I'm a disgrace.
I always thought it was my
destiny to live at sea, and now...
Umm...
What in Neptune's name is this?
Oh, this is actually a magic portal that
connects Amabri directly to Maple Land.
When the park was first built,
This gate was set up so we
could easily transport supplies.
M-M-Maple Land, that's the m-m-magical k-k-kingdom...
All of you used to I-I-live in, isn't that r-right?
Yeah, exactly.
But then we decided to have the portal sealed shut,
Since we don't really have any
use for it anymore, you know?
Oh hey, there's water leaking out.
Well anyway, I'll get the Facilities
guys to come take a look at it.
You two keep an eye on it, okay?
Aye, this be good land.
So me crew 'n' I'll be takin' it fer ourselves!
Now, all ye filthy bilge-rats better
take heed to what we tell ye to do!
And if'n ye won't listen,
you'll answer to ME, the Dread
Lady Pirate, Captain Isuzulha!
What happened?
Waa ah ah ah ah...
Ah, she's moffin' terrible at this.
Avast, ye faithful crew!
Whoever makes a fuss is walkin' the plank!
Aye aye, Captain!
Moff moff moff moff!
We won't go easy on you, pirates!
Moff! Moff!
Arrr, ye scallywags! You're gonna swab the poop deck!
Those boys are definitely lovers.
What? You're one of my followers?
I'm a huge fan! I've seen all of your flame wars!
Ye Maaa...
Fen Zongggg...
Sssshhhhhwwww!
Oh my, it looks like the performance is already underway!
Yes, I can't wait for the bows.
I shouldn't have made you sneak around with me.
Forgive me, Triken.
Oh, no, I bow down before you, Princess.
But only out of respect, obviously.
Sorry it took so long!
Dad-gum!
It should only take a few minutes, right?
Are you crazy?!
Whoa!
Get 'em, get 'em!
Oh, no that's not good!
Moffle and his friends have just been captured!
But all of us can help!
Let's all cheer!
At last, we've found ourselves a port.
Whoa, what's going on over here?!
That big ugly guy's name is Ironbeard.
Back in Maple Land, he's known as
the meanest bully on the high seas.
He must've gotten out through the underground gate.
Probably.
Arr, I was hopin' to find myself
some treasure beyond the portal.
Ah, well, sellin' off the wenches 'n brats oughta
bring in a pretty pile o' gold doubloons at least.
I be the fearsome pirate they call Ironbeard!
And I've come here to pillage and pilfer the lot of ye!
So don't bother puttin' up a fight!
What's he doing, Mommy?
Uh-oh, looks like the bad guys are here!
Moff! Moff, moff, moff!
He says "You won't get away with this!"
Ye might as well come along quietly, mateys!
I might even let ye join my crew!
Mii! Mii! Mii!
"No way, we'd never work for you!"
A cryin' shame, that.
And I was gonna let ye have
yer fun with any wench ye like.
Resistance be futile!
MOFF! Tiramy!
Traitor-ron!
Look, I know what I want, okay?!
Now, me hearties! Grab 'em!
Fire in the hole!
MOFF!
RON!
I won't repeat that!
Haa! Yah!
Zuo You Lou Xi Ao Bu...
Pr-Princess Latifah, you have to get out of here!
It's too dangerous!
Hyahhhh!
Quit yer wigglin' about!
Sir Kanie!
Um, this isn't good.
Oh, no, Princess Latifah's been kidnapped by the pirates!
Avast! It's time to celebrate!
Miiii!!
This fella says.
"Two more drinks over here,
little lady, and make it snappy!"
Uh, okay! Be right over!
And this gentleman says.
"Hey there, honey, whip us up one
strawberry and one lemon on the double!"
Coming up! Hold on a minute!
I thought that was all scripted,
So how is she translating for the seals?
In all me years o' debauchery,
I never thought we'd manage to make a
hostage outta the Princess of Maple Land!
Ahoy, what's with all the dillydally?
Fetch me another drink, ye wretched dogs!
Zhuan Shen Ban Ian Chui.
J-Just take the bottle, little Missy!
Right.
Here.
They really went all out with whatever this is!
Ron! Now what?!
Our paws are tied. We'll just have to
sit tight and see how everything plays out.
I'm alive...
Hey, what's Jaw doing here?
Chujo?!
You're eating people now?! You monster!
Huh?
N-n-n-no, wait! You've g-g-got it all wrong!
M-M-Mr. Jaw was actually t-t-t-trying to save my I-life,
So that's w-w-why I was-
M-Mr. Jaaaaaaaaah!
Acting manager! It's good to see you're okay!
Glad you guys made it!
Well, boys, it seems the time has come!
They're very excited!
PEH!
Ye three louts walk the plank.
Bosun, do the honors.
Me?
Mii!
"Walk the plank! Walk the plank!"
Ow! Tiramy, how could you do this to me, ron?!
Please don't let it end like this!
Listen! It's okay, mii.
You know I would never push my best
pal into a pool of squishy death, right?
Thanks, Tiramy.
So, you just follow my lead and I promise
I'll get you out of this mess somehow, okay, mii?
Okay, got it.
What's the plan now?
Betrayal!
They're saying "Look at him suffer!"
Oh, no! Macaroooon!
"Walk the plank! Walk the plank!"
The best way to trick your enemy
is to trick your friends first.
Our comeback starts right now, mii.
Moff, as if I'd fall for that.
Now, just stand right here at the edge of the plank...
Moff!
Mii! Miiiiiiiiii!
MOFF!
That's what I'll do.
Now, just stand at the edge of the plank...
Moff!
Moooofffff!
They love it!
Dude, what exactly were you trying to do just now?
Okay, your turn! They saved the best for last.
I think I have a plan, if you'll just, um...
M-mii...
Now he's walking?
Guess so.
Fire!
Hmm?
Yaaaah!
Who's shooting the cannon?!
Kanie?!
On yer feet! Yer comin' with me!
The princess!
Are you okay there, Miss Manager?
I'm all right, thank you.
Here we go!
It's time for a little payback!
Ronnn!
Moff!
Look at that, boys and girls,
our friends are here to rescue us!
So, I want you all to cheer nice and loud for them, okay?
Uh-oh, whose side should I take now?
Arr, you'll pay for this!
ARRR!
Hyah!
I knew this guy was tough!
Avoid the left side of the stage!
That's where most of the guests are!
Third cannon, get it together!
Second cannon, reload!
Ah, right away, Captain!
Ready! Fire away!
It's a shark!
St-stay away from me!
Have mercy, I beg ye!
Ironbeard and his gang of pirates have surrendered!
I really love a happy ending!
Ew, strawberry syrup is so sticky!
Yer a blitherin' fool if ye think ye
can treat the great Ironbeard this way.
Sure I can. You just cost us a fortune in damages.
And I'm gonna make sure you pay.
Whatever it takes.
I'd like to see ye try. Yer a...
That's enough out of you!
Unless you want double your punishment!
Ah, beggin' yer pardon, sir.
Today was exciting, huh?
I had a lot of fun!
Can we come back soon, Mommy?
Of course!
Fine then, you guys'll work here all summer long.
Without any compensation!
And I expect every guest to be entertained.
I'll do no such thing, ye...
Stop your bellyaching.
A-aye, sir.
Jaw... A-at your service!
I'd like you to serve as their team leader from now on.
Would you do that for me?
Are you sure you want ME, sir?!
Yep! I need you to watch out for them, onstage and off.
Right! I won't let you down!
M-M-Mr. Jaw, c-congratulations!
I'm truly greatful!
Thank you so much! It's an honor!
Sir Kanie...
I just wanted to apologize to you
for all that happened here today.
It's entirely my fault that everything
got out of hand. I'm terribly sorry.
Latifah...
What are you talking about?
I should say thank you!
Well, just take a look around!
A new side attraction...
New cast members...
A pirate ship!
And we basically got it all for free!
It's kinda funny!
Oh...
All's well that ends well, mii!
You know what? Nobody has anything to be sorry for!
But you do.
Wh-Who, mii?
Lady Isuzu?
Please, try not to be too harsh on him.
As you wish, Princess.
You're lucky, Tiramy.
I'll let you say some parting words before you die.
I just wanna say that I have faith in all of you!
I know you guys would never do something
like this to one of your own, right, mii?!
Ha! That's a good one, buddy-ron.
Yeah, if that's the case, then it's
a good thing you're not one of us.
Mii!
MMMIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII!!!
Well, well, well!
Never thought you'd end up being acting manager.
Look, is there anything I can do for you?
No, not really.
I just wanted to peek in on you for a bit.
From what I understand, your visitor count's been looking
a little more optimistic since the last time I saw you.
I think I get it.
I really don't know that I've done much of anything yet.
Well, then, I suggest you give it
your best shot, Mister Celebrity.
Tick-tock!
All right, let's do one last check!
Front!
Back!
Skirt!
Good! It's gonna be perfect!
Time for the attractions spotlight.
Today's feature is Blue Ocean.
It's useful for drawing in customers during the summer.
Better than anything else does, I guess.
But just like what happened today,
It does connect to other worlds from time to time.
We've already had to deal with
a kraken and a giant octopus.
And it wasn't all over the news?!
Genjuro, the dolphin, always feels responsible,
So he usually commits ritual suicide.
He usually does?!