I know it's sudden, Seiya Kanie, but...
Are you free next Sunday?
I want to go to a theme park together with you.
Is this your way of asking me on a date or something?
Sure.
And why are you packing heat?
To keep you from running.
You'll shoot if I say no?
Correct. Your answer?
Look, you can't expect me to...
Kanie...
Answer me.
Mm‐hm!
How's it going today, handsome?
Lookin' good as usual.
Since I am a total stud.
And I'm one of the smartest students in the school.
The fact that I was asked out on a date by
some transfer student I've never spoken to before,
just doesn't surprise me.
Let's go.
O‐okay...
Isuzu Sento...
That's my name.
Where exactly are we going?
Amabri.
Amabri?
Amagi brilliant park.
There's a bus that goes straight to it from here.
See ya.
Mommy!
That pretty lady's got blue stripes on her panties.
Look over there!
Just be like everybody else
and pretend like you don't see it.
So if I don't come with you, I'm dead?
That's the idea.
What's so great about this amusement park anyway?
To put it more clearly, it's a theme park.
What's the difference?
And besides, don't you think you
owe me an explanation for all of this?
It hasn't been that long since
you transferred to our school,
and you're trying this hard to get a date?
I mean I know I'm devilishly good‐looking,
but there's gotta be some other reason!
What are you trying to accomplish here?
Why does it have to be that specific park of all places?
Did you pull that out of your...
Amagi brilliant park, huh?
Have you ever been there before, Kanie?
I think I might've been to it
one time when I was really little,
but I'm not sure if I...
Doesn't look that bad.
Next stop, Amagi Brilliant Park.
I repeat, Amagi Brilliant Park.
Wait.
Please take all your belongings...
it's the next one.
Then what's that big, fancy castle thing?
A love hotel.
Oh... what?!
Yeah, I get it!
It's a common mistake.
The main park entrance used to be at that stop,
until the park was renovated ten years ago.
The love hotel was built on that land shortly after that.
That's misleading!
Why don't they just change the name of the bus stop then?
That request was made a while ago,
but it keeps getting put off for some reason.
Despite how many guests get off the bus back there.
Wait, "guests"?
You know, customers.
That's what they're called at most theme parks.
The customers are guests, and
the staff are called cast members.
Try to remember that.
Isuzu Sento,
you're kind of a strange girl, you know that?
Here we are, Kanie.
It's this dead on a Sunday?
Typical count on weekend days is 2,110.
That's precise.
Let's go to sorcerer's hill first.
"Sorcerer's hill"?
It's one of the areas of Amabri.
Since it's home to the lovable mascot
characters of the magical kingdom of maple land,
it's bursting with dreams and happiness.
The way you said that just now makes
me think it's bursting with boredom.
This is Tiramy's flower adventure.
Tiramy's a flower fairy.
I'd like to recommend climbing aboard the fancy train.
It'll whisk you away to a delightful
world full of love and cheer.
Like I told you the first time,
you're not making it sound very delightful at all.
Welcome...
Two, please.
Sure.
Seems the rails are misaligned.
That's dangerous!
I quite agree.
Weeelcome to Tiiiiramy's floooweerrrr adventuuuure!
What the...
This is the part where Tiramy's supposed to come out
and wave at everyone.
But he's missing again.
Again? Wait a minute,
how many times have you been to this place?
So, how was that?
Oh, god...
Next we have Macaron's music theater.
He's a music fairy.
Macaron's performances feature
sweet melodies and uplifting rhythms.
It's guaranteed to make your heart sing with delight.
We need to have a talk about this.
He only works when he feels like it.
That's an artist for you.
Seriously?!
This is Moffle's sweets house.
Moffle is a sweets fairy as
well as the most popular mascot.
Just one bite of these treats,
and you'll be floating through a world of bliss.
Oh, come on!
Welcome to Moffle's sweets house!
Uh‐oh, the shop is full of mischievous mice!
Use the magic water guns to teach them a lesson!
So it's some kind of shooting game?
All I have to do is shoot the mice with this gun?
Correct.
I'm a pro at these kinds of games.
Get ready to marvel at the work of a true master.
Let the slaughter begin!
Did she say "slaughter"?!
They're fast!
I got one!
We're headed for the pantry.
Don't let your guard down.
This game is freaking impossible!
Just try harder.
Okay, that was... way too hard...
Aww, darn! You didn't kill very many!
Wait! I was killing them?!
But you said I was just teaching them a lesson!
Right, the more mice you kill,
the bigger the reward you can get for their corpses.
Do you even realize how violent you sound right now?
Family‐friendly places like this aren't
supposed to use words like "kill" or "corpses."
But Moffle appreciates all your help!
Be sure to take a photo with
him in the next room before you go!
This is the room where you get
your picture taken with Moffle.
I don't really care to take pictures
with a guy in a rat suit or whatever.
Just say hello. It'll be fun, I promise.
Are you telling me there are people
who find this crazy death game fun?
Of course.
Those are photos of all the guests
who have gotten high scores in the past.
Looks like it appeals to a specific kind of person.
Moff!
Moffle, the sweets fairy.
He's the most popular mascot here.
Huh...
Something wrong?
No...
He just irks me for some reason.
We'd like to take a photo with you, all right?
Moff.
Wait, what's the point if you're not in it?!
Why are you copping an attitude?!
I'm a customer, buddy!
Try to calm down, Kanie.
Right...
Don't worry, I can be calm.
I promise I won't lose my cool.
Whatever, I'm out. I'm not gonna sit here
and take this crap from a knockoff like...
There's nothing Moffle despises
more than being called a knockoff.
So that makes it okay to throw
a camera at a customer's head?!
Why's he standing there like he's ready to punch me out?!
Wahhhhahah!
All right, that's it.
Now I'm angry!
That's better.
That crazy woman just shot me!
She actually shot me!
Am I really gonna die because of
some stupid guy in a mascot suit?!
I lived...
You two were about to engage in a fight to the death.
And I won't allow you to sully the
sweets house of happiness with your blood.
I don't see any happiness in here!
And besides, you've got no right
to talk, little miss sharpshooter!
Right. Well, Kanie,
did you have a good time bonding with
Moffle through friendly competition?
Is that what you're calling it?!
You'll get along, right?
No way!
Took the words right out of my mouth.
Wait a second, he talks too?
Well, that's enough for now.
We got our souvenir photo, so let's get moving.
We got what?
That sucked! He's a total jerk!
You really think so?
Why does this park need an angry
mouse character wearing a goofy hat?
Seriously, the guy inside the suit
must have some kind of attitude problem.
There's nobody inside the suit.
'Scuse me?
It's only Moffle.
There's nobody inside the suit.
Oh, right, I get it now.
You're supposed to tell everybody
it's a real magical mouse
thing instead of a guy in a suit,
so the kids don't stop believing
in Santa Claus or whatever.
Is that what's going on?
No, I'm saying there's no one inside the suit.
Moffle is a real resident of the magical kingdom.
"Magical kingdom"?
All right, you win, if it means that much to you.
This is the elementario theater.
Here, the four elemental spirits perform beautifully
choreographed dance numbers and unbelievable wire stunts.
My name is muse, the water spirit!
We hope you enjoy the elementario spectacular!
You can call me sylphy.
I'm the spirit of wind. You wanna be friends?
I'm the earth spirit known as kobory.
Uhmm... it's lovely to meet you.
What's up? I'm salama.
I'm the fire spirit.
All right, having fun?!
Wow, it sure sounds like you are!
Let's get this show on the road!
This is sad.
That's about how it always is.
Let's continue the tour.
The thrill coaster...
A heart‐pounding adventure aboard
a speeding train of fun and thrills.
Are you scared?
You've gotta be joking.
Good, let's take a ride.
Were you terrified?
Not really.
Oh, well, let's keep moving.
Brilliant market...
Check out Amabri's hottest merchandise.
This place looks really outdated.
Kiddie play...
A spacious play area glowing with the smiles of children.
Obviously.
Free fall...
They slowed it down so it wouldn't
scare the little kids too much.
So it's an elevator.
The coffee cups...
They're famous for their extreme speed.
I think I'm gonna puke...
I hate this!
Seems like you're upset.
Why wouldn't I be?
Every single attraction in
this park is a lame piece of crap!
Nothing works right, the service is terrible...
At least the love hotel looks nice!
And the worst part of it is the people running this
place don't know the first thing about entertainment!
Do they really think kids are
fooled by stupid gags like this?
Kids are a lot harder to trick than you might think!
It's not something you can just pull out of your ass!
You have to work hard and commit to it!
But no, this place doesn't even come close to that!
If they want to make dreams come true,
the people who work here have to
believe in their own dreams first!
I mean...
If you want to make dreams come true,
then the first thing you have to
do is believe in dreams yourself.
You said it harshly, but you're right.
But that doesn't sound like something your
normal everyday high school student would say.
Just forget it. I copied it from a book.
You know, at first,
I assumed that the reason you were
acting so irritated was because...
a strange girl forced you to come to a
theme park and wander around with her all day.
So you do know you're being a
huge inconvenience to me then.
But you're obviously frustrated because
of another issue entirely, aren't you?
It's like you're angry at the park itself.
Seiya Kanie... amagi high school class 2‐4, age 16.
Currently resides with his aunt.
How did you know that?
Attractive, intelligent, superior athletic skills.
True, but what's your point?
A man of many talents can succeed at
almost anything, but notoriously narcissistic.
Loves himself so much it's disgusting.
That's why you don't have friends or a girlfriend.
Hey, wait!
You always eat your lunch by
yourself because no one likes you.
Where did you get all this info about my life?
I've been doing extensive research.
Okay, but why did you do all that research?!
Seiya Kodama...
From what I've heard,
there was a successful child
actor by that name a few years ago.
Any adult would've called him the perfect child.
But for whatever reason, Seiya
Kodama suddenly retired five years ago.
He should be in high school by now, right?
What do you think he would say if he saw this place?
Now I get it... you made me come here,
because you knew about that from the start.
That's correct.
Look, I don't know what it is you're trying to pull here,
but Seiya Kodama's been dead for a long time, all right?
He disappeared.
So if you think you can use him to your advantage somehow,
then you're wasting your time.
That's it. Try to shoot me if
you want, but I'm outta here.
Wait!
You have to eat these before you go.
They'll be cold soon.
I don't care about your croquettes.
Just eat them, please.
The crust isn't very thick, but the crunch is exquisite.
The inside is juicy and warm.
Plus, the minced meat and mashed
potatoes make a perfect combo of flavors!
Do you like them?
Yeah...
Those are exclusive to this park.
You can't get them anywhere else.
Wow, did you make these?
I didn't.
But would you like to meet the one who did?
How are you affiliated with this park?
Did I say I was?
No, I just kinda figured it out.
Where are we going?
To the roof of maple castle.
You said you wanted to meet the park manager.
I did?
Kanie?
Something wrong?
Uh, no, I'm okay.
Good...
Then you should go say hello to her highness.
Huh?
Go on.
Hello, you must be sir Seiya Kanie.
Uh, that's me.
I'm pleased to meet you. My name is latifah Fullanza.
And I happen to be the manager of this park.
Manager?
Yes, I do so appreciate you taking the
time to come and visit our grounds today.
Uh, sure.
So you're the one who made those croquettes?
Oh, yes, I make them every day.
I like to do what I can to help
our guests enjoy themselves here.
Um, don't take this the wrong
way, but what is it you want?
And who exactly are you?
The park is quite expansive.
Have you already seen all of it?
Uh‐huh, more than I wanted to.
What did you think?
Well, where do I start?
Say no more, I'm certain it was far from ideal.
Sir Kanie...
Please grant me this one favor.
Our precious park is in danger of closing down, and
I was hoping that you could be the one to rescue it.
What?
Amagi brilliant park needs your leadership.
Please say you'll be the manager for us!
You mean you want me to be in charge of this place?
Yes...
You have what it takes to save this park from ruin.
That is what the oracle has made clear to us.
"Oracle"?
That's right.
We are residents of maple land, a kingdom of magic.
Are you serious?
Yes. You see, the kingdom where I was
born is different from the world you live in,
because magical happenings tend to be commonplace.
To tell you the truth, most of the cast members
who live and work here at amagi brilliant park
are actually native to that magical land the same as I am.
Huh?
However, if we don't succeed
in welcoming 250,000 visitors,
then the park will close in three months.
If that happens, the people of maple
land will have nowhere left to go,
which means we will cease to exist forever.
Wait a second, you can't just expect me
to believe all this magic stuff is real.
I understand this is difficult.
That's why I...
That's why I'm going to demonstrate a
bit of magic for you right now, all right?
Magic?
Indeed.
Now, Sir Kanie,
I need you to stay still please.
Oh no, Sir Kanie!
Are you hurt?!
Please help me, lady Isuzu!
We must move him inside at once!
Sir Kanie, wake up!
Oh, I'm in my room?
Better wash up.
Hey, aunt Aisu! I know you're in there!
Open up, I need to talk to
you! Aunt Aisu! Come out, hurry!
What in the world do you want at this hour?
Aunt Aisu, why is that girl here?!
Oh, you mean Isuzu?
She brought you home last night after
the last train was gone so I let her stay.
I think she told me you tripped and knocked yourself out.
Can't believe Seiya had a date with a girl.
He's really changed his ways.
Not that long ago, he thought of
every girl he met as his nemesis.
Well, as his guardian, I have to say I'm pleased.
That was really weird.
Huh?
Did you say something just now?
Something about me changing my ways?
What?! Nothing!
Wh‐what are you talking about?!
It looked like you had your mouth
closed, but I know I heard your voice.
Oh, that's right!
I must be really hungover right now!
I should probably go back to sleep for a while.
And you'd better be getting
ready for school, don't you think?
See ya!
Kanie!
It would appear that you've
just awakened to a magic ability.
Huh?!
I assume you believe what I told you now?
Time for the attractions spotlight.
This segment will showcase all the
exciting attractions Amabri has to offer.
You don't sound excited.
Our first feature is Moffle's sweets house.
The difficulty is actually adjustable.
It is?
Easy, normal, hard,
and for the toughest challengers, insane.
Insane is so brutal that some guests lose their senses.
I wouldn't advertise that.
Oh, and Kanie, you played on easy this time.
Easy?!