Come meet the lovable mascot characters
from Maple Land, the kingdom of dreams!
Where fairy tales come to life!
With so many great attractions...
there's always something fun for the whole family!
The memories will last a lifetime.
So plan your visit to Amagi Brilliant Park today!
So what do you think of it?
I wanted this promotional video to be perfect
so I poured my blood sweat and tears into it.
It's okay... Not bad, but not good either.
Actually, the whole thing is pretty bland.
So you don't like it?
No, not at all...
It looks like you created a visual
representation of your boring personality.
I see this happen a lot.
All the fundamentals are there,
but it still puts me to sleep.
To be totally frank, the product is boring
because the person who made it is boring.
You get it?
And he wonders why he has no friends.
Did you say something to me?
Not at all!
Here's the thing, Triken,
I am way too busy to hold your
hand through all of this today.
Sento.
Yes?
You were listening, weren't you?
Tell Triken what he needs to do.
Well alright... but to be fair,
I don't know anything about making videos.
Yeah, but two heads are better than one.
Understood.
It might be smart to ask the
other workers for their input too...
I'll look over the final product
when you're finished it up.
Thank you for your assistance!
Excuse me... It's time to hunch over and work!
PV... "Promotional video" is that right?
Unfortunately, as I told you before...
I don't know the first thing about this.
I don't understand what makes the video so unsatisfactory.
But I do agree with Kanie that something's not right.
Oh, so you think so too.
I believe the logical first step is to follow his
advice and gather input from the rest of the cast.
Input? What do you mean "input"?
Why don't we go see what our star mascots think?
Moff, this is no good at all.
You didn't like it either.
How do I describe it? Too plain?
This happens a lot.
All the fundamentals are there
but it still puts me to sleep.
It's like you've created a visual
representation of your boring personality.
He just said exactly what Mr. Kanie said...
They're BOTH terrible.
Did you say something?
Not at all!
If I had to pick out the biggest
problem, I'd say it needs more action.
Like the fireworks at the
beginning... explosions would be better.
Did... you say explosions?
All you need is a bit of gasoline and then MOFF!
Get a shot of somebody running past a bunch
of explosions and jumping straight off a cliff!
Then at the end you see the park
logo in front of the aftermath!
Are you sure that's wise?
This park's supposed to be family-friendly.
Don't think about too much.
Let's just try it and see what happens!
Moff.
Ron!
Heheh...
Is this any better?
Let's see... I can't say for certain...
but I think so.
Oh...! That's surprising.
For one... it's definitely not boring now.
And the explosion scenes are especially convincing.
You should proceed along these lines.
Yes Miss Isuzu... I'll see what else we can add to it.
Hmm...
This is okay I guess but doesn't tell the audience about
the kind of music I perform at the music theater-ron.
Oh, I see.
If you ask me, the visuals AND the soundtrack
could benefit from a more "aggressive" tone.
What do you mean by "aggressive"?
I'm thinkin' you gotta crank up the libido-mii!
Uh... libido as in sex drive...?
That's right. You know what I'm talking about.
To put it in simple terms I think we need to go lewder.
Lewdness?! Now THAT I understand!
Swimsuits! Short skirts! Low angles!
All you gotta do is squeeze in as much
fanservice as you can legally get away with-mii!
But... we don't exactly have enough
room in the budget to hire any models.
No problem!
Lucky for you I've been building
my sexy secret stash for years!
Secret stash?!
Who needs to hire a model when there's
this many gorgeous babes on the payroll?
It's about a terabyte's worth...
Perfectly organized, tagged, and thumbnailed of course!
I'll just go ahead and give you complete access to
the server so you can do whatever you want with 'em...
and I do mean whatever-mii.
This is wonderful!
The Goddess Libra will surely
bless your generosity, my friend!
Ooh, right there...!
Ahhh that's good...
Ahh hah hah hah...
Yeeeees! Ohhhh!
How do you like that?! I'd say it's a masterpiece!
Since I'm clearly not the target audience...
I shouldn't complain... It's not my place to argue.
Personally... I think it's extremely revolting but...
Oh well... I guess that's just how the world works.
I appreciate your understanding, Miss Isuzu.
You know... a few of these
outfits look strangely familiar...
I get the feeling I've seen them before...
But you hired models for this project right?
Oh yes...! Of course I did!
These thighs, for example. They're bothering me.
You and me both!
Fair enough... We'll keep this part in.
Thank you so much, Miss Isuzu!
Look, I'm hunched...
Anyway... It seems a little unfair to
cater exclusively to the male guests.
What do you propose we do?
Let's get some advice from the girls next.
This looks kinda familiar to me.
No it doesn't.
It's just... explosions and sexy pictures of girls.
Yeah, I'm kinda grossed out now.
Let's see what the internet thinks about this.
Ok... how can I make it better?
Where do I start?
Uh, listen... This is... just a... suggestion...
but right now there's nothing at all in
this video that appeals to a female audience.
So um... We need male nudity as
many hot naked guys as possible!
Girls want to see lots of
guy-on-guy action and tiny speedos...!
Oh and plenty of close-up shots
of their bulging muscles too!
I think that's just what YOU want to see.
Oh no, any suggestions you girls
can give are more than welcome.
After all, that's what I'm here for.
Well, if you're asking what we like,
I wouldn't mind some shots of water.
You just mean normal water scenes, right?
Yes! Looking at the water is so relaxing.
I have lots of footage of rivers and
oceans if you want me to send them to you.
If that's the case, I think I
might have a contribution to make too!
Oh?
I'm pretty sure you'll like it.
Why do you have that? Delete it right now...
They're from that sleepover at your place.
I just sent them to you, Triken.
Hopefully you'll be able to use them for something good.
Yes ma'am...! I assure you they'll be VERY beneficial.
No way! I won't let you have them!
So what do you think of it?
I'm not... sure WHAT to think.
I can't believe these are the models you selected.
Well... actually we were low on funding after
I DEFINITELY hired models for the first one,
so I asked the gentlemen from security to help us out.
You mean Okuro and the others?
Yes, luckily some of the new
part-timers were willing to play along too.
Couldn't you have enlisted someone else?
Surely they're not the most
attractive men you could've asked.
Oh? Is there anyone in particular?
Well...
Nevermind.
You were talking about Mr. Kanie, weren't you?
Shut your mouth.
I nailed it, didn't I?!
Nothing gets past old Triken!
Don't even bother trying...
I said shut it.
Consider it shut then.
Anyway... do we really need footage
of a river flowing or Muse taking a nap?
Surprisingly, Sylphy's contribution is the most relevant.
Oh, you're right, that's kind
of an unexpected twist, isn't it?
I think we need to ask for other people's opinions now.
What about the most important person?
Talk to her next.
The most important person, you say?
Yes...? You really need my help?
Some kind of promotional video? I'm sorry...
but I wouldn't know how to help with something like that.
Anything will be helpful...
Perhaps you could tell me what sort of
things you'd like the video to be about.
Hmm...
Oh I know...!
This is the perfect opportunity...!
Why don't you feature the park
employees who work behind the scenes,
so they can have a chance to shine for a change?
A promo? Well I'll be!
Maybe this is what you're looking for.
I see...
You're making a video?
That's right...! Do you think I
could get a shot of you cooking?
No thanks... too much effort.
Excuse me, Mr. Wrench.
Dammit all, can'tcha see I'm busy?!
Huh? You're filming again?
Yes. But this time I want to focus
on the security force as a whole.
Perhaps I'll get some footage of you working the
gate or training other employees, things of that nature.
Oh really? That sounds good.
I'm sorry, I'm not sure how to make accounting
look interesting on video... So what should I do?
That's alright, Miss Ashe, it doesn't have to be your job;
It could be something you do on your days off.
Yes!
It just needs to represent who you are as a person.
Who I am?
Well then...
I might have something interesting...
from back in my school days.
Ah... and what is that?
Footage of my club activities.
You need help with a promo?
Right, I'm looking for suggestions
from as many park employees as possible.
I'd love to come up with something
unique that makes a big impact.
Wouldn't you know it I have just the thing.
It's something I made with a
group of like-minded individuals.
If you gimme some time... I'll go on a
wild west adventure and film it for ya.
I think this noble endeavor could greatly
benefit from the spirit of the samurai!
Aye lads, an' I'd wager a fine pirate
like meself'd be a perfect addition.
What about a hard-hitting drama about saving the earth?
Hello... Mr. Codain? What do you think?
Do you ever talk at all? Ah! What's that?
Okay, today I'm gonna demonstrate
the proper method for slicing meat...
First you hold the knife just like this and then...
I SAID BEAT IT!
That's awesome!
I feel so inspired now!
Totally worth the trip!
Look this way, guys, you're on video!
Hyahhhh!
In my final hour... my humble
heart is cleansed of all regret.
For I know I sacrifice my life
for the sake of countless others.
I didn't understand that... but I think it works.
What?! THIS is what we want?
I'm curious about Ashe's part...
What on earth was she doing?
It's a competitive sport known as extreme ironing...
Apparently you're supposed to
iron clothes in bizarre places.
Well, I suppose we all have our hobbies, don't we?
I didn't really understand the part
with Dornell visiting the dam either.
I wasn't aware of it before, but it
turns out there's quite a fan base for dams.
Well alright then... Each part of the
video does seem special in its own way,
so it covers a wide range of interests.
Indeed... and I believe we have enough footage
to work with at this point, wouldn't you agree?
Oh I don't think I'd say that yet...
The next step is to hear the opinion of
someone who's closer to a visitor's viewpoint.
And where are we going to get that?
Talk to those three girls we hired recently.
I'd say it needs more blood and guts!
Why blood and guts?!
You know...! Everybody likes to watch
things that creep them out, don't they?
So just throw in a bit of
violence and it'll be a masterpiece.
Trust me on this one... It's
gonna be a big hit with the visitors.
Well... i-if you're sure about it...
I... I think the video looks fonderwul!
N-no wait I mean... W-wonderful!
Is that how you honestly feel?
W-well... maybe... you uh...
Actually nevermind, don't worry about it!
Wow Triken... I think you've
done a beautiful job with this.
You think it's beautiful?
Of course...! Although...
if you wouldn't mind me stating my own personal opinion...
I just can't help but feel that it's lacking a
certain emotional quality in its current state.
Emotional? Do you have an example?
You see... I happen to be quite interested in horses.
They've been a hobby of mine since I was a girl, actually.
Huh.
And not too long ago, I was lucky enough to have
a chance to witness a mother horse giving birth.
It was a horse that's been very special
to me since I was in high school...
Her name's Kikuno Scepter, isn't that sweet?
That's an interesting name...
The delivery was extremely
difficult... but now she's a proud mother!
In all my life... I've never been so moved!
Finished!
It's amazing!
Moff.
Ron!
Heheh...
That's awesome!
I feel so inspired now!
Totally worth the trip!
Look this way guys.
Hyahhh!
First you hold the knife just like this and then...
I SAID BEAT IT!
It's taking too long!
If this keeps up, Kikuno won't make it!
Let's pull it out!
It's a tough angle, but I think we're gonna have to...
Get ready!
Right!
Hang in there, Kikuno!
Kikuno, push!
Come on out, we're almost there!
She's standing up!
What the hell did you do?!
Ah yes, I knew I'd get a big reaction from you, Mr. Kanie.
Sento...! You were supposed
to be supervising this project!
What were you doing?!
I'm so moved!
What?!
It's a touching story...
of dreams coming true...
What's not to like about it?
Everything!
Moff, not enough action.
Yeah and what happened to the dam, man?
Nah, the real problem is the music selection-ron.
I thought you were gonna use our footage.
Where's my collection of sexy pictures-mii?
I don't understand why nobody
bothered asking ME for an idea.
Quit complaining...!
We can't use that one.
Actually Mr. Kanie, I took it upon myself to
upload the other video to the internet as well.
You what?!
And it's going viral.
No way!
Time for the attractions spotlight.
Today's feature is Whip Antique.
Wait, this was the last episode.
And why does it say "no image"?
Don't worry about it.
Whip Antique. Where fantasies come true.
Everybody loves Whip Antique.
Did you need to repeat that?
Come on down to Whip Antique.
Oh I get it. This is some kind of advertisement.
Remember, it's Whip Antique.
I'm not sure what kind of shop
it is, or what they sell though.
Don't you think that's important?!