Darn, that cute office girlisn't here today.
Oh, no, I hope this skirt isn't too short.
Yoritomo, 1185...
No! What happened?
It's 1192! He's got his years mixed up!
Just leave him alone.
Can I assume you believe what I've told you now?
A kiss from a member of the Maple Land royal
family has the ability to grant magic powers.
Did you say "royal family"?
Yes, she's a Princess.
It would appear that you've been given the power
to perceive what the people around you are thinking.
Try it on me.
There was one other person who
possessed this power in the past,
but it could never work more
than once on the same individual.
Wait, you mean if I tried to read your mind again later...
It wouldn't work.
You tricked me into doing it this time, so
that I'll never know what you're thinking.
That might be the reason.
But why would you guys want to
give me some superpower like this?
So you'd be more inclined to take the manager position.
We'll be returning to the park after school.
No way...
Uncle!
I'm sorry I couldn't stop by
and visit you yesterday, Latifah.
Oh, no, that's all right.
Did you get acquainted with that Kanie kid?
Yes, but he fell unconscious
during the magic-granting ritual.
So, I asked lady Isuzu to watch over him after that.
Moff, that means he and Latifah must've...
What?
Don't worry about it.
I just hope he's not inappropriate with Isuzu.
What do you mean by "inappropriate"?
Moff! Uh, well, you'll understand when you're older...
Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot.
I know it might not happen this year,
but I'll keep on wishing for it.
I believe that, with Sir Kanie's help,
things might just turn around for us.
Moff...
Macaron!
Tiramy!
Ron!
Mii!
Aw, isn't that sweet? You've got them all to yourselves.
That was fun!
I wanna stay, mom!
Ron! Ron!
Mii!
I swear I was this close to murderlize those little brats!
Try to relax.
You'll never make it in this business,
if you get upset every time the kids beat you up.
But they kept punching the crap out of me like this!
And then they were hitting me like that!
Hit me again, punk!
First, they came at me like that and that...
It's too moffin' early for this.
Oh, hey, it's Moffle!
Good morning, Mii!
You look even more cranky than usual.
Yeah, it's about the kid.
Oh, you mean the one Isuzu was giving the grand tour?
So, what did you think of him?
He's a narcissist with a bad attitude.
Just thinking about him pisses me off.
Folk, good morning, everybody!
Oh, wow, you look cute as always, Muse!
And Kobory, you're as elegant as usual.
Thank you.
Salama, you're as callous as ever.
And of course Sylphy's not listening at all!
I'm a helicopter!
Are you girls off to Elementario?
Yes, it's time for the first show of the day...
If that little takes over,
we don't stand a chance.
I still have a ton of questions.
I mean, what kind of place is this Maple Land anyway?
It's a magical kingdom resting
on the edge of land and water,
and Latifah happens to be its Princess.
Actually, there was another thing she said
before I passed out that struck me as weird.
I think she was talking about
losing the power to live or something?
That would be Animus.
Animus?
It's the crystallized happiness of
all the guests who visit the park.
Basically, Animus is our life energy.
Amabri is a facility used to gather the Animus we need.
All of the establishments that exist
for that purpose are what we call Argels.
Are you trying to tell me that...
whether or not they decide to close that old
rundown park is a life-or-death situation for you people?
Yes, of course.
Several other theme parks are secretly Argels as well.
You mean Maple Land built all
those other big parks in the area too?
Oh, no, there are multiple magical worlds,
so each one of them establishes an Argel for themselves.
Magical realms are powerless without a supply of Animus.
That's why the parks are so desperate to get guests.
And what happens if the kingdom runs out of Animus?
Then we cease to exist.
How are you doing this morning, Miss Isuzu?
Hello.
Is that guy from the magical land?
No, actually Okuro's an ordinary human being.
There are several other non-magical
residents working at Amabri as well.
What's this?
Staff housing. I also live in there.
But the place I wanted you to visit
today is the administrative building.
Here we are.
Moff...
Are you going to fight?
No getting around it.
Moff moff moff moff!
Bring it on!
Are you two done bonding now?
You really think this is bonding?!
We should go.
We'll be late if we don't hurry up.
Great, now what are you gonna put me through?
I want to introduce you to the enemy.
Huh?
My name is Takaya Kurisu.
I'm here from Amagi development.
Uh, thank you.
I don't think we've met before.
That's Seiya Kanie; He's an intern.
Shouldn't the manager be here as well?
She wasn't feeling very well today.
Since I'm the acting manager, I'll
be the one to consider your proposal.
I see; That's all right then.
I'm sure you already know this,
but your contract stipulates that the annual visitor count
must be calculated beginning on August 1st of every year,
and that if you fall short of half a
million guests for five years in a row,
Amagi development receives full control of the park.
Yes.
The park has fallen below 500,000
attendees for four consecutive years now.
You're at 250,000 for the year.
And it's already May.
I'm afraid you have less than three months remaining.
And you see, from where I'm standing,
you haven't even begun preparations to shut down.
That's correct. Because we can't be certain that...
the visitor count won't surpass
500,000 before the deadline is up.
Tell me you're not serious.
Summer break is just around
the corner. I'm sure we'll get...
Summer break starts in late July.
Two weeks won't be enough to save your park.
You're generating a considerable deficit.
If I were you, I'd start getting my assets in order.
Allow me to give you a little example here.
Let's say a family of four takes
a vacation to Amagi Brilliant Park.
Would you make a profit based on last year's attendance?
Well, it depends on how much the
family needs to spend every day,
which is...
85,000 yen.
That's almost on the nose.
It's actually 83,200.
That was quite impressive.
How would you like to come work with us?
Nah, don't think I'm interested.
Well that's a shame.
In any case, those are the numbers we're looking at here.
You just can't keep up this
indulgence of yours for much longer.
But, sir, if you give us a chance, then maybe we could...
A chance, huh?
Face it, the only thing you can do now is pray that...
another quarter million people are stupid
enough to waste their time at this dump.
No offense.
You didn't tell me you were the acting manager.
Princess Latifah needed me to do
it for a year to take her place.
Did you come up with the 85,000 yen because
you were reading Mr. Kurisu's mind earlier?
No, all I did was make a rough estimate based on
the size of the park and yesterday's visitor count.
It's a little math trick called a Fermi estimate.
I don't understand.
Look it up sometime.
More importantly, why did you bring
me here to meet with those people?
If you're going to be the manager of Amabri,
you'll need to know who we're up against.
Would you just drop it?
You take away my free time
after school and on the weekends,
you repeatedly threaten me
with that ridiculous gun of yours,
and yet you still expect me to
help you save this stupid theme park?
Who in their right mind would say yes after all that?
I'm sorry, I'm not quite accustomed to this world yet.
I don't know the appropriate
way to ask for someone's help.
So you shoot them?
Yes.
Steinberger is a magical weapon
compatible with several types of bullets.
Put that away!
The bullet I shot you with
before was called a Pain Bringer.
That variety is enough to cause double the
amount of pain of stubbing your pinky toe.
Put it down!
Plus I don't see why you would ask me instead of
somebody with professional management experience.
We tried that, but then they all quit on us.
Why?
Perhaps they didn't like being shot at.
Really?!
I feel like this is all my fault.
That's why I came to your school.
I was so desperate, I needed you to
agree to help no matter what the cost!
I've had enough.
You're leaving?!
Yep.
But you can't! You're the only chance we've got, Kanie!
Please save our park!
I can't help you.
But what about the Princess?!
Hey, there.
Hey.
What now?
You're Seiya Kodama, the child actor!
You're mistaken.
No, no, I'm sure.
But why's a big celebrity like you
working part-time in a rundown amusement park?
I said-
It's none of your business.
Well, I'm sure you've got your reasons,
but here's some advice:
Don't be stupid, all right?
If you spend your time around losers,
you'll end up a loser yourself.
Take care.
I guess the corners are round so kids don't get hurt.
How can they have time for little details
like that when the place is such a wreck?
Jeez, get your priorities in order.
Either way, I should get them to do
something about these crazy psychic powers.
I hope they're not gonna give us some kind of bad news.
I'm surprised you haven't
already heard something, Mr. Moffle.
What's your take on it, Mr. Cast-Leader?
Moff, I bet it's exactly what you think it is.
Everyone, your attention please!
The first Princess of Maple Land,
her royal highness Latifah Fullanza,
would like to address her subjects!
This is an important message!
All right, let's get this over with.
I had a feeling this was coming.
These people sure do give up easily.
Can't really blame 'em.
Good evening, my friends. It is with a heavy heart
that I must impart some very upsetting news today.
In three months' time, our Amagi
Brilliant Park will be permanently shut down.
I know it hurts to say goodbye,
but I promise I'll do everything I can
to find new jobs for every one of you.
And even though the road ahead is
certain to introduce some challenges...
Challenges, really?!
But, your majesty, hardly anybody
out there even knows who I am!
It's too late for me to build up a fan base now!
What am I gonna do?!
Well I...
I'm not quite sure, but if you try hard then...
What's the use of trying?!
I'll just wind up passing out tissues
in front of some train station anyway!
And then before you know it,
Everybody'll forget about me forever!
Without fans, I'll just disappear!
How could you let us down like this, Princess?!
Put a sock in it, Wanipee.
But I'm sad!
How many years have you worked at Amabri?
About 12.
Then you've had more than enough chances.
It's your own fault you relied too much on the park
and didn't establish your own fan base.
So why are you making a scene?
Because... becaaaaause!
Don't worry, Wanipee.
I'll be right there passing out tissues with you, okay?
If you work hard, you still have a chance of being
successful as a local mascot or something like that.
Easy for you to say.
Moff?
Come on, Moffle, we both know you could
easily move on to some other theme park.
Why would I do a fool thing like that?
You're practically identical
to Macky at Urayasu Digimarland!
Did you really think nobody noticed?!
Moff...
He's a mouse too, I'm sure you could get a good gig as...
I'm nobody's sidekick! Got it?!
I've built my career on originality!
I'm not a knockoff or a sidekick, buster!
That hurts! Let me go!
Both of you, cut it out!
We're in front of the Princess, Ron!
She's suffering more than anybody right now.
Can't you two see that?
Sorry I got upset.
No...
This is all my fault.
I've failed.
I'm so sorry!
If only I'd been able to save this place...
I know it's not enough, but...
I truly do apologize.
And I hope...
I hope you'll all forgive me...
If you can.
Don't you think it's a little early for you to apologize?
You really are a hopeless bunch.
If you're gonna feel sorry for yourselves,
at least wait until you've actually lost.
Is he the one the prophesy told us about?
Huh?
What are you doing back here, punk?
If I remember correctly,
you clowns forced me to come here against my will.
They told me you turned down the manager position.
Just get lost already!
I don't think so. I'm actually in the mood to
help you losers with your little problem now.
We can handle it just fine on our own!
We don't need help from the likes of you!
Heh! Yeah, you look like you're handling it.
Moffu?
Come on!
Every one of you is useless!
You can't attract business or make money,
and now you're all about to lose your jobs!
Oh, and guess what that guy from
Amagi development said to me earlier.
That you'd have to be a moron to
spend your money at this trash heap!
He's right!
The poor, misguided saps who do come
are wasting their hard-earned cash...
on a pitiful excuse for an amusement park
that's not even bad enough to be so-bad-it's-good!
Seriously, even I don't know what to say to that!
And what have you idiots been doing in the meantime?
Nothing! You're just whining and complaining!
It's true! I'd feel pretty stupid if I
gave my money to a pathetic lot like you!
All right, now I'm really getting mad!
Please stand down.
I do apologize, Sir Kanie.
Would you please come and join us on the balcony?
Heh...
I should introduce myself.
Name's Seiya Kanie.
And I don't even have to read your
minds to know what you're all thinking.
Let me see here, uh...
Aha! That's right, you hate my guts already, don't you?
"Where'd this jerk come from?"
"How can we entrust him with our precious park?"
"What could he possibly do in three months?"
And that's not all!
"Princess Latifah with a jackass like him?"
"I can't bear to think about it!"
Have I pissed you off enough? Good!
From now on, it's not in your hands anymore.
I'm your new dictator!
If you don't like that, I'll fire you right now!
You will do exactly as I tell you to do!
This lousy park is gonna close down either way,
so I might as well do what I want!
That said, I guarantee you'll be amazed in the end.
In these three months, this random kid you hate
is gonna pull off a miracle like you've never seen!
I'll get you those 250,000 customers.
And that prophesy or whatever?
I will make it come true!
A stunt?
Yeah, I made them angry on purpose.
Why would you do that?
Well, when I told them your customers were all morons,
that made the cast get really mad.
The fact that they were that offended
by me talking smack about the customers...
means they're serious.
So, there's still hope.
Oh, I never thought of that.
You mean, you've decided to help us out after all?
Yeah.
Three months, no more, no less.
After that, I'm washing my hands of all of this.
Right. You have my deepest gratitude.
Don't go thanking me just yet.
Well, I'm gonna give it my best shot, but...
Just don't get your hopes up.
It's virtually impossible.
But what about your big speech earlier?!
I said what I had to.
If we want to succeed here, we
need them to have a little hope left.
Well, in that case, I won't give up either.
Because your prophesy tells
you I'm gonna make this happen?
No.
The oracle does give us a little guidance for our lives,
but I have no idea what the future truly holds for us.
Then what's your reason?
Because you agreed to help us save the park, Sir Kanie.
I know things are going to change.
And I believe that Amabri has a
chance to make a brighter future.
These are the documents you asked for.
Thanks.
Is there anything else?
No.
Did you let your family know
you wouldn't be going home tonight?
Yeah.
I'll leave a blanket for you so you can get some sleep.
'Kay.
And Kanie?
Thanks for this.
Sure.
Hey! Good to see you again, Mr. Moffle!
Chilled tomatoes and a beer.
'Kay!
Yo buddy, Ron! Started without ya.
Mii, what took ya?
Moff!
Sorry to keep you waiting, sir. I brought you a beer!
Moff.
Hey, baby, Ron, could you bring
us two more of those, please?
Uh-huh.
And hurry back with that sweet ass, Mii!
Oh, you!
You really ought to watch your language
when you go out in public, Tiramy.
You never know who might be listening to what you say.
Relax, that's what these Rarapazzi charms are for.
As long as we're wearing these babies,
Nobody'll find out we're fairies!
Those only change your appearance, you knucklehead.
We'd be in hot water if word got out that an Amabri mascot
was drinking beer and checking out women's butts!
Mii! Stop tellin' me how to live my life!
What's the fun of goin' out drinkin'
if you can't check out the tits and ass?!
You better zip that dirty mouth!
Stop acting so stupid!
We're sorry.
And cheers!
What's gotcha down today, Moff-man?
Is it that Kanie kid again?
Moff!
Well, we might as well stick it out till the end, right?
I'm kinda curious to see what his game plan is, honestly.
What the hell does that rat bastard think he's doing?!
Time for the attractions spotlight.
Today's feature is Macaron's music theatre.
I haven't been in there yet. What's it like?
A sanctuary of sound filled to the
brim with the most prestigious of legends.
Wow, that sounds pretty
sophisticated. What kind of legends?
Like when Macaron got into a fist-fight with some
rude audience members and the whole stage collapsed.
That's prestigious?!