Moff! Moff!
Ro‐Ron! Ro‐Ron!
Mii!
I'll be takin' this pool fer me own!
Somebody rescue me!
Oh no! The pirates are taking that mermaid hostage!
What should we do?
I'm scared!
Quiet, ye barnacles...!
Cross me and ye'll all be sleepin' with the fishes!
Not so fast, pirate!
What the blazes...?
Curse ye, scurvy sea‐worm!
Genjuro the dolphin's here to save the day!
Let's give him a hand!
Come get your Popsicle!
Wow! They look super real!
Ew, get it away!
I far exceed human intelligence.
How dare you raise your blade to me?
Impudent fools!
Omigod I love this!
Me too! How do they do this stuff?
Welcome...
...to Amagi Brilliant Park!
The Starlight World show starts...
...now!
Ron! Moff! Miiii!!!
Evening hours are working out okay.
Yes... We haven't had any issues so far.
I think it's a good move.
So how are the renewals coming along?
Let me give you a quick update.
Whoa!
We added more audience interaction.
I don't think so!
Heavy metal music is much more participatory.
Why are they all in sync?!
Sweet, guns!
Let's slaughter 'em!
Moff!
Mission completed.
This one was highly requested by visitors.
Which visitors?!
A girl!
Yeah!
Kidnap her!
Heheh!
How could every single one of these be so terrible?
They ARE performing well with the guests.
Summer break is coming up soon,
so attendance should keep improving.
I guess so.
There you are, Mr. Kanie!
I couldn't find you!
Sorry, Triken.
The TV station is here to film.
Okay... Be right there.
Oh and... that thing you mentioned...
Right! Did you find something?
Well, it doesn't look very promising, sir.
I see.
Anyway... keep working hard.
Absolutely!
What a great crowd... especially for a weekday!
Amagi Brilliant Park is enjoying a surge in popularity,
so let's see what the hype's all about!
This little guy's not only cute,
but he's a super great juggler too!
Wow...! Hey, I think I see...
That reporter there certainly has some impressive assets.
That's it. I'm gonna find
somebody else to show her around.
That's not fair!
More importantly, there's a magazine
coming to do a special on us tomorrow.
You've got the schedule, right?
Right! And I've seen tomorrow's representative...
Her assets are even better so...
I'll be hunched over with...
Great. Then I'll find somebody else to speak with her.
I take it back!
Ahhh!
Moff!
Hey Takami, we're ready to order now.
Coming!
Hey sexy!
What'll it be?
More beers, edamame, and miso cucumbers, right?
Yes please.
And some octopus‐ron.
Right!
I'll take the Takami special!
No sir.
Takami soup and salad?
Takami sandwi...
Great... What else?
Cold tofu‐ron.
And maybe some omelet rolls too.
You got it!
That'll be all.
Thanks.
I tell ya, the drinks taste even
better now that business is so good!
We're getting more and more visitors every day!
Right‐mii...! If this keeps up we
might not be totally doomed after all!
Yeah!
Lord Moffle?
Man, I better stop drinkin' so much, I'm gettin' fat!
He's right. The guest count IS going up, but...
I know.
At this rate, there's a chance that...
Ahhh!
Now THAT'S how you knock back
a cold one, Mac, you're a champ!
Sorry we're late!
Hey you guys.
Lay back!
Heyyy...
I got a seat for ya...
Just sit anywhere.
Thanks.
Takami, we got some more for ya!
'Kay!
They're perfect.
They're orange croquettes.
I added a little touch of marmalade.
The tea croquettes are almost
done, so please try those too.
Of course.
You know, recently... whenever I open a window I can
hear guests and workers laughing all the way in here.
That's lovely.
How has Sir Kanie been lately? He must be terribly busy.
Yes...
He's been working hard.
I understand.
Oh, Lady Isuzu...?
Would you take a few of these
croquettes to Sir Kanie for me?
I'd like him to sample them as well.
Right.
Great. They're almost finished now...
You'll enjoy these...
I made them with Earl... Grey...
Your Majesty!
I'm alright...
I'm just feeling a little... dizzy...
nothing more... please don't worry.
Princess?! Princess!
How is she?
She's getting some rest for now.
That's good.
So what's wrong...?
Does she have some kind of illness?
Does she...? Tell me the truth.
No... Don't worry about it.
She'll be fine when she's rested up.
Hey...! Moffle!
You know what's going on here, don't you?
Say something!
Maple Land's residents can't live without Animus...
...the feelings of fun and happiness
experienced by the people of this world.
You already told me all that.
A long time ago...
Maple Land fell under attack... by a fearsome dragon.
A dragon...?
As in a dragon like Rubrum?
It was a lot bigger than Rubrum.
Oh...
The army did everything they could, but
they were unable to defeat such an imposing foe.
That was when the King was visited by a sorcerer.
He promised the King that he would slay the
dragon in exchange for the princess' hand in marriage.
The king agreed.
And so the sorcerer made quick work of the dragon.
I'm guessing they didn't live happily ever after.
The King didn't want to surrender his daughter's hand...
so he sent the army to attack the sorcerer.
Wounded and filled with rage, the
sorcerer placed a curse upon the princess...
that slowly drained her Animus
supply just before he fell off a cliff.
So she's... really cursed?
There was only one way to save
the princess from certain death.
She was sent to this world to recuperate because there's
an abundant amount of Animus here to keep her healthy.
And that's what the park is for.
Correct.
Which means... if AmaBri has to shut down...!
She won't make it.
How do you feel?
Sorry to make you worry.
I'll be alright if I rest a little.
Good to hear.
I understand you heard about my condition from Lady Isuzu.
Is that true?
Yeah.
I told everyone not to tell you...
I was afraid that you would be
worried about me if you knew it.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry I kept it a secret, Sir Kanie.
It's fine.
How are things in the park these days?
Everyone's working hard out there.
But uh...
Hm?
If something doesn't change... getting enough
visitors to stay open is probably... not possible.
I see.
What's with you?
Hm?
How can you possibly be calm at a time like this?!
If AmaBri closes down, you're gonna...
You have a point...
I know I probably won't be alive much longer.
So why...?!
But I refuse to give up hope...
not yet.
I told you it doesn't look good.
What's the point of waiting for a
miracle that probably won't happen?
But a miracle already did happen.
Just take a look at everyone in the park...
Everything started changing when you came into our lives,
Really?
Yes!
You've filled our beloved park
with the smiles and laughter of...
... so many happy visitors since you came to work here.
I don't know if I would consider that a miracle.
Sir Kanie...
I realize it may not seem like
anything special in your eyes but...
...to me, what you've done for us...
it means the whole world!
Yeah but... you're still in serious trouble and...
Sir Kanie?
Is everything alright?
Latifah.
Are you really okay with this?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Certainly.
Okay then.
These ideas all suck!
B‐but the visitor count's been getting
better since we started working at night.
So if we stretch it to 24 hours then...
Yeah maybe in the long term...
But that won't make enough of a
difference before the deadline!
Unless you can give me a clear guarantee!
W‐well uh...
And promoting outside the park?
It's good publicity.
Advertising takes way too long
to bring in actual results...!
We don't have time for stuff like that!
For right now, we have to do whatever
it takes to get that visitor count up!
And you guys!
The 0 yen campaign!
That's no different from the
30 yen push we're doing NOW...!
It won't give us enough of a boost!
You're right; I'm sorry that's a dumb idea...
It's almost July 31st...
What this park needs right now is a solid
idea that'll guarantee 134,000 guests before then.
Come up with something better!
He was outta line!
It wasn't nice of him to yell
at us when we're trying to help!
Yeah that was #rude.
Calm down, you guys...
I don't know. Maybe something's been bothering him.
He's just aggro over the deadline.
The classic boy‐in‐a desperate‐situation scenario!
Oooooh... Aaaahhhh...
We should pair him with a guy who's more experienced!
It's not a boy-love manga...
Let's get going.
You're making a lot of enemies lately.
I know!
But if I don't pull out all the stops, we're
not gonna sell enough tickets before the deadline.
Gettin' all moffin' mad won't help.
Everybody's trying their hardest.
I don't need you to tell me that.
But if we don't have something to show
for it, they might as well be doing nothing!
What happened to what you said before?
"Whatever it takes to get even one more guest"?
You're right...
That kinda crap is why we're about to fail here!
Moff!
Lord Moffle!
Even if AmaBri closes down, the
cast members can find another job.
But Latifah's not so lucky.
You told him, didn't you?
Yes.
I'm exhausted.
Working too hard, huh?
Something like that.
Ahhh...
Hey Aunt Aisu?
Yeah?
Being a magazine editor...
is it hard?
Not really.
Except when the manuscripts are
late and the printers get pissed.
And sometimes authors straight‐up run from us.
So uh...
whenever something goes wrong at work...
is there anything you can do about it?
Grab a beer and forget it!
What?!
Now, have a safe summer break and set the best example
you can for your fellow students, okay? You're excused.
Don't forget your books!
You're 10 years too young to
be lookin' this depressed, Kid.
What's this about?
Don't worry about it.
That'll cost ya.
You expect me to pay?!
Just moffin' ya.
I really can't stand you. You know that?
Right back atcha.
I don't get it.
What do you mean?
Why are you so desperate to fix this?
I met Latifah a long time ago.
Moff?
When I was a kid.
I wandered into the garden by mistake...
She was sitting there crying.
When I asked her what was wrong, she told
me some story about a sorcerer's curse...
and how she was really lonely.
She told you?
Yeah.
I wanted her to stop crying so I showed her
my impression of the legendary Prince Shotoku...
What?! I wanna see!
Not now.
What's your problem?
As I was saying, I was so desperate
to put a smile on her face that day.
But I failed.
You failed?
Well, she did smile when she saw my impression...
...but it was a sad smile.
Like she was just trying to make me feel better.
That's the kind of person she is.
When I saw that...
I promised Latifah that I would find a way to save her.
Come to think of it...
I was noticing that she looks exactly the same as
she did when I first met her all those years ago.
Do the people of Maple Land just not age or something?
Latifah's a special case.
That curse does more than make her weak.
Every year, it erases a whole year's
worth of memories and physical growth,
which makes her eternally young.
Wha...?
For more than a decade now, she's
been living as a 14‐year‐old girl.
So that's why her looks haven't changed since we met.
That's right.
August 1st is the anniversary of Latifah's curse.
And when that day gets here, she'll forget you too.
Who cares... if she forgets me?
Moff?
This is my problem to solve.
After I was lucky enough to be given
another chance to make Latifah smile.
I can't fail her again.
Wait and see... I can do this!
Moff...
Why do YOU care so much about Latifah?
Because Latifah's my niece, of course.
Like, by blood?!
Yeah. What about it?
Never mind.
Not long ago...
the plan was to take her with me when the
park closed down and become a street performer.
I figured a simple life like that wouldn't be so bad.
Even if it couldn't last for long.
I'd accepted it.
But when you showed up, you changed my mind.
Even if we go down...
I want to fight to the moffin' end.
What are you gonna do?
Right!
I found one...!
I did it, Mr. Kanie!
We just might reach our goal after all!
Time for the attractions spotlight.
Today we have Rubrum's Chamber of Trials.
We've been to this one before.
I'm glad to see it's getting more popular these days.
The traps we fell into the first time are still intact.
Rubrum's excited to have more work to do as well.
Are the prison cells still there?
Yes. I hear the hospitality's so good that some
visitors refuse to leave at the end of the day.
It's not a hotel!