Senketsu: HI, EVERYONE,
AND THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
"KILL la KILL" UP TO THIS POINT.
MY NAME IS KAMUI SENKETSU,
AND I LOVE IRON‐‐
ERR, BEING IRONED.
AND I’M A SENTIENT
SAILOR UNIFORM.
WELCOME TO THE RECAP EPISODE
YOU ALL KNEW WAS GOING TO HAPPEN
EVENTUALLY.
READY? LET’S BEGIN.
RYUKO MATOI IS SEARCHING FOR
HER FATHER’S KILLER ‐‐
SOMEONE WITH
A HALF‐PAIR OF SCISSORS.
SHE ARRIVES AT HONNOUJI ACADEMY
AND MEETS SATSUKI KIRYUIN,
THE STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT.
SATSUKI PLANS TO CONQUER
ALL THE SCHOOLS IN JAPAN
USING GOKU UNIFORMS ‐‐ CLOTHING
THAT CONTAINS LIFE FIBERS
AND THAT CAN UNLEASH THE
HUMAN BODY’S SPECIAL ABILITIES.
BUT WHEN RYUKO MET ME,
KAMUI SENKETSU,
SHE GAINED THE POWER TO
FIGHT SATSUKI AND HER
VILE CLUBS, LIKE...
BOXING, TENNIS,
DISCIPLINARY TRAP DEVELOPMENT,
GARDENING, RAKUGO, 100 POETS,
KNIFE THROWING, NANJING LILY,
ET CETERA, ET CETERA!
THEN THERE WAS
AN ELECTION/BATTLE ROYAL,
WHERE ALL THE CLUBS
HAD TO FIGHT EACH OTHER.
AND AT THE END OF THAT,
RYUKO HAD TO BATTLE
AGAINST THE ELITE FOUR.
SHE DEFEATS IRA GAMAGOORI,
HOUKA INUMUTA,
AND NONON JAKUZURE.
THEN, ALL OF A SUDDEN, A
GIRL NAMED NUI HARIME APPEARED.
SHE WAS THE PERSON
WITH THE SCISSOR BLADE
WHO KILLED RYUKO’S FATHER,
ISSHIN MATOI.
AND THEN RYUKO
TURNS INTO A MONSTER.
THEN WE FINALLY GET TO MEET
SATSUKI’S MOTHER, RAGYO KIRYUIN,
THE C. E. O.
OF THE KIRYUIN CONGLOMERATE.
AND THEN SATSUKI
DECIDES IT’S TIME
TO COMPLETE HER CONQUEST
OF JAPAN’S SCHOOLS
AND PUTS HER KANSAI SCHOOL
RAID‐TRIP INTO ACTION.
BUT THE SCHOOLS WEREN’T THE ONLY
TARGET. OH, NO!
SHE WAS REALLY GOING AFTER
NUDIST BEACH,
A REBEL ORGANIZATION
THAT OPPOSES THE KIRYUIN CLAN.
I WAS CHOPPED TO PIECES,
SO RYUKO GETS A MOTORCYCLE
AND HEADS TO KANSAI TO SAVE ME.
THEN SHE GETS INTO
AN EPIC BATTLE WITH SATSUKI,
SMACK‐DAB
IN THE MIDDLE OF OSAKA!
WHICH BRINGS US TO THIS EPISODE,
WHERE THE MYSTERY OF THE
LIFE FIBERS WILL BE REVEALED.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I’M SURE YOU GROANED WHEN YOU
HEARD ME SAY "RECAP EPISODE,"
BUT HAVE FAITH!
THANKS TO "KILL la KILL’S"
LIGHTING PACE,
OUR RECAP FIT IN THE PROLOGUE.
NOW LET THE EPISODE PROPER
BEGIN!
THE TIDE IN THIS WAR
IS ABOUT TO TURN!
AND AS CLUELESS AS YOU ARE,
YOU CAN NEVER HOPE TO WIN!
OH, YOU THINK I LIKE
NOT KNOWING WHAT’S GOING ON?!
IF YOU BASTARDS
HAD ANY BALLS,
YOU’D STRAIGHT‐UP TELL ME
WHAT I WANT TO KNOW!
YOU
CATERPILLAR‐EYEBROWED BITCH!
[ HELICOPTER ROTORS WHIRRING ]
[ GROANS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Soroi: MISS!
DO IT.
RIGHT!
HURRY
AND UNDRESS.
THE TRANQUILIZING COAGULANT
WON’T LAST LONG.
THANK YOU.
[ GROANS ]
[ EXHALES SHAKILY ]
[ CLATTER ]
YOU’RE MORE EXHAUSTED NOW
THAN LAST TIME.
LIFE‐FIBER OVERRIDE
IS UNSAFE, MISS.
ESPECIALLY
FOR LONG PERIODS.
I’M WELL AWARE
OF THE RISK I TAKE.
ALTHOUGH, GIVEN THAT
MATOI WEARS A KAMUI,
I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT
TO WEAR JUNKETSU TO FIGHT HER.
YES, MISS, AS YOU SAY.
AS YOU SAY.
Iori: IS THAT WISE,
UNCLE SOROI?
BY NOW, SHIRO,
EVERYONE IN OUR FAMILY
SHOULD UNDERSTAND ONE THING
ABOUT THE MISS ‐‐
ONCE SHE
HAS MADE UP HER MIND,
THERE IS NOTHING IN HEAVEN OR
ON EARTH THAT CAN DISSUADE HER.
ALL WE CAN DO
IS SUPPORT HER IN HER DECISION.
SOROI, IORI,
I KNOW I AM ASKING MUCH OF YOU.
BUT PLEASE INDULGE ME
FOR JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
NUI: My, my, my!
I had no idea you’d been
pushing yourself this hard,
Lady Satsuki!
WHO IS THAT?!
I KNOW.
SATSUKI: Harime!
YEP.
IN THE FLESH.
IORI: When did the high‐order
tailor come aboard?
OH, I GO
WHEREVER I WANT.
NO ONE CAN STOP ME,
YOU SILLY.
What do you want?
[ Mockingly ]
"WHAT DO YOU WANT."
[ Normal voice ] I DON’T WANT
ANYTHING, BUT YOUR MOM DOES.
SHE WANTS TO KNOW
ABOUT THE RAID TRIP.
YOU KNOW, HOW IT WENT
AND ALL THAT.
I HAD SOME FREE TIME,
’CAUSE SOMEONE BANNED ME
FROM HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
SO I FIGURED I’D HOP ON OVER
AND GIVE YOU A LIFT.
[ SCOFFS ] YOU CAME
BECAUSE YOU WANTED TO SEE
SENKETSU
AND JUNKETSU FIGHT.
Can’t fool you,
can I?
YOU’RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO REALLY UNDERSTANDS ME.
THAT’S MY LADY SATSUKI.
THIS, COMING FROM SOMEONE
WHO DEFIES UNDERSTANDING.
WELL, WE’RE OFF
TO THE MANSION.
WHEEEEE!
IORI,
CONTACT THE ELITE FOUR.
TELL THEM
I WILL BE DELAYED.
ALSO, THEY’RE ON ALERT UNTIL
THEY GET BACK TO THE ACADEMY.
UNTIL THEY’RE BACK,
THE RAID TRIP IS ACTIVE.
M’LADY.
Soroi:
BEG PARDON, MISS.
IT APPEARS YOU HAVE TIME
FOR ANOTHER CUP OF TEA.
THANK YOU.
Mikisugi: [ SIGHS ]
WHAT A MESS.
AT LEAST
WE’RE NOT DEAD.
AND WE SURE AS HELL
AIN’T QUITTING.
DAMN RIGHT.
[ GASPS ]
WAY TO GO, RYUKO.
YOU FOUGHT KIRYUIN TO A DRAW.
NICE JOB.
COME WITH ME.
WHOA. HANG ON.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
YOU HEARD KIRYUIN ‐‐
SHE’S TAKING THINGS
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
SO THERE’S NO POINT
KEEPING SECRETS ANY MORE.
IT’S TIME
I TOLD YOU EVERYTHING.
[ GASPS ]
AAAAAH!
OH. MY. GOD!
IT’S ‐‐
MR. MIKISUGI?!
IS THAT YOU?
OH, RIGHT. YOU HAVEN’T
SEEN ME SANS DISGUISE.
MR. MIKISUGI,
ARE YOU AN EXHIBITIONIST?
[ CHUCKLES ]
ACTUALLY, I’M IN NUDIST‐‐
YOU GUYS ARE
INTO THE SAME THING.
WE ARE SO NOT!
MAKO, YOU CAN’T
COME ALONG ON THIS.
HUH?
BETTER LISTEN TO HER.
IF YOU COME WITH US,
YOU’LL BE THROWING YOURSELF
SMACK‐DAB INTO A WORLD OF HURT.
DO YOU THINK
YOU HAVE THE GUTS FOR IT?
OH, HECK NO.
KNEW IT.
GO HOME. IT’S COOL.
I’M NOT READY TO GO
INTO BATTLE BUCK‐NAKED YET.
WAIT. WHAT?!
IT’S TRUE.
BUT I AM HER FRIEND.
AND THAT MEANS
THAT NO MATTER WHAT,
I’M GONNA GO
WHEREVER SHE GOES!
I’M COMING WITH,
AND YOU CAN’T STOP ME!
MAKO. [ CHUCKLES ]
ALL RIGHT.
YOU’RE COMING ALONG.
COOL.
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
BUT ‐‐
MAKO?
WAIT. WE’RE SWIMMING?
OF COURSE.
THIS IS THE WAY TO THE ANSWERS
YOU’VE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
LET’S GO SKINNY DIPPING!
HUH?
HEY! WAIT UP!
Hououmaru:
PLEASE GIVE JUNKETSU TO ME.
I’LL KEEP IT SAFE
DURING YOUR VISIT.
MADAME PRESIDENT
WOULD LIKE A WORD WITH YOU.
PLEASE WAIT FOR HER
IN THE GRAND BATH.
[ GROANING ]
♪
Ragyo: YOU WEAR IT WELL.
BUT YOU’RE OVEREXERTING
YOURSELF.
MOTHER...
THE WATER IS MEDICATED TO BOOST
LIFE‐FIBER HARMONIZATION.
SOAK YOURSELF IN IT.
I WILL.
[ GASPS ]
LOVELY SKIN.
NOW SIT BACK AND RELAX.
AND I’LL PURIFY YOU.
[ GASPS ]
♪
HUMANS ARE SUCH
FRAGILE THINGS, AREN’T THEY?
[ GASPS ]
AND WHEN THEY’RE
NAKED LIKE THIS,
IT MAKES THEM
SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
[ SIGHING ]
THEY’RE OVERCOME
WITH THE URGE
TO COVER THEMSELVES WITH
THE MIRACLE OF CLOTHING.
THAT IS INSTINCT,
MY DEAR.
BUT IF A SPECIES
SHOULD DEFY ITS INSTINCT,
IT WILL EVENTUALLY...
[ GASPS]
...MEET WITH EXTINCTION.
[ WATER DRIPS ]
COME OUT.
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU.
[ GASPS ]
YOU MEAN ‐‐
YES.
YOU’VE SERVED ME WELL,
SATSUKI ‐‐
AS A MEMBER
OF THE KIRYUIN CLAN
AND AS MY SUCCESSOR.
IT’S TIME I SHOWED YOU
THE SOURCE OF IT ALL.
[ ALL GASP ]
Ryuko: WHOA.
OSAKA’S GOT A CAVE UNDER IT?
[ WARBLE! ]
IT’S BUSTED UP
PRETTY BAD, HUH?
YEAH,
THANKS TO JAKUZURE.
OH, WELL.
THERE’S MUCH MORE TO THE PLACE
THAN THIS.
WHOA!
Man: OFFICER ON DECK.
TEN‐HUT!
LOOKS LIKE YOU GUYS
MADE IT OKAY.
THANKS TO YOU, WE EVACUATED
IN THE NICK OF TIME, SIR.
SOMETIMES,
BEING A WORRYWART PAYS OFF.
[ RYUKO CLEARS THROAT ]
HMM?
W‐WHERE’D YOU NUDIE BEACHERS
GET ALL THE MONEY
TO SET YOURSELVES UP
WITH ALL THIS?
Mikisugi:
IT ALL COMES FROM YOUR FATHER.
HOW?
WELL, HE WAS
A BRILLIANT SCIENTIST.
AND HE HAD
A WHOLE BUNCH OF PATENTS.
HE MADE A LOT OF MONEY
LICENSING TO COMPANIES
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
HIS MONEY
MADE OUR ORGANIZATION POSSIBLE.
THEN ‐‐
YES! NUDIST BEACH
WAS CREATED BY YOUR DAD ‐‐
DR. ISSHIN MATOI!
WHAAAAAT?!
WOW, FOR AN OLD DUDE,
YOU’RE, LIKE, SO RIPPED.
[ CHUCKLES ]
Girl:
YOU’RE SO CUTE, GRAMPS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WRONG NUDIST BEACH,
MAKO.
[ GRUNTING ]
HOW’D YOU KNOW
WHAT WAS GOING ON IN MY HEAD?
Seketsu: YOU MUST BE
TELEPATHIC NOW, RYUKO.
I’M NOT TOO THRILLED
ABOUT THAT.
NO WAY!
THIS IS GREAT!
NOW I GOT A FRIEND WHO’S
BOTH INSIDE AND OUTSIDE MY HEAD!
ALL RIGHT.
YOUR TURN, RYUKO.
OF ALL THE CREATURES
ON EARTH,
HOW MANY ARE THERE
THAT WEAR CLOTHING?
THAT’S EASY ‐‐
JUST US HUMANS.
CORRECT.
OUT OF ALL THE SPECIES
LIVING ON THE PLANET,
HOMO SAPIENS ARE THE ONLY ONES
THAT WEAR CLOTHING.
AND WHY IS THAT?!
IT’S NOT BECAUSE
WE EVOLVED TO WEAR CLOTHES.
THE TRUTH IS, WE EVOLVED
BECAUSE WE WORE CLOTHES.
THE HOMO SAPIEN WAS
JUST ANOTHER ANTHROPOID SPECIES
UNTIL LIFE FIBERS CAME ALONG.
THEY HELPED US EVOLVE.
HUMANS DIDN’T CHOOSE
THE CLOTHES THEY WEAR.
INSTEAD,
CLOTHING CHOSE US TO WEAR IT.
[ GASPS ]
IS THAT IT ‐‐
THE SOURCE?
YES. THIS IS
THE BEGINNING OF IT ALL ‐‐
THE PRIMORDIAL
LIFE FIBER.
IMAGINE A GLOWING BALL OF THREAD
DRIFTING THROUGH SPACE.
ARRIVING ON EARTH, IT
CHOSE HUMANS TO PLAY HOST TO IT,
DOOMING THEM
TO SERVE CLOTHING.
LIFE FIBERS
WILL SOON BE IN ALL CLOTHING,
WRAPPING THE PLANET.
AND THEN,
THE COVERS WILL AWAKEN,
SEALING HUMANITY’S FATE,
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
THAT’S WHERE
THE KIRYUINS COME IN.
WE ARE THE SPOKESPERSONS
FOR THE COVERS’ WILL.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
YES.
I UNDERSTAND.
PEOPLE WERE CHOSEN
BY CLOTHES?
YEAH, RIGHT.
THAT DOESN’T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
WHOA!
Mikisugi: PAY ATTENTION.
LIFE FIBERS
ARE AN ALIEN LIFE‐FORM.
THEY CAME TO EARTH LONG AGO.
THEY ACCELERATED
HUMAN EVOLUTION.
♪ HALLELUJAH ♪
HUH?!
SO, THEN,
SENKETSU’S AN ALIEN?
HE’S A SAILOR UNIFORM
AND AN ALIEN?!
SO THAT’S WHAT I AM...
NOT EVEN.
WHAT KIND OF CRAZY B.S.
ARE YOU SHOVELLING?!
PLEASE HOLD YOUR QUESTIONS
UNTIL THE END.
I’M IN THE MIDDLE OF EXPLAINING,
SO IF YOU DON’T MIND ‐‐
Mikisugi:
BACK TO LIFE FIBERS ‐‐ THEY’RE
PARASITES FROM OUTER SPACE.
WHEN THEY INFEST A LIFE FORM,
THEY FEED OFF
THE ELECTRICAL CURRENTS
OF THEIR HOST’S NERVOUS SYSTEM.
NOW, IF THEY INFEST A LIFE FORM
INTERNALLY,
THE HOST’S NERVOUS SYSTEM
CAN’T TAKE THE STRAIN,
RESULTING IN DEATH.
THAT’S WHY THEY DECIDED TO COVER
THE HOST’S BODY INSTEAD.
THE CURRENT A LIFE FIBER
GETS THROUGH THE HOST’S SKIN
IS MINUTE,
BUT AT LEAST THE HOST
WON’T DIE FROM THE TRAUMA.
THEY CHOSE HOMO SAPIENS
BECAUSE THEY HAD THE MOST
DEVELOPED CEREBRUM AT THE TIME.
WE BECAME THEIR HOSTS AND
THEY ACCELERATED OUR EVOLUTION.
AND EVOLVE WE DID.
THEY DEVELOPED
OUR THEN‐PRIMITIVE BRAINS
FAR BEYOND
ANY OTHER TERRESTRIAL CREATURE.
WE KEPT REPRODUCING
AND BECAME THE DOMINANT SPECIES
ON THE PLANET.
BUT NOT FOR LONG.
YOU SEE, LIFE FIBERS
CULTIVATED US FOR A REASON ‐‐
Kinagase: BASICALLY
WHAT HE’S SAYING IS...
HUMAN BEINGS ARE FOOD
FOR THE LIFE FIBERS.
YOU MEAN...
I’LL TRY TO EAT RYUKO?
Ryuko:
CALM DOWN, SENKETSU.
WE HAVEN’T HEARD
THE WHOLE STORY YET.
IF THAT’S TRUE,
HOW COME THE LIFE FIBERS
AREN’T IN EVERYONE’S CLOTHES?
LIKE, MAYBE
THEY’RE ONLY IN
THE UNIFORMS OF PEOPLE
AT HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
I MEAN,
PEOPLE’VE WORN CLOTHES FOREVER,
BUT WE’RE ONLY
FINDING OUT ABOUT THIS NOW?
WE HAPPEN TO HAVE A THEORY
ABOUT THAT.
THE ONLY POSSIBLE CONCLUSION
IS THE LIFE FIBERS
THAT HELPED US EVOLVE
DECIDED TO GO DORMANT
LONG AGO.
BUT BEFORE THEY DID, THEY
CONDITIONED US TO WEAR CLOTHES.
THEY ONLY JUST EMERGED
FROM THEIR SLEEP ABOUT,
OH, 20 YEARS AGO.
RAGYO KIRYUIN MADE CONTACT
WITH THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER,
AND SUDDENLY,
THEY WERE AWAKE.
THAT’S WHAT
DR. MATOI TOLD US.
THE DAMN THINGS WERE WAITING
FOR HARVEST TIME.
WAITING FOR ALL THEIR
LITTLE COWS TO GET BIG AND FAT.
ALL THIS TIME, I’VE BEEN WAITING
FOR YOU TO MATURE?
IS THAT WHY
I DRINK YOUR BLOOD?
YOU’RE MY FOOD?
CALM DOWN, SENKETSU.
YOU KNOW
YOU’RE NOTHING LIKE THAT.
I JUST BLEW SENKETSU’S MIND,
DIDN’T I?
I AM SORRY.
AND I HATE TO BLOW HIS MIND
EVEN MORE,
BUT YOU GUYS
ARE OUR ONLY HOPE.
"HOPE"?
THAT’S RIGHT.
KAMUI SENKETSU
WAS CREATED BY DR. MATOI
TO SERVE
ONE IMPORTANT PURPOSE ‐‐
FIGHT LIFE FIBERS.
AND THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN WEAR IT
TO ITS FULL POTENTIAL IS YOU.
[ SENKETSU GASPS ]
I’M THE ONLY ONE?
BUT WHY ME?
Mikisugi: YOU HAVE AN UNUSUALLY
HIGH TOLERANCE TO LIFE FIBERS.
THAT’S WHAT GAVE DR. MATOI
THE IDEA.
SO HE MADE SENKETSU FOR YOU
IN THE HOPES THAT...
YOU’D DESTROY
THE KIRYUINS’ PLANS.
ORIGINALLY, YOUR FATHER
WORKED FOR RAGYO KIRYUIN...
STUDYING LIFE FIBERS.
BUT WHEN HE FOUND OUT
ABOUT THE THREAT THEY POSED,
HE LEFT AND STARTED A
SECRET ORGANIZATION TO STOP HER.
HE CALLED IT
NUDIST BEACH.
I SEE.
DR. MATOI MADE ME TO ‐‐
YES.
I REMEMBER NOW.
I WAS BORN
IN THAT UNDERGROUND LAB.
THEN I WAS PUT TO SLEEP.
I SLEPT FOR SIX MONTHS.
AND THEN RYUKO SHOWED UP.
[ ALARM BLARING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GROANS, PANTING ]
I’M SORRY I KEPT YOU
IN THE DARK THIS LONG.
BUT THE KIRYUINS ARE POWERFUL,
AS YOU KNOW.
I COULDN’T TELL YOU
THE WHOLE STORY
UNTIL I WAS SURE YOU COULD
CONTROL ALL OF SENKETSU’S POWER.
AND IF I EVER LOST MY SHIT
’CAUSE OF THE LIFE FIBERS,
YOUR JOB WAS TO PUT ME DOWN
WITHOUT ANY MERCY.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
AND I STILL INTEND
TO DO THAT.
HEY, EASY.
NAW, IT’S COOL,
YOU GUYS ARE RIGHT.
BEFORE TODAY, I WOULDN’T HAVE
BELIEVED ANY OF THIS STUFF.
THEN YOU’RE GONNA LOVE THIS...
RAGYO KIRUIN RUNS
A CLOTHING EMPIRE CALLED REVOCS.
THEIR CLOTHES ARE FOUND
IN ALMOST EVERY COUNTRY.
THEY’VE WOVEN LIFE FIBERS
INTO EVERY PIECE THEY MAKE.
RIGHT NOW,
THEY’RE DORMANT.
BUT WHEN THEY AWAKEN,
I CAN’T EVEN BEGIN TO IMAGINE
WHAT’LL HAPPEN.
ONE THING’S FOR SURE, THOUGH.
WHEN THEY WAKE UP,
THE DEATH CLOCK STARTS TICKING
FOR THE HUMAN RACE.
Ragyo: HAVE ALL THE SCHOOLS
IN THE COUNTRY BEEN CONQUERED
AND NUDIST BEACH,
CRUSHED?
Satsuki: YES.
THEN OUR
HONNOUJI ACADEMY EXPERIMENT
CAN MOVE
TO THE NEXT PHASE.
WE’VE COMPLETED CONSTRUCTION
ON RAGYO STADIUM.
THE PREPARATIONS
FOR THE FESTIVAL ARE ALSO READY.
MAGNIFICENT.
THE PLAN IS
AT ITS FINAL STAGE.
ANNOUNCE THE CULTURAL
AND SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL.
[ GASPS ]
YES.
ARE YOU LEAVING NOW?
I’D LIKE TO
SPEND THE NIGHT.
I HAVEN’T BEEN HOME
IN AGES.
VERY WELL.
KUROIDO?
LOOK AFTER THINGS, WON’T YOU?
I CAN’T WAIT TO SEE
HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
YOU MUST BE SO PROUD
OF YOUR CREATION.
YOU’LL HAVE A WARM WELCOME,
DEAREST MOTHER.
[ SNORING ]
HUH?
OHH, NOW I GET IT!
YEAH ‐‐ YOU GUYS WANT ME
TO USE GOOD OL’ SENKETSU HERE
TO "FIGHT FOR THE SAKE
OF HUMANITY," RIGHT?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?!
YOU CAN
BLOW IT OUT YOUR ASS!
TAKE IT EASY.
SO YOU THINK SENKETSU’S
JUST A WEAPON, HUH?
JUST A UNIFORM MADE TO FIGHT
AND THAT’S IT, HUH?!
GOD,
WHAT A BUNCH OF DICKS.
HE’S NOT JUST A WEAPON.
HE’S GOT A MIND OF HIS OWN.
YOU WANT HIM TO GO
AND KILL HIS OWN KIND.
CAN’T YOU PEOPLE SEE
HOW MESSED UP THAT IS?
WELL, I CAN,
GOD DAMN IT!
[ SENKETSU GASPS ]
WH‐WHAT’RE YOU DOING?
[ GRUNTING, STRAINING ]
THIS IS NUDIST BEACH,
RIGHT?
YOU GOT A PROBLEM
WITH ME BEING NAKED?
RYUKO...
I WON’T PUT YOU ON
TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
AND THERE’S NO REASON
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT, EITHER.
[ GASPS ]
Kinagase: RIGHT.
THERE’S TWO THINGS
YOU NEED TO KNOW.
ONE ‐‐ KAMUIS THAT DON’T FIGHT
ARE USELESS.
TWO ‐‐ IF THEY HAVE NO USE,
THEY GET KILLED.
YOU’LL HAVE TO KILL ME FIRST
TO DO IT.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
YOU DIE FIRST.
I DON’T GIVE A SHIT.
[ WHIMPERS ] THINGS ARE
STARTING TO GET NASTY.
EVERYONE’S SO TENSE.
I KNOW ‐‐ I’LL HAVE A SNACK
TO HELP CALM ME DOWN.
THESE CHIPS’LL DO.
[ MUNCHES ]
AAH! THEY’RE NASTY, TOO!
I CAN’T UN‐TASTE IT NOW.
WHY, GOD?!
WHY?!
Senketsu: RYUKO LEARNS
OF HER FATHER’S WISHES.
BE STRONG, RYUKO.
YOU SCRATCH MY LAPELS,
I SCRATCH YOURS.
THE KIRYUINS
DECLARE THEIR VICTORY
AT THE CULTURAL & SPORTS
GRAND FESTIVAL,
AND WE’RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO CAN STOP IT.
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"TELL ME WHY."