[ ALL GASPING, MURMURING ]
OH, MY GOD.
COVERS.
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ SCREAMING CONTINUES ]
HUH?
HEH?
[ DISTORTED SCREAM ]
[ GROWLS ]
YAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ ROARS ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
RRRRRRRRRRRAAAH!
THIS WAY! HURRY!
RUN! RUN! RUN!
[ RYUKO GASPS ]
[ HEART BEATING ]
HOW BEAUTIFUL.
RYUKO!
HOW BRILLIANT.
THERE AREN’T MANY HUMANS
WHO CAN MERGE WITH LIFE FIBERS
SO PERFECTLY.
THERE’S NO DOUBT
YOU ARE MY DAUGHTER.
OH, MY GOD!
MY RYUKO’S
THE DIRECTOR’S DAUGHTER?!
HMM?
AAAAAAAH!
I’M BEING PULLED UP!
MAKO!
AAH!
SIS!
GUTS! OOH!
MAKO!
CUT THE THREAD!
HURRY, MANKANSHOKU!
DO IT!
GAAH!
MANKANSHOKU!
SOMEBODY HELP ME!!
[ ALL GASP ]
MANKANSHOKU!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
NO!
AAH!
I’M ISSHIN MATOI’S DAUGHTER.
GOT IT?
YOU’RE NOT MY MOM.
YOU CAN’T BE!
IF I’M NOT,
HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN THAT?
IT’S HEREDITY, DEAR.
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
SHUT UP!
CALM DOWN, RYUKO.
I DON’T GIVE A DAMN!
OH, WOW.
HOW VERY INTERESTING.
I ALWAYS KNEW THERE WAS
SOMETHING SPECIAL ABOUT YOU.
YOU’RE THE GREATEST,
RYUKO!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ Straining ]
YOU’RE WRONG...
MOTHER.
I’M NOT DONE...JUST YET.
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
Sanageyama: LADY SATSUKI!
Inumuta: LADY SATSUKI!
SATSUKI!
GRAB AS MUCH AS YOU CAN.
GUTS!
[ BOTH GASP ]
QUIT BLOCKING THE ROAD,
YOU CHEAP‐ASS SUIT!
LATER, DICK!
AAAAH!
OH, CRAP!
I‐I‐I WAS KIDDING!
YOU’RE NOT CHEAP!
DON’T EAT US, MAN!
[ GROANS ]
HUH?
GUTS?
YOU DUSTRAGS
ARE GOING DOWN!
[ BOTH GASP ]
YOU’RE
THAT ELITE FOUR CHICK!
GUTS!
WELL, IF IT ISN’T
THE SLACKER’S BROTHER.
HUH?
KNOCK A COUPLE DOWN,
AND A BUNCH MORE POP UP.
BETTER RUN!
WAY AHEAD OF YOU,
HOT STUFF.
Jakuzure: WAIT ‐‐ YOU’VE BEEN
ON YOUR OWN FOR THE PAST MONTH?
IMPRESSIVE, CONSIDERING YOU’RE
PRINCESS BOWL‐CUT’S BROTHER.
GUESS SURVIVING
RUNS IN THE FAMILY, HUH, KID?
THE NAME’S MATARO.
HMM.
ALL RIGHT, PACK IT UP.
OUR RIDE’S HERE.
COME ON! HURRY!
KEEP MOVING!
THERE’S A CHOPPER WAITING
FOR YOU JUST OVER THE HILL!
SHIT.
THEY CAUGHT UP TO US.
I HOPE YOU HOLD UP.
BLADE REGALIA MARK THREE!
[ GRUNTS ]
HUH?
DAMN!
THIS THING’S REACHED ITS LIMIT.
AAH!
GET OUT OF HERE!
WE’LL HOLD THESE BITCHES OFF!
[ Weakly ] THANKS, YOU GUYS.
[ WHIMPERS ]
US NORTH KANTO
GANG LEADERS
WANT A SHOT
AT BEING HEROES, TOO.
OKAY.
THEN SHOW THOSE DAMN RAGS
WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN THEY PUSH US HUMANS
TOO FAR!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
GET FIRED UP,
’CAUSE IT’S ON!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
TEAR ’EM A NEW ONE
FROM THE INSIDE!
[ MUFFLED SHOUTING, SCUFFLING ]
GET ON BOARD!
THEY CAN’T DISTRACT THEM
FOREVER!
[ GASPS ]
[ DISTORTED GROAN ]
SORRY I BAILED ON YOU.
Gamagoori:
EVEN THOUGH THEY WERE HOODS,
THEY WERE HONORABLE.
BE PROUD OF THEM.
WE CAN’T
KEEP GOING LIKE THIS.
EVERY TIME THEY HIT US,
WE LOSE PEOPLE.
TRUE.
WE DID MANAGE
TO SAVE A FEW LIVES, THOUGH,
SO THEIR SACRIFICE
WASN’T IN VAIN.
GET THESE REFUGEES
TO THE BARRACKS ON THE DOUBLE!
HOW YOU GUYS DOING?
WAS IT HELLA ROUGH OUT THERE
FOR YOU, TOO?
YEAH.
SO, YOU FOUND
MANKANSHOKU’S LITTLE BROTHER.
YEAH, HIM AND HIS FRIENDS
WERE IN THE SEWERS
UNDER HONNOU TOWN.
CLEVER PACK OF RATS ‐‐
THAT’S FOR SURE.
FOR THE LAST TIME,
YOU ELITE FOUR SNOB,
THE NAME’S MATARO!
GUTS!
WHATEVER,
SLACKER JUNIOR.
I’M NONON JAKUZURE,
BUT YOU CAN CALL ME LADY NONON.
THAT’S NO WAY TO TREAT ANYONE,
JAKUZURE.
IF YOU WANT HIM
TO ADDRESS YOU PROPERLY,
YOU MUST ADDRESS HIM PROPERLY,
AS WELL.
10‐4, MR. DISCIPLINARY
COMMITTEE CHAIR.
Inumuta:
SO, THE NORTH KANTO GANG LEADERS
HAVE FALLEN, TOO.
WITH THAT, ALL THE SCHOOLS
THAT WERE UNDER
HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S CONTROL
HAVE BEEN COMPLETELY WIPED OUT
BY THE COVERS.
SO WHAT YOU’RE SAYING
IS WE’RE SCREWED.
OUT OF ALL OF SATSUKI’S FORCES,
WE’RE THE ONLY ONES LEFT.
YOU GOT ANY GOOD NEWS?
THAT DEPENDS.
SANAGEYAMA’S GOKU UNIFORM
WAS THE LAST WE HAD.
HOWEVER,
WE HAVE TWO NEW WEAPONS
WE FORGED
FROM LADY SATSUKI’S SWORD ‐‐
JAKUZURE’S BAKUZAN‐GAKO
AND GAMAGOORI’S BAKUZAN‐KOURYU.
IT’S NOT MUCH,
BUT IT’S SOMETHING.
Kinagase:
THERE’S ALSO MY TAILOR’S DAGGER
AND HIS DOUTONBORI ROBO.
DTR.
LET’S NOT SPLIT HAIRS.
DTR!
[ SIGHS ]
AT THIS POINT,
I’M JUST HOPING
WHATEVER
IORI’S COBBLING TOGETHER
WILL BE DONE ON TIME.
TOO BAD YOUR PEOPLE DESTROYED
OUR R&D FACILITIES IN THE RAID.
THAT EQUIPMENT
COULD HAVE HELPED HIM.
AND WHILE WE’RE ON THE SUBJECT,
SOMETHING’S BEEN BUGGING ME.
IF YOU WANTED
TO TAKE RAGYO DOWN,
HOW COME
YOU DIDN’T CONSIDER
JOINING FORCES
WITH NUDIST BEACH?
SIMPLE ‐‐ IT’S MUCH HARDER
TO KEEP A SECRET
WHEN EVERYONE KNOWS
THE SECRET.
EVEN AT THE ACADEMY,
THE LIST OF PEOPLE WHO KNEW
ABOUT LADY SATSUKI’S PLAN
WAS SHORT ‐‐
JUST US
IN THE ELITE FOUR,
IORI OF THE SEWING CLUB,
AND SOROI, HER BUTLER.
WELL, CONSIDERING YOU KNEW
I WAS UNDERCOVER THE WHOLE TIME
AND I NEVER CAUGHT ON TO IT,
YOU GUYS HAD THE RIGHT IDEA.
WHO AM I
TO QUESTION YOUR TACTICS?
THERE’S COVERS ATTACKING SCHOOLS
ALL OVER JAPAN AS WE SPEAK.
YOU THINK YOU’D HEAR ABOUT IT
ON THE NEWS
OR ONLINE OR SOMETHING
BY NOW.
MY GUESS IS THEY HAVE EVERYONE’S
MINDS UNDER THEIR CONTROL.
HE’S RIGHT.
RAGYO KIRYUIN’S
REVOCS CLOTHING
IS WORN
BY MOST OF THE POPULATION.
THE LIFE FIBERS
WOVEN INTO THE CLOTHES
CAN MANIPULATE
THE MINDS OF THE WEARERS,
DELETING ANY INFORMATION
THAT IS DEEMED UNNECESSARY
FROM THEIR BRAINS.
THEY HAVE EYES BUT FAIL TO SEE
AND EARS BUT FAIL TO HEAR ‐‐
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
AS LONG AS A LIFE FIBER IS
FEEDING OFF YOUR NERVOUS SYSTEM,
YOU’RE ITS PUPPET.
NOT QUITE ‐‐
BY WEARING GOKU UNIFORMS,
HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S STUDENTS HAVE
ACTUALLY BUILT UP A RESISTANCE
TO THE LIFE FIBERS’
MANIPULATIONS.
THAT SATSUKI
IS ONE CLEVER GIRL.
SHE PRETENDS TO BE LOYAL
TO RAGYO TO ACCESS HER MONEY,
THEN USES IT TO BUILD
HER OWN PERSONAL REBEL ARMY.
I BET
RAGYO NEVER SAW IT COMING.
SPEAKING OF CLEVER PEOPLE,
MR. SOROI,
WOULD YOU PLEASE TELL US
HOW YOU FIT INTO
SATSUKI’S PLANS?
THANK YOU
FOR THE COMPLIMENT, SIR.
HOWEVER, I JUST MADE THE TEA,
AS I HAVE NOW.
EVEN THOUGH LADY SATSUKI
ISN’T HERE TO ENJOY IT WITH US,
I HAVEN’T GIVEN UP
ON HER.
YOU BRING UP
A GOOD POINT.
THE ELITE FOUR MANAGED
TO SURVIVE, SO WHY WOULDN’T SHE?
Kinagase: YEAH,
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER ONE?
RYUKO, WHAT’S WRONG?
WHY HAVEN’T YOU
WOKEN UP YET?
I’M SORRY WE CAN’T HEAR
WHAT YOU’RE SAYING, SENKETSU ‐‐
ESPECIALLY NOW ‐‐
BUT EVEN SO,
WE ALL HAVE A PRETTY GOOD IDEA
HOW YOU’RE FEELING.
YOU DO?
IT’S PLAIN AS DAY YOU’RE ALIVE
AND YOU’RE HER SUNDAY BEST.
WE ALL KNOW
YOU’RE WORRIED SICK ABOUT HER,
AND IF IT’S ANY CONSOLATION,
WE’RE HERE FOR YOU.
[ SOBS ]
MRS. MANKANSHOKU!
OH! THERE, THERE.
IF I WERE 20 YEARS YOUNGER,
I’D WEAR YOU IN A HEARTBEAT,
YOU BETCHA.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
HOW’S RYUKO DOING?
STABLE,
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL,
BUT THERE’S ONE THING
THAT DON’T MAKE SENSE.
SHE SHOULD HAVE HAD A WOUND
OR A SCAR OR SOMETHING
WHERE SHE GOT HER HEART
PULLED OUT, BUT SHE DOESN’T.
IT’S ‐‐
HOW DO I PUT IT?
IT’S NOT HUMAN,
IS WHAT IT IS.
WHAT’D YOU SAY?!
HEY, EASY!
WE GET HOW YOU FEEL,
BUT WHEN THAT PLACE BLEW,
YOU DIDN’T FREAK OUT.
YOU DRAGGED RYUKO
TO SAFETY.
YOU NEED TO STAY CALM ‐‐
FOR HER.
Barazo: WELL, I ALWAYS SAY,
IF A PATIENT WANTS TO SLEEP,
IT’S BEST TO LET THEM.
SHE’S HAD A COUPLE OF
NASTY SHOCKS. THAT’S FOR SURE.
I STILL CAN’T BELIEVE
RYUKO’S MOTHER IS
THAT NASTY RAGYO KIRYUIN WOMAN.
IF DR. MATOI KNEW ABOUT IT,
I WONDER WHY HE DIDN’T TELL ME.
GOD, I COULD HAVE
FIGURED OUT A WAY
TO BREAK THE NEWS TO HER GENTLY
IF I’D KNOWN SOONER.
DON’T SWEAT IT.
WHAT’S DONE IS DONE.
THINGS WILL WORK OUT
SOMEHOW.
GUTS!
DAD!
AAH!
WHOA! YOU MADE IT!
THAT’S MY BOY ‐‐
A BORN SURVIVOR!
[ GIGGLES ]
SEE WHAT
I’M TALKING ABOUT?
BIG‐TIME.
SORRY, DAD. I LOOKED, BUT I
COULDN’T FIND HER ANYWHERE.
BOY, WERE YOU SEARCHING
FOR MANKANSHOKU?
YEAH ‐‐ I FIGURED
IF I HUNG AROUND HONNOU TOWN,
I MIGHT FIND
THE PIECE OF SHIT THAT ‐‐
OH. SORRY, MOM.
...SUIT
THAT SWALLOWED HER UP,
BUT I GOT STUCK,
AND IT WAS ALL I COULD DO
JUST TO STAY ALIVE
OUT THERE.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS
YOU TRIED, HON.
SAVE YOUR TEARS,
GUYS.
REMEMBER,
SHE’S A MANKANSHOKU.
THERE’S NO WAY
SHE’S GONNA DIE THAT EASY.
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
LISTEN, BOY.
NO MATTER WHAT,
I WILL RESCUE YOUR SISTER.
I’LL DEVOTE MY BODY AND SOUL
TO GET HER BACK TO YOU SAFELY!
OW, OW, OW, OW! YOU’RE BREAKING
MY COLLARBONE, MAN!
[ Strained ] DAD!
MM. KID’S RIGHT ‐‐
COLLARBONE’S BROKE.
SO FORK OVER 10 MILLION YEN,
OR I’M CALLING MY LAWYER.
10 MILLION?!
[ CHUCKLES ]
MA’AM, WHEN I LOOK
AT YOUR FAMILY, IT GIVES ME HOPE
THE HUMAN RACE CAN STILL SURVIVE
THIS NIGHTMARE.
GUTS!
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
[ RAGYO CHUCKLES ]
I HAVE TO SAY,
YOU CERTAINLY EXCEEDED
ALL OF MY EXPECTATIONS ‐‐
OF YOUR FOOLISHNESS,
THAT IS.
BY NOW, THE COVERS
HAVE ASSIMILATED EVERY STUDENT
IN THE SCHOOLS HONNOUJI ACADEMY
WORKED SO HARD TO CONQUER.
YOU’RE A CRAFTY ONE.
YOU KNEW IF A HUMAN WORE
LIFE FIBER‐INFUSED CLOTHING
FROM BIRTH TO AGE 20, THEY’D
LOSE ALL RESISTANCE TO IT.
SO YOU BUILD AN ARMY
OF TEENAGE SOLDIERS,
THINKING THEY’D BE
LESS SUSCEPTIBLE AGAINST ME?
[ LAUGHS ] REALLY?
THAT IS THE SILLIEST THING
I’VE EVER HEARD.
YOUR FOLLOWERS ARE ENERGY
SOURCES FOR THE COVERS NOW,
AND THE MORE THEY RESIST,
THE MORE NOURISHMENT
THEY PROVIDE.
BEFORE LONG,
EVEN YOUR LITTLE SISTER
WILL BE MINE.
MY SISTER...
RYUKO MATOI.
YES.
AND TO THINK ‐‐
SHE IS THE BABY
I THOUGHT HAD DIED
ALL THOSE YEARS AND YEARS AGO.
SOICHIRO HAD DECEIVED ME
ABOUT A GREAT MANY THINGS.
MATOI AND I...ARE SISTERS.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Kuroido:
HE WAS A STUPID MAN.
Ragyo:
SOICHIRO FAKED HIS DEATH,
LEAVING YOU BEHIND
TO MOURN HIM.
THEN HE CHANGED
HIS FACE AND POSTURE
AND ASSUMED THE NAME
OF ISSHIN MATOI.
HE RAISED THE BABY
WHOSE DEATH HE FAKED
IN THAT RATHOLE MANSION
OF HIS.
AND THEN HE FOUNDED
THAT RIDICULOUS
NUDIST BEACH ORGANIZATION
AND GAVE A KAMUI
TO RYUKO.
[ GASPING ]
DAD, I ‐‐ I CAN’T...
I CAN’T...
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU DIDN’T KNOW ANY OF THAT,
DID YOU? NO.
YET YOU BELIEVED HIM, AND YOU
BEGAN PLOTTING YOUR REBELLION ‐‐
YOUR NOBLE CAUSE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT’S SO NOBLE,
IT BRINGS TEARS TO MY EYES.
PLEASE.
AS IF A WOMAN
WITH LIFE FIBERS FOR TEAR GLANDS
COULD CRY.
REGARDLESS,
I AM STILL YOUR MOTHER.
YOU SHOULDN’T TAKE MY KINDNESS
FOR GRANTED.
[ SCOFFS ]
YOU ARE NOT KIND.
ARE YOU SURE?
AND HOW WOULD YOU DESCRIBE
MY SPARING YOUR LIFE, HMM?
I’D LIKE TO THINK I DID IT
OUT OF MATERNAL KINDNESS.
IT WAS ANYTHING BUT.
YOU LET ME LIVE BECAUSE
I’M MORE VALUABLE THAT WAY.
NO MORE, NO LESS.
OH?
HOW SO?
SHINRA‐KOKETSU.
[ SCOFFS ]
YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT, EH?
IT WASN’T HARD
TO FIGURE OUT.
[ SCOFFS ]
IN THAT CASE, DEAR...
LET’S GET
YOUR BLOOD BOILING.
[ LAUGHS ]
THAT’S IT ‐‐
SEETHE FOR ME.
THE DEEPER YOUR RAGE,
THE MORE USEFUL YOU ARE TO ME!
[ HUMMING ]
WORK IS PROGRESSING
SMOOTHLY, I SEE.
THANKS TO SATSUKI.
HER LITTLE SEWING CLUB MEMBERS
ARE SO DARN CAPABLE.
HMM. MIND‐STITCHING THEM
WAS WORTH THE TROUBLE, THEN.
YEP. THEY’RE WAY BETTER
THAN COVERS.
I HOPE
SATSUKI’S DOING WELL.
SHE IS.
SHE’S DYING TO WEAR
THAT OUTFIT YOU’RE MAKING.
WAIT A SEC.
MY MASTERPIECE?
SATSUKI’S WON’T BE
WEARING IT.
OH, NO!
SHE’S GONNA BE ITS SUPPER!
ANYWAY,
WE SHOULD WORRY ABOUT RYUKO.
YES. I KNOW.
I’VE ALREADY TAKEN STEPS.
HONESTLY,
HAVING TWO TEENAGE DAUGHTERS
CERTAINLY KEEPS ONE BUSY.
THEY’VE GROWN UP
TO BE FINE YOUNG LADIES ‐‐
BUT THEN, YOU’RE THEIR MOTHER,
SO NO SURPRISE THERE.
LA VIE EST DRôLE,
ISN’T IT?
YES, LIFE IS AMUSING.
AND I CAN HARDLY WAIT
TO SHOW THIS TO THEM ‐‐
THE ULTIMATE KAMUI.
[ ALARM BLARING ]
Kinagase:
WELL, THEY FOUND US.
Mikisugi: WE’LL HOLD THEM OFF
AS BEST WE CAN.
HOPEFULLY,
THINGS WORK OUT.
THAT SOUNDS WEIRD
COMING FROM YOU.
DOESN’T EXACTLY
FIRE ME UP.
[ CHUCKLES ]
ME NEITHER.
HANG ON.
THE DTR IS GOING UP!
HM.
TAKE IT.
SWORDS ARE
MORE YOUR SPECIALTY.
THANKS, MAN.
GET FROSTY, MONKEY.
TIME TO GO.
HMM?
[ GROANS ]
I THOUGHT
I’D NEVER FINISH.
DOES IT REALLY WORK?
THEORETICALLY.
GO AHEAD ‐‐ TRY IT OUT.
Mikisugi:
OH, LOOK. THERE’S A WHOLE BUNCH
OF THEM OVER HERE, TOO.
Kinagase: IT’S LIKE SOMEONE RANG
THE DINNER BELL FOR THEM.
Jakuzure: FIVE OF US
VERSUS ALL OF THEM?
GOODIE.
I THINK I’M GONNA CRY.
NUT UP!
WE’RE THE MIGHTY FIVE NOW!
WOW. "NUT UP," HUH?
PUT YOUR GAME FACE ON
ALREADY.
OHHHH.
OKAY, OKAY. IT’S ON.
GUTS!
GUTS! GUTS! GUTS!
Gamagoori: LOOK!
IT’S THE MANKANSHOKUS’ DOG!
COULD IT BE...?
LET’S FIND OUT
IF THIS WORKS!
[ GROANS ]
UUUAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
MANKANSHOKU!
Inumuta: SHE’S OUT!
Iori: SHE’S OUT!
WHEN COVERS
ARE CLOTH‐BASED,
THEY GET THEIR ENERGY
VIA A LINKAGE THREAT
THAT’S CONNECTED
TO THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER.
THAT’S WHY
IF WE SEVER THAT THREAD,
WE CAN SHUT THEM DOWN!
HOWEVER, HUMAN‐BASED COVERS
FUNCTION AUTONOMOUSLY,
BY FEEDING OFF THE ENERGY
OF THE PEOPLE THEY SWALLOW.
THEREFORE, IF YOU CAN
EXTRACT THE HUMAN,
THE COVER’S ENERGY SOURCE
IS TAKEN AWAY
AND YOU CAN DISABLE IT!
SEE?
BY REDUCING THEIR NUMBERS...
WE’RE ADDING TO OURS!
Both:
SO WE MADE AN EXTRACTION WEAPON!
BEHOLD!
THE EMERGENCY
RESCUE SUCTION DEVICE!
IN HEAVEN’S STEAD,
I SMITE CLOTHING!
WHOO‐HOO! I’M SAVED!
A‐ARE YOU...ALL RIGHT?
YEP!
NEVER FELT BETTER!
MAKO MANKANSHOKU
HAS RETURNED!
WAIT.
[ GASPS ]
OH, MY GOD! NO WAY!
ARE YOU THE ONE
WHO RESCUED ME?!
YES. I‐I GAVE
YOUR LITTLE BROTHER MY WORD.
ANYWAY...
HERE.
YOU BETTER PUT THIS ON.
[ GASPS ]
I’M IN MY BIRTHDAY SUIT!
WELL, NOW WE KNOW
IT WORKS.
SO QUIT FLIRTING WITH HER
AND GO RESCUE SOME MORE PEOPLE.
I AM NOT
FLIRTING WITH HER!
HMM.
WE’LL TALK LATER.
GET CLEAR, MANKANSHOKU.
OKAY!
WAIT. HOW’D I GET BACK
TO OSAKA?
THAT’S SO WEIRD.
Mataro: SIS!
MAKO! YOU’RE OKAY!
I LOVE YOU, SIS!
DAD! MATARO!
[ HIGH‐PITCHED SCREECHING ]
[ GROANING ]
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?!
KILLING MY EARS,
THAT’S WHAT!
THEY COULD USE
A COUPLE LESSONS!
[ GROANING ]
WHAT’S THAT NOISE?
OH, DEAR!
[ GROANING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ ALL GASP ]
Jakuzure: OH, MY GOD.
Mikisugi: IT’S RYUKO.
Mako: RYUKO!
I’M SICK OF THAT SHIT
YOU BASTARDS ARE PLAYING!
SHUT UP!
WHAT THE HELL?!
WITH ONE SLASH?
DID YOU SEE THAT?
SHE GOT EVERYONE OUT!
[ GRUNTS ]
RYUKO! YOU’RE AWAKE!
GET AWAY FROM ME.
[ GASPS ]
I’M DONE WITH YOU.
I’LL NEVER WEAR YOU AGAIN.
[ GASPS ]
RYUKO!
JUST LOOKING AT YOU
PISSES ME OFF.
’CAUSE I’M THE SAME
AS YOU.
I’M NOT HUMAN.
I NEVER WAS!
I’M A GODDAMN
LIFE FIBER MONSTER!
DAMN YOU, RAGYO.
YOU SPARED ME
SO YOU COULD USE ME.
THAT WILL BE YOUR LAST MISTAKE.
AS LONG AS I LIVE...
I STILL HAVE A CHANCE
AT BRINGING YOU DOWN!
Senketsu: HELLO, EVERYONE.
I HAVE SAD NEWS FOR YOU TODAY.
THIS IS THE LAST TELEVISION
BROADCAST PREVIEW FOR THE SHOW,
SO TUNE IN TO THE WEB PREVIEWS
FROM NOW ON.
OUR BATTLE IS JUST BEGINNING.
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"FAR FROM THE MADDING CROWD."