[ FOOD THUDS ]
All: IT’S TIME FOR DINNER!
[ CHOMPING ]
[ Mouth full ]
YUMMY! [ SWALLOWS ]
OH, RIGHT ON, MOM!
YOUR CROQUETTES
ARE AS AWESOME AS EVER!
[ Mouth full ] WHEN IT COMES
FRYING MYSTERY INGREDIENTS,
YOU’RE THE BEST IN JAPAN,
HONEY‐BUN!
THE TRICK’S GIVING EVERYTHING
A GOOD CHOP.
THEN YOU MIX IT UP
WITH SOME POTATOES AND VOILà!
MMM, HOWEVER YOU DO IT,
YOUR CROQUETTES ARE THE BOMB!
I’M GLAD YOU LIKE ’EM!
PLEASE, HAVE SOME MORE!
OH, I CAN’T,
I’M SUPER‐STUFFED!
THANKS FOR DINNER, MA’AM.
YOU’RE WELCOME.
OH, I DREW A BATH FOR YOU
SO HAVE AT IT.
COOL, THANKS.
Both: THE BATH?!
[ GIGGLES ]
Senketsu: WHAT?
WHAT’S SO FUNNY?
I WAS JUST THINKING HOW FUN
DINNER WITH EVERYONE WAS.
HOW SO?
WELL, MY MOM DIED
WHEN I WAS LITTLE.
AND AFTER THAT, MY DAD SENT ME
TO LIVING AT BOARDING SCHOOL.
SO, I NEVER REALLY KNEW
WHAT IT WAS LIKE
TO HAVE A FAMILY DINNER.
AND I GUESS
I NEVER REALLY CARED.
BUT NOW? WHEN WE’RE ALL TOGETHER
LIKE THIS AND HAVING DINNER,
THE FOOD TASTES BETTER,
LIKE, WAY BETTER!
BUT WHAT SUCKS...
IS ALL THE PEEPING TOMS!
All: WE’RE SORRY!
THIS LOOKS AWESOME!
Both: THANKS FOR THE LUNCH!
Man: SCHA‐WING!
[ GLASS BREAKS ]
UH...
[ CHOMPING ]
RYUKO MATOI! I’M PRESIDENT OF
THE KNIFE THROWING CLUB!
JACK NAITO’S THE NAME!
YOU ASS!
YOU JUST RUINED MY LUNCH
WITH THAT DIRTY KNIFE!
START PRAYING!
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE,
KAMUI SENKETSU!
SCHA‐WING!
[ GROANS ]
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
AH. [ GIGGLES ]
[ LAUGHS ] NICE ONE.
NOW IT’S MY TURN.
I’M PRESIDENT OF
THE NANJING LILY CLUB,
KAGESABURO KAGERO!
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
[ SCREAMING ]
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU.
[ GIGGLES ]
I’M PRESIDENT OF
THE TIGHTROPE WALKING ‐‐
[ SCREAMS ]
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
[ SIGHS ]
[ GIGGLES ]
KNIFE THROWING, NANJING LILIES,
AND TIGHTROPE WALKING?
WHAT THE HELL?
WHERE ARE THESE SUPER‐SPECIFIC
CLUBS COMING FROM?
OH, THOSE GUYS ALL USED TO BE
THE ACROBATICS CLUB.
THEY DECIDED TO SPLIT UP
’CAUSE OF YOU, THOUGH.
’CAUSE OF ME?
YEP, REMEMBER?
IF SOMEONE BEATS YOU,
THEY GET PROMOTED TO THREE‐STAR.
BUT THEY HAVE TO BE
TWO‐STARS FIRST
AND THEY HAVE TO BE PRESIDENT
OF A CLUB FOR THAT.
SO THEY SPLIT UP
AND MADE NEW CLUBS.
AND THAT’S WHY
THEY’RE COMING AFTER YOU NOW.
JEEZ.
THEY’RE DESPERATE ’CAUSE
MORE STARS MEAN A BETTER LIFE.
THAT’S HOW IT WORKS HERE.
MAN, THAT’S SYSTEM’S
TOTALLY MESSED UP.
ON SECOND THOUGHT,
IT’S PERFECT!
WHAT’S THE MEANING OF THIS,
MATOI?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
CAN’T YOU READ?
I’M STARTING UP A FIGHT CLUB.
[ SCOFFS ] SURE, YOU ARE.
YOU BET YOUR ASS I AM.
YOU GUYS ARE FORCING PEOPLE
TO START ALL THESE LAME CLUBS
TO CHALLENGE ME,
SO, I’M STARTING MY OWN.
SAY HELLO TO THE PRESIDENT
OF THE FIGHT CLUB ‐‐ ME.
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK A CLUB
LIKE THAT WILL GET APPROVED?
Lady Satsuki: I APPROVE
THIS FIGHT CLUB OF YOURS.
HERE WE GO AGAIN WITH HER
UP THERE ON HER PEDESTAL.
I SEE YOU’VE DECIDED TO TAKE
PART IN MY SYSTEM, MATOI.
YEAH, RIGHT! MORE LIKE TAKE
APART YOUR SYSTEM
AND BRING IT DOWN
ON TOP OF YOU!
HMM. WE’LL SEE.
JUST TRY NOT TO LET IT
GO TO YOUR HEAD.
WHEN I’M THROUGH WITH YOU,
YOU’RE GONNA BE BEGGIN’
TO TELL ME EVERYTHING!
LET’S GET YOUR PAPERWORK
SORTED OUT.
WOW, YOU SWITCH GEARS FAST.
LADY SATSUKI MADE HER DECISION.
I MUST ACCEPT IT.
MATOI, ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO
BE PRESIDENT OF THIS CLUB?
YEP, BUT I DON’T NEED
A GOKU UNIFORM.
I GOT MY KAMUI.
SO, I’M GOOD.
UNDERSTOOD.
AS PRESIDENT, YOU WILL SUBMIT
A CLUB ACTIVITY LOG
EVERY FRIDAY.
[ GASPS ]
EACH MONTH YOU WILL FILE
AN EXPENSE REPORT
AND A REQUEST FOR
THE NEXT MONTH’S BUDGET.
YOU ALSO HAVE TO FILE
A CLUB ROOM REQUEST FORM,
A CLUB MEMBER ORGANIZATION
CHART, AND A LIST OF FAMILY.
AND YOU MUST ATTEND CLUB
PRESIDENT COUNCIL MEETINGS,
EVERY MORNING AT 7:00!
NO TARDIES!
[ CHUCKLES ]
UH, ACTUALLY,
MY BUDDY MAKO MANKANSHOKU’S
GONNA BE PRESIDENT.
WHAT?!
THAT WAS MEAN.
ALL MAKIN’ ME PRESIDENT
WITHOUT EVEN ASKING.
DON’T WORRY.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS,
OUR FIGHT CLUB’S ALL SET UP NOW.
[ WHIMPERING ]
AS SOON AS I START BEATING
THE OTHER CLUB PRESIDENTS,
OUR CLUB’S GONNA GET
MORE RESPECT,
AND THEN YOUR REP HERE’S
GONNA SKYROCKET!
WE’LL EVEN GET
A BETTER PLACE TO LIVE!
I KNOW, BUT I DON’T WANNA BE
PRESIDENT! WAH!
WHAT’S UP?!
I’M RYUKO MATOI
FROM THE FIGHT CLUB.
MAIMU OKURAHAMA, PRESIDENT OF
THE FOLK DANCE CLUB.
I’M HERE TO FIGHT YOU
AND TAKE YOUR UNIFORM!
KEEP DREAMIN’!
WE’RE GONNA DANCE ON
YOUR CORPSE!
[ BLOWS WHISTLE ]
[ JIG PLAYING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
HIGH SPEED MAYIM MAYIM!
LET’S DANCE!
HA, YOU’RE GONNA HAVE TO DO MORE
THAN DANCE IF YOU WANNA BEAT ME.
All:
AND KICK! AND KICK! AND KICK!
[ GRUNTS ]
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
ONE DOWN
AND A BUNCH MORE TO GO!
WHOO‐HOO.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SNORING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
MM.
WE’RE THE TOUKI BROTHERS
FROM THE POTTERY CLUB!
CLAY PSYCHOKINESIS, HO!
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
[ CRYING ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
FINALLY,
OUR VERY OWN CONDO.
AND WHAT A VIEW.
YEAH, IT’S GREAT.
AND I LIKE MY NEW CLINIC,
TOO.
I HOPE I DON’T LOSE ANY OF
MY BACK ALLEY PATIENTS, THOUGH.
AW, DAD, AS LONG AS
THE KIRYUINS SAY IT’S OKAY,
WHO GIVES A CRAP?!
[ GROWLING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
WE GET A BATHTUB
INSIDE THE HOUSE!
WE HAVE A WASHING MACHINE!
[ Singsongy ]
AND AN AUTOMATIC DISHWASHER!
WE’VE GOT AIR CONDITIONING, TOO!
[ LAUGHS ]
AND THERE’S ONE IN EVERY ROOM!
WE’VE GOT A FREAKING TOILET.
THIS IS UNBELIEVA‐‐
[ SIGHS ]
HEY, RYUKO,
ISN’T OUR ROOM THE BEST EVER?
I LOVE, LOVE, LOVE
BEING A ONE‐STAR!
I GUESS WHAT YOU SAID WAS TRUE.
MORE STARS DO MEAN
A BETTER LIFE.
BUT I DIDN’T THINK
IT’D HAPPEN SO FAST.
All: IT’S DINNERTIME!
NO MYSTERY MEAT CROQUETTES
TONIGHT! NO SIREE BOB!
TONIGHT, WE’RE HAVING CROQUETTES
FILLED WITH 100% REAL
BEEF AND PORK
FROM REAL COWS AND PIGS!
[ CRYING ]
MMM.
JUST ‐‐
THEY’RE SO FREAKING GOOD!
WHO’D HAVE THUNK THIS FAMILY
WOULD EVER GET A CHANCE
TO LIVE LIKE THIS?
THANK YOU, MAKO AND RYUKO,
WE OWE IT ALL TO YOU.
AW, JEEZ,
YOU DON’T NEED TO THANK US.
AS LONG AS YOU GUYS
ARE HAPPY,
THAT’S ALL THE THANKS
WE NEED.
MM‐HMM.
♪ KEEP YOUR FAITH,
RAISE YOUR LIVELY FACE ♪
♪ JUST GET RID OF
YOUR BROKEN WINGS ♪
[ AWKWARD LAUGHTER ]
Ryuko: WOULD YOU CUT IT OUT
WITH THE PEEPING?!
WE WERE JUST CLEANING
A WINDOW!
WHAT HE SAID!
IT’S LIKE A DREAM,
ISN’T IT?
EVERYONE’S SO HAPPY NOW.
FROM NOW ON,
I’M GONNA WORK EVEN HARDER.
I’LL BE
THE BEST CLUB PRESIDENT.
YEAH, I KNOW YOU WILL.
[ GIGGLING ]
AT LAST WE MEET.
I’M AIZENBO FUGUHARA,
PRESIDENT OF THE PING PONG CLUB!
CHECK OUT MY... [ GULPING ]
FLAMING SERVE!
[ ROARS ]
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
[ SCREAMS ]
I’M TATAMU OTTE, PRESIDENT OF
THE ORIGAMI CLUB! LET’S FI ‐‐
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
CONSIDERING FIGHT CLUB’S
ACHIEVEMENTS,
I MOVE YOU RAISE
OUR STANDARD OF LIVING!
I’LL PROTECT OUR LIFESTYLE,
’CAUSE IT’S WHAT MAKES
MY FAMILY HAPPY!
[ UTENSILS CLINKING ]
UGH, FRENCH FOOD AGAIN?
OH, HONEY.
ARE YOU HEADING OUT?
YEAH, I GOT A MEETING
WITH THE DOCTOR’S GUILD.
OH, RIGHT.
MM, REMEMBER THAT DIAMOND
NECKLACE I SHOWED YOU?
CAN I BUY IT?
SURE, HON, GO AHEAD.
IT LOOKED GREAT ON YOU.
HMM, I DIDN’T KNOW BACK ALLEY
DOCTORS HAD A GUILD.
[ GROWLS ]
MATARO...
OH, THAT’S RIGHT,
I TOTALLY FORGOT.
GOT INVITED TO A BIRTHDAY PARTY
TONIGHT. I’M OUTTA HERE.
WELL, I’LL BE HEADING OUT, TOO.
ENJOY YOUR DINNER, RYUKO.
YEAH, WILL DO.
SORRY, THE COUNCIL MEETING
RAN LATE AGAIN.
HEY, WHERE IS EVERYONE?
GUESS THEY ALL HAD
OTHER STUFF TO DO.
YEAH, I HEARD THAT.
OKAY, LET’S TALK SCHEDULE.
ONCE YOU’RE DONE EATING,
IT’S OFF TO THE GYM
FOR SOME WEIGHT TRAINING.
I GOT YOU BOOKED SOLID FOR
TOMORROW AND THE DAY AFTER, TOO.
WHAT?
THIS IS THE LIFE ‐‐
A HUGE MANSION,
ALL THIS STUFF.
WE’RE LIVING THE LIFE
OF LUXURY AND THEN SOME.
ISN’T IT GREAT?
EVERYONE’S SO HAPPY NOW.
LET’S WORK HARD
TO KEEP IT THAT WAY, OKAY?
UH, SURE.
WELL, I’M OFF TO BED.
NIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, RYUKO,
YOU’RE GONNA FIGHT EVERY
SINGLE PERSON IN THIS GYM!
WHAT?!
[ SHOUTING ]
EW.
[ FEEDBACK WHINES ]
[ Amplified voice ]
I’M MAKO MANKANSHOKU,
PRESIDENT OF THE FIGHT CLUB!
AND RYUKO MATOI
HEREBY CHALLENGES
ALL OF YOU TO A FIGHT!
ANY QUESTIONS? NO? FIGHT!
WAITER, BRING ME EVERY BOTTLE
OF ALCOHOL YOU GOT!
WAITER, BRING ME
ALL YOUR CHAMPAGNE!
All: WHOO‐HOO!
[ SIGHS ]
NICE HUSTLE, RYUKO.
COME ON, YOU GOT ANOTHER
FIGHT SCHEDULED ON THE FIELD.
[ GROANS ]
[ SIGHS ]
EXCUSE ME, MA’AM,
I WANNA BUY ALL YOUR CHOCOLATE.
THANK YOU, SIR.
[ GIRLS SQUEALING ]
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
[ HOWLS ]
[ ALL HOWL ]
[ GRUNTS ]
TOUCHDOWN!
AAH, AAH, AAH!
[ SIGHING ]
WHAT GIVES YOU THE RIGHT
TO BE HERE ANYWAY?
MY CLUB RESULTS
GIVE ME THE RIGHT.
THAT’S WHAT HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S
ALL ABOUT.
ONLY WINNERS GET TO MOVE UP
IN THE RANKS HERE, REMEMBER?
WE CAN’T LET THESE...PEOPLE
HAVE THEIR WAY, LADY SATSUKI.
UNLESS SOMETHING IS DONE,
MATOI AND MANKANSHOKU
WILL BE PART OF
THE COUNCIL’S INNER CIRCLE.
THE ONES WHO’VE BEEN
DEFEATED IN BATTLE
WERE OBVIOUSLY UNWORTHY
OF THEIR RANK.
LET ME FIGHT HER AGAIN.
I’LL PUT HER DOWN
FOR GOOD THIS TIME.
BE PATIENT.
WHY DID YOU AUTHORIZE
THEIR CLUB, M’LADY?
YOU MUST’VE HAD A REASON
FOR DOING SO.
JUST WATCH AND WAIT.
THEY’LL EITHER END UP
DESTROYING HONNOUJI ACADEMY,
OR THEY’LL ASSIMILATE
INTO IT.
WE’LL SOON FIND OUT.
IT SEEMS YOU’RE BACK TO EATING
DINNER ALONE, DOESN’T IT?
GUESS THE GUYS ARE BUSY, TOO.
Senketsu: RYUKO?
DID YOU THINK SUCCESS
WOULD BE LIKE THIS?
AT LAST, TODAY WE FACE OFF
AGAINST THE ELITE FOUR!
ONCE WE WIN, THE FIGHT CLUB
WILL STAND SUPREME
ON THE STUDENT COUNCIL!
WE’LL BE RESPECTED AND SHOWERED
WITH ALL KINDS OF LUXURIES!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
WELL, LOOK WHO DECIDED
TO SHOW UP.
TODAY’S
THE FINAL SHOWDOWN, SO ‐‐
WHAT’S THIS?
I’M QUITTIN’ THE CLUB.
HUH?! WHAT IS THIS?
A JOKE?
IT’S NOT A JOKE.
I’M DONE WITH IT.
BUT YOU CAN’T!
WE WORKED SO HARD FOR THIS.
IF YOU QUIT NOW, THEY’LL SEND
US BACK TO THE SLUMS!
I’M OKAY WITH THAT.
WELL, I’M NOT!
I’M NEVER GOING BACK THERE,
EVER! [ SCREAMS ]
WHAT THE...
PRESIDENT MANKANSHOK
OF THE FIGHT CLUB,
YOUR TWO‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM
IS IN THAT WARDROBE.
MY UNIFORM?
IF YOU WISH TO KEEP
ALL YOU’VE WORKED FOR,
YOU MUST FIGHT AND DEFEAT MATOI.
SAY WHAT?
AND IF YOU DEFEAT HER,
I WILL GRANT YOU
A THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM.
[ GASPS ] LADY SATSUKI...
TYPICAL!
ALL YOU DO IS PLAY DIRTY!
YOUR FRIEND DECIDES
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT.
YOU BITCH!
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE,
KAMUI SENKETSU!
SAVE YOUR STRENGTH.
YOU’RE GOING TO NEED IT
FOR YOUR OTHER OPPONENT.
FIGHT CLUB‐SPEC
TWO‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM!
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT,
MAKO MANKANSHOKU!
[ GRUNTS ]
WELL,
SO MUCH FOR FRIENDSHIP.
THAT’S OUR LADY SATSUKI.
SHE KNOWS HOW TO PLAY DIRTY.
DOES SHE NOW?
RYUKO...
SAY YOUR PRAYERS!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ METAL CLINKING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
UHH!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ EXPLOSION ]
CUT IT OUT, MAKO.
NO WAY! I CAN’T GO BACK
TO BEING POOR.
WE’RE LIVING THE GOOD LIFE,
AND WE’RE HAPPY NOW!
COME ON! SNAP OUT OF IT!
IT’S YOUR MOM AND DAD!
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
SHIT.
MY GOD. MAKO?
STAY BACK, GUYS.
MAKO’S NOT THINKING STRAIGHT.
DON’T TRY TO STOP HER
’CAUSE YOU MIGHT GET HURT!
HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU STANDING
AROUND FOR?! GO ON!
BEAT THE PISS OUT OF RYUKO!
[ GULPS ]
[ BARKING ]
SHE’S DISTRACTED! RUSH HER!
KNOCK HER LIGHTS OUT!
YOU’RE NOT EVEN GONNA TRY
TO STOP HER?! [ GRUNTING ]
SORRY ABOUT THIS, RYUKO,
BUT WE’D BE CRAZY TO WALK AWAY
FROM THIS LIFESTYLE.
DON’T WORRY, HON. WE’LL TIP
A 40 TO YOUR MEMORY.
[ SCREAMING ]
THIS IS HUMAN NATURE, MATOI.
PROSPERITY LEADS TO GREED,
GREED LEADS TO THEIR DOWNFALL.
ONE TASTE OF A LIFE OF AFFLUENCE
AND THEY’RE ENSLAVED ‐‐
SLAVES TO A SYSTEM
WHICH I’VE CREATED!
THEY ARE NOTHING MORE THAN PIGS,
PIGS IN HUMAN CLOTHING,
PIGS THAT MUST BE TAMED
BY FORCE!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ CHAIN SHATTERS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CLANK ]
[ EXPLOSION ]
[ GRUNTS ]
RYUKO, WHAT’S WRONG?
I’M FINE LIKE THIS.
THE HELL SHE POWER DOWN FOR?
SHE’S NUTS.
IS MATOI RISKING HER LIFE
ALL FOR THE SAKE OF A FRIEND?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ ALL SHOUTING AT ONCE ]
[ GRUNTING, GROANING ]
[ GRUNTS ] UHH!
[ SWORDS CLANKING ]
YOU’RE FINISHED!
[ PANTING ]
All: GET HER!
[ EXHALES ]
WHY...
WHY DON’T YOU GUYS
STOP ME?!
SHE’S GONNA DIE
IF I KEEP HITTING HER!
MY GOD, HOW CAN YOU JUST
SIT THERE AND WATCH
WHILE I’M TRYING TO KILL HER?!
WHAT KIND
OF PARENTS ARE YOU?!
WAIT, WHAT DID WE DO?
WHEN I GOT TO BE PRESIDENT,
I THOUGHT OUR LIVES WERE BETTER
’CAUSE EVERYONE LOOKED SO HAPPY.
[ CRYING ]
IT’S LIKE THE WHOLE FAMILY
WAS GLOWING WITH HAPPINESS,
BUT IT WAS ALL A LIE.
NONE OF IT WAS REAL AT ALL.
WE LET OURSELVES
BE BLINDED BY GREED.
THAT’S WHAT THE GLOW WAS!
IT WAS PLAIN OLD GREED
BURNING INSIDE US!
[ CRYING ]
WE’RE EVIL!
MOM, DAD, EVERYONE, AND SO AM I!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GASPS ]
I GUESS NOW WE KNOW THE REAL
POWER OF YOUR GOKU UNIFORM, HUH?
YOU KNOW, YOU COULD’VE KILLED ME
IF YOU WANTED, BUT YOU DIDN’T.
YOU KNEW SHE’D NEVER GO
THAT FAR.
THAT’S WHY YOU
DIDN’T FIGHT BACK.
OH, SHE WAS FIGHTIN’ HARD.
FIGHTIN’ ALL THAT
GREED INSIDE HER.
I’M SORRY.
I’M SO SORRY, RYUKO!
COME ON, LET’S END THIS.
MM‐HMM. [ SNIFFLES ]
♪ HALLELUJAH ♪
I HEREBY DECLARE
FIGHT CLUB IS DISBANDED!
I AM DEMOTING MYSELF
BACK TO BEING A NO‐STAR!
SEE THAT?! HUMANS AIN’T AS WEAK
AS YOU SAY THEY ARE!
THEY GOT THE STRENGTH TO DO
THE RIGHT THING WHEN THEY WANNA!
GO ON! DO IT!
WITH PLEASURE!
FINISHING MOVE!
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
HUH, NICELY DONE.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
AH...
HMM?
All: WE’RE SORRY, RYUKO!
I’M A GREEDY, NO‐GOOD BASTARD!
I HATE MYSELF!
I BEHAVED HORRIBLY!
IT’LL NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN!
I’M A GREEDY SON‐OF‐A‐BITCH!
NO OFFENSE, MOM!
All: WE’RE SO VERY SORRY!
ME, TOO, ME, TOO!
UH, DON’T SCREW ME OVER
LIKE THAT AGAIN, GOT IT?
All: GOT IT!
♪
WHAT TIME IS IT?
All: IT’S TIME FOR DINNER!
[ ALL CHOMPING ]
[ CHEWING LOUDLY ]
[ Mouth full ]
GOTTA HAND IT TO YOU, MOM,
NOTHIN’ BEATS
YOUR MYSTERY CROQUETTES.
Guts: CROQUETTES!
[ Mouth full ] YOU SAID IT!
THEY’RE THE BEST IN JAPAN!
[ Singsongy ]
SAVE ROOM FOR SECONDS.
MMM, AWESOME!
IT SEEMS THE FESTIVE DINNERS
YOU LIKE HAVE RETURNED.
YEP, THEY’RE WHAT BEING
A FAMILY’S ALL ABOUT.
[ CHOMPS ] MMM, MMM!
[ GUTS HOWLING ]
HOLD ON, WHAT?
I SAID, IF THE FIGHT CLUB
COULD DEFEAT THEIR OPPONENTS
SO EASILY,
THEN THE OTHER CLUBS
WEREN’T WORTHY TO BEGIN WITH.
WERE YOU TESTING THEM?
DON’T QUESTION THE MOTIVES
OF LADY SATSUKI.
EVERYTHING SHE DOES, SHE DOES
AFTER CAREFUL CONSIDERATION.
HE’S RIGHT, FOR I PLAN TO
REBUILD HANNOUJI ACADEMY’S ORDER
FROM THE GROUND UP,
AND THE FIRST STEP IS
CULLING THE UNWORTHY
FROM OUR RANKS.
M’LADY, YOU’RE NOT PLANNING
TO USE MATOI TO ROOT OUT
THE UNDESIRABLES HERE,
ARE YOU?
[ CHUCKLES ]
Senketsu: DISCIPLINARY
COMMITTEE CHAIR IRA GAMAGOORI,
SATSUKI KIRYUIN’S
RIGHT‐HAND MAN.
HE VOWS TO GET HIS LICENSE
SO HE CAN BE HER CHAUFFER.
NOW THAT’S LOYALTY,
BUT WILL HIS DRIVING SKILLS
BE UP TO THE TASK?
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"I’LL WIPE MY OWN TEARS."