DON’T!
PLEASE, DON’T!
FOR GOD’S SAKE, STOP!
SENKETSU!
[ SNORING ]
[ SIREN WAILING ]
HUH?
[ SCREAMS ]
WE’RE GONNA BE LATE,
WE’RE GONNA BE LATE!
HURRY UP AND GET DRESSED, RYUKO!
OH, WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
JEEZ, CHILL OUT, MAKO.
IT’S LIKE
4:00 IN THE MORNING.
Man: HELP ME!
I’M BEING MURDERED! HELP!
HI, MAKO.
I HAVE YOUR LUNCH ALL BAGGED UP
AND WAITING IN THE KITCHEN!
SE ‐‐ SENKETSU!
GOOD MORNING, RYUKO!
SLEEP WELL?
YES, MA’AM, I DID!
EXCUSE ME, BUT IS THAT
MY UNIFORM YOU’RE WASHING?
IT SURE IS, HON!
I’M JUST GIVING IT ONE
LAST SCRUB FOR GOOD MEASURE.
I CAN’T BELIEVE
HOW FILTHY IT WAS!
THANKS, MA’AM.
BUT I‐I CAN TAKE IT FROM HERE ‐‐
NO, YOU WON’T!
[ GROANS ]
WHAT’S YOUR JOB AS A STUDENT?
TO GET EDUCATED!
OH!
WHAT’S MY JOB AS A MOM?
TO DO THE LAUNDRY!
IS THAT CLEAR?
[ GROANS ]
NOW EAT YOUR BREAKFAST!
OW!
AND GET TO SCHOOL!
AH!
BUT I CAN’T GO TO SCHOOL
WITHOUT MY UNIFORM!
[ SIREN WAILING ]
AAH! I TOTALLY FORGOT
TO KEEP PANICKING!
COME ON, RYUKO!
IT’S THE BIG DAY!
BIG DAY?
Both: NO WAY!
IT’S YOUR BIG DAY?
YOU’RE FINE IN YOUR P. J. s!
JUST MOVE!
AAH!
DON’T WORRY! WE’LL DROP
YOUR UNIFORM OFF LATER!
YEAH, WE GOT THIS!
WAIT, RYUKO!
THESE ASSASSINS CAN’T HEAR ME!
YOU’RE THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN!
AAH!
HUH?
PLEASE DON’T LEAVE ME!
I’M BEGGING YOU! [ SCREAMS ]
HANG IN THERE, SENKETSU!
SENKETSU? WHAT’S THAT?
NO WAY, DID YOU GIVE
YOUR UNIFORM A NAME?
BOY,
YOU MUST BE REALLY LONELY!
BUT, WAIT!
EVEN MORE REASON
TO GET YOU TO SCHOOL!
WE NEED TO FIND YOU
SOME FRIENDS, QUICK!
BUT EVERYONE
WANTS TO KILL ME!
INCOMING!
I’M SORRY, SENKETSU!
RYUKO’S ABANDONED ME!
OH, THAT...FEELS NICE.
THE WRINKLES ARE MELTING AWAY.
OH. [ CHUCKLES ]
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT’S WITH EVERYONE?
THEY’RE ACTING LIKE
A BUNCH OF LEMMINGS.
TODAY’S WHEN THE NO‐STARS OF
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
RISK THEIR LIVES
TO GET TO SCHOOL.
IT’S A DAY OF RECKONING.
IT’S A DAY OF DEATH. IT’S ‐‐
NO TARDIES DAY!
HUH?
♪ HALLELUJAH ♪
WAIT. NO TARDIES DAY?
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
[ GASPS ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
DO I DETECT SOME CONFUSION,
RYUKO MATOI?
BITE ME, ELITE JERK!
MY TITLE IS THE CHAIR OF
THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE!
AND MY NAME IS IRA GAMAGOORI!
PAY ATTENTION, NEW GIRL!
YOU ARE PARTICIPATING IN
NO‐TARDIES DAY.
ONCE, EVERY SEMESTER,
YOU WILL BE REQUIRED
TO RUN AN OBSTACLE COURSE,
DESIGNED BY
THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE!
IT BEGINS AT 4:00 A. M.,
WHEN THE SIREN GOES OFF
IN THE SLUMS.
NO‐STAR STUDENTS
WILL THEN HAVE TO EVADE
THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE’S
TRAPS ON THE WAY TO SCHOOL.
THE OBJECTIVE IS TO MAKE IT
TO THE ACADEMY
BY THE THE FIRST BELL TOLLS
AT 8:30 AM!
BUT IF YOU HAPPEN TO BE LATE,
YOU WILL BE EXPELLED ON THE ‐‐
WHAT THE HELL!
THAT IS NOT
A REGULATION UNIFORM!
BUT MY KAMUI’S STILL
IN THE LAUNDRY!
IT’S GETTING DELIVERED!
HA! SPARE THE EXCUSES.
THE EVIDENCE IS CLEAR ‐‐
YOU LEFT FOR SCHOOL
IN A SLOVENLY OUTFIT.
YOU’RE A DISGRACE
TO THE ACADEMY AND LADY SATSUKI.
IT’S A MORTAL INSULT!
IT IS SO NOT!
HMM?
SHE WAS ASLEEP
TILL A MINUTE AGO!
IT’S NORMAL FOR PEOPLE TO WEAR
PAJAMAS WHEN THEY SLEEP,
ISN’T IT?
IT IS AND YOU KNOW IT
AND YOU CAN’T DENY IT.
MAYBE YOU DON’T KNOW ABOUT
PAJAMAS, IS THAT IT?
DON’T YOU WEAR THEM
WHEN YOU SLEEP?
NO, I SLEEP IN THE NUDE.
IF YOU SLEEP LIKE THAT,
YOU’LL CATCH COLD!
NUDE? AS IN...NAKED?
WHAT HAPPENS IF THERE’S
AN EMERGENCY
AND PEOPLE NEED PUNISHING?
YOU’D BE AT HOME IN BED!
WELL, I ‐‐
FROM NOW ON, PLEASE WEAR PAJAMAS
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE!
NO‐STAR, WHAT’S YOUR NAME?
MY NAME IS MAKO MANKANSHOKU!
AND MY JAMMIES HAVE MOUNT FUJI,
TWO HAWKS,
AND THREE EGGPLANTS ON ’EM!
MANKANSHOKU,
I’LL REMEMBER THAT.
MATOI! I’VE DECIDED TO OVERLOOK
YOUR CHOICE IN WARDROBE FOR NOW.
BUT I’M CURIOUS AS TO HOW YOU
THINK YOU’LL BE ABLE TO
REACH THE SCHOOL WITHOUT
YOUR PRECIOUS KAMUI!
[ BEEPS ]
BEHOLD!
THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE’S
IMPREGNABLE BARRIER!
OH, MY GOD!
LOOK, RYUKO!
IT’S LIKE THE CITY’S BEEN
TURNED INTO AN AMUSEMENT PARK!
I’VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THIS!
AH!
YOU SEE WHAT TIME IT IS?!
WE’VE ONLY GOT THREE HOURS
BEFORE FIRST PERIOD!
HUH, THE WAY HE TALKED IT UP,
I WAS EXPECTIN’ SOMETHIN’
SCARIER.
ALL RIGHT THEN,
I’M UP FOR THIS.
YOU HEAR THAT?
I’M GONNA BUST THROUGH
ALL THE LAME TRAPS YOU MADE!
WE’LL SEE!
STUDENTS!
YOUR COMMUTE BEGINS...NOW!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
STICK CLOSE TO ME, MAKO!
OKAY!
[ SCREAMING ]
THEY’RE NOT WASTING ANY TIME
ON THE TRAPS!
UP YOU GO!
[ CHIMES ]
HUH?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
CONGRATULATIONS ON CLEARING
THE FIRST CHECKPOINT.
I FORGOT TO MENTION ‐‐
USE OF THE NO‐STAR CABLE CARS
IS PROHIBITED.
OBEY THE RULES AND STICK TO
THE PRESCRIBED ROUTE!
SEE YOU UP AT THE ACADEMY...
MAYBE!
999 MORE TRAPS TO GO?
THAT’S MORE THAN USUAL!
HE’S TRYIN’ TO PSYCH US OUT!
COME ON, MAKO!
UHH!
AAH!
OH GOD, MY ARM!
LOOK, IT’S OUR CLASSMATE,
MAIKO OGURE!
UH, ARE YOU OKAY?!
CAN YOU GET UP? CAN YOU MOVE?
WHY, IF IT ISN’T MANKANSHOKU!
AND YOU’RE MATOI,
THE NEW GIRL IN CLASS.
I CAUGHT MY ARM IN
THAT HORRIBLE TRAP.
IT HURTS, BUT I’LL LIVE!
IT’LL TAKE A LOT MORE
THAN THIS TO STOP ME!
UHH!
WHOA, TAKE IT EASY!
HEY, RYUKO, SHE CAN’T MAKE IT
ALL BY HERSELF.
COME ON, LET’S TAKE HER
UP TO SCHOOL WITH US!
LEAVE ME!
I’D SLOW YOU DOWN,
SO JUST LEAVE ME HERE AND GO!
YEAH, YOU GOT A POINT THERE.
WELL, GUESS WE’LL BE SEEIN’ YA.
AAH! THE PAIN!
G‐GOTTA BLOCK IT OUT!
I CAN MAKE IT ON MY OWN!
DAMN THIS USELESS ARM!
RYUKO!
JEEZ.
ALL RIGHT, YOU WIN.
HANG ON TIGHT, OKAY?
YAY!
WE’LL ALL GET TO SCHOOL
TOGETHER!
THANK YOU, MATOI!
EH, NO WORRIES.
YOU’RE A GIRL WHO DOESN’T
GIVE UP. I GOTTA RESPECT THAT.
LOOK! YOU SEE WHAT I SEE?
[ ORGAN PLAYING BACH’S
"TOCCATA AND FUGUE IN D MINOR" ]
TH‐TH‐TH ‐‐
THAT’S THE SECOND CHECKPOINT!
HOW THE HECK ARE
WE SUPPOSED TO GET UP THERE?
[ CHUCKLES ]
OH, WE’RE SO SCREWED.
THIS’D BE CAKE
IF I HAD SENKETSU.
COMIN’ THROUGH!
BACK‐ALLEY BARAZO’S
MAKIN’ A HOUSE CALL!
UNLESS YOU WANT A CAR UP YOUR
ASS, GET OUTTA THE WAY, MAN!
WHOA!
THAT’S RYUKO UP THERE!
HEY! WE GOT YOUR UNIFORM!
[ GRUNTS ] I CAN’T HOLD ON.
MAIKO, DON’T LET GO, OKAY?!
IT’S NO USE.
[ SCREAMS ]
NO, GRAB SOMETHIN’ ELSE!
ANYTHING ELSE!
[ SCREAMING ]
YOU MANIAC!
WHY DON’T YOU WATCH
WHERE YOU’RE DRIVING?!
DON’T DIE ON ME, DAD!
TOO LATE, SON.
I’M DONE FOR.
LISTEN, DO YOUR POOR, DYIN’
OLD MAN ONE LAST FAVOR.
TAKE THIS AND ‐‐
YOU GOT IT!
AAH!
I’LL GET THIS UNIFORM
TO RYUKO SAFE AND SOUND!
I LOVE YOU, DAD.
REST IN PIECES!
HANG ON, RYUKO! I’M COMING!
[ PANTING ]
OWIE!
KEEP MOVING!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ PANTING ]
HUH?
[ SCREAMING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WHOA! SWISS CHEESE!
CHEESE, CHEESE, CHEESE, CHEESE,
CHEESE, CHEESE, CHEESE, CHEESE.
NO, MAKO! LOOK OUT! MOVE!
WHAT’S A PIE DOING ‐‐
[ SPLAT ]
CAN I LICK YOUR FACE, RYUKO?
[ GRUNTS, SCREAMS ]
I GOTCHA ‐‐ OH!
ROCK THOSE CROCS, RYUKO!
DAMN IT! I COULD REALLY USE
SENKETSU RIGHT NOW!
I’M COMIN’, RYUKO!
WHOA, SPEAK OF THE HOTTIE!
GOING UP!
[ GRUNTS ] MY ARM!
GRAB ON!
WHOA, WHOA!
[ SCREAMS ]
THANK YOU, GOD. THANK YOU, GOD.
AAH! UHH.
DOES ANYONE WATCH WHERE
THEY’RE GOING AROUND HERE?!
GUTS, THAT’S IT.
I’M DONE FOR, BOY.
LISTEN, YOU’RE TOP DOG NOW
SO DO ME A SOLID AND ‐‐
GUTS, THAT’S ‐‐
OW, THAT HURTS! DON’T BITE SO
HARD, YOU VILE HELLHOUND!
GUTS!
WHAT TIME IS IT?
IT’S 8:00.
THERE’S ONLY 30 MINUTES LEFT.
WE’LL NEVER MAKE IT.
WE CAN’T QUIT NOW!
IF WE DON’T GET UP THERE,
I WON’T BE ABLE TO GO
TO SCHOOL ANYMORE!
HEY, MAIKO?
WHAT ARE THEY DOIN’?
PSEUDO‐HOMEROOM.
IT’S WHERE ALL THE KIDS
WHO GAVE UP
TRYING TO
MAKE IT TO SCHOOL GATHER.
THEY CAN’T FACE THE REALITY
THEY’LL BE KICKED OUT OF SCHOOL
AND THEIR HOMES TOMORROW.
SO THEY SIT THERE LIKE ZOMBIES
AND TAKE ROLL CALL.
THOSE POOR BASTARDS.
OKAY, AND BY THE LOOKS
OF THOSE CONDOS,
SOMETHING TELLS ME THEY’RE GONNA
BE SUPER‐TOUGH TO GET PAST.
HEY, LOOK!
IT’S A SCHOOL BUS!
[ EXPLOSIONS ]
GREAT. A MINEFIELD.
IT CAN TAKE IT,
IT’S ARMOR‐PLATED.
THAT’S ONE‐STAR PRIVILEGES
FOR YA.
IT’S PASSING THE CHECKPOINT!
OH, MAN,
THEY GOT IT SO EASY!
I WANNA RIDE IN IT, TOO!
I WANNA! I WANNA!
OH! THE PAIN!
[ HORN HONKS ]
DAMN IT,
GET OUTTA THE ROAD, NO‐STAR!
MOVE YOUR ‐‐ AH!
[ SPITS ]
ALL ABOARD!
[ FIGHTING SOUNDS ]
QUICK QUESTION, MAIKO,
DO YOU HAVE A LICENSE TO DRIVE?
THE KIRYUIN FAMILY OWNS
EVERYTHING IN HONNOU TOWN.
SO UNLESS LADY SATSUKI
SAYS OTHERWISE,
I DON’T NEED A LICENSE TO DRIVE!
I’M NOT LOSING THIS THING!
I’LL SHOW ’EM ALL
WHAT A NO‐STAR CAN DO
WHEN THEY PUSH ’EM FAR ENOUGH!
ALL RIGHT! LOOK AT ME!
OKAY, LET’S MOVE OUT,
MS. BADASS.
I GOT A HIJACKED BUS
WITH NO‐STARS AT THE WHEEL.
THEY’RE CLEARING MINES WITH IT,
OVER.
MAN: Copy that.
You have permission to eliminate
with extreme prejudice. Over.
OKEY‐DOKEY!
[ GUNFIRE ]
[ SCREAMING ]
AH! YOU GOTTA BE FREAKIN’
KIDDING ME!
HOW ARE PREPARATIONS COMING
FOR THE LAST TRAP?
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
HUH?
[ GUNFIRE ]
THEY’RE NOT LETTIN’ UP!
THANK GOD
THIS THING’S ARMOR‐PLATED!
TIME FOR A COUNTERATTACK!
WITH WHAT?
WITH THIS!
HUH?
HUH? HUH?
OH!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ LAUGHS ] RYUKO, YOU GOTTA
GET UP HERE AND TRY THIS!
GET DOWN, MAKO!
IT’S NOT SAFE!
OH, YES!
R.P.G.!
RETRACT THE TURRET!
[ SCREAMING ]
I LIKE RIDING IN CONVERTIBLES!
A LITTLE FURTHER AND WE’RE IN
THE TWO‐STAR DISTRICT!
INCOMING R. P. G. s!
PUNCH IT!
[ SCREAMING ]
HEY, GUYS, LOOK IT!
IT’S THE SCHOOL! WE DID IT!
WE MADE IT!
WE STILL HAVE 15 MINUTES
BEFORE FIRST PERIOD STARTS.
AWESOME, PIECE OF CAKE.
PIECE OF CAKE.
MAIKO, YOU ROCK SO HARD!
COULDN’T OF DONE IT WITHOUT YA!
NOT AT ALL.
I WAS JUST BACKING YOU UP.
BUT STILL, YOU’RE SWEET.
OH, SHUCKS.
NOW WE’RE FRIENDS, YAY!
♪ COME ON ♪
WHOO!
LOOK AT THAT, RYUKO!
IT’S GUTS, AND HE’S BRINGING
YOUR UNIFORM!
HEY, GUTS! OVER HERE!
GUTS!
WHY IS GUTS BRINGING IT?
JEEZ, YOUR DAD’S GOT
THE GOOFIEST IDEAS.
OH, THE PAIN!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GROANS ]
♪ HALLELUJAH ♪
[ SCREAMS ]
OH, WE’RE SLIDING!
STOP, YOU CUR! STOP!
WAIT, GUTS!
WHERE’RE YOU GOING?
OH! [ SHUDDERS ]
THE HELL?
WHY’D YOU DO THAT, MAIKO?
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU SHOULDN’T HAVE LET
YOUR GUARD DOWN, RYUKO.
I MEAN, RYUKO MATOI!
I’VE BEEN WAITING AGES
FOR THIS MOMENT!
BUT, MAIKO!
YOU FELL FOR MY INJURED
NO‐STAR CLASSMATE DISGUISE!
BUT MY TRUE IDENTITY...
IS THE HEAD OF TRAP DEVELOPMENT
FOR THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE!
MAIKO OGURE!
TRAP DEVELOPMENT, HUH?
HUH?
YES, EXACTLY!
I’M AN UNDERCOVER OPERATIVE
AT THE ACADEMY,
WHOSE JOB IS TO SPY ON STUDENTS
AND DEVELOP DIABOLICAL TRAPS
TO TRAP THEM!
MY WORLD REVOLVES AROUND
DESIGNING TRAPS!
BUT AFTER DOING IT SO LONG,
I’M SO OVER THAT LIFE!
WHEN I HEARD YOUR CONVERSATION
WITH GAMAGOORI TODAY
OVER THE SURVEILLANCE FEED,
I HAD A FLASH OF INSPIRATION.
THE ONLY WAY TO CHALLENGE
LADY SATSUKI,
IS TO HAVE A KAMUI
THAT’S AS POWERFUL AS HERS.
I DECIDED TO STEAL YOUR KAMUI
RIGHT THEN AND THERE!
WITH YOUR UNIFORM,
WHY, I COULD BE A TWO STAR!
NO, BE ONE OF THE FOUR ELITES ‐‐
WAIT! NO!
I COULD STEAL THE THRONE
FROM LADY SATSUKI HERSELF!
I’LL BE THE NEW EMPRESS OF
HONNOUJI ACADEMY!
AND I WILL GORGE ON
ALL THE LUXURIES
THE ACADEMY HAS TO OFFER!
OH, I CAN HARDLY WAIT!
MAIKO, IF THERE’S ONE THING
I CAN’T STAND,
IT’S A FREAKIN’ LIAR.
MAIKO!
♪ HALLELUJAH ♪
GIVE IT BACK! THAT’S RYUKO’S
UNIFORM, NOT YOURS!
SHE NEEDS TO HAVE IT! ’CAUSE
WHEN SHE PUTS ON HER UNIFORM,
SHE TRANSFORMS! LIKE THIS!
SHE ACTS ALL SHY,
BUT SHE REALLY LIKES IT!
IN FACT,
SHE LOVES WHEN IT HAPPENS.
OH, THAT’S RIGHT,
HER TRANSFORMATION SEQUENCE.
I’M GONNA TRY IT RIGHT NOW!
REMOVE, APPLY.
WHAT?!
[ LAUGHS ]
WHATEVER.
IF YOU THINK YOU CAN TRANSFORM
SO EASY, KNOCK YOURSELF OUT,
YOU DECEITFUL BITCH.
I DID IT.
FU ‐‐
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE!
KAMUI SENKETSU!
OH, COME ON!
SHE FIGURES OUT THE LIFE FIBER
SEEKING CRAP ON THE FIRST TRY?
HOW’D SHE DO THAT?!
Senketsu: FORGIVE ME, RYUKO,
BUT THIS GIRL HAS NO SHAME.
[ CACKLES ]
IF IT MEANS HAVING POWER,
IF IT MEANS GETTING TO BE
TOP DOG,
I’LL GLADLY TAKE OFF
ALL MY CLOTHES!
YES! IT’S LETTING INTO ME ‐‐
THE STRENGTH, THE POWER,
THE STRE‐POWER!
NOW, WHO SHOULD I TRY
MY NEW STRE‐POWERS OUT ON?
I KNOW! HOW ’BOUT I START
WITH YOU?!
MAKO!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT’S GOING ON?
WHY CAN’T I PUNCH HER?
[ GRUNTS ]
THE HELL’S HER PROBLEM?
IT’S LIKE MY BODY’S
TURNED TO STONE!
WHAT’S CAUSING THIS?
SENKETSU! IT’S YOU!
[ SCREAMS ] NO, WAIT!
I WAS JUST KIDDING!
I SWEAR, IT WAS A JOKE!
I’M SORRY I TRICKED YOU.
WHAT’S UP? I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GONNA TRY OUT YOUR NEW POWER.
AAH, PLEASE, NO,
I’LL GIVE IT BACK!
WHAT’S WRONG WITH THIS THING?
IT WON’T LET ME MOVE!
GET OFF ME, DAMN IT!
STUPID, BROKEN, DAMN, STUPID,
GET OFF ME!
IT JUST GOT WASHED.
SO MAYBE IT’S GOT TOO MUCH
STARCH IN IT.
YOU DUMBASS!
[ GROANS ]
[ GROANING ]
AAH!
UGH, HER BLOOD
WAS ABSOLUTELY FILTHY. [ SPITS ]
I’M SORRY I WAS LATE.
NAH, IT’S COOL.
IT’S NOT LIKE YOU CHEATED
ON ME OR ANYTHING.
[ SCREAMS ]
LOOK WHAT TIME IT IS!
WE GOT FIVE MINUTES
BEFORE THE BELL RINGS!
WE HAVE TO HURRY.
I DON’T WANNA BE LATE!
I DON’T WANNA BE EXPELLED!
HURRY, HURRY, HURRY, HURRY ‐‐
OWIE.
I HIT MY HEAD ON NOTHING.
WHAT THE...
[ GROANS ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT THE HELL’S GOING ON
AROUND HERE?
[ LAUGHING ] I GOTCHA!
I HAD A FEELING
YOU’D GET PAST ME,
SO I DESIGNED THIS TRAP
AS A CONTINGENCY.
A FAKE SCHOOL!
SO LONG, SUCKAS.
[ SCREAMING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
IT’S ALL OVER FOR YOU.
I CALL THIS TRAP
"BEGIN AT THE BEGINNING,"
MY MASTERPIECE.
ONCE IT STARTS ROLLING,
THERE’S NO STOPPING IT!
LIKE HELL, IT’S OVER!
I’LL JUST COME OVER THERE AND
BEAT THE LIVING HELL OUT OF YOU!
AND I’LL KEEP RIGHT ON
BEATING YOU
TILL YOU TELL ME
HOW TO STOP IT!
NOT IF I’M DEAD, I WON’T.
ARE YOU CRAZY? GET BACK HERE!
I MIGHT’VE FAILED TO STEAL
YOUR KAMUI,
BUT I’M STILL A MEMBER
OF THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE.
MY WORK IS DONE HERE,
AND I DIE KNOWING
YOU’LL HAVE A TARDY
ON YOUR PERMANENT RECORD.
IT’S MY FINAL ACT OF DEFIANCE.
YOU DIDN’T BEAT ME!
FOR HONNOUJI ACADEMY!
KIDDING. [ GIGGLES ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WE’RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
THIS THING’S COMING APART.
HELP ME, RYUKO! HELP!
MAKO!
HURRY! PUT ME ON!
OH, RIGHT, I FORGOT!
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE!
KAMUI SENKETSU!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ COUGHS ] WHAT THE HELL?
HOW DID WE GET ALL THE WAY
DOWN HERE?
THIS AIN’T NOWHERE
NEAR THE STARTING LINE.
Senketsu:
EVEN WITH MY HELP,
YOU’LL NEVER MAKE IT UP THERE
IN TIME. YOU’LL BE LATE.
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS THE STATION
WHERE THE NON‐STOP EXPRESS
ROPE THINGAMAJIGGIES ARE
THAT ONLY THE RICH KIDS CAN RIDE
TO GET UP TO SCHOOL.
OH, I ALWAYS WANTED TO RIDE
IN ONE!
IT’S NON‐STOP?
HEY, YOU NO‐STARS
AREN’T ALLOWED IN ‐‐
SHUT YOUR HOLE AND GET THIS
THING MOVING! STEP ON IT!
[ SCREAMS ]
HURRY, MAKO! GET IN!
WAIT, WE HAVE TO PAY THE FARE
TO RIDE IT FIRST.
RATS, NO MONEY! OH, WELL.
I’LL JUST LEAVE SOME OF THE
YUMMY CROQUETTES MY MOM MADE.
OH, WHO CARES!
JUST GET IN HERE ALREADY!
YAY! I’M RIDING IT!
IT’S LIKE A DREAM COME TRUE!
HOW MUCH TIME WE GOT?
ONE MINUTE.
AFTER THAT, WE’RE LATE,
AND EXPELLED.
NO WAY!
WE’RE GONNA BE EXPELLED!
I’M GONNA GET US
TO OUR HOMEROOM ON TIME
EVEN IF IT KILLS US!
DAMN IT, I HAD ALL THAT POWER
IN MY HANDS.
OH, WELL, IT’S COOL.
I’LL JUST PLAY
THE GOOD SUBORDINATE.
ANOTHER CHANCE’LL COME ALONG
SOON ENOUGH.
I SAW AND HEARD EVERYTHING,
OGURE.
GAMAGOORI!
SO YOU WANTED TO OVERTHROW
LADY SATSUKI, EH?
YOU HAVE MORE AMBITION
THAN BRAINS!
PLEASE, SIR, I WAS WRONG.
FORGIVE ME!
NEVER!
YOU’RE EXPELLED!
YOU DON’T DESERVE TO
ATTEND HONNOUJI ACADEMY!
GET OUT OF MY SIGHT!
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ SHUDDERS ]
HMM?
DAMN HER.
WE’VE ONLY GOT 30 SECONDS!
IN THAT CASE,
WE WON’T STOP AT THE STATION.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
OKAY, NEXT IS MATOI.
RYUKO MATOI?
[ CRASH ]
[ CLATTER ]
[ HEEL CLACKS ]
[ CHAIR SCRAPES ]
UH, RYUKO MATOI.
[ EXHALES SLOWLY ]
[ SNORING ]
HERE.
Senketsu: THE MAN
IS USUALLY SILENT,
BUT WHEN HE CORNERS HIS PREY,
HE SAYS ONLY ONE THING,
"TAKE OFF YOUR CLOTHES."
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"TRIGGER."