TODAY, WE EMBARK ON
THE COMPLETE OVERHAUL
OF THE STUDENT COUNCIL!
IF YOU PARTICIPATE,
YOU WILL HAVE FREE REIGN
TO ATTACK YOUR PEERS.
THERE ARE NO RESTRICTIONS
ON WEAPONS OR TACTICS.
THOSE WHO SURVIVE WILL MEET HERE
IN SEVEN DAYS.
THESE SURVIVORS WILL THEN FIGHT
TO CLAIM THEIR SOCIAL STANDING!
A FIGHT FOR CHANGE!
AN ELECTION IN THE FORM
OF A BATTLE ROYALE!
ELECTION, MY ASS.
UNLIKE TRADITIONAL ELECTIONS,
YOU WILL NOT CHOOSE SOMEONE
TO REPRESENT YOU!
YOU WILL REPRESENT YOURSELVES!
YOUR STATUS! YOUR STRENGTH!
YOUR WAY OF LIFE!
IN SEVEN DAYS, AT 8:30 A. M.,
THE SURVIVORS
WHO HAVE ASSEMBLED HERE
WILL HAVE A SUDDEN DEATH RUNOFF!
AND IF YOU EMERGE VICTORIOUS,
I WILL PERSONALLY GRANT YOU
A BRAND‐NEW GOKU UNIFORM!
NOW,
STUDENTS OF HONNOUJI ACADEMY,
FIGHT!
BEGIN, IORI.
YES, M’LADY.
ACTIVATE THE HIGH VELOCITY
LIFE FIBER JAMMING EMISSION.
Aikuro: THAT COCOON’S MADE
OF FINELY CHOPPED LIFE FIBERS,
ROTATING AT ABOUT
A HUNDRED METERS PER SECOND.
[ SNORING ]
YOU CAN STAB IT,
SHOOT IT, NUKE IT.
THAT DAMN THING’S
PRETTY MUCH IMPENETRABLE.
EVEN WITH SENKETSU’S HELP,
I DOUBT YOU’LL BREAK THROUGH
THAT COCOON.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS GONNA BE
MY CHANCE TO GET AT HER.
BUT NO, SHE’S GOTTA
WHIP EVERYONE UP INTO A FRENZY
AND SIT IN HER BUBBLE!
IT’S ALL PART OF THE PLAN.
SHE RULES THIS PLACE
WITH AN IRON FIST.
BUT SHE KNEW AS SOON AS SHE TOOK
HERSELF OUT OF THE EQUATION,
IT’D BE ANARCHY.
SEE?
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
I SWEAR, I’M SO SICK OF HER.
AAH!
MAN, THIS IS CRAZY.
WHY THE HELL
IS SHE DOING THIS?
SHE’S TEARING APART
THE SYSTEM SHE MADE.
SHE ALWAYS TAKES THINGS
TO THE EXTREME.
TEAR IT DOWN
AND BUILD IT BACK UP.
THAT’S LADY SATSUKI IN NUTSHELL!
WHATEVS. AT LEAST IT GIVES US
AN EXCUSE FOR SOME DOWNTIME.
GOOD IDEA.
I THINK I’LL TAKE
A FEW DAYS OFF.
[ KEY JANGLES ]
SEE YOU NEXT WEEK. 8:30 SHARP.
YOU HEAR THAT?
SOUNDED LIKE A CAR KEY.
GOOD EARS. HE JUST GOT
HIS DRIVER’S LICENSE.
LADY SATSUKI NEEDED A CHAUFFEUR,
SO HE TOLD HER HE’D DO IT.
HIS LOYALTY IS IMPRESSIVE.
OKAY, I’LL SEE YOU BOYS
IN SEVEN DAYS.
I SERIOUSLY DOUBT
ANY OF US SUCKS SO BAD
WE WON’T MAKE IT
TO THE SUDDEN DEATH RUNOFF.
[ ALL GROANING ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ THUD ]
THE LOINCLOTH’S MINE!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ GROUND RATTLES ]
GOSH. THINGS ARE SURE CRAZY
IN TOWN TODAY.
HOT! [ WHIMPERS ]
Ryuko: WHAT’S EVERYONE
SITTING AROUND,
LOOKING ALL PHILOSOPHICAL FOR?
OH, YOU KNOW,
JUST THINKING ABOUT
ALL THE GOOD STUFF
WE LEARNED RECENTLY,
LIKE HOW INSTANT GRATIFICATION
AIN’T ALL IT’S CRACKED UP TO BE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
"PATIENCE IS A VIRTUE."
SEE, IF I WAIT TILL EVERYONE’S
TIRED FROM FIGHTING,
I’LL HAVE EASIER PICKINS ‐‐
POCKET PICKINS, THAT IS.
MATARO! YOU LITTLE...
NO!
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO, UH...
CAN I USE YOUR SCOOTER?
I GOT IT FOR YOU.
SCAMMED IT FROM THE GUY
WHO OWNS THE SCOOTER SHOP.
[ Singsongy ] DRIVE SAFE!
GOING ANYPLACE SPECIAL TODAY?
NOT REALLY.
SO YOU’RE JUST
TOOLING AROUND THEN?
IN THAT CASE, I’M COMING, TOO!
READY? SET?
GO!
Senketsu: UHH!
HEY, EASY!
I’M GONNA HOLD ON TIGHT.
[ SIGHS ] OH, WHAT THE HELL?
SUCK IT UP, SENKETSU.
WE’RE HEADING OUT.
[ Strained voice ]
C‐CAN’T BREATHE!
YOU GONNA FIGHT
IN THIS THING, TOO?
NAH, I’M A NO‐STAR.
THERE’S NO POINT, YA KNOW?
AND BESIDES,
IF I DON’T FIGHT,
IT’S LIKE GETTING A VACATION
FOR A WEEK!
YOU GOT A POINT THERE.
ME AND THE FAMS ARE GONNA BE
CHEERING YOU ON
IN THE SUDDEN DEATH RUNOFF,
SO KICK BUTT!
[ CHUCKLES ] ROGER THAT.
WHERE ARE WE?
MY DAD’S PLACE.
NO WAY. THIS DUMP?
THEN I GUESS YOU’RE POOR
JUST LIKE ME, AREN’T YA?
NO, I DIDN’T LIVE HERE
WHEN IT WAS LIKE THIS.
IT USED TO BE
A REALLY NICE MANSION
BEFORE IT BURNED DOWN.
OH, IT WAS? HEY, WAIT! THEN DOES
THAT MEAN YOU’RE LOADED?!
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
MY MOM DIED A LITTLE WHILE
AFTER I WAS BORN,
AND MY DAD WAS A SCIENTIST
WHO WAS ALWAYS IN HIS LAB.
HE AND I DIDN’T REALLY
GET ALONG ALL THAT GOOD,
SO HE SHIPPED ME OFF
TO A BOARDING SCHOOL.
I WAS ALWAYS
GETTING INTO FIGHTS THERE.
AND BY MY FIRST YEAR
OF HIGH SCHOOL,
I WAS A STRAIGHT‐UP PUNK.
AND THEN, SIX MONTHS AGO,
I GOT A NOTE FROM MY DAD,
SAYING HE WANTED TO TALK,
SO I CAME BACK. BUT...
[ GRUNTING ]
DAD! DAD! HANG ON!
STOP FUSSING AND LISTEN.
IF YOU WANT TO LIVE A PEACEFUL
LIFE, LEAVE HERE RIGHT NOW.
[ GROANS ] BUT IF YOU WANT
TO CONTINUE MY FIGHT...
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
[ GASPS ]
YOU’RE GOING TO NEED THAT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "FIGHT"?
IF YOU FIND THE OTHER HALF
OF THAT SCISSOR,
YOU’LL FIND MY KILLER.
BUT A CRUEL FATE
LIES IN STORE FOR YOU.
[ LOUD CLATTER ]
[ GASPS ]
HOLD IT!
COME BACK, RYUKO!
LET THEM GO!
I HAVEN’T TOLD YOU
EVERYTHING!
[ PANTING ]
[ FLAMES WHOOSH ]
DAD.
DAD!
THERE WERE TIMES
WHEN I HATED THE OLD MAN.
BUT HIS DYING WAS
A WAKE‐UP CALL FOR ME,
’CAUSE I REALIZED I DIDN’T
REALLY KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT HIM.
I DECIDED
RIGHT THEN AND THERE
I’D FIND OUT WHO KILLED HIM
AND WHY,
WHAT HE WANTED TO TELL ME,
AND FIND OUT WHAT THIS IS.
BUT I STILL HAVEN’T GOT
ANY ANSWERS.
I ALSO WANNA KNOW
WHY HE MADE YOU, SENKETSU.
THERE’S NOTHING HERE.
[ SNORING ]
WELL, THAT WAS A TOTAL WASH.
I WAS HOPIN’ TO FIND
SOME KIND OF CLUE
IN ONE OF THOSE BIG PILES
OF FABRIC,
BUT IT’S ALL GONE.
Senketsu: MIKISUGI MIGHT KNOW
ABOUT THAT.
HMM. MAYBE.
HUH?
[ SCOOTER SLOWS DOWN ]
WELL, THAT SUCKS.
DAD GOT YOU A MESSED UP SCOOTER.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
NAH. THE DAMN GAS GAUGE
IS BUSTED, IS ALL.
SAY, RYUKO?
MM‐HMM?
YOU KNOW,
YOU’RE NOT ALONE ANYMORE
BECAUSE NOW YOU GOT US
IN YOUR LIFE.
AND BY "US," I’M TALKING ABOUT
SENKETSU AND ME
AND MY WHOLE FAMILY.
WE ALL LOVE YOU LOTS AND LOTS.
YOU KNOW WE DO, RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
I NEVER HAD ANY DOUBT.
OOH, I KNOW!
WE SHOULD HITCHHIKE!
OKAY.
HEY, OVER HERE!
TWO YOUNG GIRLS NEED A RIDE!
DON’T WORRY, WE’RE NOT PICKY!
OH, COME ON!
[ BOTH COUGHING ]
[ BRAKES SCREECH ]
WATCH WHERE YOU’RE DRIVING,
YOU JACKASS!
[ CAR BEEPING ]
Both: HUH?
LADIES, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
WOW! I HITCHED US A RIDE
WITH GAMAGOORI!
OH, GREAT.
ARE YOU FOLLOWIN’ ME AROUND?
CALM DOWN. I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF FIGHTING YOU HERE.
HUH?
WE’LL FIGHT ON THE DAY OF
THE SUDDEN DEATH RUNOFF,
NOT BEFORE.
OKAY, THEN. WHAT DO YOU WANT?
GET IN.
I’M THE APPOINTED CHAIR
OF THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE
OF HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
AND WHEN I’M OFF CAMPUS AND FIND
A FELLOW STUDENT IN NEED,
IT’S MY DUTY
AS A COMMITTEE MEMBER
TO HELP THAT STUDENT OUT...
EVEN IF IT’S YOU,
SO GET IN.
BUT WE CAN’T ‐‐
WHOO‐HOO!
THESE SEATS ARE COMFY!
WOW! IS THIS A NEW CAR?
IT LOOKS NEW!
[ GIGGLES ]
IT MUST BE NEW ’CAUSE IT’S
ALL SPARKLY AND CLEAN!
LET’S GO FOR A RIDE, RYUKO!
COME ON, GET IN! GET IN!
LET’S GO!
Mako: ♪ HEY! WE’RE ALL GOING
ON A RIDEY‐RIDE TO HELL ♪
♪ HEY! UPSIDE DOWN
AND AROUNDY‐ROUND TO HELL ♪
♪ HEY! GONNA JUMP THE TRACK
AND CRASH INTO A WALL ♪
♪ HEY! REAR ENDER,
FENDER BENDER ♪
♪ CRASH INTO ’EM ALL!
HEY...♪ ♪
MATOI, MAKE HER STOP
THAT GOD‐AWFUL SINGING.
HEY, WHEN SHE’S ON A ROLL,
NO ONE CAN MAKE HER STOP.
A RED LIGHT WOULDN’T EVEN
STOP MANKANSHOKU.
THAT’S RIGHT!
’CAUSE THE TRAFFIC SIGNALS
OF MY LIFE ALWAYS FLASH YELLOW!
"PROCEED WITH CAUTION."
NICE PHILOSOPHY.
[ HORN HONKING,
MOTOR PURRING LOUDLY ]
I HATE DRIVER’S WHO DON’T FOLLOW
THE RULES OF THE ROAD.
THIS IS A NO PASSING ZONE!
DOWN, MAKO!
AAH!
[ GROWLS ]
WHO THE HELL ARE THEY?!
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
YOU DIDN’T HEAR?
THE AUTOMOTIVE
AND AIRSOFT CLUBS MERGED
TO FORM
THE AUTOMOTIVE AIRSOFT CLUB.
DON’T WORRY.
THEY’RE NOT AFTER YOU.
EVEN IF THEY GOT THEIR HANDS
ON YOUR KAMUI,
THEY COULDN’T USE IT.
MAIKO OGURE FOUND THAT OUT
THE HARD WAY.
SO THEY WANNA GET THEIR HANDS
ON YOUR UNIFORM, HUH?
RYUKO, LOOK AT THAT!
NICE CLUNKER, GAMAGOORI!
BUT IS IT FAST ENOUGH TO
ESCAPE ME, RYOSUKE TODOROKI,
PRESIDENT OF
THE AUTOMOTIVE AIRSOFT CLUB?!
COME ON, MAN! LET’S FIND OUT!
THEY’RE GAINING!
LOOKS LIKE WE PICKED
THE WRONG CAR TO GET INTO.
HERE THEY COME!
THEY’RE FAST.
BUT GOOD DRIVING TAKES MORE
THAN SPEED. IT TAKES SKILL, TOO!
[ SCREAMING ]
AAH!
WE’RE OUT OF CONTROL!
NO SHIT!
THAT’S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU CRANK THE WHEEL HARD
LIKE THAT, YOU ASS!
WHERE’D YOU LEARN TO DRIVE,
ON A GO‐KART TRACK?!
[ GRUNTS ]
YOU OKAY, MAKO?
[ ENGINES REV ]
[ CHUCKLES ] YOU GUYS THINK
YOU’RE ALL THAT, HUH?
Gamagoori:
YOU STAY OUT OF THIS, MATOI.
WHY?
IT’S MY MESS,
SO I’LL HANDLE IT.
WE GOTCHA CORNERED, BIG MAN!
WHEN WE GET THROUGH WITH YOU,
YOU’RE GONNA BE BAWLING!
[ SCOFFS ] IT’LL TAKE MORE THAN
YOU LOUSY PUNKS TO MAKE ME CRY!
BUT EVEN IF I DID SHED A TEAR,
I’D JUST WIPE
THE DAMN THING AWAY,
AND THEN PUT YOU DOWN!
HA! YOU’RE ALL TALK
AND NO ACTION! LIGHT HIM UP!
THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM!
SHACKLE REGALIA!
UH‐OH, HE TRANSFORMED!
SO WHAT IF HE DID?!
SHOOT HIS ASS!
MAN, THAT THING’S HARD.
Gamagoori: YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
AAH! [ MOANING ]
YES! MORE!
PUNISH ME!
AHH!
I’VE BEEN SUCH A BAD BOY!
WHEN YOU PUNISH ME, IT’S LIKE
YOU’RE WHIPPING MY HEART!
AND THE MORE YOU PUNISH ME,
THE STRONGER I GET,
JUST LIKE I WAS BACK THEN!
[ WHIMPERING ]
Boy:
WHAT YOU WAITING FOR? JUMP.
YOU GOT MILK ON MY UNIFORM,
YOU CLUMSY DORK.
BUT THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT!
SO WE’RE GIVING YOU A CHANCE.
YOU JUMP, WE’RE EVEN.
Gamagoori: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU’RE DOING?!
All: HUH?
WELL, WELL, IF IT ISN’T
OUR STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT.
WHY DON’T YOU DO YOURSELF
A FAVOR? DON’T GET INVOLVED.
I HAVE TO DO THIS,
GAMAGOORI!
MY DAD’LL GET FIRED
IF I DON’T!
YEAH. HIS PIECE OF CRAP DAD
WORKS AT MY OLD MAN’S COMPANY.
AND MY DADDY’S THE CHIEF
OF POLICE IN THIS TOWN,
AND HE’S NOT GONNA BUST
HIS LITTLE GIRL.
THIS IS INHUMAN! NO ONE DESERVES
TO GET TREATED LIKE THIS!
THERE’S NOTHING INHUMAN
ABOUT IT.
WE GOT STATUS. WE GOT BACKUP.
THAT MEANS WE CALL THE SHOTS.
AND IF HE WANTS TO JUMP
TO SAVE HIS DAD’S JOB,
THAT JUST PROVES
HE’S BEING A GOOD SON.
WELL? GET IT OVER WITH!
[ WHIMPERING ]
DON’T DO IT!
[ GRUNTS ] AAH!
[ LAUGHTER ]
NOW THAT’S WHAT
I’M TALKING ABOUT!
GO AHEAD. KEEP ACTING
ALL HIGH AND MIGHTY.
BUT AT
REEN NEH‐DO JUNIOR HIGH,
PEOPLE DO WHAT WE SAY OR ELSE.
[ GROWLS ]
DAMN IT!
[ WHIMPERS ]
WHAT THE...
UH...
[ CHUCKLES ]
THE KIRYUIN DELUXE TRAMPOLINE
HAS A NICE SPRING TO IT,
DON’T YOU THINK?
[ GASPS ]
[ CONTINUES WHIMPERING ]
GOTCHA!
NO, LET ME GO!
IF I DON’T DIE,
THEY’RE GONNA FIRE MY DAD!
Satsuki: YOU NEEDN’T WORRY
ABOUT THAT,
FOR I’VE JUST PURCHASED
THAT DESPICABLE COMPANY.
WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT, YOU NEW HERE?
YOU DIDN’T BUY
MY DAD’S COMPANY!
YEAH, GET LOST,
OR ELSE I’M GONNA
HAVE MY DADDY THROW YOU IN JAIL
WITH THE PEDOS!
FORTUNATELY, I’VE RELIEVED
YOUR FATHER OF HIS DUTIES.
IF YOU DON’T BELIEVE ME,
LOOK AT THIS.
W‐WHAT THE HELL?!
WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE?!
HEY, GUYS!
GO ON, TAKE THAT BITCH APART!
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
MY NAME IS SATSUKI KIRYUIN!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
[ ALL GROANING ]
FROM NOW ON,
I RULE OVER THIS SCHOOL
AND EVERY STUDENT IN IT.
YOU ARE SELFISH AND PETTY,
AND I WILL NOT TOLERATE
THUGS LIKE YOU IN MY SCHOOL.
HOLD ON!
YOU’RE USING YOUR PARENTS’
INFLUENCE, JUST LIKE THEM!
HOW ARE YOU ANY DIFFERENT?
UNLIKE THOSE CRIMINALS,
I DO NOT LEECH OFF THE POWER
OF MY PARENTS.
I AM DIFFERENT,
BECAUSE NO MATTER WHOSE POWER
IT IS, I WILL EXPLOIT IT ALL.
I WILL NOT SHARE IT WITH ANYONE!
I WILL TAKE IT, ABSORB IT,
AND WIELD IT
ON WHATEVER I SEE FIT!
MY RESOLVE IS
WHAT MAKES ME DIFFERENT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SIMPLE, GAMAGOORI.
WITHOUT RESOLVE, YOU WOULDN’T
EVEN HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO WIPE AWAY YOUR OWN TEARS.
[ CONTINUES MOANING ]
AND THAT’S HOW I MET
LADY SATSUKI.
I WAITED TWO YEARS
FOR HER TO GRADUATE,
JUST SO I COULD ENROLL
IN HONNOUJI ACADEMY WITH HER.
SHE GAVE ME THIS GOKU UNIFORM
AS A REWARD FOR MY LOYALTY.
Ryuko: WAIT.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
I’M TURNING 20 THIS YEAR.
Mako: I ALWAYS THOUGHT
HE LOOKED OLDER.
ARE YOU GONNA TALK
OR FIGHT?!
[ LAUGHS ] YES!
THAT’S MORE LIKE IT!
THE MORE PUNISHMENT I TAKE,
THE BIGGER AND HARDER I GET!
WOWSERS.
HE’S OLD AND PERVERTED
NOT PERVERTED! CONVERTED!
AS SOON AS I REACH MY CLIMAX,
THE POWER THAT’S BEEN BUILDING
UP INSIDE OF ME WILL EXPLODE
EVERYWHERE!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM!
SCOURGE REGALIA!
WHOA!
Senketsu: [ GASPS ]
A TWO‐STAGE TRANSFORMATION!
[ TANK WHIRS ]
BE CAREFUL GOING HOME.
DON’T STOP FOR ANY STRANGERS.
OKAY, DAD.
SEE YOU AT
THE SUDDEN DEATH RUNOFF.
I’LL MAKE SURE TO PICK
THE PERFECT SPOT FOR OUR FIGHT.
WAIT. WHAT?
[ STARTS ENGINE ]
HUH?
IT IS TIME, LADY SATSUKI.
[ HEEL CLACKS ]
STUDENTS OF HONNOUJI ACADEMY!
FOR THE PAST WEEK,
YOU’VE FOUGHT LONG AND HARD.
HOWEVER, YOUR FIGHT
HAS ONLY JUST BEGUN!
WELCOME TO
THE SUDDEN DEATH RUNOFF!
EVERY BATTLE OVER THE PAST WEEK
HAS BEEN RECORDED,
AND NOW WE KNOW
WHO THE SURVIVORS ARE.
BASED ON WHAT HAPPENS TODAY,
I WILL DETERMINE WHO ACQUIRES
THREE‐STAR STATUS!
[ MURMURING ]
[ GROUND RUMBLING ]
NOW WHAT?!
[ SCREAMING ]
Satsuki: THE FIVE PILLARS
ARE YOUR NEXT CHALLENGE!
FIGHT YOUR WAY TO THE TOP OF ONE
AND BE A FRONT‐RUNNER
IN THE ELECTION
THAT SNEAKY...
SHE’S MAKIN’ THIS UP
AS SHE GOES!
[ SCOFFS ] WELL, SO CAN I!
[ SHOUTING ]
WELL, WELL, WELL.
THE ELITE FOUR
LIVES UP TO THEIR NAME.
DID YOU EXPECT ANY DIFFERENT?
LADY SATSUKI!
WE, THE ELITE FOUR,
WOULD LIKE TO PROPOSE
AN ADDITIONAL RULE
FOR THE SUDDEN DEATH RUNOFFS!
HMM?
EACH OF US WANTS A SHOT
AT FACING RYUKO MATOI
IN A FIGHT.
[ ALL GASP ]
WE’RE GONNA FIGHT HER ANYWAY.
WE MIGHT AS WELL DO IT HERE
ON THIS GRAND STAGE.
IT WOULD BE AN EXPLOSIVE FINALE
TO THE ACADEMY’S FIRST ELECTION.
DON’T YOU THINK, M’LADY?
[ CHUCKLES ] IT WOULD AT THAT.
[ SCREAMING ]
A KING OF THE HILL FINAL BATTLE!
MATOI, YOU WILL FIGHT
THE ELITE FOUR.
IF YOU WIN,
I WILL TELL YOU THE DETAILS
OF YOUR FATHER’S DEATH.
YOU’RE ON!
I WILL BE THE FIRST TO FACE YOU
IN BATTLE, MATOI!
AAH!
I’M LADY SATSUKI’S
IMPENETRABLE SHIELD!
I CHALLENGE YOU,
AND I WILL CRUSH YOU!
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT!
Mika Kobayashi: ♪ DON’T LOSE
YOUR WAY IN YOUR MIND ♪
♪ WE HAVE TO BE AS ONE ♪
♪ DON’T BE AFRAID,
MY SWEETHEART ♪
♪ THIS IS THE WAY
TO BE MORE STRONG ♪
♪ HARBOR MY DEEP SECRET ♪
♪ IT MAKES ME SO BLUE ♪
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE!
KAMUI SENKETSU!
♪ BEFORE MY BODY IS DRY ♪
Senketsu: IT’S
A KING‐OF‐THE‐HILL‐STYLE BATTLE,
AND HER FIRST OPPONENT
IS IRA GAMAGOORI.
SHACKLE REGALIA,
SCOURGE REGALIA,
HE’S A TWO‐STAGE PERVERT.
HE’S A HARDASS WHO STANDS ERECT
ON THE BATTLEFIELD!
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"A ONCE IN A LIFETIME CHANCE."