AAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ RYUKO PANTING ]
RYUKO!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THAT FRIGGIN’ HURT!
BUT I GUESS
I HAD IT COMING
AFTER ACTING
LIKE SUCH A DUMBASS.
I CAN’T BELIEVE IT.
SHE SHOULD BE DEAD
AFTER SNAPPING HER LIFE FIBERS
LIKE THAT.
[ GIGGLES ]
THAT TICKLES.
NO WAY.
HER WOUNDS ARE CLOSING UP.
OH, GREAT.
SHE’S IMMORTAL, TOO.
BITCH HAS GOT LIFE FIBERS
RUNNING THROUGH HER BODY.
THROWING YOUR SCISSOR BLADE
AT ME WAS A BAD MOVE.
YOU CAN’T DEFEAT ME SO EASY,
YOU BIG SILLY.
NOW I HAVE BOTH HALVES,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
COME ON!
HURRY, SENKETSU!
RYUKO NEEDS YOU,
SO GET GOING!
RIGHT!
[ GIGGLES ]
GOODIE.
I GET TO SHRED
THAT DUMB OL’ SENKETSU AGAIN.
NOT THIS TIME!
DON’T HOPSCOTCH ON ME!
HERE WE GO, RYUKO!
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE!
AAH!
[ GASPS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
HARIME!!
[ GIGGLES NERVOUSLY ]
HUH. IT SEEMS SHE’S FIGURED OUT
HOW TO RATTLE HARIME.
DON’T YOU EVEN THINK
ABOUT LEAVING.
THIS WON’T DO AT ALL.
I TAILORED JUNKETSU
JUST FOR YOU, YOU KNOW.
I CAN’T LET YOU
WEAR THAT HORRID THING.
NOPE, NOPE, NOPE.
AWWWW!
DON’T EVEN TRY.
I AIN’T GONNA TAKE SENKETSU OFF
EVER AGAIN.
HE FEELS DIFFERENT NOW ‐‐
’CAUSE HE’S GOT
SATSUKI’S AND MAKO’S BLOOD
FLOWING THROUGH HIM.
HE FEELS WAY BETTER ‐‐
AND WAY WARMER ‐‐
THAN THAT MONSTER JUNKETSU
EVER DID!
[ Bawling ]
OH, THANK YOU, RYUKO!
DUDE!
DON’T START CRYING!
GOD, YOU WERE SO COMFY BEFORE,
AND NOW ‐‐
NOW YOU’RE GETTING
ALL DAMP AND GROSS!
RIGHT! SORRY!
ALL THIS ICKY
FRIEND NONSENSE ‐‐
GAH!
I THINK I’M GONNA HURL!
WHO CARES
WHAT YOU THINK?
YOU DON’T EVEN KNOW
WHAT FRIENDS ARE!
THESE GUYS ARE SOMETHING ELSE ‐‐
SOMETHING BETTER!
I DON’T KNOW
WHAT IT’S CALLED,
BUT MAKO AND SENKETSU
ARE MORE THAN FRIENDS!
[ GASPS ]
REALLY? ME TOO?
YEAH, YOU TOO.
YOU’RE, LIKE, THE MOST
PERSISTENT CHICK I EVER MET.
YOU DIDN’T CARE
IF I PUSHED YOU AWAY.
YOU KEPT COMING BACK
AND COMING BACK, LIKE A YO‐YO.
AND SENKETSU HERE ‐‐
WHAT THE HELL.
HERE’S A PIECE OF CLOTHING
THAT CRIES AND LAUGHS
AND WORRIES ABOUT ME.
I’M SURROUNDED BY PEOPLE THAT
ACTUALLY GIVE A DAMN ABOUT ME,
AND THEY’RE ALL
BAT‐SHIT‐CRAZY!
I DON’T KNOW
IF I DESERVE THEM,
BUT I SURE AS HELL
AIN’T GONNA LET THEM DOWN!
YOU ASSHOLES JUST WANT
TO GIVE THE PLANET UP
TO THE LIFE FIBERS.
YOU WANT TO MAKE IT
SO EVERYONE’S CUT
FROM THE SAME CLOTH.
GUESS WHAT.
I WON’T LET IT HAPPEN!
’CAUSE THIS WORLD’S BETTER OFF
WITH BAT‐SHIT‐CRAZY PEOPLE
THAN IT IS WITH YOU!
I TOTALLY DIDN’T GET
WHAT YOU SAID JUST NOW,
BUT YOU’RE RIGHT!
AAH!
IF YOU DON’T GET IT,
THEN SHUT IT.
GEEZ LOUISE.
I REALLY HATE HUMANS.
KISS ALL YOUR BAT‐SHIT‐CRAZY
FRIENDS GOODBYE!
I GOT
DAD’S SCISSOR BLADES BACK.
NOW YOU GUYS
ARE REALLY SCREWED!
[ GIGGLES ]
THEN HOW ABOUT WE MAKE THINGS
MORE INTERESTING?
YOUR FRIENDS CAN ATTACK YOU
FOR A CHANGE.
[ SURPRISED GRUNTING ]
GET READY, HUMANS!
IT’S MIND‐STITCHING TIME!
LIKE HELL IT IS!
AWW. POOR THING.
I TOTALLY FAKED YOU OUT.
IT’S ALL OVER, RYUKO.
YEAH ‐‐ FOR YOU.
MY ARMS!
OH, MY GOD! OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
MY ARMS!!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW VALUABLE MY ARMS ARE?!
I’M THE GRAND COUTURIER!
THAT’S WHY I CHOPPED THEM OFF,
DIPSHIT.
I’M KIDDING.
IF YOU CHOP THEM OFF, THEY’LL
JUST POP RIGHT BACK ON AGAIN.
AAH!
OOPS.
OOPS AGAIN.
AAAAAAAAAAAAH!
HER SCISSORS CAN KEEP
LIFE FIBERS FROM REGENERATING?
IF I’D ONLY KNOWN,
IT WOULD’VE CHANGED EVERYTHING.
GIVE UP ALREADY.
IT’S OVER.
THIS ISN’T HAPPENING ‐‐
NOT TO ME!
NOW I’M REALLY ANGRY.
LIKE, REALLY SUPER‐ANGRY!
I HATE YOU! I HATE YOU!
I HATE YOU!
I HATE YOU ALL!
SHE’S GETTING AWAY!
THAT LITTLE ‐‐
SENKETSU SHIPPU!
WHAT THE ‐‐
OW!
WE BETTER NOT, RYUKO.
WHY?
YOU’VE LOST
A GREAT DEAL OF BLOOD.
IT WOULD BE
VERY DANGEROUS.
THEN WHAT WE DO
ABOUT THEM?
POOR HOUOUMARU.
IT WAS A MISTAKE
TO GO RUSHING OFF LIKE THAT.
HUH?
SHE’S RIGHT.
THIS IS
A GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY.
[ GROWLS ]
IT’S TWO‐FOR‐ONE DAY.
WE GET LIFE FIBERS TO STOMP
AND SOME MORE RECRUITS
FOR THE CAUSE.
YOU CAN
SAY THAT AGAIN.
HEY, ELITE FOUR,
DON’T BE SHY.
YOU’RE ON THE CLOCK NOW,
SO PICK A BAD GUY
AND START SUCKING!
HM.
UH...
HMM.
GOT IT.
RRRRRRRRRAAAAAAAAAAAH!
NINE‐BARREL EMERGENCY RESCUE
SUCTION DEVICE!
[ ALL YELLING ]
I KNOW THESE PEOPLE.
THAT’S HAKODATE.
AND THAT’S FUKURODA.
AND THE REST.
I NEED MEDICS!
Together: MA’AM.
THESE STUDENTS HAVE BEEN
EXTRACTED. TEND TO THEM.
AYE‐AYE, MA’AM!
COME ON, MANKANSHOKUS!
IT’S TIME WE HELPED SOME PEOPLE,
FOR A CHANGE!
AW, MAN.
IF THEY GOT NO POCKETS,
THERE’S NOTHING FOR ME TO STEAL.
YOUR ATTITUDE IS
NOT APPRECIATED, YOUNG MAN!
OW! OKAY, I’LL DO IT!
I’M DOING IT!
GUTS, GUTS!
Iori: SEWING CLUB MEMBERS,
GATHER UP THE LIFE FIBERS
AND BRING THEM TO THE LAB, ASAP!
COLLECTION COMPLETE.
LET ME OUT!
WHAT’S YOUR PROBLEM?
I DIDN’T ASK FOR YOUR HELP!
I HAVEN’T BEEN BEATEN YET!
YOU HEAR?!
PLEASE, GRAND COUTURIER,
CALM DOWN.
WHAT COULD YOU HOPE TO ACHIEVE
IN YOUR PRESENT CONDITION?
RIGHT NOW,
COMPLETING SHINRA‐KOUKETSU
TAKES PRIORITY OVER ANYTHING
AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
YOU LOST YOUR ARMS
BECAUSE YOU WERE FIGHTING
INSTEAD OF WORKING.
SO I HOPE YOU HAVE A GOOD
APOLOGY LINED UP FOR LADY RAGYO.
YOU THINK
I SHOULD APOLOGIZE?
YOU’RE KIDDING.
RUN ALONG
TO HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
I’LL PUT THE FINISHING TOUCHES
ON SHINRA‐KOUKETSU.
AND AFTER I’M DONE,
I’LL TEACH YOU WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU MOUTH OFF TO ME.
AS LONG AS YOU FINISH
SHINRA‐KOUKETSU,
WHAT HAPPENS TO ME
IS OF NO CONCERN.
Iori: WHAT SHALL I DO
WITH JUNKETSU?
KEEP IT RESTRAINED.
SHOULDN’T YOU
TERMINATE THAT THING?
NO. THE BATTLE
ISN’T OVER YET.
Ryuko: OH, YOU’RE GONNA
PUT THAT THING ON AGAIN, HUH?
YOU THINK
YOU CAN CONTROL IT?
YES, AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I DO.
YEAH,
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
YOU COULDN’T EVEN SYNC
WITH SENKETSU.
Senketsu:
STOP HARASSING HER, RYUKO.
REMEMBER, SHE RISKED HER LIFE
TO SAVE YOU.
SO WHAT IF SHE DID?
YOU THINK
I’M JUST GONNA FORGET
ALL ABOUT THE ATTITUDE
SHE’S GIVEN ME?
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
LET ME BELT YOU ONE.
STOP IT, RYUKO.
IF I PUNCH YOU
WITH EVERYTHING I GOT
AND CAN’T KNOCK YOU DOWN,
I’LL KNOW YOU GOT WHAT IT TAKES
TO FIGHT ALONGSIDE ME.
GOD, THAT’S THE CRAZIEST THING
I EVER HEARD.
ALL SHE’S WEARING IS A COAT,
AND YOU’RE IN FULL‐ON SYNC MODE.
ONE HIT FROM YOU,
AND SHE’S DEAD.
YOU’RE FORGETTING SOMETHING ‐‐
SHE’S THE GREAT SATSUKI KIRYUIN.
VERY WELL. DO IT.
WE FACE RAGYO KIRYUIN,
AND IF I FALL TO YOU,
THEN I HAVE NO CHANCE
OF BEATING HER.
GO ON. HIT ME.
I SHALL WITHSTAND IT.
KEEP TELLING YOURSELF THAT.
WE’LL FIND OUT IN A SEC.
GET READY.
[ ALL WHIMPERING ]
HUAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
GAMAGOORI!
THIS IS
BETWEEN ME AND HER!
HUAAAAAAAAAAH!
OOF!
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT’S WITH YOU PEOPLE?!
IS THAT THE BEST
YOU CAN DO, MATOI?!
WHAT?!
DID YOU PUT EVERYTHING YOU HAD
INTO THAT PUNCH?
’CAUSE IT DIDN’T
FEEL LIKE IT!
YEAH,
’COURSE I DID!
[ SCOFFS ] IF YOU DID,
THEN WHY ARE WE STILL ALIVE?
HE’S RIGHT ‐‐
IF YOU REALLY HIT US FULL‐FORCE,
IT SHOULD HAVE KILLED US.
I PULLED MY PUNCHES
’CAUSE YOU DORKS GOT IN THE WAY!
THAT’S NO EXCUSE!
IT SHOULDN’T MATTER
WHO GETS IN YOUR WAY!
SUCH LACK OF COMMITMENT
PROVES YOU ARE NOT WORTHY
TO PUNCH LADY SATSUKI!
SCREW YOU!
I’M COMMITTED!
DOESN’T LOOK LIKE IT
FROM WHERE I’M STANDING.
LADY SATSUKI’S
GOT STANDARDS.
AND WE DON’T LET
HALF‐ASSED PUNCHES TOUCH HER!
STEP ASIDE.
I HAVE THIS.
YOU WANT TO PUNCH HER FACE,
PUNCH OURS FIRST.
YOU WANT TO CHOP HER ARMS OFF,
CHOP OURS OFF FIRST.
WE’RE THE FACE AND LIMBS
OF LADY SATSUKI,
AND WE TAKE THE HITS
FOR HER.
ALTHOUGH, US "LIMBS"
HAVE A MIND OF OUR OWN,
AND WE CAN BE
QUITE A HANDFUL.
Sanageyama:
HONNOUJI’S ELITE FOUR
ARE LADY SATSUKI’S
INVINCIBLE SPEAR,
HER TOUGH‐ASS SHIELD.
Gamagoori: IF YOU WANT TO STRIKE
LADY SATSUKI, STRIKE US!
BUT BE WARNED ‐‐
WE WILL NOT YIELD SO EASILY!
GOD!
WHAT’S YOUR PROBLEM?!
YOU GUYS ARE ALL
FREAKIN’ NUTS.
[ GASPS ]
YOU GOT BAT‐SHIT‐CRAZY PEOPLE
PROTECTING YOU,
JUST LIKE I DO.
[ GASPS ]
IT SEEMS THAT WAY,
DOESN’T IT?
I HAD TO
DEFEAT RAGYO.
AND I THOUGHT
THE ONLY WAY I COULD
WAS IF I USED OTHERS
AS MY PAWNS.
SO, NATURALLY, I THOUGHT I COULD
USE YOU IN THE SAME MANNER.
SINCE THE DAY YOU APPEARED
WEARING SENKETSU,
MY GOAL HAS BEEN TO TRAIN YOU
AS AN ASSET
TO TURN AGAINST RAGYO
AND HER ALLIES.
I TOLD YOU
I KILLED OUR FATHER
BECAUSE I WANTED TO GAUGE
YOUR AND SENKETSU’S POWER.
IF YOU COULD
HOLD ON TO YOUR FREE WILL
WITHOUT BEING SWALLOWED UP
BY YOUR KAMUI,
YOU COULD PROVE USEFUL
WHEN IT CAME TIME FOR THE COUP.
AND I THOUGHT
IF I KEPT THE TRUTH FROM YOU,
I COULD CONTROL YOU BETTER
AS A WEAPON AGAINST RAGYO.
THANKS, BITCH.
TREATING YOU LIKE A FOOL
WAS A MISTAKE.
IN THE END, I WAS USING
THE SAME METHODS AS RAGYO.
I SHOULD’VE KNOWN
I COULD NEVER WIN THAT WAY.
IF ANYONE HERE IS A FOOL,
IT’S ME.
NO, DON’T SAY THAT.
I UNDERSTAND NOW.
PEOPLE ARE NOT CUT
FROM THE SAME CLOTH.
AND NO MATTER
HOW ODD THEY MAY SEEM,
THEIR DIFFERENCES
MAKE THIS WORLD BEAUTIFUL.
OUR WORLD
IS WORTH PROTECTING,
AND I’D BE HONORED
TO SHARE THE TASK WITH YOU.
GEEZ. EVEN YOUR APOLOGIES
ARE TURNED UP TO 11.
I DON’T FEEL LIKE
HITTING YOU ANYMORE.
I GOT FOLKS
I WANT TO PROTECT, TOO.
SO IF YOU WANT TO TEAM UP
TO PULL MOM’S PLUG,
I GOT NO PROBLEMS
WITH THAT.
WELL,
NOW THAT YOU’VE MADE UP,
LET’S SIT DOWN
AND HAVE SOME DINNER.
SWEET! YOU MADE
YOUR FAMOUS CROQUETTES!
YUP, AND THEY’RE FILLED
TO THE GILLS
WITH ALL KINDS
OF CHOPPED‐UP MYSTERIOUS THINGS.
DON’T JUST STAND THERE!
DIG IN!
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
Mako: WHEN IT COMES TO
MYSTERIOUS THINGS,
NO ONE FRIES THEM UP
BETTER THAN MY MOM!
TRY IT,
LADY SATSUKI.
MMM. THIS IS...
SUPER‐YUMMY, RIGHT?
YES. VERY.
WOULD ANYONE
CARE FOR SOME TEA?
[ ALL GASP EXCITEDLY ]
Senketsu: RYUKO.
HM?
EARLIER, YOU WERE DEEPLY MOVED,
WEREN’T YOU?
WHAT?!
AFTER
YOU HEARD SATSUKI OUT.
MY GOD.
WOULD YOU GIVE ME A BREAK?
YOU SHOULD HAVE TOLD HER
HOW YOU WERE FEELING.
YOU’RE AN OBNOXIOUS OUTFIT.
AND YOU ARE COMPLETELY DEVOID
OF FEMININE CHARM.
[ LAUGHS ]
I GET WHAT’S GOING ON.
YOU MISSED HAVING ME AROUND
TO TALK TO, DIDN’T YA?
UH...
THAT’S WHY
YOU’RE PUSHING ALL MY BUTTONS.
NOW, THAT IS NOT TRUE!
[ CHUCKLES ]
RIGHT. LISTEN HERE.
I AM NOT PRONE
TO FITS OF LONELINESS.
OKAY, OKAY!
IT’S COOL.
TALK ALL YOU WANT.
PRETTY SOON, THERE WON’T BE
TIME FOR IT, ANYWAY.
WHY NOT?
’CAUSE SHE’S GONNA BE
COMING FOR US.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
Ragyo: WHAT IS IT?
RYUKO’S FREED HERSELF, EH?
WELL, BE A DEAR
AND HAVE NUI WORK FASTER.
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
HEH.
I NEVER THOUGHT MY DAUGHTERS
WOULD BECOME SUCH NUISANCES.
IT APPEARS I FAILED
TO DISCIPLINE THEM PROPERLY.
Nui:
IF IT’S THE LAST THING I DO,
I’M GONNA MAKE RYUKO MATOI
AND SATSUKI KIRYUIN PAY!
I’M INJECTING A MIXTURE
OF LADY SATSUKI’S AND RYUKO’S
BLOOD INTO JUNKETSU.
I’VE ALSO ADDED A DASH
OF SENKETSU’S LIFE FIBERS TO IT.
I GET IT ‐‐ WITH THEIR BLOOD
AND SENKETSU’S POWER,
YOU’VE TAMED JUNKETSU
SO SATSUKI CAN WEAR IT.
IT’S A SHAME
IT HAD TO BE ALTERED,
BUT IT’S THE ONLY WAY
TO MAKE IT WORK FOR ME.
AT THIS POINT, THOUGH,
I WOULD DO ANYTHING TO WIN.
SOUNDS LIKE THE WORDS OF A WOMAN
WITH VICTORY ON HER MIND.
KIND OF GIRL
WHO’S STRIPPED HERSELF
OF ALL
EXTRANEOUS THOUGHTS.
YOU’RE A PROPER NUDIST NOW,
SO YOU WANT TO GET NAKED?
HOW ARE THINGS
COMING ALONG HERE?
DAMN,
THAT’S COLD.
EVERYTHING
IS READY TO GO.
WE MANAGED TO COLLECT
MORE LIFE FIBERS THAN WE NEED.
IN FACT,
I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO START MAKING
THE NEW GOKU UNIFORMS.
WAIT ‐‐ BY YOURSELF?
I CAN HANDLE IT.
THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM,
TAILOR’S REGALIA!
Satsuki: RAGYO KIRYUIN’S
ULTIMATE OBJECTIVE
IS TO TRANSFORM THE HUMAN RACE
INTO HOSTS FOR LIFE FIBERS
AND COVER
THE ENTIRE PLANET,
TURNING IT INTO
A STARSEED COCOON SPHERE.
EVERY PRODUCT REVOCS MAKES
HAS LIFE FIBERS WOVEN INTO THEM.
THE PLAN WAS TO BEAM A SIGNAL
TO THE CLOTHES,
AWAKENING THE LIFE FIBERS.
HUMANS WOULD BE CONVERTED
INTO ENERGY SOURCES
AND THEIR CLOTHING
TRANSFORMED INTO COVERS.
THEN, 7 BILLION COVERS WOULD
RISE INTO THE STRATOSPHERE,
ENSHROUDING THE PLANET.
SHE WAS GONNA MAKE THE EARTH
WEAR A SWEATER?
TALK ABOUT MESSED UP.
I KNEW SHE WAS TRYING TO TURN
THE HUMAN RACE INTO LIFE FIBERS,
BUT I HAD NO IDEA
THE PLAN WAS SO EPIC IN SCOPE.
QUESTION IS, WHY?
LIFE FIBERS ARE AN ORGANISM
THAT DRIFTS THROUGH SPACE.
ONCE THEY REACH A PLANET
WITH INTELLIGENT LIFE,
THEY CAUSE IT TO EVOLVE
INTO A STATE
MORE SUITABLE AS ENERGY SOURCES.
THE LIFE FIBERS
CONVERT THEIR HOSTS INTO CLOTHES
AND COVER THE PLANET.
THEN, THEY USE THE PLANET
AS AN ENERGY SOURCE
UNTIL IT EXPLODES,
SCATTERING THEIR SEEDS
THROUGH SPACE
UNTIL THEY FIND
ANOTHER PLANET.
THAT IS HOW THEY CONTINUE TO
REPRODUCE ACROSS THE UNIVERSE.
MY GOD. TALK ABOUT "SEWING"
THE SEEDS OF DESTRUCTION.
OH, PUT A SOCK IN IT.
HUH?
YOU DON’T HEAR
ANYONE ELSE
BLURTING OUT LAME‐ASS PUNS,
DO YA?
I’VE HAD
JUST ABOUT ENOUGH
OF YOUR SO‐CALLED
SENSE OF HUMOR,
YOU NORTH KANTO MONKEY!
IF YOU MOCK MY HOMETOWN
ONE MORE TIME,
I’M GONNA MIX YOU UP
WITH LIME WATER AND BOIL YOU!
OH, GET A ROOM!
I’M SORRY.
I HAD TO SAY IT.
KNOCK OFF
THAT INFERNAL BICKERING!
LADY SATSUKI’S PRESENT!
[ CHUCKLES ]
NO, IT’S FINE, GAMAGOORI.
I RATHER LIKE
LISTENING TO THEIR SQUABBLING.
IT MAKES ME FEEL
AS IF I’M HOME AGAIN.
M’LADY.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GIGGLES ]
[ BEEP ]
HERE WE GO.
I’VE HACKED INTO
THE REVOCS SATELLITES.
LET’S HAVE A LOOK
AT THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER.
SECURITY’S TIGHT, BUT I CAN
STILL CONTROL THEIR CAMERAS.
RAGYO.
AS EXPECTED,
THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER
IS HEADED FOR HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
WHY’S IT GOING THERE?
Satsuki: SIMPLE.
BY ATTACHING
THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER
TO THE ACADEMY’S TRANSMITTER,
RAGYO CAN SEND OUT THE SIGNAL
TO TRANSFORM HUMANITY
INTO LIFE FIBERS.
Kinagase: BITCHEN.
THEN ALL WE NEED TO DO
IS SMASH THE TRANSMITTER,
AND WE CAN STOP HER PLAN.
THERE IS ONE SMALL PROBLEM,
THOUGH.
WHAT’S THAT?
THE MISSILES THAT’LL BE
SLAMMING INTO US SHORTLY!
NEXT TIME
WE GOT MISSILES COMING AT US,
LET US KNOW SOONER!
Satsuki:
MR. MIKISUGI.
"M‐MISTER"?
IF YOU DON’T MIND,
I’D LIKE YOU IN COMMAND
OF THIS OPERATION.
SERIOUSLY?
RYUKO AND I
WILL STOP RAGYO.
I’LL BE BUSY WITH THAT,
SO I CANNOT COMMAND, AS WELL.
GOOD POINT.
ELITE FOUR,
ARE WE CLEAR ON THAT?
M’LADY.
IT’S OUR JOB TO DESTROY
HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S TRANSMITTER.
AND SATSUKI AND RYUKO’S JOB
IS TO KEEP RAGYO
AND THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER
OFF OUR BACKS!
Y’ALL KNOW WHAT TO DO?
GOOD!
THEN LET’S GET THIS SHOW
ROLLING!
CAPTAIN BOSSY
STRIKES AGAIN.
ARE YOU READY TO GO?
YEAH. ARE YOU SURE
YOU’RE READY?
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
BETTER HURRY UP
AND GET CHANGED, THEN.
SOROI: Lady Ryuko,
look after your sister for me.
WILL DO.
READY, SI‐‐ SI‐‐
SI‐‐ SI‐‐
[ CHUCKLES LIGHTLY ]
YOU DON’T HAVE TO ACKNOWLEDGE
THE BOND BETWEEN US.
I CAN FEEL YOUR BLOOD
FLOWING THROUGH JUNKETSU.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
R‐REALLY?
YES.
[ Voice breaking ]
HOW TOUCHING.
NOT NOW, SENKETSU.
SUCK IT UP.
OKAY. LET’S GO!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
♪ DON’T LOSE YOUR WAY
IN YOUR MIND ♪
♪ WE HAVE TO BE AS ONE ♪
♪ DON’T BE AFRAID,
MY SWEETHEART ♪
♪ THIS IS THE WAY
TO BE MORE STRONG ♪
♪ HARBOR MY DEEP SECRET ♪
♪ IT MAKES ME SO BLUE ♪
♪ RUN THROUGH THIS GAME ♪
♪ BEFORE MY BODY IS DRY ♪
♪ DON’T LOSE YOUR WAY
IN YOUR MIND ♪
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE!
LIFE FIBER OVERRIDE!
KAMUI SENKETSU!
KAMUI JUNKETSU!
♪ DON’T BE AFRAID,
MY SWEETHEART ♪
RYUKO.
I SEE THEM.
SENKETSU SHIPPU!
GRAB ON!
NO. I HAVE THIS.
JUNKETSU SENPU!
♪ RUN THROUGH THIS GAME ♪
Senketsu: LOOK AT THAT!
IT ABSORBED MY ABILITIES!
WAY TO GO, SATSUKI!
LET’S HURRY.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
LET’S SET SAIL
FOR HONNOUJI ACADEMY!
[ GASPS ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
SATSUKI! THE SHIP!
YES, I KNOW. I SEE IT.
YOU GOT TO BE
FRIGGIN’ KIDDING!
[ EERIE WAILING ]
Inumuta: IT LOOKS LIKE SOME KIND
OF COMBAT‐SPEC MEGA‐COVERS.
Sanageyama:
AND IT FEELS MEGA‐GNARLY.
[ WHISTLING ]
[ ALL GRUNT ]
Mako: YAAAAAH!
MAKO MANKANSHOKU,
HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT,
IS BACK IN ACTION!
DON’T WORRY, RYUKO.
I’LL KEEP THIS SHIP SAFE
FROM THE BAD GUYS,
NO MATTER WHAT!
Senketsu: CAN A SINGLE CLOTH
COVER THE PLANET?
RAGYO’S GIANT
WRAPPING CLOTH CAN,
BUT IF THAT HAPPENS,
THIS ANIME WOULD BE OVER,
SO RYUKO, SATSUKI, MAKO,
AND THE UPGRADED ELITE FOUR
MUST STOP IT.
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"IMITATION GOLD."