NO. PLEASE DON’T.
FOR GOD’S SAKES, STOP!
[ GASPING ]
SENKETSU!
[ GASPS ]
YOU KNOW, DON’T YOU THINK
IT’S KIND OF WEIRD
HOW YOU’RE ALWAYS WAKING UP
ON MY COUCH HALF‐NAKED?
[ GASPS ]
HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT
ABOUT BEING A NUDIST?
[ BLADE ZINGS ]
ANY MORE OF YOUR LAME JOKES,
AND YOU’LL BE EATING THIS.
OKAY, OKAY, RELAX.
WHO TOOK YOU OUT THIS TIME?
IT WAS NUI HARIME
DISGUISED AS NAGITA.
OH, THAT EXPLAINS IT.
WAIT. WHEN YOU FOUND ME
OUT THERE,
WAS I LIKE THIS?
UH‐HUH. HATE TO THINK
OF WHAT WOULD’VE HAPPENED
IF I GOT THERE ANY LATER,
THOUGH.
IF THE COPS CAME,
THEY WOULD’VE ARRESTED YOU
FOR INDECENT EXPOSURE.
[ BLADE ZINGS ]
HOPE YOU’RE HUNGRY.
SOMEONE’S TESTY.
YEAH, WELL...
[ SIGHS ] WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
SENKETSU IS GONE.
NUI HARIME TOOK HIM, HUH?
TOOK HIM? SHE CHOPPED HIM
INTO PIECES.
I WAS TOO WEAK TO STOP HER,
AND I COULDN’T SUMMON
HIS POWER,
AND NOW HE’S GONE.
Senketsu’s voice:
NO, I’M NOT GONE.
[ GASPS ]
[ BLADE ZINGS ]
YOUR DUMBASS IMPERSONATIONS
AIN’T HELPING THINGS.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU’RE TALKING ABOUT.
I’M JUST SITTING HERE
LISTENING TO YOU.
CALM DOWN, RYUKO.
[ GASPS ]
YOU DID IT AGAIN!
I DID NOT. HE’S RIGHT HERE.
[ GASPS ]
SENKETSU! THANK GOD!
YOU’RE ALIVE!
I’M ALIVE BECAUSE YOU HELD ON
TO ME SO TIGHTLY.
THIS IS ALL THAT’S LEFT?
WHERE’D THE REST OF YOU GO?
YOUR SLEEVES, YOUR SHOULDERS,
YOUR SKIRT?!
I HATE TO SAY IT, BUT THAT’S
PRETTY MUCH ALL I FOUND
WHEN I GOT TO YA.
YOU WERE UNCONSCIOUS,
HOLDING ON TO THAT SCRAP
LIKE YOUR LIFE
DEPENDED ON IT.
I KNOW WHERE THE REST
OF MY BODY IS.
IT WAS DIVIDED UP
AMONG THE STUDENTS
ON THE RAID TRIP.
THE REST OF YOU’S
IN KANSAI, HUH?
YES, AND IT WAS ALL
SATSUKI KIRYUIN’S DOING.
DAMN HER ASS!
ALWAYS SCREWING WITH ME!
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
YO, WHATCHA DOING
DOWN HERE, MR. MIKISUGI?
I’M HERE, KID,
BECAUSE I’M HANGING UP
MY TEACHER PANTS FOR GOOD.
THE TIME HAS COME.
TODAY I GIVE UP MY COVER
AS A HOMEROOM TEACHER
AT HONNOUJI ACADEMY
AND PRANCE AROUND
IN MY TRUE IDENTITY.
UHH! I’M REALLY
A SPLENDID NAKED OFFICER
OF NUDIST BEACH,
WAGING AN ALL‐OUT WAR
AGAINST THE SCOURGE
OF LIFE FIBERS!
AND NOW THAT THE CLOTHES
ARE OFF, LET’S ROCK!
COME ON! NUDE SHOOTING STAR!
[ CAR APPROACHES,
TIRES SCREECH ]
AAH!
FAREWELL, HONNOUJI ACADEMY!
WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT ABOUT?
GIVE ME THE GLOW!
YOU’RE SO HOT! GOOD‐LOOKIN’!
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
I’VE PICKED THE STUDENTS WITH
HIGHEST LIFE FIBER TOLERANCE
AND DISTRIBUTED THE SCRAPS
OF KAMUI SENKETSU AMONG THEM.
WE’VE ATTACHED THEM TO
OUR SCHOOL RAID SPEC UNIFORMS.
THAT WAY, WE CAN DETERMINE
WHETHER OR NOT THE SCRAPS
CAN BE USED AS A POWER‐UP TO
BOOST THE UNIFORMS’ ABILITIES.
GOOD.
[ BEEP ]
Man over P. A.:
THE KYOTO RAID TRIP BRIGADE,
LED BY NONON JA‐KUZURE,
THE KOBE RAID TRIP BRIGADE,
LED BY IRA GAMAGOORI,
AND THE OSAKA RAID TRIP
BRIGADE, LED BY UZU SANAGEYAMA,
ARE IN POSITION
AND AWAITING FURTHER ORDERS.
THE TRI‐CITY
SPECIAL INTELLIGENCE UNIT
IS ALSO STANDING BY.
THE INFO NETWORKS
OF ALL THE SCHOOLS IN THE CITY
ARE OURS.
Currently, we’re monitoring
their telecom
and net connections.
At your command, m’lady, we will
shut the whole thing down.
PERFECT. THE SUCCESS
OF THIS MISSION WILL PLACE
ALL OF KANSAI’S HIGH SCHOOLS
UNDER OUR UMBRELLA.
TRI‐CITY SCHOOLS RAID TRIP
BRIGADE, BEGIN YOUR ASSAULT!
I’M WITH THE KAMI‐KOBE
HIGH SCHOOL ARMED FACTION!
KYUJI OBAYASHI!
AND I’M HIS DEPUTY,
KENTA SAKURAMIYA!
THERE’S NO WAY IN HELL
THEY’RE GETTING THROUGH US.
READY? LAUNCH THE MOLOTOVS!
[ ALL YELLING ]
[ YELLING ]
WE GOT THE AMERICAN HIGH SCHOOL
ON OUR SIDE!
AND WITH THEIR ARMORED
FOOTBALL CORPS,
WE’LL CRUSH THESE DICKS!
NOT SO FAST, YOU!
I REPRESENT HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
AS COMMANDER OF THE KOBE SCHOOLS
RAID TRIP BRIGADE,
I’M IRA GAMAGOORI!
AND SINCE YOU’VE CHOSEN
TO RESIST US,
WE HAVE NO OPTION
BUT TO RETALIATE!
ENHANCED COMMITTEE MEMBERS,
FALL IN!
WHAT THE HELL?
THAT DOES IT!
WE’RE GONNA MOW YOU SUCKERS
DOWN WITH OUR ARMORED PADS!
TEAM, ATTACK!
All: LET’S GO!
FIRE!
[ WHOOSHING ]
All: OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
SCHOOL REGULATIONS ARE HEAVIER
THAN STONE TO A STUDENT,
AND THE GUIDEBOOK
THAT CONTAINS THESE RULES
IS HARDER THAN STEEL!
NO ONE CAN OPPOSE
HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S REGULATIONS!
THEY ARE IRONCLAD!
IF YOU THINK YOUR ARMOR
CAN WITHSTAND OUR RULES,
THEN STEP FORWARD!
TASTE OUR FULL METAL
DISCIPLINARY GUIDEBOOK
REGULATION...HURRICANE!
OH!
[ GROANS ]
THIS IS THE MIGHT
OF HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
THE MIGHT AND GLORY OF
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT,
LADY SATSUKI!
LET’S PLAY THIS... FORTISSIMO!
[ ALL YELLING ]
WHAT THE HELL?
Genbu: [ LAUGHS ]
WARRIORS OF THE EAST,
WE BID THEE A HEARTY WELCOME
TO OUR CAMPUS.
ABEGAMO ACADEMY HAS STOOD
FOR A THOUSAND YEARS.
IT IS THE LYNCHPIN OF KYOTO’S
DEFENSES IN OUR ANCIENT CAPITAL.
IF THOU WISH TO AVOID
A FATE MOST PAINFUL,
LEAVE AT ONCE!
OR IF THOU CHOOSETH TO STAY,
THOU SHALT BE BAPTIZED
IN A TORRENT
OF DEMONS AND MONSTERS.
OH, PLEASE, YOU UPPITY TWERPS.
NO WAY THIS DUMP HAS BEEN AROUND
FOR A THOUSAND YEARS.
[ ROARS ]
WHAT IS THAT?! AAH!
THEY’RE MONSTERS!
THEY’RE GONNA EAT US!
GUARDIAN STUDENT OF THE NORTH,
TARO GENBU.
GUARDIAN STUDENT OF THE SOUTH,
JIRO SUZAKU.
GUARDIAN STUDENT OF THE EAST,
SABURO SEIRYU.
GUARDIAN STUDENT OF THE WEST,
SHIRO BYAKKO!
WE ARE THE DIVINE FORMATION,
THE IMPENETRABLE DEFENSE
OF ABEGAMO ACADEMY.
TRY AS THOU MIGHT,
YOU KANTO BARBARIANS
CANNOT DEFEAT US.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOUR "MONSTERS" ARE JUST A BUNCH
OF LAME‐ASS SMOKE EFFECTS.
CALM DOWN, PEOPLE!
THESE DORKS ARE JUST TRYING TO
PSYCH YOU OUT.
[ CROWD YELLING ]
Inumuta:
WHAT FASCINATING PEOPLE.
HUH?
WOULD YOU MIND
IF I FOUGHT THEM FOR A WHILE?
WHERE’D YOU COME FROM?
YOU’RE SUPPOSED TO BE
IN OSAKA RIGHT NOW.
I AM IN OSAKA.
THIS IS A HOLOGRAM
COURTESY OF THE FILM CLUB.
HUH?
ARMED ARTS CLUB, ADVANCE!
THIS IS A NON‐EUCLIDEAN
SPACE CREATION RITUAL
CALCULATED BY THE MATH CLUB.
ARTS CLUB,
THIS IS YOUR PALETTE
FOR A PARADOX PAINTING.
[ GRUNTS ]
OUR BARRIER! WHAT KIND
OF SORCERY IS THIS?!
UH...
AN ESCHER TOPOLOGY ATTACK.
A WHAT ATTACK?
THE DIVINE FORMATION USED
GEOMAGNETISM
TO BLANKET THE ARENA WITH
SPECIAL ELECTROMAGNETIC WAVES,
AND IN SO DOING,
CAUSED DISRUPTIONS
IN THE NERVE SIGNALS
OF THE BRAIN.
BUT THE PICTURE THE ARTS CLUB
DREW JUST NOW
ALTERED THE PHASE SPACE
IN THE ARENA
AND INTERRUPTED
THEIR GEOMAGNETISM.
WE HAVE NEGATED THEIR BARRIER!
I DIDN’T GET
ANY OF THAT,
EXCEPT THE PART
ABOUT OBNOXIOUS JERKS
BEATING
OTHER OBNOXIOUS JERKS.
YES, WELL...
HUH?
YOU SHOULD HAVE NO TROUBLE
WITH THEM NOW. LOOK.
THOU ART UNCOUTH,
AND FURTHERMORE,
YOUR WORDS ARE STRANGE!
PREPARE TO BE TROUNCED!
TROUNCE, TROUNCE, TROUNCE!
WELL, MY WORK’S DONE HERE.
YOURS HAS JUST BEGUN.
HUH. THANKS FOR NOTHIN’.
OKAY, PEOPLE, LET’S GET JAZZED!
[ ALL CHEER ]
ARMED WIND INSTRUMENTS,
COMBAT ORCHESTRATION!
"POMP AND CIRCUMSTANCE"!
[ "POMP AND CIRCUMSTANCE"
PLAYING ]
AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
What’s up,
you Honnouji Academy dipshits?
I’m Kaneo Takarada,
student council pres
of Naniwa Kinman "H"!
Y’all might think you the man
up in Kobe and Kyoto,
but this is Osaka, G.,
so unless you want
my foot up your ass,
get to steppin’!
[ CHUCKLES ] NEWS TRAVELS FAST
IN THESE PARTS, HUH?
I THOUGHT WE SHUT
YOUR COMMUNICATIONS OFF.
Who needs it when I have
the flapping gums
of all the grannies in Osaka
on my side?
You might have put the net
on lockdown,
but those chicks can spread
a rumor faster
than a pimp can slap a ho, yo.
Check it!
You in my house now, homie.
The O‐to‐the‐Saka’s
a merchant town,
and money’s what makes
this place go round.
The G. with the most coin
wins up in here, G.!
WHAT A DOUCHE.
WELL, HERE’S THE DEAL.
YOUR SYSTEM’S GOTTEN STALE,
SO WE’RE HERE TO ESTABLISH
A NEW WORLD ORDER.
IN THE NAME OF SATSUKI KIRYUIN,
I’M ORDERING YOU TO SURRENDER
OR FACE THE CONSEQUENCES!
You talking crazy talk.
You high or somethin’?
All criticizin’
our way of life.
Hell, you don’t know
the power of paper.
Well, we gonna wake
your ass up to reality,
by bitch‐slappin’ you
with fat stacks of cash!
All right, homies,
make it rain.
All: YOU GOT IT, G.!
[ CLACK ]
THOSE AREN’T BULLETS.
THEY’RE BILLS, SIR.
THEY’RE NOT SHOOTING BULLETS
AT US!
THEY’RE SHOOTING
WADS OF PAPER MONEY!
THEY’RE USING MONEY
AS A WEAPON!
I put my dollars
where my mouth is, yo.
So get lost, you suckas!
THIS FEELS WEIRD.
NOTHING LIKE
A LEGIT BANK NOTE.
IT’S COUNTERFEIT!
Nah, they ain’t counterfeit.
They’s Takarada Bucks.
TAKA WHAT?
Takarada Bucks, yo.
That’s bonafide currency.
If it’s got
the Takarada Syndicate’s name
on it,
it’s as good as gold
in Osaka.
Hell, they worth more than
that broke‐ass Japanese paper.
Didn’t you know? Oh, right.
Y’all’s from northern Kanto.
SON OF A...
ONE MORE CRACK
ABOUT NORTHERN KANTO,
AND I’M GONNA GRIND YOU
INTO KONNYAKU!
Keep dreamin’,
’cause we gon’ turn your asses
into takoyaki first!
Jack ’em up!
ARMORED PING PONG CLUB,
FRONT AND CENTER!
All: PING PONG!
ARE YOU READY, SUMO CLUB?!
STOMP ATTACK!
All: DOSUKOI!
All: OHH!
ARCHERY AND TRACK CLUBS,
MOVE UP YOUR ULTRA
LONG RANGE SQUADS!
UNLOAD EVERYTHING YOU’VE GOT
ON ’EM!
[ GRUNTING ]
Not bad, son!
NICE! NOW STORM THE BUILDING!
[ ALL YELLING ]
Y’all ain’t shit!
Push ’em back!
THEY CAN RESIST
GOKU UNIFORMS?
Huh! What, you think
the Kiryuins
are the only game in town?
Takarada Syndicate cash
is no joke, dawg!
[ EXPLOSIONS ]
HUP, HUP, HUP, HUP, HUP, HUP,
HUP, HUP, HUP, HUP, HUP, HUP!
IT’S GONNA SUCK SO BAD
IF I CAME ALL THIS WAY
AND ALL I GOT TO DO IS HAND
THESE STUPID BALLS OFF. HUH?!
OH, MY GOD!
Choir: ♪ HALLELUJAH ♪
IT’S THE SYMBOL OF OSAKA!
A STREET VENDOR SELLING
JUMBO TAKOYAKI!
IT’S NOT A TRIP TO OSAKA
IF I DIDN’T GET TO EAT SOME!
AAH! I DON’T HAVE ANY MONEY!
I WAS FORCED TO COME HERE,
AND NOW I’M HERE,
AND I DON’T EVEN KNOW WHY
I’M HERE!
I DIDN’T BRING ANY MONEY
’CAUSE I DIDN’T BRING MY WALLET,
AND NOW I’M HERE, AND I’M BROKE!
JEEZ, I WISH THERE WAS SOMEONE
THROWING MONEY AROUND!
[ GRUNTS ]
NO WAY! I FOUND A GUY
SHOOTING MONEY OUT OF A GUN!
[ YELLING ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ] STEP UP
FOR A ONE‐WAY TICKET TO HELL!
ACTUALLY, I’D LIKE A ONE‐WAY
TICKET TO HEAVEN, PLEASE.
GO ON, SHOOT!
COME ON, SHOOT ME!
NOTHING CAN KEEP ME
FROM GETTING WHAT I WANT
WHEN THERE’S SOMETHING
I REALLY, REALLY WANT!
SO SHOOT ME!
GET AWAY FROM ME!
[ IMITATING GUNFIRE SOUNDS ]
WHAT THE HELL?!
THANKS!
[ SKIDDING ]
HI THERE! MAY I PLEASE HAVE
SOME TAKOYAKI?
HOW MUCH WILL THIS BUY? HUH?
WHOA!
THEY GOT OSAKA OKONOMIYAKI
THAT YOU EAT
WITH A SPATULA HERE!
AND KUSHIKATSU THAT YOU
SHOULDN’T DOUBLE DIP!
AND KETSUNE,
NOT KITSUNE UDON!
THEY EVEN GOT BUTAMAN, IKAYAKI,
NEGIYAKI, AND MORE!
NOW THIS IS OSAKA!
A MIRACLE MILE OF FOOD!
Choir: ♪ HALLELUJAH ♪
[ CROWD SHOUTING ]
ONE LAST PLATOON TO GO.
ATTACK!
[ EXPLOSION ]
All: AAH!
HA! SORRY ABOUT
THE COCK BLOCK,
BUT WE WANTED TO SHOW YOU
A LITTLE SOMETHIN’
WE HAD OUR PALS
IN THE RUSSIAN MOB SMUGGLE IN.
AND IF THERE’S ONE THING
WE KNOW,
NO PUSSY‐ASS UNIFORMS
CAN STAND UP TO A TANK.
RESISTANCE IS FUTILE!
YOUR TANK’S LIKE PAPER AGAINST
OUR IRONCLAD RULES! UHH!
BOO‐YAH!
CHECK OUT KOBE’S NEW PRODUCT ‐‐
COMPOSITE MEAT ARMOR!
WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT THAT,
BRAH?
LOOK AT HOW YOUR IRONCLAD RULES
GET SWALLOWED UP
BY ALL THAT BEAUTIFUL KOBE BEEF!
THEY’RE MELTING IN THE MARBLIN’!
NOW WHY DON’T YOU BE
A GOOD BOY
AND GIVE UP, GAMAGOORI?
HA! WHY DON’T YOU TRY
TO MAKE ME?
[ GRUNTS ] YOU HEARD
THE DUMBASS. FIRE!
FORTIFIED DISCIPLINARY UNIT!
All: DISCIPLINE!
OUR SHIT’S COMING BACK, YO!
[ SCREAMING ]
OW, IT’S HOT!
OH, GOD, IT BURNS!
DAMN, THAT SMELLS GOOD! YUM!
THOSE KAMUI POWER‐UPS
ARE UNBELIEVABLE.
I LIKE! NOW FINISH THEM!
All: DISCIPLINE!
[ ALL YELLING ]
AND NOW THAT YOUR LITTLE TOY’S
OUT OF COMMISSION,
SURRENDER PEACEFULLY, OR ELSE!
[ ALL CHOMPING ]
HUH?
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
DAMN YOU, MATOI!
DON’T MIND ME!
JUST GETTING SENKETSU BACK!
[ TIRES SCREECH, ENGINE REVS ]
[ GROANS ]
[ CHEERING ]
♪
[ YELLING ]
THAT’S IT! KEEP POUNDING ’EM
WITH YOUR SOUND!
YOU GUYS MAKE
SUCH BEAUTIFUL MUSIC
WITH YOUR KAMUI ENHANCEMENTS.
♪
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
WELL, THAT JUST ABOUT DOES IT.
HMM?
[ SCREAMING, ENGINE REVVING ]
♪
[ YELLS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
[ REVVING ]
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
RELAX. I DON’T GOT TIME FOR YOU.
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
SHE CAN’T TALK TO ME
LIKE THAT!
OW! MY BALLS!
WHAT’D YOU EXPECT?
IT’S A BAMBOO SWORD.
[ PHONE RINGS ]
INUMUTA:
Gamagoori and Jakuzare
are wrapping things up
on their end.
How are you doing?
WE BEAT DOWN MOST OF THE KIDS
FROM KINMAN HIGH.
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL TELL
LADY SATSUKI
OSAKA WILL BE OURS SOON.
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT,
IT WON’T, PLAYAH!
TAKARADA?
YOU STRAIGHT UP UNDERESTIMATE
MY POWER UP IN HERE,
THEM KIDDIES AIN’T
THE ONLY PEEPS IN MY POCKET.
HI, Y’ALLS! HOW’S BUSINESS?!
BUSINESS IS BOOMIN’!
BASTARD! YOU’VE GOT CIVILIANS
FIGHTING FOR YOU, TOO?
TRUE DAT, YO!
BUT THESE HOMIES
AIN’T YOUR AVERAGE
EVERYDAY G’s, G.
THEY’S COMBAT CITIZENS,
PAID FOR BY YOURS TRULY.
THEY DON’T LOOK LIKE MUCH,
BUT THESE BITCHES IS TOUGH!
AND THEY WANT MONEY SO BAD,
THEY ITCHIN’ TO THROW DOWN!
WHOA‐HO‐HO! THAT’S GOTTA BE
THE NANIWA SKY TOWER!
THEY JUST BUILT THAT!
I’M SO GOING TO THE TOP OF IT!
I DON’T KNOW WHY, BUT EVERY TIME
I SEE A TALL BUILDING,
I HAVE TO CLIMB IT.
[ SCREAMING ]
OH, CRAP!
[ EXPLOSION ]
YOU LIKE THAT?
ME AND THE I HEART OSAKA BRIGADE
CAN DO IT ALL DAY.
MY HOMIES LOVE PAPER,
AND THEY GON’ DO
WHAT THEY CAN TO GET IT.
SO IF YOU WANT MY TOWN,
YOU GON’ HAVE TO KILL ALL OF US.
YOU’RE ALL FRICKIN’ CRAZY.
IF WE GO ON LIKE THIS,
WE’RE GONNA LEVEL OSAKA!
WE’LL JUST BUILD IT
BACK UP AGAIN, YO.
THE CONTRACTORS DON’T CARE,
’CAUSE THEY GON’ LOVE
THE EXTRA WORK.
OKAY, HOMIE!
WHOEVS KILLS THIS HICK
GETS A MILLION
TAKARADA BUCKS!
WHO DOWN TO GET SOME?!
[ CHEERING ]
UH‐OH! [ Singsongy ] LOOKS LIKE
SOMEONE’S OUTNUMBERED FOR REAL!
[ HELICOPTER WHIRRING ]
[ GASPS ]
YOU’RE KIDDING!
SAY WHAT?!
WHAT’S UP WITH THAT LIGHT?
[ GASPS ]
LADY SATSUKI!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
OWIE.
[ YELLING ]
WHAT THE...
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Mako: HEY! THAT’S A PIECE
OF SENKETSU!
MANKANSHOKU!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
YOU’RE SUPPOSED TO BE
IN THE BALL BRIGADE!
UH‐OH!
YOU DESERTED YOUR POST
TO GO GOOF AROUND THE CITY,
DIDN’T YA?!
AAH!
YOU THINK THIS RAID TRIP’S
FOR FUN? TIME TO GET BURNED!
PLEASE, NO! I’M SORRY!
AAH!
OHH!
GET YOUR HANDS OFF HER!
HEY, RYUKO!
I GUESS YOU HAD A ROUGH DAY
CHILLIN’ AND SIGHTSEEIN’, HUH?
YOU DON’T EVEN KNOW
THE HALF OF IT!
WHOA! SENKETSU IS ALL CHOPPED UP
LIKE A SALAD!
YEAH, BUT I’M GONNA GET HIM
BACK TO NORMAL.
AS SOON AS I FIND
ALL THE PIECES,
I’M GONNA MAKE HIM
GOOD AS NEW.
YEAH, I KNOW YOU WILL!
AFTER ALL,
HE’S YOUR ONLY UNIFORM.
Senketsu:
THERE IS ONLY ONE PIECE LEFT.
AWESOME. HOW ARE YOU DOING,
THOUGH?
DOING RATHER WELL, ACTUALLY,
BUT YOU’VE CHANGED A LOT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THE ONLY PART OF ME
GIVING YOU POWER RIGHT NOW
IS THIS SCARF YOU FASHIONED,
AND YET YOU’VE DESTROYED
EVERY GOKU UNIFORM
THAT HAD A PIECE OF ME
SEWN ONTO IT.
YOU’RE EVEN STRONGER NOW
THAN YOU WERE BEFORE.
REALLY? HOW’D I GET STRONGER?
Mako: IT’S ’CAUSE THE THING
YOU WANT THE MOST
IS ALMOST IN REACH!
HUH?
YOU’RE SO OBSESSED WITH
GETTING SENKETSU BACK TO NORMAL,
IT’S GIVEN YOU THE STRENGTH
TO KICK ALL THIS BUTT!
I’M LIKE THAT, ONLY I GET
FIXATED OVER MONEY.
I HEARD THAT, AND WHEN IT
COMES TO FIXATIONS,
YOU’RE HARDCORE.
WELL, YOU GOTTA BE HARDCORE
ABOUT FIXATED RATES.
YEAH...OKAY. ONE TO GO.
YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS, SENKETSU?
YES, I DO. HOWEVER...
WHAT?
THE PERSON WHO HAS
THE FINAL PIECE
IS SATSUKI KIRYUIN.
UGH.
SATSUKI?
WHAT?!
WHATEVER. I DON’T CARE
IF SHE’S GOT IT.
I’M GONNA GET YOU BACK
TO NORMAL.
BUT IN MY CURRENT CONDITION,
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZATION
IS IMPOSSIBLE.
HOW DO YOU PLAN
ON FIGHTING HER?
DON’T WORRY. I’LL JUST MAKE UP
FOR WHAT YOU CAN’T DO.
LIKE YOU SAID, I’M NOT
THE SAME OLD RYUKO ANYMORE.
I’M STRONGER ’CAUSE I GOT
MY SIGHTS ON SOMETHIN’,
AND I’M GONNA GET IT.
AIN’T THAT RIGHT, MAKO?
MM‐HMM!
RYUKO...
HERE I COME.
SATSUKI KIRYUIN!
♪
Senketsu: MONEY TALKS IN OSAKA.
THEY’RE MONEY‐MAD IN OSAKA.
RYUKO SHOWS UP LOOKING
FOR THE SCATTERED PIECES
OF HER KAMUI SENKETSU.
WILL KAMUI SENKETSU
BE PUT BACK TOGETHER?
WAIT. I’M TALKING ABOUT ME.
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"DON’T STOP ME NOW."