[ KEYBOARD KEYS CLACKING ]
"THE REVOCS CORPORATION,
RESPONSIBLE FOR 70% OF
GLOBAL APPAREL SALES."
HMM, I’M IMPRESSED.
OH, THEY’RE PART OF THE KIRYUIN
CONGLOMERATE. INTERESTING.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THIS LITTLE SUPER‐HACKER’S
DECIDED TO ALTER
THE COMPANY’S DESTINY.
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
UH‐OH, SOMEONE’S STOCKS
ARE IN THE TOILET.
[ ALARM BEEPING ]
OH, CRAP,
THEY’RE TRACKING ME.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING ]
AAH!
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
[ SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE ]
HOW’D THEY PINPOINT
MY LOCATION SO QUICKLY?!
AAH!
[ GUNSHOTS ]
[ GASPS ]
HEY, WHAT HAPPENED TO
"STOP, OR WE’LL SHOOT"?
[ GUNS COCK ]
I’M ‐‐ I’M SORRY.
I DIDN’T MEAN ANYTHING!
SERIOUSLY, GUYS!
I’M JUST A DUMB KID,
MESSIN’ AROUND ON THE COMPUTER!
[ GUNS COCK ]
WHOA, EASY DOES IT.
I SAID I’M SORRY.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
[ GASPS ]
DID YOU SAY YOU WERE JUST A KID?
A TRESPASSER IS MORE LIKE IT.
IT’S A GIRL?
CORRECT, THE REVOCS SITE
HAS THE TIGHTEST SECURITY
ON THE PLANET AND YET SOMEHOW,
YOU MANAGED TO CRACK IT.
YOU MIGHT BE YOUNG, BUT YOU MOST
CERTAINLY ARE NOT DUMB.
WAIT, YOU’RE THE BOSS?
TELL ME WHY YOU DID THIS.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
IT WAS A CHANCE
TO CRACK THE TOUGHEST FIREWALL
ON THE NET.
HOW TRIVIAL.
WHAT?
YOU’RE PROFICIENT AT DISRUPTING
THINGS IN THE VIRTUAL WORLD,
BUT HAVE YOU EVER CONSIDERED
USING YOUR SKILLS
TO DISRUPT THE REAL WORLD?
WHAT THE HELL’S
HONNOUJI ACADEMY HIGH SCHOOL?
MEET ME THERE
IF YOU WANNA CHANGE THE WORLD,
HOUKA INUMUTA.
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
HMM.
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
I WONDER
HOW CRAZY THIS’LL GET.
HEY, BACK OFF!
QUIT YOUR PUSHING!
WE WERE HERE FIRST.
HAVEN’T YOU EVER HEARD OF
SQUATTER’S RIGHTS?
THIS CROWD’S SO FRIGGIN’ HUGE,
I DOUBT ANYONE WOULD NOTICE IF I
SNAGGED A COUPLE OF WALLETS.
DON’T EVEN TRY IT!
SERIOUSLY, DON’T.
[ Strained voice ]
I WAS KIDDING.
DARN IT! THEY WON’T LET ME
BE RYUKO’S ASSISTANT!
IF ONLY I COULD BE
OUT THERE WITH HER,
I COULD TOTALLY HELP HER
KICK BUTT!
[ GASPS ]
GAMAGOORI! WHERE THE HECK
ARE ALL YOUR CLOTHES?
TAKE IT EASY, MANKANSHOKU.
I’VE BEEN DEMOTED, THAT’S ALL.
I’M A NO‐STAR NOW, LIKE YOU.
AND SINCE
I’M THE SAME RANK AS YOU,
IT’S ONLY PROPER I SIT
AND WATCH TODAY’S FIGHT
FROM THE NO‐STAR SECTION.
LADY SATSUKI, I SWEAR I’LL WORK
MY WAY UP FROM THIS SHAME
AND RETURN TO YOUR GOOD GRACES.
I’LL SHOW YOU THAT YOUR KINDNESS
TO ME WAS NOT IN VAIN!
YOU WANT SOME? COME ON,
LET’S GO!
YOU AND ME! RIGHT HERE!
[ GRUNTING ]
HMM?
I’M GONNA BE CHEERIN’ RYUKO ON
WITH EVERYTHING I GOT!
SO IF YOU’RE HERE
TO START TROUBLE,
GET READY TO GET STOMPED!
[ GASPS ]
CHEER ALL YOU WANT.
IT WON’T MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE
IN THE END!
NO ONE CAN DEFEAT
LADY SATSUKI’S ELITE FIGHTERS.
NO ONE!
IF THAT’S TRUE, THEN HOW COME
YOU’RE SITTING HERE?
[ GROWLS ]
GET HER, INUMUTA! BASH HER,
CRUSH HER, SHOW HER NO MERCY!
KICK HIS BUTT, RYUKO!
KICK IT!
[ SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY ]
ACTIVATING THE NOISE CANCELER.
[ SHOUTING STOPS ]
I’D RATHER NOT HEAR THE CROAKS
OF A BEATEN TOAD.
HUH!
SO NOW SHE’S BEING MERCIFUL
TO LOSERS.
I WONDER WHAT
OUR MIGHTY QUEEN’S UP TO.
DON’T BE SECOND‐GUESSING
LADY SATSUKI.
OH, MY GOD,
EVER SINCE YOU WENT BLIND,
YOUR INTUITION’S GOTTEN SHARPER
AND EVEN MORE OBNOXIOUS.
IF YOU KEEP DOUBTING HER,
YOU’RE GONNA FIND YOURSELF
IN A WORLD OF HURT.
I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT YOU GUYS DON’T KNOW HER
HALF AS WELL AS I DO.
[ SCOFFS ]
[ BEEPING ]
YOUR KAMUI’S TRANSFORMATION
WAS FASCINATING,
BUT I NOTICED
YOU’RE BREATHING HEAVIER
AND YOUR HEART RATE’S ELEVATED.
I HOPE YOU DIDN’T
OVEREXERT YOURSELF,
FIGHTING WITH GAMAGOORI.
[ SCOFFS ] YEAH, AS IF!
COME ON,
I DON’T GOT ALL DAY!
YOU’RE RIGHT, YOU DON’T.
BEGIN.
[ HORN BLARES ]
M’LADY.
THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM
PROBE REGALIA.
[ CHEERING ]
PROBE REGALIA, HUH?
SURE DOESN’T LOOK LIKE MUCH.
[ BEEPING ]
I DON’T LIKE THIS. IT FEELS LIKE
HE’S STRIPPING US DOWN.
YEAH, I KNOW.
IT’S GIVIN’ ME THE CREEPS, TOO.
I DON’T KNOW HIS DEAL,
SO STAY SHARP.
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE,
KAMUI SENKETSU!
YES,
HER STAGE ONE COMBAT MODE.
THAT’S HOW SHE ALWAYS
STARTS A BATTLE.
[ SCREAMS ]
[ BEEPING ]
RIGHT...
[ SCREAMS ]
SHE’S FASTER THAN I THOUGHT.
[ CHEERING ]
[ BEEPING ]
YOU THINK I HAVEN’T SEEN
YOUR TYPE BEFORE?
WITH ALL YOUR, "OH, I’VE
ANALYZED ALL YOUR CAPABILITIES!"
AND, "I CAN ANTICIPATE
ALL YOUR MOVES!"
SAME OLD,
SAME OLD EVERY TIME!
THERE’S ONLY ONE WAY TO BEAT YOU
AT THIS GAME, GEEKSTER.
GET RECKLESS!
NOW I KNOW WHY YOUR REACTION
SPEED WAS HIGHER
THAN MY SENSORS PREDICTED.
YOU CAN BOOST
YOUR LIFE FIBER LINK
THROUGH THE FORCE
OF YOUR WILL, TOO.
THE GOKU UNIFORM’S INTERFACE
IS THE SAME,
BUT SINCE YOUR KAMUI
IS 100% LIFE FIBERS,
THE EFFECT IS GREATER.
THE QUESTION IS, HOW LONG CAN
YOUR BODY KEEP UP THIS PACE?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
AS LONG AS I WANT IT TO!
THAT’S WHAT I HOPED YOU’D SAY!
I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT MAKES YOU DIFFERENT!
WHY CAN YOUR BODY
MOVE LIKE THAT,
IN CLOTHES MADE ENTIRELY
OF LIFE FIBERS? SHOW ME!
WHAT THE ‐‐
HE’S GONE!
HE DISAPPEARED!
WHEN INUMUTA’S
GOKU UNIFORM GLISTENS,
IT’S LIKE A WHITE BUTTERFLY
ON A SNOWMAN.
HE DIDN’T DISAPPEAR.
IT’S OPTICAL CAMOUFLAGE!
NUH‐UNH! THERE’S NO
BUTTERFLIES IN THE WINTER!
THEY’D DIE IN THE COLD!
YOU MISS THE POINT.
TYPICAL MANKANSHOKU.
[ WIND HOWLS ]
WHEN IT COMES TO
CHAOTIC ATTACKS,
THE BEST STRATEGY
IS TO DODGE THEM.
THEN,
WHEN ONE COUNTERATTACKS,
ONE CAN INFLICT GREATER
PSYCHOLOGICAL DAMAGE.
[ GRUNTS, SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
THERE’S NOWHERE TO RUN!
START GIVING ME
SOME INTERESTING DATA,
OR I’M GOING TO BE
VERY DISAPPOINTED!
SENKETSU, TIME FOR PLAN "B" ‐‐
GET EVEN MORE RECKLESS!
UNDERSTOOD!
♪ DON’T LOSE YOUR WAY ♪
[ GRUNTS ]
AND NOW...
NO WAY!
THAT’S ONE BIG EYE!
[ Strained voice ]
IF I CAN’T SEE WHERE YOU’RE AT,
THEN I’LL JUST HAVE TO
ATTACK EVERYWHERE
AT THE SAME...TIME!
[ ALARM BLARING ]
EVADE...
[ GRUNTS ]
NO!
OH, THERE HE IS.
UH‐OH, THAT LAST ATTACK
TOTALLY WRECKED
HIS HIDE‐AND‐SEEK ABILITIES,
THE POOR THANG.
THAT’S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU RELY ON YOUR EYES.
YEAH, LOOK WHO’S TALKING!
[ GASPS ]
YOU SEE?
IF YOU MAKE A CRAZY ATTACK
EVEN CRAZIER,
AND YOU’RE BOUND TO HIT
SOMETHING!
LET’S DO THIS, SENKETSU.
YOUR BLOOD IS BOILING
EVEN HOTTER THAN USUAL.
YEAH, ’CAUSE THERE’S TWO MORE
TO GO AFTER THIS ONE.
[ ALARM BLARING ]
I’VE REACHED THE LIMIT OF
MY PROCESSING CAPACITY!
AAH! [ GRUNTING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ BLADE CLINKS ]
WHOA!
NOT SO FAST!
I HEREBY FORFEIT THIS BATTLE.
[ CROWD GASPS ]
[ GROWLS ]
OKAY, WHAT’S THE DEAL?
I JUST DIDN’T WANT TO LOSE
ALL THE DATA
I’VE GATHERED UP
TO THIS POINT.
WHAT?!
I DON’T CARE AT ALL
ABOUT WINNING.
WHAT I WANT IS DATA.
I CAN’T BELIEVE THAT NERD,
SAUNTERING AWAY LIKE THAT.
I WONDER WHY
LADY SATSUKI’S ALLOWING IT.
JAKUZURE,
PREPARE FOR BATTLE.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT’S UP? YOU SEEM SURPRISED.
SHOULDN’T BE.
AFTER ALL, YOU’VE KNOWN HER
LONGER THAN THE REST OF US.
OH, BLOW IT OUT YOUR ‐‐
WAIT, I’M UP NEXT!
AREN’T YOU GONNA WATCH?
NOPE, I GOTTA BREAK IN
MY BLADE REGALIA MARK TWO.
I’M UP AFTER YOU,
YOU KNOW.
WHAT’S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
YOU THINK I’LL LOSE?
ARE YOU MOCKING ME?!
SHE CLEARED THE SECOND ELITE,
TOO.
HMM, SHE’S DOING WAY BETTER
THAN I EXPECTED HER TO.
BUT STILL...
[ GROANS ] THERE YOU GO.
OH, YOU GOTTA BE SHITTIN’ ME!
WHERE DO YOU GET OFF,
CHARGIN’ US TO WATCH?
ELECTRICITY TO RUN
THAT TV COSTS MONEY,
SO YOU WANNA WATCH?
YOU PAY.
YOU SON‐OF‐A‐BITCHIN’
EXTORTIONIST!
YOU GREEDY OLD FART!
YEAH, WHAT THEY SAID!
IF YOU DON’T LIKE IT, LEAVE.
WHY DON’T YOU MAKE US,
YOU SENILE DICK?!
GET YOUR ASS OUT HERE,
JUNIOR!
[ GROANS ]
All: YOU WIN, WE’LL PAY.
[ SNORES, GASPS ]
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE
I’M DOING?
WATCHING THE FIGHT,
SAME AS YOU.
YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL
ABOUT FORFEITING,
SO I WON’T HARP ON YOU
ABOUT YOUR DECISION.
HOWEVER, WHY ARE YOU
WEARING A TRACKSUIT?
HAVE YOU NO SHAME?!
THE LOSER IS STRIPPED OF
THEIR GOKU UNIFORM,
BUT THERE’S NO RULE STATING
THEY HAVE TO BE NAKED.
[ SHUDDERS ]
KNOWING THE RULES
TRUMPS KNOWING SHAME,
MISTER DISCIPLINARY CHAIR.
OH, FORGIVE ME,
FORMER DISCIPLINARY CHAIR.
THANKS FOR THE REMINDER,
FORMER INFORMATION
AND STRATEGY CHAIR.
UH‐OH! IT’S STARTIN’ TO GET
HAIRY UP IN HERE!
IN A MINUTE, THESE GUYS ARE
GONNA START THROWIN’ PUNCHES!
[ GROANING ] OKAY!
IF THAT’S HOW IT’S GONNA BE
GIVE ’EM HELL, MAKO!
DON’T LET THESE GUYS
GET YOU DOWN, GIRL!
YOU’RE THE BEST
AND DON’T YOU FORGET IT!
APPARENTLY, YOUR FRIEND IS
CHEERING FOR HERSELF.
CLASSIC MAKO.
WOULDN’T HAVE IT ANY OTHER WAY.
YOUR PULSE AND RESPIRATION
HAVE RETURNED TO NORMAL.
SHE’S THE KEY TO GETTING YOU
TO RELAX, ISN’T SHE?
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ BLOWS WHISTLE ]
HUH?
ENTRANCE MARCH!
UNDER THE DOUBLE EAGLE!
♪
WHAT THE HELL?
[ PLAYING FANFARE ]
SHE KNOWS HOW TO MAKE
A CHEERFUL ENTRANCE.
SORRY FOR THE WAIT,
NEW GIRL.
AND JUST SO YOU KNOW, THIS WON’T
BE LIKE THOSE CLUMSY FIGHTS
YOU HAD WITH THE BOYS.
PREPARE TO BE PUMMELED
CHEERFULLY, JAUNTILY,
AND UTTERLY ONE‐SIDEDLY!
THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM
SYMPHONY REGALIA GRAVE!
[ CHEERING ]
OH, MY GOD, HOW THE HELL
IS THAT A UNIFORM?
WAIT’LL YOU HEAR
HOW IT SOUNDS.
FOR MY FIRST PIECE,
"THE LIGHT CAVALRY OVERTURE!"
♪
GREAT, SHE’S GONNA FIGHT ME
WITH BAD MUSIC.
IT’S SO LOUD,
IT’S HARD TO THINK.
THEN LET’S SHUT HER ASS UP.
READY?! LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE,
KAMUI SENKETSU!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ DEEP ELECTRONIC THRUMMING ]
I’M GETTING NAUSEOUS
FROM THE SOUND.
THAT BASS RATTLES YOUR BONES,
DOESN’T IT?
LET’S SHARPEN UP THE TUNE
A BIT, SHALL WE?
HEY!
[ CACKLES ]
THAT’S IT! DANCE!
[ VON SUPPé’s
"LIGHT CAVALRY OVERTURE" PLAYS ]
[ GROANS ]
[ ALARM BLARING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HMM, THIS TUNE’S MISSING
A CERTAIN SOMETHING.
OH, I KNOW.
IT’S MISSING THE SWEET SOUND
OF YOUR SCREAMING!
NOT A PROBLEM.
I’LL JUST RING A BETTER
PERFORMANCE OUT OF YOU!
[ GROANING ]
SYMPHONY REGALIA PRESTO!
OH, GREAT,
IT CAN FLY, TOO?!
YEP, IT’S THE HUGEST,
FLYINGEST SPEAKER EVER!
THIS IS MY POWER, NEW GIRL!
THE OTHERS CAN’T HOLD A BATON
TO WHAT I’M CAPABLE OF.
I TAKE THAT BACK.
MY GOKU UNIFORM IS YOUR POWER,
BUT I USE THAT POWER
BETTER THAN ANYONE ELSE.
ISN’T THAT, RIGHT, SATSUKI?
[ SQUEAKING ]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I’D SURE LOVE TO HAVE A CASTLE.
All: YOU GOT IT!
BUILD, BUILD, BUILD, BUILD!
TA‐DA!
[ GIGGLES ]
THIS IS MY SANDBOX NOW,
AND I’M NOT GONNA LET
ANYONE ELSE USE IT.
OH, ANYONE EXCEPT FOR YOU,
SATSUKI!
WE’VE BEEN BESTEST FRIENDS
SINCE FOREVER!
I CAN MAKE ONE, TOO, FOR YOU,
IF YOU WANT ONE.
NO.
HUH?
I ALREADY HAVE MY OWN SAND.
THAT LITTLE HANDFUL?
IT WAS LEFT OVER FROM THAT.
MY SAND WAS TURNED TO CONCRETE
AND MADE THAT SKYSCRAPER.
AND FROM THE TOP OF IT,
A CHILD LIKE ME CAN LOOK DOWN
ON ALL THE ADULTS IN THE WORLD.
[ GROANS ]
CASTLES THAT CRUMBLE
IN GUSTS OF WIND ARE WORTHLESS.
DON’T YOU AGREE, NOHNOHN?
YEAH, BUT SOONER OR LATER,
ALL BUILDINGS CRUMBLE!
[ GROANS ]
NOT IF YOU BUILD THEM
IN YOUR HEART, THEY WON’T.
THE SKYSCRAPERS IN MY HEART
WILL NEVER CRUMBLE ‐‐ EVER.
[ GASPING ]
[ GASPS ]
FORGET THE DUMB SAND!
FROM NOW ON,
I’LL HELP YOU BUILD STUFF!
TOGETHER, WE CAN BUILD
WHATEVER YOU WANT!
EVER SINCE THAT DAY, I VOWED TO
ALWAYS STAND BY YOUR SIDE!
AND TO LOOK OUT AT THE WORLD
FROM THE SAME HEIGHTS AS YOU DO!
WELL, EXCEPT FOR NOW,
I’M A LITTLE HIGHER.
FOR MY NEXT PIECE ‐‐
THE "WILLIAM TELL OVERTURE"
FINALE!
[ "WILLIAM TELL OVERTURE"
PLAYING ]
HEY, YOU LEFT THE ARENA!
THAT MEANS YOU’RE DISQUALIFIED!
ONLY IF YOU’RE KNOCKED OFF IT,
SILLY. NOT IF YOU LEAVE IT.
AND, AS YOU CAN SEE,
I’M FLYIN’!
YOU ASSHOLES ARE ALWAYS MAKIN’
UP THE RULES AS YOU GO!
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD COMPLAIN
LESS AND FIGHT MORE.
SO HOW ’BOUT
I TURN THINGS UP A NOTCH?
LET’S SEE YOU DODGE JAUNTILY,
IF YOU CAN, THAT IS!
LIKE I SAID, HOW IN THE BLUE
HELL IS THAT A UNIFORM!
[ EXPLOSION ]
[ SCREAMS ]
THAT THING’S GOT FRICKIN’
WHISTLE‐MISSILES, TOO?!
AAH, WHERE’S A REFEREE
WHEN YOU NEED ONE?!
SUCK ON SOME OF THIS!
I GOTCHA!
GET YOUR ASS DOWN HERE
AND FIGHT ME!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GROANING, GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GROANS ]
YOU CAN’T TIE ME DOWN!
I’LL CUT THOSE FLIMSY ROPES!
SENKETSU’S BODY IS
A 100% LIFE FIBERS.
YOU AIN’T GONNA CUT
THROUGH HIM THAT EASY!
THAT A GIRL, RYUKO!
SHE’S RIGHT, JAKUZURE
CAN’T CUT THROUGH LIFE FIBERS.
THE GROUND
ON THE OTHER HAND...
HUH?
[ LAUGHS ]
LET’S SEE HOW YOU HANDLE THIS!
DON’T WORRY,
I CAN HANDLE THESE EXPLOSIONS!
[ EXPLOSION ]
DAMN IT,
THE GROUND’S BREAKING UP!
[ SCREAMING ]
OH, DEAR,
SHE’S TAKEN A TUMBLE.
[ BEEPING ]
LOOKS LIKE THE COMMS‐TRACKING
SYSTEM’S OFFLINE.
THE EXPLOSION
MUST’VE KNOCKED IT OUT.
[ LINE RINGING ]
[ BEEPS ]
YOU’RE THE LAST PERSON
I EXPECTED TO HEAR FROM.
THIS ABOUT THE GIRL
IN THE KAMUI?
Yeah, you could say that.
SHE’S TRYING REAL HARD
OUT THERE, BUT, WELL...
HEY, SENKETSU,
ARE YOU UP FOR DOIN’ SOMETHING
REALLY, REALLY RECKLESS?
I’LL DO MY BEST.
BYE‐BYE!
[ MISSLES WHISTLING, EXPLOSION ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SHUDDERS ]
[ SCOFFS ]
[ GASPS ]
♪
SHE HASN’T HAD IT LONG,
AND ALREADY IT’S EVOLVED
TO FLY?!
THAT’S MY SENKETSU!
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING!
WE’LL CALL THIS ‐‐
SENKETSU SHIPPU!
SHE’S GOING WAY OVERBOARD HERE.
IT’S EVOLVING TOO FAST.
YOU THINK THIS THING’S TURNING
INTO A WORST‐CASE SCENARIO?
Yeah, I guess.
I’M ON IT.
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ CHEERING ]
HMM.
THE SKY IS MINE,
GODDAMN IT.
SO NOW THE GLOVES
ARE COMIN’ OFF.
YOU STINKING BITCH!
Senketsu: THE BATTLE
WITH JAKUZURE
CLIMAXES AT HONNOUJI ACADEMY,
BUT THEN A GIRL APPEARS!
MEET NUI HARIME.
WATCH OUT, RYUKO.
A GIRL WITH HER NAME
ON HER EYEPATCH
HAS GOT TO BE INSANE!
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"I’M NOT YOUR CUTE WOMAN."