[ "WILLIAM TELL OVERTURE"
PLAYING ]
BYE‐BYE!
[ MISSILES WHISTLING,
EXPLOSION ]
[ COINS CLINK ]
[ EXPLOSION ]
WE’LL CALL THIS
SENKETSU SHIPPU!
[ COINS CLINK ]
[ CHEERING ]
SO NOW THE GLOVES
ARE COMIN’ OFF,
YOU STINKING BITCH!
[ CHEERING ]
TAKE HER TO THE BOARDS,
RYUKO!
YEAH, BEAT HER ASS
TILL SHE’S BLOOD AND GUTS!
GOLLY GEE! EVERYONE LOOKS LIKE
THEY’RE HAVING SO MUCH FUN!
YOU THINK
THIS CHANGES ANYTHING? HA!
I DON’T CARE IF YOU CAN FLY.
YOU’RE STILL TOAST.
YOU CAN’T STOP MY PERFORMANCE!
PERFORMANCE, MY ASS.
SHE’S JUST TAKING POTSHOTS!
Senketsu: RYUKO, WE HAVE
THE EDGE IN MANEUVERABILITY.
LET’S GET UP CLOSE AND ATTACK.
[ GROANS ] WHERE IS SHE?
WE’RE GONNA CUT HER
RIGHT OUT OF THE SKY!
ROGER THAT.
[ GROWLS ]
OKAY, THAT DOES IT.
TIME TO DROP THE BASS ON YA.
[ BLOWS WHISTLE ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTS ] LITTLE BITCH!
OH, COME ON.
CHILL OUT, JAKUZURE.
YOU CAN’T LOSE YOUR COOL
LIKE THAT.
OH, WOW! SHE’S FLYIN’!
SHE’S FLYIN’!
RYUKO’S SO COOL!
GET OFF ME RIGHT NOW,
MANKANSHOKU!
[ SCREAMS ]
OH...
I BETTER WATCH IT.
I DON’T WANNA
MAKE GAMAGOORI MAD.
ACTUALLY,
HE’S ALREADY PRETTY ANGRY.
[ GROWLING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
YOU LET HER WALTZ RIGHT IN
AND STEAL YOUR AIR SUPERIORITY!
THERE’S NO EXCUSE FOR THAT,
JAKUZURE!
OH, NO! OH, NO!
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
I WENT AND GOT GAMAGOORI MAD!
RYUKO, I GOT MYSELF
IN ANOTHER PINCH.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, RYUKO?
WE CAN FLY. MIGHT AS WELL
GO HIT OUR REAL TARGET.
YES, OF COURSE. IMPROVISING HAS
ALWAYS BEEN YOUR SIGNATURE MOVE.
YOU KNOW IT! SATSUKI KIRYUIN,
I’M COMIN’ FOR YOU!
LIKE HELL YOU ARE!
[ GROANS ]
YOU THINK I’D LET YOU
ATTACK SATSUKI?!
NO ONE GETS BETWEEN ME AND HER!
NO ONE!
BLOW IT OUT YOUR ASS, BITCH!
IT’S GONNA TAKE A HELL OF LOT
MORE THAN YOU TO STOP ME!
I’VE HAD ENOUGH OF
YOUR SOUR NOTES.
IT’S TIME FOR A NEW TUNE,
AND IT GOES SOMETHING
LIKE THIS.
SYMPHONY REGALIA,
MUSICAL BARRAGE!
[ GROANS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
UH...
[ SCREAMING ]
OWIE!
DON’T TOUCH THAT!
[ SCREAMS ]
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS
TO MY LAPTOP,
I SWEAR I’LL KILL YOU.
INUMUTA’S ON ONE SIDE,
AND GAMAGOORI’S ON THE OTHER.
KEEP HANGIN’ IN THERE, RYUKO!
I’LL KEEP HANGING IN
OVER HERE, TOO!
[ GROANS ] OW, DAMN IT.
I CAN’T BELIEVE
SHE GOT THE DROP ON ME.
[ OBJECT CLANGS ]
AAH!
SO WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR BIG PERFORMANCE?
CAN’T YOU FLY ANYMORE?
I WAS JUST WONDERING ’CAUSE
IF YOU CAN’T,
YOU ARE SO SCREWED.
SHE’S ALL YOURS, SENKETSU!
BUST HER SHIT!
WITH PLEASURE. I COULD GET USED
TO FLYING AROUND! I LIKE IT!
WHOA, HOLD IT!
I CAN’T FLY ANYMORE,
SO SHOULDN’T YOU COME DOWN
AND FIGHT?
YOU HAVE AN UNFAIR ADVANTAGE!
DON’T PLAY THAT CARD WITH ME.
I GOT A CHANCE TO WIN
AND I’M TAKIN’ IT!
FINISHING MOVE ‐‐
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
[ SCREAMS ]
Bazaro: SHE DID IT!
THAT WAS OVER
FASTER THAN I EXPECTED.
MM‐HMM.
WHY THE LONG FACE? WE WON.
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU
WAS NOT ACHIEVED.
HUH?
I DON’T KNOW WHY,
BUT I WAS UNABLE TO ABSORB
HER LIFE FIBERS.
DO NOT UNDERESTIMATE
THE ELITE FOUR, RYUKO MATOI.
Man: WE WANT MORE!
Crowd: [ Chanting ]
WE WANT MORE! WE WANT MORE!
WE WANT MORE!
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
WE WANT MORE! WE WANT MORE!
WE WANT MORE! WE ‐‐ WAIT,
WHAT AM I SAYING?
[ CHEERING ]
SYMPHONY REGALIA DA CAPO.
FOR MY ENCORE, I’M GONNA GO
WITH ONE OF THE STANDARDS.
SHE’S DOIN’ AN ENCORE?
SHE’S DOIN’ AN ENCORE!
NOW YOU’LL SEE THE POWER OF
A THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM!
JAKUZURE DOESN’T KNOW
WHEN TO END A PERFORMANCE.
HER ENCORES DRAG ON AND ON.
HERE’S A LITTLE TUNE KNOWN BY
EVERYONE ALL OVER THE WORLD ‐‐
"BEETHOVEN’S SYMPHONY No. 5,
FATE"!
[ "SYMPHONY No. 5" PLAYING ]
[ GROANING ]
MY EARDRUMS!
I’M JUST GETTING STARTED!
[ GROANING ]
YOUR CONNECTION’S GETTIN’ WEAK,
SENKETSU! WHAT’S WRONG?
I DON’T KNOW.
I CAN BARELY HEAR YOUR VOICE.
FOR REAL?
YES.
THAT MUSIC IS SO LOUD,
IT’S HURTING ME.
WHAT?
[ GIGGLES ]
YOU LOOK CONFUSED, NEW GIRL.
THE SOUND BLASTING OUT OF
MY GOKU UNIFORM
RESONATES WITH
THE LIFE FIBERS IN YOURS.
YOU’RE TAKIN’ ON DAMAGE
IN A BIG WAY RIGHT NOW.
THAT’S THE POWER OF
MY SYMPHONY REGALIA DA CAPO.
SO YOU’RE GONNA LIE THERE,
LIKE A BROKEN DOLL
UNTIL THE FORCE OF MY BATON’S
ATTACKS FINISH YOU OFF!
[ EXPLOSION ]
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING,
MATOI?!
YOU CAN’T LOSE TO HER!
YOU AND ME GOT A DATE
FOR A FIGHT!
I’M THE ONE WHO’S SUPPOSED
TO KICK YOUR ASS!
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON,
YOU MONKEY?!
YOU’RE MAKING TOO MUCH NOISE
OVER THERE.
IT’S BAD MANNERS TO TALK DURING
A PERFORMANCE, SO PIPE DOWN.
[ GROANING ] GOD DAMN.
WHY DOES EVERYONE
AROUND HERE TALK SO MUCH?!
SHUT OUT THE NOISE
AND TRY TO FOCUS, SENKETSU.
AS MUCH AS I’D LIKE TO DO THAT,
EVERY LAST LIFE FIBER IN ME IS
VIBRATING TO THAT CURSED MUSIC.
THEN HERE GOES NOTHIN’.
WELL, GUESS IT’S TIME FOR THIS
ENCORE TO COME TO AN END...
ALONG WITH YOU.
THIS IS YOUR FINALE!
YOUR FATE ENDS HERE!
[ EXPLOSION ]
OH, MY GOD, RYUKO!
HUH?
W‐WHY ISN’T MY MUSIC
RINGING OUT?
IT’S NOT THAT
IT ISN’T RINGING OUT.
I’M TOTALLY LOST.
WHAT’S GOING ON?
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
MATOI’S USING HER POWER
TO TAKE JAKUZURE’S RHYTHMS,
MAKE THEM RESONATE,
AND TURN THEM INTO A PURE TONE.
MM‐HMM.
WAIT, A WHAT?
SHE’S ALTERING THE FREQUENCY OF
THE SOUND WAVES...
MM‐HMM.
AND MAKING THEM MATCH HER OWN!
I SEE.
IT’S THE SAME PRINCIPLE
AS A TUNING FORK.
MM‐HMM.
WHEN HIT, IT SOUNDS DULL,
BUT IT BECOMES A SINGLE TONE.
MM‐HMM, MM‐HMM.
SO BASICALLY WHAT YOU’RE SAYING
IS, RYUKO’S SUPER‐AWESOME!
LEAVE IT TO MANKANSHOKU
TO BOIL DOWN YOUR EXPLANATION
TO ITS ESSENCE.
HOW’S THAT FOR A PURE TONE?
MORE LIKE PURE STUPIDITY.
HEY, SENKETSU,
YOU HEAR ME NOW?
YES, LOUD AND CLEAR.
IS THAT YOUR HEART BEATING?
YEAH,
JUST KEEP FOCUSING ON THAT.
BLOCK OUT EVERY OTHER SOUND
EXCEPT THAT ONE.
AHH. SO THIS IS YOUR SOUND.
IMPOSSIBLE! HOW CAN SHE BLOCK
MY SONIC ATTACK LIKE THAT?!
NO, SHE’S NOT JUST BLOCKING IT.
I’M SENDIN’ IT RIGHT BACK!
♪
SO SHE’S TRYING TO
PUSH ME BACK, HUH?!
TIME TO CRANK IT UP!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ "SYMPHONY No. 5" PLAYING ]
[ GROANS ] WISH I COULD HEAR
WHAT YOU’RE PLAYIN’.
THEN AGAIN,
I BET IT SOUNDS LIKE ASS!
[ "SANBIKA" PLAYING ]
[ GROANS ] YOU GODDAMN
STINKING BITCH!
SUCK IT AND TURN THAT SHIT OFF
ALREADY!
[ SCREAMS ]
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING!
HMM?
[ GASPS ]
THE KAMUI’S MADE ENTIRELY OF
LIFE FIBERS!
THEREFORE,
THE FREQUENCIES IT EMITS
ARE MORE POWERFUL THAN
JAKUZURE’S GOKU UNIFORM!
THEREFORE,
IT’S NEUTRALIZING HER SOUND!
MY ‐‐ MY SYMPHONY REGALIA!
READY?
Ryuko and Senketsu:
SCISSOR BLADE DECAPITATION MODE!
YOUR CONCERT’S OVER!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GROANS ]
FINISHING MOVE,
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
OOH!
THAT GIRL’S WEARING A KAMUI!
THAT’S SO ADORABLE!
DID YOU SEE THAT, IORI?
YES, AND I’VE ALREADY LOCATED
THE PROBLEM SPOTS
IN BOTH THE SHACKLE
AND PROBE REGALIAS.
WE’RE EXAMINING
THE SYMPHONY REGALIA RIGHT NOW.
Good. Keep me informed.
YES, M’LADY.
ALL RIGHT, PEOPLE,
GET TO WORK!
THERE ARE TWO THINGS
YOU NEED TO KNOW.
ONE, IF YOUR CLOTHES GET RIPPED,
YOU TAKE ’EM OFF.
TWO, YOU LOOK LIKE
A SACK OF SHIT IN THOSE RAGS.
SOONER YOU TAKE ’EM OFF,
THE BETTER.
IT’S A DISGUISE.
YOU KNOW THAT.
I’M A SPY, AND IF I WALKED
AROUND IN ALL MY NUDE GLORY,
I’D ATTRACT
WAY TOO MUCH ATTENTION.
[ SCOFFS ]
IT ALL SOUNDS LIKE
A BIG PAIN IN THE ASS.
HERE’S WHAT YOU ASKED FOR.
IT’S THE ONLY ONE, SO THINK
BEFORE YOU USE IT.
THANKS FOR BRINGING IT.
ANYWAY, H. Q.’s FREAKIN’ OUT.
AND I CAN’T BELIEVE YOU’RE GONNA
USE THE BULLET ON HER.
IS MATOI THAT STRONG NOW?
SHE ABSORBED TWO
THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORMS TODAY.
COMPARED TO THE LAST TIME
YOU FOUGHT HER,
SHE’S ON A WHOLE
’NOTHER LEVEL NOW.
[ HORN BLARING ]
SHE DID IT! SHE DID IT!
SHE DID, DID, DID IT! HUH?
ARE YOU GONNA SIT WITH US, TOO?
THANK YOU. EXCELLENT DATA.
BITE ME.
AND IF YOU BRING IT UP AGAIN,
I’M GONNA SWITCH OUT YOUR LENSES
WITH NONPRESCRIPTION ONES,
YOU FOUR‐EYED NERD.
FASCINATING.
I’LL SAVE THAT RETORT
FOR FUTURE REFERENCE.
[ TYPING ]
HEY, UM, AREN’T YOU GONNA, LIKE,
SAY ANYTHING TO JAKUZURE, TOO?
YOU KNOW, ABOUT HER
WEARIN’ A TRACKSUIT?
I WOULD NEVER DARE
CROSS THAT LINE WITH A LADY.
SO GIRLS GET A FREE PASS, HUH?
FINALLY, I GET MY TURN.
STEP ON UP.
TIME TO FINISH WHAT WE STARTED
ONCE AND FOR ALL,
BUT THIS TIME,
I AIN’T GONNA RUN!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
GOOD. JUST REMEMBER ‐‐
EVEN THOUGH YOU TOOK MY EYES,
I CAN SEE EVEN BETTER NOW.
AND THIS TIME,
I’M GONNA TAKE YOU APART.
PERMISSION TO KICK HER ASS
FOR GOOD, LADY SATSUKI?
YOU HAVE IT.
ROUND NUMBER FOUR...
BEGIN!
[ HORN BLARES ]
SENKETSU SENJIN
AND SENKETSU SHIPPU, HUH?
I LIKE HOW YOU EVOLVED.
EVEN SO, IT’S NO MATCH
FOR WHAT I’VE GOT GOIN’ ON!
CHECK IT OUT!
THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM,
BLADE REGALIA MARK II!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ "BEFORE MY BODY IS DRY"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING ]
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE,
KAMUI SENKETSU!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ CONTINUES SCREAMING ]
WHAT?!
HMM?
[ GASPS ]
WHAT THE HELL?!
WHO ARE YOU?
SANAGEYAMA,
GET OUT OF THERE!
WHY DOES LADY SATSUKI
SOUND SO PANICKED?
I’VE NEVER SEEN HER
LOSE IT LIKE THAT.
WOW, THAT GIRL’S TOTALLY CUTE.
[ TYPING ]
Inumuta: THERE’S NO DATA ON HER.
WHERE’D THAT COS PLAYER
COME FROM?
AAH! JUST WHEN IT WAS
GETTIN’ GOOD.
SORRY, CHARLIE, TIME’S UP.
YOU CHEAP‐ASS SON‐OF‐A‐‐
GIVE ME SOME MORE MONEY,
HONEY.
SORRY,
WE DON’T HAVE ANY MORE.
THEN WE’RE BLOWING
THIS POP STAND!
LET’S ROLL, FAMILY UNIT.
HMM?
WHERE ARE WE GONNA GO?
TO HONNOUJI ACADEMY,
OF COURSE.
WE’RE GONNA SNEAK IN AND SEE
THE REST OF THE FIGHT!
AWESOME IDEA, DAD!
MM‐HMM.
GUTS!
WHO IN THE HELL
IS THAT CHICK?
WHAT IS THE MEANING OF THIS,
NUI HARIME?
[ GIGGLES ]
[ "BLUMENKRANZ" PLAYING ]
♪ DIESE WELT IST GRAUSAM ♪
♪ ES IST TRAURIG ABER WAHR ♪
♪ DIESE WELT... ♪
NOW...
WHICH OF YOU
WILL ADORN MY BODY TODAY?
♪ DIESE WELT IST GRAUSAM ♪
♪ ES IST TRAURIG ABER WAHR ♪
♪ DIESE WELT IST SELTSAM ♪
♪ ES IST FRAGLICH ABER WAHR ♪
I’M SORRY I’M LATE, HOUOUMARU.
[ HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING ]
NOT AT ALL, MA’AM.
YOU’RE RIGHT ON TIME.
HOWEVER...
HOWEVER? WHAT IS IT?
THE GRAND COUTURIER IS PAYING
A VISIT TO HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
YES, I ALREADY KNOW.
[ CHUCKLES ] YOU’RE A SCAMP
OF THE HIGHEST ORDER, MA’AM.
NOT AT ALL! I’M SIMPLY
PLAYING ALONG WITH HER WHIMS.
SHALL I TAKE US
TO HONNOUJI ACADEMY?
NO. WE HAVE A MEETING
WITH OUR GLOBAL BRANCHES.
TAKE US TO THE HOME OFFICE.
AT ONCE.
[ GIGGLES ]
THIS ISN’T FAIR,
LADY SATSUKI.
WHY DIDN’T YOU TELL ME
YOU WERE DOING SOMETHING
THIS FUN TODAY?
I’M NOT OBLIGATED
TO TELL YOU ANYTHING.
DON’T BE LIKE THAT. I THOUGHT
YOU AND I WERE WAY CLOSER.
LIKE TWO PEAS IN A POD.
AAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHO ARE YOU TRYING
TO FOOL HERE?
YOU ASSOCIATE WITH NO ONE.
YOU’RE AS BREATHTAKING
AS EVER!
YOUR ICY STARE AND ICY SKIN
ARE SIMPLY RAVISHING!
MY FINGERS WILL BE TINGLING
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY!
Uzu: I’M NOT GONNA LET ANYONE
GET IN THE WAY
OF MY FIGHT WITH MATOI,
SO MOVE IT!
SORRY, LUV. CAN’T DO THAT.
MIGHT AS WELL FIND A SEAT
’CAUSE I’M GONNA
BE FIGHTING HER NEXT!
HUH?
I SAID, GET OUT OF MY WAY!
HAI!
Uzu: WHAT...
THE HELL?!
SHE BLOCKED A THREE‐STAR?!
WITHOUT A UNIFORM?!
NO WAY! HOW’D SHE DO THAT?
I HAVE A BAD FEELING.
BAD, LIKE, REALLY BAD?
YES, OVERWHELMINGLY BAD.
GOSH, THIS WON’T DO.
I WAS HOPING YOU’D BE MORE FUN,
BUT YOU’RE NOT.
[ GROWLS ] SON OF A...
FINISHING MOVE ‐‐
ISSHIN ZENZANKEN!
HAI!
UHH!
HUH?!
GO BACK TO BEING
A NAKED MONKEY, SWEETIE.
IMPOSSIBLE!
HAI!
AAH!
DARN, HE FELL DOWN!
OH, WELL!
A THREE‐STAR UNIFORM UNRAVELED
BY PULLING ONE THREAD?!
HOW CAN THAT BE?!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN MEAN "HOW"?
ISN’T IT YOUR JOB
TO EXPLAIN THIS SORT OF THING?!
RIGHT, BUT I CAN’T ANALYZE
SOMETHING WITHOUT DATA.
I KNOW! I KNOW!
IT’S THE RED THREAD OF FATE!
CONNECTING THE PINKIES OF PEOPLE
DESTINED FOR EACH OTHER!
HELLO. CLOTHES DON’T HAVE
PINKIES, YOU DOOFUS.
BUT THERE WAS A RED STRING.
DIDN’T YOU SEE IT?
ZIP IT, UNDERACHIEVER!
HMM!
THAT WAS ONE OF
YOUR GOKU UNIFORMS,
HUH, LADY SATSUKI?
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
MORE DURABLE. HMM.
DON’T YOU THINK THE STITCHING’S
A LITTLE WEAK FOR COMBAT?
SHE SEVERED ITS BANSHI.
BUT NO ONE CAN SPOT
THE BANSHI AT A GLANCE,
NOT TO MENTION SEVER IT
IN AN INSTANT!
Inumuta: What are you talking
about? What’s a banshi?
IT’S A LIFE FIBER
THAT’S BEEN INFUSED
WITH THE WILL
TO BECOME CLOTHING,
THE THREAD THAT’S KEY
TO CREATING A GOKU UNIFORM.
IT HAS MULTIPLE LAYERS
OF DEFENSES
TO KEEP IT SAFE FROM ATTACK.
WHY, EVEN WHEN MATOI’S KAMUI
ABSORBS LIFE FIBERS,
THE BANSHI’S THE LAST TO GO.
AND FOR ANYONE TO FIND ONE
SO QUICKLY,
THEN PULL IT OUT AND CUT IT,
IS INCONCEIVABLE!
YOU SEE?
IT IS THE RED THREAD OF FATE!
DON’T PAT YOURSELF ON THE BACK
TOO HARD, UNDERACHIEVER.
IT’S MAKO! MAKO MANKANSHOKU!
I MIGHT BE AN UNDERACHIEVER,
BUT I STILL HAVE A NAME!
DID YOU JUST ADMIT TO BEING
AN UNDERACHIEVER?!
YOU HAVE SPIRIT, MANKANSHOKU!
GODDAMN IT!
WHO IS THAT WOMAN?!
Tsumugu: WE GOT A BIG SHOT
ON OUR HANDS.
NUI HARIME.
THE GRAND COUTURIER.
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
THE ONE FROM REVOCS?
YOU KNOW OF ANY OTHER ONES?
THE HIGH ORDER TAILOR’S HERE
FROM THE HEAD OFFICE.
AND IF SHE’S HERE,
THAT MEANS SHE WAS SENT
BY REVOCS’ C. E. O.
AND SATSUKI’S MOM...
RAGYO KIRYUIN.
OH, MAN. THINGS JUST GOT
MORE COMPLICATED.
YOU DON’T MIND IF I STEP IN,
DO YOU, LADY SATSUKI?
ARE YOU ASKING
FOR MY PERMISSION?
OF COURSE! I’VE NEVER EVER
DISOBEYED YOU BEFORE, HAVE I?
GOD, WHATEVER.
COULD WE JUST DO THIS ALREADY?
RYUKO!
IF I HAVE TO GO THROUGH HER
TO GET TO YOU, SATSUKI KIRYUIN,
I DON’T GIVE A DAMN
WHO SHE IS.
SUIT YOURSELF THEN.
[ SCOFFS ]
PLEASE, MISS.
SOME TEA TO CALM YOU.
THANK YOU.
OF ALL TIMES
FOR HARIME TO SHOW UP...
IT’S JUST LIKE HER
TO SEND HER.
MISTRESS RAGYO?
WHO ELSE DO YOU THINK?
IT’S IN YOUR HANDS NOW,
RYUKO MATOI.
[ HORN BLARES ]
DON’T YOU HAVE
A GOKU UNIFORM?
OH, I DON’T WEAR
SUCH CRUDE THINGS!
BUT ENOUGH ABOUT ME.
LET’S HAVE A LOOK AT YOUR KAMUI!
[ GASPS ]
[ GIGGLES ]
I HOPE YOU’RE NOT
HOLDING BACK
JUST BECAUSE I’M DRESSED
LIKE THIS.
DIDN’T YOU SEE? I DEFEATED
THAT GOKU UNIFORM JUST NOW.
DON’T YOU WORRY!
YOU CAN CUT LOOSE WITH YOUR
KAMUI’S POWER ALL YOU WANT!
STILL ON THE FENCE ABOUT IT?
IN THAT CASE,
WANNA SEE SOMETHING NEAT?
[ Singsongy ] READY OR NOT!
♪ DA, DA, DA‐DA‐DA, DA ♪
♪ DA‐DA, DA‐DA, DA‐DA, DA ♪
TA‐DA!
[ GASPS ] THAT’S...
YEP! IT’S THE OTHER HALF
OF YOUR SCISSORS!
I GOT THIS FROM
YOUR DEAR DEAD DADDY!
IT WAS YOU? YOU DID IT?
UH‐HUH! TOTALLY!
I’M THE ONE WHO KILLED HIM!
[ GIGGLES ]
YOU BITCH!
Senketsu: SHOUTING, "UP YOURS,"
AT THE SEA, THAT IS YOUTH.
GETTING DUMPED, THAT IS YOUTH.
GIVING IN TO YOUR RAGE
AND DESTROYING THE SCHOOL,
THAT IS ALSO YOUTH.
WAIT. THAT’S BAD.
CALM DOWN, RYUKO!
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"SPIT YOUR SADNESS AWAY."