A KING OF THE HILL FINAL BATTLE!
MATOI,
YOU WILL FIGHT THE ELITE FOUR!
IF YOU WIN,
I WILL TELL YOU THE DETAILS
OF YOUR FATHER’S DEATH.
YOU’RE ON!
I WILL BE THE FIRST
TO FACE YOU IN BATTLE, MATOI!
I’M LADY SATSUKI’S
IMPENETRABLE SHIELD!
I CHALLENGE YOU
AND I WILL CRUSH YOU!
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT!
[ "BEFORE MY BODY IS DRY"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING ]
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE!
KAMUI SENKETSU!
[ GROWLS ]
NOT SO FAST.
I DON’T REMEMBER ANYONE SAYING
YOU HAD DIBS ON THE NEW GIRL.
YEAH, I WANNA BE THE FIRST
TO FIGHT MATOI.
WHO CARES! I’LL TAKE ALL
YOU PUSSIES ON RIGHT NOW!
Inumuta: YOU’RE SUCH A FOOL.
WHAT WAS THAT?!
YOU MISUNDERSTOOD OUR REQUEST.
WE’D EACH LIKE TO HAVE A GO
AT DEFEATING YOUR KAMUI.
ONE‐ON‐ONE, AS IT WERE.
I HAVE ALREADY DECIDED
WHO FIGHTS WHEN.
HUH?
HAS ANYONE EVEN BOTHERED
TO NOTICE
THAT THE PILLARS
ARE DIFFERENT HEIGHTS?
THE MORE STUDENTS
YOU’VE DEFEATED
AS AN ELITE FOUR MEMBER,
THE HIGHER YOUR PILLAR.
THEREFORE,
GAMAGOORI IS FIRST.
INUMUTA’S NEXT,
THEN JAKUZURE,
AND THEN SANAGEYAMA
WILL HAVE HIS TURN.
SHIT.
I KICKED TOO MUCH LOSER ASS.
GUESS YOUR FIGHTING STYLE IS
MORE EFFECTIVE THAN YOU THOUGHT.
SO THE GUY WITH THE LOW QUOTA
GETS TO GO FIRST, EH?
I GUESS IT PAYS TO BE MERCIFUL
WITH YOUR FELLOW STUDENTS,
HUH, GAMA?
MY QUOTA’S LOW BECAUSE I ONLY
FIGHT WHEN PROVOKED.
AND WHEN I GET THROUGH WITH HER,
YOU’LL SEE HOW MERCIFUL I AM!
[ GRUNTS ]
COME ON! WHATCHA WAITING FOR?!
WHY ARE YOU IN SUCH A HURRY?
OUR BATTLE ISN’T SUPPOSED
TO BEGIN UNTIL 1:00!
HUH? OH.
[ GROANS ] I’M NOT GONNA
WAIT AROUND TILL 1:00!
LET’S GET THIS OVER WITH.
NO, WE WILL STICK TO
THE SCHEDULE!
THAT’S WHAT WE CALL DISCIPLINE!
AND THOSE ARE THE RULES!
[ Woman over P. A. ]
HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S
KING OF THE HILL FINAL BATTLE
WILL COMMENCE TODAY,
STARTING AT 1:00 P. M.
IT PROMISES TO BE
A BLOODY CLASH BETWEEN
THE STUDENT COUNCIL’S
ELITE FOUR
AND SECOND YEAR CLASS K’S
RYUKO MATOI.
TUNE INTO HONNOUJI TELEVISION
FOR LIVE COVERAGE.
IT’S GOOD,
CLEAN FUN FOR ALL AGES,
SO GET THE FAMILY TOGETHER
AND LET’S ALL WATCH IT!
[ CHEERING ]
YOU HEAR THAT?
RYUKO’S FIGHTING TODAY!
DON’T JUST STAND THERE!
GO AND STEAL US A TV
SO WE CAN WATCH THIS THING!
[ CHUCKLES ]
WAY AHEAD OF YOU.
HUH?
I GOT ONE A LONG TIME AGO.
[ LAUGHS ] ATTABOY, BUDDY.
[ KNOB CLICKING ]
HUH? HUH?
WHY ISN’T ANYTHING HAPPENING?
[ SCOFFS ] WHAT THE HELL?
TRY HITTIN’ IT.
WELL, THAT DIDN’T WORK.
[ GRUNTS ]
OKAY.
THERE YOU GO.
SEE WHAT YOU SEE.
I DON’T FEEL ANYTHING.
HANG ON A SECOND.
WE’LL LOOK. IT’S EMPTY.
[ GROANS ]
IT’S NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
EMPTY INSIDE!
COME ON, BUST A MOVE, HON.
WE’RE GOING TO
THE APPLIANCE STORE.
I’M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
I’M COMING, TOO! WHOA!
NO MORE TV STEALING FOR ME.
HEY!
YOU WANNA HAVE SOME TEA?
MMM.
THANKS! [ GULPING ]
[ SIGHS ]
THE LUNCH MY MOM MADE’LL
GIVE YOU A MILLION HORSEPOWER!
YOU’RE A CINCH TO WIN!
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU FOUND YOURSELF
IN ANOTHER PICKLE, EH, MATOI?
HMM?
OH, HI, MR. MIKISUGI!
ARE YOU GONNA HELP ME
CHEER RYUKO ON TO VICTORY?!
ABSOLUTELY. AFTER ALL,
I AM HER HOMEROOM TEACHER,
MORE OR LESS.
BASTARD!
THE HELL’D YOU DO TO HER?!
EASY. I JUST HIT A PRESSURE
POINT TO KNOCK HER OUT
SO WE COULD TALK.
OKAY, WHAT DO YOU WANNA
TALK ABOUT?
DROP OUT OF THE FIGHT
WITH THE ELITE FOUR.
LIKE HELL I WILL!
THEY’RE ON A DIFFERENT LEVEL
THAN THE CLUB PRESIDENTS
YOU’VE FOUGHT.
AND IF YOU’RE CRAZY ENOUGH TO
FIGHT ALL FOUR OF THEM IN A ROW,
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT’LL HAPPEN
TO YOU AND SENKETSU.
IF YOU DON’T KNOW, THEN KEEP
YOUR OPINIONS TO YOURSELF.
COME ON, RYUKO.
OKAY, IF YOU DON’T WANT ME
TO FIGHT, THEN START TALKIN’.
TELL ME WHY MY DAD WAS KILLED
AND WHO DID IT.
LOOK, I‐I CAN’T.
THEN SHUT YOUR MOUTH
AND FIND A SEAT.
ME AND SENKETSU ARE GONNA BEAT
THE CRAP OUTTA SATSUKI KIRYUIN.
THEN I’M GONNA MAKE HER
TELL ME THE TRUTH.
I’LL WRING IT OUT OF HER.
[ GASPS ]
NOW HURRY UP
AND SNAP MAKO OUT OF IT.
TALKIN’ TO HER MAKES ME FEEL
A WHOLE LOT BETTER THAN YOU.
’CAUSE I’M GONNA BE CHEERING
FOR HER SUPER HARD!
DID YOU KNOW
SHE’S MY BESTEST FRIEND?
MM‐HMM.
WELL, DON’T GET
TOO CARRIED AWAY.
THE LAST THING I NEED IS TO GET
ON THE STUDENT COUNCIL’S
BAD SIDE BECAUSE OF YOU.
[ GROWLING ]
HMM? WHATCHA GLARIN’ AT?
OH, NOTHING.
HEY, YOUR MOM’S LUNCH
ROCKS TODAY!
IT’S REALLY GOOD.
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
BEGIN.
[ HORN BLARES ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WATCH OUT. HIS GOKU UNIFORM
TRANSFORMS TWICE.
ARE YOU LISTENING?
Senketsu: HUH? OH. YES.
WHAT’S UP WITH YOU?
NOTHING. JUST THINKING.
WHAT, YOU GOT AN IDEA?
I JUST MIGHT.
THIS GUY’S TOUGH,
SO DON’T GO SPACIN’ OUT ON ME.
DON’T WORRY. I WON’T.
HERE WE GO!
THAT WAS YOUR FIRST AND LAST
TRANSFORMATION, MATOI!
THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM,
SHACKLE REGALIA!
[ STEAM HISSING ]
WELL?
WHAT?
DO YOU WANNA FIGHT OR NOT?
’COURSE I DO.
THEN WHY AREN’T YOU
ATTACKING ME?
I LOVE HOW YOU GUYS THINK
I’M STUPID,
ALL CALLING ME A FOOL,
BUT YOU’RE A BIGGER FOOL!
HUH?
OH, I KNOW THE DEAL!
YOUR UNIFORM ABSORBS THE POWER
OF WHATEVER ATTACKS YOU
AND TURNS IT BACK
ON THE ATTACKER.
SO I SURE AS HELL
AIN’T GONNA ATTACK YOU!
HA! THEN I GUESS
YOU’RE AN EVEN BIGGER FOOL!
OH, YEAH? HOW?
YOU DIDN’T THINK I’D ANTICIPATE
SUCH AN OBVIOUS TACTIC?
WHAT THE...[ GRUNTS ]
IF YOU WON’T ATTACK ME,
I’LL ATTACK MYSELF!
I HAVE MY OWN SPECIAL TECHNIQUES
FOR DISCIPLINE!
I’LL KEEP SLAPPING AND WHIPPING
AND BEATING MYSELF
UNTIL I CLIMAX!
EW!
THIS IS MY HIGI JIJO‐JIBAKU!
WHAT THE HELL?!
LET ME SHOW YOU.
THREE‐STAR GOKU UNIFORM!
SCOURGE REGALIA!
[ SCREAMS ]
HMM.
MNH.
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
IF YOU FALL OFF THE EDGE
OF THE PLATFORM,
YOU LOSE THE BATTLE!
NOBODY TOLD ME
THAT WAS THE RULE!
I’M TELLING YOU NOW!
I HOPE
I’VE CLEARED THINGS UP FOR YOU!
I’LL SAY YOU DID!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
WHAT?! [ GRUNTING ]
OW!
I CAN DO THIS ALL DAY.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
SO WHAT’S YOUR NEXT MOVE?
[ Strained voice ]
NOTHING SPECIAL.
[ Normal voice ]
JUST YOUR BASIC...
IN YOUR FACE ATTACK!
FINISHING MOVE!
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
HUH?
HIS UNIFORM HAS NO LIFE FIBERS
ON ITS SURFACE.
THERE’S NOTHING FOR ME
TO ABSORB.
SERIOUSLY?!
SURPRISED? THE SURFACE OF
MY SHACKLE REGALIA
IS ARMORED FABRIC,
REINFORCED WITH A COATING
OF SPECIAL POWERS.
IF YOU WANT TO ABSORB
ITS LIFE FIBERS,
YOU’LL HAVE TO CUT THROUGH
THE OUTER ARMOR FIRST!
THEN YOU’LL HAVE TO THRUST
YOUR BLADE INTO THE UNIFORM!
THANKS FOR THE TIP.
GUESS I KNOW WHAT TO DO NOW!
[ BLADE CLINKS ]
[ GROANS ]
BAD IDEA.
IF YOU ATTACK ME, I BECOME
THAT MUCH STRONGER, REMEMBER?
[ GROWLS ]
SCOURGE REGALIA!
AAH!
RYUKO! [ GASPS ]
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
LOOK OUT!
OH, MY GOD, THIS SUCKS!
THAT ELITE DUMBASS IS
BEATING THE CRAP OUT OF HER!
OH, SHE’LL BE FINE.
I MADE A SPECIAL LUNCH FOR HER
TO GIVE HER THE ENERGY
TO RIDE IT OUT.
SHE CAN’T LOSE!
GO ON, KEEP RESISTING.
YOUR KAMUI IS FEEDING ME MORE
POWER THAN ANY GOKU UNIFORM!
YOU’RE LIKE A BATTERY
FOR MY SCOURGE REGALIA.
SO KEEP ON FIGHTING!
IT’S HELPING ME WIN!
AAH! [ GRUNTS ]
OW! [ GRUNTING ]
AW, LOOK AT THAT. THE POOR
LITTLE NEW GIRL’S ON THE ROPES.
SHE’S AN EVEN BIGGER WUSS
THAN I GAVE HER CREDIT FOR.
THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE
CHAIR’S BROW
IS LOOKING MORE FURROWED
THAN USUAL.
YEAH, WELL,
THAT’S ’CAUSE HE’S FIGHTING
IN FRONT OF HIS QUEEN TODAY,
SO HE AIN’T HOLDING BACK.
MATOI, IF THERE’S ANYONE
WITH A GREATER WILL THAN YOURS,
IT’S GAMAGOORI.
THIS IS UNEXPECTED.
WHY ISN’T THE OUTGOING
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
ATTENDING HIS GRADUATION?
YOU WANNA TAKE OVER THE SCHOOL
AND I CAN’T LET THAT HAPPEN.
SO I’M HERE TO STOP YOU,
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
I CAN’T LEAVE HERE
UNTIL I KNOW THIS SCHOOL’S SAFE
FROM YOU AND YOUR TYRANNY!
[ ROARS ]
OH.
[ GRUNTS ]
STEEL ARMOR. CLEVER.
OH, THANKS. I GOT IT FROM SOME
RELATIVES WHO RUN AN IRONWORKS.
GOOD LUCK CUTTING THROUGH IT!
EVEN WITH YOUR ARMOR,
YOU CAN’T DEFEAT ME.
I NEVER EXPECTED TO.
BELIEVE ME, I KNOW I’M NOT
STRONG ENOUGH TO BEAT YOU.
WELL, THEN WHY DO YOU
OPPOSE ME?
I CAN’T BEAT YOU,
BUT I WON’T LET YOU BEAT ME.
COME AGAIN?
YOU CAN’T BEAT ME
BECAUSE YOU CAN’T MAKE ME
KNEEL TO YOU.
SO IF YOU’RE PLANNING ON TAKING
THIS SCHOOL BY FORCE, BEWARE.
I’LL STAND ALONE AGAINST YOU
IF I HAVE TO.
I’LL SHOW YOU THERE ARE
STILL PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD
WHO WILL STAND UP
TO YOUR KIND OF TYRANNY!
THAT IS MY PURPOSE IN LIFE!
THEN WHY DON’T WE PUT
YOUR RESOLVE TO THE TEST?
BUT YOU’LL GET NO MERCY
IF YOU FAIL!
[ GRUNTS ]
HA!
AAH!
[ COUGHS ]
[ GASPING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
I’LL NEVER KNEEL,
NOT TO YOU!
AAH! AAH!
I WILL NEVER KNEEL TO Y‐‐
[ THUD ]
HMM.
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
DID I...DID I LOSE?
GAMAGOORI, YOUR WILL IS
STRONG AND UNSHAKABLE.
JOIN ME.
BE MY SHIELD, AND I WILL PUT
YOUR RESOLVE TO GOOD USE.
YOU’RE PLANNING SOMETHING BIG,
AREN’T YOU?
[ CHUCKLES ]
PEOPLE ARE PIGS
IN HUMAN CLOTHING.
BUT I WILL FIGHT AGAINST
EVERYTHING THIS WORLD STANDS FOR
AND REMAKE IT.
IN TWO YEARS’ TIME, I WILL
CREATE A NEW HIGH SCHOOL,
AND IT WILL BE MY ARMY.
IF YOU JOIN ME,
I PROMISE I WILL GRANT YOU
NEW STRENGTH AND A NEW PURPOSE.
VERY WELL.
I’LL WAIT TWO YEARS FOR YOU.
[ GRUNTING ]
I TOLD YOU BEFORE.
I AM LADY SATSUKI’S SHIELD
AND I WILL CRUSH YOU!
KEEP DREAMIN’!
’CAUSE THERE’S NO WAY
I’M GONNA LOSE TO YOU!
WHAT ARE YOU EVEN
FIGHTING FOR?
TO GET REVENGE
FOR YOUR FATHER’S MURDER?!
IS THAT IT?!
SOME PETTY VENDETTA?!
NOW YOU KNOW WHY LADY SATSUKI
DIDN’T JUMP AT YOUR CHALLENGE.
SUCH TRIVIAL THINGS
ARE BENEATH HER!
"TRIVIAL"?!
THAT’S WHY
YOU’LL NEVER BEAT HER,
AND WHY YOU’LL NEVER
BEAT ME EITHER!
UHH!
AAH!
[ CHEERING ]
HOLY BAZONKERS!
Senketsu: RYUKO,
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH. JUST CAUGHT ME
OFF GUARD IS ALL.
WE’VE COME THIS FAR,
SO IT’S TOO LATE TO QUIT.
[ GRUNTS ]
YOU’RE CRAZY AND STUPID.
BAD COMBINATION.
YOUR LUCK’S THE ONLY THING
THAT’S BAD AROUND HERE
’CAUSE YOU GOTTA FIGHT ME.
SO LET’S FIGHT!
[ GRUNTING ]
AAH! WHAT’RE YOU DOING?!
YOU CAN’T JUST WAIL ON HIM.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE A PLAN!
YEAH, OR HE’LL KNOCK YOU
ON YOUR ASS AGAIN!
SHE LOOKS SO DESPERATE.
[ SCREAMING ]
OH, BOY.
I GUESS RYUKO’S GONE OFF
THE DEEP END FOR GOOD.
SLASH AT ME ALL YOU WANT.
YOU’LL NEVER WIN!
YOU SET A BAD EXAMPLE
WITH YOUR REBELLIOUS WAYS.
NOW ACCEPT YOUR PUNISHMENT.
SCOURGE REGALIA!
IF BEATING YOU MEANS
GETTING CLOSER TO FINDING OUT
WHO KILLED MY DAD,
THEN GODDAMN IT,
I’M GONNA BEAT YOU!
GET HIM, RYUKO! GET HIM!
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHO YOU’RE DEALING WITH!
I AM
THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE!
I LEAD BY EXAMPLE.
THAT’S WHY I BIND AND WHIP
MYSELF SO MERCILESSLY!
IT’S HOW I INSPIRE YOU
TROUBLEMAKERS
TO CHANGE YOUR WAYS AND BECOME
PRODUCTIVE STUDENTS!
IT’S HOW I BRING ORDER TO
THE CHAOS AT HONNOUJI ACADEMY!
THE SHACKLE REGALIA IS
THE EMBODIMENT OF THAT ETHOS!
IF YOU REFUSE TO CONFORM
TO THE RULES,
THAT’S WHEN I BURY MY COMPASSION
AND BRING OUT THE WHIP!
THAT IS THE SCOURGE REGALIA!
AND IF THAT STILL DOESN’T
CONVINCE YOU TO FALL IN LINE,
THEN YOU LEAVE ME NO CHOICE!
I’LL UNLEASH THE MIGHT OF
THE SHACKLE REGALIA UPON YOU!
I’M GOING TO REVOKE
YOUR INDEPENDENT STATUS
AND MOLD YOU INTO
A PROPER STUDENT!
YOU HAVE THE SLUTTIEST UNIFORM
I’VE EVER SEEN!
HOW DARE YOU COME TO SCHOOL
WEARING THAT!
IT’S DISGUSTING! IT’S DEVIANT!
IT’S DEPRAVED!
WHAT ABOUT YOUR PRECIOUS
LADY SATSUKI?
LADY SATSUKI’S AN EXCEPTION!
WHAT?!
HER IRON WILL AND WELL‐TRAINED
BODY ARE IDEAL
AND MAKE ANYTHING SHE WEARS
NOBLE AND PURE!
OH COME ON!
THAT’S B. S. AND YOU KNOW IT!
AAH!
MY SCISSOR!
OH, CRAP!
[ LAUGHS ]
I FINALLY RATTLED YOUR CAGE!
NOW THEN, RYUKO MATOI,
I’M GOING TO MOLD YOU
INTO SHAPE!
AFTER I’M DONE WITH YOU,
YOU’LL LOOK LIKE
A PROPER FEMALE STUDENT!
CONSIDER IT A FRESH START!
AND NOW TASTE MY MOLD!
[ GROANING ]
GO ON, STRUGGLE
AND REFLECT
ON YOUR WICKED WAYS!
[ GASPS ] HE’S TURNING HER
INTO A HUMAN WAFFLE!
THAT’S IT! YES!
I WILL STRAIGHTEN YOU OUT!
I WON’T STOP UNTIL YOU’RE MOLDED
INTO A PROPER STUDENT!
Senketsu: DO YOU WANT TO WIN?
WHAT KIND OF QUESTION’S THAT?
OF COURSE I WANNA WIN!
THEN I JUST MIGHT HAVE AN IDEA.
IS IT WHAT YOU WERE
THINKING ABOUT BEFORE?
YES. MAY I HANDLE THIS?
GO FOR IT!
[ PANTING ]
HER TRANSFORMATION MIGHT’VE
BROKEN HER OUT OF THE MOLD.
BUT IF SHE THINKS SHE’LL WIN
LIKE THAT, SHE’S MISTAKEN.
WELL, THAT’S AN IMPROVEMENT
ON YOUR APPEARANCE.
PERHAPS YOU’RE STARTING TO
SEE THINGS MY WAY AFTER ALL!
OH, BLOW IT OUT YOUR ASS,
YOU BONDAGE‐LOVING TOOL!
YOU’LL LEARN SOME MANNERS
AT THE END OF MY WHIP!
AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GNAWING ]
HA! I’M NOT SURE
WHAT YOU WERE THINKING,
BUT HAVE I GOT A SURPRISE
FOR YOU.
SEE, YOU’VE PLAYED
RIGHT INTO MY HANDS!
AND NOW I’M GONNA
STRANGLE YOU!
[ GROANING ]
RUNNING SHORT ON BREATH,
ARE WE?
IF ONLY YOU HAD YOUR BLADE,
YOU COULD FIGHT BACK!
UH‐OH. GUESS IT’S OVER.
I WANTED TO GATHER
MORE KAMUI DATA.
NO, WAIT! SOMETHING’S WRONG!
[ GASPS ]
YOU’RE A FOOL, GAMAGOORI.
[ Strained voice ]
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE!
AAH! [ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANS ] AAH!
NO!
SENKETSU SENJIN!
Mika Kobayashi: ♪ DON’T LOSE
YOUR WAY IN YOUR MIND ♪
SHE TURNED HER KAMUI
INTO A BLADE!
♪ BE AS ONE ♪
♪ DON’T BE AFRAID ♪
YOU DON’T HAVE
ENOUGH ENERGY LEFT
TO CHANGE INTO
YOUR SCOURGE REGALIA, DO YA?!
TOO LATE!
NOW YOUR LIFE FIBERS
ARE TOTALLY EXPOSED!
FINISHING MOVE!
SEN‐I‐SOSHITSU!
[ Strained voice ] IMPOSSIBLE!
♪ BEFORE MY BODY IS DRY ♪
WHOA.
[ GASPS ]
HIS RESOLVE WAS CLOUDED
BY HIS ARROGANCE.
WHAT A SHAME.
[ CHEERING ]
YOU DID IT, RYUKO!
SHE DID IT! SHE DID IT!
SHE DID IT!
NOW THAT’S WHAT I CALL
AN IDEA!
IF A GOKU UNIFORM CAN SPECIALLY
TRANSFORM, THEN WHY CAN’T I?
I LOVE IT WHEN YOU THINK
OUT‐OF‐THE‐BOX LIKE THAT!
IT LEARNED HOW TO RECONFIGURE
ITSELF BASED ON THE SITUATION.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
BUT STILL, I WISH I COULD
FEEL HAPPIER FOR HER.
[ CRYING ] HOW PATHETIC.
I CAN’T LIVE
WITH THIS KIND OF DISGRACE!
AAH!
[ GASPS ]
LADY SATSUKI?
IT’S TOO EARLY TO BE
KNEELING IN DEFEAT,
SO WIPE YOUR TEARS.
SEE THAT, KIRYUIN?
ONE DOWN!
YOU ARE CORRECT.
HUH?
THAT MEANS I WILL BE
YOUR NEXT OPPONENT, MATOI.
HMM.
YOU ARE FREE TO REST,
IF YOU WISH.
ARE YOU FREAKIN’ KIDDING?!
I GOT THREE MORE OF
YOUR CHUMPS TO BURN THROUGH,
AND THEN
I’M COMING AFTER YOU!
NO, RYUKO!
COME ON, LET’S GET THIS
OVER WITH.
YOU’RE SO IMPATIENT.
BUT I CAN RELATE.
I HATE WASTING TIME, TOO.
Senketsu: TO BE SKILLED
AT FINDING DATA
IS TO BE SKILLED AT LOVE.
TO BE SKILLED AT DATA ANALYSIS
ONE MOST OBSERVE THE SIGNS
THOROUGHLY.
MAN VERSUS WOMAN, WHO WILL WIN?
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"I WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT YOU."