All:
WELCOME BACK, LADY SATSUKI.
YOU PERFORMED WELL
ON THE RAID TRIP.
I TRUST YOU’VE RESTED.
All: YES.
Houka: HOW’D IT GO
WITH THE DIRECTOR?
SHE SAID SHE WAS PLEASED
WITH OUR RESULTS.
AND SHE’S DECIDED TO PAY A VISIT
TO HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
Uzu:
THEN THIS IS IT?
YES. IT’S TIME.
I’M COUNTING
ON ALL OF YOU.
[ HEEL CLACKS ]
Satsuki:
STUDENTS OF HONNOUJI ACADEMY,
THE RAID TRIP WAS A SUCCESS
BECAUSE OF YOUR EFFORTS.
WE DESTROYED THE DENS
OF THE KANSAI FORCES
AND THE BASE OF
THE ANTI‐CLOTHING GUERILLAS.
TO CELEBRATE, RAGYO KIRYUIN,
THE DIRECTOR
OF HONNOUJI ACADEMY,
IS COMING.
IN HONOR OF HER VISIT,
WE WILL HOLD A CEREMONY
IN THIS STADIUM,
WHICH BEARS HER NAME.
PUT ALL YOUR EFFORT
INTO PREPARING
FOR THE DIRECTOR’S ARRIVAL.
THE TIME HAS COME
FOR THE ACADEMY’S
CULTURAL AND SPORTS
GRAND FESTIVAL!
Ryuko: SWEET, I WAS LOOKING
FOR AN EXCUSE
TO SETTLE THINGS
WITH YOU.
[ SCOFFS ]
WHAT YOU GONNA DO?
YOU DON’T GOT YOUR KAMUI
OR YOUR SCISSOR BLADE.
YOU’RE JUST A HIGH‐SCHOOL CHICK
IN DORKY UNDERWEAR.
NOT MUCH OF A THREAT
IF YOU ASK ME.
IF YOU’RE TRYING
TO PSYCH ME OUT,
IT AIN’T WORKING.
I’M READY TO DO THIS
FULL‐ON NAKED IF I HAVE TO.
YOU CAN’T DO THAT!
[ CHOIR SINGS "HALLELUJAH" ]
THE ONLY PERSON
IN THE WHOLE WORLD
A GIRL SHOULD
REVEAL HERSELF TO
IS THE ONE
SHE LOVES THE MOST!
CAN WE SAY
YOU LOVE MR. MOHAWK, RYUKO?
DO YOU LOVE HIM ALL DEEP
LIKE THAT?
DO YOU?!
I THINK YOU’RE
MISUNDERSTANDING AGAIN.
YOU DON’T,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
THAT’S WHY YOU WEAR
SENKETSU ALL THE TIME.
’CAUSE YOU LOVE HIM THE MOST.
BESIDES, IT’D BE GROSS
IF YOU WORE HIM
AND YOU DIDN’T LOVE HIM
’CAUSE HE’S ALIVE.
HUH?
A GIRL ONLY FLASHES HER BIZ
TO HER ONE TRUE LOVE.
AND NO ONE ELSE!
RYUKO, I AM FLATTERED
YOU’D STAND UP FOR ME
LIKE THIS
BUT PUT ME ON.
IF I MAY BE SO BOLD.
SENKETSU...
YOU’LL CATCH A COLD
LIKE THAT IF YOU DON’T.
I’LL CATCH A COLD?!
MAN, YOU GUYS
ARE SOMETHING ELSE.
AND EVERYONE’S FRIENDS
WITH CLOTHES AGAIN.
[ SCOFFS ]
I DON’T FEEL
LIKE SHOOTING THEM NOW.
THIS IS OSAKA?
GOD, IT’S HORRIBLE.
Senketsu: YES. THIS IS
WHAT THE LIFE FIBERS’ POWER
IS CAPABLE OF.
AND WHAT WE
ARE CAPABLE OF.
[ SIGHS ] YEAH.
MIKISUGI WAS RIGHT TO KEEP US
IN THE DARK UP UNTIL NOW.
EVEN AFTER SEEING THIS,
BEING TOLD LIFE FIBERS
ARE FROM OUTER SPACE IS...
MIND‐BOGGLING.
[ CHUCKLES ]
THAT’S FUNNY COMING FROM YOU.
THIS WHOLE THING’S
GOT ME FREAKED OUT.
WHY?
I DON’T KNOW.
IT’S LIKE EVERYTHING’S
GONE FROM A STUPID FIGHT
TO THIS CRAZY WAR
THAT’S OVER MY HEAD.
PEOPLE ARE SAYING THINGS
LIKE "FATE OF HUMANITY"
AND "EXTINCTION OF OUR SPECIES,"
BLAH, BLAH.
MY HEAD WAS SPINNING.
AND I WANTED TO SAY,
"I DON’T GIVE A CRAP!"
INSTEAD, I USED YOU
AS AN EXCUSE TO GET ANGRY.
NO, RYUKO.
YOU GOT
ANGRY AT THEM
BECAUSE YOU WERE
STANDING UP FOR ME.
THAT’S THE KIND OF PERSON
YOU ARE.
[ GUNFIRE ]
UH ‐‐
WHAT’S UP WITH HIM?
Mikisugi: YEAH, WELL,
HIS OLDER SISTER DIED
DURING AN EXPERIMENT
WITH LIFE FIBERS.
[ GASPS ]
WHEN YOUR DAD
CREATED NUDIST BEACH,
HE SET UP A LAB.
HIS TOP ASSISTANT
WAS TSUMUGU’S SISTER ‐‐
KINUE KINAGASE.
THEY FOUND THAT ONLY LIFE FIBERS
COULD FIGHT LIFE FIBERS,
SO THEY TRIED MAKING ONE
THAT WOULD OBEY A HUMAN’S WILL.
THEY RAN EXPERIMENT
AFTER EXPERIMENT.
AND DURING ONE OF THOSE,
SHE ‐‐ WELL...
JESUS.
THAT WAS HIS SISTER?
HMM?
A WHILE AGO, HE TOLD ME
I WAS HEADED DOWN
THE SAME ROAD AS HER.
OH. RIGHT.
HER LAST WORDS
TO HIM WERE,
"WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON’T STOP THE WORK".
SO DR. MATOI KEPT GOING
WITH THE EXPERIMENTS
UNTIL HE FIGURED IT OUT
AND MADE SENKETSU.
HIS BREAKTHROUGH CAME
WHEN HE SPLICED
SENKETSU’S LIFE FIBERS
WITH YOUR
CENTRAL NERVOUS SYSTEM’S DNA.
HE WHAT?!
IT’S TRUE.
THAT’S WHY
YOU’RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN WEAR HIM
AND HEAR HIM.
HE’S A COMBAT UNIFORM
YOUR DAD DESIGNED FOR YOU
AND YOU ALONE.
BUT WHY WOULD HE
DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
HE TOLD ME HE DID IT
BECAUSE HE WANTED
TO PROTECT YOU.
[ SIGHS ]
OH, MAN.
WHAT THE HELL?
Soroi:
YOUR TEA, MISS.
Satsuki: THANK YOU.
I’VE HAD A LOT OF YOUR TEA
OVER THE YEARS, HAVEN’T I?
I’VE BEEN MAKING IT FOR YOU
SINCE YOU WERE 5.
YES, YOU HAVE,
SINCE THAT DAY
WHEN MY FATHER SHOWED ME
JUNKETSU FOR THE FIRST TIME.
ON THAT DAY,
HE SAID TO ME,
"THIS WILL BE
YOUR WEDDING DRESS".
SO I’VE HEARD.
I SUPPOSE THAT DAY
WAS WHEN ALL THIS REALLY BEGAN.
SEEMS LIKE YESTERDAY.
EVEN THIS TEA
THAT I ONCE FOUND SO BITTER
IS NOW THE MOST DELICIOUS THING
IN THE WORLD.
WHAT IS IT?
Y‐YOU THOUGHT
IT WAS BITTER?
I NEVER MENTIONED THAT?
WITH THE FIRST CUP,
YOU SMILED.
YOU SAID
IT WAS DELICIOUS.
ALL THIS TIME,
YOU’VE BEEN PUTTING UP WITH IT,
HUMORING ME.
I BEG YOUR FORGIVENESS,
MISS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT’S FINE. REALLY.
PERHAPS I WAS MORE...
COMPASSIONATE BACK THEN.
TEN‐HUT! EYES FRONT!
LISTEN UP!
TOMORROW’S A BIG DAY
FOR US ALL ‐‐
THE DAY OF THE CULTURAL
AND SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL.
ALL NO‐STAR STUDENTS
AND THEIR PARENTS
ARE REQUIRED TO ATTEND
AND WELCOME DIRECTOR KIRYUIN.
[ ALL GASPING ]
THESE ARE YOUR
CEREMONIAL DRESS UNIFORMS.
AND, YES, THEY ARE REQUIRED.
AT 0830, YOU WILL CONVENE
AT THE STADIUM ENTRANCE
WEARING YOUR NEW UNIFORMS!
YOU WILL NOT BE LATE!
SHIRTS WILL BE TUCKED IN!
IF THERE IS SO MUCH
AS A HAIR OUT OF PLACE,
THE PENALTY WILL BE DEATH!
ARE WE CLEAR?!
HOLD ON A SECOND!
[ GASPS ]
AND WHO ARE YOU?
I HAPPEN TO BE
MAKO MANKANSHOKU’S DAD,
BARAZO MANKANSHOKU.
AND I’M HIS WIFE,
SUKUYO.
AND I’M HIS SON,
MATARO!
[ BARKS ]
Gamagoori:
NICE ‐‐ A FAMILY UNIT
WHERE EVEN THE DOG
INTRODUCES HIMSELF.
WELL?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WHERE THE HELL’S
MY GIRL?!
[ GROANS ]
THE WORD ON THE STREET
IS SHE GOT DRAFTED
TO SERVE ON YOUR RAID TRIP.
ALL THE OTHER STUDENTS
MADE IT BACK ALREADY.
BUT MAKO AND RYUKO
NEVER DID.
SO, WHY AIN’T
THEY BACK YET?!
MATOI AND MANKANSHOKU, EH?
THEY’RE CONSIDERED
REBELS NOW.
[ ALL GASP ]
AND SINCE YOU’RE RELATED
TO THE TRAITORS,
YOUR HOME
IS NOW CONFISCATED!
AND YOU’RE BANISHED
FROM HONNOU TOWN!
WHAT?!
BUT SINCE THE CULTURAL
AND SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL
IS TOMORROW, I WILL GRANT YOU
A SPECIAL PARDON.
IF YOU WISH
TO ATONE FOR THEIR CRIMES,
YOU MUST PARTICIPATE
IN THE CEREMONY.
AND WHEN IT COMES TIME,
YOU WILL TOAST THE GLORY
OF LADY SATSUKI
AND RAGYO KIRYUIN!
OTHERWISE, NO SPECIAL PARDON!
IS THAT CLEAR?!
I’VE GOT TWO QUESTIONS.
WH‐WHAT?
ARE THE GIRLS
STILL ALIVE?
THEY ARE.
[ SIGHS ]
QUESTION 2 ‐‐
IS THE FESTIVAL
GONNA BE CATERED?
O‐OF COURSE IT WILL.
[ ALL CHEER ]
[ GROANS ]
VERY WELL THEN!
I SWEAR ON THE HONOR
OF THE MANKANSHOKUS
THAT WE WILL ATONE
FOR OUR DAUGHTER’S CRIMES
BY EATING EVERY SCRAP OF FOOD
ON OUR PLATES,
LICKING THEM CLEAN
IF WE HAVE TO.
YOU HAVE MY SOLEMN WORD
ON THAT.
Ryuko:
SO, WHAT ARE WE WATCHING?
WE’RE LOOKING
AT A LIVE VIDEO FEED
FROM THE HIDDEN CAMERAS
I SET UP AT THE ACADEMY.
THIS THING MUST BE BIG
IF THEY GOT RAGYO KIRYUIN
COMING ALL THE WAY OUT
TO DO IT.
WHAT THE HELL’S
SHE GOT TO BE THERE FOR?
SHE’S THE HEAD
OF THE KIRYUIN CONGLOMERATE
AND THE C. E. O. OF REVOCS,
REMEMBER?
SHE MADE IT HER MISSION
TO SELL CLOTHING
LACED WITH LIFE FIBERS
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
GOD, WHAT’S WITH
THE ROCK‐SHOW LIGHTING?
SHE’S TACKIER THAN SATSUKI.
A COUPLE OF SKANKS
CUT FROM THE SAME CLOTH.
YEAH, BUT SHE’S EVEN
MORE FORMIDABLE THAN SATSUKI.
TRUST ME ON THAT.
YOU SEEING
WHAT I’M SEEING?
THEY’RE TRUCKING A HELL OF A LOT
OF LIFE FIBERS IN.
WONDER WHAT FOR.
[ GASPS ] OH, NO.
SHE’S COMING TO CONDUCT
THE FINAL EXPERIMENT
AT HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
WHAT?
THE ACADEMY
IS A TESTING GROUND.
THE FIRST EXPERIMENT
WAS FIGURING OUT
HOW TO MAKE GOKU UNIFORMS
THAT HUMANS COULD HANDLE.
NEXT, THEY TWEAKED THEM
FOR COMBAT
AND USED THEM TO CONQUER
EVERY SCHOOL IN THE COUNTRY.
NOW, EVERYONE’S BEING FORCED
TO WEAR UNIFORMS
LACED WITH LIFE FIBERS ‐‐
AT LEAST, THE ONES
WHO CAN PHYSICALLY HANDLE IT.
ONCE THEY’RE ALL IN UNIFORM
AND SITTING IN THE STANDS,
THEY’LL BE OFFERED UP
AS HUMAN SACRIFICES
TO THE LIFE FIBERS.
S‐SACRIFICES?!
YEAH, IT’S THE FINAL EXPERIMENT
IN THE CHAIN ‐‐
GET EVERYONE IN TOWN
WEARING
LIFE FIBER‐INFUSED CLOTHING,
GET THEM INTO THE STADIUM,
THEN SACRIFICE THEM.
THAT’S WHAT THE CULTURAL
AND SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL
IS ALL ABOUT.
OH, CRAP!
IF THE PLAN’S TO GET EVERYONE
TO GET EATEN BY CLOTHES,
THEN SO WILL MAKO’S
MOM AND DAD!
YEAH, I SUPPOSE
THEY WILL, TOO.
AAH!
YOU KNOW THEY WILL.
WELL, SCREW THAT!
THERE’S NO WAY
I’M GONNA LET THAT HAPPEN!
RYUKO?
RAGYO AND SATSUKI KIRYUIN,
I’M GONNA TAKE BOTH
THOSE BITCHES DOWN FOR GOOD!
JUMPING INTO THE JAWS OF DEATH
AGAIN, HUH?
YEAH, BUT THIS TIME I’M HEADING
STRAIGHT DOWN ITS THROAT
AND RIPPING ITS GUTS OUT
WITH MY TEETH!
Senketsu: RYUKO.
DON’T WORRY.
IT’S COOL.
I WON’T LOSE CONTROL.
THAT’S ONE THING I’LL NEVER
PUT YOU THROUGH AGAIN.
BUT ONE WAY OR ANOTHER,
I GOT TO SETTLE THIS FIGHT
WITH SATSUKI.
AND NOW’S AS GOOD A TIME
AS ANY.
SO, YOU WITH ME
ON THIS, SENKETSU?
OF COURSE.
HMM. ME TOO.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE
WE’RE ALL GOING.
WE DON’T HAVE
MUCH TIME, THOUGH.
THE CLOCK’S TICKING.
Hououmaru: THE HYPER‐INNER
MANUFACTURING PLANT
IN MOZAMBIQUE
WAS ATTACKED.
Ragyo:
BY MILITANT RADICALS?
YES, MA’AM.
THEY FOUND OUT ABOUT
HOW REVOCS SPECIAL MID‐LAYERS
BOOST THE WEARER’S
PHYSICAL CAPABILITIES.
APPARENTLY, THEY WANT TO SEE
IF THE RUMORS WERE TRUE.
EXACTLY AS PLANNED.
IF WE CAN’T FORCE EVERYONE
TO BUY OUR CLOTHING,
WE CAN SIMPLY TRICK THEM
INTO TAKING IT.
REGARDLESS, ONCE THEY ARE WORN
BY REVOCS CLOTHING,
THEIR FATES ARE SEALED.
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL WORLD.
NOT YET.
WE’RE JUST GETTING STARTED.
TOMORROW, WE STEP ONTO
A NEW STAGE ‐‐
THE AWAKENING
OF THE COVERS.
YOUR DAUGHTER’S
IMPRESSIVE.
TEENS HAVE THE HIGHEST TOLERANCE
TO LIFE FIBERS,
AND CONQUERING
THAT DEMOGRAPHIC
WAS A BRILLIANT MOVE
ON HER PART.
ACCLIMATING THE KIDS
TO LIFE FIBERS
BY HOOKING THEM
ON THE POWER OF GOKU UNIFORMS
WAS INGENIOUS.
Nui: HAVING ALL YOUR DUCKS
IN A ROW IS CUTE,
BUT SUPER DULL.
GRAND COUTURIER.
DULL, EH?
AH, YES, YOU FIND MATOI’S
DAUGHTER MORE INTERESTING.
UH‐HUH.
I STILL CAN’T BELIEVE
SHE HUNTED DOWN
ALL THE PIECES
OF HER KAMUI
AND STITCHED THEM
BACK TOGETHER HERSELF.
THAT GIRL TAKES INSOLENCE
TO A WHOLE NOTHER LEVEL,
AND I LOVE IT!
IT’S ALWAYS
"FAIR IS FOUL AND FOUL IS FAIR"
WITH YOU, ISN’T IT?
YOU KNOW IT.
WELL, THOSE ARE EMPTY WORDS
FROM AN EMPTY AGE.
THERE IS ONLY ONE
TRUTH NOW.
THE ONLY THINGS
WHICH CAN BE CALLED BEAUTIFUL
ARE THOSE
THAT EARN MY APPROVAL.
THE GRAND FESTIVAL
IS TOMORROW,
AND I EXPECT YOU
TO DRESS APPROPRIATELY FOR IT.
ENOUGH TO SATISFY
EVEN MY SENSE OF STYLE.
I SWEAR,
HER AND HER DAUGHTER
ARE, LIKE,
CUT FROM THE SAME CLOTH.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
YOU’RE GIVING ME
A KNIFE?
NO, A TAILOR’S DAGGER
AND A TAILOR’S GLOVE.
USED TOGETHER, THEY CAN
CUT THROUGH LIFE FIBERS.
I FIGURED YOU’D NEED
A LITTLE MORE
THAN YOUR GUNS ON THIS.
SLICE THE BANSHI,
AND THE BAD GUYS
LOSE THEIR SHIRTS.
NICE. VERY NICE.
Mikisugi:
STAY FOCUSED OUT THERE.
OUR TARGETS ARE RAGYO
AND SATSUKI ONLY.
IT’S JUST US THREE,
SO LET’S NOT MESS AROUND
WITH ANYONE ELSE.
Ryuko: IS MAKO GONNA BE SAFE
WHILE WE’RE GONE?
SHE’S GONNA BE FINE.
I HAVE A TEAM
ON STANDBY HERE,
SO THEY’LL
KEEP AN EYE ON HER.
YOU’RE TRYING TO DITCH ME AGAIN,
AREN’T YOU?
MAKO.
WELL, I’M GOING.
BUT YOU CAN’T.
IT’S NOT SAFE THERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT’S WHERE I LIVE!
BESIDES, I GOT
ALL THESE SOUVENIRS
TO GIVE TO MOM AND DAD.
DAMN IT, MAKO.
IF YOU’RE GOING BACK HOME,
THEN I’M GOING, TOO.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU’RE AS STUBBORN AS ME.
[ ENGINE REVS ]
Sanagayama:
THE CULTURAL AND SPORTS
GRAND FESTIVAL IS TOMORROW.
YOU GOT THAT?!
I EXPECT Y’ALL TO PUT
YOUR SOULS INTO IT!
All: YES, SIR!
I SAID
PUT YOUR SOULS INTO IT!
All: YES, SIR!
TILT THESE LIGHTS DOWN
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
THEY SHOULD WRAP THE STAGE
JUST LIKE THAT.
IT’S A BIG DAY
FOR HONNOUJI ACADEMY,
SO IT’S GOT TO BE
DRAMATIC‐LOOKING.
THIS IS GONNA BE GREAT.
FASTER, PEOPLE!
WE’RE IN THE HOME STRETCH!
IORI,
HOW ARE THINGS GOING?
IT’S THE DAY
LADY SATSUKI’S DREAMED OF.
WE’LL BE READY
COME HELL OR HIGH WATER.
GET BACK TO IT, THEN.
I’LL BE DONE HERE
IN A BIT.
[ BEEPING ]
IT LOOKS LIKE
THOSE NAKED APES
HAVE TAKEN THE BAIT,
M’LADY.
LEAVING THEIR HIDDEN CAMERAS UP
WAS A STROKE OF GENIUS.
THEY WILL PROVIDE
THE FINAL PIECE OF THE PUZZLE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
Satsuki: SUMMON THE OTHERS
TO MY CHAMBERS.
NOW THAT PREPARATIONS FOR
MY MOTHER’S VISIT ARE COMPLETE,
I’D LIKE TO THANK YOU
FOR YOUR HARD WORK.
All: M’LADY.
TO THE SUCCESS
OF THE CULTURAL
AND SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL.
[ GLASSES SHATTER ]
ATTENTION, HONNOUJI ACADEMY.
WE HAVE CONQUERED EVERY SCHOOL
IN THE COUNTRY.
ALL WHO OPPOSED
OUR GOKU UNIFORMS
HAVE BEEN ELIMINATED.
SO TODAY, WE CELEBRATE!
EAT AND DRINK YOUR FILL.
PRAISE THE KIRYUIN NAME.
LET HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S CULTURAL
AND SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL BEGIN!
[ FANFARE PLAYS ]
THIS IS SO EXCITING,
ISN’T IT?
WHO CARES?!
EAT, WOMAN, EAT!
WE’RE GONNA LOAD UP
AND HIGH‐TAIL IT
OUT OF HERE.
HOLD THE PHONE.
IS YOUR SUIT PAINTED ON?
HELL, YEAH.
I SOLD THAT DUMB‐ASS THING
SOON AS I GOT IT.
SON OF A ‐‐
WHY DIDN’T I THINK OF THAT?
HUH?
NOW FOR THE MOMENT
YOU’VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
JOIN ME IN WELCOMING
OUR GUEST OF HONOR.
I PRESENT TO YOU
THE FOUNDER OF THIS ACADEMY ‐‐
RAGYO KIRYUIN!
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WHAT A GRAND ENTRANCE.
IMPRESSIVE, AS ALWAYS.
THOSE WHO RULE
MUST SHINE LIKE THE SUN
AT ALL TIMES.
IT’S BEEN TOO LONG,
AUNTIE.
[ CHUCKLES ] YES.
AND HOW IS YOUR
FATHER DOING, NONON?
FINE.
THANK YOU.
AND, YOU...
STILL OCCUPYING YOUR TIME
WITH HACKING
AND STOCK MANIPULATION?
OH, NO.
NOT ANYMORE.
REALLY? WHAT A PITY.
[ GIGGLES ]
Ragyo: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
I ASK YOU, WHAT IS THE WORLD?
WHY, THE WORLD IS CLOTHING.
THE FATE OF WHICH
IS RULED BY BEINGS
KNOWN AS LIFE FIBERS.
I HAVE BEEN ENTRUSTED
TO TAKE THEIR RULE
TO THE NEXT STAGE
OF COMPLETION.
I AM THEIR EMISSARY
AND THEIR VOICE.
HONNOUJI ACADEMY WAS CREATED
AS A VESSEL FOR THEIR WILL,
WHERE THE WEAK WILL SERVE
AS THE FOUNDATION
FOR WHAT IS TO COME.
SO CONSIDER YOURSELVES
HONORED.
ANYONE KNOW
WHAT SHE’S TALKING ABOUT?
SHE’S TALKING
ABOUT ALL OF YOU PIGS.
TODAY IS WHEN YOU’LL BE EATEN
BY YOUR CLOTHING.
NOW LET THE CELEBRATION
BEGIN!
[ GASPING ]
[ SHOUTING ]
AAH! MOM! DAD! GUTS!
OH, CRAP!
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
Ryuko: YOU HEAR THAT?
SOUNDS LIKE IT’S STARTED.
LET’S HURRY!
THIS BABY WILL GET US OVER
THE WALL AND ONTO THE STAGE.
IT’S MY CUSTOM DTR.
YOUR DOTONBORI ROBO?
DTR.
YEAH, DOTONBORI ROBO.
DTR!
UH, HE HATES THAT NAME.
JUST HUMOR HIM.
GEEZ, DON’T WE GOT ENOUGH
TO WORRY ABOUT?
WAIT! WHAT ABOUT ME?!
[ PANTING ]
OH, NO. I SLIPPED.
THERE’S NOWHERE TO GRAB ON.
GO AND HIDE AND I’LL BRING
SOME SNACKS BACK FOR YOU.
DTR GOING UP!
HAVE FUN
STORMING THE STADIUM!
[ WHIMPERS ]
AT LAST, THERE IS SILENCE,
MAGNIFICENT SILENCE.
THE BABBLING
OF THE FOOLISH HUMANS FADE,
LEAVING NOTHING
BUT THE TRANQUIL FIBERS
TO FILL THE VOID.
YES, LADY RAGYO.
THE EXPERIMENT
IS A SUCCESS.
[ GRUNTS ]
YOUR LITTLE PARTY’S OVER,
SATSUKI KIRYUIN.
LET EVERYONE GO,
OR ELSE!
WELL, WELL,
YOU MUST BE RYUKO MATOI.
BITE ME!
INDEED.
AND I TAKE IT
THAT IS KAMUI SENKETSU ‐‐
THE END‐PRODUCT OF
ISSHIN MATOI’S FUTILE EFFORTS.
IT’S QUITE LOVELY.
SO, YOU’RE
RAGYO KIRYUIN?
JUST LIKE YOUR DAUGHTER ‐‐
A BIG SHOT WITH A BIG MOUTH.
HOW DROLL.
PERHAPS YOU DO NOT REALIZE
WHO YOU ARE TALKING TO.
I AM RAGYO KIRYUIN,
HEAD OF THE KIRYU‐‐ AAH!
[ GASPS ]
WHAT IS THE MEANING
OF THIS?
THE TIME FOR SPEECHES
IS OVER.
[ GASPS ]
[ GROANS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
HEAR ME, DIRECTOR.
AS OF THIS MOMENT,
HONNOUJI ACADEMY AND I
ARE PUTTING AN END
TO YOUR REIGN.
WHAT THE HELL?!
[ GASPS ]
OOH, SO THAT’S
HER GAME.
ARE YOU TRYING TO TAKE
THE THRONE FROM ME?
NO, I’M NOT!
PEOPLE DO NOT LIVE
FOR THE SAKE OF CLOTHING.
I, SATSUKI KIRYUIN, AM RISING UP
TO OVERTHROW THE LIFE FIBERS.
I DID NOT CREATE
HONNOUJI ACADEMY FOR YOU,
BUT TO DESTROY YOU.
REMEMBER THAT,
RAGYO KIRYUIN!
Senketsu: CHAOS BREAKS LOOSE
ON THE STAGE,
BUT WHO TUGS
ON THE THREAD OF DESTINY
OF THESE GIRLS
WHO FIGHT IN LIVING CLOTHES?
AND AS THE LOOM OF FATE
SPINS THE FABRIC OF KARMA,
WHO IS THAT
SMILING IN THE SHADOWS?
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"INTO THE NIGHT."