[ ALL SHOUTING ]
Sanageyama: GET READY!
HERE’S THE ULTRA GOKU UNIFORM
BATTLE FORMATION!
CHARGE!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
I’M NOT QUITTING YET!
YAAH!
IT’S A HIGH‐VELOCITY
LIFE FIBER JAMMER.
THE FIBERS SPIN SO FAST,
THEY DEFLECT ‐‐
WHOA! IT’S LIKE
A GINORMOUS RUBBER SOCK!
OW!
ARE YOU OKAY?
THAT’S WHAT YOU GET
FOR JUMPING IN HEAD FIRST.
Inumuta: OHH!
I SWEAR, YOU NEVER LEARN.
UNLESS
WE SHUT THAT JAMMER OFF...
WE’RE STUCK WITH
OUR ASSES HANGING OUT.
HYAAAAAAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAH!
HAI!
[ GRUNTING ]
ENOUGH
OF THESE DISTRACTIONS.
NOW, ALLOW ME TO SHOW YOU
WHO THE MASTER IS.
[ ALL GROANING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
HOLY ‐‐
NO WAY!
MY STARS ARE GONE!
[ ALL SCREAM ]
[ GASPS ]
SHINRA...KOUKETSU.
ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION.
WHAT’S WRONG, SENKETSU?
[ Weakly ]
I HAVE NO STRENGTH.
THAT LIGHT IS PARALYZING ME
WITH FEAR.
SHINRA‐KOUKETSU
WAS DESIGNED TO BE
THE MASTER
OF ALL LIFE FIBERS.
THOSE THAT REBEL AGAINST IT
TREMBLE IN FEAR
AND ARE RENDERED POWERLESS.
THIS IS ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION.
HERE IS THE WORLD,
SEEN VIA OUR SATELLITE.
LOOK AT ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
EVERY ONE OF THEM
WEARS REVOCS CLOTHING.
WHEN I UNLEASH THE POWER
OF ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION
UPON THE WORLD,
THE DORMANT LIFE FIBERS
IN THEIR CLOTHING WILL AWAKEN.
EVERY HUMAN WILL BE SWALLOWED
BY THEIR CLOTHING,
AND THE EARTH WILL BE COVERED
IN A SINGLE PIECE OF CLOTH.
NEW LIFE FIBERS WILL BE BORN
INSIDE THIS COCOON SPHERE,
AND WHEN THE PLANET EXPLODES,
THEY WILL SCATTER
ACROSS THE COSMOS.
FABULOUS.
THIS IS
HOW THE UNIVERSE WORKS.
AND YOU NO LONGER HAVE
ANY MEANS OF OPPOSING ME.
Both: AS LONG AS WE’RE ALIVE,
WE’LL OPPOSE YOU!
WE’RE STRIPPING DOWN...
TO OUR NUDIST SOULS...
IN OUR ULTIMATE
DOUBLE NAKED DT...
RRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR!
OOF!
HOW RIDICULOUS.
[ GIGGLES ]
DON’T YOU WANNA KILL ’EM?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
REMEMBER, HUMANS ARE
A PRECIOUS ENERGY SOURCE
FOR THE PRIMORDIAL
LIFE FIBER.
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
Senketsu:
THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER.
DIDN’T WE KILL
THAT DAMN THING?
ONCE IT ABSORBS
YOUR FRIENDS,
THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER
WILL BE GOOD AS NEW.
I AM SORRY.
IT SEEMS YOU RISKED YOUR LIFE
ON A PLAN DESTINED TO FAIL.
Gamagoori: NOT QUITE.
DON’T COUNT US OUT
JUST YET, WOMAN!
GAMAGOORI? MAKO?
GUYS!
OOH! LOOKY!
IF YOU CAN MOVE IN
THE ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION FIELD,
YOU MUST BE SUPERSTRONG.
BUT IT’S NO USE ‐‐
HUMANS ARE SLAVES TO CLOTHES,
AND THAT’S NEVER GONNA CHANGE,
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO.
AAAH!
[ Straining ]
THAT’S NOT TRUE!
THAT SO ISN’T TRUE!
RYUKO’S NOT A SLAVE
TO SENKETSU.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, NEITHER ONE
OF THEM’S THE BOSS OF THE OTHER.
THEY’RE THE BEST MATCH
OF PEOPLE AND CLOTHES EVER!
YOUR VOICE
IS SO ANNOYING.
TIME TO DIE!
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ GASPS ]
G‐GAMAGOORI!
I AM HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S
DISCIPLINARY CHAIR,
IRA GAMAGOORI!
I PROTECT SATSUKI KIRYUIN
AND ALL OF THE STUDENTS!
I AM A LIVING
[Gurgling] SHIEEEEEEELD!
[ GASPS ]
YOU UGLY, UGLY, UGLY APE!
I’LL KILL YOU FIRST!
YOU AIN’T KILLING ANYONE!
WHAT THE HELL?!
MY KAMUI AIN’T WORKING NOW,
BUT I CAN STILL TAKE YOU ON,
THANKS TO THE LIFE FIBERS
IN MY BODY.
WHAT?!
I AIN’T HUMAN,
AND I AIN’T CLOTHES, EITHER.
I’M SOMETHING
IN THE MIDDLE.
AND FOR THE FIRST TIME,
I’M GLAD I GOT STUCK
WITH THIS FREAKY‐ASS BODY,
’CAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE
I’M SOMETHING
YOUR ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION SHIT
DON’T WORK ON!
[ HISSES ]
AAAAAAH!
DON’T BE DEAD!
COME ON! WAKE UP, WAKE UP!
[ Weakly ] THANK GOD
YOU’RE SAFE, MANKANSHOKU.
THANK...GO‐‐
[ WHIMPERS ]
G‐GAMAGOORI!
[ WAILING ]
GAMAGOORI!
GODDAMN BITCH!
YOU BASTARDS!
[ LAUGHS ]
LOOK, RYUKO.
THIS IS HOUOUMARU,
SLUMBERING PEACEFULLY
AS SHE POWERS
THE ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION FIELD.
THIS IS
WHERE YOU SHOULD AIM.
STOP SCREWING WITH ME!
GO AHEAD.
STRIKE AT IT ALL YOU WANT.
YOU’LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO REACH HER!
RYUKO!
IT’S TOO DANGEROUS!
IT’S NO USE, SENKETSU.
B‐BUT IF SHE KEEPS THAT UP,
SHE’LL ‐‐
I UNDERSTAND
YOUR CONCERN FOR HER
BUT SHE WILL NOT STOP,
NO MATTER WHAT WE SAY.
[ GASPS ]
SATSUKI.
YOU CAN ‐‐
YOU CAN HEAR ME?
YES ‐‐ PERFECTLY.
OF COURSE.
IS IT TIME YET?
IT IS ‐‐
AT LONG LAST.
WITH THIS...
HUMANITY ENDS.
YOU GUY‐‐
I WILL BEGIN
WITH YOUR FRIENDS.
THEY WILL ALL BE WOVEN
INTO THE FABRIC
THAT WILL COVER
THE EARTH.
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
[ GRUNTS WEAKLY ]
H‐HOW?
I AM NEITHER CLOTHING NOR HUMAN,
JUST LIKE RYUKO.
SHIPPU SENJIN!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
OH, YEAH!
I CAN MOVE AGAIN!
HEY, I THINK OUR GOKU UNIFORMS
HAVE THEIR POWER BACK.
THEY DO, INDEED.
LIFE FIBER OVERRIDE!
KAMUI JUNKETSU!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
M‐MANKANSHOKU?
I NEVER THOUGHT
YOU’D BE SAVING ME.
THAT MAKES TWO OF US.
RIGHT ON, SENKETSU!
Satsuki:
DO YOU SEE, RAGYO?
THIS IS WHAT THE PEOPLE YOU
MOCKED AS FRAUDS ARE CAPABLE OF.
BUT HOW?
BY A KNOCK‐OFF KAMUI.
IT’S ’CAUSE
HE’S A KNOCK‐OFF.
Senketsu:
WHEN SATSUKI HEARD MY VOICE,
THAT’S WHEN I REALIZED IT.
THAT IS WHEN I KNEW
I HAD BEEN GIVEN
THE SAME POWER AS RYUKO.
NEITHER HUMAN...
NOR CLOTHING.
Both:
THIS IS WHAT IT MEANS TO BE...
...LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZED!
RYUKO!
♪
[ WHEEZES ]
DESTROY THE TRANSMITTER ‐‐
HURRY!
Together: RIGHT!
NOPE.
NOPE, NOPE, NOPE!
YOU CAN’T GET BY US,
YOU SILLIES!
[ ALL GASP ]
MON MIGNON PRêT‐à‐PORTER!
IT’S LIKE A WHOLE CLOSET‐FULL
OF CHEAP MASS‐PRODUCED CRAP!
[ LAUGHS ]
THE DATA’S
NOT EVEN WORTH COLLECTING.
[ LAUGHS ]
THERE’S SO MANY OF THEM!
AT THIS RATE...
WE’LL NEVER REACH IT.
[ LAUGHS ]
LEAVE THE TRANSMITTER TO ME!
I’M GOING TO ENJOY THIS!
GAMAGOORI?!
YOU’RE ALIVE!
OF COURSE.
I WAS WEARING
THE TITANIUM BELLY BAND
MY RELATIVES MADE
AS A PRECAUTION.
THE ONLY DAMAGE I SUFFERED
WAS A TINY SCRATCH.
OH, COME ON!
YOU TOTALLY FAINTED!
WE ALL SAW YOU!
IT’S TIME
I ATONED FOR MY BEHAVIOR.
SHACKLE REGALIA ‐‐
PERSONA UNLEASHED!
RRRRRRRRRRRRRR!
THERE!
TASTE THE POWER
OF MY EGO UNLEASHED ‐‐
UNSHACKLED,
WITHOUT SHAME!
BEHOLD!
BAKUKAI‐GOUTEKI!
YAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
WE GOT IT FROM HERE,
BIG GUY!
WHAT’S THE POINT
OF GETTING NAKED
IF US NUDISTS
DON’T STRUT OUR STUFF?!
OH, YOU GET NAKED
’CAUSE YOU LIKE IT,
AND YOU KNOW IT!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
NO.
[ RYUKO AND SATSUKI SHOUT ]
IMPOSSIBLE!
YOUR PLANS FOR THE COCOON SPHERE
HAVE COME UNDONE, RAGYO.
HAVE THEY, NOW?
NUI!
SACRIFICE YOURSELF.
[ GASPS ]
VRAIMENT?
OUI, MAMA!
[ GIGGLING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ GASPS ]
HO...LY...SHIT.
Ragyo: POOR NUI.
THE LIFE FIBERS IN YOUR BODY
WERE JUST TOO POWERFUL.
THEY KEPT YOU
FROM HAVING THE CHANCE
TO EXPERIENCE
WEARING A KAMUI OF YOUR OWN.
BUT NOW YOU CAN WEAR
SOMETHING BETTER ‐‐
THE ULTIMATE DRESS THAT IS
THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER!
Nui:
NOT QUITE, LADY RAGYO.
YOU’RE WEARING ME NOW.
I AM INDEED.
AND YOU FEEL SO WONDERFUL
ON ME, NUI.
YOU THINK SO?
I’M SO HAPPY!
DEAREST NUI,
I WILL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
[ MOANING LOUDLY ]
HEY, GET BACK HERE!
I HAVE RAGYO’S OBJECTIVE.
SHE’S HEADING STRAIGHT FOR
THE REVOCS
COMMUNICATIONS SATELLITE.
Mikisugi:
SHE’S GONNA TRY TO HOOK KOUKETSU
UP TO THE SATELLITE
AND THEN SEND
THE ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION SIGNAL
TO THE WHOLE PLANET!
Satsuki:
ALL IS NOT LOST.
THE SIGNAL CANNOT NEUTRALIZE
OUR GOKU UNIFORMS,
SO WE CAN STILL LAUNCH
A COUNTERATTACK.
NOW...
AWAKEN,
MY SLUMBERING LIFE FIBERS.
IT’S TIME
TO TAKE YOUR TRUE FORM...
[ SMOOCHES ]
...AND COVER THE ENTIRE PLANET!
SHINRA‐KOUKETSU...
ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION!!
[ ALL MURMUR, GASP ]
WE’RE TOO LATE.
Ryuko: I’LL GO.
[ ALL GASP ]
YOU HEARD ME ‐‐ I’LL GO.
I WANNA GO ON A DATE
WITH YOU!
HUH?
NO, LISTEN.
WHEN YOU GET BACK,
I WANNA GO
ON A DATE WITH YOU!
GIRLS SHOULD WEAR
CUTE DRESSES
AND CUTE ACCESSORIES
IF THEY WANT.
AND GO OUT
AND EAT ICE CREAM AND CHEESE
AND GO SHOPPING
IF THEY WANT.
THAT’S THE KIND OF WORLD
YOU’RE FIGHTING FOR.
AND I KNOW
YOU CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN!
[ Echoing ] ...IT HAPPEN!
...IT HAPPEN!
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT’S A DATE.
GO TO IT.
THE FATE OF HUMANITY
IS ‐‐
AND CUTE CLOTHES
ARE IN YOUR HANDS!
YOU GOT IT!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
I’M PUTTING ON
ALL OF YOUR GOKU UNIFORMS
SO WE CAN
GO KICK HER ASS TOGETHER!
♪
RRRRRRRRRAAAAAAAAAH!
SENKETSU‐KISARAGI!
Ragyo: HOW BEAUTIFUL.
HOW GORGEOUS.
THE COCOON SPHERE GENESIS.
WHAT’S THIS?
YOU’RE DONE, RAGYO!
INTERESTING.
YOU MADE A QUILT
OF ALL THE AVAILABLE LIFE FIBERS
TO COME HERE.
YOU’RE TOO LATE, THOUGH.
LOOK AT YOUR PLANET.
THE SIGNAL HAS REACHED
EVERY LIFE FIBER ON IT.
YOU CAN’T STOP HUMANITY’S
CONVERSION INTO FABRIC,
YOU FOOL.
AIN’T NO WAY IN HELL
I’M GIVING UP THAT EASY.
I GOT A DATE.
AND I PLAN ON KEEPING IT!
WHAT NONSENSE.
UUUAAAAAAAAAH!
[ LAUGHS ]
AWW.
WHAT’S THE MATTER?
YOU KNOW,
THE BLADES OF YOUR SCISSORS
ARE MADE
OF HARDENED LIFE FIBERS.
AND WHEN ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION
IS ACTIVATED,
ALL LIFE FIBERS
BECOME POWERLESS AGAINST IT.
WHAT?!
YOU TURNED YOUR BLADE
ON THIS GRAND CLOTH,
THE EQUAL TO ANY GOD!
AND FOR THAT...
[ GRUNTS ]
...YOU MUST BE PUNISHED!
Senketsu:
RYUKO! ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I’M GOOD.
JUST CAUGHT ME OFF GUARD.
SOICHIRO’S DYING WISH
MUST HAVE BEEN
SUCH A BURDEN FOR YOU,
MY DEAR.
AND YET, WITH ALL YOUR POWER,
YOU STILL DON’T UNDERSTAND
THE BASIC PRINCIPLE
OF THE UNIVERSE!
LOOK, RYUKO ‐‐
THAT BLUE WORLD,
THAT SHINING SUN,
THOSE TWINKLING STARS.
THIS IS THE COSMOS.
AND ONE DAY,
EVEN THIS WILL COME TO AN END.
SINCE THIS GALAXY WAS BORN,
CREATION AND DESTRUCTION
HAVE GONE HAND IN HAND.
THE LIFE FIBERS
ARE PART OF THIS ECOSYSTEM.
THEY ARE PART
OF THE LAW OF THE UNIVERSE!
WHEN ARE YOU
GOING TO SHUT THE HELL UP?!
HOW CAN YOU BE SO DENSE?
YOU ARE
MY OWN FLESH AND BLOOD.
IT AIN’T LIKE
I WAS RAISED BY YOU!
AH, YES.
I ADMIT, THAT WAS A MISTAKE!
YOU’LL HAVE TO DO BETTER THAN
THAT IF YOU WANT TO KILL ME.
INDEED. I MUST BE SUBCONSCIOUSLY
PULLING MY PUNCHES.
IT APPEARS I STILL HAVE
A SHRED OF HUMANITY LEFT IN ME.
OH, WELL.
I’LL JUST RID MYSELF
OF IT.
AND NOW YOU DIIIIIIIE!
YOU DON’T GET TO TELL ME
WHAT TO DO!
I DECIDE WHEN I DIE!
YOU’RE REGENERATING
FASTER THAN EVER.
LIFE FIBER COMPATIBILITY
IS A PRECIOUS THING.
IT’S A SHAME
TO WASTE IT!
[ PANTING ]
IF IT’S THAT PRECIOUS,
EASE UP, BITCH!
Senketsu: RYUKO,
WE’RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME!
I KNOW.
THIS TIME, I’LL END IT!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
YOU’LL END WHAT, MY DEAR?
YOUR LIFE?
I CAN HELP YOU WITH THAT!
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
THANKS FOR MAKING IT EASY.
EASY?
YOU FORGET?
THE CLOSER I GET
TO DYING,
THE STRONGER I BOUNCE BACK
FROM IT, YOU FRIGGIN’ HAG!
THEN YOU...DELIBERATELY
THREW YOURSELF AT ME?
UH‐HUH.
I TOOK IT LIKE A KID
GETTING A DOSE OF TOUGH LOVE
FROM HER BITCH‐ASS MOM.
AND I’LL KEEP TAKING IT
TILL ME AND SENKETSU MAX OUT!
GO ON
AND TORTURE YOURSELF, THEN.
I CANNOT BE HARMED
BY LIFE FIBERS.
YEAH? WHAT IF I ABSORB
THAT ABSOLUTE SUBMISSION CRAP?!
IMPOSSIBLE.
DAD MADE A WEAPON,
ALL RIGHT.
BUT IT WASN’T
NO SCISSOR BLADE.
IT WAS ME AND SENKETSU!
YOU LIE!
NOPE.
HE GAVE US THE POWER
OF INFINITE ABSORPTION.
Senketsu
I REALIZED IT DURING OUR BATTLE
WITH SHINRA‐KOUKETSU.
THE REASON I ABSORB LIFE FIBERS
AFTER BATTLES
IS TO INCREASE
MY POWERS OF ABSORPTION.
I AM EVOLVING.
I HAVE FREE WILL.
AND I CAN COMMUNICATE
WITH HUMANS IF I WANT TO!
THING ABOUT US IS,
WE’RE NOT HUMAN OR CLOTHING!
AND YET, AT THE SAME TIME,
WE ARE BOTH HUMAN AND CLOTHING!
WE ARE EVERYTHING!
PEOPLE CAN’T BECOME
CLOTHING!
PEOPLE ARE PEOPLE!
CLOTHES ARE CLOTHES!!
HOW DARE YOU SPOUT
SUCH RIDICULOUS NONSENSE!
NONSENSE?!
THAT’S HOW WE ROLL!
YO!
LISTEN UP,
YOU LIFE FIBERS!
PEOPLE ARE PEOPLE!
AND CLOTHES ARE CLOTHES!
SO CUT THE SHIT
AND TURN ALL THE HUMANS
BACK INTO HUMANS!!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
EVERYONE’S BEEN FREED.
YES.
AND I’M FREE, AS WELL ‐‐
FREE OF THE KIRYUIN’S KARMA.
Ragyo: NO.
THIS CAN’T BE HAPPENING.
IT’S ALL RETURNING
TO THE WAY IT WAS.
YEAH, MOM. IT’S OVER.
AND YOU’RE DONE.
THE EARTH AIN’T GONNA
TURN INTO A COCOON SPHERE.
AND YOU’RE COMING BACK ‐‐
WITH ME.
HOW PATHETIC.
I, TOO,
WILL DECIDE HOW I DIE!
SOUND FAMILIAR, DEAR?
WELL, NOW IS AS GOOD A TIME
AS ANY!
YOU’RE CRAZY!
HARDLY.
THIS IS NOT THE END,
RYUKO.
THE LIFE FIBERS WILL KEEP
ADVANCING THROUGHOUT THE COSMOS.
AND SOON, MORE WILL COME
TO THIS PLANET.
COUNT ON IT.
[ HEART BEATING ]
EVEN SO, PEOPLE WILL GO ON
BEING PEOPLE.
COUNT ON THAT.
HM.
LET’S GO HOME.
WHAT’S WRONG, SENKETSU?
SHINRA‐KOUKETSU’S POWER
WAS GREATER THAN I THOUGHT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HURRY!
THERE’S NOT MUCH TIME!
NO! DON’T DO
ANYTHING CRAZY!
THIS COMING FROM YOU,
THE MASTER OF CRAZY.
SENKETSU!
IT’S ALL RIGHT.
YOU FINISHED
WHAT YOUR FATHER STARTED,
AND I’M SURE HE’S PROUD.
I HAD A WONDERFUL TIME
KNOWING YOU.
[ Voice breaking ] SHUT UP!
STOP TALKING LIKE IT’S OVER!
DON’T CRY.
YOU CANNOT WEAR
A SAILOR UNIFORM FOREVER.
FROM NOW ON,
WEAR WHATEVER YOU WANT ‐‐
CLOTHES MORE CUTE
THAN ME.
[ SOBS ]
YOU GOT IT.
I’LL WEAR CLOTHES
THAT’LL MAKE YOU JEALOUS!
[ GASPS ]
SENKETSU!!
♪
Satsuki: SNAP OUT OF IT!
SNAP OUT OF IT, RYUKO!
[ GASPS ]
YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
RYUKO!!
RYUKO!
Together: MATOI!
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
RYUKO!
GUTS!
WELCOME HOME.
GLAD I’M BACK...
SIS.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ ALL CHUCKLE ]
WHAT ABOUT THE LIFE FIBERS
THAT ARE LEFT?
DON’T WORRY ABOUT THEM.
THEY’RE LIKE
THE CLOTH‐FORM COVERS.
ONCE THEY DISCONNECT
FROM PEOPLE,
THEY’LL LOSE THEIR ENERGY SOURCE
AND DIE OFF ON THEIR OWN.
AND AS FOR US NUDIST BEACHERS,
THIS WRAPS UP OUR MISSION.
THANK GOD.
I MISS MY PANTS.
[ Chuckling ]
I KNOW, RIGHT?
BUT FIRST, WE GOT TO
CLEAN UP THIS MESS.
AND BY "US,"
I MEAN US GROWN‐UPS.
THOSE GIRLS HAVE A DATE,
AND THEY EARNED IT.