Ragyo: WELL?
DO YOU LIKE
HOW JUNKETSU FEELS ON YOU BODY?
Ryuko: IT’S WONDERFUL.
RELISH IT.
YOU AND I ARE THE ONLY ONES
WHO CAN EXPERIENCE THIS FEELING.
Nui: SHE’S RIGHT.
I’LL NEVER KNOW
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
I’M SO JEALOUS.
THE LIFE FIBERS IN NUI
REPEL OTHER FIBERS.
EVEN IF SHE WERE A KAMUI,
SHE CAN’T DRAW ON ITS POWER.
THAT’S WHY
I’M THE GRAND COUTURIER.
IF I CAN’T WEAR ONE,
I’LL MAKE THE GREATEST KAMUI
EVER INSTEAD.
NOW THAT
YOU’RE ONE WITH IT,
THE PURPOSE OF HUMANS
SHOULD BE CLEAR.
HUMANS EXIST
TO SERVE CLOTHING.
EXACTLY.
LIFE FIBERS ARE THE PINNACLE
OF ALL LIVING THINGS ‐‐
ON THIS WORLD AND BEYOND.
COME ON, RYUKO.
HURRY UP AND SHOW ME.
LET ME SEE WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE
IN YOUR FINEST.
LIFE FIBER OVERRIDE!
KAMUI JUNKETSU!
Nui: OOH!
HOW BEAUTIFUL!
LADY RAGYO?
LADY SATSUKI
HAS ESCAPED.
SHE GOT AWAY?
WHY DON’T YOU
DEAL WITH HER?
YES, MOTHER.
DON’T TELL ME YOU’RE STILL
AFTER REVENGE FOR YOUR DADDY.
OOH!
[ GASPS ]
THAT WAS FOR LUCK.
IT SEEMS
SHE HAS A HARD TIME
CONTROLLING
ALL THAT PENT‐UP ENERGY.
WHAT SHE LACKS
IN EXPERIENCE,
SHE MAKES UP FOR
WITH TECHNIQUE.
DOES THIS MEAN LADY RYUKO HAS
COMPLETELY AWAKENED, MA’AM?
QUITE.
YOU SEE,
WHEN ITS HOST IS THREATENED,
LIFE FIBERS
BECOME EVEN MORE ACTIVE.
NO MATTER HOW HARD
SOICHIRO TRIED TO CONTAIN THEM,
AWAKENING RYUKO WAS EASY.
I JUST GAVE HER A DOSE OF
EXISTENTIAL TERROR, AND VOILà.
HOUOUMARU,
GO BACK TO REVOCS
AND GATHER THE EMPLOYEES
TOGETHER.
I’LL BE CALLING IN
FROM THE MANSION.
THE ENDGAME
IS UPON US, NUI.
OOH! I CAN’T WAIT!
MY HEART’S ALL POUNDING!
I BETTER HURRY UP
AND FINISH MY WORK.
[ GRUNTING ]
AND TO THINK YOU WERE
MY LITTLE SISTER ‐‐ ONCE.
Ryuko:
YOU’RE PLAYING THAT CARD?
DON’T MAKE ME PUKE.
I’M LETTING YOU KNOW
I WON’T HOLD BACK.
I’LL CRUSH ANYONE WHO BECOMES
A PUPPET TO LIFE FIBERS ‐‐
EVEN YOU!
LET’S BEGIN, SENKETSU.
Senketsu: RIGHT.
LIFE FIBER SYNCHRONIZE,
KAMUI SENKETSU!
WELL, WELL. SHE SYNCHRONIZED
WITH SENKETSU RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
OUR SATSUKI’S
FULL OF SURPRISES.
WE CAN’T JUST STAND HERE
AND WATCH!
LET’S GET IN THERE
AND FIGHT!
THAT’S THE BEST IDEA
I HEARD YET.
[ CHOIR SINGS "HALLELUJAH" ]
[ MAKO SHOUTS ]
HOLD UP A SECOND.
WE’RE A LITTLE BUSY HERE,
SLACKER‐DOODLE.
I HAVE A SUPER‐IMPORTANT MESSAGE
FOR YOU GUYS FROM LADY SATSUKI.
HERE I COME, SATSUKI!!
STILL GOT BAKUZAN?
[ CHUCKLES ]
MOMMY BREAKS YOUR TOY,
SO YOU CLING TO IT
LIKE A LITTLE KID.
IT IS MY RESOLVE.
IT IS MY VENGEANCE.
EVEN IF IT’S BEEN
SMASHED TO PIECES,
AS LONG AS ONE SLIVER REMAINS,
IT CAN BE REMADE.
THE ELITE FOUR KEPT IT SAFE,
KNOWING I’D RETURN TO CLAIM IT,
FOR IT IS THE SYMBOL
OF HONNOUJI ACADEMY’S PURPOSE,
AND WITH IT,
WE SHALL PREVAIL!
YEAH, RIGHT!
YOU DO THAT!
YOU CAN’T HANDLE JUNKETSU,
AND YOU SURE AS HELL
CAN’T GET ANY POWER
OUT OF THAT CHEAP KNOCK‐OFF.
YOU’RE ALL TALK
AND NO ACTION.
IF THAT IS WHAT YOU THINK,
THEN YOU STILL UNDERESTIMATE ME.
I SHALL CORRECT THAT.
SENKETSU SENJIN!
UAAAAAAAAAAH!
SENKETSU SHIPPU!
YOU AND YOUR CHEAP SHOTS!
I’M JUST GETTING STARTED!
SENJIN SHIPPU!
INTERESTING.
[ HUMMING ]
OKEYDOKEY.
GUESS THAT’S ENOUGH WORK
FOR ONE DAY.
NICE HIT ‐‐
FOR A STUPID RAG.
RYUKO, TAKE OFF THAT OUTFIT
AND PUT ME ON.
YEAH,
LIKE HELL I WILL.
YOU THINK I LIKE
LOOKING LIKE SOME RIDICULOUS HO?
RIDICULOUS?
YOU CAN’T MEAN THAT.
DAMN STRAIGHT.
WHAT ELSE DO I CALL CLOTHES
THAT SHRINK DOWN TO NOTHING?
EVERY TIME
YOU POWERED ON,
YOU BARELY COVERED
ANYTHING ON ME.
WHEN YOU ACCESS
THE LIFE FIBERS’ POWER,
YOU’RE IN DANGER
OF SUCCUMBING TO THEM.
DIRECT CONTACT WITH YOUR SKIN
MUST BE KEPT TO A MINIMUM.
THAT IS WHAT
SYNCHRONIZATION IS FOR.
IF YOU WANT TO CALL IT ANYTHING,
CALL IT GENIUS.
GENIUS, MY ASS. IT’S BEING
A CHICKENSHIT, IS ALL.
IT’S ABOUT YOU
WANTING THE POWER OF CLOTHES,
BUT YOU’RE TOO SCARED
TO GIVE YOURSELF UP TO THEM.
THAT HALF‐ASS GETUP IS THAT
HALF‐ASS ATTITUDE ALL THE WAY.
IT’S STRAIGHT‐UP PATHETIC,
IS WHAT IT IS.
YOU’RE WRONG.
WHEN YOU AND I
WERE TRULY SYNCHRONIZED,
YOU WERE WEARING ME,
AND I WAS WORN BY YOU.
WE WERE AS ONE!
JUNKETSU IS WEARING YOU ‐‐
NOTHING MORE.
AND WHAT’S WRONG
WITH THAT?
BEING WORN BY IT FEELS
SO AMAZING, I CAN’T STAND IT.
HUMAN BEINGS WERE BORN
TO BE WORN BY THE LIFE FIBERS.
BEING WORN BY THEM IS
A FEELING YOU CAN’T BELIEVE ‐‐
THE ULTIMATE BLISS.
IT IS THE BLISS
OF BEING A SLAVE!
IF YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH IT,
THEN DIE. SUBMIT OR DIE.
SOUNDS LIKE SOMETHING
YOU’D SAY, DON’T IT?
DON’T IT,
SATSUKI KIRYUIN?!
SENKETSU SENJIN!
[ GASPS ]
DON’T HOLD BACK ON HER.
NOW I SEE
WHAT’S GOING ON HERE.
SURE, YOU PUT HIM ON
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT YOU DON’T KNOW
HOW TO WEAR HIM YET!
SENKETSU SHIPPU!
TOO SLOW.
SENJIN SHIPPU!
NOPE.
STILL TOO SLOW.
YAAAAAAAAAH!
LADY SATSUKI!
WHAT THE HELL’S
WRONG WITH HER?!
POOR THING.
CAN’T YOU FIGHT BACK?
YOU KNOW WHY YOU CAN’T?
IT’S ’CAUSE I KNOW WHAT YOU’RE
GONNA DO BEFORE YOU DO IT!
SYNCHRONIZATION,
MY ASS!
YOU AND SENKETSU
AIN’T SYNCHING UP AT ALL!
YOU’RE JUST SHOUTING ORDERS
AT HIM,
BUT HE’S ONLY USING
HIS STRENGTH TO ATTACK.
THAT’S WHY THERE’S A DELAY
IN YOUR TRANSFORMATIONS!
YOU’RE THE ONE BEING WORN
BY HER KAMUI AROUND HERE.
YOU DIDN’T LEARN A DAMN THING
FROM WEARING JUNKETSU!
AAAAAAH!
I’M SO FRICKIN’ SICK
OF YOUR B. S.
AWW.
WHAT’S THE MATTER?
YOU DON’T LOOK
SO HIGH AND MIGHTY NOW, DO YA?
WE CAN’T HAVE THAT.
LET ME HELP YOU
GET BACK ON YOUR FEET!
FEELING BETTER NOW?
DO YA?
HUH, LADY SATSUKI?
HELL, YOUR FEET AIN’T
EVEN TOUCHING THE GROUND.
YOU’RE JUST
A SAD LITTLE PRINCESS
STANDING ON A SAND CASTLE.
AND I’M A BIG‐ASS WAVE
THAT’S GONNA WASH IT ALL AWAY.
STOP IT, RYUKO!
IT’S TRUE ‐‐ SATSUKI CANNOT
HEAR ME WHEN I SPEAK.
AND OUR SYNCHRONIZATION
IS FLIMSY AT BEST.
BUT OUR HEARTS ARE AS ONE.
ALL WE WANT IS TO BRING YOU
BACK TO YOUR SENSES!
WHATEVER.
CAN YOU IMAGINE THE STRAIN
SHE IS
PUTTING HER BODY THROUGH,
JUST TO ACTIVATE ME
AND FIGHT?
NO OTHER HUMAN
COULD ACCOMPLISH THAT ‐‐
NO ONE
EXCEPT SATSUKI KIRYUIN.
LIKE I GIVE A DAMN.
SHE’S STILL A LOSER!
I HAD ENOUGH OF YOUR B. S.,
TOO, YOU DISHRAG.
SO NOW I’M GONNA
CHOP YOU AND ‐‐
DON’T YOU DARE
MOCK SATSUKI!
HER CASTLE
IS MADE OF STEEL,
AND NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO,
IT WON’T COLLAPSE ‐‐
NOT NOW, NOT EVER!
BUTT THE HELL OUT!
IF YOU CAN’T SEE WHAT SHE’S
GOING THROUGH TO SAVE YOUR ASS,
YOU’RE BLIND!
BUZZ OFF, HUMAN!
YOU THINK THOSE LITTLE KNIVES
ARE GONNA DO ANYTHING TO ME?!
YOU HAVE A POINT.
HE LURED YOU
INTO FIRING RANGE, THOUGH.
[ BEEP ]
THAT WAS DUMB, TOO.
CANNONS CAN’T DO SHIT
TO JUNKETSU.
YOU’RE RIGHT,
BUT THEY GOT YOU CLOSER TO ME!
WHAT THE ‐‐
SAY GOODBYE TO JUNKETSU,
BECAUSE IT’S COMING OFF!
DAMN YOU, SATSUKI!
YOU LITTLE BITCH!
YOU SET ME UP!
INDEED I HAVE!
IN YOUR CURRENT STATE,
SENKETSU AND I
CANNOT DEFEAT YOU.
HOWEVER, IF I UTILIZE
THE ELITE FOUR, IT IS POSSIBLE.
[ GROWLS ]
AW, SNAP!
IT WORKED!
I’LL SAY. SATSUKI SURE KNOWS
HOW TO PLAN AN ATTACK.
I STILL CAN’T
BELIEVE IT.
BUT WHAT’S EVEN MORE SURPRISING
WAS HOW YOU RELAYED
SUCH A COMPLICATED MESSAGE
TO EVERYONE
WITHOUT SCREWING IT UP.
THAT’S ’CAUSE LADY SATSUKI
WROTE IT ALL DOWN ON MY HANDS.
MY GOD.
SHE THOUGHT OF EVERYTHING.
CAN’T BELIEVE YOU’D USE YOURSELF
AS BAIT TO GET ME.
I’LL DO ANYTHING TO WIN.
YOU KNOW THAT.
IT IS MY MODUS OPERANDI,
YOU IDIOT!
AND NOW I’M GONNA PULL YOU
OUT OF JUNKETSU
AND MAKE YOU
COME TO YOUR SENSES!
WHAT THE ‐‐
IT’S NOT WORKING!
SOMETHING’S
JAMMING IT UP!
[ GASPS ]
NO, GAMAGOORI!
RUN!
[ NUI GIGGLES ]
[ GIGGLES ]
GET YOUR HANDS OFF HER.
I GOT THIS ONE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU’RE FUNNY.
YOUR BULLETS
WILL NEVER HIT ME.
YOU HUMANS
SURE LIKE TO WASTE TIME
ON THINGS
THAT DON’T WORK.
AAAAAAAAAAAH!
ANOTHER THING THAT WON’T WORK IS
GETTING RYUKO OUT OF JUNKETSU.
[ GROANING ]
WHY’S THAT?
’CAUSE JUNKETSU’S LIFE FIBERS
ARE CONNECTED TO THE ONES
INSIDE LI’L OL’ RYUKO’S
LI’L OL’ BODY.
THAT’S WHY.
YOU CAN TRY ALL YOU WANT,
BUT IF YOU DO, THEY’LL SNAP,
AND SHE’LL DIE FROM THE SHOCK.
WHAT?!
DAMN YOU.
THE KAMUI’S BEEN STITCHED
ONTO HER BODY?
NO WAY!
THAT IS SO UNFAIR!
TOH!
THIS IS A JOB
FOR MAKO MANKANSHOKU!
HAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
Hououmaru: AS YOU KNOW,
WE RECENTLY ACQUIRED
ALL OF CHINA AND INDIA’S
GARMENT INDUSTRIES.
REVOCS NOW CONTROLS 100%
OF THE GLOBAL GARMENT MARKET.
AND ACCORDING TO OUR DATA,
EVERY HUMAN ON THE PLANET
IS NOW WEARING OUR CLOTHES
IN ONE FORM OR ANOTHER.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANKS TO YOU, LIFE FIBERS HAVE
NOW SPREAD TO ALL OF HUMANITY.
[ AUDIENCE GASPS ]
AND NOW I MUST ASK YOU
TO PERFORM ONE LAST TASK FOR ME.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
Ragyo: AFTER IT ARRIVED ON EARTH
AND GAVE US CLOTHING,
THE PRIMORDIAL LIFE FIBER
WENT INTO HIBERNATION,
WAITING FOR HUMANITY TO REACH
THE PINNACLE OF ITS EVOLUTION.
KEEPING IT SAFE WHILE IT SLEPT
HAS BEEN THE DUTY
OF THE KIRYUIN CLAN.
ONLY THE ELDER OF THE FAMILY
MAY WITNESS ITS AWAKENING.
AND I AM GRATEFUL FOR THE HONOR
OF BEING THE CURRENT ELDER.
TIME HAS GIVEN ME
THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SEE THIS WONDROUS EVENT
WITH MY OWN EYES.
OH, MY GOD!
IT’S HAPPENING!
SOON, THE WORLD WILL BE
THE LIFE FIBERS’.
BEHOLD ‐‐
THE COCOON SPHERE GENESIS.
Kuroido: CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU, KUROIDO.
WOULD YOU AND THE OTHERS
LIKE TO PARTICIPATE?
MAY WE, M’LADY?
OF COURSE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR THE HONOR.
[ GROANS ]
IT FEELS MAGNIFICENT!
WONDERFUL!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
THANK YOU, LADY RAGYO!
TAKE US TO GROUND ZERO.
NO RUSH.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ALL STRAINING ]
CHEW ON SOME OF THIS!
AAAAAAAAAAAAH!
SENKETSU!
NOW YOU’RE DEAD!
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!
I TOTALLY KNOW
WHY YOU’RE MAD, RYUKO! I DO!
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT IT ‐‐
IF YOU CAN’T CHANGE
OUT OF YOUR CLOTHES,
YOU CAN’T JUMP IN THE BATH
AND GET WASHED UP.
AND IF YOU HAVE A DATE
AND YOU WANTED TO WEAR
SOMETHING NICE, YOU COULDN’T.
I KNOW IT SUCKS,
BUT THAT DOESN’T MEAN
IT’S OKAY TO GIVE UP
AND FLIP OUT LIKE THIS!
I GOT NO IDEA
WHAT YOU’RE TALKING ABOUT.
RUN, MANKANSHOKU!
SHE’S NOT THE SAME MATOI
YOU USED TO KNOW!
NO! YOU’RE THE SAME OLD RYUKO
YOU’VE ALWAYS BEEN!
EVEN IF YOU GOT LIFE FIBERS
WIGGLIN’ INSIDE YOU.
AND EVEN IF YOU’RE SUPER‐MAD
YOU’RE NOT HUMAN,
THAT DOESN’T CHANGE
A THING.
YOU’RE STILL RYUKO ‐‐
SAME AS ALWAYS!
YOU STILL GOT SENKETSU,
HE’S STILL YOUR SUNDAY BEST,
AND YOU’RE STILL RYUKO,
DARN IT!
MY GOSH. WHAT A PEST.
MAKO!
MAKO‐O‐O‐O!
UGH!
WAH‐WAH‐WAH‐WAH!
WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU DOING ON ME?
I’M SORRY,
BUT I NEED YOUR BLOOD.
WHATEVER YOU DO,
TRY NOT TO PASS OUT.
I SO HATE IT
WHEN A GIRL GOES AROUND
WEARING CLOTHES
THAT DON’T SUIT HER.
THERE’S A WORD FOR THAT,
YOU KNOW ‐‐ "TRAGIC."
[ SCOFFS ]
BULLETS DON’T WORK, REMEMBER?
AAAAAAAAAAAH!
DOESN’T ANYONE PAY ATTENTION
AROUND HERE?
HELLO?!
YOU HUMANS CAN’T BEAT ME.
PERHAPS, BUT YOU HAVE
YET TO FACE MY WILL!
HONESTLY,
YOU ARE SO STUBBORN.
RYUKO BELONGS
TO LADY RAGYO NOW. GOT IT?
WE’LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
YOU’VE GOTTEN SOFT,
LADY SATSUKI.
YOU’RE TRYING SO HARD
TO GET RYUKO TO COME AROUND.
[ Singsong voice ]
IT’S NEVER GONNA WORK.
I THINK IT WILL.
BECAUSE OF YOU,
I KNOW WE CAN TURN THE TABLES.
BECAUSE OF ME?
THAT’S WHAT I SAID.
YOU SEE, IF RYUKO MATOI HAS
TRULY GONE OVER TO YOUR SIDE,
WHY HAVEN’T YOU GIVEN HER
YOUR BLADE?
[ GASPS ]
IT IS THE ULTIMATE WEAPON
TO FIGHT AGAINST LIFE FIBERS,
IS IT NOT?
WELL,
IF YOU STILL HAVE IT,
THAT MEANS YOU STILL HAVE DOUBTS
ABOUT HER LOYALTIES.
OUR VICTORY LIES
WITHIN THAT UNCERTAINTY.
[ GROWLS ]
THANK YOU.
YOUR AGITATION
PROVES MY THEORY.
WE WILL BE VICTORIOUS!
[ ALL SHOUT ]
WE GOT THIS,
LADY SATSUKI.
YOU GO DEAL WITH MATOI.
YEAH, YOU’RE THE ONLY HOPE
WE GOT.
HAVE AT IT, THEN.
HEY, RYUKO!
YOU CAN’T LET THESE PEOPLE
GET THE UPPER HAND HERE!
THEY’RE WEAK, AND THEY NEED
TO BE TAUGHT A LESSON!
LADY RAGYO WANTS IT!
IN FACT, SHE WANTS YOU
TO KILL SENKETSU
AND THAT LITTLE BOBBLEHEAD,
TOO!
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
[ GASPS ]
MOVE IT.
Senketsu:
STOP THIS, RYUKO!
WHAT?
YOU’RE PROTECTING HER NOW?
I AM. AND I’M TRYING
TO PROTECT YOU, AS WELL.
[ SCOFFS ] ME?
THAT’S RIGHT.
IF YOU KILLED MAKO,
YOU WOULD NEVER BE ABLE
TO LIVE WITH THE GUILT.
AND THAT IS WHY I WILL NOT
LET YOU LAY A HAND ON HER!
WHAT?!
I’M WEARING SENKETSU BECAUSE
YOU’RE ACTING LIKE A BRAT.
SO SNAP OUT OF IT, ’CAUSE
WHAT YOU’RE DOING ISN’T RIGHT!
GO BACK
TO THE WAY YOU WERE!
THE RYUKO I KNOW
WOULD TAKE OFF THAT OUTFIT,
SO HURRY UP
AND TAKE IT OFF!
YOUR VOICE
IS SO DAMN ANNOYING!
MANKANSHOKU! HURRY!
SHOVE SENKETSU
INTO THE WOUND! NOW!
WHAAAAAT?!
SENKETSU, ONCE YOU’RE INSIDE,
USE YOUR POWER
TO SEVER RYUKO’S LIFE FIBERS
FROM JUNKETSU!
RIGHT.
YOU CAN COUNT ON US!
HERE I COME!
I WILL FORCE YOU
TO PUT ME ON AGAIN!
THE POWER OF YOUR SUNDAY BEST
WILL STRAIGHTEN YOU OUT!
WAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ BELLS TOLLING ]
♪ YOU’RE ALONE IN THE RAIN ♪
♪ BEEN THINKING OF YOU ♪
[ POUNDING ON DOOR ]
[ WOOD STRAINING ]
[ CLANK ]
LET’S GO, RYUKO!
YOU’RE COMING BACK HOME
WITH US!
RYUKO!
IF YOU TRY TO RUIN MY HAPPINESS,
I’LL STRAIGHT‐UP KILL YOU!
YOU THINK THIS IS HAPPINESS?!
NOT EVEN!
TAKE A LOOK AROUND YOU!
THIS ISN’T YOU!
SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
SNAP OUT OF IT, RYUKO!
SHUT UP, YOU RAG!
YOU’RE SUCH A DUMMY!
OKAY, FINE!
KILL ME IF YOU WANT!
IF STAYING COOPED UP IN HERE
IS WHAT YOU WANT,
THEN GO ON AND KILL ME
AND QUIT BEING RYUKO, TOO!
♪ OH, GIRL,
HOW CAN I SPEAK WITH YOU? ♪
♪ IF YOU COULD HEAR MY SECRET ♪
♪ NOW I REALLY WANT TO TALK ♪
♪ IT’S A SHAME ♪
♪ OH, DID YOU KNOW ♪
♪ YOU’LL BE STRONGER FOR REAL ♪
RYUKO!!
[ ALL GRUNTING, SCREAMING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
MATOI.
OOPSIES. LOOKS LIKE THEY DIDN’T
GET HER BACK AFTER ALL.
OH, RYUKO?
I HAVE A GREAT IDEA!
LET’S SINK THIS TUGBOAT.
WHAT THE ‐‐
I’M SICK AND TIRED
OF YOUR YAPPING!
NO WAY.
HOW DARE YOU BASTARDS
MAKE ME WEAR THIS?!
RYUKO!
[ Straining ]
GET THIS THING OFF OF ME!
RYUKO! STOP IT!
I WANT IT OFF!
NO, MATOI!
NO, YOU IDIOT!
I WANT IT OFF!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
STOP IT, MATOI!
YOU’LL DIE
IF YOU TEAR IT OFF!
I DON’T CARE!
I’M TAKING IT OFF,
EVEN IF IT KILLS ME!
I GOT TO.
’CAUSE IT’S THE ONLY WAY
I CAN WEAR SENKETSU AGAIN.
Senketsu: SOMEONE ONCE SAID
THAT EACH PERSON’S LIFE
IS LIKE A TAPESTRY.
NOW IT’S TIME
FOR TWO CLASHING TAPESTRIES
TO OVERLAP AND BECOME ONE,
AND THE CATALYST IS CROQUETTES?
NEXT TIME ON "KILL LA KILL,"
"TELL ME HOW YOU FEEL."