[GER COMMANDER] This is
the commander of Zeppelin 3,
The Arthur Seyss-Inquart!
We are losing lift!
All inter-ship communication
systems are out!
Zeppelin 3 is going down!
[GER SOLDIER 1] Zeppelin 2,
The Alfred Rosenburg
is under heavy fire!
[GER SOLDIER 2] We've lost
contact with our ground forces!
[GER SOLDIER 3 7th Brigade
has disappeared from radar...
Communication has been lost!
[GER SOLDIER 4]
What happened?
Were they annihilated?
[GER SOLDIER 5] What the
hell's going on down there?
[GER SOLDIER 5]
Major, sir!
[GER SOLDIER 6]
Your orders sir!
Major please!
We need orders!
[MAJOR]
You're very irritating.
Simmer down gentlemen.
Why don't you shut up,
relax and enjoy
the thrilling climax!
So your subordinates
have been brutally killed.
It's no excuse for wailing
like a bunch of
cornered little virgins...
Captain?
[GER CAPTAIN]
Sir!
Go distribute
firearms and ammunition
to any crewmembers
healthy enough to stand.
If they can't stand,
give them grenades.
But sir,
we don't have
enough guns and
bullets anymore!
Not for the
whole crew!
Then arm them
with pipes,
scraps of metal...
whatever's handy.
Just arm and
assemble my soldiers.
Once that's
taken care of,
we'll begin a full
assault on the enemy.
How about it?
Sound like fun?
We'll charge their
ranks while singing
a jaunty rendition of
"Horst-Wessel-Lied."
[MAJOR]
Oh, that's good.
♪ Zum letzten Mal
wird Sturmalarm geblasen! ♪
♪ Zum Kampfe steh'n
wir alle schon bereit! ♪
Captain...
why aren't you singing?
[grimacing]
I've had enough...
We are not the S.S.!
We are the German Navy!
We have only
followed your orders
in the hopes of
defeating the English Dogs!
But this is not war...
This is madness!
I will not allow any
more of my men to die!
[MAJOR] To come this
far yet still not grasp
the true nature
of this struggle.
So be it.
Insubordination is
the flower of war.
[laughing]
[whimpering]
What can I say?
He's hard to hit!
How you managed
to join the S.S.
is beyond me.
Your aim is as
terrible as ever Major.
Orders sir?
Oh... Shoot him.
Spare us his
defeatist attitude.
Go arm every soldier
on board, Ensign.
Is that understood?
The fate of those
who will not obey
is in your capable hands.
It is time to teach
another lesson of war.
"All who live by the sword,
shall inevitably
die by the sword."
Everything is going
exactly as planned.
By the time they realize their
destinies never left my palm,
my fist will have already
closed in around them.
[SERAS] Master...
[ARUCARD] Who is that?
Who's there?
Oh... of course.
It's me...
[YOUNG VLAD] Lord, I would
not kneel in prayer
for my salvation.
[ARUCARD] Fight!
Fight for the glory
of your God!
God does not help
those who kneel before him.
God does not save
those who pray for mercy.
For those are
not true prayers.
Would you beg in the
presence of your Lord?
Your impiety begs
only for death.
True prayer is
forged in battle.
Dazzle your Lord with your
prayer, and you shall know Him.
You shall know Jerusalem!
After the tearing,
the crushing,
the breaking
of men's bones...
when the fruits of our
prayers lie at our feet...
God will descend
from his throne on high
to bring judgment upon his
wretched and pitiful servants!
Tell me, did your
promises come to pass?
Where's your God?
Where's your kingdom?
[ARUCARD]
What's the matter?
Answer me, King.
Mad King...
They're all dead.
Every last soul dead...
In service to you
and to your promises.
For your prayers.
For your paradise.
For your God...
All were sacrificed.
Enemies and allies...
The people you
swore to protect...
The country you
would rule...
Men, women, old,
and young...
even yourself.
[MAJOR] Irredeemable.
You are truly a monster
beyond all salvation, Count.
[ANDERSON] That doesn't mean
we just give up now, does it?
[SERAS] Master!
[ARUCARD] That voice...
calling to me...
[SERAS] Master!
[ARUCARD] Who is that?
Who's there, calling out?
[SERAS] Master!
[ARUCARD] Oh... of course.
It's you...
Master!
[INTEGRA] It's burning...
His whole world,
is burning away.
[Seras grimacing]
[SERAS] Master!
Master!
[ARUCARD] Stop yelling,
Police Girl.
Why must
you always insist
on making such
an awful racket?
You're liable
to wake the dead.
My Master...
[ARUCARD] Anderson.
There was a moment when
you could have
defeated me...
you had your chance...
As the sun set
on that barren field...
on that fateful evening
over 5 centuries ago...
I would have let
you claim my heart.
But now, your
moment has passed.
[ARUCARD]
You cannot defeat me.
Only a human
can destroy a monster.
could dare hope to.
[growling]
[ARTHUR]
Integra.
There are many immortal
monsters who roam this earth.
When I look at them,
I wonder...
Were they created out
of a desire for immortality?
Many of them desire war.
I've seen them roaming
the bloodiest battlefields.
But in their battle cries
I hear a craving...
I think, they cry
out for death.
Nosferatu: the No-Life King.
His castle, his kingdom,
it's people, his loved ones.
Even his very identity.
Everything was lost.
All that remains
is a pale shadow,
wandering from
battle to battle.
I have come to
believe, Integra,
that those
frightening immortals
are in fact,
frail sobbing children.
[heart beating]
You and I
are the same!
[gasping]
You are me!
I was just the same!
Don't you understand this
is how I became what I am!
[Arucard crying]
[Anderson laughing]
[ANDERSON]
Demons do not cry.
Are these the tears
of a long dead child?
Demons do not cry.
You became a demon
because you couldn't
cry anymore, right?
Humans cry, and when
their tears finally run dry
there's nothing left,
but a demon or a monster...
And one final
prayer for death.
So laugh, demon.
Laugh that arrogant laugh
of yours, and remember:
I beat you to it.
So how long
will it be then?
How long before
you are no longer
cursed to
walk the earth?
[ARUCARD] Until the
weight of my past
is shattered by my
oncoming future...
It shouldn't be
too long, my nemesis.
I'll see you in Hell.
[laughing]
[ANDERSON] Who is that?
The voices of children?
[ANDERSON] I can hear them...
The children...
They're all playing and...
I should go...
They're all waiting.
It's...
Is that really
you Maxwell...?
You mustn't cry,
children...
Say your prayers...
before you sleep...
Amen, children.
Amen.
[WALTER] Amen.
[gasps]
[INTEGRA] Walter!
Is that you?
[WALTER] Trash.
The dead are
nothing but refuse...
And there is no need
for anyone to mourn filth.
Isn't that right...
Integra?
Walter...
Walter, sir!
What have they
done to you?
What have
they done to me?
Obviously I've been
captured, brainwashed,
and turned into a vampire.
Then forced
against my will
to tear my friends and
masters to bloody shreds.
Was that the sort
of explanation
you were
hoping for, Seras?
I answer to no
man's will but my own.
I am myself in
mind, body, and soul:
I am Walter C. Dolnez,
The Angel of Death.
And as the dawn light cuts
through the darkness...
so shall I reap each of
your souls in bloody turn.
[INTEGRA] Walter...
Enough, Walter!
Do not use that name!
[SERAS] Don't!
[YUMIE] I'll kill you!
Kill you! Kill you!
You know nothing of what it
means to serve a master!
Nothing!
[HEINKEL] Shukuji!
[YUMIE] Shimabara
quick-draw attack!
Shoki! You're dead!
[WALTER] You're
the one who's dead...
[Yumie gasps]
Without a scream...
or a single slash...
I've nothing left...
And my world
tumbles to it's end...
[HEINKEL] Yumie!
There's nothing
you can do to stop me.
And no one will stand
in the way of my treasons.
[WALSH] Sir Islands.
[ISLANDS]
Has the Queen
been escorted to one
of the safe houses?
[WALSH] Of course.
And the nuclear submarine
Nereid should be here soon.
If things take a turn
for the worse
we can smuggle her all the
way back to the Americas.
What's London
looking like?
[ISLANDS] Same as
it was, total chaos.
Our last official field
report was from
Sir Penwood if you
can believe it.
Penwood, huh?
[ISLANDS] Yes.
Wonders never cease.
Such an idiot.
I knew all
that bluster
would be
the death of him.
I've known
some fools in my time
But very few
men have raised
foolishness into
an art form.
Damn!
These villains dare
rob us of good men.
They must be made to
answer for all their crimes!
Exactly.
Those undead
Nazi bastards
are going to pay.
And we'll
make them...
Whatever else
that much is certain.
Thanks to
the shock troops
you were so
kind enough
to drop in earlier,
we should
be able to
clear all the vampires
from our outlying bases
within...
lets be generous
and give it
half a day.
It's London
that's the real problem.
As it currently stands,
we're barely holding
our makeshift blockade
around the city.
There's also been
talk that the Queen
and her advisors
are considering
a final,
nuclear solution.
Madness...
Yes.
But three trident
SLBMs from the Nereid
is all it would take
to burn London
to the ground.
But only as a
last resort, obviously.
A nuclear attack
on her own subjects
is unthinkable.
And Her Majesty
still holds faith.
The battle of
London is not over.
Her soldiers still
fight for the capital.
[ISLANDS] Yes...
Arthur's daughter...
Arthur's daughter
still fights.
So, Sir Islands...
Concerning this traitor
at the Round Table...
Back when some
of our junior members
suspected Penwood
you were quite vocal
in your defense of him.
[ISLANDS] I was.
[ISLANDS] He was a fool.
He was also a man of
character and honor.
He would
have rather died
than betray the
Round Table Council.
Then who's
the traitor then?
You and I are all
that's left of the Council.
Is it you?
Or is it me?
[ISLANDS] Oh,
don't be absurd.
If I had turned traitor,
I imagine
I would of filed
a notice with the
main office by now.
There is something
that's been gnawing at me.
When Integra's father,
Arthur, died I gave a warning.
Arthur's younger brother
Richard was dangerous.
He would be willing
to kill Integra
to inherit
the family title.
"Keep your
eyes on Richard.
And don't take
your eyes off Integra."
That was the
warning I gave
to the Hellsing family's
butler, Walter Dolnez.
That night, the attack came,
but where was
Walter Dolnez?
What was he up to?
Arthur understood
the threat Arucard posed,
and took great care
sealing him away in his cell.
But on that
night, Integra,
in a desperate
attempt to flee Richard,
released Arucard...
Becoming the
creature's master.
What if...
that had been
the plan all along?
One could argue
that this was the seed
from which all that
chaos originated.
And if that's true,
when did his betrayal begin?
Ten years ago?
Twenty?
Or perhaps it was
September, 1944.
In Warsaw...
[HEINKEL]
He tore my face...
Why not just kill me?
"Don't interfere"?
Is that what
you're saying?
He took pity on me...
How dare he!
Am I not worthy of
a soldiers respect?!
Have I fallen so low,
that I am not even worth
considering as a threat?
[PRIEST 1] Heinkel!
[PRIEST 2] Heinkel,
are you all right?
[HEINKEL] I'm just fine!
Is Yumie alright?
[PRIEST 2] Yumie ...
I'm afraid uhhh...
[HEINKEL]
No... Yumie...
Dammit! Dammit!
That bastard!
[Heinkel crying]
[HEINKEL] Your gun!
Give me your gun!
[PRIEST 3] You're in
no condition for this!
Do you think I care?
Do you?!
He's dead!
I'm gonna kill
the fucking butler.
Do you understand me?
I'll kill him.
Kill him!
[WALTER] Get up!
Stand and face me Arucard...
lap dog of Hellsing!
[Arucard laughing]
[ARUCARD]
Angel of Death...
Weren't you the one
who said Englishmen
look forward
to growing old?
You've seemed to have
abandoned your maturity.
Truly a
terrible shame.
You were such
a lovely old man
It pains me to
see how retched
and ugly
you've become.
Your body and
soul corrupted.
A dark reaper
to the very core.
[WALTER]
Yes.
This world is after all,
a violent, fleeting dream.
And as the dawn breaks,
I shall be ready
to reap the earth!
Stand and
face me, Arucard!
You know damn well...
that the two
of us are dogs.
We don't bark
unless we're told.
[ARUCARD]
Your orders...
Give me your
orders, Master!
I can kill...
I can slaughter him
without the
slightest hesitation
or hint of regret.
I am a monster
in his cage.
And, you are...
Integra.
My hand holds
the weapon...
My sight finds
the target...
I can chamber
the round...
I can pull back
on the bolt
and I can
release the safety...
But you...
it is your will that
commands the killing.
So what will you do?
What are your orders,
my master...
Integra Fairbrook
Wingates Hellsing!
[MAJOR] Yes yes yes!
Say it, Fraulein!
[DOC] Say it. Yes,
Say it, now!
Just say it!
Say the words.
Integra!
Say it!
Say the words!
Now search and destroy!
Search and destroy!
Servant, You have
your standing orders.
Nothing's changed.
Annihilate all forces
that dare oppose us!
Crush all obstacles that stand
before you and push forward!
Regardless of what it is!
Regardless of who it is!
Destroy...
anyone...
in your way...
[MAJOR] Right there!
Did you all hear that?
She finally said the words!
Yes, My Master.
Excellent!
Just Perfect.
You were a master worthy
of my years of service!
However this
has happened to you
I no longer care.
You're nothing
but my enemy now.
You are Hellsing's enemy.
You are Britain's enemy!
You are nothing
but a traitor.
It is my pleasure
to defeat you.
To destroy you.
[MAJOR] Well said, Integra
Fairbrook Wingates Hellsing!
To think I called
you an amateur!
It appears I owe
you an apology.
At long last, you have
become worthy of this battle.
You are now my lovely,
enormously dangerous
arch-enemy whom I must
defeat at all costs.
[MAJOR] Fate has
dealt our hands.
Now come!
[MAJOR]
I call... your bet.
[SCHRODINGER]
Das Dritte Reich
sagen Sie
herzlich willkommen!
[ARUCARD] Go on...
Go to him
and kill him.
Go put an
end to this.
Yes, It's about time.
Uh-Master?
Go... Now...
Our Master will have
need of you in there...
Help her put an end
to this madman's dream.
This 50 year nightmare...
The dawn approaches...
and I still have my own
bad dream to deal with.
Walter!
I know this
is odd to say
under these
circumstances...
but... well...
Thank you
for everything
you've done for me!
Take care.
You as well.
[INTEGRA]
Come along!
Uh...Yes!
[INTEGRA]
Farewell, Walter!
Farewell, and may
we never meet again.
[SCHRODINGER]
Ladies, Welcome.
[INTEGRA]
Obnoxious Jokers.
I've had enough.
Call your bet indeed...
[ARUCARD]
Remarkable women,
don't you think?
[laughing]
They are mine now.
Mine alone...
My dear Master
to whom I belong...
my darling servant,
mine to mold.
They are lost
to you forever.
Did I make
you angry?
Get angry!
This foolish plot
of yours, ends today!
Eat this!
[WALTER]
You once told me...
Arucard...
That true
Immortals don't exist.
You might be on
to something.
So let's put
it to the test!
Let's keep
killing you
'til you
stay down.
[WALTER]
Really?
[roaring]
The black hound,
of Baskerville.
Learn to heel, mongrel.
So what's next?
What clever
little trick
do you have
for me, Arucard?
Offer some proof
of your worth...
Did you forget
who made
that gun for you?
That gun was meant
to defeat Anderson.
And I'm no Anderson.
[giggles]
[coughing]
[DOC] Oh my...
[MAJOR]
Ah! It's him!
Oh dear, what
was his name?
Eh... that's right!
He's the brother!
[DOC] He's Luke.
Warrant Officer
Luke Valentine.
I recall he was
eaten by the dog.
Now, with the dog dead,
he's able to manifest
himself once more.
[LUKE]
What is this?
What's happened to me?!
What the hell's
going on here?
[screams]
I certainly
didn't expect
to see you again,
Luke Valentine!
Excellent!
One can
always find use
for a spare
Nazi Vampire!
My body...
is starting
to give out...
I prepared for this.
I rebelled knowing
this would happen!
This was always
inevitable...
[Arucard panting]
You're back!
Well aren't you a
tough one to digest.
I always thought you
were nothing but shit...
Walter, you've made
yourself a little puppet.
Adorable.
[coughing]
Not yet...
it's too soon...
I'm not, finished!
I can't die before
I finish killing him!
Just as I thought,
we put him
through the process
too quickly.
It was risky surgery
to begin with.
[MAJOR] Nonsense.
We gave him everything
we had to give.
And in return
for these gifts
We've taken from him
everything of value.
His life, his master,
his honor, his loyalty...
and yet it still
wasn't enough!
He lives
on borrowed time,
and we are his loan sharks,
waiting to collect our interest.
But time grows thin,
and when the rooster crows,
he shall be no more.
We have all invested
the last 50 years
preparing for this fight.
50 years to prepare for
one glorious night
of battle against
the mighty Arucard.
The cards
have been dealt,
and it's all
down to one hand,
winner takes all, and his
opponent holds the Joker.
Show us what you're
made of, Walter C. Dolnez!
[ARUCARD] That was
very good shooting.
Well done,
Luke Valentine!
Your talents were obviously
wasted inside that dog.
And that's Checkmate!
You've broken
my new toy...
Still!
I've got you cornered.
This is it Arucard!
Yes, it's time to put
an end to this dance.
The heart...
it's not over
without the heart...
His heart...
Just his heart!
It's wrong...
No...
It isn't him!
[ARUCARD]
That's right.
Good try though.
Who knew that he
would be so useful?
But it turns out that
dog food will
do in a pinch.
Well come on then,
Angel of Death.
Stand up.
You're not going
to let this all end
with just one punch,
are you kid?
Whatever it is you did
to change
yourself into this,
it doesn't
seem too reliable.
You're not regenerating.
You're just wearing
that body
down to nothing.
So what's the plan then?
I mean, look at you,
you've burned through
the height of your power.
You're not
going to be able
to hold that
form much longer.
So where do
you go from here?
Back to the old man?
Or maybe, you'll slip
further back into childhood?
Hello little Walter.
Haven't seen that
face in 60 years.
[WALLY]
Bastard...
What sort of game
are you playing?
Answer me!
What game
am I playing?
Really?
No, this game
is all yours.
I'm just better at
playing it, foolish child.
The trappings of
mortal forms mean nothing to me.
I explained all of this
to you 60 years ago.
And still you
thought your betrayal
had the slightest
chance of succeeding?
Not a very good
listener, are you?
It hardly matters.
When all is said and done,
this is really nothing more
than a childish squabble.
And since your form now so
perfectly reflects this,
I felt it would be rude
not to follow suit.
It's the nature of battle.
Until you defeat
what cowers you,
you cannot truly
become yourself.
But to do that,
you must break the shackles
that hold you down.
Just as I did.
Just as Anderson,
and even the Major did.
We have all gone through
the metamorphosis
you're experiencing.
From the moment we met
you wanted to fight me.
Otherwise, how could
you ever move forward?
Would you even know how?
Were you afraid
of becoming useless?
of getting old?
Or maybe you were afraid
of being forgotten...
Little John Bull...
Don't make me laugh!
You're the one
playing games.
Look at you!
60 years and in your heart
you're still the same.
Just a scrawny brat!
Now come on...
show me what you got.