All flesh is grass, and
all the comeliness thereof
as the flower of the field.
The grass withereth,
the flower fadeth;
but the word of our
God abideth forever.
Have I been... bested... sir?
Yes, you are bested.
This is not a nightmare
you will be awaking from.
Your castles are plundered.
Your dominion's in ruin.
Your servants destroyed.
And the girl has fled
this place forevermore.
She will never be yours, Count.
You are Judged, and found
wanting, Vampire King.
You have nothing.
You are nothing.
Nothing!
Dreaming...
It was just a dream.
It was nothing.
Well now... The situation
must be impossibly dire,
if you've the gall to convene
a round table conference.
Am I right, Sir Integra?
Yes.
Civilian reports of vampire
attacks on British soil
have been rising steadily
over the past few months.
We can't keep this
quiet for much longer.
There are limits to the
information we can suppress.
What is going on Sir Integra?
We have been conducting
a thorough investigation
into the matter.
And finally we have come across
our first solid
piece of evidence.
Huh?
And what is that
supposed to be?
A transmitter,
perhaps much more.
We've been finding
these microchips
embedded within the vampires.
These chips seem to
relay information regarding
the creatures' physical
and mental state,
movements and altercations.
Good God!
These attacks are not random.
There is someone
creating these vampires.
Controlling them. Moving
towards some unknown purpose.
And that's not all.
It gets worse.
What?
Please, go on.
These are different.
Traditionally, ghouls
come from the corpses
of deflowered men and women once
they have been drained
of blood by a vampire.
But not anymore.
During these last few incidents
not one new vampire
has been created.
Even young boys and girls
who were clearly virgins
have become ghouls
instead of vampires.
Also the traditional
ghouls we've encountered
in the past do not survive
the destruction of their host.
But, during the Badrick
incident Vatican Agent Anderson
claimed to have destroyed the
vampire well before our arrival.
The host vampire had
already been dispatched,
and yet, the
ghouls still walked.
So what does it all mean?
We are at war against a
conspiracy of vampire experts.
and they're displaying
remarkable skill
Gentlemen, the enemy
is just like us.
Walter... what the
hell is that... thing??
That "thing" you're
referring to is a coffin.
I know. Why is there
a coffin in my bedroom.
Oh, it's here on
orders from Sir Integra.
"We can't have a vampire who
doesn't sleep in a coffin".
So there you are.
What have you done with my bed?
I had it disposed of. Of course.
Walter!
Fine, if it helps the
orders were confirmed
by Alucard as well.
Huh? Master?
Yes, Since you're still
refusing to drink blood
like a proper vampire,
you will slowly become weaker.
You must now sleep
in a coffin filled
with the soil of
your birthplace.
This smallest of concessions
is the only way to
keep up your strength.
I take it you're still
feeling uncomfortable
with the situation.
You're an idiot.
Master!
You chose the night.
Once you've turned you're
back on the light of day,
all the sunlight
should ever mean to you
is smoldering pain
and a slow death...
Good evening Alucard,
I have something very special
I was hoping to show to you.
Oh? What is this?
"The Jackal" a custom
13 millimeter
Anti-freak combat pistol.
It fires custom made rounds,
far more powerful than the 454
Casull rounds you're used to.
Thirty-nine centimeters long,
16 kilograms in weight.
Six rounds per magazine.
The Jackal has more firepower
then any human could
be expected to handle.
And the rounds?
Thirteen millimeter
explosive shells.
Casings?
Pure Macedonium silver.
And the tips?
Explosive or mercury?
Mercury tips, and
they're already blessed.
It's perfection, Walter.
I'm pleased that
you're pleased, sir.
I bet this beauty could
even stop father Anderson
dead in his tracks...
Oh my god. Master,
that's amazing!
Ms. Victoria, I believe
I have something special
for you as well...
Huh?
"The Harkonnen" A 30 Millimeter
Anti-freak Cannon.
Designed to be used with
both depleted-uranium shells
and exploding incendiary shells.
This weapon will destroy all
but the most heavily
armored of targets...
W-w-w-w-what the hell is that!
So this dude's friend,
I mean he's like a
real doctor but like,
does the cosmetic shit
on the side, right?
So then that same crazy
fuck with the horn comes back
but now he wants a
plexiglas plate for his skull.
And the Doctor fucking
does it! He makes a window!
You can see the
fucker's brain and shit!
This guy's got a
big monster horn
and his head meat on display!
The guys a freak!
I mean, what the fuck?
Yeah, you get it?
Shut up.
This, stream of drivel pours
from your mouth
before every job.
Can we just this once try
for quiet, focused, and cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
Same old shit.
I know. Fucking-A Bro.
Failure is not an option.
Oh please.
I could pull this job
in my goddamn sleep.
Hey, what are you
two doing here?
These grounds are off limits.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
We're on a sight seeing tour
of famous English estates.
Are you saying this mansion
isn't open to the public?
This is private property.
Please leave at once.
Yes sir.
All right.
Dude's looking kinda queasy.
He could use a nap.
Right then, ciao.
Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
I said hold your fucking fire!
Dude, Bro...
These guys are
complete fucking idiots.
Are you sure about this shit?
Please. This is a test.
An insignificant, ordinary test.
Don't forget the big picture.
His plans are moving forward,
and we are but the smallest
cogs in this great machine...
Fine Whatever.
Now, let's have a little fun.
Listen up maggots!
You know how the plan goes!
You make the kill,
you drink the spill!
And if you run into Alucard
or the Hellsing beyotch...
Don't you quit till
they're dead! Dead! Dead!
Calm down!
What's going on, Sir Integra?
Sir Integra,
this is control room 1!
What happened? Report!
We're under attack.
It's an unknown enemy!
What?
All outside communication
has been cut off!
We're currently exchanging
fire at the front entrance
Hold the line!
Buy as much time as you can!
Yes Ma'am!
Officer? I need
details! How many?
Who are we fighting?
The enemy...
Oh god... they're
enemy are ghouls...
Aim high!
Dammit! Why won't they die?!
Bastards!
Up, up!
Down, down!
Left, right. Left, right!
Bringing the motherfucking
death by Konami!
I am so goddamn hard right now!
An army? A ghoul army?
We... we need to buy time.
First priority
is our evacuation.
Secure a path to the heliport!
Great Scott!
What happened? What was that?
I'm afraid it was
the heliport, sir.
What?
This is a very well
planned attack. Damn.
Sir Integra. We can't hold
this position for much longer.
We're being overrun! It's...
Officer, report!!!
Jesus, it's...
Officer!! Hello!!!
Hello... Is this
thing on? Cool...
This is a message going out
to the round table conference.
And a very personal
and heartfelt shout out
to the queen bitch
herself, Ms. Hellsing!
All right!
You're ass is
currently being kicked,
by the Valentine Brothers!
My name is Jan Valentine,
and I can't wait to meet
each and every one of you.
We'll be getting
intimate as soon as
me and the boys finish lunch.
And let me be the
first to thank you
for providing us all
these tasty smacks.
By tomorrow Hellsing will
be nothing but a pile of shit
You've got no where left
to run and no where to hide.
Cause now I am
coming to kill you.
I wanna see you cry and beg.
In the meantime I highly
recommend pissing yourself,
followed by a course of
praying to your impotent God!
But, hey,
there's still time left
to just be a man
and kill yourself!
Thank you London!
We love you! Good night!
What do you plan to
do about this, Integra?
He said the ghouls have
taken over the estate...
They're coming for us.
What's worse,
we have a security leak.
Damn it, Integra!
What's your position, Walter?
Ms. Victoria's room
in the sub-basement.
I have already been brought
up to speed on the situation.
Outside communications
have been cut off
so I wouldn't expect
reinforcements
for at least
4 hours, maybe five.
In the meantime, our current
forces have been ordered
to defend the conference
room with their lives.
What do you recommend?
Well for starters,
pleases fortify the door
to the conference room.
Since both Alucard and
Ms. Victoria are with me
down in the sub basement,
I propose we divide
into two teams.
Alucard will head upstairs.
Ms. Victoria and I will make our
way towards the conference room.
How will you manage?
The hallway is full of ghouls.
How did you manage to find
Alucard's cell 10 years ago?
The air ducts of course!
Seems to be the best
option at the moment.
We'll both be there
shortly. Good luck.
Walter...
These animals are
eating my people.
Show no mercy. Do not let
them leave the grounds alive!
By you're orders
then, Sir Integra.
Oh, does Walter Dolneas,
the angel of death ride again?
Come on, what are
you two talking about?
You'll see soon enough.
Put the Veteran and
the rookie together
and you may as well
have one normal soldier.
This could actually
end up being fun.
Makes you wonder doesn't it...
If there are any normal people
who work in this bloody place?
Please, be quiet.
What?
Yo Luke, what up?
Can you hear me now?
This is your
brother Jan Valentine,
commander of the army of
the undead Hellsing slayers.
Ah yeah.
Letting you know the first
two floors are secure.
Now all that's left is
to take the third floor,
crash the Round Table
Conference and kick the shit
out of a little girl and
a bunch of old people!
Just stick to the plan.
Don't give them an inch.
I think I'm heading
for the basement.
Well that's enough of that.
Time to see what you
can really do, Alucard.
What the hell's going on?!
They're closing in, and fast.
They've taken the first two
floors as well as the roof.
Escape is impossible.
Just do something!
You're responsible for this!
Sir Penwood!
This is neither the time
nor place for such behavior.
I believe what Sir Integra
is trying to say is
that we must all
be expected to fend
for ourselves when the
time comes. Is that correct?
Yes Sir.
And they're ghouls,
aren't they?
And they're armed too the teeth!
We're all...
We're all going to die!
It's a... It's a bottom?
Are you're all right,
Miss Victoria?
Seras! Walter!
I do apologize for the delay.
Hi!
The manor's defensive forces
have been roundly decimated.
I don't know who armed and
trained these creatures,
but whoever did
is a tactical genius.
They knew exactly how
and where to hit us.
Walter, honestly.
Do you think we're done for?
No. Of course not!
Compared to the sorts
of trouble Van Hellsing
faced a century ago,
I think it's fair to say
this hardly rates as a crisis.
The plan is as
follows, Sir Integra.
Alucard will intercept our
attackers in the sublevels.
Seras and I will
clear this floor.
You're standing orders will
be followed to the letter.
I promise that not one
of these villains will ever
see the light of day again.
Now with your permission Sir,
I believe it's time
I gave these young people
a proper lesson in violence.
Fuck these are
some fine cigars.
Like all bourgeois and shit.
I mean, come on.
That's just fucked up.
People starving in the world
and she's wasting money on this?
A slow and agonizing
death is too good
for that stick-up-her-ass bitch.
I think it time someone gave
her an old fashion
working-class ass kicking.
I know you're in here.
Even when you're hiding,
I can feel your presence.
Why on earth would I hide?
Don't dare mistake
my patience for cowardice.
Honestly I was starting to
get a bit bored waiting for you.
It is a pleasure to make
your acquaintance Alucard.
My name is Luke Valentine.
I'm a really
big fan of your work.
Little Hellsing chicky...
we're coming to find you...
Come on out and
play little Hellsing.
I promise it's gonna
be a lot of fun.
We just want to
torture you, kill you,
maybe skull-fuck your
corpse a couple times.
Burn the house to the ground
go home and masturbate, OK?
Oh dear, did I miss?
I guess I'm not as
spry as I used to be...
My name is Walter Dolneas.
Butler to the Hellsing family.
And former master
vampire hunter.
Fire!
Bit on the slow side,
aren't they?
After all a ghoul
is just a ghoul.
In theory threatening,
certainly tenacious.
But honestly they're
quite a distance
from indestructible
or invincible.
I highly recommend
pissing yourself...
Followed by a course of
praying to your impotent God.
Now that's fucking great...
Cause I gotta tell ya,
plowing thru you people
was really starting to
bore the fuck out of me!
Oh my.
Hut!
Miss Victoria, Now would be
a good time for some support.
Sir! Right!
Huh?
Second volley!
Fire an incendiary-round
with a VT fuse strait
thru the center ranks!
Yes, sir!
Oh fuck you!
Like that, you old fuck?
Ow!!
Die!
I've got him Walter.
Are you alright?
Get off bitch!
I'm supposed to be on top.
Shit this is just
fucking degrading!
I think I'm starting
to feel my age
That is quite an impressive
hold, where did you learn it?
Well, you know I was
a police officer once.
Get the fuck off me!
Fucking vampire slut!
Is this chick the best you got?
No wonder you all went down
like a bunch of pussies!
I'll be asking the questions!
What's the objective
of this attack?
Who are you taking orders from?
Me? I'm just a tourist.
I was passing by, totally
minding my own business,
and I thought I'd have look.
So we cool, dude?
Young man...
the left one's next.
We were following
orders, alright?
We were told to attack
the Hellsing headquarters,
and kill everyone
we found inside.
We supposed to confirm the
deaths of the Round Table,
and your pet vampire.
Hold on. You're not the
only one in charge here.
Who else?
Wow. You're quick.
Right now big brother
Valentine is downstairs
beating Alucard
into a carpet stain!
Your named gets thrown
around quite a bit, Alucard.
The things people say.
They tell stories of
your amazing strength,
how you glide
thru oceans of blood.
They call you
Night-walker. Beyond human.
A monster whose powers radiate
with a darkness that casts
a shadow on darkness itself.
Finally I get to know once
and for all if there's anything
more to you then rumor.
When I was human, I feared you.
The stories anyway.
And when I gave up being human,
when I became this,
I began to admire you.
You... the first great
pioneer of immortality.
No matter what
the rest of us do,
really we're all just
chasing your shadow.
That's ridiculous.
You fool. There's no
such thing as an immortal.
Yes I know.
And once I have
your head on a stick,
everyone else will know too.
So now I get to kill you
and make my wildest
dreams come true.
You've never seen
anything like me before!
I was designed to
surpass you in every way.
I was born to be your death!
Check!
A pistol... did that? Jesus.
Your reflexes are amazing.
I told you I am
completely different
from any creature that
you've ever faced before.
I have the sum total of your
vampiric power at my disposal.
All of it and more!
Me and my brother,
we were designed
with the soul intention
of killing you fucks.
You people are so fucking
dead you don't even know it!
You're in no position
to make threats.
Dude, you must be
going senile Alfred!
And now for our next trick,
check out door number three!
My god what have you done?
It's time to get
this party started!
Stop!!
You made it. Congratulations.
Oh fuck me...
What?
He's not even trying
to dodge the bullets!
Does he think he's
indestructible?!
Everything has a breaking point!
He may act like
he's not injured,
but he's taking far
more damage than I am!
I can beat him!
Yes! Excellent!
I haven't had this
much fun in ages!
What did you say your name was?
It's Luke. Luke Valentine.
Luke Valentine.
It's obvious that
your powers are beyond
even the highest
category of vampire...
Releasing control art
restriction systems
3... 2... 1...
Approval of Situation
A recognized.
Commencing the
Cromwell Invocation.
Ability restrictions
lifted for limited use
until the enemy has
been rendered silent.
Now, Luke Valentine,
it's time to educate you
on how a real vampire
does battle!
What are you?
What in the hell are you?!
Come on! Get up!
Attack me! You've only
suffered the loss of your legs!
Summon up your familiars!
Transform your body!
Heal your severed
legs and stand!
The evening is still so young.
Come on! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Pull yourself together!
The fun has just begun!
Come on! Hurry!
Monster!
So. I see you for
what you really are.
You're pathetic. Nothing but a
useless sniveling lump of meat!
Shut up! You're nothing
but the Hellsing family toy!
A dog for the Church of England!
Not even fit to call himself
a vampire! A puppet of the-
Silence!
I'm a dog?
Then you're dog food.
Was that was really all you had?
Such a shame
I overestimated you.
As a vampire, you were
just a pathetic piece if shit.
Now you're nothing but dog shit.
The one upstairs
didn't seem like much,
but they're having
more trouble with him
than I would have expected...
My men...
They've turned all
my men into ghouls!
Seras!
That's enough! You can stop!
Seras! Please. Stop!
It's all over, boy.
Nice. Come on
kill me limp dick.
Oh, I'm not going to kill you.
Not until after you tell
me who put you up to this.
Then I'll put you
out of your misery.
Are you serious?!
You fucking pussy...
What up, bitch?!
We'll have no more
of that. I'm pissed off.
Who the hell are you people?
What did you hope
to accomplish here?
Who's responsible
for this? Start talking!
Answer!
Come on, bitch!
You know! The ones that
put the fucking chip in me.
The chip that's
sending information
and letting them
know we fucked up.
They can hear us talking.
Every last goddamn word.
And if they know I'm standing
here all fucked up and dying,
about to tell you everything,
you think they're gonna
let me fucking live?
See? I so fucking told you!
Well, since I'm fucked,
how 'bout I piss a little
wisdom on you dipshits?
You can take this clue and
shove it up your ass, bitch!
Beware the Millennium!
That's it? Millennium?
Are you all right, Sir Integra?
Yes, I'm fine. And as for them,
please, put them out
of their misery Walter?
Of course.
Walter, you will
belay that order.
The responsibility must
fall to their leader.
Sir Integra, it's your duty.
No, Sir Islands!
That's going too far!
This entire situation
should have been prevented.
Integra, Your lack of
preparation is an offence.
And since this facility
is under your command,
the responsibility is yours.
The fact that these men
died and were reanimated
as these creatures
is entirely your fault!
How dare you, sir?!
Walter!
I do not ask for
your forgiveness.
This is my burden.
Now, Walter.
See what you can find
out about this "Millennium".
I expect you to work
quickly and thoroughly.
Yes. Of course, sir.
We will see them pay a
thousand fold for this horror.
Out of the 96 members
of the Hellsing Organization's
Headquarters in London,
only 10 are left, 8
of which are only alive
because they were away
at the time of the attack.
Excluding them,
the only survivors
from this ordeal are myself,
and you, Sir Integra.
What about Seras and Alucard?
Aren't you forgetting
about them?
I didn't include them because
they're already dead, Sir.
Yes of course.
Any word yet on "Millennium"?
We solicited the resources
of the British Intelligence
Service, as well as
the National Public Safety
Commission, who went so far
as to rummage through
the unsorted book stacks
at the British Museum.
Internationally, we
discovered seven occult and
military enthusiast
organizations throughout Japan,
France, and the United States,
including a "Star Wars"
related club in Los Angeles.
Star Wars?
The Millennium Falcon... it's
the name of Han Solo's ship.
So what you're telling me
is that we have
no solid leads at all.
My apologies, ma'am.
At this point, the only thing
we know is its definition.
A span of One Thousand Years.
Now that is something...
Yes?
Don't you remember, Walter?
The Empire of the Millennium.
The order that sought the
glory of a 1000-year kingdom
and plunged the entire
planet into a world war.
Hitler's Germany.
The Millennium-order
of the Third Reich.
All is well gentlemen.
The experiment can move ahead.