God... Oh God...
An angel...
An Angel!
They're Angels...
We have come for you!
We are the righteous
soldiers of the Angel of Death!
And tonight the world
below shall know Judgment!
England is guilty!
The heathens, are guilty!
You are all now sentenced...
to your death!!
Death! Death! Death! Death!!
I can offer you my pity...
But forgiveness? Never!
Now, prepare to be
purged from the earth!
Mowed down like grass,
crushed like bugs!
Who knew?
That kid can really put on quite
a show when his heart is in it.
Major... Major,
this is dangerous!
Please, won't you
come back inside?
Doctor, is the
special project ready?
Yes, sir.
It has been prepared precisely
to your specifications.
I should remind you it is
untested, and extremely risky.
Of course doctor, thank you.
This is most splendid news.
Well, it is an
outstanding specimen.
Adequate work Doc.
It's not like you've
done any work, idiot!
I've done plenty of work!
I was watching Zorin at the
Hellsing house and everything!
Oh, yes...?
Achtung! All units, equip
your ultraviolet battlements,
and prepare to muster!
Masks!
Muster the battalion!
Enemies stand to our left,
enemies stand to our right.
Eradicate all who
stand before you!
Execute them all!
Kill them! Destroy!
Major! Do you hear me?
Please, come back inside!
The armor plating
won't hold out for long!
Major, I...
He thinks that it is music.
Music of the battlefield...
The Major... He's conducting it!
The battlefield is his symphony,
and we are his instruments!
Great howling instruments,
wailing his cacophonous notes!!
How could anything
stand against him?
We've found our target!
He's on top of the airship!
What the hell is he doing?
He's crazy! A mad ghost of war!
Major!
Die!
Quick and excellent
work, my butler.
A plan half a
century in the works!
A death's head mark for the
Hellsing's Angel of death!
Didn't they come... to save us?
Die Die Die! Kill them all!
Filthy vermin! Feel the
full force of our wrath!
The power of the Vatican!
The only good Protestant
is a dead Protestant!
You have betrayed us, Maxwell.
Sneak attacks and betrayals
are par for the course in war.
In some circumstances,
I'd even say praise worthy.
Especially against
heathens such as yourself.
However... This...
this is different.
I cannot let this pass.
Maxwell, you have
become enraptured
by your own authority.
Intoxicated by your power.
We are meant to be mere
instruments of a higher power.
I am but a blade
wielded from on high.
A guillotine blade in
the service of God.
But this Maxwell,
what you do tonight is
not in the service of God.
It is in the service of power!
You, Maxwell!
You've turned your back on God!
Father Anderson, you need
to focus on your mission,
you're orders.
Maxwell wants
Sir Integra Hellsing
taken into custody immediately.
I don't like this.
What you like doesn't enter
into it Anderson. Understand?
I still don't like this!
Seras!
Seras Victoria!
You alright Sir Integra?
Any injuries?
I'm adequate.
How's the headquarters?
We were attacked
by enemy soldiers.
We managed to kill them all.
But the Mansion
has been destroyed...
...and Mr. Bernadotte,
he is dead, sir.
Yes, I see...
You drank from
Mr. Bernadotte, didn't you?
You've finally
become a vampire...
Yes, I have.
Stand down.
Even with both of
you power combined,
that girl is way too
much for you to handle.
Seras Victoria the vampire...
I've got to say, you
are starting to become
quite the fearsome creature.
Yes Father, and I'm getting
stronger all the time.
I don't think I'll be afraid
of anything ever again.
It's as if your eyes have become
windows to a bottomless abyss.
It's striking, considering
how human you look otherwise.
I feel it...
He's returning!
This is fantastic.
It all comes crashing down...
There is something
moving up the Thames River.
What is it?
A... ghost ship...
And so it came
to pass that those
who had once gathered before
a painted line of spears,
found themselves reunited
before the real thing.
On one side a division of
panzer grenadier vampires
from Germany's Third Reich,
the dreaded 572 Vampire soldiers
of "The Last Battalion."
On the other side,
2975 Knights of the Roman
Catholic Vatican Curia,
ninth airborne mobile crusade.
In the middle, her Majesty's
Hellsing Organization.
Just three of these
mighty soldiers remain.
All is ready, the players
prepare to take the stage,
and the curtain rises
over this Walpurgis Dawn.
My lord and master,
Integra Hellsing!
Give me your orders!
Alucard, take heed!
Here are your orders!
Your silver gun shall
stain the white army crimson!
Your iron gun shall stain
the black army scarlet!
I would know my foes
by the stains of red
you leave upon their chests!
Now search and destroy!
Search and destroy!
Run them down!
Do not let any of them
leave the island alive!
My master.
It shall be done,
as you command.
Release control
art restriction, zero.
Announce your return!
Say the words and
release your full power!
Now!
I am... the Bird of Hermes...
Here standeth the Bird of
Hermes, eating mine own wings.
It's as if everyone
here can feel it coming.
Something terrible's
about to happen.
If we can't put this monster
down, we may all be doomed!
...to keep myself tame...
Here it comes... I can feel it!
A mighty river...
A river of death!
The dead shall dance...
...and all of hell shall sing!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
No... Stop it...
It's impossible!
How can something
like that exist?!
That is the true face
of the vampire Alucard.
For blood is the currency of
the soul, the vehicle of life.
Blood is the medium by which
life can be transferred.
To drink blood is to take the
essence of a soul into oneself.
You understand the
full ramifications
of this now, don't you, Seras?
Yes.
The Kazan...
and the Yeniçeri forces!
You devoured all of them?
No matter how hard we try,
we're never gonna be
able to kill you are we?
How many people have you
consumed in your time on earth?
How many lost souls
are trapped within you?
Wallachia's... It can't be...
You consumed them...
your own soldiers...
your own subjects!
You're a fiend!
A monster! A devil!
You... Dracula!
Full perimeter defense!
Square up! Close formation!
No! What is this thing
that's been awakened?
It's death!
Death has been awakened!
This is simply magnificent!
Fantastic! I must have one!
Kill it! Everyone open fire!
Open fire!
Fire! Fire! It's a nightmare
down there! It's hell!
We keep shooting,
and it keeps coming!
Our lines are crumbling!
Bishop, please order a withdraw!
We're being slaughtered! Bishop!
Shut! Up! Stop calling me that!
You address me... as Archbishop!
This is hardened tektite
compound reinforced glass!
You wont even be
able to scratch it!
Aa... Aaaaa... nderson!
Anderson!!
We are the soldiers of Iscariot.
We are the instruments
of God's wrath on earth.
Together we march in lockstep
to shatter the dreams of
the unrighteous and unholy.
Goodbye, my friend.
Anderson! Anderson! Anderson!!
Save me, Alexander,
Please! Please sir! Please!
Please sir...
Is this it?
Am I to die here alone?
No...! No...!
I was born alone...
I don't want to die alone!
Jesus...
Teacher... Mr. Anderson...
I will become great.
And once I've done so...
I'll have my revenge,
on all who have wronged me.
You are such a foolish boy.
A stupid, foolish boy...
This is Father Anderson
calling all paladins.
We're returning to the Vatican.
The Ninth Crusade
expeditionary force,
Reconquista, has been
completely destroyed.
Dawn's approaching.
Our dreams are dashed.
We're returning to the Vatican.
Anderson, you're not serious!
It's not your place to die here.
Retreat! Return to the
Vatican. Protect the Pope!
Protect the Church
till the end days.
As for me, I'm going
to be staying behind.
I will find Alucard,
and I will defeat him!
Anderson! What do you
think is going to happen
if you fight him?
It doesn't matter.
It's now or never.
Finally, Alucard has unlocked
the last of the restraints
upon his power.
He's finally in a form
I may be able to do damage to.
The last of his demonic powers
have finally been laid bare.
He has dispatched all the
warriors from his stronghold.
Right now, the lord of
the manor... stands alone!
For the first time, I can face
a single vampire in combat.
Dracula stands alone!
This- All this was
the sole objective
of that mad battalion commander.
It was a giant
sacrifice designed
to make Alucard vulnerable.
A thousand SS soldiers,
three thousand crusaders,
a million British citizens, all
of them, friend and foe alike...
And finally,
he knew I'd be here.
Farewell, gentlemen!
Do not weep for Maxwell,
the poor hopeless fool!
He died as he lived,
a spineless coward.
Farewell, and may
we meet again in Limbo.
Anderson!
Father Anderson!
My Count... You have returned.
At your pleasure, my Lady.
Hi!
it's really nice to
have you back, Master...
Um, you seem to have
grown a mustache, Master...
A moustache...
Yes Seras...
My Seras Victoria...
Nicely done, my nemesis.
I am a servant of God; an agent
of divine punishment on earth.
I am called upon to cut
away the flesh of infidels.
And remove from the earth,
all those who would defy God!
Amen!!!!
You've become a
formidable warrior.
I'm impressed.
Ready for more?
Yes... bring me more...
try to pierce my heart
with your Bayonets.
500 years ago...
100 years ago...
Now you come back to challenge
me and awaken me again...
My beloved nemesis...
Don't even need to ask!
Pure silver,
macedonium-processed
mercury ammunition--
-in Marvels NNA9 cartridges.
39cm long, weighing 16kg, with
13mm armor-piercing rounds--
The Jackal!
This weapon is perfect, Walter!
Now what? What will you do?
Your Dragon stands
before you, Catholic!
You're going to
defeat me, is that right?
What do you think
your chances are?
One in a hundred?
One in a thousand?
In ten thousand? A million?
A billion maybe?
I am more than
prepared to destroy you,
you monster, no matter what
the odds are against me!
Contact with Nordland
Platoon has been lost!
Respond, Dummbatz!
Communiqué from
the aerial cruiser!
The Bürgerbräukeller
is out of ammunition!
Nobody is responding!
Oh butler, mix me up
some Verhoeden cocoa
and bring it right away,
and don't hold back on
the cream and sugar!
London has been destroyed.
The Crusaders have all perished,
and the Last Battalion
is dying in the streets.
Alucard is down there...
And I sit up here...
It's perfection. Everything
is proceeding just as I planned.
What's the matter, Christian?
Your dragon is waiting.
You are bruised and bleeding.
Your arm is hanging by
a few strands of meat...
What are you going to do?
Will you die like a dog?
Or on your feet like a man?
What does it matter, vampire?
You think a cut on
my arm will stop me?
Now shut up, and come at me.
Come on, fight me! Hurry! Hurry!
Exellent...
Humans are such
fascinating creatures.
Exploding chain!
I want more!
More! More! More! More!
What kind of man is this?
He reminds me...
so much of those other men.
Yes. Come to me,
Alexander Anderson!
Like those other men
in that far distant time,
come and stand before my gaze.
And as that man did long ago,
try and run me thru
and pierce my heart!
Out of my way!
Damn it, I said leave!
You stupid, meddling idiots!
And what did you
expect us to do?
Just pack everything up and
run back to the Vatican?
What sad sort of
thing would that make us?
Because, none of us would be
soldiers of Iscariot anymore!
"By the cry amen and the
slaughter of the unworthy,
the world slippeth
back into place."
Those are the words
you taught us, aren't they?!
Did you think we would
abandon our righteousness?
You are the idiot!
You are such a fool!
I just wanted someone to survive
and carry on with our work!
Too many have
gone to Limbo today!
But since I'm charging
full speed into hell,
I might as well
have some company.
Guess we're gonna
do this together then!
Let's tell them who we are!
We are the soldiers of Iscariot!
We are Judas Iscariot!
Countless little lives,
struggle and writhe together...
Like tiny cells making
up a great beast,
struggling towards
it's own illumination.
Seeking blood
whilst spilling blood
continuously
multiplying and receding,
fighting against itself,
without end.
Whether they seek
that enlightenment thru
their faith in a "God,"
or in the name of "Nazism,"
Or even in the creature
called Alucard,...
We are all now united
by the same thing!
It's a dream come true
isn't it, my dark brethrens...
Till death!
Now!
Go to hell!
Amen!
You stand before me.
I'm impressed...
I'm impressed, Iscariot.
Show me more,
Alexander Anderson!
You are not the only one
who carries a mighty
weapon, vampire.
So Is this the toy
that's going to defeat me?
A nail?
The Shroud of Turin...
the Holy Grail...
the Lance of Longinus...
Should I assume that
you're threatening me
with the last of the
holy artifacts of Rome?
Oh Yes...
It still smells of blood and
miracle. The Nail of Helena!
Prepare!!
Anderson! Stop it!
Do you know what that
thing will do to you?
You'll become one
of God's monsters!
Maintain your humanity!
Don't succumb to power!
Either side, it amounts
to the same deal.
Whether in the name of
the divine or demonic,
you're still a
monster in the end.
Do you intend to use
that scrap of miracle
to become nothing but a
scrap of miracle yourself?
This duel... between us...
would you really
push it this far?
Into the realms that
lie beyond mortal life?
A monster such as myself...
A creature of such
weakness that I could not
bear the weight
of a human life...
If I am to be defeated
it must be by a human.
Don't do it, human.
Don't become a monster...
A monster like me.
I want nothing more
than to be a bayonet.
A bayonet wielded
by the hand of God.
I would have been happy
to have been born a storm,
or a divine threat,
a mighty explosion,
or even a terrible hurricane.
A divine force of nature
without a heart or pity.
And if this relic
could transform me
into such a thing...
Then I am happy to
abandon my humanity.
Y-You fool...
You bloody fool!
It's thorns... All thorns...!
Anderson... What in God's name
have you done to yourself?!
His body is no
longer that of a man's.
The only way either of
us may return to dust,
is to have it gouged out of us--
...the sickness in our hearts.
Father Anderson!
Anderson!
Father Alexander Anderson
was no longer man,
nor demon;
neither day, nor night.
Master!
Ah, Michiko. Guess what?
Daddy's gonna be the
big boss of England again!
Hey, nice ass on that one!
Oh, yeah... that's me!
I'm the sort of serious guy
who was born to be
in charge of this world.
And Daddy's got
the balls of brass
that'll help get the job done!
And you know, if
there's anything I can do
to help you out,
you just say the word.
What, you think there's anyone
in Europe who's bigger than me?
Oh, you're pressing
your luck, pal!
That's enough out
of you, you punk!
Now, come here little one...