The despicable, smug little
smirk he wore on his face.
That dreadful laugh, his cheeks
puffing up for every cackle.
He looked nothing like any
Nazi SS officer I'd ever seen.
But at the time,
back in 1941, you,
as a member of the Vatican's
European General Directorate,
collaborated with this
man and his organization.
He was accountable
to no one but the Furher.
You must understand, we were
forced into collaborating.
Yes, of course you were.
And so they set
their plans into motion.
Their methods and desires
are ingrained in my
memory, my Master.
Well done, Alucard.
Her Majesty herself has called
for a gathering of
the round table.
Really? The Queen?
Return at once to
make your report.
Do not keep her waiting.
I'm on my way.
Integra... Did you enjoy
the thrill of declaring war?
Did you feel your blood rush?
The warmth of hell's fires as
you ordered the slaughter?
Don't speak to me, you monster!
Now return immediately! Damn it!
What the hell is this, Major?
There's simply no way
I can tell you that, Colonel.
My orders are top secret, issued
personally by the late Führer.
Don't you dare take
that attitude with me!!
Why won't you turn us
into vampires? Why? Why!!!
Answer me you miserable swine!
That's enough back
talk from you, Colonel.
One more childish outburst and
I'll blow your fucking head off.
Major? What is this?
What task could be so great,
that it would require an
army of 1000 vampires?
The pudgy creature
spoke with a mad authority.
He was a man ready to command
the legions of Hell itself.
I intend to imbibe upon
the infinite pleasure of war.
And so I shall
bring forth another.
And another war,
and again, and again.
This man's plans.
They called for the
creation of many vampires...
The Führers secret
"Last Battalion". How simple.
But you did more then
help fund the operation,
and you were more
than a mere pawn.
The title more suited to you
my friend, is collaborator.
You were forced to
cooperate? Ridiculous.
You asked him to turn you
into a vampire, didn't you?
It wasn't just me!
All of us! All of us
were forced to helped him!
They tricked me!
Help me, Maxwell!
Please, I'm begging you.
No. No way. It won't work.
It's impossible.
But getting home will
take an extra week by boat.
Private jet is out
of the question.
And we can't leave his
big box here, can we?
Within this "box" is
my own true kingdom.
It is where I was born,
and where I will die.
I've had enough! Anderson!
The Vatican has a small private
jet 13 kilometers north of here.
There's your release paper.
Our people are expecting you.
So take it and get
the hell out of here
before I decide to
decapitate you again.
Amen.
We have returned
to you, my Master.
Well executed, my servant.
The Queen awaits you.
Remove your glasses.
It's been a very
long time, Vampire.
Come closer, let me look at you.
All these years, and you
haven't aged a day, Alucard.
Unfortunately, time's march
has not been as kind to me.
Can you believe how quickly
I became an old woman?
I still see the same
spirited young woman
I met 50 years ago,
your majesty.
In fact, to my eyes,
time has made you
even more beautiful,
your highness.
Proceed with
your report, Vampire.
Fifty-five years ago,
a deranged Nazi Major,
attempted to breed
a vampire army.
Walter and I laid
waste to their operation.
However, it seems they
simply refuse to die.
They've returned,
replenished their numbers,
and are ready to complete
their original mission.
That's what Millennium
truly is. The "Last Battalion".
I guess Mr. Tubalcain's filthy
blood must have given us away.
The Major sure blew that one.
Woah there.
I'm just the messenger.
I'm not here to fight anyone.
Explain this.
My deepest apologies ma'am.
I don't know how he
got past secrurity.
They are useless against me.
I'm everywhere, and nowhere.
He's only a child.
What is Millennium?
What are they after?
Stop it.
Guten tag.
To the gathered representatives
of the Vatican
and Great Britain.
My commanding officer,
the glorious Major,
has a message for all of you.
Please attend carefully.
Uh... Oh...
What's going on?
There's no picture.
Major, stop this!
For god's sake please don't.
Warrant Officer Schrödinger,
the screen is not working!
Oh, hold on...
right there. That's good.
Help! Please help!
Please someone, you must-
Major, Looks like you've
really got your hands full.
No...Things are going well.
It feels as if a great weight
has finally been lifted
from my shoulders.
I'm feeling great, in fact.
Hello, Major.
Alucard, I'm so happy
to see you again.
It's really been far too long.
What is it that you want?
Oh, finally face to face
with the Fraulein herself,
Sir Integra Hellsing.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
What's the purpose of this?
What are you trying to
accomplish? Answer me!
The purpose?
What a silly question,
my beautiful Fräulein.
"Purpose"... how quaint.
To put it in the simplest
terms possible, Fräulein,
our purpose is a
total absence of purpose.
You should be aware, Fräulein,
that there are some
people in this world,
certain irredeemable louts,
for whom the means
does not require an end.
I speak of course, of myself.
Be sure to eat every bite.
If he turns into a ghoul,
I will not be happy. No no...
Oh, wow! I didn't
think you're decision
would be that harsh, Major.
You've insane. All of you.
Did I just hear someone
from the Iscariot organization
questioning my sanity?
Then let me ask you,
if your God would allow
my madness to
flourish across the globe...
Then wouldn't it seem to
you that any God like that
would be just as mad as I?
We are the finest
of the Third Reich.
Do you have any idea how
many people we've killed?
I'm insane? What foolishness.
You didn't have any
objections fifty years ago.
But never mind that.
Try to stop me then, you
self-proclaimed "normal" people.
But unfortunately,
Iscariot is not my true enemy.
My true enemy is Britain,
the Hellsing's...
Well, really it's
that man laughing
in the corner back there.
A declaration of war.
Exellent. I can't wait
to destroy you again!
No matter what you do,
we will never give up.
We will reverse
this ridiculous situation
as many times as we have to.
Alucard, Seras, kill him.
Fine, Shoot the messenger
if this is what you've come to.
Auf wiedersehen mein Fräulein.
I look forward to meeting
you across the battlefield.
Alucard, Sir Hellsing...
Destroy them.
You have your orders.
At last Major, we have our
audience's undivided attention.
Doctor, Captain,
once I start my dance
I dance to the bitter end.
Enjoy it to the
fullest, Major...
You're so slow!
In the time it took you to
walk down one little hallway,
I went all the way to London,
got my head blown off,
and made it back.
Perhaps you should
start thinking about
going on a diet, mein Major.
Oh I could never do that.
Show some respect warrant
Officer Schrödinger.
It's all right, Doctor.
My Warrant Officer has
succeeded in his mission.
Prepare for launch!
Engaging flaps!
Deus Ex Machina,
Commence launch!
This is a message
from the Commander of the
Last Battalion to all ships.
We are headed for
the heart of England,
to once again dominate
the skies of London.
Send up the beacon!
Our signal fire of defiance,
announcing our grand return
to this mortal world.
♪ Heute wollen wir
ein Liedlein singen, ♪
♪ Trinken wollen wir
den kühlen Wein ♪
♪ Und die Gläser
sollen dazu klingen, ♪
♪ Denn es muß,
es muß geschieden sein. ♪
♪ Gib' mir deine Hand, ♪
♪ deine weiße Hand, ♪
♪ Leb' wohl, mein Schatz, ♪
♪ leb' wohl mein Schatz, ♪
♪ Leb' wohl, lebe wohl ♪
♪ Denn wir fahren, ♪
♪ denn wir fahren, ♪
♪ Denn wir fahren gegen
Engeland, Engeland. ♪
And so I have
acquired a pretty ship.
Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Sailor.
My bullet punishes
all without distinction.
Welcome aboard the Eagle Ma'am.
Everything is in order.
This ship and it's crew
are at Mellinium's disposal.
How does it feel,
My newly minted Captain?
To become a vampire, lead
a mutiny, murder your crew,
and commit high
treason all in one night?
I see.
How about condemning
your shipmates to hell,
doomed to walk the earth
as ghoulish rotting corpses?
What was that like?
Well...
Excellent work!
This is really amazing!
Millennium is happy to have to
go-getters like you on our team!
We couldn't have
done it without you!
and of course the Major!
He's so proud!
You definitely deserve
everything that's coming to you!
Well, I guess the only
thing left for you to do,
you dirty limey, is die.
The bitch set us up!
No... I only heard one shot.
That's impossible...
It can't be!
I'm the Huntress,
Rip Van Winkle.
Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Sailor,
my bullet punishes
all without distinction.
Whore!!
Silly creature.
First Lieutenant.
Oh, you're up.
I ran out of paint
before I could finish,
so I had to improvise.
It was a bit drab up here,
so I though I should properly
christen our new ship.
Much more homey don't you think?
The German Third Reich's
Atlantic Naval Fleet
Flagship Adler...
is now commencing operations!
We keep killing them, and
they just keep coming back.
You have to at least give them
credit for their persistence.
Let them return as
many times as they please,
we'll just keep killing them.
It's that simple.
At least it's not just
the two of us anymore.
Nice to have a
new piece on the board.
Actually, I've been
meaning to ask you.
Yes?
Why did you turn
Seras into a vampire?
It just seems so
out of character.
You understand my concerns.
It wasn't my decision,
it was her's.
Have you met her family yet?
No. She's orphaned.
Of course she is.
Beneath that girlish
exterior lies a fascinating
and complicated creature.
Abandoned to a town of death.
Her coworkers transformed into
hungry, mocking visages of evil.
A sadistic vampire
hunting her down
with the intention
to rape and kill her.
It was as close to hell
as any mortal could imagine.
And what does she do?
What fate did she choose?
Giving up is what kills people.
Those who refuse to give up
are entitled their time
to trample upon the weak.
So now you're just waiting
for her to drink blood,
is that right?
Give it time. She'll drink.
Eventually, she'll drink.
Why do you refuse
to drink blood?
You're not human anymore.
It's time to accept it, Seras.
But, I...
But, Sir Integra!
I cut my finger.
I don't want it to get
infected. Kiss it for me.
I just...
Do it. That's an order.
Good, Just be careful
not to bite Seras.
There, a few drops
of pure virgin blood.
Do you feel any better?
Ohh...Yes... thank you.
Now gear up and
be ready for deployment.
We've lost contact with
the aircraft carrier "Eagle".
We're assuming it's Millennium.
Sir! Yes.
Yes sir. We're
bleeding information
to them like stuck pig.
The vampires have
had their agents try
to ambush me 4 times
since I got here.
They have informants
all across the world.
South America,
Great Britain, the Vatican.
They probably even
have an informant
it the round table conference.
Just stay alert Anderson,
and do not underestimate the
resourcefulness of this scum.
So now, the question
we have to ask ourselves
is: What is Mellenium's
next move going to be?
They have their
sights set on England.
Imagine that. It's
all turned out just
as you thought
it would, Maxwell.
You must be pleased.
Quite pleased.
And yet, there's something
distasteful about the situation
Then maybe you should
have shown a little backbone.
The pudgy little
maggot dared to call
our lord in heaven a madman!
He's not the least bit
interested in us.
He's focusing all his attention
on Hellsing and Alucard.
With that in mind
I thought actions
would speak louder then words.
Ah. I see. You're going to
prepare a surprise attack.
Exactly. When the
dust has settled,
we will be the ones
standing in the ring
with our fists raised high.
His Holiness, the Pope issued
the mobilization
order some time ago.
He's transferred control
over the Knights of Malta,
the Knights of St. Steven,
the Military Order of
Calatrava la Nueva,
the Knights of the
Sagely Brethren,
and the Swiss Company
executive office to me.
The Vatican's Administration
of Holy Relics
3rd Division, Mathew,
has also gone into action.
Specialized anti-vampire
tactical armaments
are being prepared as we speak.
This almost feels
like a Crusade.
Yes. Exactly like a Crusade.
Only this time
we do not face Allah.
This time we hunt a war god.
This time, We! Face! Mars!
Destroy castle after castle.
Pillage town after town.
We will use their mangled
corpses and build monuments
to the price of such insolence.
You are the instrument
of divine will, Anderson.
Return to headquarters by
whatever means you see fit.
Yes sir.
In the name of the
Father and the Holy Spirit.
Amen!
Mars!
Mars...
All right you bastards.
It's time you had a
taste of divine punishment.
Just thirty-six hours
and fifteen minutes.
Oh, I can't wait!
I just can't wait!
We lost communication
with the Aircraft Carrier
"Eagle" 18 hours ago.
She's currently anchored
approximately 300 kilometers off
the coast of Polinton Bay.
We've confirmed
she's flying their colors.
Millennium.
That's why I called you.
The situation has moved
far outside the
Royal Navy's jurisdiction.
What's the status?
Go on.
Sir.
As the General said,
we've lost contact.
The Eagle has ignored
all emergency hails.
However, Satellite
photos have revaeled
not only the Nazi emblem,
but the presence
of a lone individual on
deck, holding a parasol.
Two SAS platoons are
currently approaching
the Eagle via helicopter, in
order to asses out the situation
and hopefully bring
this to a resolution.
General...
Yes sir?
Those men are defenseless
against what's out there.
Cancel the operation and order
them to return immediately.
Both helicopters
have been shot down!
Did the Eagle open fire on them?
No sir. Someone fired
at them from the deck.
They reported a
single musket shot.
That's ridiculous!
I'm getting confirmation...
What will you do, Sir Integra?
We're under direct orders
from her Royal Highness.
We've determined this incident
to be the work of vampires
and will be assuming
operational jurisdiction.
What?
There you are Sir Penwood.
Anything to add?
No Ma'am.
Good hunting, Sir Integra.
I'm handing over
control of this operation
to the Hellsing Organization.
Good.
They aren't
launching any attacks
but they do open fire
when we approach.
It's textbook, Ma'am.
They're trying to lure us in.
That ship is literally
a floating fortress.
I don't suppose we could
just ignore the damn thing...
How do we deal with
a ship full of ghouls?
Moving vampires across large
bodies of water is problematic.
The situation hiders their
movements and ours as well.
So what do we do
with our vampires?
We could try sending them
on our own battleship.
Would that work?
No. Between the
preparation and the voyage,
it would take far too long
and we can't count
on them to stay put.
Perhaps a faster vessel?
Walter,
they have high caliber
anti-aircraft and Gatling guns.
A speed boat would be
lost in a hail of bullets.
What about dropping
them in from above?
No. The eagle is well stocked
with anti-aircraft ordinance,
we couldn't get a
plane anywhere near.
Perhaps an airplane
with a lot of decoy chaff.
No. They still won't fool
those damn magic bullets.
What you're saying is, against
their stockpiles of missiles
and magic bullets, your
only hope is to find a way
to get me onto the flight deck
of that ship. Isn't that right?
It may not be possible.
Wait... It's brilliant.
I know an aircraft that
can get you on board.
However, I think there may
be only one in existence.
♪ Mein Sohn, nur Murth! ♪
♪ wer Gott vertraut,
baut gut! ♪
♪ Jetzt auf! in
Bergen und Klüften ♪
♪ tobt morgen
der freudige Krieg ♪
♪ Das Wild in
Fluren und Triften ♪
What's she singing?
It's Weber's Der Freischütz.
It's her favorite.
♪ ist unser und
unser der Sieg! ♪
♪ und un-ser der Sieg,
und un-ser der Sieg! ♪
What is happening?
It's him... Please no... God!
There's something
coming, on radar.
It's not possible...
it's speed is Mach 2.8.
Altitude, 85,000!
That high? What is it?
SR71. it's just a
reconnaissance craft.
It's him!
Report! First Lieutenant,
what do you see out there?
It's him! It's the Madness.
I hear him... He's come for me!
He charges his prey upon
a steed of black iron,
the stench of death
left standing in his wake.
Sitr, he's diving!
My god... He's going to ram us.
Engines to full!
Evasive maneuvers!
Get us out of the way!
Fire the guns!
I hear a voice calling me...
I hear a voice, he says
he's coming for me...
Cromwell restrictions,
3, 2, 1, released.
Soon, the light
of day will be lost.
Fate has brought you to this.
Goodbye. How sad
the hunters spirit,
for my heart will
not cease to tremble.
First Lieutenant Rip Van Winkle,
do you know how
Der Freischütz ends?
Kaspar, having trifled with
the Black Huntsman, Zamiel,
is whisked away
to hell for his sins.
His corpse is then thrown
into the bottom of a ravine,
to be eaten by wolves.
Prepare yourself,
First Lieutenant.
For now Zamiel
comes to collect you.
Those who dare
impersonate the dead
are judged to join their ranks!
Kill it!
We have to hold
out a while longer!
It still isn't time yet!
It's a monster!
Shoot! Shoot till you're empty!
Die Granate!
Throw the grenades!
Oh my God!
What in the hell are you?
Prepare yourself,
First Lieutenant.
What will you do in
the presence of Zamiel?
What will you do...
...Rip Van Winkle?
Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Sailor,
my bullet punishes all...
without distinction.
Again!
Again! Again!
Now die and go to hell!
Guess what I just caught.
I just caught you.
Rip, Van, Winkle...
Well done, First Lieutenant.
The operation was a success.
No matter how many
stones you cast upon
the water's surface,
no matter how many times
you stomp your boots
upon the creeping shadows,
they will never
submit to your will.
That is the river of death.
Life and death, when viewed
with the proper perspective,
are really just one big hoax.
Immortal, invincible,
undefeated, and almighty.
It's ludicrous.
But we can cast light
upon the shadow.
We can and will
find the tide changing.
Through your sacrifice we will
bring Alucard to submission.
Wait.
Let's not be too hasty
with our options, Doctor.
She fulfilled her mission.
Absolutely perfectly.
She deserves
to have a hunter's death.
How generous Major.
Achtung. Auf Wiedersehen.
I'll see you in Valhalla,
First Lieutenant.
Auf Wiedersehen.
Auf Wiedersehen, Frau Winkle.
Sieg Heil.
Are you having fun, Alucard?
War should be fun, after all.
So sing the
battle hymn, Alucard.
And watch as my works unfold.
I can see it.
I can see it even
through thick spectacles...
The city's lights...
Its Hawksmoore steeples...
Hear my battle hymn, Alucard.
And watch the collapse
of the British Empire.
My friends, It has often
been said that I like war.
My friends... I like war.
No. My friends... I love war.
I love holocausts.
I love Blitzkreigs.
I love defensive lines.
I love sieges, charges.
I love mop-up
operations and retreats.
Wars across prairies,
in streets, in trenches,
on grasslands, in frozen
tundra, through deserts,
on the sea, in the air...
I love every act of war that
can occur upon this earth.
I love blasting the
enemy to smithereens
with artillery salvos
that thunder across
the lines of battle.
My heart leaps with
joy whenever a soldier
is tossed high into the
air and cut to pieces
by well placed sniper rounds!
and there is nothing
like a tank operator
using a Tiegel Acht-acht
to destroy enemy tanks.
And the feeling that comes
when a soldier runs screaming
from his blazing tank,
only to be mowed down
by heavy machine gun fire,
is such an exquisite feeling.
Like when ranks of infantry
brandish their bayonets
rushing into the enemy lines.
It moves me deep
within my heart to watch,
a fresh recruit stabbing over
and over into the bloated chest
of a long dead enemy.
The sight of deserters
being strung up
from a street lamp is
an irresistible pleasure.
And there is nothing more
arousing, then the sounds
made by prisoners of
war dropping like flies,
screaming in agony
as they're mowed down
by ear-piercing Schmeissers.
When a band of pitiful
resistance fighters make
their final stand with
nothing but small arms
only to have their city
smashed to atoms block by block
by 4.8 ton bombshells,
I am in ecstasy.
I love it when
my forces are ravaged
by a Russian armored division.
It's so sad to see
towns and villages
that were supposed to
be defended at all costs
being laid to waste, their women
and children
being raped and killed.
I love to be
squashed under the heel
of the British and
American War Machine.
Oh the humiliation as my men
crawl around like vermin,
ducking the Jagdbomers
flying overhead.
Gentlemen,
all I ask for is war...
War so grand as to
make Hell itself tremble.
Gentlemen... I ask you
as fellow brothers in arms
what is that you really want?
Do you wish for
further war as I do?
Do you wish for a
merciless fucking war?
A war whose fury is built with
iron and lightning and fire?
Do you ask for war to
sweep in like a tempest,
leaving not even ravens
to scavenge from the earth?
Krieg! Krieg! Krieg! Krieg!
Very well.
Then krieg is
what you shall have.
We are a clenched fist,
ready to strike down all
who oppose us with our might.
But, after enduring over
half a century wallowing
in the darkness, for us,
a simple, ordinary war
will no longer be sufficient.
We need a massive war!
A war beyond any other that
man's history has ever known!
We are but a single battalion...
The remnants of a
defeated army numbering
less than a thousand strong.
However, I believe that
each of you old warriors
is equal to a thousand of
their sickly soft children.
We represent a force
that could easily defeat
an army of one million
and one men.
It is time for them to awake,
the ones who sent us
screaming into oblivion
and who now lie sleeping.
Let's drag them out
of bed by the hair,
and remind them of what we are!
We will remind them of what
it feels like to live in fear.
We will remind them of
the sound our jack boots
make against their throats!
We will remind them
that there are more things
between heaven and hell then are
dreamt of in their philosophy.
Ja Europe! We see
the light of Europe!
Our Kampfgruppe of
one thousand vampires
is going to burn this
world down to ash.
Yes my friends. Soon
Europe's charred remains
will illuminate the night sky!
I have brought you all back
just as I promised I would!
Back to our
favorite battlefield!
Back to our beloved war!
Major!
Sturmbannfuhrer!
Battalion Commander!
Major!
Sturmbannfuhrer!
Battalion Commander!
Major!
Sturmbannfuhrer!
At last, the sea lion
has crossed the ocean
and is heading up the hill!
Attention all soldiers of
the Millennium Battalion,
this is a message
from your commander.
Friends...
...let's bring them hell.