Alucard... Hey,
wake up, Alucard...
And who the hell are
you supposed to be?
I'm the spirit of your gun.
You can call me
Jackal... Willis.
Come on! Don't shoot the Willis!
Stop it, just hear
the Willis out!
This is ridiculous.
I'm going to leave now.
You think you can just leave?
Man, you're living in
the Willis-space now.
And one does not simply
leave Willis-space, my man.
You're gonna spend the rest of
your life in the Willis-space,
making cameo's in
various productions,
regardless of their
entertainment value.
And another thing, stop saying
I weigh 10 kilo's, already!
Get, it, right! The Jackal
weighs 16 Kilo's, my man.
Really...
The two of us will
have a savage pedal
to the metal burn
through Nakatomi Plaza...
Or you can help me
rescue Ving Rhames
from getting sodomized wielding
nothing but a samurai sword!
You, me, and Steve
Buscemi will sweep
the Golden Raspberries by going
into space to blow up a meteor!
Along the way we're
going to get jerked around
by a kid with a weird
name who can see ghosts,
and after that we're going
to roll our taxi trying
to catch Milla Jovovich...
That was a close call.
You let that impostor
get too close.
One always has to be on guard,
expecting sneak
attacks and betrayals.
Never, let another man
choose your weapon.
It's time to wake up Alucard.
Seras and Integra
are waiting for you.
Look! Isn't that General
de Gaulle up there?
Up where?
Oh!
Damn, I missed.
Hello, I'm Christopher Walken.
And I'm Tom Berenger.
Together, we are
the Dogs of War.
Stop it...
I'm Maximillian Schell.
I say, we kill them all.
Stop it!
Hello, I am the Emperor.
Who are you?
Hello. I am the Fourth Protocol.
That makes no sense.
Hello, I am the Negotiator.
Then good luck to you...
And thus, the seelöwe
shall cross the ocean,
and climb atop the hill.
Sir, our communication feed
to Vauxhall Cross has just been
cut off! The SIS is offline!
It's what?!
We've also lost contact
with London BTN control.
Civilian communication
networks across the city
are apparently also offline.
Sir, we've lost contact
with Ark Air Force Base!
No response from the Atlantic
Fleet or from Fleet Command.
We've had no word from Defence
Intelligence Headquarters.
All lines are down.
General, we've
received civilian reports
of a fleet of dirigibles
moving north over Newhaven.
They're on a direct
course for London.
Dirigibles? A fleet of airships?
Impossible. They can't be
trying to declare war on us!
We're past that.
Sir Integra...
The enemy... is at the gate.
Full speed ahead! Onward!
Faster! Faster, faster!
Push the engines harder!
Faster! Faster!
Schneller! Schneller!
We see the spires of
London! Charge the city!
Schneller! Schneller!
We shall strike the city,
and burn it down to
ash once again! Faster!
Come on, just hold up a sec!
Fuck off, you little prick!
Aw, sweetie,
don't be such a bitch!
Hey Jansen, have a
friend's back would you?
The moon...
It's the moon...
That's cool!
Soldiers of the
Last Battalion, achtung!
Gentlemen, night has fallen.
Tonight, my invincible
warriors of millennium.
Tonight, all our
promises bear fruit!
Welcome to the eve of war!
All right everyone,
it's time to for us to
open up our handbooks.
We'll start on page three:
"Operation Sea Lion,
British Invasion 2"
Please note the information
under the bullet points
"London Explodes!" and
"Crack Battle Vampires."
Uhh... Huh... Uh-oh...
Oh, dear, what is the problem
this time, Herr Schrödinger?
Doctor, I'm sorry, I seem to
have misplaced my handbook.
Oh, such trouble...
What to do with you?
Go share with
the captain for now.
Zorin... Lieutenant
Zorin Blitz...
Ready for orders.
Our primary targets are
the Hellsing Organization,
and the vampire Alucard.
The men under your command
will be the vanguard unit.
Take your Zeppelin and make your
way to Hellsing headquarters.
Yes sir.
Please avoid a
direct assault for now.
I will arrive with the
main force post haste.
I don't know why you
would even bother sir.
Without Alucard the Hellsing
forces are as weak as children.
Do not take the
Hellsing women lightly.
Integra Hellsing
and Seras Victoria
are not to be trifled with.
Sir Integra Fairbrook
Wingates Hellsing,
scion of the famed
Dr. Van Helsing, and the head
of the greatest family of
vampire hunters in history.
And she is the only authority
the Vampire Alucard recognizes.
Then there is the policewoman,
the vampire Seras Victoria.
She is... perhaps a miracle?
Perhaps you might think,
something of a joke?
I suspect that she herself
may not fully
understand her nature yet.
It certainly makes it exciting
though, don't you think?
They are both inexperienced,
imperfect, and untested.
I would therefore
argue that like Alucard,
they are archenemies worthy
of caution and scrutiny.
And that is why you shall
hold, without engaging.
Do you understand
your orders Zorin?
They are crystal clear,
Battalion Commander.
Perfect.
Then everything is set.
It is time for us to open
the floodgates of war!
Our first target shall
be the City of London--
The west bank of
the Thames; Big Ben;
the Houses of Parliament;
Ten Downing Street;
the Ministry of Defence;
Buckingham Palace; Scotland
Yard; Westminster Abbey;
Piccadilly Circus; Soho;
the City; Southwark--
burn it to the ground!
Burn the poles.
Burn the central government.
Major, what about
the Cabinet War Rooms?
Blow them up. They're awful.
Don't leave the slightest
hint they ever existed.
What shall we do about
Trafalgar Square, Major?
Destroy it.
Topple Nelson's Column.
The Tower of London,
the British Museum...
the British Library -- destroy
them all. They're repulsive.
And Tower Bridge?
Topple it. London Bridge
as well, like the song.
And what about the
Imperial War Museum?
Blow it up.
Go forth, and destroy
everything that you see.
Devour everyone you meet.
Feast and imbibe to
your hearts content.
This mighty capital of
8 million souls are nothing
but our supper.
Come, gentlemen, it's time
for us to kill and be killed.
To give, and receive death.
Now... let us
toast the occasion.
For tonight is a feast,
the likes of which has
never been seen before.
Prosit!
I want more...
Ready the refitted V1's!
Prepare to drop the
Waffen-Shutzstaffel!
Ya vol!
All retrofitted V1's
have been fired!
The blow has crippled
the infrastructure!
They are crippled! Crippled!
It's not enough...
More... I demand more!
Harvest the fruits of battle!
It's beautiful...
Like a twilight view of hell.
Below us is the only place
fit for monsters such as us.
It is the only place
we would wish to be.
Commence ground combat
operation. Deploy paratroopers!
Here we go you Frontschwein!
Off to war!
Fünf... vier...
drei... zwei... eins...
What is the meaning of this?!
Please, no sudden moves...
Sir Integra.
As of now, this facility is
under the control of Millennium.
Enough! What is going on!
Shut up!
What is going on, Sir Penwood,
is a very good day for Vampires.
A very good day indeed,
considering I've just
captured the great Sir Integra.
What's so funny?!
Why the whole thing of course.
Really, you're the vampire
equivalent of newborns.
We on the other hand
are the institution
of your annihilation.
Frogs parading
in front of a viper.
Of course it's funny
I'm not scared of you!
I hope you can
claim your Iron Cross
from your corporal in hell.
Shut up!
Walter, clean up.
As you wish, Sir Integra.
Now then, It's time to take
these children across my knee.
Die!
That all?
Bloody traitors.
Sorry, Sir Penwood.
Are you all right?
Up until now,
I had been convinced
that you were the
traitor in our midst.
I may be powerless against them,
but I'm certainly not a coward.
Sir, the city is under siege!
No word from the
Chiefs of Staff!
We've already lost
contact with over
150 military installations
and command centers
across the British Empire!
It is possible they're currently
engaging the enemy forces!
It'll be the same everywhere...
This facility is sure to
be on their list of targets.
We should be gone before they
arrive. It's time to leave.
There are Nazi soldiers are
dropping from the airships!
It's the Waffen-SS!
It can't be!
Sir Penwood, it's time.
This building is about to be
overrun by an army of vampires!
Sir Integra.
You and your man will return
to Hellsing headquarters
as quickly as is possible.
There are duties you are
honor bound to perform.
Go, and see to your
sworn obligations,
I must stay and perform mine.
This place can no longer
function as a command center.
Do you have a death wish?
It's still possible for us to
restore communications,
and we may be able
to issue orders again.
We will need to establish
a chain of command
with whatever bases are still
fighting off the invasion.
I am the commanding
officer here.
This is my facility.
I cannot abandon my post.
I know that
I'm not a strong man.
I've always been nervous.
Even I'm not entirely sure
how a man like me ended up
in such a position of authority.
No, that's not true.
I was born with
a title, and money.
My authority was expected,
and my position handed
to me by obligation.
So, given that,
the least I can do
is perform the
responsibilities I was handed.
Now, off with you Sir Integra.
There are evils moving
against us that only you-
That only Hellsing can face.
It's loaded with blessed
atomized silver tip rounds.
You should find them more
effective than ordinary iron.
Sir Penwood.
Best of luck, and good hunting.
Thank you, and good
hunting, Sir Integra.
All staff prepare
for evacuation.
Only essential personnel
will stay behind.
On second thought,
in truth, I suppose,
I'm capable of operating
the emergency systems myself.
All of you, get out
of here. Quickly.
That's enough. What's so funny?
I gave an order! Evacuate!
I'll try and establish contact
with National
Defence again, sir.
Start looking for a line!
Gather weapons and ammunition!
Let's form a garrison. Quickly!
Sir!
Hey, wait!
Start setting up barricades
at the entrances. Go!
I told you idiots!
You don't even have
to be here anymore!
There's no need
for hysterics, Sir.
And everyone knows you have no
idea how the consoles operate.
Please, sir, just
take your normal seat.
Otherwise you'll
just get in the way.
Thank you, gentlemen. Carry on.
Reassessing damage reports.
We're going to need runners!
Even if the lines are
down, we'll get through!
Then try contacting
the foreign branches.
We need data!
We're leaving Walter.
As quickly as possible.
As you say, Ma'am.
We'll take the car.
Will that be a problem?
Not in the slightest.
Nothing is going
to get in my way.
As head of the Hellsing
family... I swear it!
Run!
Oh no!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Damn it... Damn it...
Damn it... Damn it... Damn!
Little girls,
lost in a sea of flame?
Look around you,
it's hell come to earth.
But it's still a pale
shadow of the world to come.
Good boys. You defended
Queen and country.
Rest in peace.
Time is short. Let's move on.
Integra Hellsing sighted.
She is traveling
at high speed down
Regent Street
toward Hellsing Manor.
Capture her. Capture her!
Attention all soldiers...
Attention, anyone...
This is Vice Admiral
Penwood, speaking
from the British Security
Special Command Center.
I don't even know
if there is anyone left
to receive this message.
This facility will soon fall.
The monsters are almost upon us,
and through the
last of our defenses.
I now deliver the final
orders from this facility
to whomever is listening
to this transmission.
Keep fighting. Do your duty.
Are you saying... This is it?
The new head of the family?
Walter, this is a little girl!
"A Little girl?" A bit rude,
don't you think, Sir Penwood?
Well, no I, uh... It's just...
I am Integra Fairbrook
Wingates Hellsing
My uncle is dead, by my hand,
and I am now the head
of the Hellsing family.
So you are never to address
me as "Little Girl" again.
M-My apologies
Ms. Hellsing. So sorry!
Before my father died he said,
if I were to ever need
anything at all, Mr. Penwood
would happily provide.
Yes, of course!
Arthur was always
"Penwood I need you to get
me this new fancy gun!"
Or "I need a helicopter."
Or some other God forsaken
ridiculous piece of equipment!
Well, not to outdo my father,
but I may have some
requests of my own.
I am quite grateful.
You put up quite a fight,
you fat blood sack.
You think this is funny do you?
Pathetic.
Pathetic am I? This coming
from an undead maggot?
'Course it's bloody funny.
Farewell, Integra Hellsing.
It was an honor and a privilege.
No! Put down the switch!
Never!
I do not take orders
from swine like you.
Walter...
Yes, ma'am?
Faster!
What is it?
Sir Integra, please
take the wheel of the car,
and find another
way across town.
What are you doing?
Take the car and go,
as fast as you can.
Do not try and find me; and no
matter what, do not look back.
Walter...
The way I am now...
I don't know how long
I'll be capable
of holding out against that man.
Walter... Live through this.
Consider that an
order. Understand?
If you insist ma'am.
Of course... I knew it was you.
You are correct, my boy.
So, butler...
It's been what, 55 years?
It's nice to know that after all
this time, you still manage
to find a way to interrupt
me during my dinner.
Integra Hellsing is on the move.
She has changed routes,
and is moving towards
the manor at full speed.
Attention, all available
squads! Stop her!
Whatever it takes!
Integra Hellsing is unprotected.
I repeat, whatever it takes!
Pursue her! Stop her!
Capture her! Capture her!
There she is!
Panzerfaust! Zielen... Feuern!
Integra Hellsing!
By the order of battalion
commander, Prepare to-!
Hmph. You don't know
when to give up, fraulein.
No matter how much you struggle
your situation is hopeless.
Surrender. This is not
your London anymore.
This is Midian,
where there is no place
for humans to run
and hide. Give up.
Surrender? Run and hide?
Oh yes... and give up.
I should give up...
That is, what someone
like you would say to do.
Cowards, who could not bear the
weight of their own humanity.
You pathetic
monsters disgust me.
Come on! Let's have it!
Die!
What is... My body... tearing...
Oh dear!
It's you...! The Iscariot
Organization... Section XIII...
God's Assassin...
Saint Guillotine...
The Regenerator,
The Angel's Dust...
The Bayonet Priest...
Alexander Anderson!
Facing down the
big scary vampires,
sword in hand,
bleeding on the street?
"Come on! Let's have it!"?!
Did you hear that?
Well, Heinkel?
How about you, Yumie?
No doubt about it.
This woman... These people...
who else could be worthy
to be our sworn enemies?
Our archenemies!
Father Anderson,
I thought our orders
were to do nothing more
than observe at this point.
And for that matter, rescuing
the Hellsing woman sir...
that's a serious breach
of orders, is it not?
What was I supposed to do,
just sit back and watch?
WE will be the ones
who will crush them!
WE are the only ones
who deserve to crush them!
No one else may interfere!
No one else can have them!
Just us! Just us!
So you're with Iscariot...
You won't stand in our way!
Hold your tongue.
The dead don't speak!
Do the dead dare walk
the earth before my eyes?
Will the undead raise an
army, fall in, and advance?
Would those who
would abandon God,
and embrace a heretical order,
dare presume to meet my gaze?
Iscariot will not allow it!
I will not allow it!
You will be cut down like straw
trembling before my wrath!
Amen!!
Speak up you men of God.
Tell us all who you are!
We are the soldiers of Iscariot!
We are truthers Iscariot!
Well then Iscariot, I ask you,
what do you hold
in your right hand?!
Daggers and poison!
Well then soldiers of
Iscariot, I ask you...
What do you hold
in your left hand?!
30 pieces of silver
and a straw rope!
Now...!
Show them who you are,
my soldiers of Iscariot!
We are apostles,
yet not apostles!
We are believers,
yet not believers!
We are disciples,
yet not disciples!
We are heretics,
yet not heretics!
We are solders in
the service of death,
who bow are heads in reverence
to our Lord and whose prayers
are found in the withered
bodies of our enemies!
Our poisons served
at every supper,
our daggers flashing
in the moonlight!
We are the Apostles
of Judas Iscariot...
We are his holy
flock of assassins,
and upon the hour
at which we were called,
we cast our 30 pieces of silver
into the sight of the holy,
and hang ourselves
with a rope of straw.
Thus do we move to meet hell's
legions as a mighty army,
and form our squared ranks
against hell's gates,
and prepare to meet the
seven million four hundred
and five thousand nine hundred
and twenty-six
demons of iniquity
My nemesis...
My master...
I am being drawn closer...
And I shall continue the journey
within my dream as well...
Onward... to the battlefield!
Was it a dream?
I had a dream in which
I did not get to fight.
Master, I don't think
that was a dream.
What?
Well you see, these next two
volumes are mostly about,
Iscariot, the Nazis,
Seras, and myself.
I think you're
barley in it at all!
I do okay, though.
I feel so sorry for you.
I'm all over these volumes
like Sergeant Slaughter
dropping an inverted suplex.
Like the Macho Savage
I am bringing the pain!
I love the way
you bring a sparkle
to such dated and
bland material. Bravo!
What's wrong with you people?