Well, boy? Why do
you stand there crying?
Because... the kids
at my school...
They said I was a
murderer's son...
And then they said, "Your whole
family fights wars for money!"
Waste of salt,
crying over the truth.
Our men have been mercenaries
for eight generations now.
Going back to your grandpa's
grandpa's grandpa's grandpa.
What do you think your pop
died of in Columbia? The flu?
He knew you were on the
way and needed cash...
Bit off more than he could
chew... What's that look...?
Didn't your mother
ever tell you?
But... does that mean...
you killed people,
too, Grandpa?!
Course I killed people, boy.
More than a few.
But, what for...?
What did they do
to deserve... that?!
Deserve's got nothing to
do with it... It's a job...
Anyone who found himself
at the end of my gun,
he was fighting for something.
Bring down a government,
or prop one up.
For homeland, or someone else's.
For family. For a woman.
Maybe just food and drink.
So many damn reasons.
Some good... some bad.
A mercenary doesn't
ask questions, boy...
It's enough to know the other
man's dying for something...
But that reason of his...
whatever it was...
was it really worth
fighting for...? Maybe...
But who says you
need some epic cause
before you can shed some blood?
Fighting for
filthy lucre's always
been good enough for me...
Pays the bills.
Toss us a bit of coin... and
we will risk life, and limb...
They dangle their spare
change in front of our nose,
and we come running.
We march onto chessboards
all over the world,
for mere pennies.
Kill for 'em. Die for 'em.
But really...? It aint'
about the damn pennies.
We go because we enjoy it.
We fight for money,
'cause fighting
for fun's just too
horrible to admit.
Die for a dollar?
Kill for some kroner?
Sign us up. We're the
scum of the earth, boy.
With a legacy like ours,
course they're going
to pick on you at school.
You cry, but I bet you'll come
around one of these days...
You know, the apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
You were right... It's never
been about the money.
It's always been about the fun.
Hurry up! Grab
anything we can use
to block the doors
and fall back A-SAP!
Yessir!
Get Squad Two on
the radio! Move, dammit!
Help! Help me!
Someone fucking help me!
Dammit, they're pouring in!
Keep shooting! Keep shooting!
Our bullets aren't doing shit!
Fall back, now!
Where's the medic?!
They flanked us--we're
totally cut off! Fuck!
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit!
This is Squad Two...!
Captain, we're in
the shit down here!
We're not gonna be able
to make it back to you guys!
Listen, asshole...!
I don't care if
you have to crawl...!
Fall back to the round
table room--that's an order!
This is the easiest
spot to reinforce...
We can hold out for a while.
You have to retreat--you're
a sitting duck out there!
We're not going to close the
barricade until you're back!
Negative, Captain--no can do.
They've torn us all
to hell, myself included.
He's dead, okay?
Cap him again before he
tries to fucking eat us.
Someone... gimmie some water...
We'll hold them off
for as long as we can...
But you gotta close
that barricade now!
Good hunting, Captain.
[speaking French]
Be that way...
you brave bastard...
If you're ready
to die, go for it.
I guess this is adieu.
Been a hell of a ride,
Captain--I don't
regret a thing...
Goodbye!
Let's close up the barricade.
Take this huge fucking table
and add it to the pile...
Seal that goddamn hole already!
But, sir... what
about the others?
All KIA.
Understood... They'll be missed.
What's it matter...?!
We're all gonna die tonight!
Shut the fuck up!
How're we supposed to
fight Nazi vampires...?!
It's bullshit...! Integra
and Alucard sold us out!
I'm done--I'm fucking done!
What're you yellin' about...?
There's nowhere to go...
Not that I'm letting you leave.
The hell you aren't...!
I'm outta here!
Face the facts...
This place will be our grave...
This mansion our
tombstone--our gravekeeper
that cast-iron bitch Integra...
And our epitaph...?
"Here lies the badass
Wild Geese--they kicked
beaucoup de Nazi ass
for Queen and crumpets."
But they won't
write any of that...
Thanks to you,
it's going to read...
"Here lie those gutless pussies
who died pissing themselves
and crying like schoolgirls."
Man the fuck up, bitch...!
You'll die with honor if I have
to tie you to your damn post!
You take the money
because you like it
and you fight because
you like it--and now...!
You're going to die
like a merc and like it!
Yessir... Yeah...!
Fuck...! Fuck!
Come on--no one ever said dying
tonight was a sure thing...
We got a nice big barricade.
Now... get up and
come lend a hand...
Just in case ma chere
leaves us any of 'em.
Just keep shooting! Why can't
we hit these assholes?!
Fuck!
These sons-of-bitches
aren't slowing down any!
Don't you die on me, man!
I'm done--we all are.
Keep it together!
That's it! Burn it down!
Kill every bastard you find!
This is the best fight
Hellsing can put up...?
These sad meat-sacks
are your combat elite...?!
God, what a joke!
Flush 'em out.
I've got something
special for you!
That's impossible...
I'm back home...?!
Daddy!
I'm so glad you're home, Daddy.
M-Michelle...? It's not...
You're not my daughter...
She's dead...
You're not Michelle...!
Why do you look like her?!
Why do I look like who...?
What's wrong, Daddy?
You're not real...
You're not real...!
Oh, God...
You're another illusion...
You can't be standing here...
but God, you look just
like her! Oh, Michelle...!
Daddy has missed you so much!
Joke's on you, Daddy!
She's worm-food...
and so are you!
Sorry I had to cut
your reunion short!
All right, Sergeant,
what about that one?
Another? Give me a second, ja?
It's pretty sour... I'm
guessing... A-negative...!
So? Did I get
it right this time?
That's amazing, sir!
You're quite the
blood connoisseur...
It's like he told you himself!
It has a certain...
"pungent" plate.
Such distinctions
are wasted on me.
Negative has more bite...
And, type-A has a certain
bouquet that I really...
I'll... make those bastards pay.
Every last... one of 'em...
will fucking die!
I'll tear them to shreds!
Fuck! Fuck!
Sons of bitches...
they got us good...!
We're losing him...! Come on!
Dammit...! Throw chairs
onto the pile...! All of 'em!
Hurry it up, guys...!
The barricade's
not gonna hold for long!
You want some, assholes?!
You idiot...!
Get down from there!
Fuck...!
God... We're all
gonna die here...!
Shut up! Keep that
shit to yourself!
Even if we surrender,
they're just gonna torture
the shit out of us...
Then they're gonna eat us
alive... It's fucking over...
Whatever ammo's left,
hand it out!
Here, Captain...
This is it... We're out
of silver bullets...
Damn near out of
regular ones, too.
Come on, kill me...
I can't even shoot
a gun anymore--
they blew out my fucking eyes!
I take it back, sir--I
didn't mean it...!
I don't wanna die!
Good--we're in agreement.
Now stop yelling in my damn ear.
'Member that time...?
That airfield in Uganda...?
Fuckers had us pinned down...
I thought our asses
were done for...
And then the cavalry
came riding in...
Somehow, I don't see
that happening this time.
Don't give up just yet...
Seras is coming... I'm sure
of it. Bet my life on it.
I'm getting damn sick
of those rockets...
How many more until
they run out, huh?
Damage report--now...!
How many wounded?
What are we looking at?!
No...!
Stay with me...!
Don't you fucking die!
Oh, God... I'm exhausted...
I'm just gonna close my eyes...
Go on... You've earned it...
I'll see ya soon.
A direct hit, Lieutenant.
Do we advance?
Not just yet.
Let's soften them up a bit more.
This is our last
Panzerfaust, Lieutanant.
It's our trump card.
I could care less...!
You take that Panzerfaust...
and you launch it straight
up their mercenary asses!
Jawohl.
What're they waiting for?
Schiess los!
It's the bitch who
downed my zeppelin...!
You're dead!
Captain...?
Of course she's here--I
told you she'd come...
Ma chere is
reporting for duty...
Might as well smoke 'em
if you got 'em, ladies...
Time for the main event!
God, she's perfect,
isn't she...?
I should have kissed her
when I had the chance...
You're a damn fool,
Pip Bernadotte.
Outta rounds...?
Or are you surrendering?
Tough talk from
the only Nazi left!
Trust me, you'll love this!
This... this isn't real...!
It's just an illusion...
It isn't real...!
It's not reaaaaaaaal!
Don't tell me that Seras girl
has been acting up yet again.
Afraid so.
She hit one of the boys
with a rock for taking
a toy away from her.
Just a memory...!
That's all it is...!
The teachers all say it's
like talking to a wall.
Probably still traumatized
from, well, you know...
Yes... but if she doesn't start
getting along with others...
I'll happily send her packing
for the good of the orphanage.
I'm not going to break.
I want more.
That's all very noble,
but, well...
isn't there anything
you'd rather do?
No.
At least pretend
to think it over.
Your father was a fine
policeman--one of the best.
But there's a world of
possibilities out there for you.
I just hate to see you
squander your potential.
That's ancient history...!
We're going to the very bottom!
Listen to your mum...
Stay in the closet... please...
Don't come out of here,
no matter what.
Mommy... Mommy...!
Oi, piggy-piggy.
Whassa matter? Come on, mate...
Squeal like a pig, why don't ya?
One bitty squeal!
Shoulda had him
squeal before you shot.
Nah, this one's special!
He's so fucking good at it!
Squealing like a pig's
what earned him this!
He stuck that
badge-wearing snout
of his in where it
didn't belong!
You were just for fun.
Big mistake!
My eye! That filthy little cunt!
You can bitch later.
We have to get out of here.
It hurts, goddamn it!
Gimmie a second!
You ain't the one
with a fork in ya!
Lemme toss one
in the wifey first...
Fuck you want? She's dead.
Still warm, innit?
Hell, I've fucked worse.
Good morning, Seras...
It's time to wake up...
Did somebody have a nightmare?
You can do better than that...!
Now...! Scream!
Not so tough anymore!
I love the way you squirm
beneath my boot heel!
God, you're such a weakling...!
And I was so sure you were
going to be a challenge.
You're trash...
Like all those men I killed.
Now... how to end this?
Maybe I should just
cut your head off...
I've seen what's in there.
This is a kindness.
Now, die!
You first, bitch!
What...?!
Leave her alone!
That's enough of
your shit... Stay down.
Hey, Captain! Hurry it up!
The mansion's a loss...!
We gotta go!
My pleasure.
Captain... Burnadotte...
what're you...?
Don't talk.
Captain Bernadotte...
Please, run away...
Save yourself...
Just leave me behind...!
I'm being a gentleman...
Don't talk back.
Shit--we got a live one!
You asshole!
Oh my God...
Captain, you're...!
Yeah...!
Bullseye...!
Who's laughing now, hero?
Captain Bernadotte...
Say something!
Jesus... what a bloody pair...
What'd she do?!
You come charging
in to save me...
and now I have to save
you... What the hell...
Why didn't you run away...?
Finally stole that kiss!
Took you being blind
to do it, but I got it.
Bernadotte...
Hey, now...
What's with the tears...?
I had a damn good run, Seras.
Now, suck my blood...
Take me into yourself
so we can win this fight.
I told you...
Don't waste your tears...
on a mercenary...
You lost those pretty blue eyes
of yours trying to save me.
You lost your arm, too...
What a waste...
Foolish, ma chere...
Another time, maybe...
another place...
You're a rare woman, Seras...
I die so that she
can live... Alright.
Oh God...
The Captain... is... dead?
Just breaks your
heart... doesn't it?
He was a bug, buzzing
around my face...
That's why I had to
swat him down... Like a gnat.
By the way...
if you thought you'd
killed all of my soldiers
in the mansion, you were right.
But, we've had
some late arrivals.
Fuck, more of them?!
She brought back-up!
Let's take these bugs...
and crush them
between our fingers!
Such is the death
they deserve...!
The death of an insect!
Not again...! Enough
of this mind-fucking!
You called him a gnat,
didn't you...
You called him... a gnat...!
You'll pay for this.
You will pay!
You're going to pay...
You'll pay!
Thank you, Captain...
Rest in peace.
But not yet...
Not yet!
What's going on...?
She broke Zorin's spell...!
I did what you told me.
And in return you're
going to help me...
send these Nazis to hell!
What? How is this possible...?!
They're trembling...! These
battle-hardened Waffen-SS...
these vampires, who charged
into gunfire and grenades
without a moment's
hesitation...!
They're ready to piss themselves
at the sight of a girl!
One stupid, weak little girl
who's more dead than alive!
What the hell's
going on...?! Verdammt!
Open fire! Everyone--shoot!
It's not possible...
It's bullscheise!
She's cutting through
my reinforcements...
God, she's headed
straight for me!
Even if I were about to die...
I wouldn't drink a single
goddamn drop of your evil blood!
I don't want you...
inside of me!
Let's go... deeper!
That's it...!
Even deeper... Yes, take it...
Show me your pain!
What am I looking at...?
These aren't her memories...
What's going on here...?
This isn't right!--everything's
in disarray...!
Why can't I go any
deeper into her head?!
It's like these fucking
memories are protecting her!
It's him...!
That arrogant mercenary...!
That goddamned gnat!
Blood is the currency of
the soul, the vehicle of life.
Having blood offered...
is a very different
experience... than taking it!
Are you okay...? You look awful!
How are you here?
Don't act so surprised,
Zorin...! Whoa!
As they say... I am
everywhere...! And nowhere!
I am here...! To deliver a
message from the Major...
Straight from our
fearless leader's mouth!
"Every soldier dreams of leading
the charge against the foe.
Such is their reward.
But the long-suffering
commander--
what is his reward
when they fail?
When they go against
orders, lose men,
and prove themselves inept?"
That's the message...!
Under normal circumstances,
they would have burned you to
a crisp long before now... but!
The Major and Doc
got their hands
on this fascinating new toy,
and they don't have
time to deal with you...
And Seras seems to have you
pretty well taken care of.
Such a paradox...!
This monster is Seras Victoria,
yet not Seras Victoria.
Rest assured, she'll be ending
your unlife any moment now...
Auf Wiedersehen!
How does it feel having someone
fuck with your head...?!
How does it feel, you bitch?!
Look at her...
How can that be... the same
sweet girl we knew before...?
I'm heading out.
Heading out?
But where is there to go?
He told me... to drink him in...
so that we could win this fight.
And now... I think the Captain
and I are only getting started.
I-Inside...?
Right here... Captain...
This is where you
made your last stand.
You're dead...
but you're not gone...
'Cause you're
inside of that girl.
One last thing...
Thanks, sir.
Sir!
The dawn is finally breaking...
come to slay the night.
Undaunted by the light of
the sun, she speeds away...
as though fired
from a bow drawn taut.
She makes for London...
For a raid upon the morn!
This is it... What my
eyes have so longed for...
Ah, what a sight...
For what it's worth,
Zorin's dead, sir.
Killed by a gnat.
Well, that's hardly a surprise.
Watch how it burns, boy.
Like the end of the
Gotterdammerung...
Major, you're such a meanie...
You bring a whole army with you,
but really they're nothing
but kindling for
your personal bonfire.
What is hell, if not a bonfire?
"I am become death..."
I am the serpent,
devouring myself.
I take and am taken
from without end.
How many days of
wild aspiration...
how many nights
of black entropy...
have I slain to
witness this triumph...?
Our destruction approaches...
together with our victory!
A private army of Nazis
from Germany's Third Reich.
"The Last Battalion".
A division of Waffen-SS panzer
grenadiers turned into vampires.
Five-hundred seventy-two
of their number remain.
The knights of the ninth
airborne mobile crusade,
sent forth by the Vatican to
serve Archbishop Maxwell.
Two-thousand nine-hundred
and seventy-five of
their number remain.
Her Majesty's Hellsing
Organization of England.
Only three of
their number remain.
Release control
art-restriction level zero.
Acknowledged.
As you wish, my master.
Return to our shores,
and bury our foes under
the darkness within you!
Now!