[NARRATOR]
In the year UC 796,
also known to history as IC 487,
a Galactic Imperial Navy
fleet of 20,000 warships,
led by Reinhard von Lohengramm,
faced the Free Planets
Alliance Navy in
the Astarte Starzone.
The Alliance, with
its superior numbers,
attempted to surround the
Imperial Navy on three sides.
But the Imperials struck each of
their fleets individually,
leading to the loss of
the 4th and 6th fleets,
sealing the Alliance's defeat.
When suddenly,
a message was transmitted
from the Alliance.
The voice said. "Have no fear.
Those of you who
wish to survive,
remain calm and do as I say."
Yang Wen-li. Reporting
to the bridge as ordered, sir!
I've finished reviewing
the battle plan you submitted.
It's quite an interesting
proposal, Commodore.
That said. In my opinion,
it's far too circumspect,
to the point of being passive.
You think so, sir?
If we heed your advice,
you're right, we won't lose.
But, not losing is insufficient.
We want a victory.
Given our clear
strategic advantage,
I see no benefit to altering
the current plan in favor
of your
overly-cautious proposal.
Not only do our forces have the
enemy surrounded on three sides,
but we outnumber
them two to one.
That's true, but as you know,
our encirclement is
not yet complete.
I've made my decision:
I'm rejecting this proposal.
Just so we're clear,
this is a tactical call
and not a personal one.
I understand, sir.
[LAO]
Commodore!
Yes, uh... Who are you?
My name's Lao, sir.
It's an honor to serve with
the hero of El Facil. Truly.
Please don't call me that.
A hero. Anyway, did
you need something from me?
It's regarding
your proposal, sir.
I might be mistaken,
but judging from
your expression,
I'd guess it was turned down.
It was, indeed.
I looked depressed
enough for you to tell
that at a glance, huh?
[LAO]
Hm.
I won't keep you, but
if you don't mind me asking,
what are your thoughts on
our current situation?
[YANG]
My thoughts?
We do have a clear advantage.
But if I were the enemy,
I wouldn't exactly
consider myself in dire peril.
[LAO]
Sir!
I have always had
the luck of the devil.
Back when my entire
fleet was destroyed,
I was one of three men who
made it out of there alive.
[YANG] Maybe some of
that luck will rub off on me.
As someone who's
been through worse.
I'm optimistic
about this mission.
Please, sir. Don't
feel discouraged.
[YANG]
Okay...?
[MAN 2A] Patrol craft 371
to flagship Patroklos.
The Imperial Navy fleet
could not be found
in the anticipated
sector. Repeat.
[MAN 2B] The Imperial Navy
fleet could not be found
in the anticipated sector.
They're not there?
But that's impossible!
It defies all reason!
Send an urgent transmission
to the 4th fleet commander!
[MAN 2A]
No response!
It appears the enemy has
jammed the radio waves!
It all turned
out just like you said.
Not that I'm happy
about it, but yes.
[YANG] With our encirclement
still incomplete,
taking our fleets out
individually would
be the logical strategy.
[YANG] So, they're avoiding
the mistake they made
in the Slaughter at Dagon.
[PAETTA]
Commodore Yang!
Sir?
I would like your
analysis of the situation.
What do you think
they're planning?
It's clear the enemy
intends to take out our fleets
one at a time, and, given that
the fourth is the smallest
of the three, it would be
the obvious first choice
as a target.
With our forces scattered,
they can decide which
to confront first rather
than waiting until we've
encircled them completely.
[PAETTA]
Assuming you're right,
do you think the 4th
fleet can hold out?
[YANG]
The forces have clashed head-on.
Whoever has superior
numbers and strikes first
gets the advantage.
[PAETTA] Regardless, we need
to rush to the battlefield
and aide the 4th
before it's too late.
If luck's on our side, we'll be
able to hit the Imperial Navy
from the rear flank.
We'll have an instant
advantage over them.
I don't believe that's possible.
Why not, Commodore?
By the time we get there,
the battle will be over and
the 4th fleet destroyed.
The enemy
will be gone, too, sir.
They'll move to
continue their assault.
Most likely, they'll
strike the rear flank
of the 2nd or the 6th fleet.
We have lost the initiative.
In fact, they've taken it
from us at every turn.
In my opinion, we should
devise a new strategy
that doesn't play into
the enemy's hands.
And what exactly do you suggest?
[YANG]
A change of procedure.
Instead of rushing
to aid the 4th Fleet,
we merge with the 6th
fleet immediately.
Once we're united, we'll create
a new battlefield in that sector
and then challenge
the enemy there.
Combined, our two fleets
would total 28,000 ships.
As a result, our odds of success
would exceed 50%.
Are you actually
suggesting we leave
the brave people of
the 4th fleet to die?
Even if we left right now,
we still wouldn't
get there in time.
You don't know that.
The 4th fleet is strong.
They won't die so easily.
If they can just
hang on till we arrive!
Sir. I'm sorry to say
it, but the 4th fleet is lost.
Commodore Yang.
The reality of galactic
warfare does not rely
on your calculations alone!
The man leading the
enemy's expeditionary force
is Count Lohengromm.
He's young and inexperienced.
With all due respect, sir.
While it may be true
he lacks experience.
--His strategic ideas--
--That is enough, Commodore!
The Vice Admiral Pastolle
is a veteran!
He won't go down
without a fight!
[alarm sounds]
Jean. Talk fast,
we've been ordered
to halt our communications.
The enemy isn't where
we expected they'd be, Yang.
[YANG]
Yeah, I know.
There's no hope
for the 4th fleet, then?
I'm afraid not.
The enemy will most likely
attack the 6th fleet next.
If that's true, then
they're about to increase
the interference on
our comm system.
I'm afraid this might be the
last time the two of us speak.
If we don't do something
fast, we're done for.
I'll recommend to
Vice Admiral Moore
that we rendezvous
with the 2nd fleet.
I don't know that he'll listen,
but I'll try to talk some
sense into Paetta, too.
Yang.
If anything happens to me,
take care of Jessica.
Please don't start
talking like that, Jean.
[LAPP] And you call
yourself a military man?
Just because I wear
the uniform doesn't mean
I fit in here. You stay
alive and get home to her.
I don't want to hear any
dying requests from you.
[LAPP]
I'll do my best. Good luck, pal.
[MAN 2C]
Signal lost.
[YANG]
Don't die, Jean.
[MAN 1I]
The enemy's at our rear!
[MAN 1C] The enemy jam
has completely severed
our data link!
Shields incomplete!
[MAN 1I]
Transmission from the enemy.
"You are completely surrounded.
You cannot escape.
If you surrender,
you will be shown mercy."
[LAPP growls]
[LAPP]
Jessica...
[YANG] Commander. You can
see the situation we're in.
[YANG] There's no
question the Imperial Navy
will target the 2nd fleet next.
I'm beginning to wonder
if you have any ideas
that are not passive,
Commodore Yang.
No disrespect, sir,
but all of my advice
has been proactive.
[MAN 2G]
Radio signal jammed!
Scouting system
partially offline!
[MAN 2H] Optical signal
detecting an approaching ship.
Analyzing image.
Most likely enemy craft!
Order all our personnel
to report to battle stations!
Do it now!
[YANG]
That was faster than I expected.
[YANG groans]
Are you all right?
Commander Paetta is
hurt and needs assistance.
Ready the sick bay
and send a Navy Surgeon!
Listen up!
Are there any
officers still alive?
[LAO]
I'm not dead just yet.
[YANG]
Lieutenant Lao?
[groans]
You seem surprised.
I meant it when I told you
I've got the Devil's luck.
[coughs]
Commodore Yang.
You are to assume control
of the fleet at once.
You want me to take command?
The way I see it,
you're the highest ranking
officer still in one piece.
We're gonna need your tactical
skill now more than ever.
I guess, deep down,
he respected you quite a bit.
You think so, huh?
[YANG]
Message to all fleets!
Greetings. I'm
Commodore Yang Wen-li,
deputy officer to
Commander Paetta.
Our flagship,
Patroklos , has been hit,
and Commander Paetta
has been gravely injured.
Per the commander's orders,
I will be taking over command
of all fleets
effective immediately.
[YANG] Have no fear, follow my
orders and you will live.
Those of you who wish
to survive, remain calm,
and do as I say.
At the moment, our side
is losing, but the only thing
that matters is to be
winning at the last moment.
We will not lose.
[YANG] All ships, focus on
destroying individual crafts
until I give further
orders, that is all.
[REINHARD "Follow my
orders and you will live."
Those are bold statements.
I've certainly met some
braggarts in my day.
But never on this level.
He can say what he likes.
But he must realize there's
no chance he can win.
Well, no matter.
Let's find out what he's
made of, shall we, Kircheis?
Yes, let's.
[LAO]
Commander.
The enemy is reforming
into a spindle formation.
[YANG] They must be planning
to break through our center.
What's our next move, sir?
I have a plan in mind.
A plan?
How will you give
the order, sir?
Comms are still down,
our system is entirely jammed,
and the data link
isn't restored yet.
Nothing will get through.
Listen to me, Lao.
Broadcast a compressed data
transmission immediately.
Instruct every single ship in
our fleet to open code C-4
on their tactical intel system.
Yes, the enemy may
be monitoring everything
we send out, but if
that's all we transmit,
they won't understand.
[gasps]
[LAO] He knew what
he was doing all along.
I hoped this wouldn't be
necessary, but unfortunately...
Chief engineer,
maintain critical life support
but redirect all other output
to the shields immediately!
[ENGINEER 2A]
Order from flagship Patroklos .
We're to enable Code C-4
on the tactical intel system.
Then do as
you've been instructed.
[AIDE 2A]
Whoa.
[FISHER] It's a strategic plan
for countering a breakthrough
to our center.
And this is from Commodore Yang?
When did he prepare this plan?
[FISHER] In accordance with
the Code C-4 strategic plan,
we will henceforth
move as a united fleet!
Do not rely on the data link!
All ships! Commence
retreat independently at once!
[MAN 2I]
Right away!
So far, it looks
like it's working.
All right. The rest will depend
on our men following the plan.
Yeah. A single
misstep and the whole thing
will blow up in our faces.
If that happens,
what will you do, sir?
I'll pretend
I was clueless, I guess.
[REINHARD gasps]
[KIRCHEIS]
Is something the matter, sir?
What is it, Lord Reinhard?
I don't know.
Something's not right.
We're definitely winning.
There's no doubt.
And yet...
[gasps]
It can't be!
[MAN 2J] The enemy has
split up, Your Excellency!
They're advancing on us at
high speed from both sides!
We've been foiled.
They purposefully made it look
like they'd been broken up.
Then they split into two
forces to come around
and attack us from the rear!
Our strategy to
break through the centerline
has completely backfired!
We're taking fire?
What will you do?
Reverse course and
intercept the attack?
Don't be ridiculous.
If I attempted what you propose,
then I'd be as incompetent
as the commander of
the enemy's 4th fleet.
n that case, our
only option is to move forward.
Yes, precisely.
Send out the order!
Full speed ahead!
When they turn back,
come right up their tails!
[MEN grunting]
[LAO] I've never seen
a formation like this!
[YANG] I'd imagine not.
It's a first for me, too.
[YANG]
No, that's only half true.
I've read that back
when humanity inhabited
the planet Earth, this kind
of formation appeared
on battlefields a
number of times.
[REINHARD]
What a ludicrous formation!
This will be a war of
attrition by the end!
The enemy should
start to pull back soon.
Are we planning
to press the attack, sir?
Let's follow their lead.
When they pull back,
we'll retreat, too.
That's our best option.
We've already done
all we're capable of.
[REINHARD] Kircheis.
What are your thoughts?
[KIRCHEIS] I think it's
perhaps time we end this.
If we continue down this path,
it'll mean mass casualties
for both sides.
There's no advantage
to pressing on.
I hope that
doesn't frustrate you, sir.
Not particularly.
Victory is still ours.
Although it's a shame
we couldn't apply
the finishing touches.
We were surrounded
by the enemy on three sides.
Outnumbered, and yet you still
destroyed two of their fleets.
And when they reversed course,
to attack from behind.
You stopped their advance.
You were steady and confident.
For the situation,
it was enough.
To hope for more
would be greedy, sir.
Yes, I know.
[REINHARD] The commander
of their 2nd Fleet.
The one who assumed
command during the fight.
What was his name again?
Commodore Yang Wen-li.
Ah, yes. That's it.
A clever man.
He just might be the sort of
adversary you spoke of earlier.
[REINHARD] Send a message
to Commodore Yang Wen-li
in my name.
[KIRCHEIS]
Of course, sir.
[REINHARD] Now I have something
interesting to look forward to.
Acting Commander, sir.
There's a message
from the enemy ship.
[YANG]
Well. What does it say?
"I would like to offer
you my compliments.
That was a battle
bravely fought.
Until our next encounter."
High Admiral Reinhard
von Lohengramm.
That is all.
Respect for my
bravery in battle, huh?
What a humbling message.
Well, sir? Shall we respond?
[YANG] No. I doubt
they're really expecting
something like that.
Never mind.
We'll just ignore it.
More importantly, there are
survivors who need our help.
I want to save as many
lives as we possibly can.
Yes, I understand.
Thanks to you I'm still alive.
I cheated death yet again.
It was probably
just your good luck.
[NARRATOR] And thus,
the great Battle of Astarte
came to an end.
In the conflict,
The Alliance suffered over
ten times the losses
of the Imperial Navy.
But their casualties
were not in vain.
They prevented
the Galactic Empire's
invasion of the
Astarte Starzone.
[OFFICIAL 2A] Presenting
the leader of all humanity.
Soverign of all the universe.
Defender of law and order
governing the heavenly realm.
Kaiser of the sacred
Galactic Empire.
[OFFICIAL 2A] His Imperial
Majesty, Friedrich the fourth!
[OFFICIAL 2A]
Count Reinhard von Lohengramm!
Come forth at once!
[NARRATOR] On that day,
the High Admiral of
the Galactic Imperial Navy,
Count Reinhard von Lohengramm,
was named Imperial
Fleet Admiral.
However, this was not the end
of the road for Reinhard.
This was but one small step
toward his true destination.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These : Episode 3,
"The Indomitable Prodigy."