[MAN 11A grunts]
[SOLDIER 11A]
All of the nobles have fled.
Only the civilians remain
on the planets, Admiral.
[APPLETON] It looks like the
Empire is being extra cautious.
Losing Iserlohn
taught them well.
[SOLDIER 11B] We're part of a
liberation force.
You don't have to suffer
under the oppression
of tyranny any longer.
The Free Planets Alliance
happily welcomes
every one of you.
[CONNALLY] Word is that the
citizens are accepting us.
There aren't any
signs of resistance.
[BORODIN] I never thought the
occupation would be this easy.
Is it the same way
for the other fleets?
[CONNALLY]
It appears so.
But, well...
[SOLDIER 11C] You'll have
complete political authority
over yourselves as you
begin new lives as citizens
of a democratic society
free from tyranny.
[OLD MAN 11A] Excuse me,
but before you give us
this "political authority,"
could you please provide
some bread and milk for us?
[SOLDIER 11C] Oh. Of course
we'll provide food.
We'll arrange it right away.
[MAN 11B] There's nothing
here for us to eat.
Not even milk for my baby.
[MAN 11A] Just give us
anything! We're starving!
[gasps]
[OLD MAN 11A]
What're you waiting for?
[YANG sighs]
[FREDERICA]
Admiral.
[YANG]
Hmm?
[FREDERICA] We've received a
message from the ground force.
[YANG]
What does it say?
[FREDERICA] They're requesting
we send food reserves
to distribute among the
liberated citizens immediately.
[YANG] All right, then.
We'll arrange for it right away.
[FREDERICA]
Yes, sir.
[ALEX] Could you read that
report for me one more time?
[ADJUTANT 11A] "To permanently
rescue the locals from
starvation requires
the following.
One hundred eighty days'
worth of food
for 50,000,000 people,
40 artificial protein
production factories,
and 60 hydroponics plants.
[ADJUTANT 11A] These numbers
are expected to rise--
as the liberated territory
continues to gradually expand."
[ALEX] That's 10,000,000 tons
of grain alone,
which would take 50 cargo ships
in the 200,000 class.
I'd like to meet someone
who could come up with a
supply plan to feed twice as
many people as our whole navy.
[ADJUTANT 11A] Maybe if we
were to empty every warehouse
--in Iserlohn we could--
--[ALEX] It wouldn't be enough.
We'd run out in
the blink of an eye.
[ALEX]
Sorry to interrupt.
[LOBOS]
Ah, you're here.
I heard there's a matter you
wished to discuss with me.
Keep it short, if you could.
[ALEX] Very well.
I'll be extremely brief.
You see, our navy is
on the verge of facing
a very serious crisis.
[LOBOS]
What crisis do you mean?
What is this about?
[ALEX]
The request from the front line.
I assume that
you're aware of it.
[LOBOS]
Of course I am.
While it is certainly
an excessive demand,
our occupation policy
leaves us without
any other option on the table.
[ALEX] Iserlohn doesn't have the
quantities they're requesting.
[LOBOS] So just forward the
damn thing back to Heinessen.
No doubt the bureaucrats
will squabble,
but there isn't any chance our
politicians would deny us food.
[ALEX] Yes, sir. I'm positive
they'll send what we ask for,
however, I'm unsure how
long they could keep it up.
[ALEX]
The enemy wants this.
They're putting strain on
our capacity to resupply
the front line.
Which means without question,
they're going to launch--
[FALK]
Without question.
The Empire will
attack our transport,
in an effort to prevent supplies
from reaching our troops.
[FALK] I mean, that is what you
were about to say, am I correct?
[ALEX]
Right on the nose.
[FALK] There are 500
light years between Iserlohn
and the front line.
And we're in control
of that entire region.
I don't think there's any
reason for us to worry.
[FALK] Rear Admiral,
we are fighting this war
in the name of the greater good.
Did you really expect us
to achieve victory
without taking any risks?
[ALEX] That is not what
I came here to discuss!
[LOBOS] Enough. I don't
have the time to listen
to you wax on
about your cowardice.
You're dismissed.
[ALEX sighs] I've said
everything I need to say
to you anyway.
Good day, sir.
[ALEX]
Yang, please come back alive.
This battle is
too idiotic to die for.
[NARRATOR] After receiving the
massive request for supplies
from the front line,
the High Council
was thrown into turmoil.
[NARRATOR] Those who
favored continuing the war,
represented by
Councilwoman Windsor,
were locked in
a fierce verbal battle
with Finance Chairman Lebello,
who wished to withdraw troops.
However...
[SANFORD] I will now announce
the results of the vote.
Four in favor, five opposed
with two abstaining.
[SANFORD]
With a majority opposed,
the motion to withdraw
from the current operation
is hearby rejected.
[NARRATOR] As a result,
it was decided the invasion
into the Empire's territory
would continue.
With the High Council's
decision made,
supply ships departed
planet Heinessen,
heading towards Iserlohn.
Unfortunately, by
then, it was already too late.
Supplies at the front line
were nearing depletion.
So a new strategy
was implemented.
[ULANHU]
Ridiculous!
You expect us to acquire
supplies locally?
Do you know what you're asking?
[APPLETON] You want my
troops to start plundering
from the citizenry, is that it?
[BORODIN] You're telling us
to procure something
that was never there
to begin with!
[BEWCOCK]
A failed supply plan.
The first step toward defeat.
What happened to the Supreme
Commander's talk about
how flawless this operation was?
[WALTER]
They all seem rather irate.
[MURAI]
Of course they are.
Our fleet is running low on food
like everyone else, however,
we can't just let the
people starve to death.
[WALTER] If the Imperial Navy
were to suddenly show up
with food, everyone in the
Empire would instantly
forget us and bow down
to sing the kaiser's praises.
[PATRICHEV] I don't see why we
should be the ones to starve
while those people get to eat!
[MURAI]
Patrichev.
[YANG]
So we don't become like Rudolf.
That's the reason. Lieutenant.
Call Vice Admiral Ulanhu
at once, please.
[FREDERICA]
Yes, sir! Right away!
[ULANHU]
Well, Admiral Yang Wen-li.
How unexpected.
[YANG]
Vice Admiral Ulanhu.
I'm glad to see
you're looking so well.
[ULANHU]
That depends on your definition.
I'm not sure "well" properly
conveys our problems.
[YANG]
Speaking of.
I was just wondering how your
food reserves were holding out?
[ULANHU] We should have enough
to last us for another week.
If we don't receive
more before then,
we'll have no choice
but to requisition.
[ULANHU] Scratch that. There's
no point in mincing words.
We'll have to loot supplies
from the occupied territory.
[ULANHU] Real great "liberating
army" we turned out to be, huh?
[YANG] I've given
it some thought,
and I have an idea
concerning the matter.
[ULANHU] Retreat? Before we
even exchange the first fire?
[YANG] While we still have
reserves, yes.
The enemy is biding their time,
waiting for us to completely
drain our supplies
and starve as a result.
[ULANHU] In other words, they're
waiting for the right moment
before they shift
to the offensive.
[YANG] And they'll
most likely hit us
with everything they've got.
They have the home
field advantage,
plus their supply
lines will be shorter.
We're in the heart of
enemy territory here.
[ULANHU] True, however,
if all the fleets withdrew
in a chaotic manner,
we would just end up inviting
the enemy to attack us.
Which would make
matters a whole lot worse
than they currently are.
[YANG] We would have to be fully
prepared to counterattack.
That is absolutely essential.
Right now, we can
still put up a fight,
but it'll be too late once
our troops are starving.
The best option is to retreat in
an orderly fashion while we can.
[ULANHU]
You have my attention.
[YANG] If the enemy interprets
our withdrawal as a total rout,
and then decides to
come charging after us,
that could work in our favor.
[YANG] We'll have several
possible ways to fight back
if they pursue us.
On the other hand, if they think
it's too early for a retreat
or that it's a trap,
that's fine, too.
[YANG] We may be able
to withdraw unscathed.
The odds are not high as it is,
but each passing day we
wait here, they only get lower.
[YANG]
From where I'm standing,
this is the best
possible option.
We need to retreat from here
as quickly as possible.
[ULANHU] I understand,
and I trust that
your intuition is correct.
We'll begin preparations
for withdrawal immediately.
[YANG]
I'm glad.
[ULANHU] But, have you
considered the best way
of informing command
and the rest of the fleets?
[YANG] I intend to put a call in
to Admiral Bewcock after this.
I'll try to convince him to
contact Iserlohn since I have
a feeling his word would
carry more weight than if
I went to the top with the idea.
[ULANHU]
Very well.
Let's work together to make this
happen as fast as we can.
[PATRICHEV] I wholly agree
with your proposal.
[MURAI] I have no
objections to it either.
[WALTER]
An excellent decision, as usual.
[YANG] Gentlemen.
Flattery will get you nowhere.
[FREDERICA giggles]
[SOLDIER 11D]
Urgent report!
A revolt has broken out
in the territory occupied
by the Eighth Fleet!
It's a massive uprising!
[CROWD yelling]
[MAN 11C]
Hey! There's food over there!
[MAN 11D]
Do you know how to use a gun?
[MAN 11E]
Yeah!
[SOLDIER 11E]
Put the firearm down!
Refuse and I will shoot!
[MAN 11F]
That one's next!
[SOLDIER 11E] How did
things go downhill so fast?
[gun clicks]
[BOY 11A whimpers]
[SOLDIER 11E gasps]
[YANG] What a tragedy
this turned out to be.
[FREDERICA] There's no way
we can build mutual trust
with the people. Not now.
[YANG] Yeah. The enemy
got between us
and the Empire's people.
A smart but brutal strategy.
[YANG] Even if I knew it
would guarantee us victory,
I could never bring myself
to be this thorough.
[YANG] Well done indeed,
Count Lohengramm.
[YANG] Put me through to
Admiral Bewcock's vessel.
[FREDERICA]
Yes, sir.
[NARRATOR] Bewcock accepted
Yang's proposal to withdraw,
saying he would push for
a retreat to Iserlohn.
In order to do so,
he requested correspondence
with Supreme Commander Lobos.
[BEWCOCK] What's taking
him so long to respond?
[FALK]
Admiral Bewcock.
What is it that
I can help you with?
[BEWCOCK]
I asked for an appointment
with the Supreme Commander.
Don't stick your nose
where it doesn't belong.
[FALK] All communications
with the Fleet Admiral
will be conducted through me.
What is the nature
of your request?
[BEWCOCK] I have no interest
in speaking with you.
[FALK] Well, then I'm afraid
I cannot connect you with him.
[BEWCOCK]
And why is that?
[FALK]
No matter how high your rank,
you are still required
to comply with regulations.
So, shall I end
this transmission?
[BEWCOCK] All the fleet
commanders on the front line
want to withdraw immediately.
I wish to obtain the
consent of Admiral Lobos
in respect to this matter.
[FALK]
You mean retreat?
I'd expect this
from Admiral Yang,
but not from the
brave Admiral Bewcock.
You would withdraw before
the fighting even starts?
Surely not.
[BEWCOCK]
Spare me your snide remarks.
We wouldn't be in this mess if
you people hadn't come up with
such a careless deployment
strategy in the first place.
Why don't you try assuming
a little responsibility?
[FALK] If I were in your shoes,
I would never retreat.
This is our chance to
slaughter the Imperial Navy
in one fell swoop.
Unless, that is, you're
afraid of something?
[BEWCOCK]
All right.
Then I'll trade places with you.
Expect my arrival
at Iserlohn shortly,
and you can take my place
here on the front line.
[FALK] Please don't ask for
what you know is impossible.
[BEWCOCK]
Quite the opposite.
You're the one proposing
the impossible. Meanwhile,
you don't budge from the
safe haven you're hiding in.
[FALK]
I don't understand.
Are you trying to
insult me, admiral?
[BEWCOCK] I've just grown
tired of your lofty speeches
on courage. If you want to
demonstrate your talents,
then do it by actually
achieving something.
Instead of relying
merely on cheap talk.
[BEWCOCK] Why not come here
and find out for yourself?
See whether you have what
it takes to command.
Unless you're the one who's
afraid, Commodore Falk!
[FALK gasps]
[squeals]
[SOLDIER 11F]
Hey! We've got trouble!
[SOLDIER 11G]
Commodore! Commodore Falk!
[BEWCOCK]
What the hell was that?
Is he dead?
[GREENHILL]
Vice Admiral Bewcock.
[BEWCOCK]
Chief of Staff Greenhill.
Finally someone sensible.
[GREENHILL]
I'm sorry you had to see such
an unsightly display like that.
[BEWCOCK] What exactly
happened to the Commodore?
[GREENHILL]
Well, you see,
according to our
medical officer,
whenever he experiences feelings
of frustration or failure,
they cause him
to have a seizure.
[GREENHILL] Unfortunately,
since it's brought on
by a psychological condition,
if the cause is not eliminated,
he's likely to have
more episodes like this
in the future.
[BEWCOCK] Wonderful. What do
you recommend we do about it?
[GREENHILL]
Do not defy him,
avoid making him
feel frustrated,
and, according
to the physician,
make sure that
everything goes his way.
[BEWCOCK] Please tell me
you're not being serious.
[GREENHILL] As far as
treating him is concerned,
I can only see one
natural course of action.
[BEWCOCK]
You got that right!
He should be forced to resign.
[BEWCOCK] Thirty million
Alliance soldiers have to stand
in the jaws of death in order to
cure one man-child's hysteria?
If the Empire ever
found out about this,
they'd have a field day.
[BEWCOCK] So, what do say
about this withdraw proposal?
I'll tell you right now,
the troops on the front line
are in no condition to fight,
mentally or physically.
[GREENHILL]
I must ask you to wait a bit.
We need the approval of
the Supreme Commander
before we can act.
Please understand, I can't
provide you with an answer
at this moment.
[BEWCOCK] You realize
this is an urgent matter?
I'm not trying to be rude,
but if what we need here
is the Commander's approval,
isn't the next logical step
to get him on the line?
[GREENHILL] I'm afraid
that he's unavailable.
The Commander
is currently resting.
[BEWCOCK] Huh? I'm sorry
but could you repeat that?
[GREENHILL]
Admiral Lobos is taking a nap.
He's given us strict orders
not to wake him.
There's only one exception--
If the enemy were
to begin attacking.
[GREENHILL] I will relay your
request as soon as he wakes up.
Until then, I'm asking
you to please be patient.
[growls] Very well.
I understand perfectly.
[BEWCOCK] Then as my duty
serving as frontline commander,
I have no choice but to fulfill
my obligation to my soldiers.
[BEWCOCK]
Sorry for taking up your time.
Whenever he wakes up, would you
pass along the following message
to the Supreme Commander?
Tell him that Admiral Bewcock
hopes he had pleasant dreams.
[BEWCOCK]
Signing off.
[GREENHILL]
Wait, Admiral--
[REINHARD] A fleet of supply
ships will be dispatched
to the front line from Iserlohn.
That's the enemy's lifeline.
I want you to take all the
troops that I've given to you
and obliterate it.
[REINHARD] I'll leave the
details to your own discretion.
[KIRCHEIS]
Yes, Your Excellency.
I'll be going.
[REINHARD]
Kircheis.
[REINHARD] You don't seem to
be pleased with my strategy.
[KIRCHEIS]
No, that's not true at all.
By now you
should know I can tell
what you're thinking,
so speak freely.
[KIRCHEIS] While I am aware
this plan has been devised
to guarantee our
victory. I feel...
[REINHARD] You don't agree
with an approach that puts
a burden on the people.
[REINHARD]
Just remember, this is to win.
[KIRCHEIS]
Yes. I remember.
[OBERSTEIN] While Admiral
Kircheis's fleet focuses on
wiping out the rebel's
incoming supply ships,
our navy will shift
to a major offensive.
[OBERSTEIN] In accordance
with our existing plan,
the objective is to swiftly
eliminate the entirety
of the rebel invasion force.
That concludes my briefing.
[REINHARD] Our navy will take
back the captured territory.
Furthermore, our supply
corps will provide
food to the civilians.
[REINHARD] Even if it
was necessary to counter
the rebels' invasion, it was
never my wish to force
our people to the
point of starvation.
[REINHARD] We must claim victory
in this battle and demonstrate
to every resident
of the frontier why
the Galactic Empire alone is
worthy of ruling over them.
[REINHARD] As for those
arrogant insurgents...
Let none escape death.
[REINHARD]
Mittermeyer.
[MITTERMEYER]
Sir!
[REINHARD]
Reuenthal.
[REUENTHAL]
Sir!
[REINHARD]
Bittenfeld.
[BITTENFELD]
Sir!
[REINHARD]
Kempff.
[KEMPFF]
Sir!
[REINHARD]
Mecklinger.
[MECKLINGER]
Sir!
[REINHARD]
Vahlen.
[WAHLEN]
Sir!
[REINHARD]
Lutz.
[LUTZ]
Sir!
I expect the best
from all of you!
[MEN]
Yes, sir!
[REINHARD] May the great god
Odin bestow his favor upon you.
Let's Toast, Prosit!
[MEN]
We Toast, Prosit!
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
Notice to the engine department.
Transitioning to phase three of
preparation for departure.
Traffic control reports no
threats observed in the area.
Damage control personnel, shift
observation of major sectors
to alert level two.
[ANNOUNCER 11A] No warning
signals or shutdown notices
have been given
for our departure.
Data link with the control
center is currently ongoing.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
Imperial transport authority
departure checklist
for reactor and
reactor control systems
is now complete.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
Our fleet's departure signal
has received response:
"Permission granted. Comply with
regulation departure speed."
[ANNOUNCER 11A] Brünhild is
now in in-port pilot mode,
advancing at departure speed.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These: Episode 12,
"The Verge of Death.
(Part Two)."