[REMSCHEID]
That can't be.
You're telling me those
lowlifes are orchestrating
an all-out military offensive
against the Galactic Empire?
[RUBINSKY] It seems that after
capturing the Empire's pride
and joy Iserlohn, the
Alliance has acquired
a taste for conquest.
[REMSCHEID]
Hmm.
[REMSCHEID] While it's true
that by occupying the fortress,
the rebels now have a bridgehead
into imperial territory,
surely they wouldn't be so
reckless as to launch
an invasion
immediately afterwards.
[RUBINSKY] Be that as it may,
there is no debate--the Alliance
is now drawing up plans to
conduct a large-scale attack.
[REMSCHEID]
How large-scale?
[RUBINSKY]
Roughly 30,000,000 troops.
[gasps]
[DOMINIQUE] He didn't seem
to take the news too well.
[RUBINSKY] That information
was beyond a mere
high commissioner's capacity.
He'll have no choice but to
request instruction from Odin.
[DOMINIQUE]
How malicious of you.
When you received similar
information before,
you chose to keep
it to yourself
rather than passing
it along to him.
[RUBINSKY] When Iserlohn
was going to be attacked.
I was intrigued to see how their
strategy would play out.
Besides, I never expected their
campaign to be successful.
[RUBINSKY] However,
with the fall of Iserlohn,
things are different.
The balance in this war
now favors the Alliance,
therefore we need to adjust
it back to the Empire.
[DOMINIQUE]
You enjoy this.
[RUBINSKY]
Is that how it looks?
[DOMINIQUE]
Yes.
[RUBINSKY] There are many ways
entertain and enrich life--
wine, women--but nothing
compares to using the fates
of men and nations
as chips in games
of political and
military intrigue.
[RUBINSKY] Even Machiavellian
trickery, if refined,
can achieve the level of
an artistic masterpiece.
[DOMINIQUE] Unbelievable. You're
calling yourself an artist?
[RUBINSKY] Please. I'm not the
only one who holds this view.
Anyway, I'm almost certain
the one who will be sent
to intercept the Alliance
attack will be none other than
Count Reinhard von Lohengramm.
[RUBINSKY]
I need him to win,
but not by too wide of
a margin this time.
I need both sides to
keep fighting each other,
inflicting damage,
for as long as possible.
[LICHTENLADE]
We've received word
from Count Remscheid on Fezzan.
According to him, the rebels
are planning to invade
Imperial territory.
With approximately
30,000,000 men.
[GERLACH] Thirty million?
That sounds extremely serious.
[LICHTENLADE] It could be,
but at the same time,
it might prove to
be an opportunity.
[GERLACH]
How do you mean?
[LICHTENLADE] What we need
at the present time is to fight
a battle and to win.
I'm told by the
minister of the interior
that revolutionary sentiment is
growing among the commoners.
[LICHTENLADE] They're starting
to figure out Iserlohn
is no longer in our control.
We must defeat the rebels
and restore the dignity
of the Imperial household.
[GERLACH] I doubt anyone
wants the job more than
the golden brat,
so why not offer it to him?
[LICHTENLADE]
If he's successful,
his reputation would rise
to a whole new level,
which basically means
any room we had remaining
to oppose him would evaporate.
[LICHTENLADE] If he fails,
on the other hand,
we'll have to contend
with the rebels
under unfavorable conditions
at an extreme disadvantage.
[LICHTENLADE] Imagine a battle
in the middle of the Empire
against a horde of 30,000,000
troops high off victory.
[GERLACH]
The boy's not incompetent
and will surely
inflict causalities.
Even if the rebels
were to defeat him,
there's no way they'd emerge
from combat unscathed.
[GERLACH] We only need to be
strong enough to defend against
the enemy while they're
in a weakened state.
[LICHTENLADE]
I see.
That's all well and good
if the boy loses.
But, what if he wins instead?
[LICHTENLADE]
He'll earn the kaiser's favor
and receive credit
for another heroic feat,
growing beyond our control.
Imagine him becoming more
arrogant than he already is.
[GERLACH] Why not allow him
to continue his arrogance?
We can deal with a single
upstart anytime we please.
[LICHTENLADE]
Hmm.
[GERLACH] When the
rebels are finally gone,
that golden haired brat
will fall as well.
[GERLACH] But so long
as we're stuck with him.
I don't see why we shouldn't
make the best use of his talent.
[SITHOLE]
Let's begin.
First, there's the formation of
our expeditionary force.
To provide us with
a full breakdown,
here's the chief of logistics,
Rear Admiral Caselnes
[ALEX] Sir. To start,
the supreme commander of
the expeditionary
force will be
the Space Fleet
Commander-in-Chief.
Admiral Lassalle Lobos.
[ALEX] The chief of staff will
be Admiral Dwight Greenhill.
Vice Admiral Konev will serve
as chief of operations.
The chief of intelligence will
be Rear Admiral Birolinen.
[ALEX] And the chief
of logistics is myself
with one staff officer.
Next, I'll introduce the eight
fleets which will be added
to the force as combat units.
[ALEX] Vice Admiral Lefebvre
will command the Third Fleet.
Vice Admiral Bewcock will
command the Fifth Fleet.
Vice Admiral Hawood will
command the Seventh Fleet.
Vice Admiral Appleton will
command the Eighth Fleet.
[ALEX] Vice Admiral al-Salem
will command the Ninth Fleet.
Vice Admiral Ulanhu will
command the Tenth Fleet.
[ALEX] Vice Admiral Borodin will
command the Twelfth Fleet.
And finally, Vice Admiral
Yang will command
the Thirteenth Fleet.
[ALEX] These, plus independent
units brings the force's total
to 30,227,400 soldiers.
[overlapping chatter]
[YANG]
Thirty million.
That's about 60%
of our entire navy.
Good grief. It's overwhelming.
[YANG] Maybe the price we
paid for capturing Iserlohn
wasn't nearly high enough.
[JULIAN] Sorry, I couldn't
hear you, Admiral.
What was that?
[YANG]
Oh, nothing.
It's said a military victory has
an effect similar to a narcotic.
[YANG]
Both the press and the public,
they're openly calling for
an invasion of the Empire.
[JULIAN] I suppose
they don't want to break
the current momentum.
[YANG]
But just think about it.
If the fall of Iserlohn
had cost a thousand--
Scratch that.
If it had cost
hundreds of thousands
of our soldiers' lives.
How do you think everyone
would feel about it then?
[JULIAN]
I'm guessing...
...they wouldn't have
an appetite for war.
[YANG] But that wasn't the
way that things worked out.
They got it in their heads
victories came easy
and without consequences.
Ow.
[YANG]
If I'd known this would happen,
I would have gone
about it a different way.
[JULIAN] But the reason
Iserlohn's capture was such
a success was because you did
everything possible in order
to minimize the casualties.
[YANG] And the result of
that remarkable success
is this completely
unjustifiable expedition.
[JULIAN] What I don't understand
is why a plan as reckless
as this was even suggested
in the first place.
[YANG]
Because elections are coming up.
[JULIAN]
Huh?
[YANG]
The Alliance has had a number
of political scandals recently.
So it's in the government's
best interest to divert
the public's
attention elsewhere.
[JULIAN]
That can't be right.
[YANG] Just for the sake
of staying in office
another four years, they're
sending 30,000,000 soldiers
to the battlefield.
It's beyond me.
I can't understand that
kind of thinking at all.
[SITHOLE]
Gentlemen.
The decision to lead our
forces into Imperial territory
has been approved
by the High Council.
[SITHOLE] But, no specific plan
of action has been established
at this point.
The purpose of today's
meeting is to decide on that.
I look forward to
a lively discussion.
[FALK]
If I may, Chief.
I am Commodore Falk,
an operations staff officer.
[FALK] I believe this expedition
is the most ambitious
undertaking in the entire
history of the Alliance.
For me to be able to participate
in this campaign is,
quite frankly, the greatest
honor I could imagine.
[YANG] He must be the one
the chief was talking about.
[ULANHU] May I ask what
motivated this decision, sir?
As soldiers, we are obligated
to follow whatever orders
or deployment is asked of us.
[ULANHU] If the mission's
purpose is to strike
the very heart of the
Goldenbaum Dynasty,
it goes without saying
that we will happily depart.
[ULANHU] But before
we endeavor to undertake
such a large-scale invasion.
I would like to hear
what the strategic goal
behind this expedition is.
[LOBOS] Operations Staff
Officer, if you would.
[FALK]
Yes. With our massive force,
we'll advance deep
into enemy territory.
Our mere presence should
be enough to strike terror
into the souls of
the Imperial soldiers.
[ULANHU] Are you saying we'll
retreat without even fighting?
[FALK] I believe that we should
maintain a high degree
of flexibility and adapt to
the situation as it unfolds.
[ULANHU] I find your answer
far too abstract, Commodore
[BEWCOCK] What you're saying
is we just bumble around
haphazardly and
hope for the best?
[FALK]
Hmm.
[LOBOS]
As Commodore Falk has stated,
the scale of this mission
is unprecedented.
There's no doubt an
ambitious operation like this
will give hope to Imperial
citizens and lead
to an overthrow of their
tyrannical government.
[FALK]
Thank you, Admiral.
Brilliantly spoken.
[YANG] I'd like to hear why
the invasion has been set
for this particular time.
[FALK] For every battle there
is a moment of opportunity.
[YANG] So, in other words,
right now is the opportune time
for an offensive
against the Empire?
Is that what you're saying?
[FALK] No, Vice Admiral.
A grand offensive.
[FALK] The Imperial Navy
is in a state of confusion
and panic over the
loss of Iserlohn.
[FALK] With a gigantic
Alliance armada attacking in
a massive line under the banner
of freedom and justice.
There is no question
that this ends in anything
but victory for us.
[YANG] Problem is this
column formation takes us
too deep into enemy territory.
Advancing in a long line
will hinder communications
and supply distribution.
[YANG] Plus, the flanks
will be so thin that,
if the enemy attacks
us on the side,
they could easily
divide our forces.
[FALK] I fail to understand why
you only emphasize the risk
of us being divided.
An enemy brazen enough to enter
the middle of our formation
will be caught in a
pincer attack between
our front and rear forces.
[BEWCOCK]
Wait just a moment--
Vice Admiral Yang
brings up a valid point!
Do we want to repeat the mistake
at Astarte when we gave up
a chance at a concentrated
attack--and our fleets
were destroyed one-by-one?
[FALK] Such an idea could only
come from a noted tactician
like yourself, sir.
[BEWCOCK]
What do you mean by that?
[FALK] Strategically speaking,
if not tactically,
that battle wasn't
a defeat for the Alliance
because of what it accomplished.
[FALK] Ultimately our forces
drove away the Imperial Navy,
and thus prevented
a full-scale invasion
of the Astarte Starzone.
[BEWCOCK]
Oh, yes, quite the success.
[FALK] This operation has
a very different significance.
Instead of being on the defense,
we'll be taking the initiative,
leading an expedition
as a liberation force,
freeing people from oppression.
[ALEX]
If I may interject.
[SITHOLE]
Rear Admiral Caselnes.
[ALEX] As the logistics chief, I
have some misgivings with regard
to keeping our navy supplied
throughout this campaign.
[ALEX] Traveling in an extended
column formation on top
of managing the
territories we occupy as
a liberating force,
will quickly lead
to a shortage of provisions.
[LOBOS] Even if our
supplies are delayed a bit,
couldn't we simply have
the people of the territories
we are occupying
supply us as necessary?
[ALEX] Calculating unknown
variables and possibilities
is going to be difficult.
[LOBOS] Well, it's your job
so figure something out.
[YANG]
Excuse me.
The one commanding
the Imperial navy,
will likely be Count Lohengramm.
[YANG] Taking his
military skills into account,
when it comes to our strategy,
I think we should be formulating
a more cautious plan.
[GREENHILL]
Vice Admiral.
I understand you hold a
rather high opinion concerning
Count Lohengramm's abilities.
However, he is still young.
Even he must make mistakes.
[YANG] That may be true,
but in the end,
victory and defeat are
relative to one another.
[YANG] What I'm saying is, if we
were to make a bigger mistake
than he does,
it stands to reason
that he would win
and we would lose.
[FALK] That's nothing
more than speculation,
Vice Admiral.
To overestimate an enemy and
fear him more than necessary
is the greatest disgrace a
soldier could ever commit.
[FALK] It diminishes
your troops' morale
and negatively affects their
decision making skills
and battle performance,
which ultimately proves
beneficial to the enemy.
[BEWCOCK] The insinuation you
just made was disrespectful
and way out of line,
Commodore Falk!
[FALK]
I fail to see what you mean.
[BEWCOCK] Just because he didn't
agree with you and instead chose
to advise caution,
you have the gall to accuse him
of aiding and
abetting the enemy?
[FALK]
I was making a general statement
not directed at anyone.
I find it troublesome
you'd interpret my words
as slander against
an individual.
[FALK]
What we're doing is noble.
This expedition is about
rescuing and setting free
the 25,000,000,000 people
of the Galactic Empire,
who are suffering
under the oppression of
a tyrannical government.
[FALK] If we act as a
liberation force in the name
of the greater good,
the citizens of the Empire
will herald our
arrival with fanfare,
and cooperate with us willingly.
[YANG] What he's saying
is mere speculation.
It's a one-sided expectation.
What makes him think the
people of the Galactic Empire
desire the illusion of
freedom and equality
rather than genuine peace?
[YANG]
The idea of this expedition
was irresponsible enough,
but it's execution
is proving down right negligent.
[JULIAN] Then they shouldn't
go through with it.
[YANG]
Hmm?
[JULIAN] Even if it was
ordered by the High Council,
what they're proposing
is too reckless.
[YANG] That maybe true, but the
politicians in our government
were legitimately
elected to their offices
by 13,000,000,000 citizens.
No matter how reckless,
we can't refuse their decision
to go through with this mission.
[YANG] Not as long as we're
a free military in a country
that celebrates the
ideals of democracy.
[JULIAN]
Hmm.
[FALK] Any geographical
advantage or greater numbers
than ours, or even if they
have some new weapon
of unimaginable power, we cannot
let such things discourage us.
[SITHOLE]
I can't say I saw this coming.
I thought if we could
capture Iserlohn,
the flames of war would
subside, and yet here we are.
[SITHOLE] You could call
it just desserts as far as
I'm concerned, but I've made
a real mess for you, haven't I?
[SITHOLE]
I never thought I would say
something like this, but I'm
afraid that the best outcome
we can hope for is for
this expedition to fail
with minimal casualties.
An overwhelming defeat
would cause too much bloodshed,
but what happens
if we win instead?
The war hawks get
cocky and demand more.
Eventually ending up beyond
the control of the government
and the people.
[SITHOLE]
Soon after, riots break out,
and the country
hits rock bottom.
[SITHOLE] Search history
books and you'll find
countless civilizations
that have fallen into ruin
all because they won
a particular battle
they shouldn't have.
But I'm sure you
know all about that.
[YANG]
Yes.
[SITHOLE] Your knowledge of
the past has given you contempt
for authority and military
power, and I don't blame you.
But no nation can exist
without the presence
of both those factors.
[SITHOLE]
And since that's the case,
that power should be placed
in the hands of honest
and competent individuals,
so the state can be reined in
by reason, and not ruled by
the whims of the corrupt.
[SITHOLE]
I myself am a mere soldier.
I won't speak of politics.
However, as far as the armed
forces are concerned.
[SITHOLE]
That man, Commodore Falk.
He's not to be trusted.
[YANG grunts]
[SITHOLE] He's pushing
this operation in hopes
it leads him to a promotion.
It wouldn't surprise
me if he wants to reach
the highest rank the
military has to offer.
But at present,
his rival is too strong.
So he's acting out
of desperation to make
a name for himself.
[YANG]
I see.
[SITHOLE] You can be
exceedingly dense at times.
[YANG]
Huh?
[SITHOLE] The rival
I was referring to is you,
Vice Admiral Yang.
[YANG] I'm sorry,
but I'm not really worth
being called anyone's "rival."
[SITHOLE] It doesn't have
anything to do with
how you may
evaluate yourself.
The issue is more of a matter
of what Commodore Falk
thinks of you.
[SITHOLE]
You must have grasped something
of the man's
personality from today.
He'd rather display his
talent through eloquence
than actual accomplishments
and won't think twice
about belittling others to
make himself look better.
[SITHOLE] However, he
doesn't have as much talent
as he thinks he does.
I believe it's much too
dangerous to entrust the lives
of 30,000,000 men to him.
[SITHOLE]
I think you understand by now
why I rejected your resignation.
[SITHOLE]
It's not like I foresaw
our present circumstances,
but as a result of them,
your presence in
the military has become
even more important than before.
[YANG]
So what you're saying
is you want me to do what I can
to oppose Commodore Falk?
[SITHOLE]
Falk isn't the only one.
When you reach the highest
position in the service,
you'll be able to restrict
or remove people like him
altogether without having to
explain yourself to others.
That is the trajectory I'm
hoping your career takes.
[YANG]
First Iserlohn and now this.
I'm beginning to think
you enjoy giving me
impossible tasks, Chief.
[SITHOLE]
No one but you can do it.
[YANG] I'll always consider
myself a man of discretion.
I don't seek out
opportunities for heroics.
[YANG ] While I want to do a job
within the range of my ability.
Is still want to live
an easy life.
I don't think you could call
that a lazy way of thinking.
[SITHOLE]
I would. Incredibly lazy.
Hmph.
[YANG gasps]
[SITHOLE]
It's not much fun working hard
and seeing other
people live easy.
[SITHOLE] If I'm going
to trust you with this,
then I'll need you
to experience difficulty
in proportion to your talent.
To do otherwise would
be unfair to the both of us.
[YANG]
Unfair, huh? I'll say.
[SITHOLE] Sorry for keeping
you so late. Let's go.
[REINHARD] As I'm sure
you're all aware,
the insurgents of the frontier,
who call themselves
the Free Planets Alliance,
have hijacked and occupied
the Imperial frontline
base of Iserlohn.
[REINHARD] What you don't
know is that we have reports
the enemy is amassing
an enormous force there.
By our estimates, 200,000 ships,
and 30,000,000 troops.
[gasping]
[REINHARD] The rebels plan
to advance towards
the center of the Empire.
Once there, they will
launch an all-out attack.
[REINHARD] Obviously,
this is a troubling development.
I have been given the task of
intercepting them.
[REINHARD] I anticipate
the order at any time.
I expect you all
to fight bravely.
[REINHARD]
As for the other fleets.
They are mere puppets,
ornaments of the palace.
They can't be depended
upon for this fight.
[REINHARD] This is an
opportunity for you all
to move up in the ranks.
[MEN]
Hmph.
[REINHARD] Now, I'd like
to hear your opinions.
Tell me what you think
is the best method
for intercepting the rebels.
Hold nothing back.
[BITTENFELD] The moment
they exit the Iserlohn Corridor,
we strike them down.
It's the quickest and
most efficient method.
[MITTERMEYER]
I agree.
We can determine where
the enemy will emerge from
and then we either
strike them head-on
or form a half-encirclement
instead.
The insurgents
will turn tail and run
before they even get an inch
inside Imperial territory.
I commend your spirit, men.
However, they will be expecting
us to intercept them as soon
as they leave the corridor.
It's likely they'll
position their best men
on the front line.
And if we defeat them, the rest
may never exit that corridor.
Meaning we can't
launch an offensive.
[gasping]
An offensive?
You mean, you're not
satisfied simply forcing
the insurgents into a retreat?
Obviously.
Their foolhardiness should
be rewarded with bloodshed
in equal proportions.
What exactly are you proposing?
We will draw
the enemy in deeper.
[gasping]
Pardon, Your Excellency,
but we're to allow rebels
to enter our territory?
Correct.
Once their combat and
supply lines are stretched
to the limit, we hit them
with everything we have.
They'll be sending
60% of their forces.
We'll destroy all of them,
crippling their military might,
and the will of the rebellion.
[gasping]
[REINHARD]
Oberstein.
[OBERSTEIN]
Yes, sir.
[OBERSTEIN] Allow me
to summarize our current
combat strategy for you.
[NARRATOR]
Three months had passed since
the fall of Iserlohn Fortress.
And once again, the Galactic
Empire and the Free Planets
Alliance were preparing
their forces to meet
each other on
the field of battle.
[NARRATOR] On August 22,
of the year UC 796,
the Free Planets Alliance
expeditionary force established
its command headquarters
within Iserlohn Fortress.
Thirty million Alliance soldiers
from the capital of Heinessen
and surrounding star systems
assembled columns
of warships and set out
towards Imperial territory.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These : Episode 11,
"The Verge of Death (Part 1)."