[GIRL 9A]
It can't be true.
Are you really quitting,
Miss Edwards?
[GIRL 9B]
Can we change your mind?
--[GIRL 9B sobs]
--[GIRL 9C] Don't leave...
[GIRL 9A]
We're going to miss you...
[GIRL 9D]
Miss Edwards... [sobs] Please...
[sobbing]
[doorbell rings]
[JULIAN] Yes? Are you
looking for someone?
[JESSICA]
I'm sorry. Who are you?
[LEBELLO] There is no
delicate way to put this.
For many years, the Galactic
Empire and our Alliance
have fought this war
only to the extent
that it was
financially feasible.
[LEBELLO]
The times have changed.
Pensions for the families
of soldiers lost during
the Battle of Astarte require us
to spend ten billion annually.
[LEBELLO] In addition, feeding
the 500,000 prisoners
from Iserlohn demands
an enormous budget increase.
We have a debt
crisis on our hands.
[MAN 9A]
Are you saying our national hero
has led us to
financial distress?
[LEBELLO]
To alleviate the strain,
we've traditionally had two
options at our disposal:
either issuing more bonds
or increasing taxes.
[MAN 9B]
Raise taxes?
What did you promise
our constituents
in the last election?
[LEBELLO]
I know!
But if we continue to expand
this war any further,
it's going to bring about
our economic destruction!
[MAN 9C] If we're
not committed to winning,
then the Alliance has no future.
[LEBELLO] Perhaps the solution
is to simply stop fighting.
[MAN 9A growls]
[LEBELLO]
Admiral Yang's resourcefulness
awarded us Iserlohn Fortress.
The Imperial Navy
has lost its forward base
for invading Alliance territory.
[LEBELLO] Is this not
the ideal time to negotiate
a favorable peace treaty?
[MAN 9D] Have you
forgotten that we are at war
with an unjust and
tyrannical government?
[MAN 9C] Exactly.
How wise is it to give up
simply because it doesn't
suit us economically?
[LEBELLO growls]
[YANG]
Julian! I'm headed out.
[JULIAN]
Take care, Admiral.
[YANG]
Oh, yeah. I was just thinking.
Why don't we go out to
a restaurant tonight?
Go ahead and meet me at the
headquarters after school
lets out for the day.
[JULIAN]
Tonight? That's sudden.
[YANG] Yeah. I know,
but there's something
I need to talk to you about.
[gasps]
[YANG]
Well, see you later.
[JULIAN]
Hmm.
[SITHOLE] You want
to resign from the navy?
But you're still young,
only 30 years old.
[YANG]
Twenty-nine, actually.
[SITHOLE] Regardless,
don't you think it's
a little early to leave
your life behind?
[YANG] I feel as though I'm
doing the exact opposite.
My life took a prolonged detour,
and now it's getting
back on track.
I'm finally returning to the
life I intended to live.
[SITHOLE]
Surviving off a pension
and studying history all day?
[YANG grunts]
[SITHOLE] Unfortunately,
what the Free Planets Alliance
requires is not your
knowledge as a historian
but rather your skill
as a tactician.
It's a gift.
And we need it desperately.
[SITHOLE] It sounds as
though you're saying capturing
Iserlohn Fortress was
more than enough for you.
[YANG]
I wouldn't put it that way.
[SITHOLE]
Look. You should know
the High Council
is meeting today.
They're considering dispatching
troops to the Empire.
[SITHOLE] There's a new
strategy in the works.
The plan is to use Iserlohn as
a bridgehead for an invasion.
[YANG]
That's not what we intended.
It's the opposite, in fact!
[SITHOLE]
Hmm?
[YANG] It was the Defense
Committee Chairman's idea,
wasn't it?
[SITHOLE] No, the proposal
came from within the military.
A young officer from
the planning division
had brought it directly to the
National Defense Committee.
[gasps]
[SITHOLE] I have faith that
the High Council will reach
an intelligent decision
on the matter.
[YANG]
You have more faith than I do.
Well, whatever decision
they arrive at,
I'm glad to report that
it won't be involving me.
[SITHOLE] And what's to become
of the Thirteenth?
That's your fleet to command,
and it's only recently
been formed.
Once you're retired,
what happens to them?
[LOUIS] Human resources
that should be devoted to
social development are instead
being diverted to the military.
I, for one, find
this disconcerting.
[LOUIS]
Our investments in education
and vocational training have
been continually reduced.
Skill levels among our
labor force are dwindling,
as evidenced by the tripling of
workplace accidents last term.
[LOUIS]
Which brings me to my proposal.
I would like for 4,000,000
technicians as well as
transportation and
communications personnel
currently serving in the
military to be returned
to the private sector.
[LOUIS] That number
is the absolute minimum.
[TRUNICHT] You're asking
for the impossible.
Imagine if we removed that many
people from the rear services.
Our military would
collapse on itself.
[LOUIS] So the Defense
Committee chairman says,
but at the rate we're going,
our economy and society
will implode long before
the military ever does.
[LEBELLO]
In short, now is the time
to let our citizens rebuild.
To force the people to sacrifice
any more would be a violation
of our democratic principles.
They cannot shoulder
the burden any longer.
[WINDSOR] There's no reason
to pander to the selfishness
of citizens who don't understand
our great and noble purpose.
Name a time in history when
anything of significance
was achieved without sacrifice.
[LEBELLO] It would seem
a great number of people
have begun questioning if
they've already given too much,
Councilwoman.
[WINDSOR]
Some things must be done,
no matter how great the cost.
[LEBELLO]
That's not a political argument!
[WINDSOR] Our duty is to
defeat the Galactic Empire.
To rescue all of humanity
and spare future generations
from the threat of tyranny
and oppression.
[WINDSOR] I wonder how we can
claim to be walking the path
of righteousness if we forget
our greater purpose
altogether in exchange for
some cheap humanitarianism?
[LEBELLO] Your heroics at
the expense of our citizens
is the only thing I
find to be cheap!
[LOUIS]
Settle down.
[LEBELLO]
How can--
[SANFORD] It appears we need
another break before continuing,
but if I could have
your attention first,
there's something
I'd like you to see.
[SANFORD] This is the public's
approval rating for the council.
It may not come as a surprise.
[SANFORD]
We're at 31.9%.
That's certainly
not a good number.
And now, let's take a look
at our disapproval rating.
[LOUIS]
Fifty-six point two percent.
[whispering]
[SANFORD]
If nothing changes,
it's highly unlikely we'll
be re-elected next year.
I can see us being caught
between the pacifist faction
and hardliners and
losing our majority.
[SANFORD]
But it's not hopeless.
I've had the computer
run some numbers,
and if we can secure a decisive
victory against the Empire
within the next 100 days,
the data indicates
that our approval
ratings should increase by
a staggering 15 percentage
points as a direct result.
[LEBELLO]
I can't be hearing this right.
You want to escalate the war
so you all can be re-elected?
[WINDSOR]
Chairman.
Let's put the military's
proposal up for a vote.
[COUNCILMEN]
Agreed.
[LEBELLO]
Wait a minute!
We don't have
the right to do this!
The authority to dispatch troops
isn't a tool for this Council
to throw around,
just for the purpose
of maintaining political power!
[WINDSOR] My, that's quite
a righteous statement.
[SANFORD]
Eight in favor. Three opposed.
With a majority in favor,
it is hereby confirmed
that our forces will invade
the Galactic Empire.
[MAN 9A]
Well. I didn't see that coming.
The Defense Committee
Chairman himself
voted against the measure.
[TRUNICHT]
Above all, I'm a patriot,
but that certainly
doesn't mean I'll advocate
for the use of force
in every situation.
I would like the record to
state that I was opposed
to this mobilization
of our forces.
[sighs]
[WALTER]
Well, hello, Admiral.
[YANG]
Captain.
[WALTER] You wouldn't
happen to be here tendering
your resignation now, would you?
[YANG]
Guilty.
But that's not to say I expected
Chief Sithole to accept
my retirement letter with one
hand and willingly give me
my severance pay with the other.
[WALTER] You do realize
the military's never going
to let you go, right?
[YANG]
Hmm.
[WALTER]
But seriously.
I would prefer to see a man of
your caliber stay in the navy
rather than become a civilian.
[WALTER] You excel at
appraising situations and on top
of that, you're lucky.
I may not be hailed for
distinguished service under
your leadership, but I do have
a good chance of surviving.
[WALTER] You see, I've already
made up my mind to close
the curtains on this life
by dying of old age.
[WALTER] I plan on living
to be about 150 years,
lying on my death bed
while listening to my grandkids
and great-grandkids crying
for joy at the thought
of finally being rid of me.
[WALTER] The whole
dying-a-heroic-death-in-
the-midst-of-battle
thing isn't my style.
D'you think you could
find it in your heart
to help me live that
long, Admiral?
[WAITER 9A]
I apologize, gentlemen.
We're completely booked.
[YANG]
I'm sorry, Julian.
I guess we should
have made a reservation.
Let's keep looking.
[FREDERICA]
Admiral.
[YANG gasps]
[YANG]
Lieutenant?
[FREDERICA] I do own more
outfits besides my uniform.
My father has invited
you to sit at our table
if you'd care to join us.
[YANG]
Admiral Greenhill is here?
Oh, we couldn't.
[FREDERICA]
What do you say?
You must be hungry,
right, Julian?
Yes.
Vice Admiral Yang.
It's, uh, rear admiral, sir.
You'll make vice admiral
by next week at the latest.
So you might as well go ahead
and get used to people
addressing you by your new
title, don't you think?
[JULIAN]
That's amazing!
Is that what you wanted to
talk to me about tonight?
[YANG]
Uhh...
[GREENHILL] And this
young man must be Julian,
the honor student I've
heard so much about.
[JULIAN]
Sir. Nice to meet you.
[GREENHILL]
Have a seat. Please.
And if I'm not mistaken, didn't
you also win the gold medal
this year for most
points scored in
the junior division of flyball?
A master of
academics and sports.
[YANG]
Is all of that true, Julian?
[JULIAN]
Yes.
[FREDERICA] You live
under the same roof as him
and you're still the
last one to know.
Julian here is something
of a local celebrity.
[YANG sighs]
[GREENHILL]
Your recent achievements have
had consequences no one
could have anticipated.
[GREENHILL] The capture
of Iserlohn has divided
the population into pro
and anti-war factions,
and the disputes between
them have grown
quite intense as of late.
[YANG] I hope it
doesn't escalate beyond
the debate stage.
[GREENHILL]
Unfortunately, some have taken
a rather violent approach
when dealing with those
who are opposed to the war.
[YANG] Such as the Patriotic
Knight Corps, let's say?
[GREENHILL]
Those idiots?
They're hardly a threat,
and I refuse to waste breath
acknowledging their existence.
This gelatin salad
is to die for.
[YANG]
Yes, I agree.
[BOLTIK] Also, regarding
the Santa Cruz Line,
one of the largest interstellar
transport companies
operated by the Alliance.
Our shares have reached 41.9%.
[BOLTIK] Ownership is
divided among 20 people,
so they haven't realized
what's happening.
As such, we've surpassed
the largest shareholder,
a state-owned
investment company.
[RUBINSKY]
Excellent.
But we shouldn't rest until
we've acquired more than 50%.
[BOLTIK]
Yes.
[RUBINSKY]
What about the Empire?
[BOLTIK] We've made the
decision to invest heavily
in the agricultural development
of the 7th frontier starzone.
[RUBINSKY] What percentage
are we contributing?
[BOLTIK] Three of our
government-owned shell companies
control 84% in total.
A monopoly, essentially.
[RUBINSKY]
Well done.
[BOLTIK] So, you won't be
returning to your residence?
[RUBINSKY groans]
No. I will.
[BOLTIK]
Very good, sir.
I'll see you when you arrive.
[DOMINIQUE]
Sounds like it's going well.
[RUBINSKY]
Hmm...
There's a shared mindset in both
the Alliance and the Empire.
That war is nothing
more than two fleets
shooting at one
another in space.
[RUBINSKY]
But that's not true.
Only one thing
rules the universe.
[DOMINIQUE]
Money.
[RUBINSKY] The Dominion
of Fezzan owns nearly half
the war bonds
issued by both sides.
[RUBINSKY]
Soon, we'll financially control
the entire universe.
We own a piece of every corner
where humans have set foot.
[DOMINIQUE]
Oh, without a doubt.
Just as long as another
Rudolf doesn't come along
and decide to create
a new Galactic Empire.
[RUBINSKY]
A new Galactic Empire?
Not bad. You have
some interesting ideas.
[RUBINSKY] Going back
to work now, Dominique?
[DOMINIQUE]
Please enjoy your stay.
[RUBINSKY] I don't understand
why you continue to perform
even though you aren't
in need of money.
[DOMINIQUE] I don't
remember selling my freedom.
[RUBINSKY]
A new Galactic Empire, huh?
[YANG] Thank you
for letting us join you
for dinner tonight, sir.
[GREENHILL]
It's been a delightful evening.
By the way, Vice Admiral.
Have you given any
thought to getting married
--and setting down?
--[FREDERICA gasps]
[YANG]
Not right now.
I'll think about it more
when peace arrives.
I had a friend
who died in battle
and left behind his fiancée.
[GREENHILL]
I'm so sorry.
[NEWS ANCHOR 9A] And now,
more on the representative
who won this past week's
election on Terneuzen.
Jessica Edwards
will be delivering
her inaugural speech
later today.
Edwards
is said to be the vanguard
of the anti-war movement.
[YANG]
Jessica?
[JULIAN]
Wait. I've seen her before!
That's the woman
who came to the house
while you were away
about a month ago!
[JULIAN] She said she
was an old friend of yours.
[NEWS ANCHOR 9A]
Edwards' nomination
only further emboldens
the movement.
[JULIAN]
Is there some kind of emergency?
[YANG]
I have no clue.
Wait inside the car.
[OFFICER 9A] I don't believe it.
You're Rear Admiral Yang Wen-li!
I never imagined I'd would get
to meet our national hero.
[YANG] That aside,
what's going on here?
[OFFICER 9A] I'm sorry. It
seems the Urban Traffic Control
Center's computer system
has malfunctioned.
[YANG]
How come?
[OFFICER 9A] I don't have
all the details myself,
but I hear it was human
error involving data input.
Anyway, just about every
workplace is short
on experienced
people these days.
[OFFICER 9A] I suppose
it shouldn't come as
a complete surprise.
[YANG] The war's affecting us in
ways we never even imagined.
[OFFICER 9A]
They're working on a fix,
but traffic systems in
this district will be down
for some time. I'd say
the next four hours, sir.
[YANG]
At the minimum?
[OFFICER 9A]
Yes. I know it's inconvenient.
[JULIAN] What do you think
we should do, Admiral?
[YANG]
Nothing we can do but walk.
[JULIAN]
Right!
[YANG] It's good exercise.
We'll be back in an hour.
[OFFICER 9A]
Wait a minute!
I can't allow the hero of
Iserlohn to walk home.
I'll send an aircar
to pick you up!
[YANG]
No need to be dramatic.
I can't be the only one who
receives special treatment.
[OFFICER 9A]
But, sir!
[YANG]
Let's go, Julian.
[JULIAN]
Aye-aye, sir!
[OFFICER 9A gasps]
[YANG]
So, Jessica.
She didn't leave
any message for me?
[JULIAN] No. But she did seem
a little anxious when we spoke.
I kind of got the impression
there was something on her mind
she wanted to discuss
with you in private.
[JESSICA]
I see. Really.
So Yang adopted...
I'm sorry. I dropped
by without notice.
[JULIAN]
You're fine.
So, is there a message
you wanted me to relay?
[JESSICA]
No need, but thank you.
It wasn't anything
too important.
I'll be on my way.
[JULIAN] Oh. Well then,
please take an umbrella
[JESSICA]
Tell me something.
Do you want to become
a soldier when you grow up?
[JULIAN]
I do.
[JESSICA]
Right.
[JULIAN]
But it may not happen.
The admiral keeps telling
me that we'll have peace
by the time I'm an adult.
[JESSICA gasps]
[JULIAN] Could I at least get
your name to pass on to him?
[JESSICA] You can just tell him
that an old friend stopped by.
[JULIAN] In the end,
she just smiled and said,
"Please take care
of the admiral."
[YANG] It looks like you made up
your mind.
[JULIAN]
Admiral.
[YANG]
What is it?
[JULIAN] For a second, we were
both looking at the same star.
There. That big blue one.
[YANG]
Hmph.
[JULIAN]
Do you know what it's called?
[YANG] Its name is right
on the tip of my tongue.
Let's see...
[YANG] Julian, you know
you don't have to look
at the same star as me.
[JULIAN]
Huh?
[YANG]
Hmm.
[YANG] I believe every
person should take hold
of their own star,
no matter how unlucky
it may prove to be.
[JESSICA]
I have made my...
I have made my decision.
I will never again pretend that
I didn't see and didn't hear.
I'm finished being silent.
[JESSICA] That's the reason
I'm standing here today.
That's my purpose.
[JESSICA] It wasn't an easy
choice, becoming a politician.
As a simple teacher, I had my
doubts whether I was qualified
to run for office.
[JESSICA] But my mind is set,
and I have made a promise.
A promise to my late fiancé,
who sadly perished
in the Battle of Astarte.
[JESSICA] I used to think that
"history" was just "the past."
The only thing that
separated the two
was an extra coating of dust.
But I was mistaken.
[JESSICA]
The truth is...
...history is something we
create as we live our lives
in the present.
It doesn't belong only to the
names printed in history books.
[JESSICA] It's something each
and every one of us alive today
must strive to create.
Because every step we take--
pushes us further
into the future!
[applause]
[JESSICA] Our shared history up
to this point has been dominated
by the specter of war.
[JESSICA]
Where we go...
Whether we allow
this to continue...
That's a decision each of us
has to make on our own.
[JESSICA] Yes, there are
people who are adamant,
claiming we're
fighting a just war,
and that throwing these
lives away in the name
of justice is a noble act.
[JESSICA]
I ask you. What is justice?
And what's the meaning
of a noble act?
[JESSICA]
It's up to us.
We must decide on our own.
You who watch family members
leave for the battlefield.
You and I who've lost loved
ones on that battlefield.
[JESSICA] What I want,
is for those who hide away
somewhere safe and never
lose anything or feel pain,
to never again make
those important decisions
for the rest of us!
[JESSICA] Above all, I
want to keep asking those
in positions of
authority this question:
"Where are you
at this very moment,
while you send soldiers
to their deaths?
Where are you right now?
And what are you doing to help?"
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These: Episode 10,
"Interlude."