[YANG] What a tragedy
this turned out to be.
[FREDERICA] There's no way
we can build mutual trust
with the people. Not now.
[YANG] Even if I knew it
would guarantee us victory.
I could never bring myself
to be this thorough.
[YANG] Well done indeed,
Count Lohengramm.
[REINHARD] Our navy will take
back the captured territory.
Furthermore, our supply
corps will provide food
to the civilians.
[REINHARD] As for those
arrogant insurgents.
Let none escape death.
[REINHARD] I expect
the best from all of you.
[REINHARD]
Let's toast, Prosit!
[MITTERMEYER]
We toast, Prosit!
[BITTENFELD]
[SOLDIER 12A]
Enemy cargo fleet located.
They're moving along the
standard Imperial route
within possible warp range.
[SCOTT]
That's checkmate.
[speaker buzzes]
[NIKOLSKY] Sir, report to
the bridge immediately.
[SCOTT]
Hmm?
[SCOTT] What is it?
Did something happen
on the front line?
[NIKOLSKY] Hate to break it to
you, but we are the front line!
Just take a look at
what's headed our way!
[SOLDIER 12B]
Ships approaching!
Looks like an Imperial fleet!
There's eight--No, ten.
Wait, 15. Over 20,000 ships!
[SCOTT]
Impossible!
[SCOTT] They sent such
a huge force against
a mere supply convoy?
[SCOTT]
That doesn't make sense.
[SOLDIER 12C]
Message from Admiral Kircheis.
The enemy's supply
convoy is destroyed.
[SOLDIER 12C] The only
damage sustained on our side
was a single ship.
[CREW murmuring]
[OBERSTEIN]
We have succeed in cutting off
the enemy's supply line,
Your Excellency.
[REINHARD]
Connect me with my admirals.
[REINHARD] We are moving forward
with the rest of our plan.
Strike the rebels
with full force.
[MEN]
Sir!
[CHEN] We've been unable
to contact to the patrol ship
since it notified us that the
enemy fleet was located.
[ULANHU]
They're coming.
I want you to send a
message to headquarters
and all fleet
admirals immediately.
Tell them we have
encountered Imperial forces.
[CHEN]
Sir!
[ULANHU] If only we had made up
our minds to withdraw sooner,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
[ULANHU]
Send word to every ship!
Prepare for fleet action!
[BITTENFELD]
Heh.
[CHEN]
The enemy has begun firing.
Most likely from a blind spot
behind the planet.
[ULANHU] Unity trumps
geographical advantage.
--[CHEN] Hmm.
--[explosions]
[ULANHU] The Thirteenth
will be here soon enough
to bail us out of this mess.
We're talking about
Miracle Yang.
Victory is guaranteed.
[NARRATOR] At that same time,
the Imperial Navy was attacking
each fleet of the Alliance's
expeditionary force separately.
[AL-SALEM] Go full
defensive and retreat, now!
[MORTON]
Sir!
[BEWCOCK] Did we miss
our window for a withdrawal?
With our line
stretched out so far,
there's not a chance
we can keep it supplied.
At this rate, we won't be able
to hold out much longer.
[FREDERICA]
Message from Admiral Ulanhu.
"At 1607 standard
Alliance time,
my fleet will engage with
the Imperial forces."
[YANG]
So it's finally started.
[MURAI] The Thirteenth's
withdrawal from
the occupied territory
is complete.
Shall we move
out of the area, sir?
[YANG] We're going to
stay right where we are.
[gasping]
[YANG] Due to the heavy
gases in this starzone,
the range for optical weapons
is going to be diminished.
We'll confuse the enemy with
close combat and watch for
our chance to break out.
[sighing]
[YANG] Have the Spartanians
on stand by, ready to launch.
[MURAI]
Yes sir.
[POPLIN] This is our first
battle since joining
the Thirteenth, so let's
put on a good show for 'em.
[HUGHES] I was wondering
if we'd get to do anything
before shipping back home.
[SHAKELY]
I could use the workout.
I was starting to
feel outta shape.
[KONEV]
Hmph.
[POPLIN] Well, fellas, ready to
show everyone what the guys from
the 88 Independent
Air Combat unit can do?
[POPLIN]
Let's get this over with fast.
Keep the champagne
on ice for us.
[SOLDIER 12D]
You know we don't have any.
You'll be lucky to get
water at this point.
[POPLIN]
Heh. Man, what a buzzkill.
[SOLDIER 12D]
Permission to launch.
[POPLIN]
Roger. We're out.
You're mine!
[POPLIN]
I missed? I never miss!
[HUGHES]
Why isn't the output increasing?
Damn it!
[HUGHES grunting]
[POPLIN]
Hughes!
Margin of error is seven,
no, eight degrees?
[HUGHES gasps]
[POPLIN gasps]
[SHAKELY]
No, the airframe is...
[KONEV]
Shakely, don't push it.
Return to base at once.
[SHAKELY]
They've locked on to me!
[POPLIN growls]
[POPLIN] My firing line was
off nine to 12 degrees,
you bastard!
Lasers don't work out there,
so with my machine gun useless,
I might as well have
been fighting unarmed!
[TODA]
I'm sorry.
You'll have to forgive me if
the maintenance was faulty,
but ever since our supplies
were cut off, us mechanics
haven't had anything
to eat or drink.
[TODA] Unlike you and the
rest of the Spartanians.
[gasps]
[POPLIN] Fair enough.
I apologize for being rude.
I need my machine gun
adjusted right away.
Can you do that for me?
[KONEV] Both Hughes and
Shakely were killed.
It's going to be
a vicious battle.
We'll be counting on all of you!
[POPLIN] As soon as maintenance
is done, we're going back out
[CREW]
Sir!
[TODA] I'll calibrate
it right this time.
[POPLIN gasps]
[TODA] So please, Lieutenant,
win this one for us.
[POPLIN]
Sure.
We're gonna show those
Imperials we're a force
to be reckoned with,
don't you worry.
After all, we're the Thirteenth
Fleet Air Combat Unit.
[SOLDIER 12E]
The enemy has fired
a high-output energy blast!
Impact Imminent!
[SOLDIER 12F] Destruction
of enemy ship confirmed.
Long-range attack successful.
[LUTZ] Eighty percent of their
ships are already immobilized.
[LUTZ]
Hmm...
[SOLDIERS yell]
[BORODIN sighs]
[BEWCOCK] I want all of
our ships to move forward
to the front and
go full defensive!
Deploy all cruisers taking
refuge at the rear
to both flanks and fire!
Hit them from all directions!
[BEWCOCK]
Hold formation and don't panic!
We have to keep
our escape route open!
[BEWCOCK] This opponent
doesn't look like one
who'll give up victory easily.
[REUENTHAL] Well,
at least they're providing
a challenge for me.
[SOLDIER 12I] Imperial fleet
approaching, starboard side!
The enemy is within
physical firing range!
[MORTON]
They're what?
How's it possible their datalink
is functioning already?
It's too soon!
[AL-SALEM] It couldn't
be. Is that you, Gale Wolf?
[MITTERMEYER] Don't be impatient
and get too close to them.
They might counter when
we're least expecting it.
[MITTERMEYER] But then again,
that's assuming the rebels
have someone in charge
whose fleet management
is actually worth a damn.
[SOLDIER 12L] The enemy fleet
is leaving the theater!
[SOLDIER 12K]
We've lost 90% of our men.
Organized battle is no longer
a possibility, Admiral.
[HAWOOD] We were a flagship,
and yet we were discarded
without being so
much as a threat.
[EUGEN] We have taken control
of this sector of space.
Dominion is entirely ours.
[BITTENFELD] So tell me,
Captain, what's preventing us
from annihilating
them altogether?
[BITTENFELD]
Close in.
[EUGEN gasps]
[BITTENFELD]
Be thorough about it.
[EUGEN]
Yes, sir.
[CHEN] We only have about
a thousand ships left
that can fight and
that's including this one.
We can't continue this battle
any longer, Admiral.
[CHEN] The only choices we have
are surrendering and fleeing.
[ULANHU] That's certainly
a disgraceful pair of options.
Right? Surrendering isn't
my style, so we'll flee.
[ULANHU] Tell me, are there
any fleet commodores among
the remaining ships who
haven't been killed yet?
[CHEN] Commodore Attenborough
is still alive.
[ULANHU] I'm going to open up an
escape route for us, Commodore.
You will lead any ships that can
no longer fight in a retreat,
do you understand?
[ATTENBOROUGH]
Admiral Ulanhu, sir.
[ULANHU] No arguments.
I'm counting on you.
[SOLDIER 12L]
Bearing: 2 o' clock.
All ships, maximum battle speed!
[ULANHU]
Follow us, and stay close!
[BITTENFELD]
What?
[CHEN] Brilliant! The
escape route, it's opened up!
[grunting]
[ULANHU]
What's the status of our allies?
[CHEN] About half of
our remaining ships
got through safely.
[ULANHU]
I see.
[NARRATOR]
After a fierce offensive from
the Imperial Navy, what was left
of the Alliance expeditionary
force found itself at an
overwhelming disadvantage.
However...
[POPLIN growls]
[NARRATOR]
Amidst the destruction,
there was one exception.
Yang's Thirteenth Fleet.
[LUBITSCH] The enemy air
combat unit's torpedo attack
did immense damage.
We won't be able
to hold formation.
[KEMPFF grunts] Are you
saying we should give in
to the rebel forces'
insolent tactics?
[LUBITSCH] I'm saying we
should deal with the situation
before it ends in disgrace.
[KEMPFF] Obviously we
should pull back and regroup
so we can attack further!
[KEMPFF] Prepare for the
enemy's pursuit and withdraw
all our ships immediately!
[SOLDIER 12M]
The enemy fleet is retreating!
[PATRICHEV] Will we take this
opportunity to pursue them?
[YANG]
We won't.
Even if we were to push
ourselves and win here,
it wouldn't stop the enemy from
having the overall advantage.
There's only one course of
action we can take right now.
[YANG]
All ships, retreat.
[FREDERICA]
Sir!
[NARRATOR] Having escaped
Admiral Kempff's Imperial fleet,
Yang Wen-Li's Thirteenth
continued their retreat,
setting a course to
return to headquarters
at Iserlohn Fortress.
[FREDERICA] Report from
the lead patrol ship.
Multiple vessels have
been sighted ahead
with no call signs detected.
[PATRICHEV] It's probably
Vice Admiral Hawood and
the Seventh Fleet being
that they're assigned
to that sector.
[FREDERICA] There are too many
ships for it to be the Seventh.
[YANG]
How big of a force?
[FREDERICA] Roughly three
times the size of our fleet.
[YANG]
That's the enemy.
[MURAI] We have to assume
Admiral Hawood and the rest
of the Seventh have
already been defeated.
[SOLDIER 12N]
Report, sir!
We've lost communication
with the patrol ship!
[WALTER] Sounds to me
like it was captured.
[YANG sighs]
[SOLDIER 12O]
Rebel fleet located.
They number approximately
ten thousand!
[VOLKER] Comparing it
to the report submitted
by Admiral Kempff, they match.
It's most likely the Thirteenth.
[BERGENGRÜN]
Under Yang Wen-li?
[REINHARD]
A clever man.
He just might be the sort of
adversary you spoke of earlier.
[VOLKER] There's no way
we can miss the opportunity
to attack him.
All ships, maximum battle speed.
[SOLDIER 12O]
Command to all ships.
Maximum battle speed.
[MURAI] We have no choice now
except to engage with them.
[YANG] Looks like it's time to
put our plan into motion.
[GREENHILL] Since we received
word that they had encountered
the Imperials, none of
the information gathered
makes any sense.
[GREENHILL] The Third, Seventh,
Tenth and Twelfth Fleets
have so far been unable
to communicate with us.
[GREENHILL] The Fifth, Eighth,
Ninth, and Thirteenth Fleets
all still appear to be alive
and well, but we're unable
to get detailed reports
from any of them yet.
[LOBOS]
Hmm...
[LOBOS] The High Council has
been clear with their desires.
This expedition cannot
simply end with a loss
for the Alliance forces.
[GREENHILL]
What are you suggesting?
[LOBOS] We'll reorganize what's
left of the scattered fleets
and meet the enemy's attack
with our own offensive.
Relay the message
to the entire navy.
[GREENHILL gasps]
[LOBOS]
Is something wrong?
[GREENHILL] Well I was just
wondering if we have enough
forces left at the front line
for that kind of maneuver.
[GREENHILL]
Even if we did reorganize,
the enemy still outnumbers us.
So, rather than
improve the situation,
we would suffer even
greater losses.
[LOBOS] Tell the navy
to rendezvous at
the Amritsar Starzone
and prepare for battle.
[GREENHILL]
You're joking!
[LOBOS]
That was an order.
[GREENHILL growls]
[MURAI] The enemy is pushing us
back with mainstay equipment
in superior numbers, all while
supplying their forces
from the rear and
hitting our ships
with uninterrupted firepower.
[YANG sighs]
[YANG] We should use
a cautious strategy. Afterall...
I hear Count Lohengramm has
himself a brilliant subordinate.
[FREDERICA] An urgent coded
message from headquarters.
[YANG]
Read it to me.
[FREDERICA]
"Concentrate forces at point A
in the Amritsar Starzone on
the 14th of the current month.
"You are to cease combat
at once and change course"
[BEWCOCK]
Little late for that!
If retreat were that easy, then
we would have done it by now.
[YANG]
He says that like it's simple.
[MURAI]
What will you do, Admiral?
[YANG] Reorganize the fleet
into line-ahead formation,
deploy a group of dreadnought
battleships at the rear,
and create a diversion while we
find a way to leave the front.
[YANG] Our goal now is
to turn the fleet around
and proceed towards
Amritsar to regroup.
I want you to view
leaving the front as
the only tactical objective
we need to accomplish.
[YANG]
Given our limited options,
the enemy has probably already
guessed what we're going to do.
[WALTER]
If this doesn't work,
I doubt that anything
else we try will.
[MURAI] There's no denying
it's the best option available
to us at the moment.
[PATRICHEV]
Yes, I agree.
[YANG] The enemy has
three times our numbers,
we'll almost certainly
suffer damages ourselves,
but I want us to minimize
them as best we can.
[YANG] I'm going to be
counting on all of you.
[GROUP]
Hmm.
[inaudible]
[MURAI] We're sustaining
heavy causalities,
the likes of which
we've never seen.
[PATRICHEV] But we're
almost out of the weeds.
[alarm sounds]
[SOLDIER 12P] Multiple
incoming ships detected.
--[MURAI] More ships?
--[PATRICHEV] What.
You mean the enemy had
a detached force?
[SOLDIER 12N]
We've ID'd their call sign!
[YANG]
Hmm.
[SOLDIER 12N] It's Admiral
Hawood and the Seventh Fleet!
[BERGENGRÜN]
Look.
[HAWOOD] We'll provide
backup for the Thirteenth Fleet
as they withdraw!
Don't worry about how much
energy we've got left!
[HAWOOD] Hit 'em
with everything we've got!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[HAWOOD] Don't you make the
wrong choice, Yang Wen-li.
[PATRICHEV] This is our
chance to launch an attack!
[YANG]
Continue with the retreat.
[PATRICHEV]
They'll be killed!
[WALTER] There's no denying
it's a tough decision to make,
but it is the right one.
[OBERSTEIN] Though the enemy
is continuing to retreat,
they're doing so in
an orderly fashion.
It would appear
their destination is
the Amritsar Starzone.
[REINHARD]
Which is close to the entrance
for the Iserlohn Corridor.
However... I doubt they're
merely fleeing there.
What do you think their plan is?
[OBERSTEIN] I suspect they're
gathering their strength
so they can launch an offensive.
Knowing that, Your
Excellency, now what?
[REINHARD] Obviously, our navy
will gather at Amritsar as well.
Tell me, why should we deny
the rebels their final wish?
If they've chosen Amritsar as
their graveyard, so be it.
[NARRATOR] On October
14th, in the 487th year
of the Imperial calendar,
otherwise known as UC 796,
the Galactic Imperial
Navy set a course
for the Amritsar Starzone.
The location selected by
the Free Planets Alliance
for a decisive battle.
[NARRATOR] Yang Wen-li and
Reinhard von Lohengramm.
Both heroes' paths
will cross again,
when they encounter
each other next.
at the Battle of Amritsar.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These: Episode 13,
"Amritsar."