[ALEX]
You want 40 Imperial uniforms
and one of their cruisers?
Yeah.
Surely the Alliance has captured
ships laying around somewhere.
As for the uniforms,
find them however you can?
Sounds so easy.
I realize it's to prevent
intelligence leaks,
but you're making a lot of
demands without telling me
the first thing about this plan.
Tell you what. I'll treat
you to a glass of cognac after.
Not good enough.
I want no less than three.
[YANG sighs]
Consider it done.
[YANG]
By the way,
I've got one more
request I'd like to make.
[ALEX]
Name it.
Given what's happened
with the Patriotic Knight Corps,
I'm concerned about
leaving Julian by himself.
Would it be possible to
dispatch the MP to the area?
That's the easiest thing
you've asked for today.
But have you considered
the possibility of leaving him
with somebody else?
[YANG] Hm. Oh, sure.
I considered it
for a brief moment.
I'll have to refuse.
This house would fall
into ruin without me!
I can see it now:
dust accumulating
to the point it's unlivable.
I'll be the house's
commanding officer
until you return
from your mission.
You can count on me!
I'll protect our home!
[YANG] I mean,
what could I say to that?
[ALEX]
That's one dependable kid!
It's handled.
We'll make sure he's safe.
[YANG]
I appreciate it.
Sure. Now then,
let's get to the topic at hand.
[YANG] The 13th Fleet
Personnel Distribution Plan.
[NARRATOR] Shortly thereafter,
the officers hand-picked by
Admirals Yang and Caselnes came
together under the banner
of the Thirteenth Fleet.
As vice commander,
they chose seasoned veteran
Commodore Fischer,
who fought bravely in
the Battle of Astarte.
For chief officer,
they selected the meticulous
and orderly Commodore Murai.
Captain Patrichev, better
known among his peers as
"The Fighter," was chosen
for deputy chief officer.
I humbly accept the position,
but may I ask why you chose me?
Your skillful fleet
management was a great asset
to us during the
Battle of Astarte.
Here's the situation.
The Thirteenth will be comprised
of survivors from the Fourth
and Sixth Fleets as
well as new recruits.
As you can see,
it will necessitate
highly elaborate coordination.
I understand.
Quite an undertaking.
[YANG]
Hm. It's good to see you again.
I'm glad you're
doing well, Rear Admiral.
That's up for debate.
Sadly, I haven't improved at
three-dimensional chess.
And we met on Econia.
I admit, I wouldn't have
expected you to appoint me
to this position.
Is it that surprising?
I've been waiting for an
opportunity to call on you.
He's become a fan of yours,
after you handled the
situation on Econia.
If I'm tasked with
commanding a fleet,
I need someone with
an attention to detail.
I humbly request
your assistance.
You shall have it.
[ALEX] By the way, on the matter
of the adjutant position.
[YANG]
I take it you found someone?
[ALEX]
I did.
Graduated from cadet school
second-in-class out of 794.
A far superior student to you.
They're assigned
to the Integrated Tactical
Operations Center,
with a reputation
for an extraordinary memory.
Things are busy
over there right now.
I'll arrange a meeting later.
[knocking]
[YANG sighs]
What to do...?
Sub-Lieutenant
Frederica Greenhill.
I've been assigned
to serve as adjutant
to Rear Admiral Yang Wen-li.
It's nice to meet you.
Rear Admiral
Caselnes ordered me
to report here.
Well, this is unexpected.
Sir? Unexpected, how?
It's nothing important.
I'm sorry, did you say that
your name was Greenhill?
Yes, my father is
Admiral Dwight Greenhill, sir.
Oh, yeah, you certainly
are far superior to me.
No, not at all.
I am young and inexperienced
so I hope to rely on
and mature through
your guidance.
I'm glad to have you here,
Sub-Lieutenant.
Did you happen to look
over my strategy outline?
I'd like to hear
your honest opinion.
It's going to work.
[YANG] Hm. I see. And what
makes you so confident?
El Facil.
It has been eight
years since you
successfully
evacuated the planet.
Don't you think
that's awfully flimsy grounds
for such conviction in me?
Perhaps, but it's
more than enough for me.
That single event planted
absolute trust in the heart
of one little girl,
and it never left.
[FREDERICA] I was at
that airport on El Facil
along with my mother.
[FREDERICA] I'm sure you've long
since forgotten me.
You were choking on a sandwich,
and I brought you
a cup of coffee to drink.
Your reply was memorable.
[YANG]
What did I say?
Well, Admiral,
you said "Good timing.
I mean, I prefer tea to coffee,
but I do appreciate it."
I can't believe I said
such a rude thing to you.
You did. Those exact words.
That's impressive.
I'm sorry, but
concerning that memory,
I feel there must be
more beneficial uses.
Wouldn't you agree?
[FREDERICA giggles]
Yes, thank you, sir.
You heard how
they're adding new soldiers
to the survivors from
Fourth and Sixth?
[SOLDIER 6B]
This Yang Wen-li is
an inexperienced
twenty-something.
They really expect someone that
green to bring down Iserlohn?
What was going through
the Chief's mind when
he made that dumb decision?
He's a retired soldier that left
the battlefield years ago.
Looks like dementia's
catching up with him.
[SOLDIERS laugh]
[BEWCOCK] I sincerely hope
you gentlemen don't end up
with egg on your face.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Uh! Admiral Bewcock!
Don't let appearances
alone decide your opinion.
You may very well be looking
at a redwood sapling
and laughing
because it isn't tall.
It would seem as though
the Admiral's in your corner.
I would express my gratitude,
but I know he'd just
laugh in my face.
Still, though, it is reassuring.
[ALEX] That's right. I finally
read your strategy outline.
And what did you think?
It's the epitome
of recklessness.
You've outdone yourself.
It is, isn't it?
So. Who are you
going to find to star
in the leading role?
It'll take a real daredevil
to pull off a stunt like this.
I believe I've found the
perfect candidate for the job.
[FREDERICA]
The Rosen Ritter.
"Knights of the Rose."
A ground combat force comprised
of refugees from the Empire,
with tactical skills said
to be among the best
in all the Alliance.
[FREDERICA] Its 13th
regimental commander
is Captain Walter von Schönkopf.
[YANG] His Imperial language
won't be an issue?
[FREDERICA] No. But there
are unfavorable rumors.
Go on.
Of all their past captains,
a total of six defected
back to the Empire,
and there are concerns he
may become the seventh.
Based on what?
[FREDERICA] He's the 13th
captain, and 13 is unlucky.
Got it.
So these concerns
are groundless, then.
Do you wish to meet with him?
I can set up an
appointment right away.
[YANG]
No.
Thank you,
but I'll handle this myself.
I am the one asking him
for a favor, after all.
[MEN grunting]
[MEN panting]
[MAN 6E] You're out of luck.
This one's mine.
Please, that's what
you said the other day, too.
[MAN 6G] Hm. Looks like we got
a couple of fish out of water.
[FREDERICA]
This is Admiral Yang Wen-li,
and I am Sub-Lieutenant
Frederica Greenhill
of the Thirteenth Fleet.
We came here to speak with
Captain Walter von Schönkopf.
[MAN 6H] You wouldn't happen to
be Admiral Greenhill's daughter,
would you? I see the
rumors were true.
Every last one of them.
[MEN laugh]]
Talk about rude.
They didn't even
bother to salute.
Yeah, the sub-lieutenant
and I are actually here
on urgent business.
We'd like you to introduce us to
Captain Schönkopf immediately.
Well, since you asked so nicely.
I'd be happy to show
Sub-Lieutenant Greenhill
where she might find him.
[FREDERICA] Rudeness in front
of the admiral will only be
tolerated for so long.
[grosls]
[WALTER]
That'll do. Stand down.
How long are you going
to keep up that act?
[WALTER] Don't shame
yourselves any further.
[MEN gasp]
You are...?
Captain Walter von
Schönkopf at your service.
Seeing someone as
beautiful as you are, ma'am.
It makes men revert
back into little boys.
Same goes for me.
Please forgive us.
[FREDERICA gasps]
So, whatever could have
brought the hero of El Facil
to our humble barracks?
You've piqued
my curiosity already.
I'd like to chat with you.
[WALTER]
And I assume it's important?
Very much so.
[WALTER]
You're right.
That's likely the only
way to manage it.
Being stationed in
an invincible fortress
tends to make one cocky.
Now then.
You've know I'm
the unlucky 13th captain
of the Rosen Ritter.
There were six previous
who turned traitor.
What if I end up the seventh?
We're done.
[WALTER chuckles]
That'd certainly be the case,
but you've got a
backup plan, right?
Surely you've put some
countermeasure in place.
Nope. I couldn't
come up with anything.
If you decide to betray us,
then it'll be over.
End of story.
We only just
met and you're placing
your full confidence in me?
The truth is
I'm not very confident.
[WALTER]
Hmm?
However, if I don't
put my faith in you,
then the plan's over
before it even starts.
So I will trust you.
That's my number
one prerequisite.
I see. May I ask
you a question, Admiral?
[YANG]
Sure.
The orders you were
given are utterly impossible.
You have half a fleet.
Not only that, it's compromised
almost entirely
of undisciplined troops.
And you're going to bring
down Iserlohn Fortress?
I doubt anyone would
blame you for turning down
a suicide mission, so I would
like to know why you agreed
to it--was this plan something
you already had in mind?
Still, even if
that were the case,
your motivation remains
a mystery to me.
Do you crave honor or
perhaps a promotion?
I wouldn't say
it's about advancement.
It's enough I've already got
people addressing me as "sir"
before I'm 30.
Besides, if I make it
back from this mission alive,
my next course
of action is to get out.
What, you mean retire?
[YANG]
Yeah. Well, I get a pension.
And there's also retirement pay.
It'd be enough to
support myself plus another
and live comfortably.
A modest lifestyle.
You'd just walk away from
the current state of affairs?
[YANG sighs]
That's the thing.
It's because of the
state of affairs.
If our forces occupy Iserlohn,
it'd cut off what is really
the empire's only
route to invade us.
As long as we don't do
something stupid like attempting
to stage a reverse invasion,
neither force would be able
to clash even if they wanted.
That is, not on
a large scale at least.
The rest is up to the
Alliance's diplomatic skills,
but if we've secured a
militaristic advantage,
then there's a real chance a
peace treaty could be forged
with the Empire that would be
satisfactory to both parties.
As far as I'm concerned,
I could retire
with a clear conscience
under those conditions.
Seems you thought of everything,
but I wonder how long
that peace would last for.
Well, permanent peace has
never existed in human history.
We're not aiming for the
impossible here, Captain.
In truth, I don't think
it's too much to ask for
a few decades of
prosperity and calm.
If we're going to leave a legacy
behind for the next generation
to inherit, I'd want
it to be one thing.
Just one. That's a
heritage of peace.
And maintaining
the tranquility passed on
from the previous generation.
That would become
their responsibility.
If each generation can
remember their responsibility
to future descendants,
I believe long-term peace
is a real possibility.
But, like I mentioned
to you before,
realistically, I'm hoping for
a few decades at the most.
But even that would be
10,000 times better
than another war that lasted
only a tenth that long.
Between us, I have
a 14 year-old kid I look after.
The last thing I want is
to watch him get dragged
into the battlefield.
That's the way I feel.
[WALTER]
Beg your pardon Admiral,
but you're either the
most honest man alive,
or worse, the biggest sophist
since Emperor Rudolf.
[FYODOR] This strategy
sounds like a real gamble.
[YANG]
I don't deny that.
I'm at a loss for words.
[YANG]
Rightly so.
And if this plan should fail?
If things go bad,
we turn tail and run.
[MURAI]
You can't be serious.
I don't want you to worry.
It was an impossible
mission to begin with.
And the only two people who'll
be disgraced if we do fail
are myself and Chief Sithole.
The admiral and I
examined this plan yesterday,
and I believe he's right.
This is the only way we're
going to take Iserlohn.
You're positive?
It requires you playing
the most dangerous role.
[WALTER] Hmph. Well, What's the
worst that can happen to me?
If I'm taken prisoner, it just
means I get to go home.
[laughs]
Apologies. I guess
I took that joke too far.
[YANG] It may appear foolhardy
to you, but I assure you,
I've thought through this
as rationally as I could.
[YANG] By all means,
I won't ask anyone to trust me.
But I want you to
think about something.
Consider all the ways to take
Iserlohn with half a fleet.
There may be
a few possible methods,
but I think we'd arrive
at the same conclusion.
[MURAI]
Understood, Admiral.
The Thirteenth
will begin preparations
to dispatch at once.
[YANG]
Hmph.
[NARRATOR] A non-navigable
sector of space exists between
the Alliance and
Imperial territories.
Iserlohn Fortress
is located on the one
and only passable route through.
Stationed at this
formidable base
were two Imperial admirals.
One was the fortress's
commander, Admiral Stockhausen.
The other was the commander
of the fortress garrison,
Admiral Zeeckt.
[NARRATOR] Naturally, the
existence of two positions
with identical ranks created
a heated antagonism.
[NARRATOR]
The two men despised
and endlessly cursed
one another.
But whenever the Alliance
launched an attack,
they competed, refusing to let
the other have all the glory.
And thus, their rivalry
led to tremendous gains
on the battlefield.
[HANS] I've heard communications
in the vicinity of the fortress
have been disrupted
for the past two days.
What's going on?
[THOMA]
It's clear the enemy is present,
but we are unable to
locate their position.
We should deploy
our forces immediately.
I believe
I said we don't know
their current location.
Precisely why
we should move out.
To sniff out where they're
hiding before they mobilize.
Admiral, it appears
we're picking up a transmission.
It's weak. Very unstable,
fading in and out.
What does it say?
Sir.
"We are an Imperial cruiser
under secret orders to conduct
espionage within
Alliance territory.
During a mission,
the rebels detected us,
and we left the area.
Only to be pursued and
come under enemy fire
inside the corridor.
Requesting immediate
backup from Iserlohn."
End transmission.
[BOTH gasp]
It's not clear where
in the corridor they are.
We have no choice but to deploy.
Your Excellency, a moment?
Yes, Oberstein?
You have something you wish to
contribute?
[OBERSTEIN]
Yes, sir.
Very well. Let's hear it.
To be perfectly blunt.
I believe we're
walking into a trap.
A trap?
[OBERSTEIN] Yes,
one intended to draw
our fleet away from Iserlohn.
We mustn't go out.
We should observe
before making our move.
The enemy is waiting out there.
Are you saying that we'll lose
if we launch an attack?
We're soldiers,
and as such, our duty
in life is to fight.
Rather than idling in safety,
we should be proactive
in hunting down and
destroying the enemy.
Besides, how can we abandon
one of our distressed ships?
[THOMA]
I don't know, Admiral Seeckt.
Your staff officer
raises a valid objection.
We don't know the location
of the rebels or our ship.
Why don't we wait a little bit?
No!
The fleet will sortie as soon as
preparations are complete!
I wouldn't mind if he
returned bruised and bloodied.
[SOLDIER 6D]
Another incoming message!
"We will soon arrive in the
optical range of Iserlohn,
but the rebel forces
are still in pursuit.
Requesting backup."
Very well. Prepare to attack.
Sir.
Where the hell
did Seeckt disappear to?
[SOLDIER 6E]
Ships on screen!
[THOMA]
Enlarge.
Prepare to fire!
[THOMA]
Hmm?
Very wise.
Looks like they know
how hopeless it is.
[SOLDIER 6D] Another
transmission from the ship!
[THOMA]
Put in on the monitor.
[LAEKEN] Lieutenant
Commander Laeken reporting.
I request an urgent audience
with your fortress commander.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These : Episode 7,
"The Capture of
Iserlohn (Part Two)."