[NARRATOR]
Lord Oigen Castrop,
the ruler of the Castrop
Starzone in the Galactic Empire,
served as minister of finance
under Kaiser
Friedrich the Fourth.
He held this
position for 15 years,
during which time he embezzled
vast amounts of riches.
When his Lordship unexpectedly
perished in an accident,
the depths of his
fraudulent behavior
were quickly discovered.
The Empire's
Ministries of Finance
and Justice attempted to
collect the late Castrop's
unlawfully obtained wealth.
However...
[MARIENDORF grunts]
[NARRATOR] His son,
Maximillian, steadfastly refused
to comply with their demands.
And thus, the Castrop
Rebellion began.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, the
Empire's new fleet Admiral,
Reinhard von Lohengramm,
established the Fleet
Admiral's Mansion.
A compound in which he assembled
the Imperial Navy's top
up-and-coming commanders.
This collection
of talent received
an imperial order from Kaiser
Friedrich the Fourth.
[REINHARD]
Rear Admiral Ziegfried Kircheis.
[KIRCHEIS]
Yes.
Depart for the Castrop Starzone.
Put an end to this rebellion.
[KIRCHEIS]
Sir.
I humbly accept,
Your Excellency.
[WEITZ] Looking over Count
Lohengramm's appointments.
I can't help but notice
an element of bias.
[WEITZ] All of the officers he's
assembled are either commoners
or low-ranking nobles.
And this Rear Admiral Kircheis.
Is he really the man we want
handling the Castrop situation?
[WEITZ] Would the count himself
not be the wiser choice?
[LICHTENLADE] It was Count
Lohengramm who requested
the order be given to
Rear Admiral Kircheis
in the first place.
Is that so wrong?
[LICHTENLADE] Remember,
we're talking about the boy's
most trusted confidant here.
If he's successful with this
mission, then we'll reward him,
thus placing
him in our debt,
which will be to
our benefit later.
[LICHTENLADE]
And if it proves a disaster,
the responsibility
falls squarely on
Count Lohengramm for
recommending him.
[LICHTENLADE] Besides,
if his subordinate fails,
that golden-haired brat has
one less thing to gloat about.
[thump]
How did that upstart
get an imperial order over us?
Obviously the count
must have pulled some strings.
Who is this Siegfried Kircheis,
and what sort of man
will he prove to be?
It seems many
soldiers are asking
the exact same thing.
They have doubts whether
they can entrust their lives
to his command.
I'd like to know how a
man of the count's stature
became so close with a commoner.
[KEMPFF] Apparently,
the two of them have been
good friends since childhood.
Nepotism!
Looks like I was wrong
about the count all along.
And here I was thinking he'd
have great potential.
I wonder what
those other two are thinking
about all this.
I take it you're referring to
Vice Admirals Mittermeyer
and Reuenthal.
They've both fought alongside
Count Lohengramm
in past battles.
I assume they would
have a decent idea
of the Rear Admiral's character.
[PATRONS murmuring]
[MITTERMEYER]
Tell me.
How much have you heard about
this Castrop Rebellion business?
[REUENTHAL]
Only that it's still ongoing.
If he can stop it, Kircheis will
become a Vice Admiral.
[REUENTHAL] Which would then
make him equal in rank to us.
And as the count's favorite,
when I say equal,
I mean ahead.
[MITTERMEYER] Perhaps he
wants everybody in his Admiralty
and beyond to know, that
Kircheis is his right-hand man.
[MITTERMEYER]
Think it'll work out for him?
[REUENTHAL]
Who knows?
But if the count thinks
this is the best way
for him and Kircheis--Sorry.
The best way for all
of us to meet our goal,
then who are we to question him?
[MITTERMEYER]
No choice but to trust and obey.
We've been given our own fleets,
just as he promised us.
Count Lohengramm kept his word.
It's only fair
that we keep ours.
[REUENTHAL] Correct. We shall
repay him with our loyalty.
[REINHARD]
Kircheis.
[CASTROP ADJUTANT 8A]
The Imperial Navy is advancing
in our direction.
[MAXIMILIAN]
Yes, I'm not blind!
Only 5,000 ships?
We'll rip them to pieces!
[IMPERIAL OPERATOR 8A]
Castrop Fleet is approaching.
Ten thousand ships total.
[KIRCHEIS]
Begin commencing the operation.
[CASTROP OPERATOR 8A] Imperials
incoming at high speed!
[MAXIMILIAN]
All ships, open fire!
[CASTROP ADJUTANT 8A] The enemy
is attempting to surround us
rather than using
a counterattack.
[yells]
[MAXIMILIAN] You can't surround
ten thousand ships with five!
Killing these fools
shouldn't take long.
They don't know basic strategy.
[VOLKER]
We should counterattack.
Our shields, they won't last!
[MAXIMILIAN] There's a gap
in the enemy's formation
at 11 o'clock.
Order all my remaining
ships to charge into it.
[CASTROP ADJUTANT 8B]
Please, Lord Castrop!
This is basic strategy!
The enemy wants
to lure us to that point,
that way they can take us out
in one offensive maneuver!
[grunts]
[MAXIMILIAN]
Sacrifices are unavoidable.
To lay down one's life for his
master is the greatest honor
a retainer can ever achieve,
so full charge ahead!
[CASTROP ADJUTANT 8B gasps]
[CASTROP ADJUTANT 8A whimpers]
[MAXIMILIAN chuckles]
[IMPERIAL OPERATOR 8B] Enemy
fleet relocating to 5 o'clock.
[BERGENGRUN] We need
to attack, Your Excellency.
[KIRCHEIS]
We will remain on the defensive.
Let them think we're faltering,
and then allow them
to pass through.
[KIRCHEIS]
Seal off their exit!
[KIRCHEIS] Bring us face to
face with the enemy flagship!
[gasps]
[CASTROP OPERATOR 8A]
Message from the Imperial Navy!
[gasping]
[CASTROP ADJUTANT 8A]
Open communications!
[KIRCHEIS] Message for all
Castrop Navy fleets.
Greetings. My name is
Siegfried Kircheis.
Imperial Navy Rear Admiral.
[KIRCHEIS] You should know
that our primary objective
is the detainment
of Maximilian Castrop,
the leader of this rebellion.
[KIRCHEIS] The officers and
soldiers serving under him
are guilty of no crime except
obeying their leader's orders.
[KIRCHEIS]
If you cease your resistance,
you will be given fair
treatment as our prisoners,
and I give you my word
we will not take
your lives for pleasure.
[KIRCHEIS] As proof,
I'll have you note
I did not destroy
a single vessel.
[MAXIMILIAN]
So naive!
Order all ships at the
front line to lay waste
to the enemy fleet!
We'll catch them
in a pincer attack!
[MAXIMILIAN]
What're you doing?
I gave you the order to attack!
We outnumber the
bastards two-to-one!
Open fire!
Do you not understand
what a pincer attack is?
Fire the main cannons! Fire!
You spineless cowards!
Fire! Now!
[CASTROP ADJUTANT 8A]
Our allies have been ensnared.
If we fire, we'll destroy
our own forces
within their encirclement.
[MAXIMILIAN] How dare you
talk back to your master!
You're nothing but
a former commoner!
I am Lord Maximilian Castrop,
and you will show me respect!
When I give a command,
you obey it!
[MAXIMILIAN gasps]
[guns clicking]
[gasps]
You said earlier
that it was an honor
for a retainer to give
his life for his master.
But what I believe is that it is
a master's job to sacrifice
his life for the
sake of his people.
[MAXIMILIAN whimpers, growls]
[grunts]
[IMPERIAL OPERATOR 8A]
Message from the enemy flagship.
"Maximilian Castrop is dead.
We accept your recommendation
of surrender."
[VOLKER]
He's dead?
[BERGENGRUN]
But how?
[KIRCHEIS] Continue our
course for Planet Castrop.
Caution the men to handle
the prisoners with respect
and not to engage in looting
or other behavior that would
bring any harm to the civilians.
[KIRCHEIS] Anyone found
violating these orders
will be punished.
[gasps]
[BERGENGRUN]
Sir!
[BITTENFELD] He managed to quell
the rebellion in just ten days?
[LUTZ] No. Six days
were needed to travel to
the Castrop Starzone.
The actual battle only
lasted a mere two days.
Then the follow up
procedures took two more.
[WAHLEN] I guess that puts
to rest whether he deserves
to be at the count's side.
[MAN 8A]
Rear Admiral Siegfried Kircheis!
Salute!
[LICHTENLADE] Be grateful for
his Imperial Majesty's favor.
And continue to strive for ever
greater loyalty to your emperor.
[KIRCHEIS]
Sir.
You're asking the impossible.
[KIRCHEIS] There's only
one I devote myself to.
[knocking]
[KIRCHEIS]
Enter.
[SOLDIER 8A] Pardon, but we've
received an urgent message
from headquarters.
[KIRCHEIS]
What is it?
[SOLDIER 8A]
Well, sir, Iserlohn has...
I regret to report Iserlohn
has fallen to the rebels!
[EHRENBERG]
What did you say?
But Iserlohn was supposed to be
an impregnable stronghold.
[STEINHOF] Impossible!
Surely, the report is wrong!
[MÜCKENBERGER]
Admiral Seeckt is dead,
and Stockhausen is now
a prisoner of the enemy.
Somebody has to
shoulder the responsibility
for this abysmal defeat.
[MÜCKENBERGER]
Which means...
[LICHTENLADE] Imperial territory
must be kept completely
inviolable to outside invasion,
and until presently,
that has always been the case.
[LICHTENLADE] The incident
regarding the fall and capture
of Iserlohn Fortress which
troubles his Majesty's mind,
is entirely the result of my
shortcomings while serving
as your Minister of State.
[LICHTENLADE] I am deeply
ashamed of my failure.
[REINHARD] The Minister's
line of thinking is off.
[KIRCHEIS]
How so?
[REINHARD] He said we aren't
supposed to give even an inch
of Imperial territory
to outside invaders.
Which insinuates the rebels have
become an outside force equal
to our own strength.
He fails to see reality
and thus utters contradictions.
Tell me, what's the name
of the man responsible
for conquering Iserlohn?
[KIRCHEIS]
Rear Admiral Yang Wen-li.
Commander of
their Thirteenth Fleet.
We've heard the name before.
[KIRCHEIS] You may remember
him from the Battle of Astarte.
[REINHARD]
Yang Wen-li.
[knocking]
[KIRCHEIS]
Enter.
[SOLDIER 8B]
We have a man outside
requesting an audience, sir.
[KIRCHEIS gasps]
[KIRCHEIS]
We'll take him from here.
You may wait out front.
[OBERSTEIN]
I can't travel anywhere now
without military
police accompaniment.
[REINHARD] You're Captain
Oberstein, if I recall?
What business might
you have with me?
[OBERSTEIN] First, I would
ask that you clear the room.
[REINHARD] There are
only three of us present.
[OBERSTEIN] Yes. I can, in
fact, see Vice Admiral Kircheis.
That is precisely why I'm asking
you to clear the room.
[REINHARD] Anything you have
to say to me you may say
in front of the Vice Admiral.
Surely this come as no surprise.
[OBERSTEIN]
No, it does not.
[REINHARD]
If you have something to tell me
that you don't want him to hear.
Know that I do plan to inform
him later, regardless.
[OBERSTEIN] Your Excellency
is free to do as he pleases.
That said, one is far more
likely to achieve supremacy
by having a variety of talented
people by their side.
[OBERSTEIN] You tell Person
A what A they needs to hear.
Give Person B
assignments suited for B.
So on and so forth.
[KIRCHEIS]
Forgive my saying so,
but perhaps it would be best
if I waited in the next room.
[REINHARD]
Very well.
[OBERSTEIN]
The truth, Your Excellency,
is that I find myself
in something of
a difficult position
at the moment.
I believe you are aware of this.
[REINHARD] You're the
deserter from Iserlohn.
It's only natural
you'd be condemned.
Especially when
Admiral Seeckt perished
heroically during battle.
[OBERSTEIN] I'm sure to a myriad
of commanding officers,
I appear as nothing more
than a deserter and a coward.
Nevertheless, I do have
my own side of the story.
I would like you to hear
my version of events.
[REINHARD]
This is absurd.
If you insist on defending
yourself, then do so
at tomorrow's court martial,
not here to me.
[OBERSTEIN] The trial is
theatrics and nothing more.
Both my guilt and the
requisite punishment
have already been decided.
[OBERSTEIN] Please look
at this, your Excellency.
[OBERSTEIN] As the
Vice Admiral has no doubt
already informed you.
Both my eyes are
artificial implants.
[OBERSTEIN] If I was born during
the reign of Emperor Rudolf,
I would have been executed
as an infant under
the Inferior Genes
Exclusion Act.
[OBERSTEIN]
I hope I'm being clear.
I despise every one of them.
Emperor Rudolf,
his descendants,
and everything they've
brought into being.
[OBERSTEIN] I despise the
Goldenbaum Dynasty itself.
[REINHARD]
That's a daring statement.
[OBERSTEIN] The Empire, by which
I mean the Goldenbaum Dynasty,
should be destroyed.
If it were possible,
I'd have already strangled it
with my own hands.
[OBERSTEIN] However. I lack
the acumen and power to do so.
What I am able to provide is
assistance in the establishment
of a new supreme ruler.
Which has brought me here.
[OBERSTEIN]
I'm referring to you,
Fleet Admiral Count
Reinhard von Lohengramm.
[REINHARD]
Kircheis.
[REINHARD] Hand the captain
over to the military police!
He has made treasonous
statements towards the Empire.
As an imperial officer,
I cannot overlook this.
[OBERSTEIN] In the end
I guess that's all there is to you.
Very well. Depend
on Vice Admiral Kircheis
as your only trusted advisor
and continue to walk down
your narrow path.
[OBERSTEIN]
I wonder, Vice Admiral.
Could you shoot me?
As you can see,
I'm completely unarmed.
Could you still do it?
[OBERSTEIN] You can't.
That's the kind of man you are.
[OBERSTEIN] While it's clear
you're deserving of respect,
that quality by itself isn't
enough to achieve
true dominance. There is
a shadow for every light.
[OBERSTEIN] But, perhaps
the young Count Lohengramm
doesn't understand
that reality yet.
[REINHARD] You're a man
who says whatever he pleases.
[OBERSTEIN]
Forgive me.
[REINHARD] Which no doubt
meant Seeckt detested you.
Am I wrong?
[OBERSTEIN] The late Admiral was
not exactly the sort of man
who inspired loyalty in his
subordinates, Your Excellency.
[LICHTENLADE] Military Chief
of Staff Ehrenberg,
Chief of Headquarters Steinhof,
and Space Fleet Commander
Mückenberger.
[LICHTENLADE] These three
chiefs of staff have submitted
their resignations,
as an act of penitence
for the loss of Iserlohn.
[FRIEDRICH]
Which position would you like?
[REINHARD] This commendation
is not based on achievement.
I haven't earned their titles
and so must decline.
[LICHTENLADE sighs]
[REINHARD] The loss of Iserlohn
was the result of errors
made by Admirals Seeckt
and Stockhausen.
[REINHARD]
In addition.
Admiral Seeckt atoned for
his oversight through death.
And the one who surrendered
is imprisoned by the enemy.
[REINHARD] I believe justice
has been administered.
No one else deserves blame.
Therefore, Your Majesty,
I humbly request,
that you do not find fault
with the three chiefs of staff.
[EHRENBERG] Never in a thousand
years would I have guessed
I'd be indebted to that child.
[STEINHOF]
From what I understand,
he requested immunity for
Captain Oberstein along
with his transfer to
the Fleet Admiral's
Mansion. [MÜCKENBERGER] It's out
of the question to accept
his Imperial Majesty's generous
favor while allowing
the one survivor under
Seeckt's atrocious command
to be severely punished.
[EHRENBERG] Bottom line
is he voluntarily gave up
a high ranking position.
That's a surprisingly
selfless act.
[MÜCKENBERGER]
Hmm...
[LICHTENLADE]
Your Imperial Majesty.
[FRIEDRICH]
What is it?
[LICHTENLADE] I know what I'm
about to say will displease you,
but I would be
remiss to stay silent.
[FRIEDRICH]
Is this about Lohengramm?
Perhaps you feel the
need to tell me I've given
too much prestige and
power to Annerose's brother.
[LICHTENLADE] Your Majesty seems
well aware of my reservations.
[FRIEDRICH]
Since the man is fearless,
he won't be satisfied as
a mere senior statesman.
He might even get overly
ambitious and plot
to usurp my position.
Am I wrong?
[LICHTENLADE] I was hesitant to
put such thoughts into words,
but that is indeed what I fear.
[FRIEDRICH]
I see no problem with that.
[LICHTENLADE]
Sir?
[FRIEDRICH] The Goldenbaum
Dynasty has not existed
alongside humanity
since the beginning.
Just as no man is immortal,
no country is eternal either.
[FRIEDRICH] There's no
reason the Galactic Empire
mustn't end during
my generation.
[LICHTENLADE gasps]
[FRIEDRICH]
If it's going to fall anyway,
then the least I can hope is for
its end to be a magnificent one.
[REINHARD] You look like you
want to say something.
[KIRCHEIS] Are you going
to pretend you don't know
what it is?
[REINHARD]
Don't be upset with me.
It's about Oberstein, right?
You suspect him.
You're worried he's a pawn
of some noble family.
I had my initial doubts, too.
[REINHARD]
No. He isn't the sort of man
the aristocrats can handle.
He's got a sharp mind,
but too many peculiarities.
[KIRCHEIS] And you feel that you
can handle him, Lord Reinhard?
[REINHARD]
A good question.
What I do know are the qualities
I don't expect from him.
Such as friendship or
any sense of true loyalty.
He's obviously using me
to achieve his own goals.
[REINHARD] So. I'll
use that intellect of his
to my advantage.
[REINHARD] His motives
are unimportant to me.
If I can't control one man,
how could I ever be worthy
of ruling over the
entire universe?
[REINHARD]
That's enough for today.
Leave me.
[KIRCHEIS]
Sir.
[REINHARD]
Oberstein will be useful.
He won't hesitate to take
any means necessary.
[REINHARD]
For better or for worse.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These : Episode 9,
"Each Person's Star."