[NARRATOR] In the year CE 2081,
humanity relocated
its political center from Earth,
the third planet in
the solar system,
to Theoria, second planet
of the Aldebaran Star System.
Establishing the
Galactic Federation.
It was then declared
the first year of
the Universal Calendar
and heralded as an era
of long-lasting growth.
However, this prosperity
would not last forever.
And humanity found itself
eclipsed by the shadow
of uncertainty and stagnation.
Then, in UC 310,
Rudolf Goldenbaum
was elected President of
the Galactic Federation
by popular vote.
Soon after, he was appointed
Prime Minister by Parliament,
holding both offices
simultaneously.
In addition, he bestowed
upon himself the title
Emperor Rudolf the First
of the Galactic Empire.
At which point, the Galactic
Federation collapsed,
and the Goldenbaum Dynasty
was established in its place.
These events afforded
him the dual role of both
the first absolute
monarch of all humanity.
As well as its dictator.
[NARRATOR] Now a holy
and unchallengeable entity,
Rudolf shaped reality
to match his ideology.
The result was a world in which
the populace was ruled
by a subset of the nobility.
[NARRATOR] An outbreak
of widespread rioting
followed his death.
However, the empire's
foundation remained intact.
Then in the year IC 164,
a group of republicans
led by Arle Heinessen succeeded
in escaping the empire's rule.
After a journey that
lasted half a century,
they reached a habitable planet
which they named Heinessen.
And declared the establishment
of the Free Planets Alliance.
Operating under
the belief that they were
the true heirs of the
Galactic Federation,
the Alliance reinstated
the Universal Calendar.
The year was UC 527,
coinciding with
the year 218 of the
Imperial Calendar.
In UC 640,
the Galactic Empire
and the Free Planets Alliance
would first clash,
spending the next 150
years at war.
[FRIEDRICH] For your victory
in subjugating the rebel forces
in the Astarte Starzone,
Count Reinhard von Lohengramm,
I name you the
Imperial Fleet Admiral.
I also grant you the title
of Vice Commander of
the Imperial Space Fleet.
Your command is
hereby increased to include
half the armada's warships.
Thus decreed by the
Kaiser of the Galactic Empire,
in this, the 487th year of
the Imperial Calendar.
[trumpets blare]
[OVLESSER] Hmph. A
20 year-old fleet admiral.
Our once illustrious
Imperial Space Fleet,
now reduced to a child's
plaything, Your Excellency.
How tragic.
[GREGOR] So you say, milord,
but you can't deny that
the blonde brat
possesses tactical skill.
Despite being outnumbered,
he quelled the rebels.
His talent seems
to have astonished
even seasoned veterans.
It silenced Merkatz.
[OVLESSER] The man looks
like he's had his fangs pulled.
While the boy won,
in all probability,
it was an isolated event.
If you ask me, the only
reason we triumphed was
the enemy's utter incompetence.
[MAN 3A] Next, he'll go
from count to marquis.
[MAN 3B]
He's done remarkably well.
I'm sure it has nothing to
do with the Kaiser being
in love with his sister.
Nothing at all.
[MAN 3C]
And his ginger-haired stooge
is getting promoted two ranks.
[ANSBACH]
Cease the gossip!
[gasping]
[MAN 3A]
Commodore Ansbach, sir!
Their deeds
and not their relations,
have made them worthy
of the ranks they hold.
So watch your tongues!
[MEN]
Yes, sir!
I imagine you'll be promoted.
How does "Commodore" sound?
[KIRCHEIS] Every time Reinhard
takes a step up the ladder,
I'm dragged right behind him.
And at such staggering speed.
[OBERSTEIN] Captain Siegfried
Kircheis, isn't it?
That's correct. And you are?
I am Captain Paul von Oberstein.
A pleasure to finally meet you.
Do you have business with me?
[OBERSTEIN sighs]
Forgive me.
My artificial eyes seem
to be acting up.
I apologize if I alarmed you.
There's no need.
In which battle did
you lose them?
[OBERSTEIN]
None. It was a congenital issue.
How fortunate I wasn't born
during the reign Emperor Rudolf.
Otherwise, I would
have been eliminated
under the Inferior Genes
Exclusion Act.
[OBERSTEIN] You're lucky, too,
blessed with a good superior.
There are precious few
in the Imperial Army.
Those who realize their
subordinate's abilities.
But Count Lohengramm
appears to be
in a separate class. His
ideology is beyond aristocrats
who only concern
themselves with lineage.
If you don't mind me asking,
which fleet do you serve?
Formerly headquarters,
intel processing division, but
I've recently been appointed
to the fleet at Iserlohn
Fortress as a staff officer.
Congratulations on your success.
You play your cards
close to the chest, don't you?
[MAN 3D]
Salute the fleet admiral!
Captain Paul
von Oberstein, Admiral.
If I may extend
my congratulations.
Until we meet again, captain.
And you.
Please excuse me, sir.
And who might that be?
A walking enigma, I suspect.
[CROWD murmuring]
[REINHARD]
I see.
He had harsh criticism for
Emperor Rudolf, did he?
[REINHARD] It is always
best to remain guarded,
though with so many
enemies lurking,
it isn't the easiest of tasks.
Agreed.
I'm seeing Annerose,
you should come along.
Are you certain I should?
I invited you.
There's no point in resisting.
[KIRCHEIS] Back then,
the stars shimmering in the sky
seemed so far away.
Impossibly beyond my grasp.
I never even considered
reaching for them.
Until I was given a reason.
[BOY 3A]
'Bye!
[KIRCHEIS]
See you tomorrow!
The gate next door is open?
[KIRCHEIS gulps]
[KIRCHEIS]
A noble?
[KIRCHEIS' MOTHER]
Yes, that's what I heard.
Well, he didn't
look very noble to me.
There're many
different kinds, you know.
Guess what? The Baldr orchids
should be in bloom by tomorrow.
[gasps]
You really think so?
[KIRCHEIS]
Hmm. Have a good day!
[REINHARD]
Good morning.
We've just moved in,
I'm Reinhard von Musel.
What's your name?
I'm Siegfried.
Siegfried Kircheis.
Huh, Siegfried, you say?
Sounds like a commoner's name.
[gasps]
[REINHARD]
However.
Your last name is
actually quite pleasant.
It's almost poetic, really.
So, from now on, that's
what I'll address you as.
You don't mind that,
right, Kircheis?
I...
[ANNEROSE]
Reinhard?
[REINHARD]
Over here!
You little scamp.
You disappeared on me.
There's someone
I want you to meet.
Come on!
[REINHARD] I'd like to introduce
you to Siegfried Kircheis.
Hello there. I'm Annerose.
So, Siegfried? May I
call you "Sieg" for short?
[KIRCHEIS]
A-Ah... Mm.
Well, Sieg.
I hope you'll be good
friends with my brother.
[KIRCHEIS]
M-Mm-hmm! Sure!
[ANNEROSE]
My. You're energetic!
[laughter]
[TEACHER 3A]
Welcome our new student.
This is Reinhard von Müsel.
[CLASSROOM murmuring]
It's von Müsel. Get it right.
[BOY 3C chuckles]
[BOY 3D] I hated that noble
kid the second I saw him.
He'll get the picture
as soon as he shows up.
[BOY 3F]
Should be any minute.
Let's bust him up
nice and quick.
[KIRCHEIS]
Did you see where Reinhard went?
[BOY 3G] Some of the older kids
were asking for him earlier.
[gasps]
[KIRCHEIS]
Reinhard!
[KIRCHEIS pants]
[KIRCHEIS gasps]
I bet that taught them a lesson.
[KIRCHEIS]
Hmm
[REINHARD]
My uniform, though.
If Annerose knew what I'd
done, she'd be very upset.
[sighs] I have an
idea how to avoid that.
Phoo. Phoo.
[ANNEROSE]
How is it?
Perfect!
[ANNEROSE]
Have you two warmed up a bit?
[REINHARD, KIRCHEIS]
Yes.
I can't believe
you fell into a fountain.
I guess you have
a little too much energy.
[BOTH]
Hmm.
[laughter]
[ANNEROSE] What? Sometimes,
you boys act so strangely.
Anyway, I made
a Kelsey plum cake.
Go get dressed
and help yourselves.
[REINHARD gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[ANNEROSE]
Hey, what did I tell you?
Clothes first, then dessert.
[REINHARD, KIRCHEIS]
No, cake first!
[ANNEROSE giggles]
[REINHARD]
By the way, Kircheis!
My sister said she was
going to bake more
Kelsey plum cake today.
Really? I never
get tired of those.
Ah.
[KIRCHEIS] I know that crest.
Why are they at your house?
[REINHARD growls]
Wait, Reinhard!
[REINHARD]
What did you do?!
We didn't have any choice.
His Highness has demanded her.
You must realize, it's an honor.
You sold your own daughter!
Where is the honor in that?!
How could you put
a price on her life?!
[REINHARD'S FATHER] And I told
you we have no other choice!
Ugh.The decision's been made.
[gasps]
It's all right.
Everything's going
to be fine, Reinhard.
[REINHARD sobs]
This is how it worked out.
[ANNEROSE]
Sieg.
[KIRCHEIS gasps]
We didn't know
each other for very long,
but thank you.
A gift. I hope you enjoy it.
Take care of Reinhard for me.
He's going to need you.
Goodbye, Sieg.
[KIRCHEIS gasps]
[KIRCHEIS whimpers]
[gasps]
[REINHARD]
Kircheis.
Ah.
[KIRCHEIS]
Reinhard.
It's been a while.
Where have you been?
That uniform...
[REINHARD]
I joined a cadet school.
Why would you do that?
To join the military.
The fastest way to get
ahead in this world.
I came to ask you to
become a solider with me.
Be a soldier?
You and I. Together,
we will get my sister back.
[gasps]
Take care of Reinhard for me.
He's going to need you.
[BOY 3H]
So that's Countess Grünewald's
younger brother, is it?
[BOY 3I] Did you hear
about the red-headed kid?
He's a commoner!
[BOY 3J] What's a peasant
doing at our school?
[BOY 3K] He got in because
of the sister's influence, too.
[REINHARD]
Those two are sons of magnates.
They always have servants
in tow to do their bidding.
How long would
they last on the battlefield?
They will never go.
Even if they
get into the military,
most of them get stuck
in the rear service.
They have no intention
of risking their lives
by going out on the front lines.
That's how imperial nobles are.
Faster! Hustle! Hustle! Hustle!
[panting]
[BOY 3N] Move it, horsey!
Go faster! Faster!
Goal!
[grunting, groaning]
It would appear
your steed has gone lame.
A truly pathetic display.
[BOY 3N]
On your feet, horse.
[BOY 3P]
You, too.
Those boys,
neither of them have done
a single thing to earn
their standing.
There's no reason why we
should have to be downwind
of their self-grandeur.
You're right.
[MAN 3G] Graduating
students representative,
Reinhard von Müsel!
[REINHARD]
Sir!
[MAN 3G] Salutatorian,
Siegfried Kircheis.
Sir!
[REINHARD] Kircheis, have you
ever thought about it this way?
Annerose!
I'm overjoyed you
decided to visit, Reinhard.
Sieg, too!
It brings me
pleasure to see you
doing so well, Annerose.
[ANNEROSE]
Mm. And I, you.
Though you certainly
took your time.
I've been awaiting
your arrival for days.
Follow me. I'll show
you both inside.
[KIRCHEIS]
She hasn't changed. Not one bit.
Not even the Kaiser
with all his power,
can do anything
to taint these two.
They're untouchable.
Lost in thought?
Come along now.
[KIRCHEIS]
Sorry.
[ANNEROSE]
Have some Kelsey plum cake.
I made it myself,
so I don't know if it
will suit your tastes.
I'll just have to
make my tastes suit it.
Goodness, you can be so mean!
It's as delicious as always.
You are too kind.
So tell me, Sieg.
Has my dear brother been getting
you into all sorts of trouble?
No, not at all.
Go on, you can
be honest with her.
[ANNEROSE]
Don't tease him, Reinhard!
[laughs]
Oh, that's right.
I have a wonderful vin rosé
I received as a gift.
I seem to be getting your hint.
I suppose you'd like me
to locate that bottle.
I won't be gone long.
[ANNEROSE] Thank you,
Reinhard. You're a gem.
[ANNEROSE giggles]
[ANNEROSE] You've done
so much for my brother.
Please, think nothing of it.
On the contrary,
he's done so much for me.
To be a captain at my age.
It's more than I deserve.
And soon you'll be rear admiral.
Or so I hear.
Congratulations.
[gasps] That's right,
thank you very much.
I've never heard
my brother say it aloud,
and I suppose it's possible
that he simply hasn't noticed.
But he truly relies
on you a great deal.
You flatter me.
I'm nothing special.
That's untrue.
I wish you'd learn to
appreciate your value more.
Reinhard does
possess talent, and yet,
he lacks your maturity, Sieg.
He's like a wild goat
that grows too proud
of its agility only to
fall from the cliff.
His situation is
just as perilous.
So please, Sieg. I'm asking you.
Watch over Reinhard
so he doesn't meet with
a similar fate--
slipping off the cliff.
And if he's headed in
that direction, please tell him.
He would listen. I know he'd
accept a warning from you.
You have my word
I'll do everything in my power.
Your brother has my loyalty,
and nothing in this universe
will ever change that.
I swear, as long as I breathe,
I will not disappoint you.
[ANNEROSE] Mm. I know you won't.
Thank you, Sieg.
I need to tell you...
[door creaks]
[REINHARD]
A success.
You should have put it
somewhere easier to find.
My apologies.
But soon you'll see it
was worth the effort.
I'll just go fetch us
some glasses.
[KIRCHEIS] So this is
where you disappeared to.
I've come so far,
since that one night.
Kircheis, have you
ever thought about it this way?
The Goldenbaum
Dynasty isn't timeless.
It hasn't existed since
humanity's dawn.
It all began
with one arrogant bastard.
[gasps]
[REINHARD] Rudolf started
out as nothing more
than an ambitious upstart.
But his timing was right,
and he managed to become
a holy and inviolable emperor.
What do you think, Kircheis?
If Rudolf achieved such power,
do you think I'm capable
of doing the same?
[KIRCHEIS]
Reinhard.
You know the answer, so please.
Go make the universe your own.
[REINHARD] Let's go.
We return to the battlefield.
Yes, sir.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These : Episode 4,
"The Unbeatable Magician"