[FREDERICA]
The Rosen Ritter.
Its thirteenth
regimental commander
is Captain Walter von Schönkopf.
[YANG]
Go on.
[FREDERICA]
Of all their past captains,
a total of six defected
back to the Empire,
and there are concerns he
may become the seventh.
[WALTER]
You know I'm the unlucky 13th
captain of the Rosen Ritter.
There were six previous
who turned traitor.
What if I end up the seventh?
[SOLDIER 7A] Sending hull
number and crew ID codes.
Awaiting permission to dock.
[SOLDIER 7A] Request received,
permission granted.
Do either of you men
have any memories
of life in the Empire?
I don't, I'm a
second-generation refugee.
My grandfather
came under suspicion
and was executed.
I see. It must
have been difficult for you.
I grew up under Imperial
rule until I was six.
I spent most of my time
with my grandfather.
[FREDERICA]
It's been ten minutes since
the task force entered port.
There has been no request
for rescue as projected
in the event of failure.
[FYODOR] Given the
lack of transmissions,
it would seem they were
successful in docking.
The good news is
we've cleared the first hurdle.
That's true.
All we need to do is clear
the rest with the same level
of success and we'll
be in perfect shape.
I am Lieutenant
Commander Laeken.
Lieutenant Mann,
security captain.
Tell me what happened out there?
We were carrying out orders
assigned by
Admiral Mückenberger,
an espionage mission deep
within Alliance territory.
But unfortunately,
we were discovered,
and my unit was annihilated.
Amid the chaos,
I managed to obtain this.
We were the only ones to escape.
This attaché contains
blueprints from the Alliance.
[LAEKEN] It appears
the rebels have come up
with an unbelievable plan.
A manner in which to
pass through the corridor
and neutralize
Iserlohn Fortress.
How is that remotely possible?
Unfortunately,
it doesn't stop at Iserlohn.
It could very well mean the
life or death of the Empire.
You must take me to the
fortress commander at once.
He's claiming the
Alliance intends to overtake
this fortress and
infiltrate the Empire?
Sir, if what
he is saying is the truth,
then the very purpose of
Iserlohn Fortress will be lost.
You think I don't
know the implications?
Have you made contact
with the garrison?
[ADJUTANT 7A] Our communications
remain hindered
by jamming signals.
Times like this
are precisely the reason
why we require a garrison, but
that fool Seeckt had to deploy!
Ready Thor's Hammer
and all additional
cannons for battle.
[ADJUTANT 7A]
Understood!
Before you do anything else,
I want you to bring me
the captain of that ship!
[ADJUTANT 7A]
Yes, sir!
[WALTER] So, once we've
made it into enemy territory,
what's the plan then?
[YANG] Our strategy
has a single objective.
Occupying the control room
inside Iserlohn Fortress.
If that weren't
already difficult enough,
the Alliance's map of the
fortress is incomplete.
So we're unable to pinpoint the
central control room's location.
There are five possibilities.
[WALTER]
Ah. And in order to find
which is the correct position,
we let the enemy
guide us to all of them.
[YANG]
Yes. Exactly right.
And if we can
accomplish that task,
we can take down any fortress,
no matter how fortified it is.
The same could be said
about winning a woman's heart.
It's all very easy
to talk about,
but difficult in execution.
[FREDERICA]
The nearest possible location is
7,300 meters from the port.
The furthest is 21,600 meters.
[FREDERICA] You'll have to cover
a vast distance in the fortress
while surrounded by enemies.
This is the second hurdle.
[WALTER] It requires
some acting skill, then.
[YANG]
Yeah.
[WALTER'S GRANDFATHER]
Walter.
Tell me, what do you want to be
when you grow up?
[WALTER]
What do you mean?
I'm a noble, Grandpa!
That is true.
You're a noble,
but does that mean
you can't be something
else, as well?
[MANN]
What's that on your wrist?
It appears to be a tattoo.
[MANN]
Tattoos on Imperial soldiers
are forbidden by military law.
[RAINER]
Well. This is...
[WALTER (LAEKEN)] Necessary
for the espionage mission.
It was required to gain the
trust of the Alliance soldiers,
which allowed us
to gather intel.
[WALTER (LAEKEN)]
Of course.
Now that the mission is over,
it will be removed.
[MANN]
I see. Forgive my indiscretion.
It's fine.
Lieutenant Commander Remler,
control room guard captain.
If you'll follow me, I'll take
you to the commander from here.
Firearms are prohibited
in the control room, understand?
Remove any weapons
in your possession
and place them in the dock.
Afterwards, you'll be examined
by the full-body scanner
in the next room.
No exceptions,
even if you're operating
under the Space Chief Commander.
[FREDERICA] The third hurdle
will be the body scan.
You can't carry any weapons
into the central control room.
You'll be subject to thorough
checks to ensure you're unarmed.
[WALTER] Hmph. So,
what do you have in mind?
[REMLER]
Hold it!
Pardon me, sir.
[REMLER]
Hmm.
[WALTER (LAEKEN)]
It belonged to my grandfather.
I keep on my person at
all times for good luck.
It protects me.
[WALTER (LAEKEN)]
Is that all right?
Thank you.
Lastly. I will need
to see your identifications.
I believe we sent those to you
when we entered port.
These are the rules,
no exceptions.
[REMLER]
Verification failure.
I cannot allow you to
enter the control room.
How peculiar.
Might there be a problem
with the machine?
I can get
confirmation from Odin,
though the process
could take a while.
You would waste that much time?
We don't know when the
transmissions will even work!
Very well.
I'd be satisfied waiting
a month or two.
What is taking you so long?
His Excellency demands haste!
Yes, but, sir--
[ADJUTANT 7A]
That's enough! Bring them!
[REMLER]
Hmm? Understood.
[THOMA growls]
Where are they?
You took your time.
Explain what's going on!
[YANG] In order to take
the commander hostage,
you'll need to acquire a weapon
inside the control room.
Admiral Stockhausen
should be able
to provide you with one.
In other words,
at this stage of the plan,
you'll have only your
own strength to rely on.
I hate to ask this of you,
but I have no choice.
Can you do it?
[WALTER]
Hmm...
You know...
...I'm sure I can
figure something out.
I knew you were a rebel!
[REMLER]
You scum!
Ahh!
[WALTER (LAEKEN) grunts]
[THOMA groans]
Apologies, Your Excellency,
but I'm afraid you
are now our hostage.
Commander!
[RAINER grunts]
Just who the
hell are you people?
I am Captain Schönkopf.
Leader of the Rosen Ritter
of the Free Planets Alliance.
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
[LINZ grunts]
[REMLER]
Did you say the Rosen Ritter?
I'm well aware of your regiment.
You're a pack of traitors
who abandoned the Empire!
I'm happy to know that
our reputation precedes us.
You bastards aren't on
the same level as Imperials.
Our commander fears dishonor
more than death at your hands.
[THOMA whimpers]
He doesn't seem to appreciate
your estimation of
his character.
[REMLER grunts]
What did you just do?
[FREDERICA] The final hurdle
will be how thoroughly
you can occupy the control room.
Even if I've secured
the fortress commander
as my hostage,
I doubt it will be enough
to fully take over.
Agreed.
All right, then
what should we do?
[WALTER]
Karl Seffle is a practitioner
of applied chemistry.
He invented a chemical for use
in mining and civil engineering
on a planetary scale.
It's something
like a gas that reacts to
a certain amount
of heat or energy,
setting off an explosion
with a controlled range.
Seffle particles?
That's right. Seffle Particles.
I can get those into the room.
[FREDERICA]
Captain.
Normal close range
combat is one thing,
but using it in a raid may
produce unexpected
and potentially
dangerous results.
The slightest misstep and all
of you could be caught in
the explosion and wind up dead.
If you have
any other suggestions,
I would love to hear them.
However, I suspect
you've known all along
this would be the only way.
Honestly. I kinda
wanted to continue
brainstorming safer alternatives
until the last possible minute.
[WALTER chuckles] A trusting
heart you've got there.
I only hope it doesn't claim
your life one of these days.
[WALTER (LAEKEN)] If you fire
now, the particles will ignite
and everyone who's in here will
be blown into space dust.
Seffle particles.
Don't do something foolish.
Doesn't the blood of the empire
flow through your veins as well?
If you choose to surrender,
we're prepared to make you
a generous offer in return.
Oh? You have my attention.
[OPERATOR 7A] Ninety minutes
have passed since infiltration.
[MURAI] That's far longer than
we had anticipated this taking.
I hate to be the one
who brings it up,
but do you think
Captain Schönkopf
became the seventh traitor?
[YANG] If that were the case,
the Empire would have already
located our fleet by now.
[YANG]
Captain Schönkopf accepted
the most dangerous role.
Don't forget.
I will continue to honor
my word and trust the man.
I'll admit, that's quite
an attractive offer,
but sadly, I must
refuse at this time.
I need to honor
my word to the man
who has placed his
full confidence in me.
Besides,
how can you expect me
to leave the Alliance when
there are still so many women
I haven't seduced yet?
[REMLER] Then you'll meet
your end with the rest of us.
If that's the way you want it.
[REMLER growls]
[THOMA]
Remler! Stop! Drop your weapon.
[REMLER]
But Excellency...
This is a formal surrender.
The fortress is
under your command.
Well, you heard the man.
[REMLER growls]
Damn it!
[WALTER (LAEKEN)] Hmph. A truly
wise decision, commander.
[WALTER'S GRANDFATHER]
There's nothing to be done.
It's pointless to discuss it.
A noble wasn't satisfied
with his own lineage
and grew power hungry.
So he decided to steal
our family's fortune.
On top of that,
he arranged a warrant
for my arrest on the
charges of thought crimes
against the emperor.
What's the next
course of action, sir?
[WALTER'S GRANDFATHER] Now, now,
there's no need to worry.
I've arranged for us
to seek asylum with
the Free Planets Alliance.
But aren't they
our enemy, Grandpa?
[RAINER] Captain? I cleaned
the blood off, but...
Thank you, but it'll be fine.
That pen was
a family heirloom, right?
[WALTER]
Hey, come on.
Every falsehood needs
at least one element of truth
present in order to sell it.
Men are one thing, but women
will always catch you otherwise.
[computers beeping]
[MURAI]
I owe you an apology.
I was concerned that
you might betray us.
It was wrong of me
to be doubt your loyalty.
That's good.
Having people suspect me
is just part of my job.
It doesn't bother me.
[WALTER]
Admiral.
Outstanding work, Captain.
As you instructed,
we've released sleeping gas
throughout the entire fortress
via the air conditioning system.
When they wake up, we'll have
500,000 prisoners.
Looks like everything
worked out fine.
Without a hitch, Admiral.
[SEECKT]
What?
There's been a mutiny
inside the fortress?
[SOLDIER 7B] Yes, a group
of soldiers has revolted!
Immediate aid has
been requested!
The man can't even keep
his subordinates under control?
Stockhausen,
you blundering fool!
[SEECKT] We must first stamp
out the fire at our feet.
All ships return to
Iserlohn at once.
[OBERSTEIN]
Please wait.
[SEECKT] Hmm. I don't recall
asking for your opinion,
Captain Oberstein!
While I am aware of that,
I wish to express
my views nevertheless.
This is clearly a trap.
I'm starting to think
those artificial eyes of yours
see everything as an ambush.
Excellency. Listen to me.
Enough! All fleets turn around!
Head to Iserlohn Fortress
at combat speed two!
Those space moles will be
indebted to us after this!
[OBERSTEIN] Communications
have been disrupted for so long,
and he isn't even curious why
they're suddenly working again.
There's no point
talking to such
a small-minded bastard.
Full of anger and no reason.
[SOLDIER 7C] The enemy fleet
has entered firing range.
[SOLDIER 7D] Energy charge
to the fortress's main cannon
is complete.
[SOLDIER 7E]
Aim is set.
Ready to fire at any time.
Change the main cannon's angle.
Set it to seven degrees.
[FREDERICA gasps]
[MURAI] Forgive me, but at
that angle, the shot will only
succeed in grazing
the armada's left flank.
[YANG] They'll get the
message loud and clear.
Fire it.
[SOLDIER 7F]
They attacked their allies?
[SOLDIER 7G]
No. It must be the rebels!
[SOLDIER 7H] What do we do?
We can't fire back!
How do we escape Thor's Hammer?
[SEECKT]
Have they gone mad? Return fire!
Hit the fortress with
everything we have!
[YANG]
Change the main cannon's angle.
Target the fleet's right flank.
[YANG]
Fire again.
[WALTER] I think you'd be
hard-pressed to find anyone
who would call this combat.
"Massacre" is a word
that comes to mind.
[YANG]
You're right. It's one-sided.
We may have their base, but we
won't act like the Empire.
[YANG] Allow them the
opportunity to surrender.
If they refuse to do so,
advise them to flee
and we will not pursue.
[SOLDIER 7B]
Transmission from the fortress!
"Iserlohn has been
occupied by the Alliance."
But how?
[SOLDIER 7B "Further bloodshed
will benefit no one.
Surrender."
[SEECKT]
They must be joking!
[SOLDIER 7B] Also. "If you
refuse surrender, then flee.
We will not pursue. Alliance
Navy Rear Admiral Yang Wen-li."
[SEECKT gasps]
[SOLDIER 7B]
Your Excellency!
We've confirmed
an Alliance fleet behind us!
We'll be caught in
a pincer attack!
[SEECKT]
We're surrounded?
[SOLDIER 7B]
What shall we do?
We won't surrender
or run from Alliance scum!
To face the Kaiser after
losing the fortress and half
of our ships, that's a fate
worse than a thousand deaths!
[SOLDIER 7I] "You fail to
understand the heart
of a warrior. We know the
path of dying to preserve
our honor, but to live
in disgrace, we know not.
All of our ships
will henceforth charge
into an honorable death.
The only way to repay the
Kaiser's favor towards us."
You call that a warrior's heart?
[SOLDIER 7C]
All enemy ships are charging!
Can you identify
the garrison's flagship?
[SOLDIER 7J]
Yes, sir.
Then concentrate
all fire power on it.
This is the final barrage.
If they lose the lead ship,
the remainder will retreat.
Fire.
[gasps]
[SOLDIER 7C]
Enemy flagship destroyed.
All other ships are retreating
and leaving the front.
[SOLDIERS cheering]
Sub-lieutenant Greenhill.
[FREDERICA]
Yes?
Would you send a
transmission to the Alliance?
Tell them "It's over, we won and
if you ask me to do it again.
I can't." Take care of the rest.
I'm gonna go get some sleep
Understood, sir.
The heart of a warrior, indeed.
As long as men like him exist,
this war can't end,
and I've reached
my limit of dealing
with those types of soldiers.
[OBERSTEIN]
I suppose some will see me as
a coward and a runaway.
I'll certainly be the ideal
scapegoat for anyone looking
to preserve their reputation
after this debacle.
[OBERSTEIN]
Now, then.
[ADRIAN]
Oh?
So Iserlohn has fallen
into the Alliance's hands?
[BOLTIK] That is what's being
reported, Landesherr.
Who would have ever
predicted they'd be successful?
Yang Wen-li. I'm beginning to
find the man quite intriguing.
[ADRIAN] Contact Heinessen
and collect information on him.
Sir.
It would be
prudent of us to ascertain
what kind of man he is.
[JULIAN] "Iserlohn Fortress,
which we've sacrificed countless
lives and resources
attempting to overthrow,
was recently brought down
in a daring raid resulting
in zero causalities
to our side.
The brilliant strategy
that resulted in
the base's capture has truly
earned its architect the
titles 'The Unbeatable Magician'
and 'Miracle Yang.'"
Hear that?
[YANG]
Magic and miracles.
Those people have no
idea what I went through.
Still, this means I've done as
asked, and my work is complete.
[YANG]
Now I can request retirement
with a clear conscience.
[JULIAN]
Retirement plans aside.
I think you've earned the
praise everyone's giving you.
[YANG]
Uh-- Ah...
So why don't you
just let yourself enjoy it?
You're only praised for
as long as you continue to win.
But if I were
to keep on fighting,
I'd eventually lose.
Watching people's
attitudes shift would
be interesting, but only
if it was happening
to someone other than me.
[YANG]
By the way, Julian.
Yes, can I do something for you?
Well, for starters,
you can give me back
that bottle of brandy.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These : Episode 8,
"The Castrop Rebellion."