[JULIAN]
Commodore Yang! It's morning!
If you don't wake up soon,
you'll be late!
[YANG groans] Who's going to
be late for what now?
[JULIAN]
I said rise and shine!
[YANG groans]
[JULIAN] What a way
to start your morning.
If I didn't wake you, you
probably would have missed
the memorial service.
You're right. Thanks, Julian.
[JULIAN groans]
[YANG] By the way, where did
you put those books from the box
I hadn't unpacked yet?
[JULIAN]
On the shelf, where they belong.
[YANG] And the Wanli porcelain
from the box next to it?
[JULIAN] I set it inside
the hutch for display.
[JULIAN]
See you tonight.
Listen. Julian.
Yes?
Sorry for making you do so much.
I'll try to act more like a real
guardian when I get back.
See ya.
[gasps]
Commodore Yang!
[YANG yawns]
[ALEX] Doesn't look like
you're quite awake yet.
Late night, Hero of Astarte?
And who would that be?
The person standing
right in front of me, of course.
That's what the press
has been calling you,
at least--no sense fighting it.
Not to dampen the mood,
but... we didn't win.
That's true,
the Alliance Navy did lose.
And that's exactly the reason
why we need a hero now.
We wouldn't have
any need for one
if we were on the winning side.
After a defeat, you have
to take the people's focus away
from what's going on.
It was probably the same
for El Facil, am I right?
By the way, why is your
uniform completely drenched?
Well... [chuckles]
[applause]
Brave citizens and soldiers.
I ask you, for what purpose
have we all assembled
here in this auditorium today?
To commemorate the lives of the
one and a half million heroes
who perished in the
battle of Astarte.
Those who nobly
laid down their lives.
Who defended the freedom
and peace of our homeland.
But also...
...to remind us.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen,
the departed have a message
for those left behind.
There was something at stake
more valuable than their lives.
What is that something?
The preservation of our
homeland and our freedom!
Why did 1.5 million
soldiers die?
Because their leaders
failed to command them
effectively enough.
[TRUNICHT] Because our way
of life comes at a cost!
It demands sacrifice!
I would like to
make this abundantly clear.
Our freedom, our homeland,
more than anything else,
these are worthy of defending
with our very lives!
And pacifists
advocating for reconciliation
with the Empire--
Awaken from your delusions!
Peace is hard-earned,
not attained with ease!
[YANG]
I don't know.
Warmongering from behind a nice,
safe lectern looks pretty easy.
Those who oppose this
righteous war are in support
of the Galactic Empire's
autocratic totalitarianism!
They have forsaken our
founding principles!
I say do not
forget our grand history!
Our proud republic with
its illustrious legacy!
Our homeland and its freedoms!
I implore everyone to
stand with me in united defense,
of the one thing in life
truly worth defending!
Let us fight now,
for the homeland!
Long live the Alliance!
Long live the Republic!
Death to the Empire!
[CROWD]
Long live the Alliance!
Long live the Republic!
Death to the Empire!
--[applause]
--[chanting continues]
Long live the Alliance!
Long live the Republic!
Death to the Empire!
Get up. Why aren't you standing?
I'm just honoring
the theme of his speech.
This land is built upon freedom,
which means I that can
choose not to stand.
I am merely exercising
those liberties, Captain.
Then why is it
you're choosing not to stand?
I'm free to not
answer that question.
What, are you trying
to make the Navy look bad?
[TRUNICHT]
Christian.
[CHRISTIAN]
Hmph.
Now, then.
It is important
that we remember,
the greatest weapon
in our arsenal is unity.
[TRUNICHT] So long as
we live in a free country,
governed as a
democratic republic.
No objective, however
noble it may appear,
can be forced upon the people.
Chairman Trunicht, excuse me.
My name is Jessica Edwards.
Jessica?
[JESSICA]
I have something to say.
I'm the fiancée of
Jean Robert Lapp,
of the Sixth Fleet
who died in Astarte.
Correction. I was his fiancée.
[gasps] Well, that's
extremely regrettable.
A shame, truly.
I'm not here to
demand your condolences.
My Jean. He died a noble death.
He gave his life in defense of
the homeland that he loved.
Yes, of course.
Miss, you are a role model that
all women on the home front
should strive to emulate.
I have no doubt a brave
and generous spirit like yours
will be richly rewarded.
That's kind of you to say.
However, Chairman,
I did not come here today
to be commended,
but to ask a single question.
Yes? And what
question might that be, miss?
Where are you at this moment?
Um. Where am I?
My fiancée went
willingly to the battlefield
to protect everything
you claim to hold dear.
Because of that, he will
never come home to me.
Again, Chairman. Where are you?
Where do you stand
as you glorify death?
I gave you Jean!
That was my sacrifice!
You preach the
need for such sacrifices,
but where is your family?
There's no fault
in your speech,
and I won't deny a single word.
But are you living by
the same standard?
Security, please
escort this young lady
from the premises.
She's clearly upset.
Please play the national anthem.
I'm done.
[national anthem plays]
[gasps]
Let's go.
Y-Yang!
I don't think this is the place
you need to be
right now, Jessica.
[alarm sounds
[horn honking]
[JESSICA gasps]
Find something
you can hold onto.
Right!
[horn honking]
[JESSICA grunts]
[YANG gasps]
[JESSICA gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
[JESSICA] I'm sorry
I dragged you into this.
[YANG]
What happened wasn't your fault.
[JESSICA]
Yang.
[YANG]
Mm-hmm?
[JESSICA] You must have thought
what I did during that ceremony
was really horrible.
[YANG]
How so?
Most of the bereaved
families are enduring
their grief in silence,
but I had to make a big scene,
shout about what I was feeling.
I'm sure you're disgusted.
No. I'm not at all
[JESSICA] I heard about
everything you did
at Astarte, Yang.
Jean Robert was always so
impressed by your achievements.
"Yang's the pride of
the class" he'd say.
Outside of yourself,
the entire admiralty should be
ashamed of their incompetence.
Over 1,000,000 people died in
a single battle because of them.
It's a complete
ethical disgrace.
[YANG] I don't know if
I agree with you there.
[JESSICA]
Hmm?
The admirals
may have been foolish
by allowing that
many people to die.
But then, what if we'd been on
the winning side and killed over
a million of their soldiers?
Should we be praised
for taking that many lives?
[JESSICA gasps]
Whether you win or you lose,
there's no place
for ethics in war.
I'm glad to see you
haven't changed one bit.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to be argumentative.
I should be going,
but thank you
for keeping me company, Yang.
You take care.
Keep on climbing the ranks.
For Jean Robert, too.
[YANG]
Hmph.
[JULIAN]
Welcome home, Commodore.
Sorry to keep you waiting
[JULIAN] I was worried you
wouldn't be coming home tonight.
I'm glad you made it
back in time for dinner.
Afterall, I cooked up that
Irish stew you always enjoy.
Well, in that case,
I'm glad I showed up
with an appetite.
But what made you think
I wasn't coming home?
I heard you
ducked out of the ceremony
with a beautiful woman.
[gasps]
Well, at least that's
what Rear Admiral Caselnes
told me when he called
the house earlier.
[YANG sighs]
What a classy guy.
[YANG]
Your future?
You haven't even
finished school yet.
No, but there's a system
that allows students
to earn extra credits
and graduate early.
[YANG]
Hmm. I see.
So, are you planning on
becoming a soldier, then?
Yes. I am a
soldier's son after all.
There isn't any law
that says a child has
to inherit their
parent's career.
My father was an interstellar
trader and look at me now.
[JULIAN] The military's
paying for my upbringing.
If I don't enlist, those loans
will need to be paid back.
I'll pay for it.
[gasps]
You really shouldn't
underestimate
your legal guardian.
I've been putting
money aside for it.
And besides, why are you
so eager to graduate
ahead of schedule anyway?
How about you try having
a little fun instead?
There's no way
I could leave you with
that kind of burden!
Hey, you're still a kid
so don't talk back to me.
Haven't you heard?
Children are supposed to leech
off adults while they grow up.
Thank you very much, sir.
But still...
[beeping]
Maybe I'm out of touch,
but are packs of clowns
loitering outside of
people's homes at
night the latest trend?
They're the
Patriotic Knight Corps.
[YANG] Huh. I don't know any
circus troupe by that name.
[JULIAN] It's a radical
nationalist group.
They've become notorious
for harassing anyone
who criticizes the Republic.
Or opposes the war.
What I don't get, is what they
could be doing at our house.
[YANG gasps]
[groans]
[VOICE]
Commodore Yang.
We of the Patriotic
Knight Corps condemn you!
Drunk off arrogance
from your exploits,
you have disturbed
the unity of our navy
and compromised
its will to fight.
You know what you have done.
[VOICE]
You chose to disgrace
a sacred memorial service!
While everyone else in
attendance responded to
the Chairman's speech by
standing and swearing
to defeat the Empire.
You refused!
By remaining seated, you
assumed an attitude of ridicule
not only towards
the citizens present
but the entire republic!
If you have
anything to say
or choose to
refute these charges,
step outside and face us like
the soldier you claim to be!
Please tell me
what they're accusing you
of isn't true.
Well, kinda?
Why didn't you stand?
Even if you didn't agree with
what the Chairman was saying,
what harm would it have
done to get up and clap
with everybody else?
Then nobody would
have had to know
what you were really thinking.
You sound more like
Rear Admiral Caselnes
than I'm comfortable with.
There's no reason to bring
the Rear Admiral into this!
Even a child would have told you
to just stand up and applaud!
[VOICE]
Not coming out?
Seems we'll have
to convince you.
[YANG]
Get down!
Julian, what's the
sprinkler code on the domcom?
[JULIAN] It's 2-A-4.
What're you planning to do?
[YANG] Heh. I think we need to
teach these guys a thing or two
about having some manners.
Okay...
[VOICE] How about it?
Ready to talk to us now?
If you don't answer,
we'll just send another.
[clicking]
[SOLDIER 5A grunts]
[SOLDIER 5F groans]
[VOICE]
Stop! Stand your grou--
[gasps, growls]
Maybe in the future,
those thugs will think twice
before they anger a gentleman.
It can be a dangerous pastime.
[YANG]
I can help with that.
No. Thank you,
but you'll only get in the way.
Why don't you just take
a seat on the table
until I'm finished
with the cleaning?
You mean on
that table? You're kidding.
[YANG]
My Wanli porcelain...
It belonged to my father--
the only thing of his
that wasn't counterfeit.
[phone rings]
Hey there, kiddo.
Put that guardian of
yours on for me, would ya?
He's over there.
I'm just going to
assume sitting on tables
wasn't frowned upon
in your household
when you were growing up.
On certain days of the week.
Yeah, whatever.
There's a matter that
demands your attention.
You have to report
to the Integrated Tactical
Operations Center.
[YANG]
As in right now?
[ALEX] It's a direct order
from Chief Sithole.
Did he say what
he wanted me to come in for?
[ALEX]
All I know is it's urgent,
so you'd better get going.
I'll see you there later. 'Bye.
I'll probably be out
late, so don't wait up for me.
[JULIAN]
Yes, Commodore.
[YANG] I think we'll eventually
be able to laugh about
what happened here
tonight, but for now,
I have a feeling things
will be getting worse
before they get better.
It may be gradual,
but I'm afraid we're in
for some dark times ahead.
I understand.
And, sir, whatever I've
said, please never doubt
my trust in you.
I wouldn't ever want you to
start second guessing yourself.
Above all else,
I want you to walk the path
that you believe is right.
If there's anybody
who knows what's best,
well, that'd be you!
[YANG sighs]
[SITHOLE] I see you haven't
gotten any better at chess.
Sir, did you truly call me
out at this hour to assess
whether my chess skills
had improved recently?
Of course not.
You're here because I needed
to inform you of something.
The letter of
appointment won't formally
be issued until tomorrow,
but to cut to the chase,
I wanted to tell you that you're
being promoted to Rear Admiral.
This decision
is firm, not tentative.
You know why you're being
promoted, don't you?
Because I lost
at Astarte, right?
You really haven't
changed since the academy.
A sharp tongue that's concealed
behind a benign expression.
It was your signature even
back when you were a cadet.
That aside, my guess was
correct, wasn't it, Headmaster?
Chief. Uh, sorry about that.
[SITHOLE] And what led
you to that conclusion?
[YANG] There's ancient military
texts that say showering
someone with rewards is
proof you're in dire straits.
Apparently out of
the need to divert
people's attention from defeat.
I'll admit that
in a sense, you are correct.
We have just suffered our
greatest loss in recent history.
Both our servicemen and our
citizens are badly shaken up.
The easiest way
to soothe their fears right now
is to give them a hero.
That hero would be you,
Rear Admiral Yang.
[YANG]
Hmph.
[SITHOLE] I suppose
you aren't keen on the idea
of becoming an artificial hero.
Why don't we change
the subject, then?
Before the start of combat in
Astarte you submitted
a battle-plan of yours
to Vice Admiral Paetta.
Do you believe we would
have won if that proposal
had been implemented
as you suggested?
Yes. I do.
Would it not be
possible to use this strategy
of yours against the Imperials
on another occasion?
And whenever that time comes,
perhaps we could have our
revenge on Count Lowengromm.
[YANG] If this victory
has made him arrogant,
and he can't resist the
temptation of taking on
a massive force with
a smaller one again,
I'd say the plan
could be revived.
However...
Go on.
[YANG]
Quite frankly, sir,
I don't think it's
likely to happen.
[YANG] While defeating a larger
force with a smaller one
certainly looks spectacular.
It strays from
common tactical practice.
It's really more
sleight of hand than
it is sound military strategy.
I'd find it hard to
believe that Count Lohengromm
doesn't know that.
He'll most likely attack with an
overwhelmingly large force next.
That's true,
you're probably right.
There was one more thing,
and this is a tentative
decision, not a firm one.
There will be some
changes happening to
the Alliance Navy's formation.
After much deliberation,
it's been decided
to reinforce the remnants
of the Fourth and Sixth Fleets,
with additional recruits
and then combine them to
create the Thirteenth Fleet.
You will most likely be
appointed as the first commander
of this new force.
I didn't think command of
a fleet was given to anyone
not ranked vice
admiral or higher, sir.
This new fleet will be
approximately half the size of
a normal one.
You should also know that the
first mission the Thirteenth
will be tasked with
is the capture of
the Imperials'
Iserlohn Fortress.
[YANG scoffs] You're telling me,
you mean to take Iserlohn
with only half a fleet?
[SITHOLE]
Correct.
I'm sorry,
but have you been listening
to anything I've said tonight?
Every word.
And honestly, it's only
convinced me further.
Then you actually
believe it's possible.
[SITHOLE] What I believe,
Rear Admiral Yang,
is that if you can't do it,
there is no one who can.
[SITHOLE]
Do you think you can do it?
[SITHOLE] If you were
to successfully lead this
new fleet in the capture
of Iserlohn Fortress,
it might solve some
problems for you.
Complete a mission like this,
and Chairman Trunicht
will have no choice.
He will be forced to recognize
your talents in the field
regardless of whatever
his personal feelings
are toward you.
[sighs]
I'll give it my best shot.
[ALEX] The chief has about
70 days left in his term.
Obviously, he's hoping
to win a second.
Which doesn't leave
you much time to capture
Iserlohn Fortress before
the election happens.
If the Thirteenth's
mission is successful,
then it means the
Chief's standing
with Chairman Trunicht
will be reinforced.
The man is cunning,
I'll give him that.
[ALEX] Come on, the chief
is practically a saint
compared to that bastard.
Speaking of which,
the Patriotic Knight Corps.
Their leader is...
None other than the
Chairman himself, am I right?
That much was apparent.
Heh.
[YANG groans]
Things're getting busy.
You'd better rest up.
Honestly. Why would anyone in
their right mind be a soldier?
You can complain
as much as you want,
but the navy will
never let go of you.
Be ready, Yang Wen-li.
Thank you for the lift, sir.
I guess I'm not going
to get to drink any of the tea
Julian makes for a while.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These : Episode 6,
"The Capture
of Iserlohn (Part One)"