Thank you for shopping with us.
Thank you for-
They have it, Jun. This is the
kind of tea they wanted, right?
[Jun] Let's go with that for
now. Oh, and we need sugar, too.
[Azusa] Why don't you go, get us
a basket?
[Jun] Okay.
[Old Woman] Excuse me.
[Azusa] Let's see, we're also
suppose to get toothpicks,
right?
[Cashier] Oh, yes
I'm sorry, ma'am!
[Azusa] We need these, please.
Yeah, sure thing, miss.
We'll also need
a receipt, please.
And you can make it out to
Sakuragaoka Girls' High School,
Class 2-1 festival fund.
Oh yeah, and under "Comments,"
please put "Tea supply for
mock coffee shop."
(opening song,
"Utauyo!! MIRACLE")
[Azusa] Do you think we
should've bought more milk
while we were there?
No, we should probably wait
until we run out again.
I can't believe how hectic
it is today...
The first day is always that
way. Besides, that's what
makes it so much fun.
[Jun] Something wrong?
Is the Light Music Club show
Oh, sorry about that.
[Azusa] tomorrow gonna go
alright?
[Jun] Let's get back to
the classroom.
(minor freak out)
Look the paint is peeling!
Don't worry. I think
that should be just fine.
[Girl 2] This area here
is the problem.
[Girl 3] Hey wait I forget,
[Girl 3] is the right color
for this spot?
[Girl 4] Where did the
prop dagger go?
[Girl 5] Yeah, yeah, sure.
[Girl2] Romeo!
Um, my line...
You broke my concentration, and
now I've forgotten every single
one of my lines!
O Romeo! Romeo!
Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
O! Uh...um I...
O, speak again...
speak again...bright angel?
Why are you getting yourself all
tensed up again NOW?
[Yui] Granny, my nice neighbor
lady told me that whenever you
get nervous,
you should write the word
"pumpkin" on your palms and then
swallow it!
I think you might
have heard that wrong.
Yui. I think she meant, "Imagine
the audience members are all
pumpkins".
Really? You think so?
You swallow the character
for "people."
[Mio] Pu-um...
...p-kin.
What are you? Mio!
Oh man, she tried
to swallow it for real...
Does anyone know if
all the costumes ready?
Miss Yamanaka was in charge
of costumes, right?
She said that she was going
to lock herself in the sewing
room
and work all night.
Has anybody seen her?
I'll go check on her!
Okay, thanks a lot Chika!
[Tsumugi] Is this all of the
props?
[Girl 1] I didn't see Romeo's
dagger.
[Girl 2] Mio!
[Mio] Please, don't talk to me
right now!
Look you've got it right there,
Mugi!
[Yui] Hey, now!
[Tsumugi] All that's left
now is the lighting,
[Tsumugi] and sound effects.
[Girl 3] Don't touch it yet!
[Girl 3] The paint isn't dry!
They look pretty hectic...
[Ui] Thank you for coming!
[Azusa] I'm here!
Welcome back, Azusa-chan.
How did things look in my
sister's class?
They looked pretty busy, so I
just turned around and left
without bothering them.
Yeah, their play is this
afternoon.
Hey, how long are you two gonna
keep goofing off out there?
Oh, I'm sorry!
[Jun] You go ahead and
handle the kitchen, Ui.
[Ui] Okay, sure.
[Jun] Azusa, you handle this.
[Azusa] No problem.
Wow, I'm beat...
Finally time for a break...
Those crepes look delicious!
You're pretty energetic.
[Ui] Oh wow. That one
looks interesting!
[Hawker] Step right up!
[Azusa] Mammoth Meat?
Wow, Class 2 really went
all-out!
Their costumes are cute, too...
[Jun] They're doing pictures,
too. They thought of everything.
The costumes at the mammoth
booth sure were cute.
I hear that Miss Yamanaka
made all of theirs,
plus Class 3's vampire cafe
costumes.
[Azusa] Miss Yamanaka
did all that? Just exactly...
...how spread thin are you?
[Nodoka] Ma'am? Are you all
right?
[Sawako] Yes... I spread myself
a little too thin this year, but
I'll manage.
Because every costume
I make is a labor of love!
Mio-chan, you look amazing!
Come on, don't stare!
[Ritsu] Begging your pardon,
good sirs!
[Tsumugi] Oh, you're
super cute, too, Ri-chan!
[Ritsu] Right?
[Yui] Yeah, but I still think
it's kinda weird, you playing
Juliet!
If we did a survey,
I think that 100 of 100 people
would say that YOU are the weird
one here.
Alright, I need all the actors!
Okay!
Come on, you. Let's go.
[Nodoka] Our Romeo is
being henpecked by Juliet...
Look at that crowd!
[Yui] It's already a full house!
Hey, look, isn't that
Mio's fan club over there?
Hey Nodoka-chan,
is it true that Sokabe-senpai is
going to be coming to see our
show tomorrow?
Yep, she sent me a message
saying she couldn't wait to see
it.
All right, let's all go out
there and nail this play
everybody!
[Announcer] And now, a
performance of...
[Mifuyu] Guys, this is
the moment we've...
[Announcer]
Romeo and Juliet by Class 3-2.
[Mifuyu] all worked really hard
for. So let's give it all we've
got!
Let's have no regrets!
Is everybody ready?
Ow!
[Mifuyu] Okay!
Then let's break a leg out
there!
[Class] Yeah!
The auditorium is packed
already!
Are there any seats left?
[Azusa] Towards the end,
the others hardly ever came by,
the club room to practice for
our show.
Do they even care about it
anymore?
[Sawa] Azusa-chan!
Yes?
Come on! Over here! Hurry!
[Azusa] No, I shouldn't
think things like that.
Sorry about that.
(buzzer buzzing)
[Azusa] I mean, after all,
this is their very last school
festival.
I just need to keep my fingers
crossed and hope their play
goes well.
O he jests at scars that
have never felt a wound.
If thou wishest then laugh.
For I have known pain!
The pain of being lost in love!
I know this sweet ache in my
bosom well!
So do the trees in this play
really need to have faces?
It's better not question these
things.
Didst thou hear a sound
encroaching on the night?
What manner of scoundrel has
found his...
[Jun] I'm on the edge
of my seat.
[Eri] ...way into the
Capulet orchard?
Yeah...
[Azusa] Me too, but for another
reason.
I'm terrified that Yui-senpai
might screw everything up!
O Romeo, wherefore art thou
Romeo?
O, speak again, bright angel!
How camest thou hither?
Tell me, and wherefore,
the orchard walls are high
and hard to climb!
With love's light wings did
I o'er-perch these walls;
For stony limits cannot hold
love out!
O, Romeo!
My fair Juliet!
Stop messing around!
I'm not just keep going!
Romeo!
Fair Juliet!
My heart's pounding a mile a
minute!
Mine is too...
[Azusa] So is mine...
...but not because of the
story!
Within the infant rind
of this small flower...
[Nodoka] Good job holding it in,
Yui.
[Chika] Two such opposed kings
encamp them still in man as well
as herbs, grace...
You would have ruined the whole
play if you had let go with a
sneeze out there.
[Mio] Good marrow, Father.
[Ritsu] I mean, "Forsooth!
[Yui] Ri-chan, you're still in
character!
[Ritsu] What's wrong with that?
I'm staying in character
until the play is over!
It's all going smoothly so far.
Mio-chan seems to be getting
into the swing of things, too.
My heart's dear love is set on
hers.
[Mio] But this I pray, that
thou consent to marry us to-day.
[Chizuru] It's gone!
[Chizuru] The tombstone prop
for the final graveyard scene!
I don't see it anywhere!
Is she whom thy didst love,
so soon forsaken?
K-ON!
In his wisdom,
her father hastes our marriage
to stop the inundation
of her tears.
It wasn't in our
classroom, either!
Well, if it wasn't in there
then, it means that it must have
been dropped somewhere,
along the way when
it was being delivered here.
Could we do it without
a tombstone?
But the graveyard scene is the
climax of Romeo and Juliet! We
need to have it!
Right. I really don't
want to this halfway.
What if we made one now?!
There's no way we would
finish it on time.
What if we borrowed one
from a class
that's doing a haunted house
for the festival?
Japanese graves are different.
[Shizuka] Wait a minute,
I think I remember seeing
something that,
looked like a tombstone
at the Occult Club's display.
I have a friend in that club,
so I'm going to go and ask
if we can borrow for the play!
What about your part?
Yui! You do it!
You can count on me!
I'll go with her and make sure
it'll work!
Are you going to be able to
memorize your lines in time?
[Yui] Nodoka-chan!
Quick I need a script!
Calm don, Yui. It's alright.
Yeah, don't worry,
you don't actually have any
lines.
If I may trust the
flattering truth of sleep,
my dreams presage
some joyful news at hand.
She's playing a different tree.
A double tree role?
[Occult club member] This is not
a tombstone, this is a Rosetta
Stone,
inscribed with various ancient
languages.
The text is mostly words of
praise for Epiphanies
Eucharistos
of ancient Egypt's Ptolemaic
dynasty.
[Occult club member] We would be
happy to lend it to you, though.
If you need it.
[Both] Oh thank you!
We'll bring it back in a few
minutes!
[Chika] Who bare my letter,
then, to Romeo?
By my brother hood, unhappy
fortune!
We'll never make it!
We got it!
Okay, let's all get to work now!
They seem like they're
a little bit frazzled.
I wonder if everything's okay?
Ah, dear and darling Juliet,
Why art thou yet so fair?
I will stay with thee, and never
from the palace of night depart
again.
Here will I remain with worms
that are thy chamber-maids!
Looks like we're going to
make it without any foul-ups!
Yes...
O Romeo!
O churl! Drunk all, and left no
friendly drop to help me after?
O happy dagger!
This is thy sheath;
there rust, and let me die!
Oh, wow...
It's almost like,
Mio-senpai and Ritsu-senpai,
are really Romeo and Juliet.
They must have rehearsed
like crazy.
It's no wonder they didn't have
time to come to the music room.
[Azusa] But still...
It's like they've really
forgotten all about the
Light Music Club!
Wow Azusa, it really
moved you that much?
Honey, we're home!
Boy, I am totally beat!
[Tsumugi] You two were
really terrific!
See? Practice makes perfect!
[Yui] Azu-nyan!
So what did you think?!
How was our play?!
Well, um...
What's this?
Are you feeling lonely,
because we haven't been
hanging out with you lately?
No, of course I'm not!
It's...
Well, you haven't been coming to
the club room much lately.
And that's made me
worried that, well...
that you don't care about
our show anymore.
Azusa...
I-I'm so sorry! I know that
you've been really busy with
your play and all.
I mean if you want to put
on such a great play,
you can't do it without
tons of rehearsing, right?
Geez, sometimes you're
such a dummy.
We do care about the Light Music
Club. More than anything
in the world.
We're sorry for making you
worry, Azusa.
You mean it?
They're right, Azu-nyan!
As for me, I think about you
all day long, every single day!
Think about me a little less!
Right! We're gonna sleep here
and practice for tomorrow's
show!
[Mio] Is it okay to spend
the night at school?
[Ritsu] Not a problem!
[Tsumugi] Even if we didn't
bring any supplies for us to
sleep over with?
[Ritsu] No problem!
Can I have all the refills
of rice that I want?!
[Ritsu] All you want!
Wait, what?
[Sawako] Girls, I have
sleeping bags for you all.
See?
Thanks, Sawa-chan! Are you
pulling another all-nighter
tonight?
Yeah, I still haven't finished
all of your costumes for the
show tomorrow.
I have to lock myself in
the sewing room again.
By the way, no peeking, promise?
Just like The Crane Wife...
Okay, commence practicing!
[Girls] Yeah!
(Light Music Club practicing
"Fuwa Fuwa Time!")
Sounds like Sis and the others
are practicing really hard...
[Ritsu] Yum!
There's plenty more where those
came from, so please eat all you
want, everyone.
[Yui] Ui, these are so good!
We've already arranged
for a really great dessert,
so you're more than welcome
to join us if you want, Ui-chan.
Really? Can I?
[Ui] Thank you very much!
[Mio] No sweets before
bedtime...
It's all right, Mio. Tonight it
doesn't matter at hour we eat
our cake.
For you see,
we're not going to bed at all!
We're not going to sleep?
Of course not! With school
festivals,
it's all about staying up
all night to get ready!
I won't let you fall asleep,
little kitty!
[Azusa] Please leave me out of
it.
[Yui] Meanie!
(knock on the door)
Staying here overnight is fine,
but have you submitted the
proper form?
I forgot all about it!
I'll give you a copy, then.
The application!
[Ritsu] Oh you're awesome,
Nodoka!
Thank you so much, Nodoka-chan!
[Ui] We have plenty of food.
Please have one.
Thank you that's very kind.
[Ui] Are there a lot of students
staying up all night to get
ready?
Yes. Even though it's the second
day, there are quite a few.
Why do you suppose so many
people wait until the last
minute to get ready?
I'm sure that some of
them do it deliberately.
I mean, staying up all night
is kind of fun, isn't it?
Alright, who are you, and
what have you done with Nodoka?
Well, I'M going home, anyway.
[Jun] Azusa, let's go home-
So Jazz Club isn't staying up
all night?
[Jun] What, the Light Music Club
is?
I'm so jealous!
No fair! It's just not fair!
[Ritsu] Okay, the amp's
staying off from now on.
[Tsumugi] What will you do
for drums?
[Ritsu] I'll just pile these
all up like this, and presto!
I've got myself and instant drum
kit!
[Mio] Don't pile up
our textbooks!
[Ritsu] You should have seen us,
we were so freaked out when
we couldn't find the tombstone!
I thought we were going to
practice straight through the
night until morning.
[Ritsu] We need a change of
pace. Clear out the cobwebs, you
know?
[Mio] Azusa?
Boy it looks like there are a
lot of students in there who are
still awake.
[Ritsu] Hey, you know,
come to think of it,
we were rushing around all day
getting ready for the play.
We didn't get a chance to see
anything.
Then this is the perfect time!
Why don't we go around and look
at the student festival at
night?
That's a great idea!
Let's do some exploring!
[Yui] Guys! Come look at this!
Their meat is mammoth!
That's really elaborate.
I had some for lunch.
How was it?
[Yui] Oou!
So what kind of meat have
you found this time?
[Yui] It's Juliet's grave stone!
Somebody must've thought
it belonged to this stand,
so they delivered it here by
mistake.
Well, it does fit in here...
[Tsumugi] Oh, hey! Why don't we
go and share some of the great
food,
that Ui-chan brought for
us tonight with the Occult Club?
[Ritsu] Good idea.
We can thank them for helping
us.
[Ritsu] What's the matter?
Are you scared, Mio?
[Mio] I-I am not!
[Yui] Come on, we'll be fine!
Let's go!
[Yui] Looks like they're still
up.
[Azusa] I wonder what kind of
presentation they're getting
ready?
[Ritsu] Some kind of
bloodcurdling ritual, you
suppose?
(knock on the door)
Hello?
Come in.
Thank you all.
If you like to, please come
to our discussion,
on cattle mutilations
tomorrow. It'll be fun.
[Yui] Sure!
[Ritsu] We're there!
Just so long as we don't
get abducted ourselves...
Thank you, we'd be honored if
you would come see our show
tomorrow, too.
[Ritsu] Mio's gonna get abducted
on stage!
[Mio] I am not!
[Yui] You're so lucky, Mio-chan!
Wait a minute are you jealous?
[Tsumugi] What are alien
abductions?
[Ritsu] Are you blind?
[Ritsu] We even managed
to make friends with
the girls of the Occult Club at
the end.
You know, school festivals
really are the best!
I know what you mean.
[Yui] There's still some
onigiri left in the box.
Shall we take them over to
Sawa-chan?
But she made us promise not to
peek.
[Yui] If we peek,
she'll fly back to the moon!
[Ritsu] Hey, you got the wrong
fairy tale!
Is it really all that funny?
Is it me, or do you get kinda
wound up when you're at school
at night?
I know, I know! I'm itching
to get into mischief!
Mischief...
Can I help you with something?
Not really.
Everyone's totally snapped.
All right, let's write
a new song right now!
You've snapped, too, Mugi?
I wanna do My Protracted Love
for You!
No way, it's gonna be
School My School Bag!
No, My Protracted Love for You!
[Mio] In that case, let's do
The Raccoon Stole My Heart!
What do you mean, "In that
case"?
Azusa's finally snapped, too?
No it's just really, really
late. I think it's about time we
all called it a-
But I still haven't had any
yakisoba...
I really like yakisoba.
[Mio] She's already asleep.
[Ritsu] That was fast.
[Azusa] Okay then, lights out.
[Yui] Oh, my!
[Ritsu] Show me all you have
and I shall be avenged!
(laughter)
[Mio] Quiet down, Ritsu!
[Ritsu] Why are you singling me
out?!
Have at you!
Fine, whatever.
Tomorrow?
Let's give it all we've got.
[Sawako] Girls! I've finished
your costumes for the show!
Oh, come on...
Hey! Wake up!
Don't ignore me!
That hurts more than anything!
Sorry, Sawa-chan... We're too
groggy to work up a decent
comeback for you...
But I worked so hard all night,
just to make these for you!
Wow!
It's so cute!
Sawa-chan, that's great!
[Ritsu] Good job, Sawa-chan!
Is this... what it feels like?!
Praise me more!
[Yui] Good job, Sawa-chan!
[Sawako] More! More!
[Ritsu] Good job, Sawako!
[Sawako] More praise!
(closing song, "NO, Thank You!")
[Ritsu] Well? Should we head
over there?
[Yui] It'll be okay, Mio-chan!
[Tsumugi] Just remember
our special training!
[Mio] You're right.
[Azusa] Just play like you
always do.
[Mio] Okay.
[Ritsu] You guys ready to rock?!
[Girls] Yeah!
[Tsumugi] Another live show for
us!
[Girls] Yeah!
[Azusa] Our best gig ever!
[Yui] And then we get to
eat cake!
[Girl] Yeah! Huh?