(band playing, "Fuwa Fuwa Time")
(cicadas chirping)
Drumming's going to kill me!
(groans)
It's another scorcher today.
Huh? Where did Yui run off to?
(groans)
It's so hot...
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
(sighs) I wish summer would
just go away already... Ugh.
Oh, please. You'll be saying
the exact opposite once
winter's here.
Noooo...
[Azusa]
Here's some water, Senpai.
(happy)
Thank you, Azu-nyan! Thank you!
Azu-nyan...(groans)
My face is hot...
[Mio] Then don't do that.
I have to say, it's like
an oven in here...
Long hair makes
your neck sweat like crazy.
Oh! Why don't you just put
your hair up, then?
Okay, all done!
Ah! You look just like
Azusa-chan!
Yeah, it looks terrible!
(gags)
You're the one who did it!
(choking) I-I I'm sorry...
(Azusa gasps)
What's going on?
Oh Ton-chan!
Did he get a sunburn?
(sighs)
No of course he didn't!
Ton-chan's molted.
Molted?
[Yuri] Malted?
I didn't know turtles did that.
Of course they do
they're reptiles.
The turtles that we have at
home have all molted, too.
(sigh of relief)
Thank goodness...
I was so worried that
Ton-chan might be getting sick.
I've got it! We should all
shed too, just like turtles do!
Ah?
You do know that humans can't
shed their skin, right?
Oh, but we can, Ritsu!
Yosakoi!
That's what you meant?
Ah... This is kinda comfy!
It might be easier
to play this way.
Not happening.
Why don't you put yours on,
too, Mio-chan?
No, no, no, no!
No one but you would ever
wear something like that to...
Mugi-chan!
Seriously?
Hm...
I wonder if it's cold
on top of the desks?
Are you doing what I think?
Here goes...
Oh wow, how does it feel?
Ah...
(disappointed)
It wasn't as cold as
I hoped it would be...
Mm-hm.
(groans)
It's not cold either...
For some reason,
today seems especially hot.
Still, with all this sweating
we're doing, we're sure to lose
some weight.
[Tsumugi] Sauna suit time!
[Mio] This will do the trick,
right?
No way.
Those again?
Mm.
(poorly played bass and
keyboards)
[Mio] I'm sweating, all right...
[Tsumugi] But I can't
play properly.
[Ritsu] Hey, let's play
a word association game!
Huh?
What says "summer in Japan"
more than anything else?
Watermelons!
Big wind chimes!
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Uh...
Ice cream!
I know, it's fireworks.
No, no, no, no!
Oh! Chilled Chinese noodles?
You're not even close.
Wow, it's all about food
with you, isn't it?
Huh?
What could it be, then?
The answer is... scary ghost
stories!
Ah!
Sorry.
This is a story that
is told in this school.
Apparently, a student came here
alone
one night to retrieve
something she had forgotten.
The school should have been
deserted, and yet the notes of
piano being played,
could be heard emanating
from the music room!
(piano music)
(screaming)
Mugi!
Heh.
[Ritsu] She thought this was
unusual,
so she peeked into the music
room, and what did she see?
Sawa-chan, tutoring a student
who was applying to a music
school!
(screaming)
(inflating noise)
Ah, isn't there anything else
we can do to cool off?
You know it's bad for your
health to get yourself so
agitated.
Man it seems like the
harder we fan ourselves...
(groans)
...the hotter it feels whenever
we stop.
Thinking about how hot it is
only makes you feel even hotter
than you really are.
Oh you mean mind over matter?
Okay, Ri-chan, let's think
about lots of cool things!
Things that are cool, huh?
So cold!
[Yui] It sure is nice and cool.
[Ritsu] It sure is, Yui.
[Yui] It's all about mind over
matter.
You know, you maybe right.
It's hot...
(gasps)
Don't give in, Yui!
Think about how cool it is!
(determined)
It's so cool! It's so cool!
It's so cool...
(sizzling)
Yui-senpai, are you feeling
okay?
This is so hard!
I can't tell my mind it's cool
when the matter is so hot!
Hey, back at the beginning of
the school year, when we were
all cleaning in here,
I could swear that I put
a fan in the storage room...
That's it!
Mio-chan, you're a genius!
Found it!
It's ancient...
(fan working hard)
Well, I guess I know
how she feels...
This way, the breeze should
hit everyone, okay?
Oh!
Here goes...
(happy)
(satisfied)
Hello? Excuse me?
I'm not getting any wind
at all back here!
You're way in back,
what did you expect?
(stunned)
(angry)
Hey! Ritsu!
Right, then! Ultra-maximum
power! We are go!
(fan on super high power)
(Ritsu's excitement
echoing through fan)
(fan overworking)
(girls screaming)
(fan imploding)
(groans)
I think it broke...
Nothing we can do...
[Tsumugi] Hey guys!
I brought ice with me today.
[Ritsu] Sweet!
[Yui] Yahoo!
(excited)
It's cold!
Let me see!
[Mio] Mugi, when did you
get these-
[Ritsu] Down the hatch.
Wah!
That's freezing!
What do you think you're doing?!
Now, now, how could I pass that
up?
Well, the truth is, I had
planned to use this to make us
some shaved ice.
Awesome!
But I forgot to bring
my shaved ice machine
from home...
(disappointed)
Ah... It's so nice 'n chilly!
Really?
Me, too! Me, too!
You weren't kidding!
That's freezing!
You know, it's kinda
lukewarm now.
Ice sure melts quickly
when it's hot.
Ri-chan, go buy us
some more ice.
Uh, why don't YOU go buy some.
Don't wanna, it's too hot.
It's hot for me too.
Just go get it, Ri-chan...
Oh no! My chronic back pain
has returned!
That's no fair! I was here with
my feet in the bucket first!
And MY feet were in the bucket
for a lot less time than yours
have been!
Ri-chan, you're the one who
should go!
No, YOU should go!
Ri-chan!
Yui!
(water spilling)
Would you two give it a rest?
For pete's sake...
Seems like a big waste
to throw away all this ice.
Oh? Why don't we gather it up
and put it in Ton-chan's tank,
then?
No you can't!
The tank has it's own
thermostat,
so he's fine just the way he is!
Oh Azu-nyan I was kidding.
Well you know, your jokes never
really sound much like jokes,
Yui-senpai.
It says here a turtle's growth
is based on the size of its
tank,
so if we want Ton-chan to get
bigger, we have to get him a
bigger tank!
So then, the reason Ton-chan was
shedding,
Is because he wants
to grow big and strong.
In that case, we have a larger
tank than this at our house that
isn't being used.
Wow, really? You do?
But how in the world would
we get it over here?
Didn't Miss Sawa-chan say to us
once that she had a car?
Hey, you're right she did!
Let's go and ask her if she'll
help us!
Sawa-chan hasn't come
to the club lately, has she?
Good thing. If she was here,
it would just make the room
hotter.
Oh wait I know, maybe she's
passed out from the heat around
here somewhere.
(giggling)
Like the two of you have
any right to laugh at that.
[Sawako] What's the matter,
girls? What brings you two here
to the staff room?
What? Where are you two taking
me?
It's so hot...
Miss Yamanaka, look at Ton-chan!
(groans)
What, isn't he in the water
where it's nice and comfy?
Oh, looks like he's molting.
That's why we want to switch him
into a larger tank that Mugi has
at her house.
Would you mind helping us out
and bringing it over here in
your car?
(moaning)
It's way too much work...
Look Sawa-chan, I have an
ice cream float for you!
I'll fetch my car at once!
[Ritsu] She's SO easy
to manipulate.
K-ON!
(car pulling up)
Thanks for waiting.
Bye! It's my job as club
president to go.
Wha? No fair! You can't
go by yourself!
I wanna go, too!
I wanna ride in Sawa-chan's car!
[Yui] Hey! No cutsies!
[Azusa] I can't go?
[Mio] They're going to Mugi's
house so Mugi has to go no
matter what.
You're lucky, Mugi-chan!
So Mugi-chan gets shotgun,
and me, Azu-nyan, Ri-chan,
and Mio-chan will all
ride in back seat.
How about that?
My car only seats four,
so that only leaves
two seats free.
In that case, do you wanna take
Sawa-chan's spot, Ri-chan?
Okay!
Well who's gonna drive the car?!
Hm. I hate to say it but, you
really should've bought a
bigger car, Sawa-chan.
I didn't buy the car for you,
so if you don't mind you can
spare me the commentary.
Um, you know the fish tank
is rather large and bulky,
so there's a really good chance
it could take up the entire
inside of the car.
[Mio] Well then, assuming the
tank will take up the rear of
the car,
Mugi's the only one who can go.
Say what?!
We'll be back soon, everyone!
[Yui] Have a safe trip!
It's hot...
(excited)
I'm riding in my teacher's car!
[Tsumugi] Oh, what's that
on your mirror?
It's a good-luck charm.
You can see everything
from the front seat!
Ah! The seat moves!
[Sawako] I knew that was coming.
[Tsumugi] We're back!
[Ritsu] Look at that!
It's huge!
That's amazing...
Incredible...
What do you mean incredible?
It was just incredible!
I'll be sure to make home visits
more often all right?
Thank you for looking out
for me.
[Ritsu] Thanks for doing
this for us.
[The girls] Thank you very much!
[Sawako] You're welcome, girls!
[Yui] Thanks for waiting,
Ton-chan!
Look, here's a big, new tank for
you!
Isn't that terrific, Ton-chan?
Oh! The sunlight's hitting
one corner of the tank!
Yeah, you're right, we'd better
cover it up with something.
[Ritsu] Don't we have some
packing tape?
[Yui] I think there was
some in the storeroom.
You think that'll work?
It should be just fine.
Okay then, I think it's time I
headed back to the staff room.
Wait don't go yet!
You need something else?
Oh please stay, you're the
only one that we can turn to!
Right. I'm going now.
Sawa-chan!
I said no!
Mugi!
Sawa-chan, would you like
a nice chocolate frappé?
Yes please!
[Sawako] An air conditioner,
huh?
[Yui] Can you do anything
for us?
I don't know.
Oh, really?
[Ritsu] Right!
In that case, we'll buy
the air conditioner ourselves!
Where are we supposed
to get that much money?
We'll get ourselves some jobs!
(cheering)
Don't you guys need to study for
your college entrance exams?
Oh, wait a minute.
Why don't you go and
ask the Student Council?
Good idea!
Do you really think
they would okay the request?
Air conditioners aren't cheap.
Yeah...Maybe this calls
for a little bribe.
You know, Nodoka-chan was saying
earlier that she wished she had
a computer!
Mugi, rustle up a computer right
away!
Right, you go it!
That would cost as much as
an air conditioner.
We've got an emergency,
Yui's passed out from the heat!
R-Ri-chan... Just once before I
died, I wanted to snap my
fingers and...
Yui... Yui!
Is your wish for an air
conditioner of gold,
or an air conditioner made of
silver?
Mighty God, my only wish is
but for an ordinary air
conditioner...
How honest this creature is!
So I shall grant thee
a brand new air conditioner!
Oh! Praise God!
What's with the all the cheap
theatrics?
Sorry for all the ruckus.
So, what is it you want?
[Yui] The thing is, we came here
to ask for a favor from the
student council.
Wait, Yui.
Feel the air... It's cool here.
(gasps)
[Ritsu] This room has
an air conditioner!
[Yui] It what?!
Abuse of authority!
Nodoka-chan, I believed in
you...
What are you talking about?
We talked about this at
the Club Presidents' Council.
The school had decided to okay
air conditioners in the club
rooms,
so I said that any clubs that
wanted one should put in a
request.
(whistling innocently)
President?
[Ritsu] I forgot to attend the--
Ow!
I'm so sorry...
Is it too late to apply?!
Uh, well um...
[Ritsu] We're back.
How did it go?
I'm going to put in a formal
proposal, at tomorrow's Club
Presidents' Council.
Council?
I've never heard of that.
What do you guys talk about
there?
Don't know, never been to one.
I wouldn't be boasting!
Well does the council ever vote
to turn down requests made by
the clubs?
I suppose so.
But I really wanted an air
conditioner!
We'll just have to plead
our case convincingly.
(thinking)
Well for now, why don't we
rehearse our petition to the
council?
What do you mean rehearse?
We'll think of reasons that
they might turn down our
request,
and then prepare
counter-arguments.
Oh, I follow you! Good idea!
Very well, those with business
before this council, raise your
hand.
Here! The Light Music Club
requests an air conditioner!
Heh.
Those in agreement with
Miss Tainaka's request say
agreed.
Agreed!
Uh...
If you all agree, it defeats the
purpose!
Right, those opposed to the
request?
(groans)
President!
We heard petitions for
air conditioner at a previous
council,
so I believe it is far too late
to request one now!
Uh... That was because--
Ma'am! The Light Music Club
doesn't seem to practice all
that often,
so do they really need an
air conditioner in their room?
(nervous)
I'm so sorry I wasted your time!
I withdraw my request!
Why the heck are you giving up?!
Because, this is hard...
[Tsumugi] You have to make
some kind of counter-argument.
It'll be okay, Ri-chan!
You can do it! I know it!
You're a club president! You're
a big sister! And you're a good
drummer!
Hey, you're right, Yui...
Bring it on, Azusa!
One more time, then...
I don't believe that the Light
Music Club needs an air
conditioner
because they never practice!
We DO to practice! All the time,
but it's a secret practice.
Why do you have to say
that our practices are secret?
Ma'am! I believe that there is
more to being a club than
practice!
Wow, Yui said something
that made sense for once!
We deepen our bonds of
friendship!
And we interact with students
of other class years!
That's right, that's right!
We also eat cake, drink tea,
and go to the beach!
See?! The Light Music Club has
no need for an air conditioner
in their room!
If we had an air conditioner,
we would practice!
Would you really?
We sweat like crazy when
we play our instruments all-out!
Drums are physically demanding,
which makes them very dangerous
to play in the summer heat!
Uh, nevertheless-
Plus, if we had an air
conditioner,
our performances would be a lot
cooler!
Yeah they would!
You've made your case.
Oh yeah! Now I'm ready for the
real thing!
[Yui] Go get 'em, Ri-chan!
[Ritsu] Watch what a club
president can do when she sets
her mind to it!
(laughing)
So is there any other
business today?
Ma'am!
Miss Tainaka.
The Light Music Club
requests an air conditioner!
Are there any objections
to the proposal?
Huh? Wait, so you're okaying it?
But madam president,
the Student Council's budget
for the year is already
fully allocated.
Well we could hold off on
replacing the copier at least
until next year, right?
Yes we could. That would do it.
That's it?
Seriously?
(happy sighs)
We're in heaven!
It's so cool!
Now we can finally practice
without sweating like mad.
I say we all just call it
a day and relax.
Hey!
I'm just kidding!
(giggling)
Oh good grief...
Here we go! One! Two!
Three! Four?
What's the matter, Yui?
I-uh, forgot that air
conditioning makes me queasy...
What are we supposed
to do, then?
[Yui] I feel terrible...
(groans)
[Ritsu] We can't win.
(closing song, "Listen!!")
Another training camp!
[Azusa] Um, are you sure a
training camp is a good idea?
We're not going to get eaten
alive up there, are we?
[Mio] I really don't know what
you're thinking, but whatever it
is, it's wrong.
I want to die...
Oh wow! Two days
surrounded by music!
[Yui] I hope that I can just
keep on playing in a band
with you guys forever!