[Yui] Um... Not quite...
Ui!
Just what are you doing, Sis?
Ui...
What am I gonna do?
(opening song,
"Utauyo!! MIRACLE")
[Azusa] Good morning, Ui.
[Ui] Oh hey, Azusa-chan,
good morn-
What happened to your hair?
Is this a new look?
I've been so out of it,
I must have forgot to put it up.
Why are you so out of it today?
Is everything all right?
Yeah, yeah, it's all right,
I'm fine...
Azusa-chan! Your shoes!
Thank you.
You're not acting like
yourself today.
It's just, with the
school festival over,
I'm totally drained.
[Ui] It still might be nice
to change your hair, though.
What do you say I try
something new?
Sounds fun. So what are you
thinking?
Ta-dah!
Azu-nyan!
Why would you want to change
yours to match Yui-senpai's?
I've wanted to give you a big
hug like this for a long time.
[Jun] What are you two doing?
We're just talking about
hairstyles.
Whoa, you and your sister could
be twins!
Wow thank you!
That's not a compliment.
[Azusa] Wait, that's
Yui-senpai's...
I've worn them all morning.
You're just now noticing?
I'm really out of it.
So why do you have the hair
pins?
[Ui] Oh, I put them on
earlier this morning.
Yeah, but why?
Because me and my sister
were playing around with,
a bunch of different kinds hair
styles.
She couldn't decide which
hairstyle looked best on her,
so I decided to put her hair
pins in my hair so she could see
what it looked like.
She says the senior pictures
are coming up soon.
For the graduation album.
Got a headache?
No it's something else,
see I'm not my usual self today.
Well you look exactly
the same to me.
Nodoka-chan, you've known me
for so long.
Right here.
Hair pins. So did you forget
'em? Or just lose 'em?
Ui still has them.
I tried some new styles in
the mirror, but just wasn't
feeling it.
So I experimented on Ui
to get a better look at them.
So that's why you came
to school like this.
Yeah, and it feels real weird
not to have my hair pinned
down here like it should be.
Nodoka-chan, do you have
something I could use to pin it
with?
Let me see...
Sorry but this is all I have.
A binder clip, huh?
Well I suppose that it could
work.
[Tsumugi] You're welcome to use
this.
Shall I tie it back?
Would you please? Thanks so
much!
[Tsumugi] Your hair's not quite
long enough for a traditional
pony tail. So...
[Mio] Yui? What's going on?
It's Mugi-chan! Look what she
did to me!
Cause of your forehead?
What's that?!
Show it loud and proud!
You have a rather impressive
forehead, too, don't you?
No, please! Any hairstyle but
this!
Okay.
[Ritsu] Aw that's cute!
[Yui] Really?
[Nodoka] Really. I've seen
puppies who look just like that.
[Yui] That means I look like a
dog!
[Nodoka] Yes, but in a cute way.
Hey there Sis!
[Yui] Now I'm really
embarrassed!
Oh, Ui-chan. What brings you
here?
Sorry to bother you.
But could you give this to Yui?
[Mio] Yui.
Thank you, Ui!
[Azusa] The track seems kind of
deserted.
[Ui] It's probably because the
seniors in the athletic clubs
have stepped down.
[Jun] Same with our club.
Hey, wait...
Seniors step down from
their clubs after the school
festival!
And they're about to take
their senior pictures!
Have they already-
Azusa, why are you out of
breath?
Are you okay?
You guys are still here.
You ran here because you
couldn't wait to eat Mugi's
yummy snacks, right?
Say "ah"!
I'd appreciate it if you didn't
drag me down to your level.
Let me guess, you were scared
that we'd stepped down,
and would stop coming to the
club so you freaked out?
NOW she's observant?
Aw, Azusa didn't want to be
alone.
That is so cute!
Stop the violence! Stop the
violence!
She's scary!
Ease up on the drama!
[Azusa] What are you all doing
in the club room anyway?
What do you mean? It's comfy
here.
It's got air conditioning!
And there's always snacks!
There's really no reason NOT to
come!
[Both] Right?
You're here, too?
Actually, all joking aside,
we thought this was a good place
for us to study for our entrance
exams.
Wait, you're okay with that
aren't you?
Yeah, of course, if that's why
you're here, I have no problem
at all.
Plus, it's nice to have company.
[Ritsu] That's the spirit,
Azusa!
This way, you won't be left
alone!
But the real question is, can
you guys actually study here
without goofing off?
[Ritsu] 'course we can!
[Yui] She has no manners!
[Sawako] By the way,
Ri-chan and Yui-chan...
I know this strawberry
shortcake's amazing, right?
Actually what I wanted to
discuss was your career goals.
[Sawako] Have either of you
written up your plan yet?
Well, we both went to summer
school! Doesn't that count for
something?
We thought we'd go to college.
Okay then. Which college? And
what majors?
Well, I...
I wanna do what you do
Sawa-chan!
That's so sweet, thank you,
that's very flattering.
Yeah, I wanna eat snacks, drink
tea, and just hang out and
chit chat every day, like you
do!
[Sawako] I do have a job, thank
you!
Oh Mio-chan, you should
submit your application soon.
Okay.
[Yui] What application?
To take the admissions test.
[Yui] Wow, really?
[Sawako] With your grades,
Mio-chan,
you wont have a problem passing
the entrance exams national
universities.
[Azusa] Wow, that's fantastic!
[Mio] Uh, I guess.
[Azusa] You're applying to a
private all girl's college,
right, Mugi-senpai?
[Ritsu] Well, maybe I'll go
to the same school as Mugi.
Then I'll go there, too!
[Sawako] Put a little more
thought into the decision, all
right?
And keep your academic
abilities in mind as well.
[Yui and Ritsu] Yes, Ma'am.
[Sawako] And, Mio-chan. Make
sure you get that application to
me by tomorrow.
[Mio] Uh okay.
Now that our career goals
are taken care of.
[Azusa] You haven't taken
care of anything.
On to this!
[Azusa] Why the sudden interest
in hair?
I'm trying to pick a new hair
style for my graduation picture!
It'll be with me the rest of my
life! Do I want to make sure
it's perfect!
Shouldn't you guys be trying to
study?
Entrance exams aren't until next
year,
but our senior pictures are day
after tomorrow, Azu-nyan!
Um "Next year"?
Even I have to question that
logic.
Listen to me. If you fail to
study for that test, you'll
flunk it.
"Flunk" and "fail" are two words
that no test-taker ever wants to
hear.
[Ritsu] Same goes with
"split up" or "break up"...
That applies weddings!
Ha! We just created a three-man
skit!
Woo-hoo!
Oh, Mio-chan, did you find
a style you like?
Are you gonna get your hair done
like that for the senior
picture?
Of course not.
I'd prefer something like...
this.
Okay, that was a joke.
[Yui] I was thinking of going
with something like this.
You want to make that drastic a
change?
What's wrong with
the hairstyle you've got?
I actually think
it's pretty cute as it is.
[Yui] You think so?
Hey, I'll bring a camera with me
tomorrow, and we can take some
test pictures.
K-ON!
[Yui] I was grinning in
this grade school picture,
but then I got nervous for
this junior high photo.
I should've tilted my chin
down more in this one.
Here, too much tilt.
And this one, my bangs are
too short. And here,
they're a bit long.
You think so?
That's why...this year
is going to be perfect!
[Ritsu] Hey, looks like you'll
be first, Ritsu-senpai.
Your hair is so silky!
It's really beautiful.
Hey, that's enough of that talk.
I just want to keep touching it
forever!
Stop it!
Here we go...
[Tsumugi] A little higher,
maybe?
Too high?
It goes here.
Okay. You ready?
Sure.
Alright, one more.
[Yui] It's perfect!
Ritsu never worries about
having her picture taken,
and they always come out
perfect. There's proof.
Okay. You're up next,
Mio-senpai.
[Yui] Looks like she wants to
run away.
Yup. There's that look again.
She has that freaked out
expression in every school
picture she's ever taken.
Just try to relax a bit more
for tomorrow's photo.
It's your turn now, Mugi-senpai.
Ready!
[Ritsu] Why?
Well you see, I always seem
ditzy in my pictures,
so I thought I'd try
looking serious this time.
Yeah, but I think that ditzy
thing looks really good on you.
You think so?
You just have be your self.
Okay, the ditzy look it is.
Yeah!
Alright Yui-senpai, you're the
last one.
'kay!
Aw come on, Azu-nyan!
I'm sorry!
[Azusa] Hey, that looks pretty
good.
You look so prim and proper.
Oh, you almost look like
a serious student.
Whoa. I can't believe no one
had a comeback for that.
Do you think my bangs look long?
Not at all. They look good to
me.
Mm-mm. They're just a bit long.
Really?
Scissors!
[Tsumugi] Yui-chan!
[Azusa] Don't do anything rash!
If you want them cut,
you should go to a salon!
It doesn't cost much to get a
simple trim.
Yeah, but when I go to a salon,
they always cut them too short!
In a week they end up being the
perfect length, but I don't have
that long.
I need perfect bangs by
tomorrow.
Then at least let Mugi cut them!
What?! That might be too
important of a task for me to
do!
Don't worry. I trim up my
own hair all the time.
I can't bear to watch!
What do you think?
They look great!
Stop while you're ahead.
Maybe they're still a wee bit
too long...
[Both] No don't!
I may have cut it too much...
How does it look?
I-It looks wonderful!
It's weapons-grade cute!
Yeah! It makes you look a lot
younger!
Y-You don't mean like baby
younger do you?
But it looks intentional like
you meant to cut off that much.
Honest? Do you really mean that?
Its my senior picture...
It'll be with me the rest of my
life...
Hide it! No one will ever know!
Thanks, but doing the forehead
thing is really not my style.
Well, excuse me...
You know, I think it might look
better,
if you tried to brushed it to
the side.
You see? Like that.
Look.
[Yui] Better?
Yep, super cute!
Yeah, it looks great!
Agreed!
You mean it?
Yeah, you look very refined now!
You think so?
Anyway, who's up for tea?
[Mio] I am.
[Tsumugi] I brought Mont Blancs
today!
Mont Blancs?!
Yum!
Here you go.
Really?
Wow, you guys really
do enable her, don't you?
Thank you... Everyone!
[Yui] See you tomorrow!
Yep, good night.
See you soon!
[Ritsu] Later!
[Mio] See ya!
Hey, by the way Mio, weren't you
supposed to hand in that
application thing today?
Yeah.
So then, what? Did you forgot
it?
Don't you have your own things
to turn in? Like a career plan,
maybe?
Well yeah, but you-
[Mio] I'll hand it in tomorrow.
Good morning, Azusa-chan!
Morning.
[Yui] Good morning everyone...
Senpai? Are you still
bothered by your hair?
I wish I could turn back the
clock...
Just deal with it.
You're acting like a baby.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be better eventually.
Yui-chan, if you keep up this
behavior,
there will be no snacks
for you today, young lady!
[Ritsu] What are you, ten?
It's almost your turn.
Okay, you look good.
[Sawako] Miss Akiyama!
Here!
There's nothing to be afraid of!
Right! Give 'em hell!
See you in a jiffy!
[Yui] Mio-chan!
[Tsumugi] You can do it!
Relax, relax!
[Yui] Fight on! Fight on!
Now I'm even more embarrassed...
Just remember to breath, okay?
I guess I'm up next!
Be right back!
[Sawako] Miss Hirasawa!
Sorry.
[Yui] All done!
[Tsumugi] Welcome back!
[Sawako] Oh. Miss Akiyama,
please stop by the staff room
after we're finished.
Yes, ma'am.
[Mio] Sorry to interrupt.
Why did she call you to
the staff room, Mio-chan?
You decided not to take
that admissions test, didn't
you?
How'd you know that?
[Ritsu] I figured as much.
It's not your style to forget
to hand in paperwork,
when a teacher asks you for it.
Why would you turn it down,
though? That's a really big
deal!
Uh...well I...
Because to be honest,
I'd rather study with you guys.
And if...if it's at all
possible...
I'd really like to go to
the same college that you all
do.
We all go...
To the same college?
[Ritsu] Mm I'm starving!
[Yui] Me too!
[Mio] You had a tart earlier.
[Yui] Oops, I forgot!
[Ritsu] Later!
[Yui] Yeah, see ya!
[Tsumugi] Bye-bye!
[Azusa] Good night.
[Mio] Ma'am.
What brings the three
of you here all at once?
We've come to hand in
our career plans to you!
All right. Forms accepted.
Yahoo!
[Sawako] Work hard, girls.
I hope everyone of you gets
into that all girls school.
[All three] Thanks!
[Ritsu] Ooh, she finally
accepted them!
[Yui] Did you hear the
good news already?
Let's work hard, okay?
[Ritsu] Of course!
[Yui] But first, let's have some
tea!
[Ritsu] Yeah! Good call!
[Mio] Hey!
[Ritsu] Tea! Tea! Tea!
(closing song, "NO, Thank You!")
[Yui] "Who"? Like owls?
[Ritsu] Based on my careful
testing of pencils of all types,
Hexy #7 is clearly the top
choice, with its astonishing
60% accuracy rate!
[Mio] Just one problem.
This test actually has
9 multiple choices answers
for each question.
[Tsumugi] How about we take
a quick break?
I'll go put on some tea.
[Azusa] What have you been
wishing for?
[Ui] I've been wishing that my
sister and the others all get
into the same college,
and that they all graduate
together without any problems.