Oof...
Here we go...
Hey, this is...
[Nodoka] Dear Sokabe-senpai.
The weather has finally turned
warm. How have you been?
I'm writing to you today because
there is something that I wish
to tell you about.
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
Oh, Mio-chan? What's wrong?
You seem real fidgety.
Well, I've had this weird
feeling all morning long that
I'm being watched.
It's because you're really
popular.
No, not that, Mugi. It's almost
like somebody is staring at me.
Staaaaare...
[Mio] Don't do that!
Sure you're not just being
self-conscious?
Ritsu, I'm serious!
I can feel someone's eyes
on my back at this very second!
[Sawako] Guess who!
Heh.
[Girls] Sawa-chan...
Huh?
[Sawako] So you feel like
someone's watching you, huh?
Personally, everyone's eyes
are always on me!
Because your book has
a really nice COVER, anyway.
Hey! What do you mean, "cover"?!
Maybe you're the culprit
who's been tailing,
Mio around and creeping her out.
As if! If it were me, I wouldn't
stop at just watching her!
Oh yeah, good point!
(laughing)
I've got it! The culprit
is really Ton-chan!
Huh?
See? It's all because
you're scared of Ton-chan,
and you always try
to avoid looking at him.
So Ton-chan glomped onto your
back!
[Mio] Get it off! Get it off!
[Mio] It's no use... These
people aren't going to help me.
Come on guys, I think you should
show a little more concern here!
She might be the target
of some creepy stalker!
Azusa!
Now I see. I think I solved the
mystery.
The culprit...
Is you!
(confused)
[Tsumugi] I'm sorry guys,
I always wanted to do that!
But the part about solving
the mystery was true.
Mio-chan, you had a yakisoba bun
for breakfast this morning,
right?
Y-You're right, I did!
I overslept and didn't have time
to sit down and eat breakfast
like I usually do.
And that yakisoba bun
was 20% off, wasn't it?!
H-How in the world did you know
that?!
(giggling)
From this. You see?
Hm?
Uh!
Oh, I get it! You've been
walking around all day with that
stuck to your hair!
That's why everyone was staring
at me?!
[Nodoka] What are you two doing
out here?
[Mio] Nodoka, who are these two?
[Nodoka] I'm not-
[Fan A] Hey we're not
criminals or anything!
Yeah! We're just members
of the Mio-senpai Fan Club!
The fan club?
Ugh, I came THIS close to
forgetting about that picture...
Wait, you didn't come here to
see the sticker in Mio-chan's
hair, did you?
Yeah! We heard about it from
the other members!
If you're her fans, why didn't
you say something to her about
it?
Well, I did say to everyone
that we really ought to tell
her...
But having something stuck in
her hair like that is just so
Mio-y and wonderful!
[Ritsu] Wonderful?
I was actually wondering if you
had stuck that thing there on
purpose!
You mean you knew about it!?!
[Nodoka] I'm sorry.
It's because I've been so
undependable that those two fan
club girls-
What are YOU apologizing for?
Wow, I didn't know
your fan club was still around!
[Tsumugi] Yeah! I thought it had
disbanded after Sokabe-senpai
graduated.
Wait, Sokabe-senpai? Who's that?
Oh yeah, that's right, you never
met her.
She used to be the president of
the offical Mio-chan Fan Club
here at school.
That's right... Oh has it been
so long since those events
transpired?
What events?
[Ritsu] Well, it was March,
just before graduation.
Mio was scared, thinking that
she was being constantly watched
by someone.
I couldn't bear seeing her like
that,
so I advised her to go talk
to the Student Council about it.
Really the Student Council?
Dial down your imagination,
okay?
Nobody took me seriously,
so I decided on my own to go
talk to the Student Council
about what was happening.
So you feel like there's someone
always watching you?
I wonder if it's a stalker?
It's hard to believe there could
be a intruder on campus, but-
Mio, why are you crying?
I'm so happy that someone
is finally reacting normally!
How are they treating her
in the Light Music Club?
[Megumi] Miss Manabe, are you
there?
Oh Senpai?
Oh, we have a visitor?
[Nodoka] Is there a problem?
[Megumi] Not at all, I brought
the handover paperwork.
Nodoka, who is this?
[Nodoka] Megumi Sokabe,
the Student Council President.
Well, former president.
A pleasure, Miss Akiyama.
Uh, same here.
I suppose that a member of the
Light Music Club might not have
heard of me.
I-I'm really sorry!
[Ritsu] That was the moment
of their first encounter!
However, poor unsuspecting Mio
had absolutely no idea what
fate held in store for them!
Lay off the creepy narration,
will ya?
So what kind of fate
are you talking about?
That's where it gets weird...
[Megumi] Here. I'm afraid it's
not as fancy as the Light Music
Club's tea.
Not at all, this is fine.
Wow, a stalker...
This is a rather serious matter.
Miss Manabe, will you please
inform the Disciplinary
Committee of this?
Yes of course.
Y-You don't need to go
through all that trouble!
It's no trouble at all. If a
student at our school has a
problem,
we want to do everything
we can to help them out.
I wish my club president
could hear you say that...
Still, I wonder what sort of
person would follow Mio around?
A member of her fan club,
perhaps?
You know about that?
Oh. What's wrong?
Uh nothing, it's just that you
know an awful lot about the
Light Music Club.
You even knew my name.
[Nodoka] Come to think of it,
you also knew that their club
has tea parties.
Um... You must have mentioned
it to me, Miss Manabe!
I don't think I did.
Really, you didn't?
Well, the Light Music Club is
rather famous around school.
Well, I should be going now,
goodbye.
Senpai. Wait you dropped
something.
"Mio Akiyama Fan Club Membership
Card"...
[Megumi] I found this in the
hall earlier!
But Miss Sokabe, your name
was written on the front of it.
Oh no, I have to say something
to break the tension!
Gosh, is it possible
that you're the culprit?
Oh right, as if!
(laughter)
Miss Sokabe, you couldn't be
the stalker yourself, could you,
huh?
I didn't mean to frighten you!
Uh?!
[Megumi] I'm graduating soon,
you know?
The thought of never seeing you
again was almost unbearable...
I just couldn't help myself...
[Mio] It's okay.
I have to admit that I'm
flattered to hear you say that.
And embarrassed, too...
Miss Akiyama...
[Nodoka] Member #1?
Yeah that's right, I'm also
the president of the fan club.
(shocked)
So you mean the Student Council
President was actually the
culprit?
She couldn't be open about it
because of her position.
I suppose.
It was tough for her. That's why
we all wanted to come up,
with a special something to do
for her, for her graduation.
Yeah. So we...
[Nodoka] The Light Music Club
asked us to come to the
auditorium... I wonder why?
[Megumi] To get even with me?
[Nodoka] Oh, I doubt it.
Sokabe-senpai,
congratulations...
[The whole band] ...on
graduating!
I uh...
Sakura High's Light Music Club,
would like to play for you
to celebrate your graduation!
We hope you enjoy it!
[Band] It's Fuwa Fuwa Time!
[Ritsu] One! Two! One, two,
three, four!
("Fuwa Fuwa Time" instrumental)
(music ending)
[Nodoka] Senpai? Senpai?
Senpai! They finished playing
the song!
What's the meaning of this,
using the auditorium without
permission?!
Is what I'm suppose to say.
Thank you all so much.
It's the best gift I've ever
gotten.
(happy)
She liked it!
[Megumi] To mark the occasion...
Please autograph this!
(Mio cries out)
Please sign it "From Mio-tan"!
My image of her as
a wise elder, is shattered...
So did you sign it from
"Mio-tan"?
[Mio] I did...
Sokabe-senpai was
totally ecstatic.
Membership card number 0001?
It's in your name, Nodoka?!
[Nodoka] You see,
after you played...
[Megumi] I've decided, that you
should also take over as
the fan club president.
Thank you but absolutely not!
[Nodoka] I couldn't turn down
this membership card,
so I gave in and accepted the
position
but I never had time for it, and
never carried out any of my
duties as president.
Nodoka-chan...
[Nodoka] That's why I came
today to ask a favor of you.
To ask if you would mind holding
a tea party for the members of
the fan club.
[Tsumugi] A tea party?
[Nodoka] Right. I could
never look her in the eye,
if I don't do at least try.
[Yui] You bet! We'll be honored
to help you, Nodoka-chan!
Uh?
Yeah! You're always helping us
out, so we owe you!
Uh...
What sort of tea party do
you think we should have?
Et tu, Mugi?!
Hey come on, let's not rush
into this, okay?
[Yui] Oh and there has to be
a cake-cutting ceremony!
[Ritsu] And a bouquet
presentation and a memorial
album!
What is this?
[Azusa] Why don't we do
a Q&A period, then?
[Ritsu] Great idea!
They're not listening...
So is it all right to take you
up on your offer
and leave all the planning
of the event to you, then?
I'll go and secure a venue for
us and make the notifications.
I volunteer to make all the
posters!
And I'll bring an extra large
cake!
[Mio] You're way too into this!
[Ritsu] Let's go all out!
It's a special occasion!
[Nodoka] With everyone's help,
this is going to be an amazing
tea party, Sokabe-senpai.
[Mio] K-ON!
[Nodoka] Things certainly seem
to be coming together nicely.
[Yui] We're pulling out all the
stops for Mio-chan's fans!
Mio-chan pencils! Mio-chan
erasers! Mio-chan tissues!
Mio-chan chocolates! Mio-chan
bottle openers! Mio-chan
chopsticks!
And the Mio-chan back scratcher!
Don't make weird stuff like
that!
I just put a Mio-chan sticker on
it!
It's simple, but don't
you think it's cute?
[Mio] Why would anyone even WANT
one?
Ui even made these cookies for
the party.
Yeah and they're Mio-chan
cookies!
(Mio sighs)
Ritsu-senpai, don't even think
about charging admission,
I know that look.
Hey, don't make me sound
like I'm some kind of miser!
(knock on the door)
Hm?
Yes!
Excuse us! We have
a special delivery for you!
You do really?!
Please all of you help
yourselves.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Wow look, it's yakisoba buns!
And tea, too!
[Yui] Mind if I eat now?
[Tsumugi] That was fast!
Thank you.
We're looking forward to the tea
party!
Sorry we bothered you!
Thanks again guys!
So cute!
I'm glad that everybody seems
to be looking forward to it.
Nodoka, is Sokabe-senpai
coming to the party?
About that...
[Azusa] She can't come?
I wrote her a letter inviting
her,
but she says that her college
club has a big trip that day.
So there's not much point, is
there?
Can we change the date?
She insisted that since
we've already announced it to
everyone,
we shouldn't reschedule the
party.
No way...
[Nodoka] She said that her dream
is
to keep the fan club going
strong and to get everyone
excited about it,
so if the current fan club
members had fun at the party,
she said that, that's enough for
her and that she's happy.
What a mature thing to say...
Well she is in college.
So when she graduated, she also
moved on from being a Mio fan,
huh?
That can't be true!
I bet she just had conflicting
plans and couldn't make it
that's all!
[Nodoka] Yes, and maybe she
just didn't want us
to go to any special
trouble on her account.
[Mio] When I... When I graduate
from here, will I become as
mature as her?
[Ritsu] Just then, touching
images of the happy days
Mio spent with her friends
flashed before her eyes...
[Mio] I said to cut out
the stupid narration!
(Ritsu laughing)
In that case, and in keeping
with Sokabe-senpai's wishes,
let's go ahead with the date as
scheduled.
[Tsumugi] Here, this is the
day's program.
Ri-chan, you and Yui-chan
will act as hosts.
[Ritsu and Yui] Aye, aye!
[Nodoka] As far as
the venue is concerned...
[Mio] It's not in the program
or anything,
but maybe I should do
something special for them,
too.
[Nodoka] But don't go overboard.
[Nodoka] Let's just keep it
simple and informal.
Okay, let's all run through
the program together.
[Ritsu] Welcome everyone! The
Light Music Club thanks you for
coming here today,
for the inaugural Mio Akiyama
Fan Club Tea Party!
We will be acting as your
masters of ceremonies today!
My name is Ritsu Tainaka!
And I'm Yui Hirasawa!
Have a great time, everybody!
(clapping and cheering)
[Azusa] Wow this is a great
turnout!
[Nodoka] I think I see some
familiar faces out there, too.
[Nodoka] Miss Sasaki is a
member?
[Ritsu] Anyway, as we all know
life is an exciting journey,
that is full of ups and downs-
[Yui] Ri-chan, that's
a wedding toast, too!
So, let's leave our skit at that
and get the Mio Akiyama Fan Club
tea party started!
Here comes our guest of honor!
[Yui] Mio Akiyama!
(cheering and applause)
Mio-chan looks so cool!
But her uniform's so boring!
Don't worry!
We've planned costume changes!
No, we haven't!
(disappointed)
Thank you for taking time out
of your busy schedules to-
[Fan 1] Mio-chan bit her tongue!
[Fan 2] But that's cute, too!
They're eating it up...
...to join us here today!
To join us... for a bite.
(laughter)
Wow, Ri-chan, she's a bigger
hit than our skit was.
Seriously?
[Yui] And on that note,
let's cut the speeches short,
and get right to the cake
cutting!
[Yui] Go on, Mio-chan! This is
your very, very, first act as a
couple!
Act with who?!
Azu-nyan will be helping you!
(shocked)
[Yui] And now, the cake
and tea service will begin!
And all your table candles will
be personally lit by Mio Akiyama
herself!
Senpai, we're ready for you over
here!
Here, too!
[Ritsu] And now, we'd like to
move on to our special event!
We call it 100 Questions With
Mio Akiyama!
(horn honking)
[Ritsu] Oh one more thing,
each time a question is
answered,
please extinguish one candle
on your table, alright?
Okay, time for the first
question!
What is the scariest story
you've heard in your life?!
What kind of question is that?!
Next question! What's
the second scariest story?!
Third question! What's the
third scariest story you've
heard?!
The next, next, next, next
question! What's the fourth
scariest story?!
They're playing Tales of Terror?
(Mio screaming)
Mio, hang in there!
You can do it, Mio!
Mio-san!
Let's open the floor to you!
Who has a question to ask?!
(clammering fans)
[Fan 4] When you take a bath,
what do you wash first?
I-I wash the shower head...
She washes the bath?!
[Fan 5] When you have grilled
octopus, do you start with the
head?
The cucumber...
Where's that?!
[Ritsu] And now, let's move on
to the next portion of our
program!
[Yui] Let's have an intimate
look back at the first half of
Mio's life,
with the following slideshow put
together especialy for this
party!
My life is half over at 17?
Heh.
(slideshow music)
Oh wow, she was so cute!
Look at how much she's grown up!
[Fan 7] She's so cute I'm gonna
burst!
Hey is it just me, or are these
slides more about you than
Mio-senpai?
Duh! That's because I got them
from my own photo album!
[Ritsu] Sadly, the end of this
inagural tea party is now upon
us.
As the grand finale, we of
After-school Tea Time would like
to play you a-
[Mio] Wait!
Um, there's something that
I'd like you all of you to hear.
[Mio] I knew I wouldn't be able
to express my feelings clearly,
so I put them into lyrics
instead.
(cheers, excitement)
Big surprise!
Heart-throbbing Sugar...
I make a caramel sauce
for you, my beloved.
Granulated and brown sugar.
Maple, honey, and
wasanbon sugar.
A caramel sauce for you,
my beloved.
My heart is also caramel sauce.
Even if it gets a little burnt,
your tender heat will
make it taste delicious!
Oh! (nervous)
Figures, not even Mio's fans
can make heads or tails
out of her lyrics.
And now, it's time for
our performance!
[Ritsu] A new song
by After-school Tea Time!
[Yui] It's called
Pure Pure Heart!
[Tsumugi] Shoo, shoo!
(band playing and singing)
(fans clapping)
[Yui] Everybody say cheese!
[Ritsu] Alright, look over
here next, please!
[Tsumugi] And now over here,
please!
[Ritsu] You're all crowded in
too close to Mio!
I wish that Sokabe-senpai could
see how excited everyone here
is.
Oh, hey!
Hey what are you going to do
with that?
I thought I'd take a picture
of this and send it to her!
Uh? But I don't know her cell
number.
Just look it up at the
Student Council office!
[Girl] I'm gonna go buy
something to drink, okay?
Okay.
(Megumi's phone rings)
They all just gave me
another wonderful gift.
[Nodoka] Dear Sokabe-senpai.
Please be sure to come to
the next tea party we have.
I'm sure that it will be
another terrific one.
(closing song, "Listen!!")
[Sawako] This is your future so
give it a lot of thought, okay?
[Yui] It seems like it's still
so far away and it's real hard
for me to picture it.
[Mio] Yui! You haven't decided
on your life plans yet?
[Mio and Tsumugi]
I know what you mean!
[Azusa] Really? 'cause
I'm completely lost.
[Nodoka] For now,
just writing down
whatever it is that comes
to mind, should be fine.
[Yui] Whatever comes to my mind?
Got it!