[Yui] Look! Look!
Aren't they cute?
Aw...
[Ritsu] Go ahead,
have another one, Azu-nyan.
[Azusa] No thank you, that's all
right.
Sawa-chan said that she would be
in late today, so she didn't
need it.
Yeah, it would just go
to waste if no one ate it.
Ah, come one, Azu-nyan! Your
face has "Gimme!" written all
over it.
Are you really sure?
You have something in your hair.
[Azusa] What is that, a sticker?
[Yui] I've been totally into
them lately-
Azusa, you forgot this back
in...
[Jun] Were you guys taking a
break?
[Azusa] No! We were just... I
mean...
(opening song,
"Utauyo!! MIRACLE")
Okay, I want you to write down
what the Light Music Club does
on a typical day.
All right.
[Jun] That's a lot of meetings.
So, what is it that you guys
talk about in all these
meetings?
Hm? Well I don't, um...
I can't tell her.
You guys talk about
music-related stuff, right?
Um, sure.
We talk about what
we're gonna call our next live
show,
and about the set list, and
funny stuff to say during our
audience banter.
You've changed, Azusa.
You know, the Jazz Club
has already started practicing
for the big school festival.
[Jun] Azusa? Hello?
[Azusa] This is bad! Really
bad! Really, really bad!
When did I get infected with
their slacker attitude?!
All right! Beginning today,
I'm making my comeback!
That was a very Yui-senpai thing
to do...
[Azusa] Okay, let's do this!
That was a Ritsu-senpai thing to
say.
All right, let's get to work.
Hm, that was Mio-senpai.
Shall we begin, then?
No, that was Mugi-senpai...
Everyday, I'm forgetting
who I am more and more.
No, if I give up now, I've lost!
Alright!
No body's here yet?
[Azusa] Something's there...
Mugi-senpai? W-What happened to
you?
Oh, dear. I guess I must
have nodded off for awhile.
Azusa-chan, good afternoon...
Oh my goodness,
you scared me half to death!
The sun is pouring in through
the windows, so this spot is
really cozy and warm.
Would you care to join me?
Thank you, but I'll pass.
[Tsumugi] Oh, really?
What in the world were
you doing down there, anyway?
Oh! Well, I thought I would
scare the next person to come
in, so I was hiding.
Jump out and go, "Boo!"
[Azusa] She sure comes up
with cute plans...
I hope someone comes in soon!
Oh!
Boo! Boo!
Mugi-senpai, you can't
really surprise someone,
after you've told them
what you're about to do.
Yikes! You scared me
half to death, darn it!
Boo!
[Azusa] Mugi-senpai.
Do you know when Yui-senpai
and the others will be here?
No, they're all on cleaning
duty, so they said they would be
here late.
Oh, they will, huh?
[Tsumugi] Boo!
[Azusa] Hey wait, it just
occurred to me,
that I'm hardly ever alone in
the music room with
Mugi-senpai.
[Tsumugi] I wonder if I can do
this as well as Ri-chan did that
one time.
Maybe I'll practice my guitar
while I'm waiting for them!
In that case, I'll go and get
some tea ready, okay?
I get really nervous when
I think about being alone with
her.
I mean, she has those amazing,
huge eyes, beautiful hair, fair
skin.
And she's next to me!
Oh did I do something odd?
N-No, it's all right.
Really? I'm relieved.
Hey Azusa-chan,
is the guitar a hard instrument?
Huh? I guess it can be...
Would you like to try?
May I? Thank you!
Um, it's all right to hold it
normally. You know?
Sorry, but could you move
your hair for a sec?
The strap goes right over
your shoulder like this.
Thank you very much.
I remember when Ri-chan tried
her hand at it last semester.
Well? So how does it look?
It looks just as good on
you as it did on her!
Huh? There are stickers here,
too?
It must've been Yui-senpai.
[Tsumugi] Azusa-chan, here.
Thank you for letting me hold
it.
You're not going to play it?
[Azusa] All right now,
this next one is petty tough.
Everyone has trouble holding an
F chord when they first try to
do it.
Are my fingers in the right
position?
Yes, that looks pretty close to
me. Go ahead and give it a
strum.
Here goes!
There's something cute about
that.
[Tsumugi] Drink up.
Thank you, Mugi-senpai.
The guitar is a difficult
instrument, all right.
It does take a lot of patience.
I see. I've studying the piano
ever since I was a very little
girl,
but
I've made sure to practice every
day.
I was told if I didn't, my
fingers would lose flexibility.
Then I guess it's the same with
guitar as it is with the piano.
Yes, it is.
Hm. I wonder why
Mugi-senpai decided to join,
the Light Music Club in the
first place?
Image-wise, you'd think she'd
be more cut out for classical
piano.
I've never talked to her about
stuff like that, have I?
What? What's the matter?
I don't have something on my
face do I?
No, I uh...
You have some frosting on your
cheek.
I do?!
Wait a second, hold still.
Oh thank you.
So now you know I've been
sneaking bites to eat...
Wait, you've done this before?
Yeah, sometimes.
(snickering)
I feel so stupid now for
worrying so much and being
nervous and stuff!
(door opens)
[Ritsu] Hey, quite pushing!
[Yui] I can't help it!
[Mio] Be quiet, you two!
What are you guys doing out
there?
Geez, come inside instead of
eavesdropping from the hall next
time.
You two had a real
interesting dynamic going there.
What is that suppose to mean?
Mugi-chan, this cake you
brought it's yummy!
Is it? I'm glad you like it.
[Tsumugi] Oh! Just a moment,
I have something to hand out to
everyone.
What is this?
Yeah, it's you again, isn't it?
You and your stickers.
Pretty cute, don't you think?
Don't do that!
Thank you for waiting!
I decided to try writing a new
song for the school festival!
Hey, way to go!
[Yui] And Mugi-chan gets a gold
star!
[Azusa] Again with the stickers?
[Ui] When my sister's into
something, she's REALLY into it.
[Jun] I had no idea Mugi-senpai
had such a cute side to her.
She has more than a few odd
sides to her, too, though.
You mean like she suddenly
appears out of no where like
she's teleporting?
Not really.
I think it's great how
she's so sweet and kind,
and thoughtful even though
she's really, really rich.
Yeah I know.
She's always acts so cheerful
whenever she serves tea and
pastries to us.
So in other words, you look
forward to drinking her tea
every day.
I-It's not like that at all!
Calm down. Still, I gotta say
I'm pretty surprised,
she's been sneaking bites
of food all this time.
Yeah I know, right?
[Azusa] I didn't go to the club
room to think about how cute
Mugi-senpai is!
All right, today is the day
I'm going to make my comeback!
No, that sounds wrong.
[Mio] What does?
[Azusa] Mio-senpai?
What is it that sounds wrong?
[Azusa] N-No, it's nothing!
So I see that the others aren't
here yet.
[Mio] No, they're busy with
stuff like supervising class
chore teams today.
Maybe we should start
practicing without them, then?
[Mio] Sure, good idea.
[Mio] Give me a minute, okay?
I really want to change my
strings first.
Sure.
Azusa, is something wrong?
Not at all!
Are you sure?
Yes!
Oh! What songs do
you want to do for the festival?
Well, we should definitely
include the song that Mugi just
wrote,
but other than that...
Well I've been thinking that a
ballad might be nice for a
change.
Hey you know, that just might
work for us!
Okay, let's propose
that idea to the others.
Sure!
[Mio] A ballad, huh? That sounds
like fun!
I'm making my comeback!
[Mio] Hm? You say something?
Uh... No!
[Mio] Really?
[Azusa] Yes!
[Azusa] Sitting here doing this,
it almost feels like,
we're a real Light Music Club,
doesn't it?
[Mio] Yeah. But we ARE a Light
Music Club.
Okay, that should do it then.
Oh great. In that case,
I'll go get the tea ready.
[Mio] Oh, you want to have tea?
Well, the others aren't here
yet,
[Mio] so I guess...
[Azusa] It was just a
suggestion.
[Mio] If you want to have tea,
we can.
[Azusa] It was a suggestion!
But you-
(Ritsu busts through the door)
Oh, it's you, Ritsu.
Don't scare me like that!
[Mio] What's wrong?
M-Mio!
I'm begging you! Help me out
with my Home Ec assignment!
With Home Ec?
I forgot what the assignment
was.
Ri-chan doesn't have
a clue how to sew a skirt.
Oh, that one.
Yeah, well you can't do it,
either!
I'm gonna have Ui help me,
thank you very much!
Is that really something to brag
about?
But you're really good
at sewing buttons on.
This is on a sewing machine!
I'm really bad at it.
Oh, brother... I guess I have
to.
It's not like we can blow off
school work to do club stuff.
Ri-chan, I'll be happy to help
you, too!
Let's head over to
Ri-chan's house right now!
[Ritsu] Thank you, thank you,
everyone!
The way this is looking, we're
not gonna-
Um, what about band practice?
Hm? What's wrong, Azusa? Aren't
you coming too?
I knew it!
[Azusa echoes] I knew it!
K-ON!
I came with them...
[Ritsu] Azusa!
Why are you still outside?
[Azusa] Coming!
Thanks for having me.
(Toilet flushes)
[Satoshi] That you, Sis?
Mom said to put your
dirty clothes in the wa-
Hi, Satoshi.
Hey, these are my friends
from the Light Music Club.
Pardon the intrusion!
Sure...I uh... Hi. Excuse me.
He went back into the bathroom.
He's a weird kid.
She's really good at that...
Azu-nyan! Here you go!
You forgot this in the club room
when you left yesterday.
Oh, thank you for picking it up!
Can I peel this off?
[Yui] Azu-nyan, you meanie!
Okay, all done.
Huh? Already?
[Tsumugi] You are so good at
this!
Hey, where's Ritsu?
You know, she went downstairs
and never came back.
Oh, excuse me. I need to step
out and use the ladies' room.
Do you know where it is?
Sure. I saw it by entryway
when we walked in.
[Mio] What's up, Satoshi?
Sis said to call you guys
downstairs.
Wow, did you made
all this yourself, Ri-chan?
[Ritsu] Indeed I did!
That smells great!
Ri-chan, thanks for going
to all this trouble!
Yes, thank you very much!
[Ritsu] Oh don't sweat it!
What kind of friend would I be,
if I didn't do anything for all
your help?
Now, let's all sit down and dig
in!
Alright then, I think
that's everything we need.
Mio, do you have tea over there?
[Mio] Yeah, I'm fine.
Ritsu-senpai!
What? Did I forget anything?
No, it's nothing to do with
the dinner you made...
There's something over here
that's not really fit for the
dinner table...
Sorry! They're my dad's.
No, I'm really sorry that I
brought it up.
[Yui] They're pink!
Let's not talk about it!
Now, why don't we all try this
again.
[Everyone] Thank you for the
meal!
Now dig in, everyone!
The hamburger steaks is
delicious!
[Ritsu] You think so? Glad to
hear it!
And the rice is really tasty,
too!
[Ritsu] You have my family's
prized rice cooker to thank for
that!
You do love your rice, don't
you, Ritsu?
Yeah! I'm Japanese, after all!
I think, rice is amazing too!
But sometimes we have toast
in the morning instead.
Strawberry jam is so yummy!
What do I usually have?
[Ritsu] Foolish girls! When
you're Japanese, you eat rice!
Rice!
So you just ended up going over
to Ritsu-senpai's place and
goofing around?
We went to go help her
with her homework assignment!
I'm jealous! You got to
have her home cooking!
Yeah, and everything she cooked
was really delicious too.
Oh boasting now, are we?
You're trying to make me
jealous?
I-I didn't mean it like that!
Now, now. It's good to do
something like that once in a
while.
Every journey needs some rest
stops.
You really think so?
Yep, I do!
[Jun] Oh, hey, about our next
assignment-
Our problem is that rest stops
are all that we do in this
club!
Today, I am definitely,
definitely, definitely
making a comeback!
I'm a lot less confident
now for some reason.
[Azusa] No! Third time's the
charm!
[Azusa] Yui-senpai?
Hi Azu-nyan!
[Azusa] Good afternoon.
The others haven't gotten here
yet?
Nah.
Oh, really?
We're going to practice today
anyway!
Before we do that,
come over here and look at this.
Ton-chan's tank looks funny.
[Yui] You think that maybe
we should clean it?
[Azusa] Yeah, you're right.
I'll go get the hose.
No! I'm getting infected by
her slacker attitude again!
We're going to practice today!
We're going to practice!
[Yui] For Ton-chan, we scrub
his tank all sparkling clean!
[Azusa] Focus on cleaning the
tank instead of singing your
weird songs!
[Yui] Yes, ma'am!
For Ton-chan, we scrub
his tank all sparkling-
[Azusa] Yui-senpai!
[Yui] You're a harsh mistress,
Azu-nyan-senpai.
[Azusa] What are you talking
about?
Oh, why don't we also get rid of
the stickers on that mirror
over there while we're at it?
[Yui] For Azu-nyan,
we scrub his tank all sparkl-
[Azusa] Would you PLEASE
stop singing that ridiculous
song?
All done!
[Yui] It looks a lot more comfy
now.
Isn't that great, Ton-chan?
Aw you really do love Ton-chan,
don't you, Azu-nyan?
That's really not it at all.
Ton-chan took my mind off my
problems!
All right, why don't we go
practice now?
Sure, why not?
That's right! There was
something that I wanted you to
help teach me how to do.
Mugi-chan wrote that song
a little while ago, remember?
It's kinda complicated.
Ah, you must mean the guitar
solo in it. Sure, I can help!
[Yui] No, not that.
Um... I can't figure out how
you're supposed to read it.
You don't know how?
[Azusa] So on the third verse,
you skip to here, this symbol is
a dal segno,
and tells you to jump back
to the other one like it,
and then we end at this al fine
here.
Yui-senpai?
Sorry, sorry! It's just a little
convoluted.
That's true, it is a little
hard to remember it all.
I just wish that she'd written
it in Japanese, instead of like
that.
Instead of forte, say "loud"!
Instead of fortissimo, say
"really loud"!
Oh, and you know that little
symbol near the very end of the
song,
that you thought looked kind of
neat
that one's called a fermata
and it tells you to pause.
Oh, so that's what it's called!
Leave that one as "fermata"
it sounds way cooler!
Make up your mind.
Wow, the rest of the guys
sure are taking their time.
They are.
I could use Mugi-chan's tea
about now...
Yeah, me too.
N-Not this time!
Let's start practicing!
We're practicing today,
no ifs, ands, or buts!
Sitting around like this is
what's wrong with this club!
Practice! Practice!
Hey, what's gotten into you,
Azu-nyan?
You're so gung ho today.
T-Today is no different!
I'm always like this, senpai!
You are?
Yes, I am!
Um. I think.
I suppose you could say
that this is the real me.
Or that I've been off my game
lately. Or maybe just a little
lazy.
Wait! That's right! I just
wouldn't be the real me if I
wasn't acting like this!
I get it!
Wow, you really think up some...
...really philosophical
stuff, huh, Azu-nyan?
I guess I never really gave any
of that all that much thought.
Well, you know...
Guess I'm trying to say that
you're your own person.
[Yui] Ri-chan is Ri-chan.
Mio-chan is Mio-chan.
And Mugi-chan is Mugi-chan.
So I suppose that's why I really
never put too much thought into
it.
I could go for one of
Mugi-chan's cakes...
Right AFTER we practice!
[Yui] You just got fortissimo
mad!
[Azusa] Please don't
use musical terms that way.
[Jun] Well, I'll be.
You two are getting along.
Well, yeah, but I went there
so we could practice.
Is Azusa-chan here?
Yes, what is it?
Here, for you.
[Girl] This is yours, isn't it?
No way!
Is it yours?
Yeah! Thanks a lot!
Sure thing!
How did she know it was mine?
What was that about?
Nothing major.
[Tsumugi] Thank goodness you
found it.
[Azusa] I know. Yui-senpai,
I really want to thank you.
[Ritsu] Shucks, it was nothin'!
[Mio] You didn't return it.
[Yui] Alright! So that's
everybody!
[Ritsu] Yep!
[Yui] This cake was worth
fermata-ing for!
That's not how you use that
word.
[Tsumugi] Here, Azusa-chan.
Sawa-chan says that she's
not going to make it today.
But I had it last time. Are you
sure?
[Ritsu] Your name was on it,
so it's yours.
Isn't that sticker so cute
you want to hug it?
[Yui] Eat lots so you can
grow up big and strong!
Do you mind if I peel this off?
No way! Leave it on.
All right everyone,
please decide which position you
want to fill and sign up by next
week.
[Ui] Azusa-chan!
[Ui] What do you think you're
going to want to do?
Well I haven't really decided
yet.
I guess I think I'm going to be
a waitress this time.
"Welcome to our cafe!
May I take your order, please?"
[Ui] That sounded perfect!
That's pretty good, so what kind
of cat are you going to be?
What do you mean?
Well, you will be wearing
cat ears, won't you?
Why would I do that?
Huh? Waitresses at a cafe always
wear cat ears, don't they?
Azusa-chan...
You're in the Light Music Club,
all right.
[Azusa] T-This isn't...
This isn't the real me!
(closing song, "NO, Thank You!")
[Mio] You sure seem
excited today.
[Yui] Yeah, the school festival
is soon!
[Sawako] How about your
classroom?
[Yui] Thanks for waiting!
[Ritsu] Now off to
the club room.
[Sawako] Yeah, about
the club room...
Sawa-chan?
It's out of use for a while.
What is?
The club room.