He's so cute...
Mio are you scared of it?
I'm not scared, I just haven't
reached the point where I think
it's cute yet.
But he IS cute!
Right, Ton-chan?
[Tsumugi] He looked at you!
He's looking at me!
I'm right over here!
[Yui] Ton-chan!
Hey! Ton-chan!
[Yui] You try calling him,
too, Mio-chan!
Ton-chan...
(snort-like sniffs)
Kay, that was cute...
Right? Right?
Yui-senpai, if we're going to
keep him,
we have to look after him
properly, too.
The water must be kept at a
precise temperature and changed
regularly.
Wow, he's higher maintenance
than Geeta.
[Azusa] He also has to be fed
every day.
Oh, if you ever run low on food,
I'll bring some from home.
We have Chinese pond turtles,
Asian yellow pond turtles,
and eastern musk turtles too.
She's an expert!
That'd be a big help!
Don't you worry, we're all gonna
take real good care of you.
That's right, we won't get sick
of you and just throw you away.
[Ritsu] I'm sick of this!
I'm sick of the drums!
[Yui] Ri-chan, what's the
matter?
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
What do you mean,
you're sick of the drums?
Sorry! That was an exaggeration.
However... Look at this!
This is our Club activity
footage recorded by
the student council.
I got it from Nodoka.
[Tsumugi] That's our
freshman year!
[Yui] That takes me back!
[Azusa] I saw that one!
We all saw Mio-senpai's--
[Mio] Ah! Stop the video!
No way! Look at where
the drums are!
[Yui] You're all dark, Ri-chan!
Your forehead is
nice and bright!
Hey shut up!
I guess the lights
just aren't hitting you.
Yeah, because you're way in
back.
When looking from straight on,
you're the only one of us who
isn't visible.
And it's not just this show!
[Ritsu] Last year's
welcome show!
[Tsumugi] You're dark!
[Ritsu] And this year's
welcome show!
[Azusa] I think I saw your foot!
[Mio] Wow, the camera
misses you completely.
(Ritsu weeping)
So...what do we do?
[Ritsu] I wanna play
another instrument.
Wait just a minute.
You can't just change
instruments. Who's gonna play
the drums if you don't?
(soft whining)
She hasn't thought this
through.
[Mio] Besides, weren't you the
one
who said you hated how "fiddly"
all the other instruments were?
That's true.
But maybe we should try
switching instruments every
once in a while.
Just for laughs.
That sounds like a lot of fun!
That's a great idea!
Wanna try playing the guitar?
Is it okay?
Eh!
Ta-dah!
That suits you rather well!
Yeah, looking real good, senpai!
It seems out of character.
[Tsumugi] Why don't you
try playing something?
[Yui] Wah!
What's the matter, Yui-senpai?
Geeta's cheating on me!
You willingly handed him over
with a smile on your face!
Thank you, Geeta.
We had good times, you and I.
If it's not one thing, it's
another...
So, teacher, what do I do first?
Me? Teacher?!
[Yui] Sure Ri-chan, I'll teach
you!
I'll just go make us all some
tea. She'll get bored of this
soon enough.
You form the chords with your
left hand and strum with your
right one.
Sorry, but I already know all
that stuff.
What should I teach you, then?
Fine, I guess I'll be handling
this.
For now, let's try playing
"Fuwa Fuwa Time".
Yes, ma'am!
Let's see...
It might be easier if
you played sitting down.
Then I'll sit down...ready.
Okay, the first chord in the
song is an E.
Your index finger goes
on string 3 at fret 1.
And uh... And the middle one
on string 5 at fret 2.
And then your ring finger
goes on string 4 at fret 2.
Um...
Your index finger goes here.
And the middle one here.
Just like this. You see?
Now, pressing down your fingers
like that, strum the guitar.
Um, Ri-chan? Try to keep your
right hand really relaxed. Like
a cooked noodle!
And keep the fingers pressing
on the strings curled more.
Some of the notes
aren't coming out cleanly.
Ri-chan, you need to hold
the pick gently! Very gently!
[Azusa] Okay, the sound is
starting to come together.
Ritsu-senpai, keep your back
a little straighter.
[Yui] You should move your
left wrist forward a little.
So, shall we move on to the next
chord?
[Yui] It's pretty tough to play,
isn't it?
I'm not cut out for this.
Wow, it's a big pain to have
to keep track of all that stuff.
I had no idea.
[Yui] That's quite all right.
Welcome back, Geeta!
Who's a good boy?
Good morning Miss Yamanaka!
Good morning.
Good morning, Ri-chan.
Oh hey, Sawa-cha-huh?
Sawa-chan is glowing!
[Everyone] Let's dig in!
Nodoka, your lunches always
look so wonderfully delicious.
Yeah, Nodoka-chan has
always been a terrific cook!
[Mio] So's Ui-chan.
Am I the luckiest girl
in the world, or what?
I've noticed your lunches
are always packed full, Mugi.
I burn up a lot of energy.
On what?
Mio, your lunches,
always look so cute and cuddly.
Wow, I guess your mom must still
think of you as her darling
little girl, huh?
What's Ritsu doing?
[Yui] Just wandering around.
Like a bird.
Kind of like Cozy Powell, in a
good way.
She's been restless for as long
as I've known her. She gets
bored easily.
But her drumming has
been the one constant.
I'm back!
Welcome home!
Ritchan here! Have some of
Nodoka-chan's omelette!
Can I?
You already took a bite...
And on that note, I'll be trying
out the keyboard today!
Exactly what note are you
talking about?
Another Shine On, You Crazy
Ri-chan instalment?
You don't understand, Yui,
I HAVE to shine!
When everyone has their eyes
on you, that's when you sparkle!
Look her!
What was that?
Just look at her!
Ever since Sawa-chan became
our homeroom teacher,
it seemed like her skin's been
glowing, and her hair's been
silky and shiny!
It's like she's blossoming or
something!
I guess I get more chances to
take the stage, a teacher's
lectern in this case,
now that I'm a homeroom teacher.
And I wanna sparkle, too!
So you're going to try out the
keyboard.
It said "Bingo"!
Can you read sheet music, Ritsu
senpai?
It said, "I read it fine!"
How can she interpret that?
You're making trouble
for Mugi, so--
Or not.
My keyboard is actually
speaking!
Oh! It just said "Mugi-chan"
just now!
It did, it did!
[Mio] Oh, brother...
It's neat how you can get so
many different tones out of a
keyboard.
I'm getting all sorts of
wonderful ideas for new songs!
[Azusa] What kind of songs?
This is so cool!
That looks like fun.
Mugi, you think I might
be able to have a try?
Stop that!
I hate that, Ritsu,
stop making that sound.
Fine! I'm sorry!
[Mio] What're you doing?
[Ritsu] Jerk!
Hey Ri-chan, aren't you
gonna try playing the bass?
No, not the bass!
[Yui] Why not?
I'm on bass...
And I don't ever want to play
anything but the bass,
I only want to be a bassist.
I just love its low, deep sound.
The way it supports all of you
without ever standing out...
I also like writing bass lines
that fit in with everything
you're doing.
One who doesn't take center
stage,
but doesn't get drowned out
by the other members.
That's the kind of bassist
I always want to be.
I know, Mio.
That's why I'll never touch your
bass, Mio. So don't worry about
it.
I do declare I'm kind
of jealous, Miss Tainaka!
Don't be like that!
I said way too much...
Uh-oh! Hey Mio-chan! Mio-chan!
Hello?
Oh, no! She's turning
into one of the living dead!
That is so great. It's just like
Mio and her bass are one and the
same.
I know what you mean,
I love her bass playing!
So do I.
Oh, come on! How long is she
going to stay stiff as a board?
Don't worry, Ri-chan!
Just leave everything to me! I'm
going to work this all out!
You'll see!
[Yui] Snap out of it Mio,
[Yui] or Death's gonna
come for ya!
[Ritsu] What am I leaving
to her?
(clinking sounds)
[Ui] Sis? What're you doing?
That's bad manners, you know?
I'm sitting here in a dark
corner
trying to formulate Operation:
Shine On, You Crazy Ri-chan.
Well, I'd like to wash
the dishes but...
I guess it can wait.
(dejected)
[Yui] K-ON!
Okay, here we go!
There's another class after us,
so get into position quickly.
Alright, how do you want us
to line up?
[Sawako] Um, by seat number?
Wouldn't it be better
if we lined up by height?
Oh, you're right.
Thank you for that.
This is the very first homeroom
class I've ever had,
so please, if I make
any mistakes, be sure
to point them out.
Miss Yamanaka is really great.
It's like she's getting prettier
and prettier every day.
I like being on the end.
I think I'll stand here!
Scuse me!
[Ritsu] Could you squeeze
over just a little bit?
[Mio] We're lining up
by height, remember?
[Ritsu] Watch this!
Ah, Ri-chan,
you've grown taller!
You're sneaky.
Look, we're all together!
I guess we're not going by
height anymore.
I say we're better off
being all together.
Me too! It's gonna be
a great class picture!
So is everyone in position?
Alright, whenever you're ready!
Okay! Everybody smile!
[Photographer] Say cheese!
[Yui] Hey, this is great!
[Ritsu] What are you doing?
Ri-chan! We moved
the drum set around! See?
You're smack in the middle now!
I was thinking about
this idea all night long!
You were right about changing
things! Come on, try it out!
Try it out!
Alright Yui!
Okay! We'll use this position
from now on!
I'm embarrassed...
I think this works best.
[Everyone] Yeah so do I.
But don't worry, Ri-chan!
You'll still shine!
I'm going to use this
head lamp to light you up!
Cut it out!
Shine on, you crazy Ri-chan!
[Miu] Stop it, Yui! Look at her!
[Mio] She's gasping for breath.
[Yui] Oopsie!
Hey Ri-chan, you aren't lonely,
are you?
Why do you ask?
Well, you're always in the back,
so I thought you might
feel lonely.
No, not really.
What if we try something new?
[Yui] While we're playing, we'll
just interact with you more.
Kinda like this.
Right, now you guys try it.
Let's practice how we're going
to interact with Ri-chan,
who's feeling lonely there in
the back!
Let's do it! One, two!
Hey!
Doesn't that work perfectly?!
Yui, you don't understand,
that's really not why I'm doing
this...
Don't go it alone. Ri-chan,
if you're hurting, we're all
hurting!
[Yui] I won't let you suffer
alone!
[Ritsu] Yui! Look, I'm not
suffering!
Let's get through this together!
Why won't you listen to me?!
Aw, and I brought all
this other stuff too!
Just give it up, Yui,
and take it all back home.
Hey Azu-nyan?
Yes?
If Ritchan doesn't play the
drums,
I was thinking I might take
over.
Why do you say that?
Well, something's really
bothering Ri-chan, I know it.
It's like she's in a, what's the
word I'm looking for?
Sounds like "gut"... Not
"mutt"...
Wait, do you mean rut?
Yeah, that!
Then you were pretty far off.
[Yui] I think that's why she
suddenly,
wants to try out a bunch
of different things.
You really think so?
That's why I'm going to
start playing the drums!
I'll just sit behind you guys
and play the drums!
Maybe not, I think I'd rather
you stay where I can see you.
Aw, why?
You're reading too much into it,
Senpai.
This will make my skin glow even
more!
(phone vibrates)
Thinking about it, I just
realized I haven't played my
drums for a few days.
I was the one who suggested it,
but...
I've played the drums every
day,
ever since I decided I was
going to be a drummer.
Let's start a band, Mio!
And I'll be the drummer!
Sounds like fun, but why the
drums?
Isn't it awesome, how
they flail around back there?!
Oh...
[Ritsu] Well, I could only
afford drumsticks at first.
And later on, I finally got
my hands on a used drum kit.
And every day since...
I still have some calluses.
I really whaled away on them at
first.
[Satoshi] Sis! Keep it down!
(panting)
How could you have overslept?!
I was up late watching a movie!
In a village far from
civilization, they had this
horrific custom where they--
[Ritsu] I'm kidding.
It was a Who concert.
What?
The Who.
Oh, right. You like
that band's drummer,
don't you, Ritsu?
(school bell rings)
Crap! Mio, get a move on!
[Sawako] Please make sure
you fill out
the self-study activity form
for the class trip by
tomorrow, okay?
There are so many temples
that it will seem daunting,
but plan ahead to give
yourselves enough time to
visit each in turn.
Ri-chan! Mio-chan!
[Yui] I thought you were
home sick!
Sorry about that!
Heh... Whoa!
All right, take your
seats please.
[Ritsu] Sawa-chan?
[Yui] What's wrong, Sawa-chan?
[Ritsu] It's freaky!
I've been trying all sorts of
creams to make my skin glow
even more...
Oh my goodness...
(Sawako sobbing)
[Both] You overdid it.
Ta-dah!
It's drums or nothing for me!
Yeah, I figured as much.
She told me she watched
a Keith Moon DVD yesterday.
Who's that?
He's a drummer Ritsu
really admires.
Oh, he's the guy they called
Moon the Loon and Mad Moon,
right?
[Azusa] I heard that he
demolished his house with cherry
bombs or something.
Well that's not what I
admire about him.
You know, even if I'm in
the shadows and aren't
in the spotlight,
and you can only my feet,
I still love playing my drums!
[Yui] Yeah!
No one but you can be
our drummer!
[Ritsu] Yui?
[Yui] When we all look back at
you when we're just about to
start a song,
you count us in with your sticks
and you have a big grin
on your face.
That always gets me
so pumped up!
[Yui] Besides, I also learned
some things thanks to you.
Even though we're all
in the same band,
what we see and think are
sometimes very different.
We all have our own places here,
and each of us is different,
but when...
But when we start playing,
we become one!
Right!
[Ritsu] You know, as I sit on
my stool and watch your backs...
I listen to you play and
I bang away on my drums!
I love it!
Oh, I also did something
thanks to you. I wrote us
a brand new song.
And it was all because you made
my keyboard speak to me
that day.
You mean those noises?
What kind of song is it?
I wanna hear it!
(keyboard and humming)
Yeah, I like it!
Hey I think you should play and
sing this one, Mugi-chan!
Great idea!
[Mio] Yeah, that might work!
Mio, get to work on the lyrics!
Um you guys, I also thought of
a real good title for the song.
[Yui] What is it? What is it?
I call it "Honey Sweet Teatime."
Tea again, huh?
Wow, these rusks are fantastic
when you put honey on
all over them!
It's the intermingling of
flavors, the combination
of tastes!
You've got some sticky stuff
on the side of your mouth.
Wipe it for me, will ya?
No way!
They're a good team
in their own way.
[Azusa] Here wipe it yourself!
What am I going to do with you?
The honey-colored afternoon
passes by...
And it's "Honey sweet teatime."
Hey how would it sound if
we repeated that phrase twice?
That could work!
(loud nibbling)
I can't concentrate...
Well then maybe we should
all just take a break?
(closing song, "Listen!!")
[Speaker] Kyoto... Kyoto...
[Yui] Ritchan, what's that?!
It looks like a giant daikon
radish!
There's one over here, too!
[Ritsu] (laughs) That's so
goofy!
[Yui] "Kitano Tenmangu"?
[Ritsu] Hey, is this place
famous or something?
What a view!
[Yui] Wow! All of that is Kyoto?
[Ritsu] Oops.
How could this have happened?
[Ritsu] We're lost.
Please, just for a while!
I have tasty snacks, too!