[Ritsu] C'mon, Mugi, let's go!
I still have to finish my
journal and hand it in,
so go on ahead.
I didn't think you were on
cleaning duty today, Mugi?
Well, actually Yui was
supposed to do it, but...
(snoring)
She's been sleeping like that
since lunch break.
(frustrated)
I've been trying to wake her up,
but...
Come on, Yui, you've got to wake
up.
Hey, Yui! Wake up!
It's okay, Ui...
Today's Sunday after all.
That's impressive
positive thinking!
Wake up, Yui! You got shows!
You gotta practice!
You gotta play your guitar!
Yui, we've got cake...
Liars. No cake.
We're losing her!
Mugi, go get some cake!
[Tsumugi] Roger!
Miss Tainaka.
Bye, Yamanaka.
Bye Miss Tachibana.
Could you guys please return
those animal costumes I lent you
a couple weeks ago?
The Drama Club wants
to use them next week.
[Mio] Animal costumes?
Ritsu, you havn't
returned those yet?
Oh, you mean those things?
Let's see what did I do with
them?
[Ritsu] After we used them
for our recruitment drive,
[Ritsu] I put them in
the storeroom.
[Mio] Give them back.
I'm stunned.
I'm so sorry!
Let's see... where did I put
those things?
See? Here they are!
Light Music Club Sandwich...
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
So because of that, we're going
to do some spring cleaning!
And you can wipe those "I don't
wanna" looks off your faces.
Right! Let's knuckle down and
practice all-out today!
Yeah, you got it, Ri-chan!
It's Budokan or bust for us!
Wow, you're that opposed to
cleaning up?
C'mon...
[Yui and Ritsu] We hate cleaning
more than we love three meals a
day!
[Mio] That's not how that saying
works!
And anyway, shouldn't
the people who've been assigned,
to Music Room cleaning duty
do all the cleaning in here?
And not us?
Yeah, yeah!
Well normally, that would be
right...
[Mio] But we can't make someone
else clean up a mess,
that's mostly our own personal
belongings.
It's not "mostly",
it's all personal belongings.
Indeed, it is as you say!
That's my froggie!
Guess we'd better
put these away.
I already put this away once...
Don't put them back, darn it!
Okay, let's do this right!
This really is a lot of stuff...
Yes, we've used it as a
"for the time being" storeroom,
for any odds and ends
we were carrying with us.
[Ritsu] That's a lot of odds and
ends. What with this pile of
dolls?
(excited) I scored that big one
over there for just two dollars!
I didn't ask that.
Here you go, take it home.
Okay, I got 'em...
[Ritsu] Wait a minute.
Don't forget this one.
But that one isn't mine.
Then who--
It's yours, Mio?!
I brought this coffee set in
last year, but we never got
around to using it.
Wait a minute, you're gonna
clean out the cupboard, too?
Might as well, we're cleaning,
anyway.
[Ritsu] Seeing it all laid out
like that, they sure look
expensive, huh?
How much is this tea set worth,
Mugi-chan?
Well um, I don't know the exact
price,
but I was told that the royal
family of Belgium has the same
set.
Royal family?
Watch it!
(workout chants)
[Ritsu] Well that's most of it.
Yes, but...
There's a lot of personal items
here that don't belong to us.
Perhaps they belonged to the
previous members of the Light
Music Club.
It looks like the earlier clubs
had a lot more membership.
They must have had proper club
activities back then.
[Yui] Look, look!
Ta-dah!
Look what I found way in the
back!
[Ritsu] Oh! That case looks
expensive!
What sort of treasure
do you think lies within?
[Yui] It's a guitar!
It's kinda old, but it looks
really nice.
[Ritsu] Dang, I was hoping
for something cooler.
Yeah it's pretty lame.
[Azusa] We're the Light Music
Club, how can an instrument be
lame?
My goodness, that really takes
me back.
What do you mean?
So this is where it was...
Is this yours, Miss Yamanaka?
[Sawako] Yes, though
I never really used it much.
Were you a part of the Light
Music Club when you were in
school?
That's right.
Didn't I mention that to you?
I knew it had to be something
like that!
That time you played with us at
the school festival, I thought
you were fantastic!
I'm okay.
I havn't played for a while,
but I guess I'm better than
Yui-chan is right now.
Oh please, you've got to teach
me!
Of course I will!
Hey check this out, this is what
she looked like back in high
school.
I think I'll pass.
How come?!
We're all taking home our own
personal stuff that we've kept
here,
so you can take yours.
Geh! It's musty!
I really don't really have time
to play anymore...
What do you want to do
with your guitar, then?
I want you to sell it, and put
the proceeds in the club fund.
You're so generous!
It's more like-
We're doing her dirty work!
But isn't this an awfully
fancy guitar to be selling?
I got this guitar a long time
ago, from a friend of my father,
but if it's this dusty and
moldy, it might not really be
playable anymore.
Besides, if it's in sellable
condition,
I'm sure this old guitar would
be a lot happier if it was being
played by someone.
[Yui] It's so musty...
You're so mean, for making me
carry it the whole way!
It's your own fault for losing
three rounds of rock-
paper-scissors!
Come on, you can do it,
Yui-chan!
Yeah but my bag is really heavy
today!
You have no one to blame
but yourself for that.
Really good work, Yui-chan.
It's time for another round.
[Yui] Really? Great!
No way am I losing this time!
Alright then, prepare to get
shot down!
[Azusa] You're like a bunch of
children...
[Ritsu] I AM a child!
[Azusa] Let's act like adults,
okay?
[Tsumugi] I can see it! Is
that suppose to be scissors?
[Yui] You're not supposed
to say, Mugi-chan!
Hey C'mon, Mio!
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Mio] Look at this.
You mean that sales ad you
picked up?
[Mio] Would one of these
fit in the prep room?
[Ritsu] A shelf set?
[Mio] I think one of these
would help us organize things.
[Azusa] You're right.
At that price, I think we can
manage with the funds in the
club account.
[Mio] Hm, where's the furniture
section?
Wow! So this is a home center?!
Mugi-chan?
They sell all manner of items
here, right?
Like light bulbs in all sizes?
And vinyl tape in all the colors
of the rainbow?
[Mio] Yeah, I guess.
Mugi, this is your first time
in a home center?
Mm-hm!
I've always wanted to visit one!
Let's go!
Me, too!
Hey, Yui! The guitar!
[Tsumugi] Oh, my, my, my, my,
my! Amazing!
Look!
It says that this pen will mend
holes in walls and make them as
good as new!
Right.
This makes it super easy
to bind up old magazines!
This stuff seems that amazing to
you?
This will restore faucets
to a sparkly, new finish?
[Tsumugi] Will it really?
Mugi-senpai! Look at
what they have up here!
A cake slicer that cuts any cake
into eight neat, equal pieces?
It looks like an umbrella!
Will this really work like it
says?
Guys! Guys! Come over here!
[Yui] Look at this!
Check out all these screws!
[Azusa] You're spazzing out,
too?
These are ALL screws!
Uh-huh...
It's so pretty!
Check it out! I feel so cool!
Wah!
[Azusa] What the heck is that?
A cordless screwdriver!
Bang! P-pow!
Quick making noise!
Done! You two are now dead!
Unbelievable...
Unbelievable's right...
Yui, you're such a baby.
Ah! I'm blind!
Take that off!
Please, Miss, stop it, I beg of
you! Stop!
[Mio] Quit playing around
with stuff you aren't going to
buy!
[Yui] Azu-nyan! Azu-nyan!
What is it this time, Yui?
This is really easy to move in!
It's hanging off of you.
Maybe we could us these for a
show!
And we could write
After-school Teatime across the
backs!
You mean like a biker gang?
Thanks. I'm sorry to disturb
you.
Sawa-chan says that
we can keep it in the room.
Okay, that's perfect.
We'll have them deliver it to
the club room after school
tomorrow.
Where are the others?
Oh they're around here
somewhere.
Here comes Mugi!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Wah! Exactly how much did you
buy?!
[Azusa] A turtle?
Or a terrapin?
Azu-nyan!
What'cha lookin' at?
Cut that out! Don't do that
here!
[Yui] W-What a cute little
terrapin!
Cute? I don't even think it is a
terrapin.
Even among terrapins,
this one here is a total babe!
No, I mean it...
It says it's a pig-nosed turtle!
It's a turtle! You see?
It's so cute I wanna stick
peanuts in its nose!
Exactly how are you defining
the word "cute"?
I can't believe I lost four
straight matches after the
store.
Hail the scissors!
[Store clerk] Well, I'm going
to need to appraise it.
[Mio] Please do.
[Mio] What are you looking at?
I was wondering what our band
would sound like if we had this
many members in it?
I know what you mean.
It would be nice if we
had that many people.
[Store clerk] I'm done
with the appraisal, Miss.
Thank you all for your patience.
Now about this guitar of yours.
We'll be able to offer you
$5000 for it.
$5000?!
[Yui] K-ON!
Is there a problem?
Thank you it was delicious!
Let's go!
Hold it.
B-But...$50,000!
Calm down. You added a zero
there.
Thank you for all your help.
You're agreeing too quickly!
So why is that guitar worth so
much? Is it a favor to Mugi and
her family?
Uh, no, she has nothing to do
with it.
[Clerk] This particular line of
guitars was born in the early
1960s.
At the time, they hadn't
completely pinned down its
materials and shape yet,
and it underwent a series of
minor changes until they settled
on its current design.
The guitar that you brought in
has a fingerboard made of
Brazilain Rose wood.
A wood that's very rarely found
in a musical instrument these
days.
That's one reason that
it commands such a high price.
Unfortunately, the guitar's
tailpiece has been swapped out
with a replacment.
Since it's not a full original,
that lowers its value somewhat,
but the playability of this
particular tailpiece is
superior,
and since many customers favor
that type, that hardly counts
against it at all.
Plus, this guitar appears to
have been in kept in its case
for a long time,
so there are no scratches
or any fret warping.
For a guitar its age,
it is in excellent condition,
and that's why we're
offering such a high price.
A-Anyway, it's a very rare
guitar!
[Ritsu] Look at that stack!
What? It's just a special
burger.
I'm not talking about the
Isn't that an awful lot of
french fries?
Hey, we're loaded to the gills,
now! So I ordered us the extra
large size!
Keep the change!
You used the money?!
'Course not,
I paid for all of this myself.
But are you sure it's okay for
us to split it amongst
ourselves?
Well what else can we do?
Sawa-chan said that we should
put it in the club fund.
Oink oink!
Yeah but I-
Look! Five grand, split 5 ways
is a thousand each!
There's a guitar effects pedal
that I've been wanting
for awhile...
There you see?
Azu-nyan's given in...
Idiot! Don't wave that
huge wad of cash around!
You see this? A thousand
of it is yours, Mio.
A thousand, huh?
Gee with that much...I could...
Get a fantastic state of the art
multi-base amp simulator
and a brand new amplifier...
I'd get cool new twin base pedal
and maybe a new floor tom to
round out my kit?
How's this Yui, is this okay?
No harder!
Um, are you guys okay?
Over here! Hi!
Wow! It's perfect!
It's all neat and tidy now, huh?
Yeah.
Yui.
We all agreed to take home
our personal belongings.
But I've got all this stuff left
even after everything I took
home yesterday!
If I take any more,
Ui's gonna get mad real at me!
Yeah well if you leave it here,
I'M gonna get mad at you!
But Ui's so scary! yesterday,
she--
Out.
Oh Ui please forgive me!
It's like she doesn't know
SHE's the older sister!
I promise I'll clean them out
later, just let me keep them
here a little longer!
Oh, all right. But just those,
got it?
What the heck are you doing,
Ritsu?!
(door opens)
[Sawako] Hello!
So did the shelves arrive?
Hey, that looks great!
What's the matter?
I said hi but you didn't say
anything.
Goodness, Sawa-chan! There you
are! Sorry I didn't hear you
come it!
So guys, how'd it go yesterday?
Ah! Yesterday?
Yes with my guitar.
How much did you get for it?
Oh! That! Um, I forget.
How much did we get for it?
Oh, I think it was...
Well, it was pretty old you
know, and being over 50 and all
affected its value.
Really?
Oh, my! Does that mean,
that you're in your fifties,
Sawa-chan?!
You can tell us!
How many women in their fifties
are as hot and nubile as THIS?!
We didn't mean it!
We're sorry! We're sorry!
I told you that I got it from
a friend of my father, remember?
Oh, right I forgot.
Now then, how much money
did you get for it?
Well, it was around...
a hundred dollars.
Ritsu!
What are you thinking?
We're being way too greedy!
Sorry, it slipped out!
Yeah well I figured as much.
It was moldy, after all.
(breath of relief)
Alright, why don't
you give me the sale ticket?
Beg pardon?
I need the reciept so
I can ear mark it, for the club.
Don't tell me that you
didn't get a receipt!
No, um...
Oh, you have it right there?
She ate it! Our hero!
Chow down! Chow down!
What are you doing?!
Spit that out this instant!
Forget it!
Spit it out RIGHT NOW.
Plegh!
No way! It was worth $5000?
That's amazing!
They said that it was extremely
rare!
Forgive me!
I didn't mean to lie about it
and hide it from you,
but the vast sum of money turned
my head around and I just
couldn't help myself!
She's easily corruptible.
She's always been this way.
You two don't have any right to
talk!
Okay, then. I'll go ahead
and donate the $100,
that Ritsu mentioned to
the Light Music Club account.
Consider the rest as going
to pay for those shelves.
Aw you mean that's all?!
I would've given you the whole
thing if you'd come clean in the
first place.
You're lying about that, I know
it!
This whole mess is your fault,
Ritsu. That's what you get for
trying to hide it.
She's right! I told you
we should have just come out,
and told her the truth
from the very begining!
Oh yeah? As if!
Please Sawa-chan!
I have one last request!
Please slap me with the wad of
bills! Slap me in the face
really hard!
Now I'm happy...
Your in your own happy
world, must be nice.
Oh well, all right.
I've decided to use a portion of
this money to buy one thing for
you guys.
You really mean it?
Talk it over and decide
what it is you all want.
So one thing, huh?
I say that you make it five
things, and not just one!
Don't push your luck.
Ow.
I guess an amp is the thing
we need the most of all.
Personally, I think we could use
a guitar effects pedal a lot
more than an amp.
Maybe, but neither of those
things is something all of us
can use.
[Yui] Oo!
[Mio] What is it?
Why don't we just buy
another cute little froggie?
If we had two, I bet we'd get
more members for the club!
[Frog] Welcome to the club!
[Girl] It's so cute!
Wah...
[Tennis coach] When you grip the
handle, just don't hold it too
tightly.
Hit the ball with your whole
body.
If you only hit with your hand,
you'll hurt your wrist or elbow.
Got it?
[Tennis players] Got it!
Well it looks like all the other
clubs,
have their new members in place
and are getting down to work.
Guess so.
[Yui] Azu-nyan's lonely?
Mm-hm.
I know she said that she
was okay with the five of us,
but I know she wants a kouhai.
The very same thing had occurred
to me.
You know, I was thinking that
too.
Yeah, remember how happy we were
when Azu-nyan joined our club?
That settles it, then. Here
goes!
One of you new students...
Help me to the music room
please!
You tried that already.
What do we do, then?!
(thinking)
I have a great idea!
Hm...
What's this doing here?
Meet Ton-chan, he's our brand
new member!
We asked Sawa-chan to buy him
for you!
This is your new kouhai.
So be good to each other!
You know, I was expecting
a bigger reaction, weren't you?
Mm-hm.
You were the one who said that
Azusa would like this turtle,
Yui.
But Azu-nyan was staring at him
like she wanted him really
badly.
[Azusa] You were the one
who was staring at it, not me.
I was just looking because
I thought it had a really
strange face.
Man we really blew it.
Uh Yui?
What made you decide to do this?
Well...
We thought you might be lonely
because you didn't have a
kouhai.
That's why.
So we bought a new member for
you...
It must stink to become
someone's pet,
because they jumped
to the wrong conclusion.
Wow it nodded!
That was so cute!
Don't you worry. I'm going to
take real good care of you from
now on, okay?
[Yui] Yeah, yeah, yeah!
I'm going to take care
of him too!
[Azusa] It's too much
responsibility for you, Yui!
[Yui] Aw come on! It is not!
(closing song, "Listen!!")
[Yui] He's so cute...
[Ritsu] Listen to me ever since
Sawa-chan became our homeroom
teacher,
hasn't it seemed like her
skin's been glowing,
and her hair's been soft and
shiny?!
It's like she's blossoming or
something!
I wanna shine like her, too!
[Tsumugi] Heh. He looked at you,
Yui-chan!
[Ui] That's bad manners you
know.
It's okay, I'm thinking about
how we can make Ri-chan shine,
even when she's
sitting in the dark.