(Yui running and panting)
(unzipping case)
(guitar strumming)
(playing guitar)
(Yui humming along)
(uh?)
[Yui] I look so awesome!
[Ritsu] What are you doing?
[Yui] Huh?
Working on a signature move for
our freshmen reception show!
(intrigued)
It's just kind of weird to see
you here so early.
I set my alarm clock wrong
and came to school an
hour early by mistake.
(ah...)
There's something on your face.
(Hm?)
Oh? Huh?
(Yui gasps happily)
Bread! Bread crumbs!
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
[Yui] Azu-nyan! Congratulations
on becoming a junior!
[Azusa] Why congratulate me for
that?
You know, you really don't look
all that different from last
year, Azusa.
Oh yeah? Well like you're one
to talk, Ritsu-senpai!
[Ritsu] Hey what's the big deal?
I was talking about your height!
[Azusa] Then why were
you looking at my bust line!?
Not much has changed now
that we're seniors.
I have to agree.
Alright! Since we're all here,
how about we practice?!
Yeah!
[Yui narrating] These five
people are the members of
our High School's Light Music
Club.
My name is Yui Hirasawa,
on guitar and vocals.
My favorite things are stuff
that's cute or delicious.
Our drummer and club president
is the ever-energetic Ritsu
Tainaka.
On keyboards is the kind-hearted
and slightly spacey Tsumugi
Kotobuki.
Mio Akiyama's on bass.
She's level-headed, but she's
also really shy and a
scaredy-cat.
And also on guitar is the tiny
and adorable Azusa Nakano.
She's our beloved kouhai!
Azu-nyan is a junior this year,
and the other four of us we're
seniors.
I feel so grown up!
(Hm?)
We all play in a band together
it's called After-school
Teatime,
and have tea and lots of fun
every day!
[Yui] All righty, then...
I can't believe we're finally
seniors! Time sure flew by!
I don't get what you're so happy
about.
Aw come on, Ri-chan,
can you really blame me?
There's something so cool about
it! So what are seniors supposed
to do anyway?
Learn how to set your alarm
clock correctly, for starters.
[Yui] Ri-chan old girl,
take a gander at this!
[Yui] What'cha think?
Hm?
Do I look like a senior?
Am I giving off a new vibe?
[Ritsu] What could possibly have
changed in the last two seconds?
[Tsumugi] Your part!
[Mio] You changed sides!
(gasping)
It's... It's!
It's too hard to tell. Denied.
(Yui upset)
[Yui] I wonder what our class
assignments are gonna be?
[Ritsu] Maybe you'll be off by
yourself in another class again,
Mio!
[Mio] Anything but that!
It'll be all right, Mio.
Goodness! What shocking
development is this?!
(Mio gasping)
[Ritsu] Kidding, I can't see a
thing.
[Mio] I wanna go home...
[Yui] Ri-chan!
[Ritsu] What?
I'll make my way in and take a
look.
[Ritsu] Good luck!
[Yui] Pardon me! Coming through!
(breath of relief)
(Hm?)
But this means--
(struggling) Oops!
I fell down!
What're you doing? Get up Yui.
(sobbing)
Well? So what did you see?
Hm? What do you mean?
Oh! We're all going to be in the
same class together this year!
No way!
We really are?!
Yeah! Isn't that amazing?!
[Ritsu] That's so gross! You've
got snot hanging from your nose!
[Tsumugi] You don't want
to go to class like that.
Hey Mio, isn't that great?
We're all together for senior
year, so you don't have to...
I-I'm so happy!
You could at least try
to pretend like you don't care.
The second time we went, we saw
a lot more of the country...
[Yui] Look, look!
Nodoka's in our class too!
(Ah!)
Looks like this is going
to be a boisterous class.
Isn't this the best class ever?
It's like someone rigged it
to keep us together.
It does! What an amazing
coincidence!
Wait, you don't think--
Did you use your power as
student council president?
No, of course I didn't. No one
could possibly fix it so that--
All right, everyone.
Please take your seats.
She could!
This is my very first time
acting as a homeroom teacher,
so even though I have my share
of shortcomings, let's all have
a good year.
How lucky! We've got Miss
Yamanaka as our homeroom
teacher!
She's gorgeous, and she seems
really nice.
(agreeing)
Hey you shouldn't let
appearances deceive you.
[Ritsu] Sawa-chan is really--
[Sawako] Miss Tainaka?
(shocked)
Ma'am?
Please refrain from talking
class.
I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean anything by it!
There you are!
Hm?
Sawa-chan! We need to talk!
The five of us want to ask you
something really important.
Did you have anything to do with
our homeroom assignment this
year?
Of course. I put all of you
in the same class.
Wait, can you do that?
Aren't you abusing your power?
So what's the problem? Aren't
you happy?
Of course we're happy, but
still...
Besides, it means I have five
fewer names to memorize.
Ah, that explains it.
I absolutely love it! Thank you
for doing that Miss Yamanaka!
You're very welcome.
(heavy breathing)
Quit spazzing out, Yui.
(gasps) But I'm excited
we all get to spend
our final year of high school
together!
It's great that we're together,
but we all need to start
thinking about our future plans.
But this means we all
go on class trips together
and do our school festival
presentation together!
And we can study for all
our tests together,
and I'll be able to copy
your homework too.
[All three] What's that last
one?
[Yui] I'm so psyched to be a
senior!
The orientation ceremony
is about to start.
You should get to the
auditorium.
Yes, ma'am!
(Yui giggling)
See ya later, Sawa-chan!
[Yui] It's gonna be so great
to be a senior!
(gasps)
Ready!
[Teacher] All rise for the
school song.
[Azusa] Let me at it!
What are you so psyched about,
Azusa?
I'm going to get more people
to join the Light Music club!
Yeah!
[Nodoka] Yui.
Ah, Nodoka-chan.
What are you doing there?
It seems like I'm one short of a
dozen.
So you are. Well, I'm off to
the student council meeting.
And I'm gonna go practice for
our reception show right now.
I hope you're able to find some
new members for the club.
Well, I don't mind too much if
we don't.
Do you really mean that?
(mm-hm)
But once you all graduate, Azusa
will be the only one left in the
club.
Wow, you're right...
You need to start thinking
things through. Well, practice
hard.
She's right...
The Light Music Club has
to work hard, for Azusa!
Yeah!
[Yui] K-ON!
[Yui] It's so relaxing here
in the club room!
[Ritsu] I know what you mean. I
had the urge to come here over
spring break.
Yeah so did I!
Okay! What's our first order
of business in this year?
[Azusa] To go and recruit new-
[Ritsu] To eat Mugi's delicious
cake!
I'm kidding, We'll get to that,
I promise.
Geez, take this seriously, would
you?
She's right, Ri-chan.
If we don't get new members,
Azu-nyan's gonna be the only
one left in the club next year.
She's spouting serious words
with a slacker pose...
I hadn't thought of that...
Still, that means that you're a
total lock for club president
next year!
[Ritsu] Sorta like this!
(Azusa laughing)
I-I couldn't care less about
that!
She thought about it.
Just for a second.
Anyway, let's get to work on
scouting new members right away!
She dodged it.
She panicked and changed the
subject.
Oh, I forgot! I made
some recruiting fliers for us!
No way!
My sister Ui said
she thought it'd be a good idea.
Oh...
Here!
Join the Light Music Club!
[Azusa] Why am I a pig?
[Yui] You complete
the Light Music Club Sandwich.
[Azusa] Sorry, I don't get it.
[Yui] We're a club, and club
sandwiches have bacon in them,
get it?
[Azusa] Fine, whatever. Let's
just hand out these fliers.
(Yui dejected)
[Everyone] Join the Light Music
Club!
No one is coming.
At this rate, the club
will be disbanded next year...
[Yui] Azu-nyan's gonna be all
alone.
Senpai... I'm so lonely...
(scared, screaming)
What is it?
[Mio] Azusa!
We can't let that happen!
I agree Yui, we can't!
President!
Right... And having more members
means more money in the
treasury.
Oink, oink!
Yeah! Operation: Capture
New Members is now underway!
[Girl] So anyway...
[Ritsu] Whoops! Whoa!
Uh, hey are you okay?
I'm sorry, but would you mind
helping me to the Light Music
Club room?
[Girls] Is anyone here?
Yes?
Are you all right?
We're here for you.
Hang in there.
Thanks for the help cause...
Right now the Light Music Club
wants you...
Welcome!
[Tsumugi] Would you like
some tea?
[Yui] Sign right here
and you can join us!
[Girls] No-no thank you!
We have cookies!
My "collapse in the hallway"
plan failed.
No Ri-chan, you shouldn't give
up so soon!
Sorry, dearies, but do you know
where the Light Music Club room
is?
[Ritsu] An accent?
[Azusa] What's she doing?
Oh, I think she's getting
directions from them.
I guess that's only natural.
How dumb is she?
Next, we'll go with a spy
operation!
So the basic idea here is
to join a club ourselves,
and see how they get
new members to sign up!
Softness overcomes hardness!
Judo is the art of mastering
techniques in order to hone the
spirit!
Right!
Ah I see, so they use pep
talks.
You know, I think I wanna
join the Judo club!
The hunter becomes the prey!
Go is a microcosm of the
universe.
(Oh?!)
Be my guest.
(disgusted)
Ri-chan it's so bitter...
All those clubs were really
neat, huh?
Yeah.
Wanna take a peek in here?
Is anybody home?
[Ritsu] Greetings!
It says "The sweat of youth."
This one has a special bonus for
joining.
(door opens)
Welcome to the club!
[Ritsu] Geez, it's you guys?
[Tsumugi] We've been handing out
fliers!
[Mio] How did it go on your end?
We didn't have much luck.
You guys went out dressed like
that?
You're very devoted.
(door opens)
Welcome to the club!
[Ritsu] It's just Sawa-chan.
Real nice.
I was wondering, what are you
going to wear for your
performance tomorrow?
Our uniforms are fine!
I made miniskirt maid-
Uniforms!
But they're cute.
(door opens)
Welcome to the club!
[Ritsu] Oh it's just Nodoka.
Oh are you doing costume
fittings?
[Nodoka] Look, about your
live performance tomorrow...
So does this look okay for our
set list?
Let's have a look...
Have a look?
Hm looks good!
[Ritsu] Mugi, when we do this
song, could you have her put a
rift...
[Yui] The first time
Azu-nyan heard us play,
was the moment that she decided
that she wanted to join the
club, wasn't it?
I'm sure that there'll be
more people this year
who will feel the same way
that Azu-nyan did!
I hope. There SHOULD be.
There will be! Probably.
What're you doing over there,
Yui?
Oh! it's almost time for us to
go on!
Awesome! Let's rock this show,
people!
Yeah!
[Yui] Testing, testing...
To all you new students,
congratulations on starting
school!
Welcome all of you!
Aw man. They would've looked
great!
Super cute!
We're the Light Music Club.
And our band is called
After-school Teatime,
and we all have tea and stuff
every day,
it's a whole lot of fun
playing music together.
If you're interested,
join the Light Music Club!
[Ui] Hurry, hurry!
[Jun] Have they already started?
[Ui] Did we miss them?
("Fuwa Fuwa Time" ending)
(applause)
That was great!
Our show this year was awesome!
Azusa and Yui, your guitar work
was in perfect sync today.
Wow! You really think so?
Yes, but Yui burned up all of
her energy and is conked out
over there.
[Azusa] You can't rest now,
Senpai! We have to go hand out
fliers!
(Yui objecting)
No one is coming...
Well, there's still
plenty of time.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Are you going to
hand out fliers?
No the restroom.
You, want to go out and
hand out fliers again?
It's really strange that no
one has come to check us out...
I even made the club room
a more inviting...
(door opens)
(panting)
Yui-senpai! Put this away!
Aw, that was a great idea!
[Yui] You're mean!
(lunchtime chatter)
Azusa-chan!
Real good work.
You still don't have any new
club members?
Is our club really that
unpopular?
[Ui] I don't think that's why.
Yeah, you were great during your
show.
I heard a whole bunch
of new students saying so.
(Azusa happy)
It probably seems like the Light
Music Club is so tightly knit,
that it's hard for anyone else
to break in to it.
[Azusa] Oh. You really think so?
Well yeah, you guys seem
like your such good friends.
[Azusa] Yeah.
Either that, or they've gotten
wind of how weird you guys are.
(dejected)
[Ui] How can you say that?
[Jun] I'm kidding!
Wow, that omelette looks
terrific, Ui!
Want some?
Thanks!
[Mio] Looks like we're not
getting any new members today.
[Ritsu] Guess not...
[Tsumugi] I wonder why?
[Ritsu] Geez, is everybody mad
at us or something?
[Mio] That can't be it.
[Tsumugi] I'm sure that
things will work out.
I mean they have to, right?
[Ritsu] Let's come up with
our next plan of action!
[Ritsu] Operation: Bug Catcher!
[Mio] Operation what?!
Yeah! We'll use big butterfly
nets to catch freshmen!
[Mio] Come on Ritsu,
no one's going to fall for that!
Actually, I'm fine with
the way things are for now.
[Yui] For now, I want things
to stay the way they are.
You know, hanging out in the
club room together like this.
Well, Azu-nyan isn't
here right now but...
Drinking tea, practicing,
and performing together...
Always the five of us.
[Ritsu] I guess you're right.
We'll worry about next year next
year.
That's fine, but a year flies
by fast, you guys.
But that's 365 whole days!
[Yui] Well, a few days
have passed already.
So, Mugi-chan, what's on the
menu today?
[Tsumugi] Help yourselves!
[Yui] (squealing) Which flavor
do you guys want?
[Ritsu] I can't decide!
Oh! I think Azu-nyan will want
the banana cream one!
[Yui] Let's set that one aside
for her.
[Ritsu] Fine, I get the orange
one, then!
[Sawako] I'll take the chestnut!
[Yui] I call dibs on the
chocolate!
[Tsumugi] Vanilla for me!
[Mio] I get the strawberry then.
[Yui] Wow! These look so good!
S-sorry Azu-nyan! We'll go hand
out fliers right away!
Mugi-senpai, could I have
a cup of milk tea, please?
Oh and also that banana cake?
I've decided that this year,
I want to keep on playing
with just the five of us.
Azu-nyan...
Azu-nyan!
Yui-senpai. I'm going to be even
harder,
on you this year, understand?
Come on, take out your guitar.
I changed my mind!
New club members come on!
(closing song, "Listen!!")
[Mio] For those reasons, we are
going to do some spring
cleaning!
[Yui] Hey guys! Look at what I
found!
[Ritsu] Oh that case looks
expensive!
[Ritsu] What sort of treasure
do you think lies within?
[Tsumugi] This makes it super
easy to bind up old magazines!
[Azusa] But are you sure it's
okay for us to split it up
amongst ourselves?
[Ritsu] What else can we do?
Sawa-chan said that we should
just put it in the club fund.
[Yui] Oink!
[Ritsu] Gee, it looks like all
of the other school clubs,
have their new members and
are getting down to work.