[Ui] And that's that...
That takes care of the clothes.
Hanky and tissues, check.
Guidebook, check.
Various snacks, check.
Right, preparations complete!
Okay! The class trip
starts today!
Sis', that is.
Wake up! It's morning!
(groaning)
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
[Ritsu] Yay! A trip! A trip!
Oh yeah! I'm getting
even more amped up!
Hey, you really should
keep your feet off the seat!
She's right, it's not
very ladylike, you know.
[Mio] And you shouldn't eat
snacks nonstop, either, Yui.
[Mio] Put it away and-
[Yui] Here, guys! I'm sharing!
[Yui] I've got some
Matsutake Mountain!
[Mio] Hey wait!
(Mio sighs)
[Girl] Thanks!
No one listens...
[Tsumugi] Here!
Have a cup of tea!
Thank you Mugi!
That's our Mugi!
Oh, right! Let's all take
a picture together!
I agree!
Could you please
settle down a little?
It'll be something to
remember our trip.
I wanna look real cute.
You there! Sit down!
Don't leave your seats
unless it's very important!
We told Mio that, but
she was wanted a picture!
What are you talking about?
Get back to your seats
this instant.
[Ritsu] We want you in it, too!
[Yui] Come on and join us!
No! I'm not to joining you!
You girls are just unbelievable!
Don't let it get to you,
we're just getting started.
[Yui] But you should wrap the
seaweed around the rice first!
The seaweed tastes
a lot better when it's soft!
That's why you're still
such a little girl, Yui.
With seaweed, you wrap it around
the fillings right before you
eat it,
and that lets you savor the
aroma and the crispy texture!
Yui! It's Mt. Fuji!
Where?!
[Yui] I dropped my snacks!
Huh? Are you two, grade
schoolers?
Ow!
(Ritsu in awe)
Pretty!
Oh wow! It's so big!
[Ritsu] Clouds are
drifting past it!
[Yui] They're moving so fast!
[Mio] Oh, good grief...
You mean, you're not in
the same group as us?
[Nodoka] I'm afraid not,
it's four girls to a group.
And the Light Music Club
should all be together.
It's going to be a lot of work,
but try to keep Yui
out of trouble.
Mio! Mio! Take a picture!
And get Mt. Fuji
in the background!
It's not just Yui, I have
to keep Ritsu in line, too!
I feel like someone is
staring at me...
[Speaker] Kyoto... Kyoto...
Make sure you have all your
belonging as you leave the
train.
We're finally here!
We made it to Kyoto, Ri-chan!
I forget, where do we go first?
[Tsumugi] It says that from
Kyoto Station, we're suppose to
board a bus to-
Let us sally forth!
Sally forth?
Yeah! Right? We're in
the ancient capital of Kyoto,
so let's play a game where
we talk all old-timey!
[Yui] Game huh?
[Ritsu] Verily!
Alright, I want all the team
leaders to make sure that your
team is accounted for.
Why is she making us all sit
down here? I mean take our rest
upon ye floor.
It's just so she can take roll,
there's almost always one or two
students missing at this point
in the trip.
We don't want to cause
any trouble for people around
us,
so walk in single file, okay?
Is she...asleep?
It's because she overate.
Sometimes she is such a ditz.
[Yui] Ri-chan, what's that?!
It looks like a giant daikon
radish!
[Yui] There's one over here,
too!
[Ritsu] That's so goofy!
Hey! Hurry up and get on the
bus!
Gotta take a load off!
I'm tired
You're just sleepy from eating
so much.
I think I'll eat these next!
Give it a rest, will ya?
[Yui] Ri-chan! Hurry up!
This way!
I see it! I see it!
Pretty!
[Mio] That's amazing... It's so
shiny!
[Yui] I've never seen anything
like it.
Is it really made of gold?
I mean, made-y of golde?
[Ritsu] It sure is!
I mean, verily and forsooth!
But thinkth not of stealing, um,
absconding with some, er,
trifling amount of yon gold!
A cop, er officer of ye lawe
will arrest, thee forthwith!
That is...
Um. Verily.
She's finally tired of it.
The original Kinkaku-ji was laid
to waste by fire in the year
1950,
and what stands before
thine eyes is newly constructed.
The pavilion once resides the
reliquary
the enshrined bones of
the Buddha contained is known
by,
all as Kinkaku-ji,
the Golden Pavilion Temple.
However, Deer Garden Temple
is its true monicure.
(Ritsu sobbing)
[Yui] Oh look, they have matcha
tea here!
Now that's the really bitter
kind of tea isn't it?
[Ritsu] Yeah but it comes with
sweets! You wanna try a cup?
How is that any different from
what we do after school every
day?
So what if it isn't?
Come on let's try it!
Well down the hatch, I suppose!
From what I've been told, when
you drink matcha in a tea
ceremony or whatnot,
you always eat the sweet first,
and then you drink the tea.
Apparently, doing that enhances
the bitterness of the matcha.
Hey don't give me that.
You know studying a little
refined etiquette like that,
would probably do you a lot of
good.
She's right. You eat like
a glutton, Ri-chan.
You're quite uncouth, and
unrefined.
You're one to talk!
[Yui] "Kitano Tenmangu"?
[Ritsu] Hey is this place
famous or something?
[Yui] I don't know. Beats me.
[Ritsu] It's not like we don't
have lots of Shinto shrines
around our school.
I bet there's a big Buddha
statue here!
[Ritsu] That's a temple.
This shrine's god is well-known
as a patron of knowledge and
learning.
He's famous among students
who are taking college exams.
Oh...
Now there are cow statues
scattered all around the shrine.
They say that if you pet
a cow's head like this,
it can actually makes you a bit
smarter.
[Both] That's a good little moo
cow!
[Both] Who's a good cow?
[Yui] I'm rubbing you,
so you better make me smart!
[Both] You like it here, don't
cha?
I wonder if they'll
be struck down for this?
Stop that!
[Sawako] I can't believe you!
[Sawako] Are you nuts!?
[Nodoka] Thought so.
Ri-chan look! Ema horse prayers!
Ema, huh?
Okay, Yui! This'll make for some
good memories! Let's go write
something!
Mm yeah, let's go send our
wishes to the god of this place!
Right! Ema! Ema!
Moo! Moo!
They'll get denied.
[Sawako] Excuse me, I'd...uh...
like one of these marriage
charms, please.
That will be 6 dollars please.
Here you are.
[Yui] Hey, god! Mighty Tenjin!
[Tsumugi] Please hear us!
[Yui] Please grant our wishes!
[Ritsu] Please grant the tender
wishes of us maidens!
(cow bell rings)
[Ritsu] Think they'll come true?
[Yui] I hope so, Ri-chan!
[Tsumugi] Please grant them!
[Ritsu] Oops! We forgot
to make a donation!
[Yui] What?! You mean
we have to do it again!?
[Sawako] What is the matter with
you girls?! Are you doing this
on purpose?!
[Ritsu] Sawa-chan,
you've got it all wrong!
[Tsumugi] We were simply writing
down our wishes on prayer
plaques.
[Yui] Yeah Sawa-chan! To remind
ourselves what our dreams are.
[Sawako] Don't give me any of
your lame excuses! Get over
here!
I'm exhausted!
Me too. I was in a cold sweat
back there.
[Ritsu] Yui, make sure
you get changed first.
[Yui] Aw, I don't wanna...
[Ritsu] Hey, don't give me
any of your lip, young lady!
[Yui] Oh, you wanna fight, huh?
You know what,
we still have a bit of time,
so why don't we make ourselves
some tea?
We should've brought some games
or something that we could play
with.
Hey I have some cards.
Really? In that case,
why don't we play this?
It's called the Life Guessing
Game!
Yeah! That's the one where you
do whatever you have to become a
celebrity!
I think we should have
some snacks while we're playing!
Agreed!
But we'll be eating dinner
in a little while!
Don't worry about it!
[Ritsu] We'll have room for
dinner, too.
Well you better clean your
plates.
You mean you guys are full
already? Wow, what a waste.
We're just taking... a little
break.
Yeah we'll finish...everything.
You know I've always thought
that you have such lovely hair.
I do?
Well thank you. But it is a pain
when it gets dry in the winter.
Your's is really nice, too.
Do you have a perm, Mugi?
[Tsumugi] Not at all,
it's naturally frizzy.
Maybe I should grow my hair out,
too.
I wonder if it would make me
look more feminine...
Hey, what's up with you?
You're laughing!
[Ritsu] What're you picturing?!
[Yui] Bangs Monster!
Do you want to grow taller, too?
I'll be tall one day, and then
you're going to be really sorry!
Okay, I'm turning off the light.
Ready! I've got the alarm clock
set!
We have an early day tomorrow.
Teacher! Miss Kotobuki did it!
Mugi! What are you-
You want to have a pillow fight?
You're on!
How about a little less talking
and a lot more fighting, little
lady!
Oh yeah? Well feel the wrath
of my mighty pitch!
You gotta try harder than-
What a heavy pitch...
You will pay!
(pretend snoring)
Now go to sleep!
Wow, that was a close call!
What?!
Mugi! Our glorious battle
is not yet finished!
Well bring it on!
(girls pillow fighting)
Okay, lights out.
Sure. Good night guys.
[Tsumugi] Good night!
[Ritsu] Honor has been
satisfied!
[Yui] Can you turn off the night
light?
[Tsumugi] Skull...
(Tsumugi and Yui giggle)
[Tsumugi] Lycopene...
[Ritsu] Lyco ping!
(Yui giggles)
(Tsumugi giggles and snorts)
[Ritsu] Mugi snorted!
(Yui and Tsumugi giggle harder)
(Yui giggles then
starts coughing)
[Yui] K-ON!
[Sawako] All right now,
is everyone assembled?
Today is your independent day.
It's very important that
each team, sticks to their
planned routes.
And if anything happens,
call me on my cell phone.
[Yui] Anyway, that store was
having a big sale on snacks!
So that's why you had so many of
them crammed into your bag.
[Yui] Yeah that's right!
Get back here, you two!
Let's see now... Our team is
suppose to go up to Mt. Arashi
this morning.
[Tsumugi] Hey why don't we
all take a taxi there, then?
Good idea. That will save us
a lot of time, and it should be-
Huh? Where's Yui and Ritsu?
Right! This is our first stop!
We've come all the way to Kyoto,
and you're looking at a music
store?!
Get a move on! We're going!
You're so mean!
You'll have time to look
after we come back!
We just wanted a minute!
Come now or we'll just leave you
behind.
Hey, they have lefty models
on display here!
(shocked)
So this is Mt. Arashi, huh?
[Yui] Wow! Look at all
the cute shops!
[Ritsu] And there's
lots of people, too!
Okay, we'll start with
the Togetsu Bridge, and-
[Ritsu] Awesome! Look!
It says right here that
there's a monkey park!
[Yui] Really?! Monkeys?!
They have monkeys here?!
[Mio] We've come all the way to
Kyoto,
and you want to go look
at a bunch of monkeys?!
[Mio] Yui! Ritsu!
[Ritsu] Yahoo, we're here!
The top of the mountain!
Oh! What a view!
Wow! All of that is Kyoto?!
I wasn't expecting such a
terrific view.
Hey Mio, it looks like they have
it set up
so you can feed the monkeys
over in that rest area.
There's nothing to be afraid
of, Mugi-chan! Look!
See?
I did it!
[Yui] See?
[Tsumugi] Yes.
It wasn't frightening at all!
[Yui] Boy that ways fun. We sure
got our monkey's worth, huh?
[Ritsu] That was fun!
Look, they have souvenirs!
Wow! You're right!
Those are so cute!
[Yui] That reminds me, we have
to buy something for Azu-nyan!
[Mio] That's right.
She had to stay behind at
school.
In that case, shouldn't we get
her something that shouts
"Kyoto"?
Something that shouts "Kyoto"?
[Yui] This, maybe?
[Tsumugi] How about this?
No, way! Get this!
No, this.
[Yui] Gosh, we saw so much!
[Mio] I wish we'd seen
more famous spots, though.
[Ritsu] Man, I'm so glad that I
had a whole bunch of money in my
wallet today,
check it out look at
all this stuff I bought!
Yeah me, too!
Why did I have
so much money, anyway?
To buy souvenirs for
your families, remember?
You really forgot about that?
[Mio] Well, it's about time.
Let's head back to the hotel.
[Tsumugi] Why don't
we take the train back?
[Mio] Good idea.
Alright then! The station
is this way! Follow me!
[Ritsu] Oops.
Ritsu, are we lost?
We're not lost.
You were looking at
the map the whole time!
I'm double-checking it
right now.
(Yui laughing)
Cut it out! Cut it out!
Stop it! That really tickles!
[Yui] Okay! Sit there!
Shake hands!
Incredible.
Um, forsooth, perhaps ye
coulde help us?
[Woman] Wha?
How dost we get-ith to yon
train station from hence,
milady?
[Woman] Oh, the station?
Go straight that way for
a few blocks,
and then turn right when
the street dead ends.
[Ritsu] Verily? Many thanks!
She understood!
Congrats, Ri-chan!
Well? Were you able to
get directions?
Oh yeah, you bet!
This way guys! Follow me!
[Ritsu] We're lost.
How could this have happened?
It would simplify things
if we knew where we were...
Oh, right!
Azu-nyan? Listen we managed to
get ourselves hopelessly lost.
How is calling Azusa
suppose to help us?!
You're right!
(hang up)
Look! Yui's over there.
Yui! Mio!
[Yui] Nodoka-chan!
Thank goodness we're saved!
Hey, do you guys know
where the train station is?
[Mio] So you guys are lost, too?
[Nodoka] Yes, but
that way is north,
so this should be
the right street,
don't you think?
[Mio] Probably.
If we stick with Nodoka-chan,
we'll be fine.
[Mio] We turn left here, right?
[Nodoka] I think so.
Okay, if we just follow
this road then we should be...
[Ritsu] We're right back
where we started.
That's so strange.
Nodoka...
[Nodoka] Hang on,
let me check my map again.
Aw, skull.
(Mio laughing)
Skull.
Mio?
(laughing)
I'm glad we made it back
in time for dinner!
Now listen, don't you ever
worry me like that again!
I'm sorry. Milady.
(quiet chuckling to laughter)
Yon rice, madam?
I am lady Akiyama,
on ye bass guitar!
[Mio] I can't stop! (laughing)
[Sawako] Hey what are you
two doing out here?
It's late, so go back
to your room.
[Student 1] Yes, ma'am.
[Student 2] Alright we will.
[Student 2] Good night,
Sawa-chan.
Sawa--
I think we can afford
to relax now.
Tomorrow's just the train home.
True. But there's still one
more night to get through.
[Mio] Okay, I'm turning off
the light.
Today was fun!
Let's go straight to sleep
this time, all right?
[Everyone] All right!
Mio?
This long night of terror has
only just begun, Mio-chan!
Keep it down!
(screaming)
Now you hurry up and
go to sleep!
Who are you?
I'm your teacher!
Even on a big trip like this,
you four don't ever change!
You're ten times scarier
without makeup, Sawa-chan.
What? I didn't quite
catch that, Ritsu.
Would you mind repeating
what you just said to me?
I didn't say anything!
I didn't mean it!
Now everyone, go to sleep!
C'mon, please! Can't we
just chat like friends
like we always do?
Look Yui, I'm suppose
to be your teacher now!
Aw, just for a while!
I have tasty snacks, too!
You're always trying to
snare me with-
It's all your fault that all the
other students are calling me
Sawa-chan now,
and aren't showing me the
respect that I deserve
as a teacher.
You're ruining my image
at the school!
I've worked really hard to
build up my "nice teacher" act-
[Both] We shouldn't
have asked her to join us.
I'm a senior now...
This is our last year as
the Light Music Club, too...
But I really want to keep on
playing with all of them
in a band...
Forever... and ever...
Miss Yamanaka!
(screams)
Don't scare me like that!
Anyway, I'd already been
given a copy of that book!
So I ended up giving it
to my little-
Yui! Mt. Fuji!
[Yui] Where? Where?
I want to see, too!
Oh I dropped them...
Mio-chan, you're just
as bad as me!
Yeah you're right!
(laughter)
(closing song, "Listen!!")
[Ui] Did you make it?
Since you haven't called me,
I'm just going to assume
that you were able to
make it on time.
Are you at the station by now?
Um, pardon us...