[Azusa] I hope this letter finds
you well in spite of the
lingering summer heat.
Summer vacation is halfway over.
How have all of you been
since we last saw each other?
(radio chatter)
[Azusa] Hmm, seems
a little stiff and formal.
[Azusa] Ton-chan is
doing well again today.
In addition to his usual five
food pellets, he also ate a
slice of cucumber-
No, they don't really need to
know the details of Ton-chan's
diet...
How are your studies going?
Well, I hope.
No, there's at least one whose
studies obviously won't be going
very well.
(phone ringing)
It's from Yui-senpai!
"Azu-nyan, how are you?"
"Thanks a lot for looking after
Ton-chan over summer vacation!"
"Right now, we're studying
really hard in the library!"
Yui-senpai beat me to it!
She's actually studying!
I guess everyone really
is busy with their studies...
And Mugi-senpai is off in
Finland.
Please work hard to make sure
your last high school summer
isn't filled with regrets.
I'm so bored...
Oh forget this! I'm gonna go
have fun!
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
Hurry!
Wait for me!
Whoa it's so huge!
[Azusa] Isn't it? My mom said
I should bring you guys a gift.
Thank you very much!
Where's Yui-senpai?
After she came home from the
library,
she ate lunch the lunch I made
for her and went back to her
studies.
Wow, she really works hard
when she applies herself.
(Yui playing the guitar)
Or maybe not.
I wonder if she's decided to
take a break?
Anyway, I'll bring her some
of this watermelon.
[Azusa] You're not slicing it?
Nope. Her dream has always been
to,
take a big watermelon
that's been cut in half like
this,
and eat then eat through the
seedless area in the middle with
a spoon.
[Ui] Hey, Sis! Azusa-chan
brought over a watermelon for
us!
I'll leave it out here for you!
I just left it outside her door!
(upbeat tempo)
She changed her tempo?
Yeah she sounds like she's
feeling happy.
Does that mean she's eating
while playing the guitar?
Yeah, it was just like this
at lunch time, too.
At lunch time?
You had chilled soba noodles?
[Ui] Yeah. But you get the
summer doldrums if you only eat
noodles,
so I made some tempura too.
Tempura...
Watermelon...
[Azusa] Senpai don't eat it!
[Ui] What's wrong?
Yui-senpai!
(sad tempo)
Oh my goodness...
It was a dream?
(doorbell rings)
[Azusa] Coming!
Good afternoon!
Hi Ui, Come in!
Sorry, I had sorta conked out
for a minutes.
Who are you?
You came to my house,
so you know who I am!
Sorry, for a second
I didn't recognize you.
Sheesh...
You look sleepy.
I was watching TV last night,
and before I knew it,
it was really late.
So I've been walking around the
house,
pretty much half-asleep all day
today.
You get lazy over vacation
without even realizing it.
So, what do you want to do
today?
Why don't we invite Jun-chan
along and go hang out?
Didn't she say that her Jazz
Club
was gonna have practice
everyday over summer vacation?
In that case, why don't
we take her a care package?
I don't think anyone's in there.
I guess the Jazz Club
takes Obon day off, too.
Though I'm not really surprised.
Oh, hey. Since we're here and
all,
why don't we go eat in
the Light Music Club room?
Oh can we?
Yeah, let's go do it!
We'll need a key to get in,
though.
I wonder if any teachers are
here.
Excuse us, ma'am.
Oh. Who are you?
You were there with at Natsu
Fest when I got this way!
Relax, I was joking.
So, what brings you here?
We came to deliver a care
package to the Jazz Club, but no
one was there.
Yeah, it's just because
of the Obon holiday.
The other teachers are all away
visiting their families or on
trips and such,
so I'm here holding down the
fort.
It's letting me get a lot
of extra work done.
Oh, really it is?
So anyway, we came to see if
we could borrow the key to our
club room.
[Ui] Be my guest.
But I didn't get you anything...
Don't mention it, you always
take good care of my sister.
Oh not at all, I'm in their debt
for always imposing on them
and slacking off in the club
room.
[Ui] So has my sister
been studying lately?
[Azusa] What a great sister!
[Students] A-E-I-U-E-O-A-O.
[Students] Ka-Ke-Ki-Ku-
Ke-Ko-Ka-Ko.
[Students] Sa-Se-Shi-Su-
Se-So-Sa-So.
[Azusa] Have you gotten
any texts from Jun-chan?
Not yet.
I wonder what's keeping her?
Maybe she's already gone
somewhere else to hang out for
the day.
Would you rather have peach or
plum?
[Azusa] Plum.
Here you go.
Thanks.
You know it's kinda warm in here
today...
Yeah.
[Ui] It's so quiet...
If we had other members, maybe
I'd be practicing like them
right now...
Hey! Hey! Wanna go out and catch
a movie?
That might be fun. Maybe we
could go see a summer horror
movie.
Mio-senpai?
(evil laughter)
I get it, she's training
herself to overcome her fears
by going all by herself
to see horror movies.
It's already scary right now...
I wonder if she's going to be
able to handle this?
(heavy breathing)
(screaming)
That's amazing. Has her
training paid off?
But if this film stays true
to the horror movie formula,
the next scene is probably
gonna get extra scary!
(intense screaming)
(evil laughter)
No way! She didn't even flinch
at that scary scene!
Running down the list of
possibilities, this either
isn't Mio,
or she's passed out!
Oh no! I knew it!
I thought something was weird.
(phone ringing)
Mio-senpai's cell phone?
But they said to turn off our
phones off during the movie...
Senpai!
(phone vibrating)
A dream? Oh?
[Azusa] Ui, your cell.
Sorry, I fell asleep.
Hey, it's from Jun-chan look!
Like we thought, she had the day
off.
She says she went to visit her
grandparents out in the country.
It's kinda lonely without
Jun-chan around.
"When you get back,
let's have lots and lots of fun.
Okay?"
[Ui] You said you wanted
to see this one, right?
[Azusa] Nah, let's just skip the
horror movie and see this one
instead.
Okay, but there's a pretty long
wait until the next time they
show it.
Well let's go kill some time
somewhere, then. Okay?
That reminds me, I didn't send
out my late-summer greetings
texts yet.
How about postcards?
But I spent way too much at
Natsu Fest,
so money is tight for
the rest of the month.
[Azusa] Maybe I should've gotten
a summer job after all.
Plus, once Jun-chan gets back,
we have to go out and stuff.
How about this job?
The pay is a little low, isn't
it?
How about this?
$150 per day sounds
a little bit fishy to me.
Let's see... How about that?
[Azusa] Lottery assistants?
[Ui] Let's go check it out!
7th Prize, a pack of tissues!
Thank you very much for playing
today!
All that's left now is 1st
Prize, the trip to Finland,
and 7th Prize, a pack of
tissues.
Which means that there's only
one red ball and one gold ball
left in here.
[Tsumugi] I'd like to play!
[Azusa] Mugi-senpai?
I thought you were in Finland.
Yes, but I had the overwhelming
urge to play the shopping arcade
lottery,
so I came back home a day early.
I've always dreamed of spinning
this rattling contraption around
and around and winning some
tissues!
Oh please God, if you're
listening,
please grant her wish
of winning a packet of tissues!
And...!
7th Prize, a big packet of
tissues!
[Tsumugi] Hooray!
[Azusa] Good for her.
But that means that all that's
left in here now
is the grand prize trip to
Finland.
Why don't you give it a whirl,
Azusa-chan?
I have an extra ticket you can
use.
[Azusa] All right.
And...!
I won!
We have a winner!
[Azusa] Hey, wait a minute!
What if this is just another
dream?
Ui, Mugi-senpai, please
pinch my cheeks right away!
[Ui] Is this okay?
I knew it!
[Tsumugi and Ui] One, two!
It doesn't hurt!
So what if it's only a dream?
You can go to Finland anyway!
Congratulations on winning,
Azusa-chan!
Congratulations!
...Congratulations...
ations... tions...
[Kid] Teto! Teto!
I woke up before
I went on the trip!
[Movie] Teto! I'll never
leave you again!
[Azusa] And not only that,
I slept through the movie!
K-ON!
Where is she?!
She'll be here any minute.
[Azusa] Sorry! It took
a while to get ready.
Who are you?
I knew you were gonna say that!
[Jun] How come your skin
is so tan now?
[Azusa] I guess I just burn
right away when I go
outside in the sun.
[Jun] Outside?
[Azusa] Oh, the Light Music Club
went to Natsu Fest.
Natsu Fest?!
How did you swing that?
Maybe you should've joined
the Light Music Club, Jun-chan.
I-I'm not jealous of you
or anything!
They went to the beach for
their training camps
the last two years.
My sister said they go to
a summer house with
a recording studio!
A summer house? With a studio?
Want to join up, Jun?
I have no regrets!
Jun-chan, your swimsuit is
really cute!
Thanks! I bought
a brand new one this year.
Azusa-chan, are you done
changing yet?
Please don't look at me!
[Jun] Wow, those are
some impressive tan lines.
Wah!
(snickering)
Oh Azusa-chan...
Hey. I've got it!
If you completely cover up,
it'll solve everything!
Cover up?
Yay!
Let's play!
That'll make me stand out even
more.
I'll work on an all-over tan
at the side of the pool,
so you go have fun.
[Jun] Here it comes!
And catch!
That's so cold!
I feel kinda bad about
leaving Azusa.
Hey, let's go over and
check in on her.
Oh my.
Oh wow, we're really high up,
aren't we?
Hey, why don't you go first,
Azusa-chan?
[Ritsu] If you're going to
slide, you'll need this!
It's yours take it!
Ritsu-senpai?
What are you doing way up here?
And what's with the yakisoba?
This is the Yakisoba Slider!
It's all the rage!
Look there. You go down
the water slide like that.
Hey, wait a minute. Isn't
that...
Yui-senpai?
And Mugi-senpai?!
And Mio-senpai?!
[Yui] Darn it!
[Tsumugi] Aw I didn't get
to eat any of it again.
[Mio] Ritsu!
Another order for me!
[Yui] Me, too!
[Tsumugi] And for me!
Go on, Azusa! It's time
for you to slide away!
Wait! I-
Don't push! No one said
anything about yakisoba!
[Ritsu] Here.
Thanks, but I don't want any!
[Ritsu] No can do.
You gotta take it!
Have a nice trip!
(slide screaming)
(gasp)
(panic scream)
Dad, get my swim ring
and toss it over here!
A dream?
[Ui] Azusa-chan!
We bought you some yakisoba!
There was a long line,
so it took a while.
[Jun] Hey, you've got
a nice, even tan now!
It's looking better.
[Jun] Yakisoba always tastes
better when you eat it outside
like this.
[Ui] I know what you mean!
[Azusa] Now that you mention it,
Mugi-senpai was looking
forward to
having yakisoba at Natsu Fest,
but they sold out fast and
she never got to eat any.
Gloating about Natsu Fest again?
When you guys were
in your tent at night,
I bet you spent the whole time
fooling around and making
a ruckus.
That's for sure!
Ritsu-senpai was her usual
hilarious self, and-
[Jun] Fine, I admit it!
I'm jealous!
How can you keep having
training camps like that?!
Well, I guess because we...
I have a summer house
we can use!
Why don't I take you guys there?
We-We don't have many members,
so we have plenty of funds
to go around!
[Jun] Oh. I envy you guys.
[Azusa] I can't tell her
we went for free...
[Jun] You're so lucky
in the Light Music Club.
Mio is gorgeous,
and she's great on the bass.
[Azusa] She is, isn't she?
[Jun] Yui-senpai's
a great guitar player, too.
[Azusa] You think so?
I've got admit,
I've been really surprised,
at how much better she's gotten
lately. It's pretty impressive.
[Jun] Well, that's Ui's sister
for you.
[Azusa] But she can't be
bothered to learn the lingo,
and she can't read sheet music
very well.
She has a long way to go.
[Jun] Oh, I had no idea.
[Jun] That was so much fun!
I hope we can go one more
time before summer ends.
Yeah!
Ui?
Azu-nyan!
It's Yui-senpai.
[Yui] Azu-nyan!
Are you guys just heading
home from the library?
Yeah. And we're on our way over
to the Sakuragaoka
summer festival to unwind a bit.
Sniff! Sniff! Sniff!
Hey, you smell like
a swimming pool, Azu-nyan!
Please don't sniff me.
And it's because
we all just came from the pool.
Hey, you three should come and
hang out with us at the
festival!
Kay?
[Ritsu] Hook me up with
another, Pops!
[Pops] Sure thing.
By the way, Mugi-senpai.
Weren't you suppose to be
in Finland?
Actually, I came back
a little early because
I wanted to come to
the summer festival.
I'm bound and determined
to eat yakisoba this time.
[Mio] Mugi! We found some!
I'll be back!
[Yui] Get yer grilled corn
right here!
Now to eat it,
you gotta go like this!
What are you,
some kind of a rodent?
Here! You have some!
Isn't it terrific?!
It's a little bit charred,
but it tastes totally delicious!
[Yui] You know, the charred
parts are my favorite!
Okay now, people! Next up on
the agenda is mango shaved ice!
[Yui] Watermelon flavor for me!
[Mio] There's no such flavor!
[Jun] Strawberry for me!
[Ui] Me, too!
[Ritsu] Green tea and beans!
[Yui] Oh, you're so traditional!
[Mio] I'll have melon.
[Tsumugi] I'd like the
Blue Hawaii.
[Yui] In that case, I'll go
with the Purple Argentina!
[Mio] Quit making up flavors!
[Azusa] I think I'll have
the strawberry milk.
Look at me! Look at my tongue!
Would you stop that!
Your tongue is a funny color,
too!
[Ui] Sis! Look, they've got
a goldfish scooping booth
over there!
I'm so there! We'll put them
in Ton-chan's tank to
keep him company!
But the goldfish might
be eaten if we do that.
Oh, well I'm sure they'll
be eaten pretty quick!
They'll be like "Crunch!" and
"Gnash!" and "Rip!" and "Tear!"
Cut it out!
[Yui] But Ton-chan's tiny,
so I think they'll be safe.
[Ritsu] Yeah I was kidding,
they'll be just fine.
[Azusa] My life is definitely
more fun...
[Yui] Then let's all go...
[Azusa] ...when I'm with
theseguys.
[Yui] ...catch us some goldfish!
No we can't!
(fireworks go off)
Look, they're launching
fireworks!
What?! Why didn't
they say anything about it?!
[Ritsu] It doesn't look too far
away...
Let's get moving, people!
[Yui] What'cha doing?
[Girls] Yeah!
C'mon let's go, Azu-nyan!
[Ritsu] And we're off!
They're so pretty...
Is this real?
Am I dreaming again?
[Ui] Azusa-chan!
Where's my sister
and the others?
I don't know, we got separated.
Will they be okay?
Oh yeah, I'm sure they'll
be just fine.
You're right.
[Jun] Think we should head home?
[Ui] Sure.
[Azusa] Hey, Jun.
Why not join the Light Music
Club? There's still time.
It's tempting...
I'm in.
Hey, good for you, Azusa-chan!
[Jun] If you don't get any other
new members next year, that is.
I don't even want to
think about that.
But maybe there'll be no point
if all the cool people like
Mio-senpai are gone.
[Azusa] Huh! What did you say?!
[Jun] I'm kidding, I'm kidding!
Today was a lot of fun.
But what if it was all
just another dream?
Ow! No, it's not a dream...
I almost forgot. After this
year is done, I'm going to be
all alone.
Stop that!
Think positive thoughts!
I'll work hard with the others
and knock their socks off at
the student festival!
[Azusa's mother]
Azusa, we're finish this
watermelon without you!
[Azusa] No! Wait for me!
[Yui] I'm home!
Ui!
That's pretty weird,
did I get home before she did?
Leftovers from lunch detected!
Lucky!
Down the hatch!
(phone rings)
Yui here, hey Azu-nyan?
So what's up with you?
You sent me what? A letter?
A postcard? No, I haven't seen
one.
Oh, maybe this is it.
"Shaved ice and tempura
don't go well together,"
"so whatever you do,
do not eat them together"
(stunned silence)
Azu-nyan? What do I do?
(closing song, "Listen!!")
Looks like there's an extra
piece of cake.
It'll be kind of hard
to divide this into fifths.
[Tsumugi] Rock-paper-scissors?
Come on, no way, I'm terrible
at that stupid game!
[Yui] Alright, then let's settle
it the old fashioned way!
Very well, I'll take you on.
Nodoka-chan...you...