[Tsumugi] Finland this year
is gonna be really fun...
Huh?
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
[Sawako] The first thing in
the morning is homeroom.
Which means that I'm teaching
back-to-back classes from
first to third period.
Over lunch break, I took a
student home who had collapsed
from anemia.
And in fifth period,
I patrolled the campus,
looking for students
who were skipping class.
After school, I've been
supervising the Brass Band
Club's practices,
because they have a competition
soon.
[Yui] Ah, that's why
you're soaking your feet.
Yep.
Who can blame you,
you've been up on your feet all
day.
Have you tried orthopedic
sandals?
No, I can't. Even the freshmen
think of me as an elegant,
ladylike teacher.
Hmm...
Have you ever thought about
coming clean about your Light
Music Club past?
You know, you just say
"I used to be like this!"
Never! Gimme that!
You just don't know what it's
like.
In education, showing the
slightest weakness can lead to
catastrophe.
If they ever learned of my
past...
Um, you're interrupting, please
stop it.
Up yours!
You used to be exactly like this
back when you were in high
school.
Ain't that right?
(laughter)
...that's what would happen!
I think you're probably blowing
it out of proportion.
(phone vibrating)
Oh?
Excuse me for just a second.
You're taking the call?
[Sawako] Hello?
Guh!
Just what the heck are you
thinking, calling me here like
this?!
Hmm...
Um, I'll be right back, okay?
Seems pretty fishy...
Oh yeah, she was all: "Just what
the heck are you thinking,
calling me like this?!"
(laughing)
Oh! That reminds me!
[Mio] That happened this
morning?
This morning, she's dropped off
at school and has an argument
with the driver
and then she's surprised
by a sudden phone call.
The normal conclusion would
be that the mystery caller is...
No way!
Her mother?
[Azusa] You shouldn't worry
about this, Yui-senpai.
(dejected)
Why not?!
Because this isn't kids' stuff
we're talking about.
Oh look, speak of the devil.
[Yui] Sawa-chan spotted!
[Ritsu] Yeah, and take a look
at that suspicious behavior!
This isn't the usual way
that she goes home afterschool.
Oh! Mio-chan, you sound like a
detective!
Come on! Let's follow her!
Ah...
Wait! Are you sure this a good
idea? If she spots us-
Look she's turned left!
Come on, let's hurry!
Mugi-senpai is into this
more than anyone else!
[Ritsu] Okay... Target acquired!
Yui, you're to maintain watch,
focusing on the right.
Mugi, you exercise the utmost
caution, so that Sawa-chan
doesn't spot you.
[Yui & Tsumugi] Roger that!
This is a stakeout?
[Yui] Oh, right! You, too,
Mio-chan!
You came ready!
Looks like something in
the area has spooked her!
You too!?
[Yui] You're right...
[Azusa] You'd think she really
has-
[Tsumugi] But wait, doesn't
she always complain about
how lonely she is because she's
single?
[Mio] Maybe teachers have to
keep certain parts of their
lives secret.
Huh?
Certain parts?
No, not me! I'm not hiding
anything!
You know, come to think of it,
you are a hottie, Mio.
I wouldn't be surprised at all
if boys liked you just as much
or more than girls do.
Neither would I.
[Mio] How did we get on this
topic?!
Mio-chan, congratulations!
[Mio] What are you doing!?
Don't run with that joke!
Hm...
[Mio] Don't stare at me!
Look, I'm not interested
in that kind of stuff!
You could say that the Light
Music Club is my boyfriend right
now.
Oh... (clapping)
[Ritsu] Ow!
[Ritsu] Why was I the only one?
[Norimi] Heh. Sorry I'm late.
Didn't I tell you never to call
me during school hours like you
did?
I'm really sorry!
Yeah well...
Isn't that a girl?
Oh. Darn.
It's a woman...
Well, you don't need
to read too much into it.
(snapshots)
Why did we follow them in here?
It's like we're in a soap opera!
Today is the day you get your
comeuppance, you scheming vixen!
They'll hear you!
Pardon me.
[Girls] (gasps) Y-Yes?
Party of five, ladies?
[Girls] We, uh...okay!
Um, mind if we sit over here?
We're still in our school
uniforms...
Mugi, keep your head down.
Oh, alright.
Come on, Azu-nyan, scoot over!
Why don't you sit on the other
side, huh?
[Yui] Aw, that's so mean!
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing really.
That was close...
[Ritsu] Yui, stay down there.
I'll give you these.
I don't wanna...
Hey... Watch it! Don't just
force your way in like that!
You're squishing me!
Would the both of you please be
quiet!
You mean they're holding the
party THERE?
[Norimi] That's right.
Oh hey, isn't that-
Excuse me, girls. May I take
your order?
Uh... Five black teas, please.
We have a lovely self-service
area over there.
[Norimi] Come on,
don't be like that.
[Ritsu] Not good.
Um... I'll have this chocolate
cake, then.
Hey, don't order just for
yourself!
We need something.
In that case, I'm going to have
the pumpkin custard a la mode.
They serve amazing things like
that here?!
I think I'll have the cream
anmitsu.
That's what I wanted!
You CAN order the same thing,
you know.
That'd be a waste!
They have so much good stuff
here.
Um... I-I guess what I'll have
is...
Um... I guess I'll have...
(gasps)
T-This! This please...
We've completely lost sight
of our initial objective.
We're paying separately,
and not dutch, you got that?
What? We are?
Obviously.
Well, then in that case...
Will you please make up your
mind. We're gonna be spotted.
(gasps)
Geh!
You've been acting strange
since we got here.
It's nothing.
Liar. You keep looking behind
me.
Shh! Shh!
Please, think about it
one more time, all right?
Talk about pushy...
It cost me $14.80 with tax...
There goes my allowance.
You didn't actually need
to buy it, you know.
I didn't want to miss out
on all the good stuff!
You know we never did figure out
who the woman with Sawa-chan
was.
That's true.
[Yui] I recognize her.
Huh?
Yui, you know her?
Yeah, oh course.
She was with Sawa-chan in all of
those old pictures we found
remember?
Pictures?
Huh...
She's Death Devil's-
Name is Christina!
(screaming)
Sorry. Was I a bit overboard?
Oh no, she's always been like
this.
Really?
Let me guess, you're
the Light Music Club, aren't
you?
Are you another master
detective?!
We're wearing our uniforms and
carrying guitars, it's not a
huge stretch.
[Norimi] I need to talk to you
about something as a Light Music
Club alumnus.
Who's president?
Eh...
(nervous)
[Ritsu] Mio is.
[Azusa] Don't abandon your post.
Wow, this is one hell of
an axe you've got here.
Oh thanks...
This really takes me back.
(strumming)
She's good!
Maybe even better than Miss
Yamanaka!
Really? Thanks a lot.
Sawako and I used to have
technique competitions every
day.
Oh wow you did, really?
Oh. Don't be shy, go ahead
and order something.
Pops, another round
of juices for the girls.
[Pops] Sure thing, Nori-chan.
Nori-chan?
[Norimi] Sorry about that.
My name is Norimi.
(gasps) Oh my goodness! You mean
you're not a foreigner of some
kind?!
Or course she isn't.
But her name...
(chuckling)
I'm sorry. I should have
introduced myself sooner.
By the way, if there's anything
else that you girls would like
to eat,
just say the word, okay?
[Yui and Ritsu] She seems really
nice!
Then I would like the ganmodoki,
please!
[Pops] One ganmo coming up.
Oh do you like those?
I don't know, I've never tried
it before.
Its name makes it sound
just amazing, Ganmodoki.
You really think so?
So, what did you want to talk to
us about?
Well, it's nothing major
or anything like that.
Oh?
[Norimi] The thing is,
Sawako is set to get married.
(the girls scream)
(strumming)
Don't worry. That was a just
joke.
(sighs)
You call that a joke?!
An old classmate of ours from
the Light Music Club is getting
married,
and she says that she wants
the old band to play at the
reception.
But Sawako is the only one
who isn't on board with it.
Yeah, she treats her Light Music
Club past as a dark secret.
[Mio] Yeah.
[Pops] One ganmodoki.
It's more mundane
than I expected.
Well did you have pictured
in your head?
[Tsumugi] Something spiny,
I guess.
[Azusa] Spiny?
[Yui] She seems so cool...
Ah. I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to keep it so long. Here.
Kay.
(strumming)
(thinking)
[Norimi] Sorry, did I mess
something up?
Nuh-uh.
No, everything's fine.
(playing guitar)
[Sawako] K-ON!
[Sawako] English class today
will be independent study.
Work quietly.
Miss Akiyama.
It's from Miss Kotobuki.
Thank you.
"Mio-chan, have you
thought of anything?"
[Mio] "I've been thinking
about it a lot,
but if the old club members
couldn't convince her,
I don't see how we're going
to be able to do it."
[Mio] Thanks.
Here.
Thanks a lot.
[Tsumugi] "Apparently
other teachers and members,
of the Newspaper Club
are coming to the reception."
[Mio] "Maybe we could disguise
her with makeup or something?"
[Tsumugi] "But considering the
outcome if she's found out,
perhaps she shouldn't."
[Mio] "Good point."
[Mio] "What do you think, Yui?"
[Yui] "Mio-chan,
your handwriting's so cute!"
[Mio] "How about you, Ritsu?
You're our president."
(chuckling)
[Mio] "Be serious!"
(stifling giggles)
(snorting and laughing)
[Sawako] Miss Akiyama.
Wah! Um...
Did you draw this picture?
No!
[Mio] You traitor!
[Ritsu] "I am an ink pen."
[Tsumugi] It was me.
Miss Kotobuki?
Mugi?
I was the one who sent
the first note and started all
this.
So Mio-chan isn't the one
to blame for any of it.
Oh, but still, she had-
The hallway! May I stand out
there as punishment?
Wha?
That's really not-
I want to stand outside!
So this is what it's
like to stand out here!
Twelve years after starting my
school career, my dream has
finally come true.
I can graduate with
no unfinished business.
What kind of dreams do you
have?!
I did it! Ri-chan, look, I
reached it!
Yui seems to be having a grand
old time.
To get back on topic,
what do you think we should do?
Don't you people remember what
Norimi told us about Sawa-chan
last night?
[Ritsu] Of course.
[Yui] I forget, what'd she say?
Get with it, Yui...
[Norimi] Fine, I'll let you guys
talk Sawako into playing.
But you know Sawa-chan can
be really stubborn, sometimes.
So what? You throwing
in the towel already?
Well, if you guys can't
talk her into it then...
What will you do?
Let's just say that I have some
special training for you.
(nervous)
Wait, that happened?
You don't remember?!
I wonder what "special training"
means.
When a club alumnus says
something like that,
it tends to be some
kind of harsh practice.
That's true, but we
aren't an athletic club.
No, but with the
Light Music Club, it might be...
All right girls, you're going to
play until I can hear the music!
(gasps) But we don't have any of
our-
They say music comes
from the soul, don't they?
Put your hearts into it, and you
should be able to make music
without instruments!
Get started!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I'm not hearing anything!
We're so sorry!
...like that.
Seriously?!
Come on, don't joke around about
that.
Oh my...
It was a joke?
Fine, let's all talk to her
right after school is finished.
(door opens)
You going to stand out here all
day?
Get back to your
independent study, alright?
[Girls] Okay!
[Ritsu] Pardon us.
Is Miss Yamanaka here-
Thank you, Miss Yamanaka!
We don't want to bother the
other teachers, so let's keep it
down, okay?
[Yui] Wow, Sawa-chan sure is
popular, huh?
Yeah but it kinda makes
it hard to ask her.
[Norimi] I see.
[Mio] We're sorry.
[Norimi] So, Sawako is
just as popular now.
[Mio] Yes.
[Ritsu] So, um, what's this
"special training" you
mentioned?
[Norimi] Oh, that? I was just
kidding.
[Norimi] No I wasn't.
[Norimi] I just want
your help with something.
This is really hard...
Hey big sis, you still haven't
taken your bath yet?
No, I'll take it in a little
while.
But you'll oversleep again.
You know, Ui.
Adults are pretty amazing,
aren't they?
I guess. Why do you ask?
When I'm grown up and an adult,
will I be all mature, too?
Big sis, do you want some juice?
Today, I shall have tea.
Coming right up.
[Sawako] Congratulations.
Oh, Sawako!
Good to see you again!
I'm so sorry that I can't play
for you.
Now that I'm a teacher,
I have to be careful what I do.
It's all right.
We can't wait for the show!
[Yui] Geeta!
[Mio] Quit crying!
It only makes you look scarier!
[Tsumugi] Actually,
I rather like it on you.
[Azusa] You overdid it,
Mugi-senpai!
[Norimi] Oh, and Miss President?
I want you to use this to
breathe fire, okay?
[Ritsu] Um... Thanks, but NO
WAY!
[Announcer] And now ladies and
gentlemen,
it's time for a special
performance by Death Devil,
a band composed of
the bride's high school friends.
Furthermore, today's performance
will feature a special lineup.
[Sawako] Hey! What do
those girls think they're-
Yui-chan, what did you do to
your guitar?
What are you doing with them?
Buckle up, you bastards,
tonight we're gonna rock!
[Yui] I missed a note!
[Azusa] Yui-chan, what are you
doing?
[Yui] I'm sorry, let's take it
again from the top!
With a name like "Death Devil,"
I was worried what kind of
band they'd be,
but they're awfully cute.
C-Cute?!
You can do it, Death Devil!
We're all rooting for you!
Rooting for them?!
[Crowd] Death Devil!
Death Devil!
This is all wrong...
This isn't what Death Devil
is about.
There has to be a
brutal clashing of souls.
That's when Death Devil
is at its best.
No, I mustn't!
I'm a teacher now...
I left that part of me
long ago in the past!
And it would be an insult
to these people who are
trying so hard.
[Yui] Gosh, I'm so sorry!
I'm all thumbs!
[Sawako] This is wrong.
Death Devil is...
The Death Devil that I pursued
all those years is...
Death Devil!
MY DEATH DEVIL IS!
What happened?
Where's the lights?
They'll come back.
I know.
Sawa-chan!
It's Sawako!
[Norimi] Here it comes!
[Sawako] Death Devil
ain't this half-assed,
watery crap these kiddies
were trying to play!
So I'm gonna show you
bastards how it's done!
Okay! Let's do it!
One, two!
Catherine! Yeah!
Okay...
Yeah!
(crowd cheering)
[Sawako] What have I done?!
[The girls]
Look what we made her do!
I'm finished...
The genteel, ladylike image
I've worked so hard to
cultivate...
[The girls]
We're truly ashamed
of ourselves.
It's okay. In the end, it was...
Yeah you're right, it's your
own fault for snapping like you-
I SAID it was my fault already,
didn't I?
[Ritsu] I'm sorry.
(knock on the door)
Come in.
Um...Miss Yamanaka? Is that you?
Huh?
Thank you so much!
I can't believe it! You were so
awesome in that show last night!
We can't wait until
the next time!
I don't get it.
[Yui] Well, I'll be.
It looks like Sawa-chan is
popular no matter what she does.
I'm thinking that maybe a band
has to be way over the top
if anyone's going to
remember them.
Maybe...
[Ritsu] Okay, let's do it!
Slap some makeup on Mio!
[Mio] Don't even think about it!
[Tsumugi] I rather like
the whole idea of it.
[Azusa] You really go
overboard with that stuff!
[Tsumugi] Do I?
[Yui] For mine, I wanna go
way...
(closing song, "Listen!!")
It's so hot...