So what are you going to do
this year?
Hey Jun, are you taking up
candy making or something?
What? Oh boy no.
It's for Valentine's Day.
Oh, right. Well who are
you giving them to?
A senior in Jazz Club.
I thought I might try making
them by hand this year.
Who are you going to
give some to?
Maybe to one of the seniors
in the Light Music Club?
No. I didn't really give
any last year, either.
What? No one at all?
Well I had brought some
to give out, but then...
The Belgian royal family?!
Yes! I just learned that
I've been given access to their,
Royal Warrant certified
chocolates, so I'll bring some.
They were so good I completely
forgot to give them my own.
I hate you right now...
And you?
I made some last year,
but I didn't really
make very many.
I only gave them out to
my sister and the nice
neighbor lady next door.
Oh, bummer.
You know, now that
I think about it,
I've never given them
chocolates, not once.
Something wrong, Azusa-chan?
I-I don't know what
you just said,
but I definitely wasn't thinking
about Valentine's Day!
[Yui and Jun]
Jeez, you are so obvious...
(opening song,
"Utauyo!! MIRACLE")
[Yui] I don't know.
Who? Like owls?... Means birds!
If it says Who, they're
obviously talking about Keith
Moon's band.
Wow? Really?
[Tsumugi] In this instance,
though, it doesn't mean that.
I think this particular "who" is
being used as a relative
pronoun.
It refers back to this clause,
where in the book-
I don't get this...
It's basic stuff.
Hey! Don't worry, Ri-chan!
You've always got your secret
weapon!
Yeah, totally!
[Mio] Secret weapon?
Check it! Leave all your
multiple-choice needs to this
bad boy!
Hexy #7!
THAT'S your weapon?
[Ritsu] Watch your tone!
Based on my careful testing
of all pencils types,
Hexy #7 is clearly the top
choice, with an astonishing 60%
accuracy rate!
[Ritsu] For example,
the answer to this question
is...
Number three!
She's right!
[Ritsu] 'course I am!
With Hexy on our side,
we're going to pass this text
for sure!
[Ritsu] Oh yeah!
[Mio] Just one problem.
This test actually has 9
multiple choice answers for each
question.
[Ritsu and Yui]
Then we fail for sure.
[Mio] Really?
[Ritsu] But if I can't
use Hexy...
[Azusa] Should I give them
chocolates?
Seems kind of embarrassing.
And presenting them formally
just seems weird.
[Tsumugi] Azusa-chan?
[Tsumugi] Something wrong?
Oh. nothing. I'm fine.
Azusa, please don't worry about
us at all, okay? Just keep on
practicing
Yes, go ahead.
[Ritsu] Give us some mood music!
[Yui] Yes!
Well, alright...
(Azusa playing the guitar)
I like it keep playing!
[Azusa] Thank you.
Come on, why don't
we get to studying guys?
Kay!
[Mio] Focus!
[Ritsu and Yui] Sorry!
Unbelievable...
How about we take a quick break?
I'll go put on some tea.
[Ritsu and Yui] Yahoo!
[Ritsu] I can't take it anymore!
I've gotta play my drums for a
bit!
[Yui] Yeah same here!
But I gotta make a quick pit
stop first!
[Tsumugi] Join us for tea,
Azusa-chan!
Okay.
I'm sorry. I kind of feel
like my practicing,
is interrupting all your
studying.
No way, look, you're suppose
to practice in the club room,
we're imposing on you by
studying in it.
And to be honest,
I concentrate a whole lot better
when
there is music playing in the
background.
So go ahead and wail away all
you want!
Are you all right with
milk tea, Azusa-chan?
Yeah, of course.
I'm so sorry, it looks like
I've only got some cookies to
offer.
That's fine. Worry about
studying that's what's most
important right now.
Well, since Valentine's Day is
coming up and all,
I had really hoped to have
some chocolates for everyone.
[Jun] Oh, I see you've decided
to give out chocolates this year
after all?
[Azusa] Yep. It doesn't sound
like
Mugi-senpai will have time to
get chocolates this year.
So I thought it might be kinda
nice, for this one time, to give
them all something.
I'm jealous! They're getting
your handmade chocolate!
I'll give you some, too.
Wow thanks! I'll make extra
for you as well.
Now I'm jealous! You're each
getting handmade chocolates!
Don't worry, you'll get some,
too, Jun.
Oh yeah!
Now with that said...
Zip it! You have to keep your
mouth shut and not tell them
about this!
I mean it!
My lips are sealed.
However, there might be a few
other people in on the secret.
You can do it, Azusa-chan!
She's so adorable!
[Azusa] W-What just happened?!
[Ritsu] I'm freezing!
[Tsumugi] I can't believe it's
snowing on the day of the exam.
There it is. My admission slip
is safe and sound, right in this
pocket.
You are so paranoid...
Do you have yours with you,
Ri-chan?
Of course! It's right here,
all ready to go.
No way.
Are you serious?!
Wait, could that be it over
there?
[Ritsu] That was close!
Come on, don't DO that!
My bad.
Here she is!
[Tsumugi] Good morning,
Yui-chan!
[Mio] Morning!
Please don't say anything to me.
If you do, the vocabulary in
my head will start to spill out!
No! Something fell out just now!
Oh please don't be important!
[Ritsu] That's some serious
last-minute cramming.
[Azusa] I wonder if
the test has started yet?
Azusa?
Oh, Jun.
Are you out doing
your Valentine's shopping?
Uh-huh.
So what are you making?
I was going to make a chocolate
cake,
but the recipe I found is so
complicated.
What kind of ingredients are in
it?
Let's see, some granulated
sugar, and heavy cream...
Oh hey, looks like they've got
some sugar right here.
[Azusa] Oh, you're right.
Wait, that's brown sugar...
Yeah, but chocolate brown too,
so this should good with it.
[Azusa] Uh, really?
And if I remember right, I think
they've got some good chocolates
just over here.
[Azusa] But that chocolate's
not for baking.
Chocolate is chocolate. It's all
the same.
[Jun] Now let's see,
the cream is-
[Azusa] Jun wait a sec..
Yeah?
You HAVE made a chocolate cake
before?
Of course I have!
Why don't I believe her?
[Ui] Hey! Azusa-chan! Jun-chan!
[Azusa] Ui!
Hey there! You doing your
Valentine's shopping, too?
Who all are you baking for?
[Ui] I thought I'd start with
something for my sister first.
[Azusa and Jun] That's all
for one person?!
So what are you going to make,
Azusa-chan?
[Azusa] It's SUPPOSED
to be a chocolate cake...
So you want to make it together?
[Azusa] But I...
[Jun] That would be really
great!
Where's all that confidence you
had?!
I've got two, but one set are
these big fluffy panda slippers.
Which do you want?
[Jun] Both.
[Azusa] One each.
[Jun] Measure out the
amounts precisely, okay?
[Azusa] Right.
Jun-chan, has the chocolate
melted yet?
[Ui] Hey! Don't!
It's yummy!
I know, but just don't eat it.
Can't we just give it to them
as a gift like this?
[Azusa] No!
[Yui] Hello!
Y-Yui-senpai!
[Azusa] What bad timing!
[Ui] Hey there Sis, you're home
early!
Yeah, we just covered two
subjects today.
Hey guys, you decided to drop
by?
Yeah, we did!
I have to make sure she
doesn't suspect anything!
So, how do you think you did on
the exam?
Uh, I...
I've no idea.
[Azusa] Figures.
What'cha guys making here?
Whatever it is it sure smells
chocolatey and yummy!
It's, um...
It's a chocolate cake!
She told her!
Wow, really? When it's done,
let me have some, okay?
Yeah of course.
Why did you tell her?
I'm always making snacks,
it'll never occur to her that
it's for Valentine's Day.
Are you sure?
Uh oh, looks like we don't have
powdered sugar for the
decorations.
What'll we do?
The store on the corner
has it, I'll get it.
No, hold on if you don't want to
I'm happy to-
(Door opens, cold wind blows)
-keep an eye on things here.
Really?
[Ui] Once the timer goes off,
take it out of the oven, okay?
[Jun] Got it!
[Azusa] It's freezing!
I bet Jun will taste- test
everything.
[Ui] Wait a sec.
[Azusa] A hundred prayers?
[Ui] Yeah. It's right next door,
so I throw in ten cents every
time I walk by.
This has to be about the
hundredth time...
[Azusa] That's some bad
bookkeeping...
What have you been wishing for?
Oh, I've been wishing that my
sister and the others get into
the same college,
and that they all graduate
together without any problems.
I see. I guess I'll do
the same then.
[Azusa] It's freezing!
[Azusa] K-ON!
I'm a nervous wreck
for some reason...
[Jun] I gave it to her!
How did it go?
Perfect!
What's up? Are the guys from
Light Music Club not here yet?
No. You sure that
it's a good idea
that I give it to them here
at the front of the school?
It's really kind of
embarrassing.
Why do you think that?
S-Senpais! It's for you!
Though the chocolate may be
bitter,
it is full of the sweet feelings
that I have for you!
[Girls] Um. Thanks.
You're right, I see how that
might be embarrassing.
[Azusa] Like I would ever say
that.
I know, how about sneaking it
into a guitar case or something?
Yeah, but the issue with
that is when to do it.
Ah. Oh, but-
[Yui] Take cover! It's a bomb,
Commander!
That might cause a big fuss.
[Azusa] And it wouldn't happen.
Well if that won't work,
then maybe put it in one of
their desks,
when they're not looking.
That's not bad. I could make
that work.
Hey Ritsu! We're leaving now!
I'll be right there!
There is that chance.
Yeah, THAT I could see
happening.
[Yui] No, you've got to have
the black sesame custard roll!
[Ritsu] Eh, is that even a
thing?
Yeah! And it's totally
delicious!
[Yui] What would you want,
Mugi-chan?
[Tsumugi] Me? I suppose an
anko bean bun.
[Jun] Aren't you going?
[Azusa] Yeah.
[Yui] An anko bun, huh?
[Mio Fan] Akiyama-senpai!
Uh both of us would like you to
have this!
Oh, uh... Thank you.
Wow, it's huge!
[Ritsu] Befitting for our
legendary live vocalist!
[Mio] Back off!
[Ritsu]
Oh my, somebody's blushing!
[Jun] You're not going?
Mm... No.
[Ui] You haven't given it to
them yet?
Nope. Not yet, and
it's already lunch time.
Well that's all right, you can
still give it to them after
school, can't you?
Well she can but, I bet you
anything Mio-senpai gets a ton
of chocolates.
What if they divide them all up
and eat them together?
When school's out the last thing
they'll want are chocolates.
I don't think they'd wolf them
down all at once like that.
My point is, "Victory goes to
the swift."
Don't you worry about it. I'm
sure that they'll be happy to
get it whenever.
Do you think so?
Maybe I'll give her mine now.
Who is it?
It's Mio-senpai.
She's my bass guitar idol.
O-Okay.
[Ichigo] That's the Light Music
Club.
Hey, you're right.
Mio and the others went to the
staff room.
Thank you so much!
[Jun] I'm a nervous wreck!
[Ui] They remembered us.
They here?
Yui-chan and Ri-chan, got
accepted to their third choice
school.
Mio-chan and Mugi-chan, were
accepted to their third and
second picks.
You are true to form, bad at
rehearsals, but great when
you're up on stage.
Word!
That wasn't a compliment.
We just have to hear from
your first choice school now.
When do they post their results?
Two days from now.
All right. I'll keep my fingers
crossed, that you're all
accepted.
Thanks!
[Sawako] Well, that's
the last of all your exams
girls.
Now you can just kick back
and relax until graduation.
You've earned it.
[Azusa] Graduation...
[Girls] Will do!
Ah, nothing.
[Tsumugi] Look, it's Azusa-chan!
Hello!
What is it? Here for a teacher?
Uh actually...
Azusa go on!
Um, well here you go!
This is for you, Mio-senpai.
Thank you.
[Jun] And these are for
the rest of you. Here.
[Girls] Thanks!
[Ritsu] Ours are, dinky!
[Tsumugi] But very cute, though.
Just do it, Azusa.
Ah. Okay...
[Mio] You brought us
something, too, Azusa?
Azu-nyan chocolates!? Awesome!
Um...I...
[Azusa] I um...have to use
the bathroom right now.
Wait, what? Hey, Azusa!
I'm confused.
Oh, to be young!
[Jun] Azusa!
Azusa. What's wrong?
Just give it to them,
it's not THAT embarrassing.
All you've got to do is hand
them the box and say, "Here you
go."
That's not it.
That's really not it at all.
[Azusa] It hit me.
They're really gonna graduate.
They really are gonna leave. All
of them.
[Jun] There, there...
Okay, I'm off to Jazz Club now.
All the seniors said they
were coming in today for sure.
Later.
Bye!
Azusa-chan I-
[Jun] Azusa!
Whatever you do just make sure
you give it to them!
She's right.
You have to do it, Azusa-chan!
Girl power!
Yeah!
Here goes...
[Yui] Ow!
[Azusa] Yui-senpai?! Are you
okay?
Wait, why are you down there?
I sensed your presence
outside...
Um you sensed my what?
[Tsumugi] Oh, Azusa!
I decided to break out
my special reserve tea today.
Oh, wow, you did?
Well it sure does smell really
good.
[Ritsu] While we're talking
about it, whatcha got for snacks
today?
[Tsumugi] I'm sorry, I didn't
bring anything today!
But I have a feeling that
Azusa-chan may have brought
something instead!
[Azusa] How did you guys find
out?!
[Ritsu] As we left the office,
Sawa-chan said: "Save a piece
for me please!"
[Yui] So good!
You are a cake genius!
I wouldn't go THAT far.
It really IS quite delicious.
Y-You guys think so?
Azusa! Seeing as how this is
a chocolate cake, does that mean
it's a-
Well um, how can I put it?
It's a token of my gratitude, I
guess.
Ah, gratitude? Do tell.
And in return for your
amazing gift, I give you this!
What is it?
[Yui] Candy!
A return gift for White Day!
[Azusa] Too soon!
[Ritsu] Too cheap!
[Ritsu] If you don't give the
gift ON White Day, it's
pointless.
[Yui] Oh, really?
[Girls] Thanks for the treat!
Thank you all, you're too kind.
I really hope Sawa-chan gets
here soon.
What is it?
Snow.
[Mio] It's snowing a lot, too.
Wow, you're right!
Everything is all white!
Yeah? Let me see.
[Ritsu] That truck is totally
buried!
[Azusa] You're right, it is!
I want to see, too!
Well...So do I!
We're all going to have
to squeeze in pretty tight.
[Yui] Wait! What about me?!
Don't leave me!
[Ritsu] Fine, fine, get over
here.
[Yui] Hey I can't see
anything...
[Ritsu] Yo, watch with the
pushing!
You're such a baby.
[Yui] Oo! It's all white!
[Tsumugi] It's lovely.
[Ritsu] We're getting a lot
of snow this year.
[Girls] Look out!
[Ritsu] Whoa, that girl
almost slipped and bit it.
[Azusa] She sure did..
[Mio] Loafers fail when it
comes to-
Ah! Don't say fail!
[Mio] Sorry.
You know, this is nice.
All of us huddled together
like this. It's nice.
Even though it's been
freezing all day long,
when I'm with you guys
like this, it doesn't seem
cold at all.
Oh, that goes for you too
Ton-chan.
Yui-senpai?
You're all warm and cozy,
Azu-nyan!
Thanks.
[Ritsu] Warm and cozy!
[Ritsu] That tickles!
Cut it out!
Sawa-chan!
[Azusa] Ten cents times 100!
May all my senpais, please,
please, please, please please!
Oh please!
Get accepted to their
first school of choice.
So they can all go to
college together!
And may we spend every
single minute
until they finally graduate
laughing and smiling.
The candy Yui-senpai gave me...
That's sweet...
[Ritsu] Ready! One, two!
Come on, this is still
just a practice run.
[Mio] That one essay.
I know that I messed up
that essay question.
[Ritsu] You don't know
if you flunked just yet, okay?
[Mio] Yeah. You're right...
Even if I go to a different
school, let's stay friends,
okay?
Just wait until you see
the dang results.
[Ritsu] And if you leave before
you look at that board,
you're dead to me.
[Mio] No! Don't say that!
[Ritsu] Okay, for reals
this time!
[Ritsu] Let's do it!
[Girls] Yeah!
[Girl 1] There's my name!
[Ritsu] We so got this!
[Girls] Yeah!
[Ritsu] After School Tea Time!
[Girls] Yeah! Huh?
[Girl 2] You should call
your mom!
Why did you do that?
One, two!
[Azusa] They did it!
They got in!
(closing song, "NO, Thank You!")
[Mio] It sure is warm today.
[Yui] Don't mind me.
[Ritsu] You wanna go
somewhere and hang out?
[Tsumugi] Let's just stay here.
[Mio] But what should we do,
though?
[Yui] Let's have an epic battle!
[Mio] It's our classroom,
but still, some how it feels
kind of different now.