[Nodoka]
Miss Tachibana. Miss Akiyama.
Miss Matsumoto. Miss Akiyama.
All right then, for our
production of Romeo and Juliet
at the school festival,
Our class has voted that the
role of Romeo will be played by
Mio Akiyama.
Mio-chan's the star!
That's amazing!
Way to rock it, Mio!
Anyone home there?
She's out cold.
(opening song,
"Utauyo!! MIRACLE")
I-I object!
[Nodoka] To what, Miss Akiyama?
Um well, you see, it's just
that, I don't think it's
a good idea,
to vote on who should be
the lead actors.
But if you'll recall there were
no volunteers or nominations,
either.
Fine! Then I-I nominate Ritsu!
She's energetic, and brave! And
she's always practicing pro
wrestling moves!
What does that have to do
with being Romeo?
I mean after all you're the only
girl here with her very own fan
club.
That makes you the obvious
choice!
I get it! The obvious choice
to play Ro-MEO is Mio?
Is that your idea of a joke?!
Relax, it'll be fun.
And hey on the day of the play,
I'll even do your makeup!
I'm thinking, lots of heavy,
purple eyeshadow...
I'm Romeo not a witch!
And I'll be sitting there
right in the front row,
making sure that I catch
every second of it on video!
Put yourself in my shoes...
[Nodoka] Miss Tainaka.
You've been cast too, as Juliet.
Nope! Objection!
Wow Ritsu, that's quite the 180
you've just made now that the
tables have turned.
How in the world could
I possibly play Juliet?
The decision wasn't mine.
The class voted for you to play
that role.
But there's lots of people
in class better suited for that
roll!
Like, uh...Mugi there!
I'd love that role, but I'm
directing.
How about Ichigo, then? She's
got that "cute princess" thing
going on!
No way.
What about you, Mika?
Didn't you say you wanted
to play a princess?
But Mio's been cast as Romeo.
So what?
It's gotta be!
Look, if Mio is playing Romeo,
then the only one
who can play Juliet is you!
[Girl] Hey she's right,
you know!
[Ritsu] What!?
Yeah think about it, you guys
are a duo.
You can't put the straight guy
up there without the funny
sidekick!
What are we, a vaudeville team?!
If Mio-chan and Ri-chan
are gonna be the leads,
then I think I'm going to make
some major rewrites!
[Both] What are you up to?
Okay, since there are no real
objections to be dealt with
here,
Then I'm going to move on to
selecting who will do the other
jobs.
[Ritsu] She just blew us off...
First, up the costumes-
Me! I nominate myself!
Yes but we can't ask a teacher
to-
It's okay, I promise you won't
regret it.
Why are you so scared?
[Azusa] Wow, so your class is
going to be putting on a play,
huh?
[Tsumugi] Yes we are!
Which is why Mio-senpai's like
that?
I have to say, the thought of
you on a stage playing Juliet
is-
If you wanna laugh, fine! Go on!
I wasn't laughing at you
I promise, I was just...
Okay that's it!
I'm sorry!
You laughed again!
Wait who's Yui-senpai playing?
Tree! I'm tree G!
A, B, C, D, E, F... does the
play really need that many
trees?
[Yui] Having to stand perfectly
still... makes this a very
demanding role!
What kind of play are they
putting on?
[Tsumugi] Okay we need to run
some lines right now,
so I'm going to head
back to the classroom.
Once Mio calms down, we'll join
you.
Now, then... What to do about
Mio?
Hey, Ton-chan would you
like to trade places with me?
[Ritsu] Mio.
[Azusa] I know you can do it!
You'll make a fantastic Romeo!
I can't wait to see you on
stage!
I really wouldn't get your hopes
up too high. I don't want to do
this at all.
But you landed the lead role!
This year's school festival is
going to be like all Mio all the
time!
[Ritsu] Really? Were you trying
to make her feel worse?
[Azusa] I'm so sorry!
Hey where are you going?!
We've got to rehearse the play!
Oh yeah, I just remembered,
I'm transferring to a different
school.
You see, my papa is moving the
whole family to Irkutsk because
of his job.
Terrible liar.
"Papa"?
I meant Dad!
A-Anyway, that's what's
happening. Goodbye!
Not so fast!
Come on, let me go! I'll move
back as soon as the school
festival is over!
But what about our show?!
[Mio] My twin sister will fill
in for me!
You don't have one!
Wait it was a dream?!
Wow, that was scary!
I had this crazy dream where
I was picked to play Romeo in a
play!
She just keeps sinking
deeper into a state of denial.
All right, I think it's time
we start practicing for
our concert at the school fes-!
[Ritsu] We're going.
No! I don't wanna! I don't
wanna!
[Mio] No! Please!
[Ritsu] Shut up!
[Mio] Forehead freak!
(door closes)
Shouldn't you be going there
too?
I have to practice holding
completely still, Nodoka-chan
said so.
Oh.
Hark Benvolio! Is Benvolio here
praytell?
[Nodoka] She wont?
She says we can't talk her into
it.
A lead role is just too much...
It's too bad, but she has
the concert to think of too.
I see. Well, if you're that dead
set against it, I may
reconsider.
Really?
But just remember you were
chosen to do this by your class,
so maybe you should
at least give it a try.
The whole class seems
to be into this play. See look.
As I hate all Montagues,
repent thine ways!
It's sounding like a samurai
drama!
(girls laugh)
I'll try.
That's great!
Nodoka's persuasive.
I really don't think the class
picked Mio for her acting
skills, though.
I can hardly wait to see Mio
play Romeo!
Me too!
Hark, art thou not Romeo sir,
and a Montague as well?
[Tsumugi] Cut!
Ri-chan, I need you to dig
deeper into Juliet's emotions!
I'm sorry...
And now you, Romeo!
Okay... I'm happy to be neither,
fair maiden, if thee by chance
happen-
[Tsumugi] Cut!
[Mio] -to dislike...
Mio-chan, you're still
way too embarrassed.
You're really harsh.
You're up, Ri-chan!
Where was I?
[Ritsu] Do I really have to say-
[Tsumugi] No cut!
[Tsumugi] You're still-
[Ritsu] Mugi.
You're not just shouting "Cut!"
all the time because you think
it's fun, are you?
Maybe I am. I guess I just
wanted to sound like a director,
sorry.
You need to talk louder, Mio,
or no one will hear you.
Okay, sorry.
[Girl] You've got a great voice,
so let us all hear it!
[Tsumugi] Alright, let's focus
on that and try it again.
We'll start with your line,
Ri-chan.
[Ritsu] Got it. Um...
Good night, good night!
Parting is such sweet sorrow...
So I guess that I shall just say
good night then or something...
Ri-chan, you have more lines.
...till it be the morrow.
GAH!
I'm gonna hurl!
What kind of dialogue is this?!
Now SHE'S losing it?
And what's with this damn story,
anyway?
Everything they say
is all hoighty toighty!
If they really hate
their parents that much,
just run away already and be
done with it!
[Girls] It's a Shakespeare
meltdown...
And it looks like Mio's
spiraling down again, too.
[Girl] I give up.
[Mio] I'm done.
And now you can see why the
class is rather concerned about
them.
[Azusa] Well, I definitely see
how Ritsu-senpai playing
Juliet could pose a problem.
[Ritsu] No, don't sugar coat it
for me...
Wow, she can barely get a
comeback out!
Oh, hey! I just had a great
idea!
Like what?
Listen, listen!
If Ri-chan starts acting
more feminine in general,
and if Mio-chan starts
acting more masculine,
even when they're
not rehearsing for the play...
[Azusa] Oh yeah, that actually
might work!
All right, it's settled,
from now on Ri-chan,
you can no longer talk like a
tomboy.
Dude, come on!
Yep! No more of that.
[Yui] And let's hold our teacup
in both hands, shall we?
[Yui] And stick out your pinky!
[Ritsu] What for?
Oh! And you also have to make
sure
that your blouse is always
tucked into your skirt!
Feels weird.
It kind of looks weird on you
too.
[Yui] We're finished with
Mio-chan!
[Mio] Is this really going to
help?
I don't like it...
Whatever. Let's just practice.
Now my waist feels all sweaty.
[Yui and Tsumugi] Sit like a
lady!
I can't do that while
I'm playing the drums!
This still feels pretty weird...
I can feel a draft hitting my
stomach.
Hey, Ritsu.
I know it's kinda late, but
shouldn't we just tell them that
we want to quit?
R-Ritsu?
[Ritsu] Ah! I can't handle how
stuffy I feel with my shirt all
tucked in!
Fix yours the way you like Mio.
Intensive training begins now!
[Ritsu] You wanna go on letting
them make fools of us?! Is that
okay with you?!
[Mio] Yeah, I guess it is.
[Ritsu] Well, it's not okay
with me! Let's get to it!
K-ON!
[Satoshi] You're in a play?
Seriously?
Yeah. So don't come into
my room while we're rehearsing.
[Satoshi] What role are you
playing?
I'm Juliet.
(sputtering)
Don't laugh! It's not funny!
How silver-sweet sound lovers'
tongues by night like softest
music-
[Ritsu] Wrong! All wrong!
You keep acting like that missy,
and you'll never be a star!
Who are you?
Let's hear what YOU'VE got then!
Sure, I'm way better...
Hark, tis almost morning;
Like a poor prisoner in his
twisted gyves, And with a silk
thread-
[Mio] Y-You are SO not Juliet!
Quit laughing!
At least I can get the line
right!
Well the line maybe right,
but you are way wrong!
Oh shut it.
(Satoshi and Mio laughing)
It's hopeless.
At least we managed
to get all the lines
memorized...
Yeah, but you were
laughing the whole time.
Well of course, I mean
your Juliet is kinda-
What? The very thought
of it makes you laugh?
Your Romeo's nothing special
either,
whenever you said a line
your eyes would get all shifty,
like the last thing you
were interested in was me!
But I can't help it.
I'm nervous like that in real
life too.
You know, they should've picked
you to be Juliet not me.
You can do nervous and timid...
Romeo, O Romeo!
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
Come on, I'm not like that!
If you were Romeo, you'd be all-
Ah Juliet, what light through
yonder window dost break?
Like that.
Romeo wouldn't talk like that.
[Mio] All I'm saying is that
you'd be better at playing Romeo
than Juliet.
I am no pilot; yet, wert thou
as far as that vast shore
wash'd-
What?
Your performance was spot-on!
You know, when you were trying
to be me your Juliet was good
too!
[Mio and Ritsu] We did it!
[Girl] Then hie you hence
to Friar Laurence's cell!
Hie to high fortune!
Honest nurse, farewell.
So Ritsu is playing Juliet
by imagining Mio playing her?
And Mio is choosing her
performance based,
on how she imagines Ritsu
would be playing the role of
Romeo?
That's confusing...
So Mio is Ritsu?
The heavens smile upon on us!
Amen, amen. But come what sorrow
can-
[Class] Speak up!
C'mon, Mio, you did this
yesterday!
Yeah I know, but that was in
front of you this is totally
different now.
[Ritsu] Goodness...
[Tsumugi] Then maybe you should
just pretend that Ri-chan is
the only one here in the class
room.
Just Ritsu?
What's up?
Come on, dude.
("Ritsus" talking at once)
So noisy...
["Ritsus"] Was that a crack at
me!
I really hope she can get
over her stage fright.
If not we're going to be in
trouble.
Yeah, I suppose you're right...
I know!
[Tsumugi] Mio-chan!
Are you free this Sunday?
For what?
To give you some special
training!
Are you in?
Do I need it?
Just what do you have in mind?
Okay, listen close...
Good idea...
I just remembered! I have plans
this Sunday! I totally forgot!
[Class] Miss Akiyama!
Fine.
W-What IS this place?
It's a high end tea room
run by a family friend.
Tea room?!
Yep! And we're going
to be working here today!
Yeah the idea is, that working
with all these customers will
help get you over your stage
fright!
Well, come on, everyone let's
go!
That looks really nice on you!
Yeah? You think so?
Yours is super cute, too,
Mugi-senpai.
Aw thank you!
And Ritsu... you look...
If you've got something to say,
just go on and spit it out!
Mine feels kinda tight to me...
Yeah, so does mine.
Hey, Are you sure you gave them
the right sizes for us?
I did. But they said
they might not all fit
since we're kind of in
a growing spurt right now.
Where does it feel tight?
Well, it's a bit tight
around the waist for me.
For me it's across the chest.
[Yui] Mio-chan?
Very well, girls,
I'll leave it to you, then.
Now you might feel a bit
overwhelmed until you find your
footing, but you'll get it.
Just remember, the important
thing
is to greet the customers with
a big smile and a warm welcome.
Yes, sir!
A big smile?
Azu-nyan, what do you say?
Let's give it a try!
Sure.
How may I help you?
Thank you so much for coming
today!
Yeah, we get it, you're both
real cute.
[Yui] Now you give it a try,
Ri-chan!
Well uh...sure...
Thank you so much for waiting!
Were you the one that
ordered the apple tea, sir?
I didn't know you could be so
cute!
That's enough from you!
Azusa!
By the way girls, where is Miss
Akiyama?
Oh, I'm sorry. Let's see,
chances are that she's just
hiding somewhere.
Commander! I've spied her over
there!
Come on. You wont get any better
if you keep hiding back here all
day.
[Mio] You don't need me!
You've already got plenty of
waitresses.
I'll just get in the way!
We're here because of YOU,
remember?
[Mio] All right, fine...
[Shop Owner] If you're ready,
I'll open for business.
(door opens)
Here you are, Miss.
So this doesn't make
you guys nervous at all?!
I guess you could say...
that thanks to a certain someone
we've built up out tolerance.
[Woman] Excuse me.
[Ritsu] Go on, your audience is
waiting!
Just get in there!
I uh... would you... have a nice
flight!
Could you take our order now?
Yes, of course, go ahead.
My pen...where'd I?
It's all right, there's really
no hurry.
I am very sorry!
Please just give me one minute!
Yui! Quick, I need
something to write with!
Here!
Why is there string cheese
in your pocket?!
[Yui] The nice old man in
the kitchen said I could have
it.
But if you need it, here you go!
A pen! Not a piece of cheese!
[Yui] Oh, well this is a pen!
You see?
That's confusing!
It's a skit, right?
Has to be.
They must be high-schoolers.
Well they're awfully cute.
[Mio] T-Thank you for waiting.
No problem.
You okay?
Y-Yes, ma'am! Thanks for asking.
Are you all right, Mio-chan?
I'm just not very good at this.
Everywhere I go I create a mess.
Instead of thinking of the
customers as a bunch of
strangers,
why don't you try imagining
them as your close friends?
I guess I could try that.
Let's see... I'll have the
parfait and the vanilla ice
cream, oh and the cake!
What else? What else?
Gimme a minute, 'kay?
Oh sure.
I'll take the custard plate
please, and supersize it!
[Mio] I'm not so sure
we can do that.
[Yui] Yum pie!
[Ritsu]C'mon, of course you can!
[Yui] That sounds good
but so does....
All you have to do is put some
extra custard on the plate!
And now I'm annoyed.
Oh dear, that's not good...
She doesn't exactly seem to
be picking this up so easily,
does she Senpai?
Not at all.
But even when
she's playing bass for the band,
she's only half as good live as
she is when we're just
practicing.
But for the really big concerts
she does do fine. She can even
sing, too.
Yeah, you're right about that!
When she's backed in
a corner, she- Hold on!
Maybe if she had no choice
she could do it.
Girls? This is generally
a slow time of day for us,
so if you all would like to take
a break got right ahead.
Okay, thanks!
You too Miss Akiyama and Miss
Kotabuki.
Ah no break for Mio.
She's the one that needs
the practice, so get to it!
Well if you say so.
[Mio] R-Ritsu!
See ya! C'mon, it's break time!
Wait! I feel bad leaving her!
[Ritsu] Trust me.
Ah. All right.
[Ritsu] Yui and Mugi,
[Ritsu] you're on a break too!
[Mio] Ugh, Ritsu...
This cup is really beautiful!
[Tsumugi] From what I'm told all
the tableware they use here
was brought over from Europe.
Wow, really?
Yep, and the tea that I'm always
serving,
at the Light Music Club
comes from here, too.
It's expensive.
You haven't looked at the menu,
till now?
It's shocking to learn we've
been guzzling such expensive tea
this whole time, huh?
Do you really think Mio-chan
is gonna be okay out there?
She looked like she
was having a rough time.
I think that when she's under
pressure, she always steps up.
Guess we'll soon find out.
[Mio] Thanks for dining with us
today!
[Yui] Wow, check out Mio-chan!
That smile alone gets
perfect marks!
See?
Mio-chan!
Mio-chan?
This is bad!
It's a smile trance!
Yo! Mio! Get it together!
[Ritsu] Oh no!
What have I done?!
[Mio] Good morning!
Wow!
[Yui] Her smile is perfect!
That special training
must have worked!
Yeah, and at the end, she got
pretty good at dealing with
the customers.
[Mio] Mhm, now I can interact
with them.
Really?
[Mio] But back to my face...
It's been stuck this way
since yesterday.
It was really that hard on you?
Sorry! But don't worry,
I'll fix you right up!
[Mio] Ow!
[Ritsu] Get better, get better!
[Mio] It's fixed!
[Yui] The old Mio-chan is back!
The real question is, do you
think you'll be alright for the
play rehearsals today?
[Mio] Not at all.
Customers and audiences are
two different things entirely.
I dressed like that for nothing?
But your smile was perfect!
[Tsumugi] Give it a try, maybe
you'll find you did learn
something.
[Mio] I doubt it.
So, Mio-senpai and Ritsu-senpai
are-
Mhm. They said they're going
to have to double their
rehearsal time,
just to get comfortable with the
play!
Oh. Okay then.
[Yui] And now...
When the curtain falls,
I exit the stage!
Is our show gonna be okay?
(closing song, "NO, Thank You!")
[Jun] The auditorium is
packed already!
[Ui] Are there any seats left?
[Mio] For I have known pain!
[Mio] No sweets before bedtime.
[Ritsu] It's all right, Mio.
Tonight it doesn't matter at
what hour we eat our cake...
For you see, we're not...
[Azusa] Can I help you
with something?
[Ritsu] Show me all you
have and I shall be avenged!
(laughing)
[Yui] I won't let you
fall asleep, little kitty!
Come in...