Summer vacation is starting,
so try to spend it in a
productive manner.
[Sawako] Now, as seniors, you
will have summer session
classes, so--
Summer vacation...
[Yui] Let's have another
training camp!
Huh?
Another training camp!
Oh yes, let's!
Good idea!
Wait! We have entrance exams to-
Now, all those in favor say
"Aye"!
Aye!
Hey! If we're voting, we're
gonna have to ask Azusa if she
agrees-
I already texted Azu-nyan
and asked her to vote on it.
That makes it 4 to 1.
Right, then! We're having
a training camp again this year!
[Yui and Tsumugi] Yeah!
[Mio] Y-Yeah.
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
Come on in, everybody!
Thanks for having us over!
Hey big sis!
Everybody's here now!
Hey, guys!
C'mon in, c'mon in!
(awkward laugh)
Lazing around the house?
[Yui] Come sit!
Let's play video games!
[Tsumugi] Let's! Let's!
[Azusa] Remind me what
we come here for, again?
[Mio] It's suppose to be a
meeting about the camp.
[Mio] Come on, let's get down to
business.
[Yui] Aw, we can play for a
while...
[Ritsu] Yeah!
[Azusa] Um, are you sure
a training camp is a good idea?
Why wouldn't it be?
Well, for one thing, you're all
seniors.
Yeah, but we could use a break,
ya know?
Yeah that's right!
You sure it's going to be just
"a little"?
You know, we went to the
beach the last two years,
so how about the mountains this
time?
Ah! I wanna go to the beach
again!
We'll be able to catch fish
and have a barbecue!
Oh...
That sounds pretty tasty...
Right?
I knew it, you guys just want to
goof off.
[Mio] By the way, where
would you rather go, Azusa?
Well um, Natsu Fest takes
place in the mountains.
vvReally?
Gnatso vest?
Nutty pest?
No, no! Not those things. Natsu
Fest!
Natsu Fest, is a huge outdoor
festival where lots of different
bands play!
Tens of thousands of people go
every year!
I've always wanted to check out
Natsu Fest at least once!
Yeah me too!
Plus, it'll be a real learning
experience, to watch
professional bands at work!
So, are we all agreed?
Natsu Fest is a mountain?
The venue is IN the mountains.
Inside a mountain...
(tribal music)
We're not going to get
eaten alive up there are we?
[Mio] I really don't know what
you're thinking, but whatever it
is, it's wrong.
What are we going to do
about getting tickets, though?
Is it too late to buy any?
Uh...
What would you do without me?
No more rescuing you.
(gasps)
That's amazing!
That's our Sawa-chan!
Wait! When did you get here!?
Could I get a cup of barley tea,
too?
O-of course.
Wow, my first Natsu Fest...
Yeah, I've never seen an outdoor
show before, either!
I bet it feels really great!
Keep that carefree attitude, and
you're looking at defeat.
Defeat by what?
By summer! Pay attention!
The glare of the blazing sun!
The sweltering heat!
And the summer insects that even
now are waiting to eat you
alive!
Those who choose to do battle in
Natsu Fest must face all these
challenges!
Prepare yourselves!
Yes, ma'am!
Mio-senpai is all jazzed up!
Looks like, nobody's here yet.
[Tsumugi] Azusa-chan!
Good morning, Mugi-senpai!
Good morning.
Oh, are you the only one here?
[Azusa] Yes-
[Ritsu] Morning!
[Ritsu] Hey!
[Mio] Figures, you two are the
only ones who managed to make it
on time.
Oh...
You look like you didn't get
much sleep last night,
Mio-senpai.
No. She was up all night,
working out which bands she
wants to see.
It's packed with bands
I don't want to miss!
Yeah, it looks like they have
a whole bunch of stages there.
Oh look, the bus is here...
I better try calling Yui-senpai!
I'm right over here, you guys!
[Yui] Hi! Good morning!
[The girls] Yui!
[Azusa] You should've said
you were already here!
Well...I was waiting to see
when you would notice me...
[Azusa] I'm sorry, but it
never occurred to me that
you might be the first one to
get here.
Of course we're still missing
one person from our group.
(groaning) Girls...
Sawa-chan, what's the matter
with you?
I went out to a show last night
and drank until morning...
I came straight here from the
club.
[Ritsu] Sawa-chan, that was
stupid.
Why would you do something like
that if you knew we were leaving
today?!
[Mio] Come on, let's hit
the road!
[Azusa] You told us to
take this trip...
(queasy) I feel sick...
Oh yeah, welcome to my life...
You're sick because
you're hung over, aren't you?
Yeah, I live the rock-n-roll
lifestyle...
I really don't know what that
means...
You two all right?
Yui-senpai gets carsick easily,
huh?
[Mio] I'm going to see this band
and this band, period!
You can't, Mio. They're playing
on different stages at the same
time.
Then I want two bodies!
Ugh.
Choose one or the other.
Or only listen to half of each
one.
Then I want a teleport!
[Ritsu] Get real.
Mio-senpai is acting like a
baby.
I want yakisoba! Yakisoba!
Yakisoba is the one thing
I intend to eat there!
[Azusa] Mugi-senpai
is acting childish, too!
You guys are...
I want to die...
I can't believe I'm going to be
able to listen to music from
sunup to sundown...
You know, she's been getting
more and more wound up.
[Yui] Can you really blame her?!
[Ritsu] You've got ice cream!
They've got lots of great things
to eat!
And they sell lots of souvenirs,
too!
Rest stops are so awesome!
They have everything!
[Azusa] I thought you were
feeling car sick and yucky.
I'm all better now!
Have a taste of this, Azu-nyan!
Soft serve made from rich
highlands dairy!
If you're offering.
Our rest stop is nearly over.
But I haven't bought any
souvenirs yet!
This isn't our destination,
Yui-senpai!
Indeed it isn't! This is no
place for one eat yakisoba!
[Azusa] Mugi-senpai
is slightly off-kilter, too...
Are we there yet?!
Yui-chan, please,
stay down in your seat...
We'll make the opening
ceremonies, right?!
Relax, we'll make it!
They'll have tasty food there,
won't they?
Oh wow! Two days surrounded by
music!
Yui-chan! Yakisoba! Let's eat
yakisoba!
[Ritsu] Let's just enjoy
ourselves.
Are you guys going to be a
problem?
Please don't talk so damn
loudly, okay?
It's crowded!
Oh man, there's already
so many people here...
Are you okay? It hasn't even
started.
This sure is amazing, all right.
There must be, 300 million
people!
That's more than the population
of Japan.
[Sawako] Come on, girls!
The slacker attitudes end here!
[Yui] You were slacking
more than any of us were!
You were flat on your back
with a massive hangover!
I've cast off the me of
yesterday.
The festival entrance!
Beyond there lies a battlefield!
Lay it on thick?
(determined)
[Sawako] The wristbands you
got in exchange for your
tickets,
are your passport into this
festival!
If you lose them, you won't be
allowed back in, so keep a eye
on them!
Okay! Before we go in,
let's go to the camp area!
We need to secure
a place to sleep tonight!
[Sawako] Damn! Too late!
The flat area is already taken
up!
We'll have to settle
for the inclined area.
But won't our blood pool
in our heads while we sleep?
You sleep with your head uphill,
dummy.
Wow, you're really an old hand
at this.
All right, put your things
inside the tent.
[Tsumugi] Here goes...
Mugi-chan?
[Tsumugi] Yahoo! It's a bit
stuffy, but this is wonderful!
It's rather painful on the back,
though...
Yeah, we get it, come on!
Do you have everything you need
with you?
Yes, ma'am!
Have you all put on your
sunscreen?
Yes, ma'am!
Have you brought something to
drink?
I got it all covered! My heat
stroke countermeasures are in
place!
That's no good!
You should have a sports drink!
Should I leave this here?
No, bring it.
Water is useful for washing your
hands, or pouring over yourself
when you get hot.
I guess some people enjoy being
anal retentive about this
stuff.
Gah! Why aren't you
wearing your sneakers?!
[Tsumugi] I didn't bring
any other shoes with me.
Don't worry, Mugi-chan,
I'll lend you my flip-flops!
I brought them because I thought
we might play in the river.
Do you even remember why we're
here?
Yui-chan, thank you!
[Yui] Don't mention it!
Wait a minute, what about bug
repellant?
Bug repellent present
and accounted for, Miss!
Here!
Thanks a lot, Mugi-chan!
And now, here's some for you.
This reminds me of a grade
school hike for some reason.
It's your turn, Mugi-chan! Give
me the bottle so I can spray
some on you!
Thank you, but I can
take care of it myself.
Aw, but I wanna make
the bottle go "pshew," too!
All right, you can.
Yep, definitely grade school.
[Yui] Ri-chan, Azu-nyan,
I'll get you guys next!
Alright then! Are you done
dawdling?!
[Yui and Ritsu] When did
Sawa-chan get over there!?
Forward, march!
Here you are.
[Festival Worker]
Please follow our zero-litter
policy!
[Festival Worker]
Garbage bags will be provided!
Thank you for your cooperation!
The Natsu Rock Festival
is about to begin!
[Yui] K-ON!
All right, let me explain
how the grounds are laid out.
Yes, ma'am!
[Sawako] First is the Fire
Stage, a main venue.
This is one of the two main
venues, with a capacity of
roughly 40,000!
It has a gentle slope, so even
people in the back can easily
see.
This is the Thunder Stage,
or the alternate main stage.
It can hold over 10,000
spectators,
and tons of cutting-edge,
underground bands play here
throughout the festival.
People must go back and forth
between those stages a lot.
Definitely.
They're 700 almost meters apart.
(gasps)
Even running at 100m/s,
it'll still take 70 seconds to
cross!
Just breathe.
There's also this indoor stage,
where up and coming bands play.
The stage furthest in back
features jazz bands and the more
"unique" bands.
There's even a small stage that
features acoustic musicians.
This is truly, a festival of
music!
And food! Where is it
that they sell food?!
Remember, Yui-chan,
I'm in it for the yakisoba!
Something is seriously off
kilter with these two...
No kidding...
You know, I'm pretty amazed that
you just happened to have those
tickets.
Well, I come to this festival
every year.
But why did you have six of
them?
I was expecting to come here
with some of my friends,
but they cancelled on me
at the last minute.
Do they hate you or something?
Of course they don't!
Uh...
I think.
How am I supposed to react to
that?
(crowd cheering)
Mio-chan, are you okay?
You know, now that I'm actually
here, it's really hot and
crowded.
(band getting ready)
Let's get started!
(cheers)
Are you ready?!
Yeah!
[Singer] Alright! Let's ramp
this up!
(music begins)
Oh! Wow!
Their sound is so big!
This is really Natsu Fest...
This is...
(excited cheering)
...is Natsu Fest!
Mio-chan just made her Natsu
Fest debut!
Isn't this band fantastic?!
Oh yeah, the singer's voice is
awesome!
All right, people! We're moving
on!
But I wanna listen to this band
some more! Don't you?
My top band pick is playing at
the indoor stage pretty soon.
It's a little far, so we're
gonna have to sprint it!
Maybe you should just go
by yourself, Sawa-chan.
[Sawako] Suit yourselves!
I'm out of here!
[Mio] Ritsu! Ritsu!
I'm leaving, too!
[Mio] I'm going over to
the Thunder Stage!
[Ritsu] Right now?
Come on, hurry! If we don't
we'll miss the opening!
Mio-chan, I'm going to stay
here, okay?
Yes, I'll stay, too.
[Mio] Okay! We'll see
you guys later, then!
We'll touch base later and
meet up somewhere! Okay?
[Mio] Hurry! Hurry!
Alright, I'm coming!
See ya later! Have fun!
Hey Mio, wait up!
You sure about this?
You want to stay here and listen
to this great band, too, don't
you?
And what about you?
Yes, well, I can't
really run in flip-flops.
[Band lead] It's good to be
back here at Natsu Rock Festival
for the first time in three
years!
Ritsu! Ritsu!
Huh? What is it?
This band's guitarist is a
lefty!
[Ritsu] Wow, you're right.
(happy)
You were right, lefties
really DO look kind of weird!
But I'm really not one to talk,
though.
I'm glad you found a
fellow southpaw and all,
but could you please
bring it down a notch?
(band playing)
Yui-senpai's transfixed.
Staring at the stage.
I hope that being here inspires
her
to take her practicing
more seriously from now on.
[Yui] Azu-nyan, I want to ask
you an important question.
Yes? Ask me what?
How do you think their bassist
gets his hair to stay like that?
I mean it's so cool!
It has to be naturally curly.
You too, Mugi-senpai?
It's popular...
It's okay, we'll stand in line
with you!
Yeah, let's go!
Right!
[Yakisoba vendor] Excuse me,
everyone!
[Yakisoba vendor] Sorry folks,
but we're all sold out!
Mugi-senpai!
Just stay strong!
Don't let it get you down!
Mm. Okay, let's go get
what you want to eat.
Yui-chan...
Aw, this stinks...
I just wanna go home now!
Please don't throw a tantrum.
(Yui's phone ringing)
[Yui] Oops, I got a text!
[Azusa] She snapped right out of
it!
[Yui] It's from Ri-chan!
"We'll be at Fire Stage from
2PM, then Thunder Stage from
3PM,
and then Fire Stage again at
4PM."
[Azusa] Wow, packed schedule.
Right! I'll run there now!
[Yui] Mugi-chan!
[Azusa] Mugi-senpai!
(music)
[Sawako] Yeah! THESE GUYS ROCK!
Thank you!
Good. It's down to a drizzle
now.
We have some time to kill before
the next band we want to see.
Is anybody hungry?
We missed lunch and I'm
starving.
You ate crepes and ice cream,
and funnel cakes, remember?
That's dessert, not lunch,
silly.
Tell you what, I'll go buy
dinner for us, then, okay?
Hey, I'll go with you!
Don't worry, I've got this.
You guys stake out a spot for
us.
Okay, you know that river that
runs through the middle of the
boardwalk area?
[Ritsu] We'll wait for you
there.
[Ritsu] So, should we set up
here?
[Azusa] It looks good.
(jumping effort)
[Tsumugi] Mio-chan!
Welcome back... Thanks for
getting food.
They were selling t-shirts!
Look! It's for that band with
the lefty guitarist!
Where's dinner? Hm?
How does it look?!
Wow, that's nice...
I think I want to get one too!
Why don't we all buy one?
I'd like one as well!
[Yui] Let me see, let me see!
(Ritsu's phone ringing)
[Mio] See? What do you think?
A text from Sawa-chan.
She says she bought a bunch
of takoyaki for us to share.
Takoyaki!
Ah, I'm myself again!
They even have baths here!
It's amazing.
[Azusa] I have pins
and needles all over...
[Ritsu] You're red as
a lobster again this year...
I used a whole bunch of
sunscreen, but it didn't work
for me!
It's okay, you look so cute!
Well, I'm going to turn in now.
Huh? Already?
My neck's killing me
from the headbanging...
You thought it was because
of my age, DIDN'T you?
Perish the thought!
(street chatter)
[Azusa] Senpai?
[Yui] Hey, Azu-nyan.
[Azusa] What are you doing
up here all by yourself?
[Yui] I've been listening to
all the songs in the distance.
They really do play music
all night, don't they?
Come on, sit down.
O-okay.
[Azusa] Aren't you getting
bitten by mosquitoes out here?
Not a problem! I'm wearing
two bug repellant wristbands!
Here, I'll give you one.
Thank you.
Goodness gracious me!
Are you two having a secret
little chat?
[Yui] Come on over, you guys!
Let's listen to the songs here
for a bit.
[Mio] It's almost like a dream,
isn't it?
Yes, it feels kind of magical.
Yeah, music playing nonstop in
a wide open place like this, is
wonderful.
Everyone of the bands
I saw today was totally awesome.
Right. The music's energy...
Its intensity was completely
incredible.
Yeah, but I think our
performances are even more
amazing.
Where do you get off
comparing us to pros?!
Huh?
My point is, you should
get good enough to play,
your guitar without flubbing
notes before you say stuff like
that!
Ouch, you hit my vulnerable
spot...
Still, I do think we're more
amazing then all of those bands.
[Yui] The way we become one,
or... how do I explain it?
Right! It's our aura!
Do you even know what
the word "aura" means?
Uh-uh.
[Mio] She's right.
Hm?
After-school Tea Time is
an awesome band, too!
Mio?
[Mio] Right, Yui?
[Yui] Right you are, Mio-chan!
[Azusa] You're right! We're just
as good as these pro bands are!
[Ritsu] Wait, you too?!
[Mio] Next time, we won't come
to Natsu Fest to listen, we'll
come here to play!
[Ritsu] A-Are you serious?!
[Tsumugi] Right! To play!
[Yui and Azusa] Yeah!
Yeah, you're right... Wouldn't
it be awesome to get the chance
to play here?
[Yui] Yeah!
I hope that I can just keep on
playing in a band with you guys
forever!
So do I.
Mm-hm.
Me too! Forever. And ever.
(closing song, "Listen!!")
[Jun] Yakisoba always tastes
better when you eat it outside
like this.
[Ui] I know what you mean!
[Azusa] Now that you mention it,
Mugi-senpai was looking forward
to having yakisoba at Natsu
Fest,
but they sold out fast,
and she never got to eat any.
[Tsumugi] I have a summer house
we can us.
You can go to Finland anyway!
[Sawako] Why don't I take you
guys there?
Who are you?
[Jun] I had no idea.
[Yui] Leftovers from
lunch detected!