[Young Yui] Hello, turtle,
Mr. Turtle! Mr. Turtle, hello!
In all the world and outer space
above you and below,
nothing walks as slow as you.
Look at how you go.
Why, oh why, oh Mr. Turtle,
why are you so slow?
(excited)
Hey Yui come here!
[Young Nodoka] Hey, c'mon!
[Young Yui] Nodoka-chan!
Look, we're leaving to go on our
walk now.
Wait for me! Wait for me!
[Yui] Hmmm...
(thinking)
What are you "Hmm"-ing about,
Yui?
Oh hi, Nodoka-chan.
I can't decide on my top school
choice.
What?! You mean you haven't
submitted your life plans
questionnaire yet?!
But that was suppose to be in
ages ago!
But, but, I'm not really
smart about this stuff,
and I don't really know
which universities are good.
Yui, at this rate, you really
are going to end up a NEET.
This time, that word sounds
like an actual threat!
(opening song, "Go! Go! Maniac")
(contemplating)
(uncertain)
(groans) I give up,
I'll be a NEET...
"N.E.E.T."
Stop that Yui.
[Yui] What about you?
What did you put down for
your top school choice?
Who me? I put one of
the national universities.
I know it's a bit of a long
shot, but I figured that I'd
give it a try anyway.
Cool, then I'll put that down,
too!
[Nodoka] What?!
[Yui] But I wanna go to the same
school as you, Nodoka-chan!
(groans)
Hey what's the ruckus?
Let's go practice.
The thing is, Yui still hasn't-
Yui! You still haven't
decided on a school yet?
Mio, what school did you put
down? What's your top pick?
Well actually, I thought
I'd try for recommendations.
"Recommendations U."
Yui, do you even know what
recommendations are?
Nope.
[Yui] Where are you going,
Mugi-chan?
To the women's university
I told you all about.
Oh, wow! Very prestigious!
I'll put that one, too!
Will you just give it a rest?
[Yui] Is it hard to get into
your school, Mugi-chan?
Well I suppose...
I have their test prep guide
if you'd like to take a look.
Let me see.
English!
My eyes... I see flashes!
Welcome to the real world.
This is Japan! We don't need
no stinking English here!
Amen, sister!
We'll stand strong!
We shall live by Japanese alone!
Amen, sister!
(laughter)
[Mio] If you flunk English
in school, you'll get
held back a year.
(gasps)
But on the entrance exam,
you'll do fine if you get
good marks in other subjects.
See? It also has Japanese.
Really?
Lit? Right! Ri-chan, handoff!
All... right! Let's see?
"Select which of the following
auxiliary verbs is used in the
same manner."
Mm. Mm. Mm.
I never learned any of this!
We covered that our
freshman year.
(shocked)
But that's-- That's--
That's-- That's-- That's--
Impossible!
[Tsumugi] Didn't you ever learn
how to memorize auxiliary verbs
with a song?
A song?
-Muzu, -mu, -zu, -ji, -shimu,
-mashi, -mahoshi.
-Ru, -ra, -raru, -sasu, -ri,
-ri, -ri!
-Tsu, -nu, -tari, -keri,
-tashi, -tashi, -ki, -kemu!
-Ramu, -beshi, -rashi,
-maji, -nari, -meri.
Why, oh why are you so -tari
-gotoshi?
That's it, right?
You see Yui? You DO know them!
So, um, what do I do with all
those?
What's the point of
knowing the song, then?!
So what school did you pick,
Ri-chan?
I just wrote "undecided".
I mean, I have no idea what
I want to do with my life yet.
Oh right, I'll just put down
"undecided," too, then!
[Mio] Is that a good idea?
[Ritsu] Our future can't be
decided by a measly scrap of
paper!
[Yui] Amen!
[Sawako over speaker]
Miss Tainaka and Hirasawa,
please report to the
Staff Room immediately.
Of course it isn't...
You guys just go on up to the
club room without us, alright?
[Ritsu] What a hassle...
Oh brother.
[Mio] You sure have
your hands full with her.
You, too, Mio, with Ritsu.
Yui hasn't changed one bit from
way back when she was a little
girl.
But believe it or not,
she's improved a lot.
And Ritsu can pretty much do
anything she sets her mind to.
It's the same with Yui.
She can have amazing focus.
Hey could we please continue
this up in the club room?
Whoa what are you so suddenly
so wound up about, Mugi?
(door opens)
Good afternoon.
[Mio and Tsumugi]
Pardon the intrusion.
That summons was for Yui-senpai
and Ritsu-senpai, right?
[Mio] Yeah. They brought it
on themselves, though.
[Azusa] Oh did they do
something again?
[Nodoka] Again?
Um, it seems like they were
being called in to discuss
their future plans, that's all.
Here's your tea, Nodoka-chan.
Thank you, Mugi.
[Mio] I've been wondering, when
did you and Yui first meet each
other?
Way back in kindergarten.
Goodness, so how did you two
meet?
Well, there really wasn't
anything special about it, I
guess...
(kids chattering)
Heh.
Wanna draw together?
[Young Nodoka] Sure, okay!
[Nodoka] Before I knew it, she
was sitting there next to me.
[Mio] Maybe she knew
instinctivly that she could
count on you.
Yui, are you done already?
Yours looks yummy!
[Young Nodoka] Yes it does.
Ah!
No don't eat that!
(giggling)
She was like that even as a
baby?
Right. We ended up being in the
same class at school every
single year after that.
We definitely have some sort
of strange connection.
I bet that she's caused a lot
of trouble for you, hasn't she?
Well, I'm not sure you
could really call it trouble...
We went camping one time in
grade school.
We were supposed to bring
instant meals.
[Azusa] That sounds like her,
all right.
[Nodoka] And there was this
other time when we were making
takoyaki in Home Ec.
We were each assigned an
ingredient to bring from home.
Okay, I'm ready for the octopus.
Oh?
[Nodoka] Yui was in charge of
bringing the octopus, but she'd
forgotten it.
We ended up making octopus-free
takoyaki.
Even without octopus it's really
good!
Octopus free!
You know, I could tell you
stories about stunts
she's pulled until
the cows come home.
But when you see that
innocent look on her face,
you just can't help
but forgive her everything.
[Tsmugi and Mio]
I know what you mean!
You do?
Because I'm completely lost.
By the way. When I told you
earlier that in spite of
everything,
Yui had improved quite a bit.
I think that it's all because
of the Light Music Club.
So, thank you.
Nodoka-chan, You're so mature!
You sure are. You're almost like
a mommy.
[Tsumugi and Azusa] A mommy?
(freak out) I meant "mother"!
[Sawako] This is your future
we're talking about, so put some
thought into it.
Alright.
And you still can't decide,
Yui-chan?
It seems like it's so far off in
the future that it's hard to
picture it.
Well it's not far off at all.
It's almost here.
[Ritsu] That explains why
you keep looking older.
Did you say something?
No, I didn't ma'am.
Hey, you know. You were like
THAT back when you were in high
school
so what is it that made you
want to become a teacher?
Well, uh, that's...
What is it, what is it?!
Uh, it's a little bit
embarrassing...
We want to learn from your
example, so tell us everything!
There was this boy I liked, and
he said he wanted to be a
teacher someday...
And I said, "So do I!"
[Ritsu] Talk about impure
motives.
So what eventually happened
with you and that boy?
He just dumped me! (sobbing)
[Yui] Yeah, but thanks to
that boy,
you went to college and got your
degree and became a great
teacher, right?
[Ritsu] Yeah! I mean it's
not the past that counts,
it's the here and now,
Sawa-chan!
But you don't have a boyfriend
in the here and now, either.
(sobbing again)
(door closes)
So, how did it go, Yui?
Well we learned one more thing
about Sawa-chan's interesting
past!
Huh? So she didn't chew you two
out?
See guys, you never really know
what life will throw at you, do
you?
Wait, you didn't pull another
one of your stunts, did you?
No, no, I just mean that
whenever life throws you for a
loop,
it can make you stronger.
Huh?
Then she was okay with your
future plans questionnaire?
Not one bit.
Isn't there anything that you
want to be when you grow up?
Something that I want to be?
Mio-chan, what do you think
I should want to be?
Decide it for yourself.
(thinking)
Back in middle school, didn't
you say that you wanted to be a
kindergarten teacher?
That's right, I did!
I think it was when
we were reading our essays,
on the topic of "Future Dreams"
in front of the class.
My dream of the future is to be
a kindergarten teacher someday.
I want to become a kindergarten
teacher
and play with kids all day
until they go home!
(class laughing)
(laughing)
[Mio] Sounds like Yui!
Speaking of reading essays in
class,
there was this one time when
Mio actually won an award.
No! You can't tell them about
that!
Oh tell us!
Yes please!
A-Azusa, let's go and practice!
Okay?
You're not getting out of this
one, Mio. Give it up.
[Ritsu] K-ON!
(class chatter)
[Ritsu] Even back in grade
school, Mio was a quiet,
mild-mannered girl.
She always seemed to have
her nose in a book.
Huh?
Hm...
And that's when...
(nervous)
Hey what'cha reading?!
[Ritsu] She was even more shy
back then than she is now.
C'mon, let me see, let me see!
[Ritsu] I loved seeing her
reactions!
Wow, Mio-chan, you're great at
drawing!
[Ritsu] I was teasing her
constantly.
Wow Mio, you got a hundred?!
You're so lucky, Ri-chan, I wish
I could've teased her, too.
Don't you think that was
more like bullying?
Nah, totally different. In grade
school, you always tease the
kids you like.
Everybody knows that.
It's just what you do.
But we really didn't get along
all that well at first, did we,
Mio?
Of course not! After all
that teasing you did to me?!
I'm getting ticked off just
by thinking about it.
Now show me your forehead.
Uh? What're you gonna do?
Huh?
(snickering)
My forehead...
Relax, it's a water-based
marker.
So tell us, what exactly
happened when you were reading
your essays?
Oh, you remembered that...
[Ritsu] Ah lighten up, Mio,
just tell them the story.
Look! I'm a three-eyed alien!
We were in fourth grade.
And I recieved an award from
the prefecture for my essay.
But all the award winners
had to read their essays
in front of everyone at
an all-school assembly.
I was depressed because I didn't
want to read mine, and that's
when...
[Young Ritsu] What's wrong?
[Mio] Ritsu came up and talked
to me.
You don't want to read your
essay at the assembly? Well why
not?
Because I'm really
embarrassed...
Don't be embarrassed, Mio-chan!
You're awesome!
I-I am not! I'm just regular.
Mio-chan, you were the only one
in the whole class to get an
award!
If it was me, I'd be rubbing
it in everybody's face!
Then you should've won the
stinking award! Cause I don't
want it!
I don't want to get up in front
of everyone and read it!
(gasps) I-I'm so sorry...
Wow, I didn't know Mio-chan
could yell so loud...
That's... so cool!
Hey! Come to my house
for some special training!
[Young Ritsu] Just come on!
But-but I...
[Young Ritsu] Without further
ado, Grade 4, Class 1, seat #1!
Mio Akiyama!
But I can't do it!
Is the platform too low?
Want me to make it higher?
No, it has nothing to do with
that!
Hm...
Oh!
Give me just a minute.
First, I'll take this off and do
this...
Sorta like this, I guess.
Right! Okay, I'm all done!
What are you doing?
[Young Ritsu] I'm a pineapple!
My dad told me that whenever I'm
nervous,
just imagine that everyone in
the audience is a big fat
potato!
But I have no idea how to do
a potato impression,
so instead pineapple!
Look at me, I'm a pineapple!
(giggling) No you're not!
[Young Mio] And so, it was
passed down from one person
to the next. The end.
Grade 4, Class 1. Mio Akiyama.
[Mio] Thanks to Ritsu's help,
I was finally able to relax.
What a wonderful story!
Wow, you used to be really
nice, Ritsu-senpai!
That's so out of character
for you, Ri-chan.
Geez! Don't you two even know
how to compliment someone?!
So, did Mio's essay go over
well? Did everybody really like
it?
Well, it was something that Mio
wrote, so it had a serious fairy
tale vibe.
Itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy!
You can just imagine.
Yeah.
But it was right after that,
that I started going over to
your house all the time, Ritsu.
Remeber?
Yeah, and I started teaching you
all sorts of cool stuff! Didn't
I?
Right, lots of things...
To overcome shyness, you gotta
learn to have some
self-confidence, okay?
You start with how you speak.
If you say "Dude!" at the end of
your sentences, you'll sound
confident!
My name is Mio Akiyama, dude!
Good, good, just like that!
Lots of things...
You didn't teach me anything
that wasn't rude or crude.
[Mio] Maybe I should never have
gone to you for help back then.
(sad)
That's so mean, Mio-chan!
You said mean things to her
just a minute ago!
But I am grateful to her for
introducing me to music and
playing in a band.
I guess.
[Everyone] Mio-chan!
[Mio] Hey, we weren't talking
about me and Ritsu!
We were talking about what to
do about these two and
their futures!
[Yui] Oh.
Yeah she's right.
Don't try to think of
anything specific at first,
just start out by thinking in
very general terms of what you
might want to be.
Okay. Then a florist, maybe?
Hey, that sounds like a good
thing to be!
Hi! I'm Yui Hirasawa, the town
florist!
Is this type of flower
difficult to care for?
No idea.
Right, you need to know
about plants to do that...
Then how about an office worker
at some company?
I'm a rookie office worker!
I'm late again today! Tee-hee!
I'm sorry! I'm late,
I overslept!
You work at the company that's
two doors down the hall, Miss.
Right! Sorry, bye!
Anything with fixed hours
might be a problem...
That was mean, Azu-nyan!
Being a bus tour guide
might be fun!
Yeah, I could go to
all sorts of places free!
That might work...
I'm a bus tour guide!
Now if everyone will look to the
right of the bus, you'll see-
(gagging)
(horn honking)
[Azusa] That might be a bad idea
for someone who gets carsick.
Why don't you try being a
waitress?
Heh. I'm a waitress!
They have to remember
big orders all the time.
How about a pastry chef?
Look! I'm a pastry chef!
I think she'd eat everything
herself.
Yeah, you have a point there.
For now, I think you should
just put down
the very first thing
that comes to your mind.
The first thing that comes, huh?
Ri-chan, I got it!
Yeah!
Rejected.
[Both] What?
[Ritsu] What's the deal?
[Yui] We filled it out,
didn't we?
(door closes
[Yui] The mission was
a failure, Commander!
So you wrote "Musician"?
You should take this seriously!
But we were being
totally serious, Mio.
(chuckling)
Geez! Nodoka-chan is
laughing at us!
But not because it's funny.
You see, this whole thing was
actually an elaborate gag,
designed by Ri-chan and I
to make Nodoka-chan laugh!
You know they're never going
to buy that story, Yui.
(dog barking)
[Yui] Ui, what're you gonna do
after you graduate?
I can't tell her. I can't say
that I want to go to the same
school as her,
because I worry about her.
Uh, I really haven't thought
that much about it yet.
[Yui] Oh. Well, you need to give
it a lot of thought before next
year.
How about you, Sis?
I'm thinking about it right now.
She hasn't decided yet!
Well I always wanted to be a
beautician, so I'm going to go
to a beauty academy.
Oh, okay.
Art University, I'm gonna
study photography.
You mean there are schools
for photography?
University of Foreign Studies
so I can study in China.
Oh...
I've decided to go to nursing
school.
Help run my family's liquor
store.
I'm less sure than ever
what to put down...
(sizzling)
[Yui] Please do me
the honor of accepting this!
Rejected.
(door opens)
Hm?
[Yui] Thank you for your time.
(closing song, "Listen!!")
[Ritsu] What the heck is
wrong, Sawa-chan?
[Sawako] I'm having big time
tea and sweets withdrawal!
Why haven't we been having any
tea and cake parties lately?!
[Yui] That might just work!
[Azusa] I don't know
who I am anymore...
[Granny] Yui-chan!
[Yui] Granny!
[Yui] Thank you so much!
[Yui] Thank you for
always loo- Ow!
[Granny] What are you doing now?