[Ritsu] Mugi!
Good morning!
[Tsumugi] Good morning!
[Ritsu] Sorry we're late!
[Mio] We had to go back
for Ritsu's handkerchief.
Hey, Yui's not here?
But it was her idea that we
all walk to school together
in the first place.
[Mio] She picked a bad day
to run late.
I'll try texting her.
Oh! She just replied back.
So fast?
"Goe awne whithote mee"?
[Mio] Is she okay?
I think it says
"Go on without me."
Oh right!
I'll give her a call.
Nothing.
So do you think we should
go on without her?
Let's wait a bit more.
Okay.
[Mio] She's here!
[Tsumugi] Yui-chan!
I'm so sorry!
I woke up early, so I started
playing with Geeta-
No worries, it's okay.
Come on! Let's hit it!
(opening song,
"Utauyo!! MIRACLE")
Good morning, all.
Is the entire class here yet?
No, not everyone!
We're still missing
Miss Akiyama, Miss Kotobuki,
Miss Tainaka, and Miss Hirasawa.
Wait!
[Class Rep] Once you have your
corsage to pin on the graduates,
please proceed to
the auditorium.
Here.
[Jun] Azusa, let's go.
[Ui] Graduation is finally here.
It's time to say goodbye
to all the seniors...
[Ritsu] Hurry up!
[Mio] I think we'll make it!
[Yui] Geeta's so heavy!
[Ui] Hey Sis!
Classic Light Music Club.
They're always living on the
edge.
Ow!
[Jun and Ui] What's wrong?
I walked into the wall!
[Light Music Club] We're so
sorry!
What is wrong with you girls?
We're sorry, Sawa-chan!
Geez...
Miss Hirasawa!
[Mio] Yui! You have a hole!
[Yui] Oh no! I tripped on the
way here!
[Sawako] What'll we do?
[Nodoka] It's all right.
Ui left a change of tights with
me in case you need them.
[All] Whoa! She's psychic!
[Sawako]
Hurry up and get changed.
[Yui] Right!
I'll go along and help her.
No running in the hall!
It's always something.
Hey, you haven't signed
this yet, have you?
It's a gift for Miss Yamanaka.
[Ritsu] Sure thing, I'll do it
right now.
[Natsuka] You four are the
only ones who haven't signed it.
[Mio] Sorry.
You okay?
I can't believe it, today of all
days...
It's okay, you can't tell
with your bangs covering it up.
Really?
I gotta say, I hope gradation
goes well, no surprises.
It'll be fine! Just fine!
Nothing else will go wrong!
[Teacher] All remaining
students, please pin a corsage
on a graduating senior.
[Nodoka] Sorry!
They're here!
It took much longer than I
thought!
[Sawako] Thank goodness you
made it! Now go get a corsage!
[Yui] Yes, ma'am!
Um congratulations.
Thanks so much!
[Ritsu] Yui!
You ready?
Congratulations.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Yui, you've got to sign this.
Sign what?
A surprise present for
Sawa-chan.
The whole class is signing it.
You brought the card with you?
Busted.
[Sawako] Let's go girls!
Hurry up and get inside!
Coming!
What's going on?
Nothing!
Nothing at all, Sawa-chan.
What am I suppose to do with
this during the ceremony?
I don't know.
You could use it as a fan?
That really wont be necessary
in there. Try something else.
Maybe Sawa-chan could hold it
for us.
Uh no, try again.
Oh, right.
I know, what if I keep it hidden
here?
Through the whole ceremony?
Now I feel bad.
Well, I guess that's our only
option.
Oh wow, the auditorium looks
so much different than it
normally does!
This is really it... graduation.
[Teacher] The 85th
Sakuragaoka Girls' High
School...
commencement ceremony will now
begin.
Here is our principal. Please
stand.
[Principal] I'd like to take
this opportunity to
congratulate,
all of our graduating students.
As well as their families on
this momentous occasion.
Please take your seats.
[Principal] In your three years
with us,
you graduates have made many new
friends, had a number of new
experiences,
[Mio] I'm so worried about Yui
hiding it that I can't focus on
the ceremony!
On behalf of myself and the
members of the faculty,
we wish you well in all
your future endeavors.
[Sawako] Everyone is fussing
over Yui...
What's that about?
[Principal] All rise.
[Sawako] She's holding herself,
does she have a stomachache?
No, she was hiding something
earlier.
But what?
Snacks?
Geeta?!
Surely not Ton-chan!
No...
[Principal] Be seated.
What could it be?
[Principal] And now on with the
ceremony.
Will the class representative
please take the stage?
[Mio] Is she looking at Yui?
She's totally focusing on her!
Now graduates, please rise.
Pass this on to Yui, tell her
that Miss Sawako is concerned
about her.
Got it.
Mugi-chan.
Miss Tainaka.
She what?!
Message from Mio-chan. She says
Miss Sawako is corn fed for you.
Sawa-chan is corn fed?
[Yui] Why is she eating corn?
And why do I need to know that?
[Principal] Be seated.
I'm really confused. What is
Mio-chan trying to tell me?
[Principal] The valedictory
address.
Yes, sir.
Nodoka-chan's speech!
[Nodoka] Honored faculty.
First off I would like to thank
you all for gathering here
today,
on this special occasion. Our
graduation.
Looking back on the past,
our three years at this high
school,
were some of the most fulfilling
years of our young lives.
[All] K-ON!
[Yui] I kept it safe!
[Tsumugi] Thank goodness!
[Mio] I was freaking out
through the entire ceremony!
Yeah I know, I was totally
freaking out, too!
So what did you mean by
Sawa-chan is corn fed?
The message I sent you said that
Miss Sawako seemed concerned.
[Yui] Really?
[Tsumugi] By the time it go to
me it was still "concerned".
It all worked out!
You messed it up, didn't you?
So, have you signed it, Yui?
Have you?
No, not yet.
You should sign it pretty soon.
Here's a pen.
Thanks, Mugi-chan.
Sawa-chan, best wishes to you.
Yours-
That doesn't sound quite right.
That's what you'd write for a
wedding!
But I already wrote it!
That's going to seem like
you don't care. She'll be hurt.
Okay, then I'll add-
Alright girls, it's time to head
back to the classroom, girls.
I'm going to hand out your
diplomas.
[Yui] Y-Yes, ma'am!
And by the way, Yui-chan what
were you doing at the ceremony?
[Yui] Nothing at all.
[Sawako] Liar.
I was so focused on what you
were up to I missed the whole
ceremony!
I was keeping it safe!
What?
We'll see you in the class room!
Tell me now, I mean it!
[Tsumugi] We should really get
to the classroom, Sawa-chan!
[Ritsu] Hurry! Hurry!
[Sawako] Hey!
You've graduated, Yui.
Thanks to you.
[Sawako] Have you all checked to
see
your names are correctly
written on your diplomas?
Once you've checked that they
are correct,
put them away carefully
and take them home.
I love that sound!
[Sawako] All right. Listen, this
marks the end of a big chapter
in your lives,
your high school years are over.
[Sawako] And well...
Because you were the first class
assigned to me you will always
be special,
I consider it a privilege that I
could share this important day
with you.
Your future awaits you.
Embrace it.
All right... Class dismissed.
[Takahashi] Ma'am!
Well um, the class would like
to give you something,
as a thank for everything
you have done for us.
So who was the last person to
have it?
[Yui] Oo! It's me! It's me!
[Takahashi] In that case,
Yui-chan, go ahead and give it
to her.
(Yui singing)
Isn't that the theme for
winning a medal?
Miss Yamanaka, thank you
for looking after us!
Wait, is this what you were
trying to hide during the
ceremony?
You caught me!
Well thank you.
I'll cherish it always.
[Class] Thank you Miss Yamanaka!
[Sawako] I... I'm the one who...
Who should be thanking you.
I was very lucky to have you
as my first class.
Even though you've graduated,
please come and visit.
[Sawako] I've been waiting
for you people to arrive!
[Nakashikma] Whoa, Sawa-chan!
[Girl A] 'Bye.
[Girl B] See you.
Goodbye.
Azusa.
Azusa!
Japanese doll.
Oh. Hey Jun.
Are you okay?
Hey listen, I'll be heading up
to the Jazz Club room now,
try to keep it together.
See ya.
You'll be going up to
the music room now, right?
Yeah, and you?
My family is going to be
celebrating my sister's
graduation,
so I have to go home and get
ready.
Celebrate, huh?
Yeah of course! It's a happy
occasion!
I'm kinda sad that I won't get
to wear the same uniform as my
sister anymore, though.
It seems like no matter what,
she's always been one step ahead
of me, leaving me to catch up.
But that's not her fault,
she is my big sister.
Ui...
Sorry. I'll start being
happy for them, too.
Thanks!
Excuse me.
Can I also get a picture
with the Light Music Club?
Course you can!
You bet! Stand here in the
middle!
Thank you so much.
I heard that you're all going to
the same college next year.
So you guys can keep on
playing music together.
Your shows at the school
festival were always...
Really funny!
[Yui] Funny?!
[Ritsu] What?!
[Yui] Not "awesome" or "really
good"?
Later!
Bye-bye!
Going on a graduation trip?
[Yui] Sawa-chan sure is
popular...
Do you think she'll come up
to the club room later?
She'll come for tea.
For sure.
[Nodoka] Well I need to stop
by the student council office.
[Yui] Okay!
[Ritsu] See ya, Nodoka!
[Tsumugi] See you!
[Mio] See you later!
Nodoka-chan!
Hey, why don't we walk
home together today?
I'll text you later!
Thank you, ma'am!
How can I erase that?
Thanks Mugi-chan!
[Tsumugi] Sure.
(door opens)
Hey! Azusa!
[Azusa] Sorry.
Well you see, I thought it'd be
nice if I made tea for you
today.
[Tsumugi] How thoughtful.
[Ritsu] Azusa! Over here!
[Ritsu] Listen, Azusa...
[Azusa] Yes?
About the future of
the Light Music Club...
It'll be fine!
But we never took the time
to find anyone to replac-
Really, I mean it, it'll be
fine.
I'll do whatever it takes to
get new club members.
I promise that no matter what
I'll never let the club be
disbanded!
Azusa-chan...
More importantly, I have
something I want to give you,
I feel like I've never thanked
all of you properly.
So I wrote a thank-you note
for each of you.
I kind of did it in a hurry
before rushing here.
Ritsu-senpai.
[Ritsu] Thanks.
[Azusa] Mio-senpai.
[Mio] Thank you.
[Azusa] Mugi-senpai.
[Tsumugi] Thank you.
[Azusa] Yui-senpai.
Oh wow thank you.
So then, can we read these now?
Sure, go ahead.
[Yui] Oo, I wonder what mine
says?
[Mio] Thanks, Azusa.
You're welcome.
I want to wish you,
congratulations on your...
Is something wrong?
[Mio] Azusa?
[Azusa] Please don't graduate...
[Ritsu] Azusa?
[Azusa] I won't yell at you for
leaving the club room a mess,
and for doing nothing
but drinking tea all day.
Just please don't graduate.
Azu-nyan!
I'm sorry... I just-
What happened to your forehead?
Oh did you hurt yourself?
You run into something?
Yes... I know it's your
graduation...
And we should celebrate.
Hey it's okay, I have a bandage!
Done!
I'm really sorry... I promised
myself that I wouldn't cry...
I wanted to look happy for you.
[Azusa] I'll be fine.
I'll keep the Light Music Club
going, I promise.
And I have Ton-chan, so I wont
be...
I want you to have this!
[Yui] It's a picture of us from
a long time ago. When we were
freshmen!
We were younger then than you
are now.
Here! This is for you, too!
It's a flower with five petals!
Just like us, Azu-nyan!
Way to upstage us with
a bunch of cool stuff, Yui!
She's right you're making us
look bad!
Azusa, we have a song
that we want you to hear.
Not you, too, Mio!
And we wrote it just for you,
Azu-nyan!
That was supposed to be my line,
Yui-chan!
[Yui] Azu-nyan.
Come sit over here.
(testing instruments)
Wow, you guys really
aren't very good!
[Azusa] But I want to hear you
play again and again anyway.
Encore!
[Yui] Why don't you join in
on this one, Azu-nyan?
Sure!
[Yui] You came here to
listen to us play!
One, two!
(closing song, "NO, Thank You!")
The Light Music Club?
The third floor?
Maybe the problem is that you're
overthinking it too much.
She's right.
Take a more organic approach and
just write down whatever pops
into your head.
What really? I don't think I've
ever heard anyone practicing
on the third floor.
For the visuals,
I envision a music video,
with you guys playing in
an old warehouse or something.
You make the camera angles
super high! You'd look
totally awesome!
That's it!