[Principal] I want to give
a warm welcome back
to all the students of
Sakuragaoka High School.
The long summer vacation is now
over and a new school term is
once again upon us.
I hope that each and everyone
of you had a busy and
productive summer.
It gives me no end of joy to see
all your tanned, energetic faces
here once again.
The experiences that you gain
during high school are
irreplaceable and,
are crucial to your development
in your productive citizenry.
(opening song,
"Utauyo!! MIRACLE")
Summer vacation went
by way too fast this year.
[Ritsu] It's not like you
didn't have a lot of fun.
Yeah, well I suppose but...
How could you spend
the time goofing off?
How about college exams?
We did manage to make a lot of
wonderful memories, though.
Natsu Fest and
the summer festival!
Going to that dagashi store!
Good morning!
Hi, everyone! The second term
is starting! Isn't it exciting?
I'm blind!
Second term means the big school
festival! And our live show!
Ah, so that's what you've got
yourself so wound up about.
We have to work hard to get
ready for it.
But first we've got this.
[Yui] A marathon?!
Has its hour at last
come again this year?!
That's it!
I've decided that I'm going to a
college that doesn't have
marathons ever!
Actually, your average college
doesn't have marathons.
I'm off to school!
Oh!
Yui-chan, good morning.
Good morning!
Take care of yourself today.
Okay! I'm cutting it kind of
close, so I have to go!
You have a good day!
[Yui] It's time to eat!
[Mio] Huh? Mugi, you're having
eel and rice for lunch?
[Tsumugi] I'm trying to build up
my stamina to get ready for the
marathon.
Yeah, you're plenty strong
alright,
but you've never really had much
in the way of stamina. You know?
That's great! You're trying to
overcome your shortcomings. Good
for you, Mugi!
Yeah, and I've been training
hard by sprinting at top speed
from home to school every
morning!
That's not training, Yui,
that's just you oversleeping
everyday!
Well I guess you pretty
much got me there...
I don't understand. Why do we
have to run a whole 42.195
kilometers?
You realize, It's not a full
marathon. It's 4.5 kilometers.
It involves a whole bunch
of running either way,
so it's basically the same
thing.
[Sawa] If you really hate
running that much,
why not consider wearing one of
these to make it more fun for
you?
The rest of you, too.
Never gonna happen.
Those would be HARDER to run in.
If the entire student body ran
around town wearing stuff like
that,
this would be the last year
the marathon is ever held.
Yes, that's it! You're right,
Azu-nyan! That's a really great
idea!
What are you talking about?
I was kidding. It was a joke.
Your tea's ready, Sawa-chan!
Just what I've been waiting for!
[Yui] It's black...
[Sawa] Is it black sesame?
Unique flavor...
What's this invigorating
fragrance that's wafting,
through my mouth that's
so redolent of the sea?
To prepare for the marathon,
I thought we should build up our
iron reserves to help fight off
anemia,
so I brought blancmange
made with kelp and hijiki!
[Sawa] Perhaps the normal kind
might be better next time?
[Ui] Sis! This pair looks really
comfortable to run in, doesn't
it?
Wow Ui-chan, you're right!
I'm not sure I want to spend
my whole allowance.
(car door closes)
It's Sawa-chan!
[Yui] After all this time,
I finally get to ride in your
car!
Ma'am, were you out doing
your shopping too?
No, I'm on the clock.
I was buying some things that
the school needs for the
marathon.
We teachers are splitting up all
the work.
Sports drinks and lots of paper
cups...
If you're working,
is it okay to give us a lift?
Yes, it's fine. I was just about
to head back to the school,
while driving over the marathon
course, so I could check it out.
[Yui] Mochi and azuki beans?
[Sawa] After the marathon, we'll
be making oshiruko red bean soup
in the schoolyard.
Red bean soup?!
You wouldn't believe the work
goes into this marathon.
There's shopping to do,
checking the race course,
filing for permits with the
police...
Back when I was a student in
high school,
I thought that the teachers had
it so easy because they didn't
have to run in it.
Maybe I can muddle my way
through if there's gonna be red
bean soup at the end.
Well we made the course
a lot tougher than last year's,
so I'm pretty sure
you're gonna hate us for it.
You start here in the business
district.
There'll be pastry shops
with their sweet smells,
clothing boutiques
with their vibrant colors,
and general stores with
their shelves full of cute
items.
You'll have to overcome
the temptation to window shop
to put the bus loop behind you.
You'll cross the bridge,
pass the residential district
and,
find the vast expanses
of the rural district.
It's a leisurely one-way road
with heads of rice heavily laden
with seeds.
But after that looming up
ahead is Heartbreak Hill,
a demoralizing monster,
a living hell coming or going.
A literal heartbreaker, a battle
against your own limitations!
But if you're not victorious,
all will be lost and
you'll never reach the finish
line!
As soon as you conquer
this trial and crest the hill,
you'll be greeted by the sight
of the checkpoint at this park!
You'll need the little strength
you have left for the final
stretch!
The finish line is
so close you can taste it!
It's like that.
Look, we're close to our house.
[Yui] She doesn't have
to be THAT eager about it.
It's not that she's eager,
it's that you've already given
up.
What's wrong, Ui?
One of those mochi got
mixed in with our all stuff.
I can't believe the race is
tomorrow...
Hey, how many snacks
are we allowed to bring?
A marathon isn't a school hike,
you know!
Well, I'd feel a lot more
motivated
about the race if they'd just
let us take a snack with us.
We can't have snacks,
but the teachers will have red
bean soup ready and waiting for
us after the race.
As much as I love red bean soup,
it stinks that we have
to run all that way,
and make it all the way
to the finish line in order to
get any.
You're eating mochi with your
rice?
Please tell me you don't think
eating sticky, stretchy things,
will make you tough and
tenacious!
Of course not, Sawa-chan
gave it to me yesterday.
When I tried to return it, she
said I should go ahead and eat
it and do my best.
It's real hard!
You know, the race would have to
be called off if it were to rain
tomorrow.
That's it! That's what we'll do!
The marathon will be cancelled,
and we'll have a red bean soup
contest instead!
[TV] There's no percent chance
of rain tomorrow everywhere.
It'll be a beautiful day,
perfect weather for hanging the
laundry out to dry.
What are you doing there, Big
sis?
I'm making a string of
upside-down terabozu dolls.
Granny Tomi from next door said
that if I did this, it would be
sure to rain.
[Yui] Why?
[Nodoka] On behalf of all
athletes,
we hereby pledge to follow
the rules of good sportsmanship,
and will see this race through
to the very end in a fair and
open manner.
Student Council President
Nodoka Manabe, Year 3, Class 2.
[Teacher] All right, everyone!
On your marks!
Get set!
(bang)
Wow, they're all taking
this pretty seriously.
I'm going on ahead, okay?
Everyone here's trying way
too hard, even Nodoka-chan.
Yeah, and it's not like there's
a big prize or anything for the
winner.
The way these things normally
go, you'd have a bet going with
the Judo Club,
and the winner would get the
loser's club room for the rest
of the year.
Really?
No, nothing like that happens.
It's a nice day out,
so let's just think of it as a
class hike!
Even though there's no snacks...
But if we run really slowly
and finish dead last then...
(cheering)
I don't want that kind of
attention!
All right, come on people!
Put some effort into it!
Not you, too...
Still, it's kinda nice to leave
campus on a school day,
and not get not get into
any trouble for doing it.
And the weather is nice.
You know, you're right.
[Jun] Wait!
Let's run... a little...
slower...please...
Sorry!
(panting)
Mio-senpai!
I thought you we're running
with my sister and the others?
They're further back in the
pack.
Was my sister actually
running when you saw her?
Well I wouldn't exactly call it
running,
but she's with the other girls,
so I'm sure she'll be all right.
[Jun] Mio-senpai!
Why don't you and I run
together!
Uh, sure.
Well you're full of energy
all of a sudden.
You were at death's door a
second ago.
No I wasn't! I-I was adjusting
my pace, that's all.
Let's move!
[Ui] You know, there's something
really fun about being outside
in the fresh air,
when we'd normally be in
a classroom having lessons.
[Azusa] And the weather's nice,
too.
[Jun] Yeah.
Hey, that bag is cute!
[Azusa] Let's come here
and check it out on Sunday.
Look at that cake! It looks
delicious...
[Yui] Oo, kitty!
Oo, I've never seen
that kind of juice before!
It's brand new? And it's only
$1!
[Machine] How may I help you?
That thing talked!
(bark)
Even if she had all the strength
and stamina and endurance
in the world,
could there be a girl less cut
out for running a marathon?
[Tsumugi] Mio-chan!
[Yui] I'm so glad you waited
for us! Thank you, Mio-chan!
Thank you!
K-ON!
Drink up. The finish line is
just a stone's throw away now.
Hang in there.
Thank you very much, Ma'am.
We're almost at the
checkpoint, Jun-chan!
I'm sorry...
I can't go any farther...
Go on without me...
(Yui panting)
I'm so pooped...
You shouldn't be wiped out
this fast.
An arts and culture...
club like ours...
is at a... big disadvantage...
in this race...
We're no match...
for the Track and Field Club...
or Softball or Judo Club!
Come on the Light Music Club has
its own way of doing things.
Why don't we just act like were
a light music club and try
running to a rhythm?
Hey, you're right!
We should run this marathon
while singing a song!
[Ritsu] Whenever I look at you,
I feel my heart go doki doki.
[Yui] You're going too fast!
[Ritsu] I get so giggly
and wiggly-
Huh? "Fuwa Fuwa Time"
was too tough for you?
How about we try
"My Love is a Stapler"?
[Yui] Why is it this way?
On nights like this my mind...
My mind begins to stray...
[Tsumugi] I can't run and
sing at the same time!
Mugi's down for the count, too?
I guess we could just
sing in our heads.
Yeah that's it!
(gasps)
What's up?
I forgot the lyrics!
You what?!
The go "La la la" or whatever
you need to do and fake it!
I can't!
Save yourselves!
Don't worry about me! Leave me!
It's okay, just go!
I'll survive!
Forget about singing, then.
Why don't you try thinking of
something else you really like
while you're running?
I think I might be able
to do that!
(happy humming.
Oh, you! I couldn't possibly
eat another!
What the heck is she imagining?
Something pleasant...
[Ritsu] And she's trying
too hard.
I've got it!
What if we sang a song?
And we're back to square one!
What's the matter, Mio?
Some lyrics just came to me.
(gasping)
"Heartbreak run,
my heart just shatters."
"Pounds so hard
it'll soon be tattered."
[Ritsu] Is this that "runner's
high" deal I've heard about?
[Mio] "Or is it all because
of the marathon?"
[Girls] Fight on!
[Ritsu] Hang in there, Mugi!
We've officially conquered
Heartbreak Hill!
It's level roads
from here on in!
[Ritsu] Hey!
Oh, you're Azusa's friend.
Um... don't tell me...
it's Sasaki, right?
Suzuki, dummy.
Yeah, yeah, you're Jun-chan.
That's right.
So, you chose to stick with the
rest of the Light Music Club,
Mio-senpai?
Hey, uh, where's Yui-senpai?
Huh?
[Mio] She's vanished?
[Ritsu] She's lost at sea?
How do you get lost at sea on a
road?
Yeah, well, I hate to say it,
but with Yui, it's entirely
possible.
Ah.
[Jun] Ma'am! There's an
emergency!
What's wrong?
Yui! Are you around here?
She couldn't have simply
wandered this far off the main
road, could she?
I doubt that even Yui would
mistake
a tiny game trail in dense
forest for the marathon course.
Wait a minute, where are we?!
[Tsumugi] Ah! Have we gotten
ourselves lost at sea, too?!
Did we underestimate the perils
of a race?
But no body needs to worry!
I've got our survival needs
covered!
There are edible mushrooms
there! See? Now look right
there!
Those really pretty ones with
the red and white polka dots...
those are the ones that
are highly poisonous.
[Sawa] Hey you three, what
are you girls doing up there?
Heh.
Have you found Yui yet?
[Tsumugi] No not yet.
Up until right around here,
we were running together,
singing a song to keep us in
good spirits.
What she said! And that's
when Miss Akiyama here,
began composing
a bunch lyrics in her head!
[Mio] I couldn't help it,
great lyrics were just coming to
me.
Anyway, we better split up
and look for her.
I'll look over there. Now get
going!
[Ui] Jun-chan is taking a long
time...
I wonder what's keeping
the Light Music Club?
Good work you guys.
There's red bean soup waiting
over there.
You should go and
get some before it's all gone.
Sure.
Should we go ahead and eat
without them?
I guess so.
[Nodoka] Oh and just
one mochi each, all right?
[Both] Right.
[Ui] Jun-chan! Over here!
Something has happened!
Yui-senpai vanished somewhere
along the course!
What!?
Yui!
It's no use. There's no sign of
her.
[Girl 1] You know,
now that you mention it,
there have been a lot
of UFO sightings in the area.
[Girl 2] Hey, why don't we use
that as our research topic for
the school festival?
You don't think Yui got herself
abducted by aliens, do you?!
[Ui] Hey, everyone! Excuse me!
[Tsumugi] Ui-chan!
Have you guys found my sister
yet?
No, I'm afraid not.
We've looked everywhere
and can't find her.
Jun-chan told me what happened.
She disappeared right before
you got to the park checkpoint?
Yeah. At least, that's when we
all first realized that she was
missing.
Then I think we'll find her
hanging around somewhere in that
area.
It's standing!
[Granny] Your tea stem
is standing upright.
That means that something
good will come your way today.
[Yui] Really? But you know that
terabozu weather doll charm,
you told me about didn't work
the way you said it would.
[Granny] Oh, it didn't?
[Yui] I really should get going
now!
Yes, I suppose you should.
In that case, eat this
before you take off.
You need energy to run your
hardest.
(doorbell rings)
Oh, another visitor?
[Ritsu] Do you have any idea
how worried we all were?!
And here you are, eating
chestnut jelly cakes without a
care in the world.
I'm sorry!
I tripped and skinned my knee
just as Granny was passing by.
And she cleaned it up and
put a bandage on it,
and then she invited me in for
tea, so I took a little break...
Were you hurt badly?
[Yui] Nah, its just a little
scrape.
Thank goodness it wasn't
anything serious.
I'm just amazed that
you knew to look for her here.
The course passed close
to our neighborhood,
so I thought there was good
chance she might be here.
I'm sorry for the trouble she
caused.
I'll go on ahead to the school
now and let everyone there know
that she's okay,
and that nothing really
bad happened to her.
You guys just take your time
finishing the race. Okay?
That's one level-headed girl.
[Yui] Let's take her up on her
offer and take our time reaching
the finish line.
And one that screwed up.
We're gonna be dead last now,
that's for sure.
That doesn't bother me.
No way... they'll all stare at
us, and I'll die of
embarrassment!
[Ritsu] What's this I see?
You tripping and getting even
more fans?
[Mio] Spare me the twisted
predictions!
[Ritsu] Ow!
It's great news that
Yui-senpai is okay, huh?
Yeah, it really is.
Hey look, they're back!
I knew it,
everyone's watching us!
It's okay, let's just
focus on crossing the
finish line together!
[Azusa] Senpai!
If you don't hurry,
they're run out of mochi
for the red bean soup!
What's up, Yui?
No mochi?
(reverse slow-mo)
It's that mochi!
I ate that mochi with my lunch,
so that means that they're
going to be one short for
the red bean soup!
And that means the person
that finishes last won't
getting a mochi!
What?!
Mochi!
Hey, wait for us!
The loser won't get any mochi?!
[Mio] I don't want to
finish last!
Wait!
They're all running faster
all of a sudden.
I wonder why?
Where is she getting
all this power from?!
Mochi!
Mochi really means
that much to you?!
I am NOT going to finish last!
Uh oh.
Hey, are you all right?
I drew attention to myself!
It's great that they
had enough mochi,
even for the person
who finished last. Right?
Well of course that makes
perfect sense.
They wouldn't have bought
exactly the same number of mochi
as there are students.
Now would they?
Thanks to Yui's crazy idea,
I ended up...
My prediction came true!
I'm real sorry, Mio-chan.
Still, it was kind of fun,
wasn't it?
Yeah! I could get used
to running marathons!
[Both] Hey! Speak for yourself!
I'm really sorry.
Hey does anyone want to have
seconds of soup? There's still
plenty of mochi left.
The ones that are left
are for the teachers.
Speaking of teachers,
where is Sawa-chan?
Hey Yui, are you there?
Where are you?
There isn't going to be
any soup left!
I am so hungry...
(closing song, "NO, Thank You!")
[Jun] Okay, I want you
to write down
what the Light Music Club
does on a typical day.
[Azusa] Alright.
[Azusa] This is bad! Really bad!
When did I get infected with
their slacker attitude?!
[Mio] Give me a minute, okay?
I really want to change
my strings.
[Tsumugi] I decided to try
writing a new song for the
school festival!
[Azusa] Sitting here doing this,
it almost feels like we're
a real Light Music Club,
doesn't it?
Today is the day I'm going
to make my comeback!