Saber!
Made it.
You're safe.
Saber!
I'm back.
But how?
Who are you?
Better yet...
What are you?
On-site investigations are still ongoing,
but ask the police arrived this moring,
Shirou.
Shirou?
Oh, sorry. What's up?
I was...
I was just thinking about Saber.
She left in a hurry.
Oh, yeah.
But now, since she's gone,
you aren't going to have to go
out at night anymore, are you?
So you won't be in danger like you were.
Isn't that right?
No.
You've got it wrong.
I wasn't going out at night to help Saber.
Saber was the one that was trying to help me.
In fact,
I might have to start going out more often.
But you know,
I'd feel a lot better if you didn't keep
waiting up for me at the front door.
I'll be fine.
That's right. It's not over yet.
I still have a fight to finish.
Right here in this city.
New City, Central Park.
Ryuudou Temple.
What exactly is that damn shadow thing trying to do?
And what's it got to do with Zouken?
Is he controlling it?
Or maybe he's exploiting it.
I should talk to Tohsaka.
What the...
Okay, little more.
Hey there, Big Brother.
You're still alive!
What's your name? Will you tell me?
Please tell me, Big Brother.
Uh, okay.
My name's Shirou. Shirou Emiya.
Shirou! Shirou, Shirou!
Good.
Hey, what are you doing?
Aren't we enemies, Illyasviel?
You can call me Illya.
And masters only fight against
each other at nighttime, you know?
I just wanna have a little chat with you.
Um, wait a sec.
After attacking me the way you did...
Now you wanna chat?
Attacked you? That wasn't my fault.
You're the one who recklessly jumped
into the fight even though you're so weak.
If I wanted,
I could easily kill you right here and now.
Since you don't have Saber to protect you,
it would be over in an instant.
And besides,
I've been waiting a long time to get this chance.
Don't I deserve a chat?
So, you said you live in that castle in the forest?
All alone?
Sella and Liz live there, too.
As a matter of fact,
I had to sneak past Sella on
my way out to come see you today.
You should feel honored!
Uh, all right.
Okay, I've got another question for you.
Does the name Kiritsugu Emiya mean anything to you?
Illya?
No, it doesn't.
Never heard of him.
Ever.
I'm going home now.
Wait!
Emiya?
Uh, Tohsaka.
Great timing.
I wanted to talk to you about something myself.
Why do we have to talk here?
We go to the same school.
Archer, could you make us some tea?
Huh? What do you mean, no?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Jeez.
Fine, I'll do it.
No way.
Isn't that...
What are you doing?
Come on. Let's figure out our game plan.
I should probably start making dinner.
Why didn't you tell me that Sakura
had a fever in the first place?
Because you wouldn't stop talking
long enough to give me the chance.
It's open.
Sakura?
Are you awake?
Emiya! Oh, great!
Shinji!
Let Sakura go!
Don't worry, Sakura. It's okay.
I promise I'm not going to kill Emiya.
I just want him to suffer.
Make him feel a little bit of pain, that's all.
You're going to fight Rider.
If you can survive that, then I'll let her go.
Rider, get him.
You're a fool.
If you came here to fight...
You shouldn't have done so all by yourself.
Try harder, Emiya!
It'll be terribly dull if you kick the bucket too easily.
Endurance rewards the true victor.
Excellent.
But no more going easy on him.
Kill this pathetic charlatan right now!
Shinji, please stop!
Sakura.
Shirou?
How?
It was Magecraft.
Rider!
Kill that bastard now!
T... Tohsaka?
But why?
Emiya and I have a mutually beneficial arrangement.
Because of that, we happened
to be working together all day.
You used Sakura as bait.
That was a big mistake,
'cause that makes you my enemy.
Sakura.
Sakura, Sakura, Sakura, Sakura, Sakura, Sakura!
Why do you care so much about what happens to her?
I'm the Matou that became the master here!
Stand up, Rider!
Damn you!
You can't!
Rider, you can't! It has to stop now!
Sakura. Emiya, get down!
You're kidding.
Rider?
She's still...
Very good, Rider!
Now end it by slaughtering them all!
Uh, hey! Rider!
Yes, of course.
The Matou blood line is run too thin.
It's impossible for a mage to
be born into that family now.
I assumed Zouken was the one who summoned Rider,
and he was lending her to Shinji,
but the real explanation was far simpler.
What do you mean?
The way things stand for the Matous,
only one person is fit to become a master.
The rightful heir of the Matou name...
the true mage of this generation...
the one Rider serves. Right, Sakura?
You mean Sakura is a master?
A command spell transfer.
She used that to force Rider to follow Shinji's orders.
That's how he became Rider's so-called master.
Hey.
Meanwhile, you lost your authority as her true master,
which made you an ordinary mage.
What the hell?
What are you people looking at?
After all, the Matous created command spells.
That's how your trick was possible. Right, Sakura?
Hey!
Look over here!
We haven't finished yet.
One more time, Sakura!
Give me control of Rider one more time!
Why are you acting like a goodie-goodie all of a sudden?
You have one more command spell.
Use it already!
Shinji, if the last one is used, Rider will be set free.
At that point, none of your orders will work.
Your books will burn up, and that'll be it for you.
Using borrowed command spells to control a servant
means you were never really a master to begin with.
Shinji.
That's right.
I knew that. I knew that.
I knew that! I knew that!
I've always known that I'd never
be fit for the role of a master!
And that's why you have to do it.
You have to kill them in my place, Sakura.
Kill them all.
Shinji, I can't.
We have to stop this.
Did you already forget the promise you made me?
You said that you weren't going to kill Shirou.
So please, no more!
Fine. Have it your way.
That's how you wanna play it?
Then die.
Sakura!
Shirou!
No, don't look at me!
Sakura.
Damn.
It doesn't look like she can control it.
Get out of here now.
Once she feeds on your mana, there's no going back.
I need you to stay out of the way.
Rider, hold back.
Your master has lost all control.
If this keeps up she'll run
out of mana and self-distracted.
She can't run out of energy as long
as she takes in more than she's losing.
So, no matter who your master is,
it doesn't change the fact that you're a rotten bitch!
A barrier?
Stop it!
I'm begging you, Rider, to stop!
Please.
It's not why I summoned you.
I didn't want anything like this.
I cannot adhere to that command.
Your life takes priority over everything else.
No way. Mystic Eyes of Petrification?
Tohsaka!
Look out!
Sakura...
Sakura!
Emiya.
Are you all right?
Tohsaka.
Oh, good. You're finally awake.
I've just finished administering
treatment to the Matou girl.
Sakura? How is she? Is she all right?
Calm down.
Rider helped us bring her here.
Kirei, could you give us an update?
I wouldn't say her condition is stable,
but her life's been spared for now.
Hang on a second.
Your magic crests.
What happened to them?
Using them all was the only means
I had to treat the girl successfully.
You used all of them?
And there's something else I think you need to know.
She has crest worms?
What the hell are those?
One could opt to think of them as living magic circuits.
Once a crest worm sinks its teeth into a subject,
it penetrates every last inch of their body,
voraciously devouring their spirit from within.
It pierces through the skin
using its mucus as a lubricant.
Finally it begins to feed by stimulating
then decomposing the brain's pleasure center.
Therefore,
any woman swarmed by such creatures
will find themselves completely violated.
Both her mind and body will eventually be destroyed.
Sakura Matou has experienced just s...
That's enough!
I felt it was prudent to provide a thorough explanation.
As long as these crest worms remain inside her body,
her spirit... the very essence of her
life... will continue to be sucked away.
Ultimately, her life will be forfeit.
You said her treatment was successful.
Not entirely.
They've been there for 11 years.
If we pry them all out by force,
that, too, would mean her death.
If you truly wish to eliminate them all,
that's a task that can only be
accomplished with the Holy Grail.
Tohsaka.
It's my job to protect Fuyuki.
I'll take care of her.
Take care of her?
You're going to kill Sakura Matou?
Yes.
Mages that can't control their
own powers can't be allowed to live.
She's a lost cause. A master gone mad.
Despite the fact that biologically
speaking, she's your little sister?
She's your sister?
The Tohsakas... my parents-originally had two children,
but mages only pass their craft to one child.
I was the chosen successor for our family.
But the Matou... or Makiri-bloodline had run thin.
So they decided to adopt Sakura
and make her their successor.
So...
By blood, Sakura and I are sisters.
Even though neither one of us has
ever described the other that way.
Hold on, Tohsaka.
If that's true, then you can't...
If I leave her alone in the state she's in,
that's going to happen again.
But next time to innocent bystanders. Entirely at random.
So I don't have a choice.
I have to kill her.
I guess you win, Sakura.
So here. This is for you.
This is the second time.
The second time someone dear to
me gave me something so special.
Where is she?
I've gotta find her before Tohsaka does.
But when I do find her, then what?
Good evening to you, Shirou.
I thought masters fought at night.
They do.
But you're not a master anymore.
I know everything there is to know.
Rider's master has fallen so there are only two left.
And now you're hoping to save Rider's master,
but you can't find her, right?
Shut up!
It's okay to cry, Shirou.
Illya, you're not mad at me?
Of course I'm not.
I'm on your side, Shirou.
You're on my side?
You asked me about Kiritsugu.
I lied. I knew him.
To be honest,
the whole reason I was born was
so that I could win the Grail War,
but my own personal objective
was to kill Kiritsugu and you, Shirou.
However, if you say you're trying
to protect someone dear to you,
I admire that.
So therefore, I'm on your side now.
It's only natural to protect someone you love.
Wouldn't you say?
I know all about love, you know.
I don't have a home now.
There's nowhere left for me to go.
Sakura.
Shirou.
It's you.
Hey there.
Come on.
Let's go home.
You've still got a cold, remember?
I can't go back.
The stuff in that vial, it wasn't a poison.
It's more like an elixir that
sort of heightens the senses.
Just a few drops... that's all it
took for me to completely lose control,
and I ended up hurting you.
You didn't hurt me at all.
Just look at me. I'm fine, aren't I?
I'm the Matou family mage,
and I've been hiding that from you.
I did the same.
I'm a master, after all,
and I didn't tell you.
The reason I spent so much time at your house
was 'cause I was too scared to stand up to my grandfather!
I said I was there to help you
but I was lying the whole time!
All this time, I've always known the truth,
that I'm not the kind of person
who deserves to be by your side.
So every day I kept on telling myself,
Starting tomorrow I'll pretend
I don't even know him, and...
I'll ignore him when we pass each other in the halls,
and after school I'll act like he's a complete stranger.
I'll just walk back home all by myself
and I'll forget about everything... all of it.
But I couldn't make myself do that!
It was more terrifying to me than
the time I put a knife to my wrist.
I was scared of lying to you
but I was also scared of telling you the truth.
Everything in my life was so scary!
I couldn't take a single step forward.
I didn't have any idea what to do!
And I didn't wanna give up my time with you.
That idea was what scared me most of all.
Because for me...
for me, that was the only thing I had.
The only thing that held any meaning to me.
Someone I want to protect.
Someone who's dear to me.
I'll do whatever I can to dry her tears.
Since nobody else will punish her when she's in the wrong,
she has to do it herself in order to atone.
But I'll take her by the hand
and I will lead her out of the darkness.
Even if no one will forgive her, I will.
It's okay.
If you won't forgive yourself,
I'll do it for the both of us.
So quit your crying.
I know all your terrible secrets now
and I'm still here.
That's not enough.
What happens when I lose control of myself again?
Next time I might do something I can't take back.
So where can I go?
Where does someone like me belong?
This is your home, Sakura.
Always.
I can't.
Because I...
I'm not a virgin, Shirou.
The first time it happened was a long while ago.
But it didn't stop there.
Ever since then,
I've been constantly violated by things I can't explain.
I don't deserve your protection!
But you'll get it, no matter the circumstances,
even if I have to stop you from taking your own life.
I'll protect you, Sakura.
Shirou.
I will become a hero of justice for you alone.
You can't do that.
If you do,
then I'm going to end up hurting you.
I'll hurt you in the end.
Let's go home.
Hello, Sakura.
big sister?
I mean, Tohsaka.
Shirou Emiya.
If you're going to keep on sticking to your beliefs,
that's fine.
The results should be obvious.
However, if you stray onto a different path,
Shirou Emiya will have no future.
Make that mistake and you'll lose everything.
You must be tired.
Why don't you get some rest?
Uh, okay.
What's wrong?
Sakura?
You don't have a fever, do you?
You were out in the rain a long time.
No, it's not that.
I don't have a cold.
It's just that my mana is running a bit low.
Oh.
Well, is there anything that I can do?
I don't know.
I guess...
Do you want to...
Never mind. I'll be fine.
If you could just let me drink a little bit of your blood?
Uh, sure.
Will that be enough?
Yes.
DO you feel better?
Okay, that's good.
So, um, goodnight.
Night.
I can't. I've gone too far already.
I can't corrupt him like that.
Sakura, can you start the soup stock?
Of course.
What about the spinach? Can I help with that?
I say we dress it with sesame today.
All right, pass me some eggs.
Here.
Thank you for the food.
This is nice.
It's been a while since we cooked together.
Yeah.
Go ahead and eat.
It's okay. There's no need to be shy.
No, thank you.
Servants do not require nutrients like you do.
Oh, really?
Saber ate food with us all the time.
I'm not suited for mannerisms such as these.
Oh, I get it.
No problem.
Let's talk strategy.
I'm gonna help Sakura win,
so she can use the Grail.
Sakura, I think it's best if you stay inside till then.
It's too dangerous.
You could run into Zouken.
I'm inclined to agree.
That said, how do you intend to
defeat a powerful mage such as him?
I think we should work with the
other masters, if they're willing.
But who?
Who else is even left at this point?
Tohsaka and Archer, Sakura and Rider,
Zouken's still got Assassin working for him,
then there's Illya and Berserker.
Are you sure it's all right?
Yeah.
But, uh, make sure you stay inside the house, okay?
You're not regretting this, are you?
I can't have regrets.
I've come too far for that.
Rider, if things get too dangerous
out there, bring Shirou home.
You know, Sakura...
It's fine to be wary of the old man,
but I think the one we really
need to worry about is that priest.
Oh, yes. He is a problem.
I won't argue with you on that.
Although, there's nothing to be afraid of,
because no matter what,
he'll never be able to beat me.
Good.
Shirou!
I got it.
I just had to keep him here all the time.
If he can't leave,
then he won't ever be in danger anymore, will he?
That's weird. What did I just...
I can't remember.
This is tougher than I thought.
Does it want me to follow it?
Where'd it go?
Why'd it stop here?
You're as cowardly as your master.
That makes you the perfect pair.
It feels as though you have no intention of fighting us.
Do you really value your life that much?
Yes. I thought that was obvious.
My only desire is immortality.
Just look at this body.
I'm a walking corpse-rotting, stinking...
and my mind is slowly deteriorating along with it.
You can't even begin to comprehend the indescribable
pain of decomposing while you're still breathing.
There's no human in existence who doesn't fear death.
If it meant I'd be given eternal
life without all this pain...
I'd gladly kill every single person on this planet
one by one.
I'm disgusted by you.
Have you really lost yourself that much...
Makiri?
Don't you remember what our greatest desire used to be?
Don't you remember the miracle we
were fighting so hard to achieve?
Remember what it was all for.
Why did we strive to attain these inhuman capabilities
without giving up our human bodies?
That's quite the speech, coming from a mere puppet.
They taught you how to imitate your ancestors very well.
But I'm afraid play time is over.
Now I... Zouken Matou-will finally
claim the Einzbern's Holy Grail.
No! Berserker!
Tohsaka.
How did...
Oh Emiya, I never thought you'd
come up with the same idea as me.
Impossible!
You have to get out of there!
If that thing gets you, you'll never be able to come back!
The score has been settled.
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Don't let all this effort go to waste.
Take care of the Einzbern girl.
Berserker!
Illya!
You're a dick, you know that?
Berserker.
I'm your opponent.
Leave them out of it.
Archer.
I'm counting on you.
It's over.
A Cursed Boundary Layer.
No heroic spirit could fight that,
which means that at this point,
you're no more than the weak phantoms of this forest.
Berserker!
This isn't good.
Berserker.
No!
Berserker!
It can't be.
No!
My task is complete.
The rest is in your hands.
How generous.
I suppose I owe you one.
Saber!
Illya!
That's far enough.
You are unnecessary.
You can't finish off this boy
without resorting to an ambush?
So pathetic.
You again?
How are you still standing?
Who's to say?
Archer!
Get moving!
If that thing catches you, it's over.
We can talk later.
Now get out of here!
You decided to take Illya's hand.
Keep her safe until the end.
Let's go.
How?
How can you still move?
Isn't that obvious?
The thing is, I'm not a legitimate
heroic spirit like the rest,
and since I'm not pure like them,
a little corruption doesn't affect me as much.
In other words, I'm a heroic
spirit as twisted as that shadow!
That was fantastic, Archer.
You can return to spirit form.
Now, let's hurry up and get going.
Look out!
Oh, no.
Archer!
You can't!
Hurry up and get out of here, morons.
It's an incredible amount of energy!
This is real bad!
Tohsaka, run!
I am the bone of my sword.
Steel is my body.
I have created over 1,000 blades.
Rho Aias.
Shirou.
No. No, please!
S... Shirou!
Shirou.
Shirou!
Guess this is the end.
Take care, Tohsaka.
Have you gone mad?
Do you know what will happen to you if you do that?
There's nothing to think about.
If I do nothing,
there'll be two bodies to bury.
This way, at least one of them will survive.
I'm home, Sakura.
Oh, yeah. My arm.
You don't need to worry about it. It's nothing,
Okay? It's just a scratch, really.
I know it looks bad because of all the bandages
but it's not that big a deal.
Honestly, I promise.
Oh, while I was out, I ran into Tohsaka.
She gave me a hand.
We've agreed to a ceasefire.
Oh, and this is Illya.
I'm sorry to surprise you with company, but...
Sakura?
Can you move that arm?
No.
Figured as much.
Transplanting a limb from a
servant to a human is unheard of.
Shirou, if you do move that arm even once,
Archer's magic circuits will activate,
but your body won't handle it.
The power will overwhelm you,
and you'll collapse from the inside.
So then, these bandages...
They're a seal.
Thank you for everything.
W...What are you thanking me for?
I'm only here because we're
working together to defeat Zouken
and because it's convenient for me to keep her close by.
Just as I thought.
You're worried about Sakura, too.
I'm telling you, that's not it.
Besides, if I hadn't become a master myself,
we probably never would have even
known each other in the first place.
Hmm. Actually, you'd be surprised.
If I'm being completely honest,
you may not have noticed me,
but I've known about you for quite a while now.
I think it was about four years ago.
Anyway, this boy kept trying to do
the high jump over and over until sunset.
I happened to walk by.
Clearly, the idiot was never going
to pull it off, but he kept jumping,
and I was the bigger idiot 'cause I kept watching.
Personally, when I realize what
I'm trying to do is impossible,
I accept it and give up.
I guess I'm just cold like that.
But then again, mages always are.
I'd always dismiss it. Oh, well, it's fine.
I didn't need that impossible thing.
But then I saw someone who
seemed to be exactly the opposite.
It was an eye-opener for me.
Don't take that, too.
That's my memory.
Don't take it.
Maybe if I take this off, my arm will be back to normal.
Holy shit.
This is...
This isn't good.
Shirou.
We need to talk.
I have a question for you.
It seems Sakura's happiness depends
entirely upon having you by her side.
That is all she wants and wishes for nothing else.
My wish is for her continued survival.
Truthfully, I'm rather fond of her.
Shirou, can you tell me you're on Sakura's side?
And will you stay there no matter what comes to pass?
Shirou.
Sakura?
Oh, yeah. You're running low on mana, huh?
Okay, come on in.
Let's see.
Where did I leave that box cutter?
Um, Sakura?
Tell me, Shirou.
I need to know.
Why are you trying to protect me?
Because I...
I belong with you. I wanna be by your side.
I'm protecting you 'cause I need you.
Life without you isn't something I can imagine.
Do you mean I'm like family to you?
Or do you mean you wanna be with me as a girl?
Sakura, what I mean is I'm in love with you.
Then make love to me.
Or maybe... maybe I'm too impure for you.
Just look at me. I know I am.
I simply step inside your room
and I'm overwhelmed with desire.
What's wrong with me?
Even when I'm by myself, I can't stop wanting this.
I... I can't think of anything but you, Shirou.
I'm so... so disgusting.
No, you're not.
You're not disgusting at all.
You're beautiful, Sakura.
Oh, Shirou.
I... I couldn't take it.
I got so scared.
When big sister was alone with you, I thought...
I was afraid she was gonna take you away from me.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I'm sorry.
Shirou.
Sakura.
I love you, Shirou. So much.
It's time for a blessing.
A blessing?
What do you mean?
Another Holy Grail is just about to be born,
and I welcome it.
That vessel which is responsible for
creating all the evils in the world,
forged by humanity, yet desired by none.
So why should it even exist?
If the grail has the answer,
why not search for it instead
of looking for the answer myself?
See what I mean?
Soon I will know the truth,
and if God himself should
consider this question blasphemy,
then I shall stand before him and ask it once again.
For I will give up my soul, if I must.
Since you're letting me stay here,
the least I can do is make us all breakfast.
Um, excuse me.
I'm gonna see if Tohsaka needs any help.
Uh, hey, Sakura?
Yes?
If you want, with Tohsaka?
I wonder, what should I make today?
Hey, Sis. I'll wash the vegetables, okay?
Okay, thanks. That, um...
Is it too weird being around me like this, big sister?
No, there's nothing weird about it at all.
You know, Illya, I was thinking,
do you think that my room would be a good place?
What are you talking about?
Secret weapons.
I thought we might need to have
one or two of them up our sleeves.
That arm has memories.
It contains knowledge about the Einzberns.
I suggested to Tohsaka there might be
something useful inside that could be worth a look.
I personally have no interest in
what Kischur Zelretch left behind.
Then again, it's possible his so-called treasure chest
might be pretty.
That was weird.
Shirou?
I just, um... thank you. Thank you so much.
I've only ever been able to watch her from a distance.
Never in my wildest dreams did I think there'd be a day
when I could call her big sister.
So you didn't have any interaction with
her at all after the Matou family adopted you?
None.
We knew we were sisters,
but only as a concept.
It wasn't really real for either of us.
In fact, we tried our best to
avoid each other most of the time.
I was afraid if she ever found out about my Magecraft,
she was going to hate me.
Why would she hate you for magic?
Because of the Matou technique.
It's entirely based on stealing from others.
That's all we do,
and we never give anything back in return.
Sakura, do you hate the Matou's Magecraft?
I don't know. The teachings were certainly strict,
though compared to you, I think
my training's a walk in the park.
I watched you one night.
You were working so hard. You kept on pushing yourself.
There were so many moments I thought I
should do something to try to stop you.
Your workout looked dangerous.
It was making me nervous.
It was like... like you were stabbing your own throat.
That's how it looked.
Even though no one was there telling you to do it,
you just kept on going and you were all by yourself.
That's why out of all of us,
I'm sure you're the strongest.
It has nothing to do with Magecraft.
It's because you're so determined and pure at heart.
I've always known since the first day we met...
That no matter what happened,
Shirou Emiya would never betray anyone.
You bastard!
This is all your fault, Emiya!
Why?
Why won't... why won't anything happen?
And now for our top story.
The bodies of four possible murder victims were
found in Central Park in the New City District tonight.
Look at that.
Some of these weeds have turned black.
That means the shadow did this.
Do you think Zouken's controlling it?
I don't know.
I doubt Zouken would leave evidence like this behind.
I can't taste anything.
He's so warm.
It's all right.
I can still feel this.
I wish this moment would last forever.
Flip flop and off I go.
My clear head sways to and fro.
Bless what the nitty-gritty in this beautiful meadow.
A shiver and a tremble and a big go, go.
A song and a giggle and a big go, go.
Like paper balloons, my limbs roll around.
Just tumbling and tumbling across the ground.
Huff and puff, away I'm blown.
That's when I'll be fully grown.
Go, go. Go, go. Go, go.
Squeak, squeaking voices come for me.
Cackle, cackle, cackling full of glee.
I don't like them.
What's so funny?
Skritch, scratch, they're far too loud.
My tummy rumble grumbles for a candy cloud.
You're working hard, huh?
I told you you should die before it's too late.
Twinkle, twinkle. So pretty.
Your grace period is over,
and trust me, this is mercy.
Oh? You're still breathing, huh?
It seems your shadow isn't the
only thing about you that's changed.
Did you honestly think you could make me kneel for you?
Damn you!
I can't believe it.
You've gotten it.
Did you see that?
Shirou!
Get up and come with me.
It happened around 10:30 tonight.
A wide-spread blackout centered
around the New City Station.
We're told the police have received multiple
incomprehensible reports about neighbors disappearing,
missing family members and people
suddenly and inexplicably vanishing.
Sakura!
Hang on.
I'll go get the first aid kit.
Saku...
Just ignore it.
Don't look.
Don't even think about how much it looks like her.
This morning the body count continues to rise,
now totaling over 60.
No estimate yet for how many have gone missing,
but roughly 40 buildings were effected.
How's Sakura?
She's alive.
At least.
What is it? Something wrong?
Sakura's body.
At a glance it appears to look just fine,
but under the surface, her muscles are shredded.
No question.
At some point, Sakura was dead.
I don't have any idea who did it to her,
but it's quite possible the pain
destroyed her brain as well as her body.
We need to defeat Zouken and
that shadow as soon as possible.
Let's get ready because we're running out of time.
Shirou, I'm worried.
'Cause what if Zouken and the
shadow aren't what we think they are
and are completely separate problems?
What are you going to do then?
Good morning. Am I still talking to Sakura,
or someone else?
Where in the world did you get a soul like that into you?
I know you don't have Assassin or Rider yet,
but you're already full?
That's hard to believe.
Sakura, do you understand what's going to happen to you?
No.
What's going to happen? Tell me.
You will die. Nothing can save you.
I'm back!
Better late than never, huh?
Uh, hey!
Shirou, are you here?
Who's she?
Ah, jeez.
Where the heck has he disappeared to now?
Especially when you're so sick.
Oh! Oh, sweetie, no! Don't hurt yourself.
Shirou said he was going to protect me no matter what.
Oh.
But...
I'm sorry.
But it's all my fault.
His dreams will be shattered 'cause of me.
Why's that?
Because I'm a...
Well, because I'm a bad person.
Even so, you know Shirou will help
you atone and show you how to do better.
Besides, you wanna change all the
bad things about yourself, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Then there's nothing to worry about.
And Shirou's dream is to
become a hero of justice, isn't it?
So it only makes sense there's
someone he wants to protect.
But doesn't that mean he should protect everyone?
Oh no. Not if he's trying to be like Kiritsugu.
In fact, he probably should have someone special.
Kiritsugu played favorites.
I mean, he was only human, after all.
Even once he started calling this place home.
That man did a lot of traveling all the time.
He went overseas a lot.
Right up until he wasn't able to move anymore.
I'm sure it's because there was
someone he desperately wanted to see.
Not being able to see someone you care about,
it's unbearably painful.
Even for a hero of justice.
So please.
Do him a favor and stay by his side.
All right, Sakura?
Are you a traitor?
Will you betray yourself, who you used to be?
Hey.
No, stop.
If that's what you intend to do...
...you've lost.
Leave her alone!
No.
No way.
It can't be.
Shirou Emiya, correct?
My lord mage would like a word.
Well, you're here even sooner than I expected,
young child of Emiya.
Zouken.
I've got one thing to say to you.
Release Sakura right this minute.
Release her, you say?
I guess that's one way to put it.
Listen to me, boy.
I called you here because I have a favor to ask.
I'd like you to exterminate that shadow for me.
What do you mean?
Isn't that thing on your side?
Don't be silly.
You honestly think I have the
means to communicate with it?
If last night's any indication, I can't even calm it down.
Oh, right. Of course.
I suppose it would be prudent for me
to tell you what exactly the shadow is.
To put it bluntly,
that thing is the contents of the Holy Grail.
The will of the gate we call the Grail is overflowing,
and that will is the shadow.
I don't get it.
Gate?
I asked for you to kill the shadow,
but that task is not an easy one.
However, killing the gate
shouldn't be much trouble for you.
It would sense my presence or that of the Tohsaka girl.
Servants would be wasted. Nothing more than food.
No. Stop it!
Ten years ago I found a fragment of the Grail.
I planted it and I've been
nurturing its growth ever since,
but the only one who can kill
the Holy Grail of the Matou...
That's enough!
Surely you've noticed, haven't you?
The resemblance between Sakura and the shadow?
She's merely a doll that does nothing but exist,
to die at the hands of the man it loves.
It'll be happiest this way.
Time has run out.
Once Sakura loses what's left of herself,
the Holy Grail that's lain dormant
in her subconscious will emerge.
The catastrophe of ten years ago will then repeat itself.
Or if you truly wish to save her,
you need to endure until this
war has reached its expiration.
If previous examples are any
indication, that's about four more days.
What do you think?
Can Sakura last that much longer?
She can!
She's stronger than you think she is!
Perhaps, but what about
everyone else who lives in this city?
Last night's little feast may have been enough
to keep it all filled up for the time being,
but come tomorrow, it will be hungry again.
How many days will it take before every
last human being in this city has been devoured?
Do you understand?
Vanquish evil to save the rest.
If you wish to carry on Kiritsugu's legacy,
then only Sakura Matou is your true enemy.
Sakura.
Are you awake yet?
Yeah.
Good morning, Shirou. How are you?
Hey, Sakura.
When this thing is all over,
is there anything you wanna do?
I don't know, Shirou. Not that I can think of.
I mean, as long as I can be with you,
it doesn't matter what we do.
In that case,
how about we go on a trip somewhere together?
Where would you wanna go?
I think I'd like to go look at cherry blossoms, maybe.
All right.
That's a promise.
I'm trying to have a happy dream
while my heart is frozen.
Someday winter will pass
and spring will come again.
And when it does...
We'll see the cherry blossoms.
Yeah, when spring comes.
Hi, Shirou.
I'm Sakura Matou.
This is for you.
This is the second time...
Someone dear to me gave me something special.
Shirou.
I wish this moment would last.
Shirou. Shirou. Shirou. Shirou.
Shirou...
Will you betray yourself?
Yeah.
Yeah, I will.
Thank you for everything you've done, Shirou.
You've given me more than words can say.
And thank you, big sister.
Being able to call you that made me very happy.
Miss Fujimura, I wanna thank you, too.
But I can't keep my promise to you.
I'm sorry.
Rider, thank you for not killing Shirou.
Sakura.
My last command spell.
Please, Rider. For me.
I will stop Grandfather. I have to.
I know it's too late
but I can't cause any more trouble
than I already have.
Good morning. How are you...
Well. Hello, traitor.
You took your sweet time coming home, huh?
U... um, Shinji, I, uh...
Here. Hold onto this for me.
Nothing dangerous.
Beautiful.
You amaze me, Sakura.
Someday you might even surpass Tohsaka.
What are you...
Don't be so full of yourself.
After all, you're just my puppet.
I must have made another mistake.
That's why he does these things to me.
But it's okay.
Just put up with it for a while. Same as always.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
Sakura.
Stop!
Never again, Shinji.
Leave me alone.
My heart is Shirou's!
What the hell?
I see he's got you tamed even better than I thought!
No!
Hey, what's the matter? Don't be shy.
Why does it always end like this?
Come on!
That question's always plagued me.
I've harbored this anger so long.
I don't understand why the entire world hates me.
It hates me so much.
Yeah.
I have to tell Emiya about this.
About how you begged... pleaded for me
to have my way with you over and over.
I'll tell him about everything!
About every single time we fucked!
I wish this person would disappear.
Hey, Shinji?
Sakura!
I told you, remember?
That I'd become a hero of justice for you alone.
So get ready, 'cause I'm coming for you.