[TOMOE]
Hey, Kyosuke.
[KYOSUKE]
Tomoe.
[TOMOE]
I heard a rumor.
Is it true you're
running Stride again?
You there?
[KYOSUKE] Yes, but Honan
is the only place for me.
[TOMOE] I had a feeling
you'd say that.
Anyway, I'm back in Japan and
I'd love to catch up with you.
We should hang out sometime.
Who knows?
Maybe I can convince you
to change your mind.
I'll keep in touch. Later.
[HEATH]
It's over.
After a week of torture.
The wait for
End of Summer.
Is now over!
[HOZUMI]
Yay!
Whatcha gonna do?!
All of a sudden I've
got a serious case
of déjà-vu, you guys.
It's time to determine
which high school team
is the best in East Japan.
We'll be competing against three
other schools in the finals.
[door opens]
[DAN]
Is everybody here?
[RIKU] Whoa, what's in that
giant envelope you got there?
The registration documents
for the final tournament.
The first race is a
non-elimination time trial
to determine the pairings
for the final event.
[RIKU] Okay, so we're gonna
be running in the afternoon,
that's cool.
Let's see who we're
racin' against.
Kakyoin High School from Miyagi?
You ever heard of them?
[AYUMU]
Nope, I can't say that I have.
They definitely weren't
in last years' top eight.
In fact, now that
I think about it,
they weren't even
in the top 16.
Maybe they're a brand new team.
Then this'll be an easy win!
[DAN]
Yudan.
[HOZUMI]
Taiteki?
[AYUMU]
Kinmotsu?
Kyoteki!
[HOZUMI, AYUMU] How do you keep
coming up with this stuff?!
Guys.
They mean the same
thing, chill out.
It doesn't matter where
they ranked last season.
Teams go through a lot
over the course of a year.
They can rise or fall
significantly in that time.
You all should know that
better than anyone,
look at how far Honan
Stride has come.
Mr. Dan's right, why worry
about our competition?
Let's just focus
on training hard
so we can crush it
at the finals.
Right on, man!
[NANA] This is the competition
that inspired me to join Stride.
I still can't believe I
get to be a part of it!
[RIKU] It's late, why don't
you let me walk you home?
Uh! Are you sure?
I thought you and Takeru
raced home every night?
[RIKU]
He'll get over it.
Besides, I'd feel
like a total jerk
if I left a young lady
all alone at this hour.
[NANA] Uh. Good work today,
Takeru! Be careful going home.
--We'll See you tomorrow!
--[phone rings]
[NANA]
Great, where'd I put my phone.
Hello?
[JOE]
Hello, Nana.
Uh. [gasps]
Hi Dad!
How've you been?
[JOE]
Good.
And what about you?
How's school?
Great!
Thanks for asking.
So is this your new number?
Wait, Dad?
Here you go, please sign...
[NANA] I just realized you're
not calling from the US.
[JOE] No, I arrived
in Japan this morning.
I'm not in Tokyo though.
[NANA] How long are
you gonna be here?
I'd love to see you
before you head back.
[JOE]
Actually, I'm here to stay.
I've taken a job at
a high school in Sendai.
Yeah?!
[JOE]
Look, the phone's so impersonal,
I'll give you the details
when I see you.
You know, you should
transfer here.
Oh, I dunno Dad,
this is really sudden.
And I like the school
I'm going to right now.
[RIKU]
You comin', Nana?!
[NANA]
Uh. Sorry, I gotta go.
The bus is here.
I'll talk to you later.
Was that your dad
who just called you?
[NANA]
Yeah, it's been a while.
He's been living in the US.
When you introduced yourself
and said you were
living with your uncle,
I assumed you'd lost your folks.
[NANA]
No, just my mom.
She passed away
when I was little.
I see.
Yeah, It hasn't been easy,
but Dad's back in Japan
and this time he's staying.
[RIKU]
Awesome! I'll bet you're happy!
Yeah!
[CROWD chattering]
[HEATH sighs] Riku and Takeru
should be here by now.
[HOZUMI]
Where are they?
Uh. Heh, heh.
Speak of the devil.
[RIKU, TAKERU panting]
Dang! He beat me!
[HOZUMI]
Did you race to the airport?
[TAKERU]
Didn't plan to.
[RIKU] We ran into each other
and it just kinda happened.
But brainiac here went
the wrong direction.
I never said that I
knew the way here.
[RIKU] But you were
running so confidently!
Who does that when they don't
know where they're going?!
[NANA laughs] You were lost
and racing at the same time?
[RIKU] Yeah, an easy trip to the
airport turned into an ordeal.
I ate breakfast but
thanks to four-eyes
I've already
burned it off!
You have horrible
fuel efficiency.
[stomach growls]
[NANA]
Uh? I almost forgot!
I made you guys some onigiri!
You're the greatest, Nana!
Holy cow.
[HOZUMI, AYUMU gasp]
It's a staple of youth!
A school girl's
handmade onigiri!
Please have some, Mr. Dan.
I made enough for everyone.
Oh, no thank you.
I had my breakfast this morning.
[stomach growls]
Uh, Honestly, I've
already had my share--
[stomach growling]
[BOTH gasp]
[TOYA chuckles]
Thank you Miss.
This has been
a crazy day for me.
My flight was late
coming in from Frankfurt
so my team left without me.
I was hoping I'd have time
for breakfast but no such luck.
Your team? Wait a minute,
you're not attending the
EOS tournament, are you?
[TOYA]
Don't tell me you're going, too?
Yes!
What a small world!
My name's Toya Natsunagi.
I'm gonna be the Relationer for
the Kakyoin High School team.
[gasps] You're kidding me!
I'm the Relationer
for Honan High School!
I'm Nana Sakurai.
Same position
and everything!
[NANA] Wait, so whaddya
mean by gonna be?
Believe it or not,
I'll be meeting my team
for the first time in Hokkaido.
Really?!
You've never met your team and
you guys are competing at EOS?!
[TOYA]
Yep, that sounds about right.
I'm super excited!
[CROWD cheering]
[NANA] Oh, wow!
Check out all the people!
This is perfect.
Not too hot, not too cold.
I'm really diggin'
the north's tempernance.
[AYUMU, HOZUMI laugh]
Okay, it's not a real word,
but you get what I'm sayin'.
[RIKU]
I figured the final tournament
was gonna be off the chain,
but I wasn't expecting all this!
Who knew Stride was
so friggin' popular?!
[TAKERU]
You're overreacting.
[RIKU]
No I'm not, you buzz-kill!
What's with all
the big dudes here?
I mean, they're not super ripped
but they're still massive.
Think they're third years?
[HEATH]
It's not that they're big,
it's that you guys are puny.
You're a lot skinnier than them.
I'm mean, you're tall but thin.
Whatever, we'll
catch up eventually!
Yeah, we're still growing boys!
Um. I think it's time you
face reality, Hozumi.
Whaddya mean?!
I'm staring reality straight
in the face right now!
Be patient, your body will grow
whenever it feels it's ready.
Perhaps it's waiting
for the perfect time
to awaken a hidden power
deep within you.
[HOZUMI]
Uh. Is he trying to cheer me up?
He's right.
In fact, I can see it now!
As Hozumi strives to do his
best in the final tournament
the sleeping dragon
within him...
...awakens!
This power!
Even Bruce Lee's got
nothin' on me!
[yells]
[yelling]
Nope, that's Kenshiro from
"Fist of the North Star".
[HOZUMI laughs, grunting]
[AYUMU]
No, that's Chan.
Now look what you did,
you gave 'em material;
they're gonna be
goofin' off for hours.
--[AYUMU] Still Lee!
--[KYOSUKE chuckles]
[AYUMU] That's Chan again!
[HEATH] Whoa, does he seriously
think that's funny?!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Saisei High School
pulls off another
perfect Relation!
And now their final
runner, Reiji Suwa,
is making his way
toward the finish line!
[VOICE 8A]
End of Summer!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Saisei wins!
Not only that, but with
near record timing!
At five minutes
and 5.48 seconds,
they're only 0.8 seconds
away from our all-time record.
[HEATH]
Now that was one heck of a race.
Aw, man!
I really hope that we get a
chance to run with Saisei again!
Yeah, me too, it's fun!
Next time, we'll win.
Heh. You kids are gutsy
for a bunch of first-years.
[ANNOUNCER 8AA] And now,
introducing the two teams
who'll be running
this afternoon!
First we have
Kakyoin High School!
[RIKU] Check it out!
That's our opponent!
[ANNOUNCER 8AA] This team
has been completely overhauled
thanks to their new coach!
And while he may
be new to Kakyoin,
he's definitely not
new to Stride.
Meet the man responsible
for making it the popular
sport it is today.
[ANNOUNCER 8AA] Let's hear
it for the father of Stride.
"King" Joe Sakurai!
[gasps]
Oh, wow!
I had no idea "the king"
was back in the game.
He's a Stride legend!
No way.
Is Something wrong?
That's my Dad.
[BOYS]
Huh?!
[AYUMU] I thought the shared
last name was a coincidence.
You didn't know your dad
is the "King of Stride"?!
No, I swear!
Look, I know it sounds crazy,
but he never really talked
to me about his work.
You're so defensive.
I'm sorry.
I'm just a little freaked
out 'cause I didn't know.
I'll be fine.
[ANNOUNCER 8AA] Let's start
the team introductions
with Kakyoin's two
first-year members...!
[NANA] That's the guy
I met on the plane!
[AYUMU] They sure are
getting a lot of airtime.
Must be the team
to watch this year.
That would explain the hype.
Maybe so, but they seem
pretty sketch to me.
They ditched their old team and
recruited stronger runners.
[ANNOUNCER 8AA]
...Hajime and Ryo are best known
for their mind-blowing
acrobatics!
Here's a little trivia,
when we asked the twins
how they learned to do
all those crazy stunts,
they said they learned them all
while performing in the circus!
And now, Nampei Aoba!
Not only is he
Kakyoin's captain,
he's also the only
returning member
of the school's original team.
Will he be able to lead
his new teammates to victory?
And last but not least,
the shining star of
high school Stride...
Tomoe Yagami!
[RIKU gasps]
[CROWD cheering]
[HOZUMI]
Did you know about this?
Hey, Riku...
[RIKU] Eh. Uh, no,
I haven't talked to him.
I mean, I heard he was back
in Japan, but that's it.
[HEATH] What's wrong, bro?
Are you scared?
[RIKU] No way, man!
I'm just surprised, that's all.
Can't say I blame ya
'cause I am too.
I wasn't expecting to see him
here, much less run against him.
What are your thoughts, Kyosuke?
[KYOSUKE]
His presence means nothing.
I'm focused on one thing,
running for my team.
[TOYA]
Fancy meeting you here...
Hey, Miss Sakurai.
[NANA]
Oh, hi, Mr. Natsunagi.
Good to see you again.
I can't wait to race
my new friend
and her team in the time trials.
This'll be fun!
Oh. Yeah. I'm looking
forward to it.
[TOYA] I don't mean to pry,
but is everything all right?
[NANA]
Huh?
You seem kinda tense.
It's got to be hard
for you to concentrate.
And your mind is noisy,
like an orchestra tuning
their instruments.
[RIKU]
This is it.
I just have to focus
and do my best today.
I can't let Tomoe distract me.
[AMATSU]
Just so you know.
There's no point in
even trying to race me.
I'm pretty much unbeatable.
[TAKERU]
Oh, really?
We'll just see about that.
I suggest you think twice before
you get an attitude with me.
Y'see, I'm not
like everyone else.
I don't run, I lead.
You can try.
[AMATSU]
Ha, ha. Yeah, right!
You may think you're fast but
you don't even know, fool.
Tryin' to one up me is
a waste of your time.
Why don't you go home while
you still have your pride?
I'm not just any
runner I'm the best.
Seriously, you look up the
word "fast" in the dictionary
and you'll find a picture of me.
[TOMOE]
Hey, Kyosuke.
It's been a while since we've
had the chance to run together.
[KYOSUKE]
Yeah.
I'm surprised you went
back to Honan Stride
after everything that happened.
[KYOSUKE]
We've made amends.
I've decided it's
where I belong.
[TOMOE]
Hm. If you say so.
[TOYA] It's not that
emotions are a bad thing.
You and your teammates are
all battling them right now,
but you have to
work through them.
And you have to do it together.
In my opinion, that's what
Stride's all about.
[MANNOUNCER 8A] Even though
it's only a time trial,
our next race features one of
the most anticipated match-ups
of the entire tournament.
Kakyoin High School,
led by the king himself,
Mr. Joe Sakurai will race
against Honan High School!
The king's daughter,
Nana Sakurai,
or shall we say "the princess of
Stride", is Honan's Relationer!
Yeah, That is what
Stride's all about.
I completely agree.
Nice, sounds like the
orchestra's tuned now.
Good luck, Miss Sakurai.
You, too!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the showdown is about to begin!
[NANA] It's inevitable that
my emotions will affect me.
I can't help it,
I have a lot of heart.
[ANNOUNCER 1B]
On your mark...
[NANA] We all do.
Every member of our team.
[ANNOUNCER 1B]
Get set...
[NANA] But right now,
we've gotta focus on the race.
We're gonna give it our best!
Watch out, Dad!
[buzzing]
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] And Honan
High School takes the lead!
Riku Yagami, younger brother
of Kakyoin's Tomoe Yagami,
Atta boy, Hajime.
Stay on him for now.
[HAJIME]
How dull.
[TOYA]
Okay, you're good to go.
Take the first left.
[NANA] Uh? Why's he sending
him the long way?
Nicely done.
Let's hit from the outside.
[HAJIME]
Understood.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Hajime Izumino shows off
his acrobatic skill, jumping
ahead of Riku Yagami!
Wait and see...
[RIKU]
What the--?!
How's he accelerating
like that?!
[NANA]
Riku's 1.2 seconds...
No, make that 1.5
seconds behind!
Okay, thanks.
[HOZUMI]
I've gotta try to pick up time.
C'mon, hurry, Riku!
[NANA]
All right, he's coming. Get set!
[RIKU]
Crap!
Why do I always end
up losing my lead?!
[HOZUMI]
Riku!
[RIKU]
I'm Sorry!
[clap]
[HOZUMI grunts]
[RYO]
Too easy.
[HOZUMI]
I won't lose!
[RYO]
He's so slow.
[HOZUMI grunts, panting]
[HOZUMI]
Here we go! I'm catching up!
Kay, that's enough, Ryo.
Time to push it.
[NANA]
Clear to pass on the right.
[TOYA]
Watch your right side!
Try on the left side!
[TOYA]
Left! Incoming!
[NANA] How's he know
what I'm gonna call?
[HOZUMI] There's no way
I can pass this guy,
but if I can stay
close to him...
Heath can pull ahead.
[RYO]
Analysis...
complete.
[HOZUMI gasps]
[NANA]
They did it again.
Their runner accelerated
toward the end.
I wonder, could they be
doing it on purpose?
[CROWD cheers]
[HEATH grunts]
[HEATH]
You think you're big shots,
but you guys're
just a pickup team!
All right, here's my chance!
He's on your left side!
Coming up on your left again!
[BOTH panting]
[NANA] Heath's actually
caught up to their runner.
If only he could pull ahead.
[TOYA]
Now Nampei!
Let's go!
[NAMPEI]
I've been waitin' for this!
[HEATH panting]
[NAMPEI]
Peace out, loser!
So I was right.
You're letting us catch up.
I'm sorry.
This is our team's very
first race together.
The guys said they wanted to try
a few things this time around.
[AMATSU] Man, this guy
is so freakin' slow!
I tried to tell him that racin'
me was a waste of his time!
He's gonna have to train
for a million years
to even come close
to my level of speed!
[TAKERU] This is what I've been
working towards my whole life.
I'm not going to
let you ruin it.
[TAKERU]
Amatsu, Ida!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Kakyoin's
final runner, Tomoe Yagami,
has made his way outside of
the arena with a huge lead!
At this point, there's no way
Honan could possibly catch up!
[TOMOE] We may not be
running for the same team,
but I'm still thankful I get
to run with you again, Kyosuke.
Now, let's make the most of it!
[TOMOE gasps]
[TOMOE]
Kyosuke?
[TOMOE] I thought we shared
the same drive and ambition.
But I guess I was wrong.
[TOMOE] You and Heath
are nothing like me.
[TOMOE]
I see it now.
What a shame.
[RIKU]
Tomoe's run.
It's so powerful.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
And we have a winner!
[CROWD cheering]
[TOYA]
Well, that's that.
[NANA]
Yeah.
[NANA] We're a lot
faster than we were
before the training camp,
but it didn't matter.
They still beat us
by a long shot.
[footsteps]
[TOYA] Uh. Oh, uh, my teammates
are here. I'd better go.
See you later, Miss Sakurai.
[AMATSU]
Nice work today, Toya!
[TOYA]
Nah, It was all you guys.
[NANA]
Daddy!
Did you watch me?!
I won the whole race!
I saw.
You ran like a pro
out there, Nana.
Stride's a lot of fun, isn't it?
Yeah! It's like the best
thing in the world!
[JOE] Good, 'cause
this is your Daddy's job.
[NANA laughs]
[JOE]
You're gonna be around it a lot.
[NANA]
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Listen to your grandparents
and be a good girl, okay?
I'll call you as often as I can.
Don't go.
Don't leave Daddy,
I promise I'll behave if
you take me with you!
I don't want you to go!
Come back!
I wanna go with you!
Don't leave me all alone.
Please, Daddy.
[NANA]
I can't believe it.
After all these years,
we're finally reunited.
Why'd it have to
happen like this?
[TOMOE]
Kyosuke.
I'm sorry I tried to
get you to join us.
I realize it was wrong of me
and I never should've
bothered you with it.
What do you mean?
[TOMOE] Back when you and Heath
and I were all on the same team
it just felt right, you know?
Almost as if our destinies
had been fulfilled.
I honestly thought
the three of us
had created the
ideal Stride team.
But now I know better.
Even though we worked
well together,
we never really connected.
Yes, we all wanted to win,
but we had different
reasons driving us.
So this is it.
I've gotta say goodbye, Kyosuke.
Dammit!
What's with the long faces?
Cut it out, you guys!
At least this was just
a time trial, right?
Woo-hoo!
We're still in the game!
Yeah! We'll go home, train,
and then crush 'em
in the final tournament!
[AYUMU sighs]
[DAN]
Kadowaki is absolutely right.
Don't dwell on this
loss start thinking ahead.
Find your weaknesses and conquer
them before the next match.
Understood?
[STRIDE CLUB]
Yes, Sir.
Where are you going?
None of your business.
[TAKERU]
There's no time to be depressed.
We have to get back
to our train--
[RIKU]
Shut up!
I don't wanna hear it!
You're just like Tomoe.
[door creaks]
[RIKU]
We always ran together.
More like, I was always
chasing his back.
[RIKU] I tried to catch up
to him but I couldn't do it.
I thought if I trained
hard enough,
then one day I'd
be as fast as him.
But I was wrong.
No matter how much I ran,
I could never catch up with him.
He was too fast.
I started to think that maybe
there was something wrong
with my brother.
Nothing stopped him
from training,
not even the pouring rain.
He'd run for hours soaking wet.
I thought he had some
kinda sick obsession.
How else could you explain it?
[TOMOE]
C'mon Riku, let's go running.
[RIKU]
No thanks.
[TOMOE]
Hey, What's the matter?
[RIKU] Nothing, it's just...
running with you isn't fun.
I don't wanna do it anymore.
You can't give up now,
you've got talent but y--
[RIKU] You've taken all
the fun out if it, Tomoe!
Look, I don't wanna
do Stride anymore!
I never wanted to.
You forced me.
[TOMOE gasps]
I understand.
I'm sorry I pushed it on you.
[TOMOE]
Riku.
[RIKU gasps]
[NANA]
Oh no, I forgot the onigiri!
[RIKU] Aw man, I was
ready to chow down!
[AYUMU]
Watch your back, Riku!
[RIKU] What?!
[HOZUMI] I don't think you
understand how desperate
Ayumu is to get his hands
on that delicious onigiri!
[AYUMU]
It will be mine!
Next on "Prinstride," "We all
run for the giant onigiri"!
[STRIDE CLUB]
Yummy!