[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 1A]
Just look at him go!
Yagami runs as
smooth as a river!
I've never seen anyone
move this fast before
and look good while doing it!
He's remarkable!
The cameras are
struggling to keep up!
[CROWD cheering]
[NANA]
Two hands slap together.
A relay so perfect,
it's as if they had no
doubt it would happen.
[NAN] How can two people
trust each other so much?
Hearts connected,
running like the wind.
There's no other team like them.
[NANA]
Honan Academy Stride!
Well, here goes.
The beginning of my new life
at Honan starts today!
Better hurry up, new kid!
You don't wanna start
the year off tardy, do ya?
[NANA] Huh?! Wait!
Don't close the gate yet!
Why should I wait?
Try being on time, young lady!
[NANA]
'Kay, I'm sorry! [pants]
I barely made it.
[RIKU grunts]
[TEACHER 1A]
Forget it, kid!
[panting]
[gasps]
[RIKU groaning]
[RIKU]
Safe!
[NANA] I hate to break it to
you, but I think you're out!
[RIKU groans]
[NANA]
Are you all right?
Oh, no, you're bleeding!
I'm fine. It's just a scrape.
[NANA] Still, you need
to take care of it.
Oh, wow. You're so nice!
[NANA]
Uh... Huh?
Thank you, Miss!
My name's Riku Yagami,
by the way.
And starting today
I'm a freshman here
at Honan Academy.
I hope I see you around maybe!
[RIKU]
I'm a big fan of yakisoba,
especially when you
put it in a bun!
But I like sports even more
than I like fried noodles!
I'm gonna kick butt at the
try-outs for the school teams!
Just watch me!
All done.
[CLASSMATE 1A]
Well, that was interesting.
[RIKU]
Yes! Way to win 'em over, Riku!
[DAN]
Next.
[CLASSMATE 1B]
Yes, sir!
I can't wait to get to know
everyone this year.
[RIKU gasps]
[RIKU] What's his problem?
I don't know him, do I?
[RIKU]
Ah!
Takeru Fujiwara.
[DAN]
Is that all you got?
[TAKERU]
Yep, that's it.
[RIKU]
Talk about a lame introduction!
I get the feeling this
guy's gonna be trouble.
Why does he keep staring
at me like that?
I'm Nana Sakurai.
I just moved here from Hokkaido.
Tokyo seems nice,
and I love the warm weather.
[RIKU]
Don't tell me he's stalking her!
Luckily, I'm staying
with my uncle
who doesn't live too
far from school.
I don't quite know my way
around town yet, but...
...I sure would love a tour!
[RIKU]
Oh, Miss Sakurai!
She's such a cutie!
[TAKERU growls]
[RIKU]
Oh, that creepy dude!
He's such a nut job.
[bell chimes]
Heh, heh. You can't
get past me.
[BOTH grunting]
[BASKETBALL CLUB 1A]
Uh?
Ah...
[RIKU]
Uh-oh.
Ah. Look at that guy.
I know.
Wow.
[BASKETBALL CLUB 1A]
Hey, man.
[RIKU]
Uh?
Listen, you wanna join our club?
[RIKU]
Yeah, sure!
As long as I'm allowed
to be in more than one.
Huh?!
[laughs] I wanna be involved in
as many sports as possible!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[NANA]
Uh.
It's the first day
and the clubs are hunting
for new members.
Pulling out all the stops
to attract fresh meat.
I mean, just look at all
these posters. Crazy, huh?
Uh... Hey.
[NEWSPAPER CLUB 1A]
Hm?
Do you guys know where I
can find the Stride Club?
I thought they'd have posters
up but I don't see any.
Stride Club?
Huh. Are those guys
even still around?
[NANA]
Huh?
[RIKU grunts]
Sorry!
[VOLLEYBALL CLUB 1A]
No prob!
Here!
My bad!
[BASKETBALL CLUB 1C]
Huh?!
[BASKETBALL CLUB 1B]
There's no way
he can catch up with that ball!
[RIKU grunts]
[groans]
Uh!
[BASKETBALL CLUB 1C]
He caught up to it.
[BASKETBALL CLUB 1B]
Nah, man.
He passed it.
Hey dude, interested
in joining our club?
Okay!
[VOLLEYBALL CLUB 1A]
Really?!
Yeah, I'm joinin' all the clubs!
[VOLLEYBALL CLUB 1A]
Uh.
Didn't see that one
comin', did ya?
What a waste, bro.
[VOLLEYBALL CLUB 1A]
You a first year?
What's your name and class?
Who, me?
I'm in class 1-C.
Riku Yagami.
[RIKU]
Mm.
Ah!
I'm outta here! [screams]
[TAKERU exhales]
[NANA] I wonder where
their club room could be.
[TAKERU]
Nana Sakurai.
Oh. Hi, uh...
You're Takeru.
We're in the same class, yeah?
[TAKERU]
Come with me.
[NANA]
Uh. Wait. Where are we going?
Whoa, this is it.
The Stride Club.
Wait a second, how'd you know
I was looking for them?
[TAKERU] Don't worry
about it. Let's go in.
[NANA]
Uh...
[HEATH]
Do-over!
[AYUMU]
Not happening.
[HEATH]
Ah... What?!
You gotta be kidding me!
C'mon man, please?
[AYUMU]
No!
I said no!
This is RTS!
Don't be such
a jerk about it.
Dontcha remember the
time I let you do it?
And what "time"
was that, pray tell?
Do you happen to recall
the year, month, day,
hour, minute, and rotational
position of the Earth?
[HEATH] Dude, your insults never
made it past the third grade.
[TAKERU]
They haven't noticed us.
[NANA]
No.
They seem pretty
distracted right now.
Wait, the Shogi Club?
[BOYS shouting]
[HOZUMI]
Excuse me.
[yelps]
[gasps]
[HOZUMI] Are the two of you
looking to join our club?
[NANA]
Well, yeah?
[HOZUMI]
Really?! That's awesome!
We're happy to have you!
I'm Hozumi Kohinata,
second year.
It's nice to meetcha!
[HEATH]
Get over here! Do-over!
[AYUMU]
No way!
[HOZUMI] Hey, guys!
We got new members!
[HEATH]
Oh, yeah? For which club?
[NANA]
Huh?
[AYUMU]
Your glare.
Your glasses.
Yes!
Shogi Club!
No, sir.
Denied!
No offense, but I came
here to join Stride.
[HOZUMI]
Ah!
Eh? Wait a sec,
you're Takeru Fujiwara
from Tsurugiya, aren't you?
Yep. That's right.
[AYUMU]
I knew I recognized you!
You're pretty famous in
the Under 15 category.
Can't believe you moved all
the way to Tokyo from Hyogo.
Oh!
--[HOZUMI laughs]
--[NANA] Huh...
Stride's off to a good start
now that we've got a big
name like you on the team.
That means you must be...
Uh...
[AYUMU] The first female
member of the Shogi Club!
No, sir.
Denied again!
Sakurai's here for the
same reason that I am.
Stride.
[HOZUMI]
Huh?!
[NANA] Uh! Oh, um.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Nana Sakurai.
Your Stride team is the reason
I moved here to Tokyo.
Just to go to Honan.
I'd love to be your manager,
if... you'll have me.
Of course, the more the merrier.
I'm Ayumu Kadowaki, second year.
I'm the "boss of bishops,"
the "keeper of kings,"
the president of the Shogi Club.
[NANA] 'Scuse me. Sorry, but,
we don't wanna play Shogi,
we came here for Stride.
Well, I'm the president and
captain of the Stride Club.
Heath Hasekura. A third year.
Doesn't matter which
club you wanna join,
'cause you're automatically
in both of 'em.
[NANA]
Uh. What do you mean by that?
[HOZUMI]
Here at Honan Academy,
clubs with less than three
members get disbanded.
Basically, if you join
one of our clubs
you're automatically
enrolled in the other
so nobody gets shut down.
[NANA]
Okay, I think I get it now.
So the three of you are...
[AYUMU]
That's right.
Whether you're looking
to join Stride or Shogi,
we're the whole club!
[NANA]
Seriously?
But I saw a video of Honan
Stride on the internet.
It's what made me want
to come to school here,
so I could join the club.
Check it out!
[HEATH]
Video?
[NANA]
Yeah!
You suck, Stride Association!
I hate you!
[HEATH sighs]
Well, then,
tell us what was so great
about this video.
[NANA]
It was amazing!
The first time I'd ever seen
Relations done at full speed.
[gasps]
[NANA] I can't tell you how
much I love Honan Stride!
[HOZUMI] Um, so the runners
you saw in that video.
Well, they're third
year students now.
Unfortunately, they're not
members of Stride anymore.
[NANA]
Huh?!
[HOZUMI] I know it's not
what you wanna hear
but we just don't
have enough members
to participate in a match.
On the other hand, all the
Shogi team needs is three.
Tell you what,
since you guys came all
this way just for Stride,
we'd be more than happy to
train with you, if you wanted.
[HEATH] If we can't compete in a
match then why bother training?
--[NANA] Uh?
--[TAKERU grunts]
[HOZUMI] Nana, you said you
wanted to be a manager, right?
Well, to compete, each Stride
team needs five runners
and a Relationer for
a total of six members.
Find us two more people and we
can start entering tournaments.
Make that three, Hozumi.
Don't count me. I don't
want any part of this!
I promise I can
find you two more!
There's gotta be other students
here who love Stride!
I just have to go
and look for them!
Good luck, nobody wants
to join Stride anymore.
I'll make it happen,
you just watch me!
There has to be someone
else at this school
who loves it as much as us!
[HEATH]
Uh...
[AYUMU shrieks]
[gasps]
[TAKERU]
Hm. Good calf strength.
--[AYUMU] Hands off!
--[HOZUMI] You noticed!
Yeah, we've been keeping
up with our training.
That way, the 'keeper of kings'
might actually be able to
make it through a match.
[AYUMU]
You lied to me! Traitor!
I thought we were training
to become the fastest
Shogi Club in the world!
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Listen, bro.
We had to trick you into
training, so that way,
when the time came, your body
would be ready for Stride!
[AYUMU] What have you done
to my once doughy physique?
You asked why you
should bother training
when you can't even
compete in matches.
And yet, you went
out of your way
to train a complete outsider.
[TAKERU]
Sakurai.
Uh. Yeah?
We came to this
school for Stride,
so it's up to us
to make it happen.
I promise that I'll find
you two more members!
And when I do, then we can be a
full-fledged Stride Club, right?
[HEATH]
Yeah, sure.
If you can make it happen
then I don't see why not.
You have my word.
[NANA laughs]
We only need one more.
[NANA]
Huh?
[PING PONG CLUB gasping]
--[ALL] Yeah!
--No way, man!
--That was my point!
'Kay, I'll be back soon!
[HEATH]
All right, where were we?
Wha--?!
Uh. Hey, did you...?
How many times do I have to tell
you not to break the rules?!
[HEATH] I tried to ask you
politely for a do-over!
[AYUMU]
Yeah, and I said no!
[HOZUMI]
Things are lookin' up, Heath.
[PING PONG CLUB]
Join us!
We need you on
the Ping Pong team!
You can be in all
the clubs you want!
[RIKU laughs]
Then count me in!
[ALL gasp]
Yagami.
Hello, Riku!
Heh! What's up, Nana?
Uh...
What are you doing
with this guy?
Hey, thanks again
for this morning.
I got some blood on this,
so I'm gonna have to
get you a new one.
Oh, no, you really
don't have to do that.
Listen, what's fair is fair.
C'mon, I gotta pay
you back somehow.
Okay.
Well, there is something
that you can do for me.
I could use another
member in my club--
especially someone
who's as fast as you!
Ya think so?
Then you can count me in!
I'd be happy to help you out!
[NANA]
You mean it?
Yeah, I love all sports.
Well, I take that back, all
of them except for Kabaddi.
[NANA]
Ka... baddi?
Yeah.
You have to say
"kabaddikabaddikabaddi"
really fast and it
makes me bite my--
[yelps]
[TAKERU]
Good legs.
Let's go.
[RIKU]
Uh... What was your name?
Like, Takeru?
So, uh. Are you also a member
of this club Nana's
trying to put together?
[TAKERU]
Obviously.
C'mon, let's take him
back to the others.
[RIKU]
Uh...
Okay, guys.
You wanna tell me
what club I'm joining?
[BOTH]
The Honan Stride Club.
[grunting, rumbling]
[RIKU]
Hey, let go of me!
[NANA]
Careful! Don't hurt him!
[RIKU]
Let go, man!
Here. We found one.
I said let go!
I'm warning you!
--[NANA laughs]
--[RIKU grunting]
He doesn't look too happy.
Does he? Did he agree
to join the club?
--Yes, sir.
--[NANA] Well...
[HOZUMI]
Huh.
[AYUMU]
You're killing me, Hozumi!
It's you.
Riku Yagami!
He's a Yagami?
No way, you've gotta be kidding!
I mean, what are the odds?
[HEATH]
No joke. It's crazy.
Destiny is seriously in motion.
[ALL]
Huh?
[HEATH]
I'm a man of my word.
Looks like we're back
in action, you guys.
Sweet, now that we've got
five runners, we're ready!
You're still counting me
in that number, aren't you?
Of course.
Why do you think I
kept making you do
all that training with us?
Tough break, bro.
Man, this sucks!
You guys tricked me!
[HOZUMI] All club activities
are based on deception!
[AYUMU]
Ooh, Sun Tzu.
Someone thinks they're smart.
[HEATH] All right, that's
enough! Play nice, you two.
Okay, so all we need
is a Relationer
and we can start entering
tournaments, right?
--Yeah.
--[HOZUMI] Uh-huh!
[TAKERU]
We have one.
[NANA]
Huh?
Who, me?
But, I don't know if girls
are allowed to be Relationers.
[HOZUMI]
Sure they are.
It's rare but I've
seen it happen before.
They're usually on
the best teams, too.
No way.
I never could've imagined
this would happen.
Me... a Relationer
for Honan Stride!
Hey, uh.
I'm not really
into Stride, so...
Uh? I don't wanna force you,
but you said you'd help.
Yeah, and I'm not
gonna let you down.
Besides, you're not the one
who's holding me against my--
Watch it.
You're getting on my last nerve!
[TAKERU] We came to Honan
Academy to join the Stride Club.
[RIKU] What does that
have to do with me?!
Let go! Seriously!
Cut it out!
'Kay, now listen up!
[CAT TOY]
Meow.
[HOZUMI]
Stop yelling!
You won't solve
anything that way.
Here's an idea,
how 'bout we settle this
with a friendly match?
[CAT TOY]
Meow.
[AYUMU]
Color me intrigued.
Please go on, kitty,
tell us more.
[HOZUMI]
All right.
I propose that we resolve
this argument once and for all
with a one-off Stride match
that'll determine
the fate of the club!
--[NANA laughs]
--[RIKU] Uh...
[HEATH] Hey guys, Heath
from Stride Club here.
Sorry for the short notice but
we're gonna have a race tonight.
Yep, you heard me!
Stride Club is back!
Thanks for your support!
[DAN]
Interesting.
[STUDENT 1B]
The Stride Club is still around?
[STUDENT 1C] It's gonna be
a two-on-two mini-match.
[STUDENT 1D] Why would anyone
wanna join a running club?
[STUDENT 1E]
Bring me some marking tape!
[STUDENT 1F]
We need more mats over here!
[STUDENT 1G]
Hey new kid, come help us out.
[STUDENT 1H]
Extra! Extra!
The Stride Club is back!
[STUDENT 1AA]
I'm gonna go watch the match.
[STUDENT 1BB] The older girls
told us not to mess
with the Stride Club.
[STUDENT 1CC] Yeah, but what's
the harm in watching? C'mon!
[FEMALE STUDENTS giggle]
[ANNOUNCER 1AA] The race
will begin in ten minutes.
During the match we ask
that you please refrain
from entering the
course perimeter.
If you must pass through,
look for a cheerleader with an
armband and ask for assistance.
[NANA]
Wow. Everybody's really excited!
[AYUMU laughs]
Crazy to think
our club's on the verge
of disbanding.
I mean, whenever
there's a match,
spectators come out in droves
just to watch it go down.
Since we race city streets
it kinda turns into a party.
Tonight we're only doing
a lap inside the school.
It's a lot shorter than
a real Stride course
but that doesn't mean
it's gonna be easy.
There are plenty of
drop-offs and sharp turns
that are gonna require some
finesse from our runners.
The most dangerous
part of the course
is probably the narrow hallway
that's being used
as the Takeover Zone.
You'll have to pay close
attention to the Relationing.
No need to worry, you just
have to trust your runner.
[NANA]
Right.
[ANNOUNCER 1AA] The race
will begin in one minute.
[HOZUMI sighs]
I'm starting to get pumped!
Hang on.
Don't you need your
glasses for the race?
No, I prefer to wear
contacts when I'm running.
[HOZUMI] All right, Takeru,
let's do our best out there!
[TAKERU]
Yeah.
[RIKU] I wonder.
Can Takeru pull this off?
What if he gets lazy and
keeps us from winning?
That would mean...
[HEATH]
Aw, man.
I forgot all about
the pre-race nerves.
It's been a while
since I had 'em.
I kinda missed it.
[RIKU]
Yeah, me too.
It's been a long time.
Okay, Riku and Takeru.
I hope you guys are ready.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 1AA]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we will now begin
the Honan Academy
Stride Club "Revival Race"!
[GIRLS]
Hey! Congrats, Heath- senpai !
Yagami!
Hold up, are they
assuming Stride's back
'cause they think
you're gonna beat me?
Sorry, kid. I'm leavin'
you in the dust.
Uh!
Get a good wind in your heart.
You know what I'm sayin'?
[ANNOUNCER 1B]
On your mark...
[TAKERU]
There's no way we can lose.
Not you and me.
[ANNOUNCER 1B]
Get set.
[TAKERU]
There's no way we can lose.
[ANNOUNCER 1B]
Go!
[CROWD cheers]
[TAKERU, HOZUMI panting]
[HOZUMI panting]
[TAKERU panting]
[HOZUMI grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[NANA] Wow, look at
Hozumi go! He's so fast!
Well yeah,
he's gotta keep up with
a famous Under 15 runner.
The Trickster of Honan's
gotta be at his best!
Get ready, Nana.
They're almost there!
Okay!
[AYUMU]
Heath, set.
[NANA]
Riku, set!
[exhales]
[NANA]
Three... two... one...
Go!
[RIKU grunts]
[HEATH gasps]
[RIKU panting]
[HOZUMI gasps]
Watch out, Takeru! You'll
overrun the Takeover Zone!
[RIKU grunts]
[NANA]
It's okay.
[RIKU]
I can.
[TAKERU]
We can.
[RIKU, NANA, TAKERU]
Connect!
[CROWD cheering]
[BOTH panting]
[gasps]
[RIKU panting]
[RIKU laughs]
[CROWD chattering]
Amazing!
[AYUMU laughs]
Hey, check it out, Nana!
Look at the time!
It's the same!
It's a tie!
D'ya hear that, kid?
--[panting]
--Good job.
I don't get it, senpai.
How come you're not
out of breath at all?
[HEATH]
You'll get there, rookie.
[footsteps]
[HOZUMI]
All right!
[RIKU laughs]
[RIKU]
You win.
This time.
[RIKU] On behalf of the
famous Yagami bakery,
I'm here to present
a new product!
Da-da-da-da! Behold!
[TAKERU]
Protein Bread.
[RIKU]
No, it's not!
[TAKERU]
I have faith that you can create
the most muscular
toast in Japan.
Next time on "Prinstride,"
"The Suspicious
Relationship Between
Natural Yeast and
Muscle Development."