[DAN] The Trial Tour
begins next Sunday.
Interested in knowing
your first opponent?
It's Mihashi High School.
[AYUMU]
Oh really?
Those ichthyomaniacs.
Every year, the Mihashi
High School Stride team
flies giant carp streamers
during Boys' day festivities!
Way to go!
You tell 'em, 'Mu!
[RIKU] Isn't that what
you're supposed to do?
[AYUMU] Yeah, but Mihashi's
are ginormous because they're
from Saitama which is
the number one manufacturer
of carp streamers in Japan!
[HOZUMI]
That's right!
You schooled them,
Prime Minister of Trivia!
The first match
of the Trial Tour
is gonna take place in Atami.
Whoa! No way. Ha! Seriously?!
Awesome! Atami's a
sweet hot springs resort!
[DAN clears throat]
Yudan Taiteki .
Remember, our focus
is the EOS trials.
This is Hasekura's
last chance to compete.
[RIKU, AYUMU]
Uh.
[DAN] We can't afford to slip
up like we did against Saisei.
[RIKU, AYUMU groan]
Aw, c'mon, you guys,
what's with the long faces?
You're bringin' the room down.
It's never too late
to turn things around.
[AYUMU grunting]
Yeah!
One failure will not defeat me!
All Shogi pieces move forward!
[HOZUMI] Right behind ya,
unbreakable Shogi-Strider!
[HEATH grunts]
Whoa, that was killer, man!
Thanks. That's called the Vault.
It's one of the most basic
moves used to clear obstacles.
Ooh, my turn! Watch!
Oh, wow!
Dang! Did you see that?
He hopped right over that
bar like it was nothin'!
[AYUMU chuckles]
That particular move
is what's known as
the Monkey Vault.
It's challenging because
it requires the runner
to jump higher
than other Vaults.
There's the Kong Vault,
the Dash Vault,
the Pop Vault, the Gate
Vault, the Sky Vault,
the Reverse Vault, the...
[RIKU] Why don't you get out
there and show us one, senpai?
[gasps] Uh, yeah sure,
that's a great idea!
I'd be happy to!
What better way is there
for you to learn?
[AYUMU inahles, exhales]
[AYUMU gasps]
[RIKU]
That was pretty solid!
Too slow.
[RIKU, NANA]
Uh.
Jumps like that
won't win matches.
You don't have to be
such a jerk about it!
[HOZUMI]
All right! Nice one, Takeru!
That was great but
it'd look cooler
if you pull your knees
in when you jump.
As long as it's
fast and accurate,
I couldn't care less
whether it "looks cool."
[HEATH] Heh. Always has a
smart-ass remark, doesn't he?
[TAKERU] Stride is a speed
sport, not the circus.
[HEATH] Okay, let's split up and
get in some solo practice time!
Don't hurt yourselves!
--[HOZUMI] We won't!
--[NANA] Right!
[HEATH] Hey, Hozumi,
be sure to lock up, all right?
[HOZUMI]
You got it.
I'll leave the keys
out for Takeru
since he'll probably be
the last one to leave.
[AYUMU]
Hozumi.
[HOZUMI]
Mm? Hey, what's up?
You're not gonna wear
that thing home, are you?
Help me conquer my fear
of course obstacles.
[HOZUMI]
What, right now?
Yeah.
Uh! Okay! Let's do it!
[HOZUMI]
You gotta go full speed!
There ya go! Don't let
your fear get to you!
Don't stop before the jump!
Keep your focus on moving
forward, not the obstacle!
[AYUMU]
I'll try it again.
[AYUMU screams]
[AYUMU panting]
[AYUMU yelps]
[HOZUMI]
You all right?
[AYUMU sighs]
Yeah, I'm fine.
I think I was on to
something that time!
Really? Good!
Then I say we keep at it until
you finally get it down perfect!
[AYUMU]
Okay!
[HOZUMI] One hundred more
tries should do the trick!
[AYUMU] Nah! How about we start
at 50 and see what happens?
[RIKU]
I got a proposition for ya, Cap.
Please? Lemme try your bento
and I'll let you try mine.
[HEATH]
Sure, you got a deal, man.
[RIKU] Aw yeah,
seafood's the way to go.
[HEATH]
Mm! The beef's pretty good.
Okay, trade me back.
Hey, cut it out!
Salmon roe's my favorite!
I said you could try it,
not eat it all!
I can't help it, it's so tasty!
[HEATH growls, sighs]
He barely left me any.
Hey, Takeru. Gonna let me
try your bento, too?
You know what,
never mind, I'm good.
I'm just gonna stick
with what I've got.
[TAKERU]
Go ahead and take a piece.
You don't have to share yours.
[RIKU]
Thanks, but no thanks.
If you're serious
about End of Summer
you'll start eating more
white meat and lean protein.
The fat content of
white meat chicken
is a low 0.8 grams per
every 100 grams,
and it has 23 grams of protein.
Thigh meat has 14 grams of fat
in the same amount of meat,
and has only 19
grams of protein.
A sirloin steak has
22 grams of protein
but it also has a
whopping 24 grams of fat.
Pork belly has a mere
14 grams of protein
and a ridiculous
35 grams of fat.
Saury has 19 grams of protein
and 25 grams of fat.
You like instant
noodles, right? Well...
How does he know
all that stuff?
It's almost as if he's memorized
the nutritional values
of every food he's
ever put in his mouth.
I know that we should
eat well and train hard,
but in the end
it's all up to fate.
C'est la vie.
Well, the way you've
been training,
you're gonna kick fate's butt!
Atami! Ha, ha, ha!
Uh?
Check it out! A foot bath!
[HOZUMI]
Sweet!
[RIKU] I'm gonna stick my
feet in, who's with me?
You down, Hozumi?
Yeah, I'm all about it.
What could it hurt? I mean,
soaking our feet is basically
the same as a pre-match warm-up!
If you want a warm-up,
we could always
sprint to the hotel.
[HOZUMI, RIKU, AYUMU]
Uh!
Why bother with just your feet?
C'mon, a quick run will
warm-up your whole body.
"A quick run"?
But the hotel's far away!
[AYUMU, HOZUMI]
Uh! He's doing it!
Oh, it's on!
Last one there buys
everybody drinks!
The first to play is
usually the first to win!
[HOZUMI]
Wait for me!
So we're doing this?!
Hey!
[NANA laughs]
The guys are really excited.
I hope they're prepared,
'cause this first to play
may not be the first to win.
[NANA]
Huh?
[RIKU] An open-air bath?!
This is so awesome! Ha, ha!
Last one in's a rotten egg!
[splash]
Ahh! Aw, yeah, this'll do.
We ran all the way here
from the station,
and then ran to
check out the course.
[gasps]
What?
Quit staring.
[RIKU gasping, yelps]
Nice deltoids, Yagami.
[RIKU]
Ah! Let go!
[TAKERU] Your pectoralis
major needs work.
You get your filthy hands
off of me, ya perv!
Would you quit screamin'?
You're gonna get us in trouble.
[TAKERU]
I didn't know you were here.
Your femoral muscles
are quite impressive!
So strong.
[HEATH] Knock it off, Takeru!
I'm warnin' ya!
Uh!
[gasps] No! Please
Don't come in here!
I don't have the
muscles they do!
[HEATH]
Get him off of Hozumi!
[RIKU]
Quit bein' a creep, Takeru!
What are they doing over there?
[HEATH] Well, you guys,
it all starts tomorrow.
It should be fun,
but we gotta focus 'cause
this year's course is tough.
Be careful out there.
Don't wanna get hurt.
I'm gettin' worried about Ayumu.
Shouldn't he be back by now?
[HEATH] Depends on how far
he went to get us drinks.
[NANA] I don't wanna step
on your toes or anything.
But I was thinking it might
be smart to double-check
the running order
before the match starts.
If you want to.
[HEATH]
Nah, there's no need.
We've been training
in that order
since the last competition.
[gasps] Long time no see.
I hope you guys will
be gentle with us today.
Meet Yu Kamoda.
He's Mihashi's Relationer.
And this is ours, Nana Sakurai.
[YU]
Uh? But she's a girl.
Yeah, got a problem with that?
Forgive me for sounding rude, it
certainly wasn't my intention.
I'm just surprised, that's all.
I'm sorry, Miss.
Oh. No prob.
Y'know, if you're feeling guilty
you could always make it up
to us by sharing
your running order.
C'mon, Kamoda.
You're my buddy, aren't ya?
Of course I am!
But I can't do that.
[HEATH laughs] I was just
messin' around with you, man!
You could've given me
a fake running order
and I wouldn't have
known any better.
I swear, you haven't
changed one bit, have you?
I've never been good
at that kinda stuff.
Kei's the one who's always
got the snappy comebacks.
You ready, Bro?
Quit yammering and get to work.
Did you finish checking
the equipment?
No, not yet. Sorry.
I'll do it right now.
That's Kei Kamoda.
Team captain and
Yu's little brother.
[NANA] The younger
brother's the captain?
Hello, I'm Nana Sakurai.
It's nice to meet you.
I heard you guys got beat
by Saisei at the last match.
Looks like Honan's reign
is officially over.
C'mon, let's go, Yu.
[YU]
Uh...
[HEATH] You really oughta teach
him to respect his elders.
Our team's strategy has
always been runner-centric.
So I'm really nothin'
but a figurehead.
[ANNOUNCER 4A] Welcome to
beautiful Atami, Japan,
ladies and gentlemen!
The battle for this year's End
of Summer is about to begin!
Our competitors for the first
match of the Trial Tour
are Honan Academy
High School from Tokyo.
And Mihashi High School
from Saitama!
Now let's take a look at
the teams' running order!
[HOZUMI, AYUMU whimpering]
[AYUMU] I'm running
against this behemoth?!
[AYUMU screams]
Hey, I'm Nagatsuka!
Nice to meet you!
Ha, ha! Ha.
[AYUMU]
He's freakishly strong!
Time to show off
my acting chops.
I gotta win today.
Not just for me,
but for my little sister
who's desperately ill.
What?
[AYUMU]
She's on death's door.
The only thing that could
save her now is surgery,
but she's too scared
to go through with it.
"I'm so scared, big brother!"
[HOZUMI]
He doesn't even have a sister!
I visited her before I left.
"I'll make a deal with you, Sis.
If I win this match,
will you have the surgery?"
She agreed.
The feels, man!
[HOZUMI]
He bought it!
No offense, but I have
to kick your butt today.
It's to save my sister!
[NOBUHIKO]
I understand!
[yelps]
It's so admirable of you to
fight for your little sis!
Tell you what, I'm gonna
run as fast as I can
so that your win'll
mean even more to her!
[AYUMU yelps]
[HOZUMI] May your scheming
soul rest in peace, Ayumu.
[JUDGE 4A] Competitors,
bow to your opponent!
[ALL]
May the best team win!
[HONAN STRIDE]
Good luck, Ayumu!
You'll need it!
[CROWD cheering]
[TAKESHI]
Can I ask you somethin' man?
I heard a rumor you're Tomoe
Yagami's brother, is it true?
'Cause dude could run.
Yep, he's my brother.
No, way!
Does speed run in the
family, 'cause if so,
you gotta be pretty
fast yourself, huh?
[RIKU exhales]
I know that we're competitors,
but good luck to you
and your team.
You, too!
[ANNOUNCER 4A]
On your mark...
Get set...
[buzzing]
[TAKESHI]
Whoa, he's fast!
But there's no way he'll
keep up that speed for long.
[NANA] What the--?
He's going way too fast!
Be careful, Riku!
Listen, there's a tunnel
ahead that's tricky.
It slopes up so you're
gonna need to--
[RIKU panting]
[gasps]
Sounds like you were a
bit late on that one.
[NANA] I didn't have the chance
to warn him to hold his pace!
[ANNOUNCER 4A]
This Atami course is a hard one.
It's full of slopes and
inclines from the start!
Let's see who'll come out
ahead in this first leg.
And it's Mihashi High School!
Takeshi Eifuku has
taken the lead!
He's barely edged out
Honan Academy's Riku Yagami!
[NANA]
The guy overtook him.
The first runners have
gotta to be exhausted
but I can't rush things.
[YU]
Shima, set.
[NANA]
Takeru, set!
[NANA] I need to wait till
he gets a little closer
to the Takeover Zone before I--
And go!
[NANA gasps]
Already?! Without a countdown?
You'll have to hurry, Shima.
[NANA]
Oh, no, I'm late!
Takeru, go!
Sorry 'bout that!
[NANA] I screwed up!
I made the call too late,
now he won't be able
to catch up to Riku!
[clap]
[gasps]
[RIKU]
Go!
[ANNOUNCER 4A]
A close call!
Honan Academy almost
had a collision
but pulled off their Relation
at the last second!
[NANA]
But how...?
So my call wasn't
late, after all.
Did Yu make his too early?
[TAKERU panting]
[AOI]
Are you serious?
All right Heath, are you ready?
We're 0.2 seconds
behind right now.
Harigaya, get set.
Get set!
[NANA]
Why's he waiting?
[HISATO grunts]
[NANA gasps]
[BOTH]
Go!
[NANA] Their runner took off
before he even got the call!
[HEATH]
Aw, crap, I'm late!
[YU]
Your second runner.
Looks like he's moving too fast.
He should slow down or he'll
fly past the Takeover Zone.
[NANA] I have faith that
Heath can pull it off.
[TAKERU panting]
[TAKERU]
Come on!
[HEATH] My team may be full of
rookies, but they're awesome!
[HEATH panting]
[clap]
[ANNOUNCER 4A]
And they connect!
What a daring stunt from Honan!
Just when it looked like
they were about to miss
the Takeover Zone,
they made magic happen!
Good job.
I thought you were gonna
call it but you didn't.
I had to throw out a bluff.
No hard feelings.
Unfortunately, it's the only
way I can help my team.
[NANA]
What's he mean by that?
I'm really nothing
but a figurehead.
[NANA]
The Mihashi runners
aren't even listening
to Yu's instructions.
But then, who's
giving them the go?
[KEI grunts]
[NOBUHIKO]
Overtaken.
Hey, Kadowaki.
Yeah? What's up?
I just wanted to wish you good
luck before we head out.
Thanks.
Okay, Nagatsuka. Get set.
[NANA] I'm not gonna
let him trick me again.
Are you ready?
Get set, Ayumu!
Heath has a narrow
lead right now!
[AYUMU]
If I lose to this guy,
I'm gonna bring
the whole team down.
[NANA]
Three... two...
[AYUMU]
I've gotta win!
[NANA]
...one...
Go!
[HEATH]
Keep it movin', Ayumu!
[AYUMU panting]
I hate running uphill!
[AYUMU]
Aw, man. This sucks!
I was right.
I just don't have the talent.
Well, the way you've
been training,
you're gonna kick fate's butt!
[gasps]
[AYUMU] It's not over!
I can't give up!
[NOBUHIKO]
Huh?
[NANA]
He took a shortcut?
But there's a giant drop!
[AYUMU]
I can do it!
I'm not the same
person I was before!
I've got this!
Just watch!
[gasps] Ayumu, are you there?
[AYUMU grunts]
--[crash]
--[NANA gasps]
[KEI gasps]
[HOZUMI] Uh! Nana?
What happened to him?
Tell me he's okay!
Come in, Ayumu!
What's wrong?!
[NOBUHIKO]
Kadowaki!
Uh!
Can you hear me?
Ayumu- senpai , come in!
Let me know you're okay!
Please, Ayumu...
[AYUMU gasping]
[NANA gasps]
I have to connect.
I have to connect...
...with Hozumi!
[NANA gasping]
You ready, Hozumi?
Get set!
We're behind by four seconds!
It's in the bag.
[HOZUMI grunts]
Three... two... one...
Go!
[HOZUMI panting]
[AYUMU panting]
[HOZUMI]
There he is!
[HOZUMI] C'mon, Ayumu!
We've gotta connect!
[AYUMU groans]
Hurry!
[KEI]
We did it! Another match won!
[KEI gasping]
[KEI panting]
[KEI]
I'm not gonna lose this race!
No way! I've gotta win!
I have to!
What's wrong with you?!
You're making all of
your go calls too late!
Sorry.
[TAKESHI] It's a shame 'cause
Kei's timing is spot on.
I bet we'd be near perfect
if he made all the calls.
[KEI] My brother's
graduating this year.
This is his last chance to
make it to End of Summer.
That's why we have to win!
We have to!
He's depending on me!
I gotta do it!
[RIKU]
Keep movin', Hozumi!
Go!
[HEATH]
You're almost there, man!
There's only a little ways left!
C'mon, I know you can do it!
Run, Hozumi, run!
[HOZUMI panting]
[KEI] How did this happen?!
I thought we had it!
We needed this win!
[ANNOUNCER 4A] Ladies and
gentlemen, the winner of...
[HOZUMI]
Ayumu!
[ANNOUNCER 4A] ...Trial
Touris is Honan Academy!
They narrowly defeated Saitama's
Mihashi High School
and will move on to
the next stage!
I dunno about y...
Poor Ayumu.
I'll go to the hospital.
You kids go home and
I'll keep you updated.
[sirens blaring]
[NOBUHIKO]
Kadowaki!
I'm willin' to give
you another chance
to save your little sister!
We'll race again once you're
feeling up to it, okay?!
Honan's a good team.
They fought till the end.
Yeah! Ha, ha.
I'm up for another race,
how 'bout you?
I'm really sorry, Kei.
I know I let you down.
Would you stop
apologizing all the time?!
I'll try.
I wish I was a
better Relationer.
I'm no good at it.
Now you know that's not true.
[gasps]
[KEI] You could be
a great Relationer,
but I never gave you the chance.
I'm sorry.
Can we just start over?
I won't get in your way
anymore, I promise.
I wanna see you reach
your full potential.
'Course we can. Thanks.
[TOMOE]
Kyosuke, long time no talk.
I know this is outta
the blue, but
I was thinkin' maybe we
should get back in action.
Sorry, but I no longer
have the right
to participate in Stride.
[TOMOE]
Oh, gimme a break.
You never change, do ya?
I gotta admit, I've always
liked that about you.
I'm comin' back to Japan soon.
I'll get in touch with
you when I'm home.
Okay, well... Take care.
[NOBUHIKO]
I hope your sister's surgery
saves her life, Kadowaki!
[AYUMU]
Thanks, Nagatsuka! Careful!
I'm in a lot of pain!
[NOBUHIKO]
Are you sick, too?!
[AYUMU] No! Listen, my
sister's a delicate flower.
--[NOBUHIKO] In the shower?
--[AYUMU] Ina Bauer!
[HOZUMI]
Next on "Prinstride,"
"Ayumu's Sister is Probably
a German Figure Skater"!
Hurry and get better, man!