[HEATH groaning]
[HEATH groans]
Don't Kyosuke--
[CLUB MEMBERS panting]
[gasps]
Kuga- senpai ?
[HOZUMI]
How could you do this?
You're a disgrace to
the Honan Stride Club!
Not tryin' to pry, but...
...did somethin'
happen to your foot?
It's fine.
That Atami course was a killer.
I'm bein' a little cautious,
that's all.
Just checkin'.
[HEATH]
One minor injury
can lead to a lot of
deeper problems.
I don't want any of
you to forget that.
Put your safety
before anything else.
What did they say?
[AYUMU]
I broke my clavicle,
but I'm sportin' some
pretty sweet battle scars!
Tough guy.
[AYUMU] You know it!
They're moving me to a hospital
in Tokyo tomorrow.
[AYUMU gasps]
I've spotted an "HTH"!
A "Hottie in the Hospital"!
[AYUMU yelps]
What are you doing with that
needle, my white coated angel?!
Don't stick me with it!
I'm still tender!
Please be gentle...
[click]
[RIKU gasps]
You still there?!
He sounded okay.
Yeah, he'll be fine.
Hope so!
Well, that news oughta put
an end to your worryin'.
Yeah, I'm so relieved.
[HEATH] All right,
start your stretching.
Take your time warmin' up.
No more injuries, got it?
--[RIKU] Got it!
--[TAKERU] Yes, sir!
[HOZUMI]
Ayumu.
[RIKU grunting]
[DAN] I've got news regarding
our next match.
Unfortunately, we don't have
enough runners to participate.
If worse comes to worst, I'm
afraid we'll have to withdraw.
[TAKERU]
We're not withdrawing.
[RIKU] Then I guess we'll have
to find a new team member.
There's gotta be someone out
there who'd wanna join up.
[HEATH] Good luck, nobody wants
to join Stride anymore.
[RIKU]
Someone fast.
I know!
[TAKERU gasps]
Let's go talk to them right now.
[RIKU]
Senpai, remember that one guy?
[NANA]
Wait up, guys! I'm coming, too!
Chototsu Moushin .
Those first years
sure are dedicated.
Then we should probably
go help 'em out.
[TAKERU] You don't even know
where to find him?
I should have guessed.
[RIKU]
I would have asked Heath,
but you dragged me away
before I had the chance to!
[TAKERU]
No excuses.
[RIKU]
That wasn't an excuse!
[NANA]
You guys, cut it out!
Let's just go back
and ask him, okay?
[RIKU]
That's the guy!
[HEATH]
What's the matter, Hozumi?
Aren't you gonna tag along?
[HOZUMI]
Ayumu was the only one.
[HEATH]
Huh?
[HOZUMI] He wasn't even
interested in the Stride Club.
But he joined us because
he knew we needed somebody.
[HOZUMI] It'd be different if
Kuga hadn't caused the incident.
[RIKU]
Excuse me!
You sure he's the one?
Yeah, man.
Heath told me they'd
been running together
since they were
in middle school.
We're desperate for runners.
Will you join us?
You can't tell him
we're desperate!
Forget he said that!
[TAKERU] Will you please join
the Stride Club?
We would like to recruit you.
[KYOSUKE] I no longer have the
right to participate in Stride.
Say what? What's that
supposed to mean?
Hey, hold up! Will you
at least think about it?
[HEATH]
You asked Kyosuke to join?
I tried.
The other day you were talking
about what an awesome runner
he was, so I thought
I'd give it a shot.
It didn't work though.
I see.
So, what did he say to you?
It was something about
not having the right to
participate in Stride.
I don't get it, I thought anyone
was allowed to join the club.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[RIKU] Man, why doesn't anybody
wanna be part of the team?
[NANA]
They've probably all signed up
for other clubs already.
Yeah, but why're
they runnin' off?
They get within three feet
and then high-tail it!
It's like some creepy
ghost of Stride Club past
is scarin' 'em away!
You have good, strong legs.
My club and I
really need your body.
[CLASSMATE 5A wailing]
[RIKU, NANA]
That explains it.
[CLASSMATE 5B]
Says here the Stride Club
is lookin' for a new member.
You need one person and
you'll be able to compete?
[RIKU, NANA]
Yeah, Do you wanna join?
We'll have some work
to do on your thighs.
In Stride you get to
whoosh through the air
and bust through
the wind like pow!
All while using teamwork!
I appreciate the offer and all,
but I have a low
tolerance for pain.
Stride Club is a little too
dangerous for me, ya know?
I mean... I guess I get it.
One of our members
did get injured
during a match
the other day,
but that's not the norm.
You mean to tell me that none
of the other club members
told you about the KGB incident?
[BOTH gasp]
[RIKU]
KGB?
I dunno, you guys.
I find it hard to believe
Kyosuke got kicked out
for fighting during a match.
People can surprise you.
From what he said, KGB stands
for "Kuga Going Berserk."
I don't know though.
Yeah.
I don't really know him
but he doesn't seem like
the violent type to me.
[HOZUMI]
Please don't let him join.
[gasps]
[NANA]
But why not, senpai?
[HOZUMI
Anybody but him.
I know it's really important
that we find a teammate
as soon as possible.
I get it.
But just I don't want him
replacing Ayumu.
I can't let that happen.
I'm sorry!
Hozumi- senpai , don't go!
[door opens]
[RIKU, NANA gasp]
[AYUMU sighs] I'm bored.
Hospitals are so dull.
My brain is turning to goo.
Give me sweet freedom!
[knocking]
You up for... Shogi?
The valiant knight is back
from his quest for treasure!
Sit! You must be weary
from your long journey.
[HOZUMI] Sorry I haven't
been able to visit more.
How ya doin'?
Aw, don't sweat it!
I think the bandages do a lot
for my rugged good looks!
They sure do.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
Who knows? You may be
running by the weekend!
[HEATH] Something happened
beginning of last year
that almost shut down the club.
A lot of our members
ended up bailing.
Not that I blame 'em.
We were barely hangin'
on by a thread.
Hozumi took it upon himself
to keep things rolling,
and talked Ayumu into joining.
[NANA]
Oh, I see.
That must be when he recruited
him from the Shogi Club.
Well back in those days
we didn't even have a
Shogi Club. Ayumu would just
play by himself wherever
he found an empty spot.
[NANA, RIKU]
By himself?
[HEATH]
Heh. Yeah, so we made a deal.
We joined each other's clubs
in order to keep them goin'.
[RIKU]
That sounds pretty desperate.
[HEATH]
Didn't matter to us.
We were just happy
to have a team at all.
And Ayumu dedicated
himself to the training.
[TAKERU]
He had to have.
There's no way Shogi could've
prepared his body for Stride.
[HEATH laughs] True and we had
to prepare our minds for Shogi.
[AYUMU grunts]
It's harder with my left hand.
[HOZUMI]
Ayumu, this is all my fault.
I'm so sorry.
Why're you taking the blame?
I'm the one who tried
the fancy footwork.
[HOZUMI]
You wouldn't have gotten hurt
if I hadn't dragged
you into this!
It was wrong.
You didn't wanna join
the Stride Club!
[NANA]
I get it now.
Hozumi doesn't want Kuga- senpai
on the team 'cause
Stride takes trust,
and he can't trust him
after the whole KGB thing.
[TAKERU, RIKU]
Huh?
I'll bet he's also
blaming himself
for Ayumu's injuries,
since he's the one who
got him to join Stride.
[RIKU]
It's totally possible.
Sure sounds like him. Yeah.
Hate to think he'd feel guilty
for bringin' his buddy in.
[AYUMU]
Don't you have practice today?
[HOZUMI]
I skipped it.
But shouldn't you be scouting?
You need another runner.
[HOZUMI]
I only wanna run with you.
'Fraid I can't right now.
I mean, look at me.
[HOZUMI]
Aw, c'mon!
Stay positive! 'Kay?
For all we know your muscles are
healing at super-human speeds
and you'll end up
faster than all of us--
[AYUMU]
Hozumi.
I think it's time we stop
lying to ourselves.
Even if a miracle happened,
I'm just not cut out for it.
I tried, but the team
deserves to win.
We need to win the next race.
But no matter what, you and
I will always be teammates.
[TAKERU]
He wasn't forced to join.
[NANA, RIKU, HEATH gasp]
He chose to.
Ayumu's legs prove that
he's dedicated to his training.
You've got a point.
You're a palm reader.
That's cool. 'Cept it's legs.
[TAKERU] Let's go.
We're wasting our time here.
Uh.  You're right!
[NANA]
Go where?
[RIKU] Hmm. We should probably
go find Hozumi- senpai .
We can't let him go
through this all on his own.
We need to let him know
that his teammates
will always have his back.
[NANA]
Great idea!
Wait, you guys don't even know--
[RIKU] Hold up, does anybody
even know where he went?
[HEATH sighs]
I'd like to thank you, Hozumi.
I'm really grateful
that you invited me
to join the Stride Club.
Sure, it's a challenge
but I love it so much
that I wanna protect it
just as much as you do.
Do the right thing for the club.
Work hard, so we'll win.
[HOZUMI]
Ayumu...
[knocking]
[AYUMU]
Mm? Come in!
Hey! There you are!
Why look, my guild has
come to pay homage...!
[RIKU]
We've been looking everywhere!
We finally had to ask Heath..
[AYUMU]
...I'm not crying.
I'm sorry.
But I still stand
by what I said earlier.
[RIKU]
And we're fine with that!
We're not here to convince
you to let him join.
We wanna know how you're
feeling, that's all.
In Stride when someone's injured
the rest of the team
suffers with them.
I can't run with Kyosuke,
not after he betrayed us.
And if we had to run together,
we'd never win.
Our team trusted him
wholeheartedly,
and then he went and
hurt Heath's ankle!
There's no way I could put
my trust in him again.
So that's why.
[HOZUMI] Nearly everyone quit
the team after the KGB incident.
Heath did everything he could
to keep the club alive
even though it was on
the brink of shutting down.
He wanted to run again
but it took his ankle
a whole year to heal!
It was all Kyosuke's fault!
[HEATH growls]
[crash]
[HOZUMI] That's why I'm
not okay with him joining.
He chose his path.
I can't forget what he did
just because we need help.
It's just... not right.
Thank you for telling
us what happened.
I suppose we've got no choice.
We'll simply have to
find someone else.
[RIKU, HEATH]
Wait a second!
[gasps]
[RIKU]
Senpai.
[HOZUMI]
Is something wrong?
[HEATH]
About my ankle.
It wasn't Kyosuke
who injured it.
[HOZUMI, NANA gasp]
The truth is... he saved us.
Kyosuke sacrificed
everything for Stride.
That's not what we heard.
Do you know something we don't?
[footsteps]
[HEATH] Listen. What I'm about
to say never leaves this room.
Is that understood?
[RIKU]
Why, is it some kinda secret?
[HEATH]
I guess you could say that,
if the wrong people
get a hold of the truth,
there's a good chance our
club will be shut down.
[NANA, RIKU, TAKERU gasp]
I don't understand!
What are you saying?
[HEATH]
I'm sorry, Hozumi.
I shoulda told you
but I kept it to myself
in order to protect the club.
Here's the real story
of the KGB incident.
[HEATH]
Up until last year,
Honan Stride had
tons of members.
And almost all of them
were third-year students.
When Mr. Dan officially
became coach
he decided to change
things up a little.
He put me, Kyosuke, and
Tomoe on the starting roster
even though we were
second-years.
That move didn't go over too
well with the rest of the team.
We were undefeated, but
one-by-one they started to quit
right before the second
match of the Trial Tour.
During the event our Relationer
was an experienced third-year,
but he got tricked by a bluff.
I was late on the timing.
Go!
Kuga!
Go! Now!
[laughs] You can't be serious!
It was just a bluff!
You amateur.
What have I done?
Kuga, hold back!
Hasekura, speed up!
You got this, Satta!
Bring it on home now!
Come on!
You wanna prove yourself?
Get the lead out, man!
I wouldn't push him like that.
I mean, it's not his fault
you made a bad call.
If they stay at that pace...
[RELATIONER 5A]
They might collide.
[KYOSUKE]
Heath!
[ANNOUNCER 5A]
Honan Academy, disqualified!
[THIRD-YEAR 5A growls]
Dammit, what is wrong with you?!
[THIRD-YEAR 5B] Hasekura wipes
out and Kuga just stops running?
Unbelievable.
You don't belong here.
[TOMOE]
Don't blame them.
Hate to call you out, senpai,
but you got tricked by a bluff.
[THIRD-YEAR 5A]
How would you know?!
'Cause I heard it
all in my earpiece,
it wasn't their fault.
You better shut your mouth!
Of course you'd be
on their side.
[KYOSUKE]
Heath!
You faker! Stop pretending
you hurt yourself!
[KYOSUKE]
Huh?
[HEATH groans, scream]
[KYOSUKE gasps]
[HEATH groaning]
[THIRD-YEARS yell]
[TOMOE]
Huh?
Don't, Kyosuke.
[STRIDE MEMBERS panting]
But Kuga- senpai ?
[HEATH] Kyosuke decided to take
on all of the consequences.
We knew if word got out that
a bunch of Stride members
had gotten into a fight,
the school would shut us down.
So Kyosuke took
the blame for himself.
He said he did it all,
even injured my ankle,
and then resigned.
Nobody ever denied the story.
[NANA]
Wow.
So, to protect its members,
he quit the Stride Club.
[HEATH] Yeah. Kyosuke
took the punishment,
Tomoe got invited to the US,
and the other guys
quit the team.
The Stride Club survived
all the drama but in the end,
Hozumi and I were the only
members who were left.
It's funny how it
worked out, eh Hozumi?
[HOZUMI]
No, it's not funny.
They didn't want you guys
on the team from the start.
They pushed you around
and walked away
without even a slap
on the wrist.
And it wasn't right for Kyosuke
to take the blame for it.
A Stride team's supposed to
stand together no matter what,
but he left you to deal
with everything alone.
[HOZUMI] Kyosuke thinks he
"saved the club" by ditching us.
Doesn't that seem
wrong to anybody else?
[RIKU grunting]
[TAKERU]
His brain blew up.
I have somethin' to say!
Why can't he be on the team?!
It's been a while since all
of that crappy stuff happened
and none of those other dudes
are even running
with us anymore!
[gasps]
[RIKU]
Hozumi!
If Kyosuke comes back it'll
take some pressure off Heath,
which is what you want!
If we ask and he says yes,
everything'll be cool!
[HOZUMI]
Uh...
Look, we need somebody
to run with us
and he's available, so why not
give him another chance?
C'mon, the guy deserves
another shot!
[TAKERU]
That was redundant.
I dunno.
I just found out the truth,
I'm not really ready to--
[HEATH laughs]
[ALL gasp]
[HEATH] Never thought I'd say
it, but you're right Riku.
There's no reason to beat
ourselves up over this.
We need a runner and I happen
to know a great one.
Okay, then.
Time for us to let go of the
past. All right, you guys.
We have a member to draft.
Hope he's ready to
race tomorrow.
Yeah, that's what
I'm talkin' about!
[HEATH]
Good work.
I hope that you can
forgive me for this.
And, thank you.
Seriously?
Let's get this show on the r--
[HEATH]
Hold it right there, Riku.
Let me handle this one, okay?
I'm sorry about the
freshmen bothering you.
[KYOSUKE] Who, Tomoe's
brother and his friends?
[HEATH] They've opened my
eyes to a lot of things.
I'm proud to run with them.
Every one of them
really deserves to
be in the Stride Club.
[KYOSUKE]
That's good.
Kyosuke, you deserve
to be in Stride Club.
[gasps]
[HEATH] You've been training,
haven't you?
You're ready to run.
[KYOSUKE]
Heath, you already have
an excellent team to work with.
If I were to join, you would
just be criticized.
You saved the club.
I sat back when I should've
spoken up for you.
Would you please give me the
chance to earn your trust again?
I'm so sorry. I wish things
hadn't ended that way.
You'll never be put
in that position again.
If something goes down,
I'll protect you, Kyosuke.
I promise! Please, come back!
Everybody wants you on the team.
[NANA, RIKU gasping]
The whole KGB incident
wasn't your fault.
You protected us.
You lived by the Stride
team's code no matter what,
and gave it your all.
There's a race comin' up
and we're down a guy.
So, are you up for it?
We could really use your help.
We can't do it without you, man.
We'll lose if we don't
have you on the team.
Don't make me beg! I wanna
run alongside you again!
Kyosuke, please!
[HEATH]
Uh.
C'mon, man.
[AYUMU whimpering]
[knocking]
[door opens]
I knew that you'd come.
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER 5AA] Coming up next
is the Junior Stride League!
It's a good day
for a run, isn't it?
[JUNIOR 5A]
Absolutely!
The wind's a little
stronger than expected,
but we can't wait to
get out there and race!
[GUIDE 5A] All teams must
submit their running orders
for the Summer Trial
Tour at once.
Late entries will
not be accepted.
Any teams who have
not yet submitted
their starting line-up,
please come to the East
Square Headquarters Tent
or you will be ineligible
to participate. All teams...
Um, Honan Academy?
We're gonna need your
running order now, please.
[NANA]
It's coming!
We just need a little more time.
Well, then. I guess that's that.
[RIKU gasps]
The wind's dust attack
penetrates lens armor.
The pain is super effective!
[RIKU, NANA gasp]
[ALL gasp]
Dude, you're late.
Welcome back.
Kyosuke Kuga,
third-year student.
I'd like to sign up for the
Stride Club starting today.
[RIKU, AYUMU laugh]
Kyosuke!
[DAN]
Ichiro Junpuu .
[RIKU] Hey, Cap, aren't you
supposed to be studying
for college entrance exams?
[HEATH]
Uhh, well, Riku, I--
[TAKERU]
It's not important.
[RIKU]
Nobody asked you!
[TAKERU] We shouldn't focus
on anything but End of Summer.
[KYOSUKE]
I agree.
Let tomorrow's troubles
blow in with the wind.
[RIKU] Sounds like you're
avoiding exams, too.
Next on "Prinstride," "Kyosuke
of the Valley of the Wind"!
[TAKERU]
Start training!