[pop music plays]
[REIJI] The stars are so
bright they're blinding.
But I'll be fine as
long as I have you.
You're the Milky way
to my Andromeda.
Together, we'll spread love
throughout the universe!
[SHIZUMA] Let's follow our
hearts on a galactic voyage!
[ASUMA] Take my hand,
and don't let go!
[BANTARO]
Our fiery passion
will rip through the
darkness of space.
Just like a shooting
star in the night sky!
[KAEDE]
I'm gonna stick with you
until the end of the time!
[TASUKU] Are you up
for a cosmic connection?
Only one group can
give it to you.
[ALL]
Galaxy Standard, yeah!
[CROWD]
One more song!
One more song! One more song!
Well, okay.
One more song, just for you!
[CROWD cheers]
What're those guys
doing up there?
As if Saisei High School Stride
wasn't cool enough already,
they're also members of a pop
group. And they're known as--
[TAKERU]
Galaxy Standard, yeah.
[AYUMU] Stop! You stole
the words outta my mouth!
Can you believe this is the
eighth generation of the group?
It's crazy. I've heard of
Gal-Stan but I had no idea
that the bands' members were
on a high school Stride team.
Not only are they
amazing runners,
they're great singers, too!
Okay, sure, they're
talented and all
but they're not models like us.
[AYUMU]
Yeah, none of them
are plastered on a giant
billboard like our Hozumi!
[HOZUMI]
Ah! Don't remind me!
She promised it was
just a test shot!
There's no need to worry!
Nobody's gonna figure out
that's you dressed up in
ladies clothing 'cause you
look just like a chick!
Trust me!
[ONLOOKERS]
Huh...? Ah!
Riku, how could you?!
[RIKU]
So lemme get this straight,
the Gal-Stan guys gave that
crazy high energy performance,
and now they're gonna race us?
[TAKERU]
That's correct.
Talk about stamina!
This means we'll
have the advantage
because they're gonna be pooped.
Hey, not good
sportsmanship, dude!
Look, this is just the
beginning, you guys.
Once the Trial Tour starts
we're gonna face some
stiff competition.
And we'll beat 'em all.
Ha, ha. After watching
the guys onstage today,
I'm not so sure we're
gonna beat 'em, Senpai.
Hey.
[RIKU]
Uh?
You care to explain?
Explain what?
[door opens]
[ASUMA]
Uh! I know you!
[gasps]
'Sup?
Hey, I met you the
other day, right?
Good to see you!
But what're you doin' here?
Aw, c'mon, man!
Whaddya think I'm doin' here?
I'm in Gal-Stan, duh!
What?! No way!
How come I didn't
see you up there?
I wasn't front and center
but you couldn't miss me!
[laughs] Look at it
this way Asuma,
you're such a natural you
blend into the background.
[KAEDE]
Hate to break it to ya dude,
but nobody remembers the average
lookin' guy in a boy band,
that's just how it is.
Yeah. He's got a good point.
We'll have to get you a
flashier costume next time.
Why, you...!
Sorry man, that was
totally my bad.
[ASUMA] You guys are with
Honan Academy Stride, right?
[RIKU]
Who, us?
Yeah. I'm Riku Yagami, runner.
First year, and my
buddy here is--
[TAKERU]
Takeru Fujiwara.
Same.
Yagami, huh?
[RIKU]
Uh.
[ASUMA chuckles]
I'm Asuma Mayuzumi, from Saisei.
I'm not tryin' to
intimidate you guys,
but I'm a year older than you,
I'm a second year runner.
Whoa, are you kidding
me?! But you--
You look so young, Sir.
[ASUMA] Don't call me "Sir"
like I'm an old man.
[BANTARO]
All right, break it up you two.
I'm Bantaro Chiyomats but
you can call me Ban- chan .
And this is Kaede Okumuda,
aka Mei- chan .
Jeez, would you cut it out?
How many times do I have to tell
you to quit calling me that?
It's like some kinda inside joke
you haven't bothered
to tell anyone else.
Hey, my name's Tasuku Seno.
It's nice to meet ya.
Now, why're you wearing
your school track suits,
don't you have sponsors?
[RIKU]
Uh. Oh, um. We do but, uh...
[REIJI]
Hello again.
[RIKU]
Uh?
Oh, hey, what's up?
[RIKU]
Uh...
[KAEDE, BANTARO]
Uh?!
[ASUMA]
Huh?
[REIJI chuckles]
Look.
[gasps]
Whoa, did you seriously
go all the way to Kobe
just to get a cell phone charm?!
Kinda.
I decided to pick one up, too.
[door opens]
[HEATH] Okay guys, get in
here for the team meeting.
What up?
Hi, Hasekura.
Wow, long time no see.
I'd hoped to run
into you last year,
but you weren't in any matches.
Heh. Yeah, right.
I swear it's the truth.
[KAEDE]
Excuse me. All right.
That means he's gotta
be here. Where's Kuga?!
[NANA]
Uh?
[HEATH]
Sorry pal, he's not here.
What, did he catch
a cold or somethin'?
[ASUMA]
Whoa, back off, Kaede.
Why're you flippin'
out? Come on.
[KAEDE]
I just don't get it.
They don't stand a
chance without him!
Why isn't he here?
Yeah, sure, he's a
great runner and all,
but Honan Stride can
still win, Kyosuke or not.
[TASUKU] You think so?
I wouldn't be so sure.
I mean, Kuga's the one
who elevated your game.
If you ask me,
you're nothing more than
the B-team without him.
Now Tasuku,
I don't believe anyone did
ask for your opinion.
Heh, heh.
I'm counting on you.
Don't let me down, okay?
C'mon, guys.
[RIKU]
Uh, yeah.
See you on the course.
[NANA gasping]
[HOZUMI]
Mmm...
[AYUMU growls]
Can you get outta the way?
[NANA] Aw, man!
They're so intimidating.
[HOZUMI]
No kidding.
How're we supposed to
compete with that?
[AYUMU coughs]
[HOZUMI]
You okay?
Gal-Stan are such stars,
they're like the freakin' sun!
And I'm the tiniest
of plant life
photosynthesizing their rays.
Impossible.
He's right, I hate
to break it to ya,
but you need
chloroplasts for that.
Riku's an academic?
I'd heard that people
who don't like to study
tend to be better at science but
I didn't believe it till now.
[growls] Who cares?!
That's nothing compared
to a singing Stride team!
For real, right? No wonder
everyone looks up to Gal-Stan,
I mean, they're awesome!
Yeah!
[TAKERU]
Are you done fawning over them?
[RIKU]
Uh...
[TAKERU] Saisei is a challenge
for us to overcome.
And nothing more.
[NANA]
Uh.
Gimme a break, man,
are you tellin' me you aren't
even the least bit impressed
with those guys?
Remember, they're high school
students just like we are.
My understanding was
that we came here to win.
Or was I wrong?
[RIKU grunts, gasps]
No, you're right
but let's be real.
If you don't stop fighting
I'll separate ya.
[NANA]
Uh?
[door opens]
[NAN, RIKU]
Uh?
I hope everybody's ready.
[ALL grunt]
[DAN]
Okay, Sakurai.
Give them the running order.
Yes, sir!
Here we go.
Line up in running order, teams!
Hey. I've got a question for ya,
but this might not be
the best time to ask it.
It's too late now.
All right, fine, are you
Tomoe Yagami's brother?
[gasps]
I'm sorry, dude!
I knew I should've waited
until the match was over.
Just forget I even asked!
Tell you what,
let's clean the slate
and run like we've got
no worries, okay?
You with me, Buddy?
Uh. Yeah, sure.
Awesome!
Here's to a good race
and you eatin' my dust!
Maybe for that split second
it takes me to pass ya.
Whassup? You racin' me?
Yeah. I guess so.
It's so warm it feels
like summer out here,
you gotta be burnin' up in
that old-school track suit.
Kinda, yeah.
But the rules say we
have to wear 'em,
and this is all we
have right now.
I've gotta admit it,
yours are pretty cool.
Dude, I know, right?
By the way, the
name's Ban- chan .
I'm Hozumi.
Man, I love your enthusiasm.
Hey, Hozumi, do you have
a twin sister who models?
[HOZUMI]
No, I don't!
Why would you even ask me that?
What're you starin' at, creeper?
Somebody I don't like.
What, do you wanna
fight me or somethin'?
Heh. Reiji's determined
to win this.
To do that, I've gotta outrun
you. Shouldn't be too hard.
[HEATH]
Yeah. We'll see about that.
Hi Kadowaki!
It's an honor to run
with you, Sir!
Oh, thank you.
Right back at ya.
Mind if I ask you
somethin' real quick?
Uh...
Why isn't Kuga competing
in this match?!
He should be here with you guys!
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid that's a little
difficult for me to ans--
Is he hiding some sort
of terrible secret?!
No, it's nothing like that--
Oh wait, I know!
You gonna use him like a
secret weapon, aren't ya?
He's not gonna
be here, okay?
[KAEDE]
He's so incredible,
he probably thinks we're
unworthy of his presence.
In that case.
I'll do my best to impress
him out of hiding!
[AYUMU] Who would've thought
that I, Ayumu Kadowaki,
would ever be outpaced
in a conversation?
Hey, it's good to see
you again, man.
I didn't expect to get the
chance to run with you so soon.
No offense,
but I'm not one to shake
hands before a match.
Heh. How very stoic
of you, but it's cool.
Our opponent for this festival
was changed at the last minute.
Do you have any
idea why that is?
I don't know any
of the specifics,
but apparently the
change was ordered
by the Stride Association.
It sucks for the other school,
but I'm glad I get to race you.
[TAKERU]
Yeah, same here.
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
Hope you're ready, Stride Fans!
Whether you're here with us live
or watching our broadcast,
allow me to welcome you
to Inogashira Park!
Now let's get this
show on the road!
One of the most anticipated
matches of the season,
the Kichijoji Spring Stride
Festival, is about to begin!
[NANA]
We can do this.
I think we made
the right choices
when it comes to
the running order.
Everybody seems to
be well matched.
[NANA]
Now, it's up to me.
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
On your mark...
[NANA] I need to connect
with each of them,
just like we practiced.
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
Get set...
[buzzing]
[BOTH grunt]
[ASUMA grunting]
[ASUMA]
Whoa! He's fast!
[SHIZUMA] Well, you're off
to a good start, huh?
Hm?
[NANA gasping]
[CROWD cheering]
[ASUMA]
Not too shabby, kid.
But you ain't seen nothin' yet.
I was playin' it safe,
but not anymore!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER 3A] Let's hear it
for Asuma Mayuzumi of Gal-Stan,
ladies and gentlemen!
Not only did he clear
all three obstacles,
but he did it with finesse!
[RIKU]
One hundred and twenty meters.
Now 80.
[RIKU]
Okay, only 50 more to go!
There's the Takeover Zone!
So close!
[NANA] What's going on?
Did he lose focus?
[SHIZUMA]
Asuma.
Go.
[NANA gasps]
[ASUMA]
All right, here we go!
Time to switch
it into overdrive!
[RIKU]
What the--?
[ASUMA laughing]
[NANA]
Oh, no.
Chiyomatsu.
Get set.
Are you ready, Hozumi?
They've got the
lead by 2.3 seconds.
Not for long.
It's gotta suck knowin'
your team's behind, huh?
[HOZUMI] Nah, I'm not
too worried about it.
[BANTARO]
Maybe you should be!
[NANA]
Three... two... one...
Go!
[NANA gasping]
[CROWD cheers]
[SHIZUMA] What's the matter?
You feeling tense?
[NANA]
Yeah. A little.
[BOTH grunt]
[RIKU panting]
[HOZUMI]
Riku!
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
And both schools complete
their first Relay
without a hitch!
[SHIZUMA laughs] Listen to
your team mate's breathing.
They're obviously having
a blast out there.
[HOZUMI panting]
[HOZUMI]
I'm comin' for ya, Ban- chan !
[BANTARO] It's like bein'
back on the playground!
Yeah!
[CROWD cheers]
[BANTARO]
My balance is on point!
There's no stoppin' me
today, Honan Stride!
[HOZUMI] What's with the
acrobatics? Show off.
[HOZUMI grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[NANA]
He's right. I can hear it.
They're having the
time of their lives!
[BANTARO]
Sorry Kohinata, it's over.
You gave it a good shot,
but on this narrow bridge?
There's no way!
You don't stand a chance
of overtaking me here!
[HOZUMI]
Now, Nana!
You got it!
Okay, are you ready,
Heath? Get set!
[BANTARO]
Almost Relation time.
[SHIZUMA]
Look out, he's coming.
[BANTARO gasps]
[BANTARO]
He took a shortcut!
[HEATH panting]
[HOZUMI grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[SHIZUMA]
Uh.
That was pretty slick.
It was risky though.
If he had slipped on that jump,
he could've lost the race
for your whole team.
[SHIZUMA]
Lucky for you, he didn't.
Now we're back to square one.
[TASUKU, HEATH grunting]
[TASUKU]
This guy's built like a wall!
It'll take more than
that to knock him over.
[BOTH grunt]
[HEATH]
I can't run alongside him.
In that case, I'll get in front!
[HEATH panting]
[TASUKU]
Nice try,
but defense is my
biggest strength.
And I'm not known
for playing nice.
[TASUKU]
Take notes.
That's what we call
"counter hit"!
[HEATH] I'm not lettin'
you get away that easy!
Look at him go!
Yeah, Senoo's great.
Your Hasekura's going
to have a hard time
catching up with
him at this point.
We've taken this leg, for sure.
[TASUKU]
This loser's no match for me.
But I can't get cocky;
it's not over yet.
I gotta win this for Reiji!
[NANA]
Okay! Ayumu, you're up!
They have the lead
by two seconds!
[AYUMU]
Aw, man. Not good!
[NANA]
Get set!
[AYUMU]
It's up to me?
[NANA]
Three... two... one...
Go!
[HEATH panting]
[AYUMU panting]
[AYUMU]
Holy crap! He's hauling!
I just gotta keep moving!
I have to try to close the gap!
[NANA]
We connected.
We can still come
back and win it!
[gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER 3A] Give it up
for Saisei's Kaede Okumura!
If you wanna see aerials,
then look no further!
He's got skills and he's
not afraid to show 'em off!
Always the entertainer,
even on the course!
Okumura's a serious competitor,
but knows what the fans want.
He's a crowd pleaser,
that's for sure!
This is Saisei!
This is Gal-Stan!
[AYUMU]
I can't do it.
Try as hard as I might,
I'm no match for these guys!
[AYUMU] It's useless.
I don't have their talent!
[gasps] Oh, no!
Don't give up now!
You've gotta keep going!
C'mon, Ayumu! Pick up your pace!
Isn't that a shame?
Seems our race is over
before it even began.
[NANA] We're four
seconds behind, Takeru!
Set!
Well, I guess I'll
see you later.
[NANA]
Three... two... one...
Go!
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
Saisei's Reiji Suwa
has the lead as he turns
the final corner!
Not long to go now,
ladies and gentlemen!
Suwa's making his final dash
toward the finish line!
[REIJI panting]
[SHIZUMA]
Watch out, he's catching up!
He's right behind you!
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
Saisei Academy high school
wins the match thanks to
the incredible Reiji Suwa!
Honan's Fujiwara made a valiant
effort at the end there.
Unfortunately, too
little too late.
[RIKU]
Takeru!
[REIJI panting]
[RIKU]
You okay? Here's some water!
Dude, that was sick!
[DAN] Even though the
time difference was only
0.4 seconds, in essence,
we were destroyed.
[gasps]
[rattling]
[AYUMU]
I'm sorry. It was all my fault.
That's not true!
[HEATH]
Yeah, for real, man.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
[NANA, HOZUMI gasp]
[HEATH]
Look, the records don't lie.
You might've felt like
you slowed us down
but you had one of
your best times.
You did a great job
out there today.
Thanks, President
of the Shogi Club.
[AYUMU gasping]
Way to go, you had
no reason to worry.
[AYUMU laughs]
I say, Kendo Chorai ! This is
just the beginning for us.
Uh. But, sir.
We lost the match, which means
that we lost our sponsor.
And we can't
compete without one.
[footsteps]
Did ya miss me?
[STRIDE CLUB gasps]
What're you doin' here Sis?
[RIKU]
Uh!
Now listen up!
I was gonna wait until
after the match,
but I decided to go ahead
and start a brand for you.
--[RIKU] Huh?
--[NANA] Really?
And I call it...
Runruly!
[ALL gasps]
But I don't understand.
You know we lost, right?
I am well aware, but Saisei's
sponsor is our rival.
[laughing]
[DIANE]
The way they gloated.
It seriously pissed me off!
[STRIDE CLUB whimpers]
[DIANE] If you lose wearing
Runruly, I will kill you all.
[RIKU] Whoa! These track
suits are the best ever!
Yeah, and they fit perfectly!
Must be made to order.
I know it's for running
but it'll also up my
intimidation factor in Shogi!
Wow, this is really comfortable!
I don't know about the logo,
I'm worried the fans
won't be able to see it.
It's kinda small.
Have I made the team
captain unhappy?
[HEATH] Shut up!
I was just trying to help!
Who cares about the logo?
You're the ones who're going
to sell the brand for me.
[ALL gasp]
[DIANE] Enough with the gloomy
blues, it was time for a change!
Now Honan Stride is
a crisp, clean white!
The color of new beginnings!
Fitting, don't you think?
And so it starts.
Yeah.
What starts?
I dunno.
[AYUMU laughs]
Only the biggest summer
Stride event in all
of East Japan!
Also known as--
[TAKERU]
End of Summer.
[AYUMU] Stop! You stole the
words outta my mouth again!
We call it EOS for short.
It's not somethin' you
can just sign up for.
In order to compete,
you have to pass the trials
and they start next month.
[RIKU]
Next time, I wanna win.
[ALL gasp]
Next time, we're
gonna defeat Saisei!
Uh?
[gasps]
[HOZUMI, AYUMU gasp, laugh]
[STRIDE CLUB]
Yeah! You know it!
[KAEDE] Jeez, what's with
all the racket in there?
[TASUKU]
Sounds like a party.
I've never heard of a team
celebrating a loss before.
Honestly, it doesn't
surprise me.
Honan Stride's always
been different.
Looks like they're back.
I don't know if I would
say that, Reiji.
They've got a lot of work to do
before they're a
major contender.
There's a distinct possibility
that they weren't at
their best today
simply because Kuga
wasn't competing.
I wonder why he didn't make it?
It must be 'cause he's
suffering from influenza!
[BANTARO]
Y'know, he's got a point,
what if the reason they
didn't do so hot today
is because they didn't
bring their best runner?
Well, I suppose it's possible.
They have a lot of
rookies on their team.
Hasekura was the
only third year.
Kuga's great.
But those first-year
runners aren't bad either.
[KAEDE]
Huh?
One competed in
the Under 15 matches,
and as it happens the other
is Tomoe Yagami's brother.
Whoa, seriously? Which guy?
[ASUMA] Heh. The guy that
I ran against today.
[REIJI]
This is going to be fun.
[AYUMU] It's the battle
for the End of Summer!
Determined to overcome his
overwhelming lack of talent,
Ayumu Kadowaki
begins secret training.
When a fierce enemy approaches,
he tackles it head on!
Can he make it to
the end in one piece?
Next on "Prinstride,"
"Farewell Kadowaki"!
[KAEDE]
Not you too, Kadowaki?!
Oh, no!