[NANA]
We've got a big day tomorrow.
You ready to race Saisei?
[TAKERU]
Yeah.
We're going to win.
It's what we've been
working toward.
Takeru?
[TAKERU]
Huh?
[RIKU gasps]
What's up?
Uh... I...
Well, uh, I just
wanna say thanks.
For what?
Y'know. I thought
Tomoe ruined Stride for me
'cause he made it a chore.
I hated it for a while.
But now, running with you
and the rest of the team
has made me realize
I love Stride.
In the beginning, I thought
you were hassling me
but now I know you were helping
me get my act together.
And I'm really glad you did.
I gotta say, I'm thankful you
guys forced me to join!
[TAKERU]
Not quite.
[RIKU]
Uh...
[TAKERU]
Sure, Sakurai and I invited you.
But the three of us were meant
to be in Stride together.
I don't follow you.
Uh. Hang on, are you
tryin' to say it's, like,
our destiny or somethin'?
No, I don't believe in destiny.
[RIKU gasps]
I'm confident that we'll win
the End of Summer tournament.
Because we made a--
[TAKERU]
Tomorrow we face Saisei.
Let's win!
Ha!
[RIKU]
Uh.
[NANA, RIKU]
Yeah!
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
The wait is over, folks!
After a season of training
and preparation,
our teams are ready.
The End of Summer semi-finals
are about to begin!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
Smile Land is proud
to be hosting this
year's competition!
Racing today we have
last year's semi-finalist,
also known as the popular
music group Galaxy Standard.
It's Saisei Academy
High School of Kanagawa!
[CROWD cheering]
Y'hear that?!
The crowd's goin'
insane for 'em!
Almost feels like we're
the away team, you know?
Yeah, those guys
have plenty of fans.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
And here's the one team
everyone has an eye on.
A returning juggernaut
in the world of Stride, Honan
Academy High School of Tokyo!
Honan!
[CROWD cheering]
--This is great!
--Honan all the way!
They're cheering for ya!
It looks like we have fans, too!
[HEATH]
Oh, man, this place is packed
and the energy from the crowd's
gettin' me hyped for the race!
Awesome!
[HOZUMI] My heart's about
to jump out of my chest.
Hozumi. Enjoy the fresh air.
The sun's shining
and the sky is clear.
It's a perfect day for Stride.
[ANNOUNCER 11A] Ladies and
gentlemen, the time has come!
Which of our teams will move on
to the End of Summer finals?
No matter the result,
this will definitely be
a race to remember!
Yes!
Let's keep our heads up
and our eyes on the prize.
'Cause This is my last chance.
[ANNOUNCER 11A] All right!
Let's get both teams onstage!
You Ready to do this, Honan?
[ALL]
Yeah!
All competitors,
bow to the opponent!
[ALL] Let's all make
this a good match!
How ya doin' there, Hozumi?
Since we're racin'
at Smile Land,
I say we run as
fast as we can
but try to have fun
at the same time!
That's easy, you've got
such a great attitude
you make everything
fun, Banchan!
Yeah, guess I do!
Everything's ♪ fu-fu-fu-fun! ♪
Now you!
♪ Fu-fu-fu-fun. ♪
Why sing Beethoven's 5th?
Why not? May it inspire us
to follow our destinies
and face our challenges
without fear!
[KAEDE]
Though I will always
think of myself as
your biggest fan--
with utmost respect I'd like to
become a worthy competitor.
I wanted to race but
only when I deserved
the privilege of facing you.
That's been my wish
for a long time now.
Today I think I'm finally
prepared to make it happen.
I will not lose.
How admirable.
That said, I have no
intention of losing, either.
Please go easy on me,
Mr. Team Captain.
Nice try but you're not gettin'
under my skin today, bro.
Ever since we first met,
you've said you're determined
to help Reiji get to
the top, no matter what.
Just wonderin' if
that's still true.
Absolutely. We're too
close to back down now.
Listen. Reiji and I have
somethin' in common.
If we lose this match,
it's over.
So I'm gonna run this race
like my life's on the line.
Heh. What, is that supposed
to intimidate me?
Enjoy running your last race.
[RIKU]
To throw salt on someone's game.
[ASUMA]
Huh?
[RIKU] It means to screw up
someone's plans.
In other words, by helping me
you could've messed up
your team's plans to win
the next match against us.
[ASUMA] So you finally
looked it up, huh?
[ASUMA] Gotta say,
I'm glad you didn't quit, man.
Thanks for believin' in me and
remindin' me why I love Stride.
Sorry I have to
kick your butt today.
Yeah, right!
All joking aside,
I can't think of anyone
I'd rather run against.
[REIJI]
Hey.
This should be a good race.
Yeah, I think so too.
[REIJI laughs] I can sense
those hidden feelings again.
They're bubbling up
inside of you.
Remember what I said last time?
Make sure you set
them free today.
[TAKERU]
I will.
You better not
chicken out on me.
Never.
I'm ready to let them go.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
All right, folks!
It won't be long now!
The moment of truth
is almost here!
In this round of the End
of Summer semi-finals
it's Saisei versus Honan.
Who'll come out on top?
The runners have taken
their starting positions,
and in just a few seconds,
the battle will begin!
[ANNOUNCER 1B]
On your mark...
Get set...
--[buzzing]
--[CROWD cheering]
[HOZUMI panting]
[BANTARO panting]
[SHIZUMA] Well, here we go,
are you ready for this?
You bet!
I've been working really hard
to build trusting relationships
with the team.
Just like you suggested!
Nice.
You're much more confident
than you were before.
This should be an awesome race.
Good luck, Nana.
You, too!
Just know that we're
gonna hit you
with everything we
learned at camp!
We've come a long
way since then!
[BANTARO]
I'm closin' in, Hozumi!
[HOZUMI] I can't believe
we've made it all the way
to the semi-finals.
This is Heath and Kyosuke's last
chance to win End of Summer.
If I screw this up,
then it's all over!
I've gotta do my best!
I've gotta get a lead for them!
[NANA]
Watch out, Hozumi!
[HOZUMI gasps]
[BANTARO]
Wee! Ha, ha, ha!
[HOZUMI]
No way!
[NANA] Don't worry about him!
Keep running straight ahead.
Take the high road!
It's close, Bantaro.
Stay sharp!
And I need you to--
Heh. Keep having fun!
[BANTARO] Aw yeah!
That's what I like to hear!
When you run with
a smile on your face
there's no
way you can lose!
[HOZUMI panting]
[NANA]
Okay, you're closing in!
Take it to full speed!
Trust Kyosuke!
[NANA]
Kyosuke. Get set!
He's coming in fast!
Ready.
[NANA]
Three!
Two!
One!
Go!
[KYOSUKE]
Hozumi!
Jump!
[HOZUMI panting]
[KYOSUKE]
I'll catch you, I promise!
You have to trust me!
[HOZUMI]
I do, Kyosuke!
[ANNOUNCER 11A] Honan completes
a mid-air relation!
Kohinata was in a tight spot
but that miraculous
move just saved him!
The spirit of Stride...
That was awesome.
Way to go, guys.
[BANTARO panting]
[HOZUMI sighs]
[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH]
Nice one, bro!
[KAEDE panting]
[KAEDE] I gotta run as fast
as I can to keep the lead!
If Kuga gets in front of me we
might never get ahead again!
[SHIZUMA]
He's coming up behind you!
[KAEDE gasping]
[KAEDE]
He passed me.
[KAEDE] There's no way
I can catch up with him!
What now?!
I could just follow behind
and trace his path.
Huh?!
[KAEDE]
No, I can't give up!
I've gotta push myself!
I'm worthy of
running against him!
I know I can beat him if I
give it everything I've got!
[KAEDE yells]
[NANA]
Get ready, Heath!
They're pretty much
neck-and-neck!
Well, well looks like
that first-year of yours
has some skills.
[NANA]
Get Set!
Three...
Two...
One...
Go!
[HEATH]
I'll take it from here!
[KYOSUKE]
Heath.
It's all up to you now.
Make our last summer count!
[HEATH] There's no runnin'
side-by-side with this chump.
[TASUKU]
Why'd he back off so easily?
He's got something
up his sleeve.
[HEATH]
Jeez, that was a risky move.
This is no time to be reckless.
Get injured in the semi-finals
and it's over for your team.
[TASUKU] I'll do whatever
it takes to get ahead!
We've come too far
to lose to Honan!
This is Reiji's last shot
at winning End of Summer.
We have to do it for him!
[HEATH]
Fine, then.
Two can play at that game.
I may be crazy for tryin' this,
but I've got to!
If we lose this match it's over.
I won't let our summer end.
[HEATH]
Not yet!
[HEATH grunts]
[NANA]
Hey, Riku. Can ya hear me?
[RIKU]
Yeah.
[NANA]
They're coming.
Let's win and go to finals.
It's all up to you now!
[RIKU inahles]
[TAKERU]
I'm confident
that we'll win the End
of Summer tournament.
Because we made a--
[NANA]
Head's up!
We're in the lead!
Point eight seconds!
[RIKU]
Got it!
Don't you worry, Takeru!
I'll be there in no time!
[TAKERU]
Riku.
[panting]
[TAKERU]
It's no use!
I'm running as fast as I can,
but it's not fast enough!
There's no way.
I'll run right into him!
[RIKU]
I know you can do it!
Run, Takeru!
[TAKERU]
Riku.
[ASUMA] The last half coming up
is all about endurance!
Luckily, it's also
Riku's weakness.
Which means it's time
to take it up to 11!
[RIKU] Asuma's haulin'!
I can barely keep up.
He's way faster than
he was back at the camp!
It doesn't matter!
I'm closin' in on him!
I've gotta push it so we
can win this thing!
We have to!
I'm confident that we'll win
the End of Summer tournament.
Because we made a--
[RIKU]
What'd he mean by that?
We made it our goal?
I mean, we did.
But that's not it!
[SHIZUMA]
Get ready, Reiji.
They're on their way.
[SHIZUMA]
It's tight.
Riku doesn't seem to be
slowing down at all.
In fact, he's right
on Asuma's heels.
It's up to you.
[REIJI]
Shizuma.
We'll win, for sure.
[gasps]
Of course we will.
--[NANA] Takeru, get set!
--Okay Reiji, get set!
[NANA]
We're 0.5 seconds behind!
[RIKU panting]
[NANA] Oh no, don't start
slowing down now.
Maybe I should wait
to make the call.
[TAKERU] Trust him!
I know he can do it!
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
Here we go, folks!
The final relation is coming up!
Three...
Two...
One!
[TAKERU] I'm running as fast as
I can, but it's not fast enough!
He's slowing down!
[RIKU]
No! Don't give up!
I know you can do it!
Run, Takeru!
[TAKERU panting]
[RIKU]
I'm totally spent.
I can't keep going much longer!
I know you can do it, Riku!
[panting]
[RIKU]
Takeru!
Go! Hurry!
[RIKU groaning]
Takeru!
Go! Hurry!
I remember.
It's all coming back.
[RIKU]
Good job, Takeru!
We make a great team!
When we get older we're gonna
crush it at End of Summer!
[TAKERU]
Yeah!
If you work really hard you'll
get faster than you are now!
Probably even faster than me!
Do you think so?
[laughs] 'Kay!
[NANA]
Isn't Stride so much fun?
[RIKU] Yeah! I'll bet
if we made a team
we could be the best
in the whole world!
[TAKERU]
I'll practice.
And then one day, the three of
us will be teammates for real!
--[NANA] Yeah!
--[RIKU] 'Kay!
And then we could
enter End of Summer!
That'd be awesome!
But wait, that means
we'll have to go
to the same high school one day.
[RIKU] Okay! Let's see,
the only school from Tokyo
that qualified for End of
Summer this year was...?
[TAKERU]
Honan!
Honan Academy.
Yeah, let's go there!
When we're old
and in high school,
we'll join the
Honan Stride Club!
Then we can beat all the other
teams and win the End of Summer!
You think we can win?!
[RIKU] If we're gonna do it we
might as well aim for the top!
If we work really hard,
I know we can win it!
[RIKU]
Yeah!
[NANA]
I'm in!
We're gonna win
the End of Summer!
[ALL]
It's a promise!
[TAKERU]
Yes!
I'm going to keep my promise!
[AYUMU gasps]
Go, Reiji!
[TAKERU panting]
[RIKU]
If you work really hard
you'll get faster
than you are now!
[TAKERU]
I will!
[RIKU]
I'll bet if we made a team,
we could be the best
in the whole world!
[TAKERU]
You were right, Riku.
It's just like you said.
[TAKERU]
We're the best!
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
The winner is...
...Honan Academy first-year
student, Takeru Fujiwara!
Incredible!
He beat Reiji Suwa
of Saisei High School
by a mere fraction of a second!
[RIKU]
Hey, buddy.
You know that's not good for ya.
How many times have you told me
you're supposed to catch your
breath before you collapse,
huh? [laughs]
[TAKERU chuckles]
It's like watching baby
birds leaving the nest.
I thought these kinds
of emotional breakthroughs
only happened in the
best Shogi matches!
Hey now, don't start that,
you'll get me goin', too!
[HEATH]
This is a happy moment, man.
No need for waterworks.
What makes you think
I'm crying?!
Maybe it got really hot
on the bleachers
and I'm sweating from my eyes!
[HEATH] Okay, dude.
Whatever helps with the shame.
[HOZUMI laughing]
[HEATH]
Aw, man, did I make it worse?
C'mon, pull it together, bro.
[REIJI]
Nice work, Honan Stride.
Congratulations on
making it to the finals.
We enjoyed racin' you today,
and I mean that.
We had a great time, as usual.
Thanks again for
everything you did for us.
It was our pleasure, Heath.
Next you have to face Kakyoin.
You can bet we'll be rooting
for Honan all the way.
Thanks.
Oh, and Takeru, I can't
wait to see you outrun
every athlete at the finals.
You're an incredible talent.
Thanks.
[ASUMA]
Riku!
[RIKU]
Uh.
Ow, be careful, bro!
[ASUMA]
I'm so proud of you!
You remember that at the finals.
It's all up to you.
Promise you'll put your heart
and soul into winning!
[RIKU gasps]
[RIKU]
I will.
You bet I will!
[REIJI]
Congratulations, Honan Stride!
Time to celebrate!
Here is a special
song just for you!
[GALAXY STANDARD singing]
[NANA]
Beautiful!
To think I first met you
guys seven years ago.
And at an EOS pre-party,
too. It's crazy, huh?
Yeah, it was all new to me.
I'd never heard
of Stride before.
[RIKU]
Good job, Takeru!
We make a great team!
When we get older we're gonna
crush it at End of Summer!
[NANA]
I'm sorry that I forgot!
[RIKU]
Yeah, me too, man!
But to be fair,
you look way different thank
you did seven years ago!
Well, except for the stoic
look and the glasses.
Okay. My bad.
Sorry it took me this
long to recognize you.
Are we cool?
I'm not upset that you forgot.
All that matters is the
three of us are together
doing stride again.
Just like we said we would.
You may not remember,
but we made a promise
to one another that day,
and I want to make it a reality.
We promised to win
End of Summer someday.
Didn't we?
Yeah.
I think we should make
the promise again tonight!
Agreed! This year the three
of us and our team,
Honan Stride, are gonna
win the End of Summer!
[TAKERU, NANA]
Yeah!
[ALL]
It's a promise!
[ALL laughing]
[RIKU]
Hey, guys.
I have something to confess.
[NANA]
Huh?
I've been thinking,
and I've decided I
wanna run against Tomoe.
[TAKERU, NANA gasp]
You sure about that?
I'm not running away anymore.
[TAKERU]
Good.
[REIJI] All right Honan,
we only ask one thing.
Please accept the well wishes
of the Galaxy Standard
"Beautiful Eight."
[HEATH]
"Beautiful Eight"?
[REIJI] What, don't you
find us beautiful?
[SHIZUMA]
Allow me to explain,
the seventh generation
of Gal-Stan,
the one before us, was
called the "Exotic Seven."
[REIJI]
Je t'aime , Andromeda.