[NANA]
Stride.
It's a spark that ignites
a runner's will
to reach faraway places
and lofty goals.
[NANA] In an unfamiliar town,
on an unfamiliar road,
five runners and one Relationer
come together,
with their hearts connected,
running like the wind.
[NANA]
Two hands slap together.
A relay so perfect,
it's as if they had no doubt
that it would happen.
Energy is transferred from
one runner to the next.
Which then pushes that runner
to move even faster.
[NANA] Stride.
It brings people together.
It requires more trust and
connection between teammates
than any other sport.
[HOZUMI]
Not bad! Not bad guys.
Riku, don't push
against the landing
you need to remember to cushion
it so you can soften the blow.
Don't put excess pressure
on your ankles.
Gotcha!
[HOZUMI]
And Takeru,
you're starting your
jump a little early.
Get closer before
you make your move.
Will do.
Hey, Ayumu.
Let's raise the bar another
five centimeters!
[AYUMU]
Aye aye, sir!
I'd like you to spend some time
working on defensive tactics.
It'll depend on the course,
but the streets in Shibuya
are pretty narrow.
Let's try a two-hundred meter
dash with a tighter track.
Kuga, I want you to block
Hasekura from passing
and come in under 24 seconds.
--[KYOSUKE] Sounds good.
--[HEATH] Let's do it!
[HEATH]
All right, listen up.
[RIKU]
It's so hot!
It's summer, of course
it's gonna be hot.
No! Really?!
I thought it was winter!
[HEATH] You don't have to
be such a smart ass, bro.
[AYUMU]
Here.
[HOZUMI]
Oh, thank you.
It's so stinking hot
I was worried I was
gonna melt head first.
[HEATH] You need to remember
to stay hydrated, guys.
We only have two weeks
until the Kakyoin match.
We gotta be at our best
or we don't stand a chance.
So make sure you
get plenty of rest,
at least seven or
eight hours a night.
[AYUMU] Ooh! Did you secretly
sneak off to medical school
and become a doctor? You've
got all the pro health tips!
Hooray for Dr. Hasekura!
[HEATH]
Would you morons shut up?
[BOTH]
Whatever you say, Doctor!
All right everyone.
Let's get back to work.
It's about time we moved
on to Relation practice.
Now listen up,
the relay order's gonna be
Yagami, Kuga, Kohinata,
Hasekura, and then Fujiwara.
[ALL]
Yes sir!
We're counting on you, anchor.
Our will is in your hands.
It's up to you, Takeru.
Yep. You've totally got this!
It's crazy to think we've
got a first-year runner
as our anchor but you're
just that awesome, man!
[HOZUMI]
No doubt about it!
Forget it.
Yagami should be the anchor
in the Kakyoin match.
Uh!
[HOZUMI]
Uh. Hold up.
What did he say?!
You want Riku with his
incredible rocket start
to be our anchor?!
Are you serious?
I dunno, man.
Riku's never run
that position before.
It'd be like we were starting
over from scratch.
We can't just put
him in the position
and see how it works out
at the friggin' finals.
[TAKERU]
Trust me.
It may sound crazy, but he'll
run faster than anyone
if he runs against Tomoe.
[AYUMU]
Huh. He's got a good point
but there's no way
of guaranteeing
Tomoe's gonna run
anchor for Kakyoin.
[RIKU]
It'll be him. I know it.
He's the fastest
runner they've got.
It's a risky move, but please...
I want to run
against my brother.
[TAKERU]
Please take a chance on Riku
and grant him this opportunity.
[RIKU]
It would mean the world to me
if you'd let me be the anchor.
[TAKERU, RIKU]
We're begging you!
What the...?! Seriously?
I don't have any
problem with it.
Are you kiddin' me?
No, it makes perfect
sense to me.
Given their history,
Riku's bound to run his
fastest against his brother.
He's very strong willed.
'Kay, Let's go for it.
[HEATH]
Uh.
[AYUMU] Riku's got an
impressive starting dash
but in our last match he
proved he's got stamina, too.
You saw it!
He even got faster towards
the end of the race!
[HOZUMI]
Whaddya think?
[sighs] Am I the only
one who's worried
about taking a risk
this late in the game?
[HOZUMI] Aw c'mon,
you know you're all for it!
Just admit it!
Well, Mr. Dan. Whaddya think?
[DAN]
Mm. Manjou icchi .
From this day forward,
we will practice with Yagami
in the anchor position.
[RIKU] Thank you, sir!
You won't regret it!
That Practice nearly killed me!
No joke. And look at those guys.
I can't believe they're still
going at it after that.
[HOZUMI grunts]
They're just nervous
'cause we haven't done
a Takeru to Riku relation
since the beginning
of the school year.
[AYUMU] How has it been
four months already?
Time sure flies when
you're having fun.
Yep.
That reminds me.
[AYUMU]
U-Uh...
[HOZUMI]
It's been a long time
since we've played
a game of Shogi.
We're not playin'...
...till we win!
[HEATH]
What a crazy day.
I really hope we made the right
choice lettin' Riku be anchor.
It's funny, he didn't even
wanna join Stride at first.
Now our chances of winning
EOS are all ridin' on him.
You had to have known
this might happen.
Yeah, I guess.
The thought crossed my mind
when I heard his last name.
Even so, I chose to give
him the starter position.
It works for him.
He's not great at obstacles,
and most courses have a ton
of 'em towards the end.
He'll be an awesome anchor,
but I'm losin' the fastest
starting dash on the team.
I dunno who to put in his place.
[KYOSUKE snickers]
[HEATH]
I heard that.
What's so funny, bro?
Nothing.
[sighs] There's so
much to figure out,
and I'm runnin' outta time.
I'll see ya.
Later.
Uh? Hey wait a minute,
where's your bike?
It's at home.
I'm not riding,
not until finals are over!
What is with you guys?
Man.
Guess I better do the same!
[NANA] It's amazing how much
everyone has improved
since we started
training in April.
Starting tomorrow, we'll
have the team practice
as though they're running
the actual race.
That Sounds like a plan.
Sakurai, I don't mean to pry.
But how are you
feeling these days?
I'm great!
Never been better!
Good to hear.
Let's make sure your father
sees how happy you are.
Yeah!
[DAN] I commend you all
for your hard work.
At this point,
we've done everything we can
to prepare for the finals.
I want you to go home
and get some rest.
We've got a big day tomorrow.
[STRIDE CLUB]
Yes, sir!
Ichiro Maishin , If you work
hard to achieve your goals,
the path to victory
will clear itself.
I'm proud of you.
[STRIDE CLUB]
Thank you, Mr. Dan.
Hey, man.
So how ya feelin'?
About what?
[HEATH]
About Your Relation.
You know, with Takeru?
[RIKU]
Oh! Uh.
It's goin' great!
You nervous at all?
Uh... Kinda, I guess.
But there's more
to it than that.
Kakyoin has no idea how
much we've improved
since we raced them
at the time trials.
We'll show 'em tomorrow.
You excited?
[RIKU] I mean yeah,
but its hard to explain.
You're right. I'm
definitely excited,
but also really nervous, and
the anticipation is killing me!
It's a mix of all those things.
I feel ya.
Here's a bummer,
can you believe that our
summer break is almost over?
We've been training
so hard it flew by!
[HEATH]
For real.
Uhh, the last thing I wanna
think about right now
is homework.
[laughs] Yeah, I'm with ya!
We've only got one
more week of vacation
and then it's back
to the grind...
That means it's the--
[TAKERU]
End of Summer.
[AYUMU]
Stop!
You stole the words
outta my mouth!
[ANNOUNCER 12A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the event
considered the pinnacle
of high school Stride
in East Japan!
The winner of the End of Summer
tournament will be determined
in our final match today!
[REIJI]
Hello, hello!
How's it going, Honan?
[HONAN STRIDE]
Uh...
Did we surprise you?
We just wanted to say hi.
Hozumi! I'm here
to cheer for ya!
[HOZUMI]
Banchan!
[REIJI]
You ready to win?
[HEATH]
Yeah, you know it!
I heard you're not the
anchor for this race.
No, it's Riku's turn.
And I trust him.
Gotcha, well I'll be
rooting for you.
Y'know, I'm gonna be really
pissed off if you lose.
Reiji never got the chance.
So you gotta win EOS for him!
[HEATH]
I will. Count on it, bro.
Wow, So you're the
anchor now, huh?
Dude, you're so gonna kill it.
I can't wait to watch you
cut through that finish line!
Ha, ha!
Thank you, man.
OMG. No way!
Yeah! Asuma from Gal-Stan!
This is bad!
The fans spotted me!
If you didn't wanna be found,
then you shoulda come incognito.
Too late now!
Bye! And Best of luck to ya!
[ASUMA laughing]
[GIRLS shrieking]
[PA 12A]
Attention competitors,
please make your
way to the stage.
Well, we made it to
the finals, you guys.
If we play our cards right,
this could be Honan
Stride's big comeback.
All we gotta do now
is win this thing.
Let's do it!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ANNOUNCER 12A]
Believe it or not,
the very first Stride
event in Japan,
Naked Speed, was held
right here in Shibuya.
And now the finals of the
End of Summer tournament
have come back to where
the legend began!
Today, the King of Stride,
Joe Sakurai, will be competing
against his daughter, Nana,
the Princess of Stride!
This is gonna be
a good one, folks!
Today's match is sure to
be one for the record books!
Let's begin.
Honan Academy
High School, Tokyo!
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
[REFEREE 12A]
And Kakyoin High School, Miyagi!
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
[REFEREE 12A]
Welcome to the final race
of the End of Summer tournament!
Now, bow to your opponent!
[ALL]
May the best team win!
[CROWD cheering]
[PA 12A]
Attention competitors,
please take your
starting positions.
[gasps]
Takeru.
I'll fulfill our promise.
I swear it.
Yeah.
Tomoe.
[TOMOE]
Hey, Riku.
You're Honan's anchor?
[RIKU]
Yeah.
Really? That just doesn't
seem right to me.
Oh, yeah? And why's that?
Well, I don't mean to be rude,
but I thought Kyosuke or
Fujiwara would be anchor.
[TOMOE]
I'm sorry.
I just... I don't
get why you're here.
[HEATH]
All right, Nana.
It's about that time.
Let's do a quick mic check.
[NANA]
Okay!
You heard the Captain, guys!
Is everybody ready?
[AYUMU]
Go out there and kick some butt!
[NANA] Ah! Calm down, senpai!
We're doing a mic check!
[HOZUMI]
I'm ready!
Hozumi here, totally hyped,
and maybe a little nervous.
This place is packed!
Even Shibuya's back streets
are overflowing!
[HEATH] Well yeah, everyone
comes out to see the finals.
I'm good, you, Kyosuke?
[KYOSUKE]
Yes, I'm in place.
[TAKERU]
Takeru here.
I'm ready to go.
[TAKERU]
Hey...
[HONAN STRIDE]
Anchor!
Yeah, this is Riku.
I'm as ready as I'll ever be.
Let's do this, Honan!
How bout you. Ready, Relationer?
[NANA]
Yep!
All right everyone, this is the
moment we've been waiting for.
I know we're nervous but
let's do our best today!
We've gotta fight,
for all the other teams we've
defeated to get this far!
We can do it!
Let's win this! Okay, guys?!
--[HEATH] Hell yeah!
--[HOZUMI] Woohoo!
[RIKU]
You really wanna know?
Huh?
I'm here because I wanna be.
[ANNOUNCER 1B]
On your mark.
Get set.
[buzzing]
[RIKU] Remember when we
used to run together?
Even though you'd cheer me on,
I could never seem
to catch up with you.
It bothered me so much
it created a block
that kept me from
getting any faster.
[RIKU] I decided I might
as well give up on Stride
since I could never
be as good as you.
But I realized...
...I couldn't completely
give up on it.
I would skip the bus,
run to school,
and jump the gates
when I was late.
--[TOYA] Let's go!
--[NANA] Go!
[RIKU]
When I started at Honan,
a couple of weirdoes
pushed me to join Stride.
It's more like they forced me,
but to be honest,
I'm really glad they did.
I'm countin' on you!
[RIKU] Before we joined, Honan
Stride was a shell of a club.
It was just Heath,
Hozumi, and Ayumu,
so they were happy to have us.
Kyosuke joined later and
suddenly we had a full roster!
--[BANTARO] Aw, yeah!
--[KAEDE] Go!
[RIKU] We've competed against a
lot of great teams to get here.
And every single one of them has
taught us an important lesson.
Not just about the sport,
but about ourselves.
[HOZUMI grunts]
[RIKU] I'm here 'cause this
is where I'm meant to be.
Running alongside my brother.
[TOMOE gasps]
And also 'cause I have a
promise to keep with my friends.
Kay, Here we go, Takeru!
We've got the lead
by 0.4 seconds.
Get set!
[AMATSU] So, fool, you still
think you're gonna beat me.
Absolutely.
Huh?!
I have to, because
I made a promise.
[NANA]
Three!
Two!
[TAKERU]
We'll win End of Summer!
--[NANA] Go!
--There's no stopping us!
[HOZUMI panting]
Takeru!
[TAKERU]
Right here!
[TOMOE]
You have a promise to keep?
You've come a long way, Riku.
[TAKERU panting]
[TAKERU]
Yes!
This it is!
This is what we've worked for!
An ideal Stride team
made up of close friends!
This is what I've
always wanted!
And now, it's finally
become a reality!
[TAKERU]
I can't let this guy pass me!
If he does,
it'll ruin everything!
I can go faster, I know it!
[TAKERU] I've gotta keep
the lead for Riku!
Impressive, your friend's fast.
He's leading Amatsu.
Listen Tomoe,
don't go easy on me.
Don't plan to and
just so you know,
I have never gone easy on you.
[gasps]
[RIKU]
Thanks, I remember that.
Here we go.
You ready for this, Riku?
It's all up to you now,
so run like the wind!
[HOZUMI]
Believe in yourself!
'Cause we believe in you!
[AYUMU] Sure, you've been
knocked down a few times
but you always get back up.
And every time it
makes you stronger!
[KYOSUKE] We will be the wind
that carries you to victory.
You can do it, go forth
and have no fear.
[HEATH] Hit Tomoe with
everything you've got!
Show him Riku Yagami's run!
Come on!
[TAKERU] Riku, when I met you
and Nana seven years ago,
I figured out what was
missing from my life.
It was the first time
I felt like I belonged.
Three.
[TAKERU] I finally had
a goal to work towards.
[NANA]
Two!
[TAKERU]
You trusted me and pushed me
to become a better runner.
I'm the athlete I am
today because of you.
[NANA]
One!
[TAKERU] I'm honored to
run on a team with you,
and to call you my friend.
[NANA]
Go!
[TAKERU]
The only reason I'm here today,
is because you took a
chance on me back then.
You changed my life forever!
Thank you, Riku.
[RIKU]
Jeez, Takeru!
Why'd you have to go
and say that?!
Save the mushy stuff
for after the race!
[RIKU]
It's hard to run Stride
when you've got
tears in your eyes.
[NANA panting]
[TEACHER 1A]
Better hurry up!
You don't wanna
start tardy, do ya?
[NANA gasps]
I barely made it.
[gate closes]
[gasps]
[RIKU groaning]
Well, looks like I win!
Nope. I win because
I stuck the landing.
The deal was whoever
gets here first,
and my foot was on
the gate way before you!
[NANA]
Morning!
[TAKERU]
Uh.
[RIKU laughs]
[HEATH]
This is... RTS!
[AYUMU]
Do-over!
I said no!
You heard me this is
Real Time Shogi!
Don't be a jerk about it,
dontcha remember the time
I let you do it?
Not really.
And what time was that?
You don't happen to recall the
year, month, day, hour, minute,
and rotational position
of the Earth, do ya?
I'd resign if I were you.
[HOZUMI] Okay, so the object
of the game is to capture
your opponent's king.
To do that...
Hey!
--I demand a do-over!
--[HEATH] Not gonna happen, bro.
[RIKU] You guys fightin'
about Shogi again?
Yes, because unlike you two,
we take our roles in
this club seriously--
I'm never playing Shogi.
[AYUMU]
Denied, yet again!
[NANA] As the cicadas sing,
a warm wind blows by.
Carrying so many
emotions with it.
[NANA] The sun shines
brightly overhead,
as summer finally
comes to an end.
[NANA]
Okay, guys!
Let's make this a great day!
Zento Youyou --
Hibi Shoujin .
--[HEATH] Ain't that right!
--[AYUMU] You got it!
[NANA] But our story
doesn't end here.
No, not by a long shot.
It will continue on and on.
[NANA]
My story.
[RIKU, TAKERU]
Our story
[NANA, RIKU, TAKERU] The story
of how we found our Stride.
[NANA]
Takeru, where are you going?
[TAKERU]
For a run.
We've gotta keep up
with our training.
[RIKU] Yeah, we get it but
aren't you forgetting something.
Here we go!
[HONAN STRIDE] Thank you
for watching "PrinStride"!