[ALL gasp]
Dude, you're late.
Welcome back.
Kyosuke Kuga,
third-year student.
I'd like to sign up for the
Stride Club starting today.
Awesome!
Now that you're on the team,
you're gonna need a uniform
so I'll lend you mine.
Not like I need it. Here!
That's very kind of you.
This is a...
little bit tight for me.
Yeah, I'll say.
Can you even run in that?
There, much better.
[AYUMU] Ooh! Way to
represent with style!
The wind's blowing
strongly today.
To be honest,
I find it comforting.
[gasps]
[NANA]
Honan Stride is back.
Just like the video!
[RIKU, NANA laugh]
[SHIKI] You had me worried for
a while there, Honan Academy.
[HEATH]
Hey, Dozono.
[SHIKI]
Hasekura.
Your team found a new member,
just in the nick of time.
Well, well, the infamous
Kyoske Kuga.
I'm surprised you're back.
I thought your career was over
after that nasty
assault incident.
So the little guy in glasses
isn't gonna be
running this time?
Aw, what a shame.
But at least there's more
of a challenge this way,
if he ran we'd annihilate you.
You don't know how
hard he's worked!
Chill out!
Scary! You're gonna fight me?
You guys're so aggressive!
Honan must be a rough place.
Let's try to get
through this match
without anyone being assaulted.
[NANA, RIKU exhale]
Who's this guy?
Is he the Relationer
for Ichijokan?
Something tells me this
is gonna be a tough one.
Thank you for waiting,
ladies and gentlemen,
today's match is about to begin.
Would the Ichijokan
High School team
please come up to the stage?
[SHIKI]
That would be me.
We'll see you on the course,
and remember,
let's try to keep
it civil, okay?
Is it just me or was
that guy super rude?
I wanted to slap that
perma-smirk off his face.
Don't let him get to you, man.
Ha! Honan Stride's about to
start an exciting new chapter!
[ANNOUNCER 5AA] Next up, we have
Honan Academy High School.
Here we go guys!
[ANNOUNCER 5AA] Would you
please come to the stage?
[ALL]
Yeah.
[REFEREE 6A] Competing in
Shinjuku's Trial Tour
are Ichijokan High
School of Hokkaido
and Honan Academy
High School of Tokyo.
Both teams, line up
in your running order.
Well, I'll be.
Honan's Relationer is a girl.
Nice to meet you.
Let's do our best out there.
Hey, so are you really
Tomoe Yagami's little brother?
Uh, yes, I am. Why?
I heard that your bro
is stupid fast.
I bet you're super stoked to
have such an awesome runner
for a brother, aren't ya?
Well, I dunno if I'd
call it "super stoked."
It's nice to meet ya.
I'm lookin' forward to the race.
C'mon, drop the act.
[HEATH]
Huh?
Why bother being
polite to the guy
you're gonna
end up losin' to?
[HEATH] His smack talk's just
gettin' me more fired up.
Hey, I'm Kaoru Shishibara.
I've seen you run before man,
and you're pretty good.
But that was a long time ago.
Hope you can keep up with me.
Here's a warning, girly-boy.
What'd you call me?
You've been spoiled
by easy victories
but that's about to change.
I take this
competition seriously,
and there's no way
I'm gonna lose.
You can run as fast as you
want but it won't matter.
In the end, I will crush you and
my team'll take home the title.
Takeru Fujiwara, right?
Your record's pretty
impressive for a first-year.
'Kay, I guess you're not
into shaking hands.
You look nervous there, sport,
but I would be too if my team
had to face our princess.
[TAKERU]
You can't intimidate me.
I'm simply going to do my
best and trust my teammates.
[KIYOTO]
Easier said than done.
That Kuga guy's got a shady past
and it's been a while
since he's raced.
[ANNOUNCER 6A] This is it,
ladies and gentlemen,
the second match of
the EOS Trial Tour
will begin momentarily!
Here we go!
[ALL]
May the best team win!
[CROWD cheers]
[NANA] We were so close
to not competing.
Now that we can, we have to win!
[NANA]
Uh?
I have to admit,
I find you rather intimidating.
Who me? Really?
[SHIKI] I saw your last match
and I was incredibly impressed.
I found your dogged pursuit
of victory inspiring.
[NANA] Thanks, that's nice
of you to say.
[SHIKI]
I'm being completely honest.
I've always admired those who'll
do whatever it takes to win.
As we both know, in Stride,
you're worthless if you lose.
I have to disagree.
Stride's about more than
just winning and losing,
at least it is to me.
[SHIKI]
Uh... Huh?
During every match
it's my goal to connect with my
teammates on an emotional level.
[SHIKI laughs]
I'm sorry for laughing,
but do you realize how creepy
that sounds, Nana?
[NANA]
Uh.
[SHIKI] Heh. Anyway,
I can't make any promises
but I'll try to play nice, okay?
After all, I'd hate
to break you.
Best of luck to you
and your team.
Here's hoping that
your teammates
don't get themselves
disqualified again.
[gasps]
[AYUMU]
Woo! And here I thought
the winds couldn't
any crazier today!
Here's that drink you wanted.
Uh. What's up, Nana?
Something bothering you?
Maybe I was wrong.
I've always thought
Stride was about connecting
the runners' emotions.
[gasps]
[exhales]
I dunno.
If every Stride team was
emotionally connected,
things would probably
be pretty different.
Like, I doubt the KGB incident
would've happened.
I mean, sure,
it requires trust
between teammates
but that's true of any
sport, not just Stride.
You follow me?
Yeah, I guess so.
But...
I learned something
from getting hurt.
There's no way I can
run in my condition,
but I wanna contribute.
It sucks.
'Cause I wanna help out
but I'm useless right now.
I almost didn't
come along today,
till I realized there
is something I can do.
I can be here for you guys,
to cheer you on
throughout the race.
'Cause Stride's more than
just winning or losing.
There's something
about you guys.
You first years, I mean.
You're helping us to connect.
Y'know, now that
I think about it.
Maybe you're right.
I suppose what I feel
could be considered
an "emotional connection",
after all.
That's what I would call it.
[AYUMU]
All right, I should get going.
I'll be rooting for you
from the stands!
'Kay!
Thank you!
[SHIKI] I may have taunted
them a bit but nothing major.
It's funny how
flustered they get.
[YURI] You go ahead and
play your mind games,
but we're gonna focus
on winning the match.
Yeah well, that's gonna
take some effort
now that Kuga's
back on the team.
There's gotta be a way we can
use him to our advantage.
I'm sure we can find a
wound to rub salt into.
Look, whatever,
I just wanna win this.
All right. Leave it to me.
Ready, Hachiya?
[TETSU]
Let's get this show on the road!
[ANNOUNCER 1B]
On your mark...
Get set...
[TETSU] Dude, it must
be pretty stressful.
Knowing everyone's gonna
compare you to your brother.
[buzzer]
[ANNOUNCER 6A] And both teams
are off to a good start!
[laughs]
[NANA]
Was he laughing?
Why?
[NANA]
That's weird.
Why'd Riku start
the race at top speed?
[RIKU panting]
[NANA]
He's already out of breath.
What happened?
Something's wrong.
[RIKU grunting]
[RIKU]
This is tough.
[TETSU]
He can't keep this up forever.
He's gonna break.
Any second now.
[RIKU]
This course is endless!
I'm startin' to lose steam!
I know!
[TETSU]
Nice try!
[RIKU]
He dodged it!
I can't...
[RIKU panting]
[TOMOE]
Aw, c'mon, Riku.
You gotta try harder than that.
[RIKU]
I'm trying as hard as I can!
Trust me!
You're gonna have
to get a lot faster
if you wanna compete in Stride.
You have talent but
you've gotta train.
That's the only way
to get to my level.
[RIKU]
I tried my best.
I gave it my all but it
wasn't enough for him.
He made me feel worthless.
That's why...
I have to prove myself!
[NANA] Keep it up, Riku!
You've got this!
You're almost there!
[NANA]
Heath's ready and waiting!
Go!
[RIKU grunting]
Sorry!
[HEATH]
No apologies needed!
You done good, kid!
[panting]
[HEATH]
This blows!
The guy keeps blockin' me!
I can't get around him!
[SHIKI]
I don't wanna brag or anything
but Samejima's
block rate is 100%.
Looks like we're gonna
win this segment, too.
[NANA]
All right, Kyosuke. Get set!
We're behind 0.5 seconds!
[inahles]
[NANA]
I can picture his speed.
I know we can do it.
A perfect relation,
just like the video!
[NANA]
Go!
[SHIKI]
Shishibara.
Go!
[KYOSUKE panting]
[SHIKI] Hasekura's endurance
never ceases to amaze me.
[NANA]
Uh.
Most runners would've petered
out by now but he's
giving it everything he's got
right up until the very end.
It's great.
He'd probably win
against anybody else.
But Shishibara's got
a one-track mind.
He's focused passing
the guy in front of him.
[gasps]
If they stay at this pace,
they might collide.
[gasps]
[KYOSUKE]
Heath!
[NANA]
Slow down, Heath!
You've gotta hold back!
[HEATH]
Not falling for it!
[NANA gasps]
He's running faster!
[BOTH panting]
[HEATH]
Kyosuke.
I've waited for so long.
I was worried I'd never get the
chance to run with you again.
[KYOSUKE] Now that we've
let go of the past...
[HEATH, KYOSUKE] ...we won't
let anyone get in our way!
[HEATH]
Together, I know we can do it.
We're gonna make it
all the way to the top!
[knocking]
I knew that you'd come.
Nice to see ya.
[KYOSUKE]
How're you feeling?
[AYUMU]
Much better than before.
Well, that's good.
It seems Hozumi's
not too keen on you
coming back to Stride.
I guess it's because
he's had to watch Heath
go through the
wringer ever since
that whole mess
went down last year.
He's got some
pent-up frustration.
Yeah.
And, now that I'm hurt,
he feels like he's
responsible somehow.
But it had nothing to
do with him, y'know?
Right.
[AYUMU] There's no way I'm gonna
be able to run this weekend.
I hate to ask you this,
but I'm in a bind.
Would you cover
for me at the match?
I'd love to. Sure that's
what you want?
[AYUMU] Yeah, I think
it's good for the team
to have more members.
Just remember one thing, senpai.
Once my injuries are healed up,
I'm takin' back my spot!
[ANNOUNCER 6A] Honan takes
the lead as the teams
make their way to...
[SHIKI]
Dammit!
All they had to do was keep
the lead and they blew it!
We'd better not lose. Ah!
[SHIKI]
There you go, Shishibara!
C'mon, I know you can
outrun that loser!
Get our lead back! Do whatever
you gotta do to win!
Hey, Kuga- senpai !
You've got this!
I believe in you!
[KYOSUKE]
Thanks, Ayumu.
[KYOSUKE, KAORU panting]
[KYOSUKE] He can't handle
the wind like I can.
--[DAN] Kadowaki!
--Win it! Please, do it for me!
[KYOSUKE] I'm going to do
my best to make that happen!
[HOZUMI]
I have to Relation with Kyosuke.
I dunno. I don't think I can.
[YURI] Whatcha thinkin' about?
If I were you,
I'd stay focused on the race
I'm about to run instead of
whatever's going on inside
that pea-brain of yours.
You think you've
got this in the bag?
Well guess again, girly-boy,
'cause my team's a force
to be reckoned with.
Underestimate us
and you'll regret it.
[NANA]
Okay, Hozumi!
Get set!
[HOZUMI] I can't let my
feelings about Kyosuke
ruin this match for us.
I have to let go of the past.
Heath has waited a long time
to get the chance to
run with him again.
I've gotta do it for him!
[ANNOUNCER 6A] Kuga's making
his way from the outside!
He's right behind Shishibara!
[KYOSUKE] I know this
is hard for you, Hozumi,
but you have to remember...
[HOZUMI]
You didn't leave out of spite.
You were trying to
protect the club.
[KYOSUKE]
I'm so thankful
everyone's welcomed
me back to the team.
[HOZUMI]
On one condition...
Don't ever ditch us again!
[KYOSUKE]
I promise.
I'll protect Honan Stride
with my life!
[HOZUMI panting]
[HOZUMI]
He's got the lead.
I've made it through
the hardest part,
now I've gotta focus on
getting past this guy!
[ANNOUNCER 6A] Look at Himemiya
fly over those obstacles
and Kohinata's right behind him!
It's neck-and-neck, folks!
[YURI] Well played,
girly-boy, well played.
[SHIKI grunts] What's the
matter with you, Himemiya?
You were supposed to use
the obstacles to get ahead!
You screwed us!
Can't you idiots see you're
completely ruining my strategy?
You better start following my
commands or we're gonna lose!
Let's not forget that
I'm the Relationer,
you morons can't
even start running
until I give you the call!
You've got it easy!
All you boneheads have to do
is listen to me and do as I say!
You shouldn't talk to
your team like that.
The hell...?
[NANA] Whether Relationer
or runner, everyone's equal.
When one of us is down,
it affects the entire team.
And we work through it,
together.
That's how it's supposed
to be anyway.
You'd understand if you weren't
so preoccupied with winning.
[SHIKI growls]
You've done nothing but belittle
your teammates the whole race.
You should try working with them
instead of barking
orders at them.
[SHIKI]
Shut up, bitch!
Don't tell me how to do my job!
C'mon, Himemiya!
You've gotta take back the lead!
Pass that guy and show
this bitch how we do this!
Do you hear me?
That's an order from
your Relationer!
How dare you turn
your radio off
while I'm talking, you princess!
[YURI] I've had enough
of your yelling, Dozono.
There's nothing you
can do at this point.
It's up to us to win!
[HOZUMI] Honan Stride is back.
There's no stopping us now.
We have to win!
Together, I know we can!
[NANA] Okay Takeru,
we're 0.5 seconds ahead!
Three... Two...
One...
Go!
[HOZUMI]
Takeru!
[HOZUMI groans]
Go!
[KIYOTO, TAKERU panting]
[KIYOTO]
Whoa, this guy's so fast!
I can't keep up with him!
What the--?
No way! He keeps
picking up his speed!
[TAKERU]
I have to go faster.
[KIYOTO]
Are you kidding me?
[TAKERU]
Faster! I've gotta push it!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
And we have a winner!
Let's hear it for Honan!
I told you this would
be a close one, folks,
and I wasn't lying!
Both teams killed it but in
the end Ichijokan's anchor
was no match for
Honan's Fujiwara.
Today's win for
Honan Academy means
they'll be moving on to the
next round of the competition!
[SHIKI] Ah! Those idiots!
All they had to do was run!
How'd they screw this up?!
We would've won if
they had listened to me!
We won.
We actually pulled it off.
[YURI]
Congrats, girly-boy.
I thought we had this one,
but you guys turned it around.
You won fair and square.
[HOZUMI gasps]
[NANA]
Mr. Dozono.
You may think it's
"creepy," but Stride
is about connecting
on an emotional level.
[SHIKI]
Huh?! Spare me the lecture.
I think it's something
you need to hear.
Your teammates, too.
You guys need to
learn to connect
and to trust each other.
Otherwise you lose sight
of what's important.
And it's not winning.
It's facing all our
challenges together.
You could learn from us!
[SHIKI growls]
I can't even begin to tell you
how proud I am right now!
[HEATH]
You're embarrassing me, Sis!
...now the brand's sales
are going to skyrocket!
[HEATH]
You're greedy.
Each of you had your struggles,
however, you did well overall.
That cheerful enough for you?
[AYUMU]
Heh. Y'know.
I thought I'd hate sitting in
the stands but it was cool!
Felt like I was running
along with you!
And with good reason.
You were running along with us.
[AYUMU]
Uh.
[HEATH] That is, until
Mr. Dan stopped you.
[AYUMU]
Uh.
[NANA]
We did it!
[RIKU laughs]
Heck yeah, we did!
[NANA] You were awesome
out there, Riku!
[RIKU]
Thanks! Right back at ya!
[NANA]
You too, Takeru!
[AYUMU]
Way to go, buddy!
[HEATH]
Hey, don't leave me hangin'!
[HOZUMI]
No way!
[RIKU] This is your chance,
Hozumi- senpai !
C'mon, smack him with
everything you've got!
[HOZUMI]
I dunno.
[TAKERU] I'm gonna have
to agree with him this once.
[HOZUMI]
What, you too?
Go ahead, he can handle it!
Do it, bro.
About time you let all
that repressed anger out.
Ain't that the truth!
Let's wrap this up, Hozumi.
From here on out,
we're teammates!
[HOZUMI]
Mm.
[HOZUMI] Kuga- senpai ,
I didn't want you on the team
'cause I blamed you for
pulling the club apart.
But now that I know the truth.
I'm happy to have you!
[HOZUMI screams]
Wow, he got me
pretty good, look.
[HEATH] Yeah, he hit you so hard
you've got internal bleeding!
Um, I think I might've
broken something!
[NANA]
Really? That's all it took?
[HOZUMI]
My hands are delicate, okay?
--[HOZUMI, NANA chattering]
--[STRIDE CLUB laughing]
[DIANE]
Mm. Very nice, Kyosuke.
I like this look.
It's wild and sexy!
[PHOTOGRAPHER 6A] Okay,
now straight at the camera.
Wow, he's really
good at this, huh?
I was worried he
might be nervous.
Yeah, it's hard to believe
that this is his
first time modeling.
[TAKERU]
He's a natural.
[HOZUMI]
It's not fair.
I could rock a
"wild and sexy" look.
But here I am stuck in a dress.
[ALL snicker]
[NANA]
That one's a perfect fit!
[RIKU]
Yeah!
Now we really look
like a winning team!
Here we go,
everybody look at the camera
and give me your biggest smiles!
[RIKU]
This is it, you guys!
Honan Stride's new
chapter starts today!
[KAEDE panting]
I'm so happy you're
still alive, Kuga!
[SHIZUMA]
Would you please calm down?
[KAEDE]
Sorry, I can't help it!
Hey, check it out,
it's the Saisei guys.
What's got you
all riled up, Kaede?
[KAEDE]
See who's down there?
It's Kuga in the flesh!
Look at him! He's so awesome!
Is that Riku? Hey, bro!
[RIKU]
What up, Asuma?
It looks like he's back.
[TASUKU]
That's Kyosuke Kuga?
And what makes him
so freakin' special?
[BANTARO]
Obviously you've never seen
that old Honan Stride video.
If you had,
you'd totally get it.
I've seen it, but that
was a long time ago.
Who knows if he's
still any good?
Let's keep an eye on them.
This could change things.
[REIJI] Yes, indeed.
But it's exciting.
Now that Kuga's
back on the team,
Honan may prove to be
a worthy opponent.
I look forward to
competing with them.
[SHIZUMA]
Me, too.
[SHIKI]
Himemiya! Do what I say!
[YURI] Quit yelling,
I need to concentrate!
Stride's like walking
a tight rope without a net!
Our last match was a circus,
with you as the clown.
[AYUMU] Aw Snap!
Next on "Prinstride,"
"The Cruel Angel
Arrives on the Field"!
Do I smell Kua- senpai ?