[TOMOE]
Riku. Long time no see.
So you decided to come
back to Stride, huh?
[RIKU]
Yeah.
I'm kinda hurt that you
never called to tell me.
We're brothers, you know.
Anyway, I'm glad you're
up and running again.
I've always thought
you had talent.
Maybe at the End Of
Summer finals we'll--
[RIKU]
Forget it.
I'm not the anchor so I won't
be running against you.
That's too bad.
Guess I'll see you around.
[RIKU gasps]
Ah! Stop! That hurts! [groans]
Where's the wind?
It's so still right now.
Man, Heath's either really
focused or we finally broke him.
He's probably as upset about the
time trial results as we are.
[AYUMU] I know precisely
what's bothering him!
He must be suffering
from B.N.S disorder!
What's that stand for?
[AYUMU] Allow me to explain,
B.N.S. is short for
"Best of, Natsuno, Semeku!"
AKA, summer homework!
You're right, with
his bad grades
I'm sure his teachers assigned
him a ton of it, too!
Let's face it, even though
Heath is good looking,
and team captain,
he's just not all that bright.
Poor guy.
He's so close to the T3A!
The trifecta of
terrific advantages!
[HEATH] I may not be
the smartest guy in school
but I ain't as dumb as you
two're makin' me out to be!
Um, we were just joking Heath.
This is bad.
I don't wanna die today.
Run for your life, Hozumi!
[HEATH]
Hey, get back here!
Think I can't catch you?!
[DAN sighs]
Kijitsu Bikyu .
They should be busy
training right now,
but no, they're playing.
Huh?
[DAN] I realize everyone's
feeling a little defeated.
And with good reason,
Kakyoin completely trounced
us at the time trial.
[AYUMU, HOZUMI]
Ouch! He's so blunt!
[DAN]
I'm only being honest.
However, your time
wasn't all that bad.
It was comparable to
the other two schools.
Also, from what
I saw in Hokkaido,
out of all the competing teams
your running and
Relationing skills
have the most
potential for growth.
Really?!
Well, that's reassuring!
Yeah, but it's just a nice way
of saying our team's a big mess.
Why do you have to be
such a party-pooper?!
I'm not! I'm tellin' it
like it is, you morons!
Yeah, we know,
but we could really use
some words of encouragement
from our captain.
That's enough.
We've only got a month
to get it together.
I need all of you
to stay focused
and train as hard as you can.
Now, as far as words
of encouragement...
[inhales]
Kishi Kaisei , Ichinen Tsuuten ,
Iki Kenkou , Shichiten Hakki ,
Zento Youyou , Taigan Jouju ,
Ikkaku Senkin ,
Gashin Shoutan ,
Kiu Soudai , Jisetsu Tourai ,
Ichibyou Sokusai ,
Ikka Danran ,
Gouka Kenran ,
Yuusou Kappatsu ,
Toushi Manman ,
Tenka Taihei ,
Funrei Doryoku ...
Yuuki Rinrin !
Whoa, that was amazing.
Yeah, but he stuck a few
weird ones in there.
Shinki Itten.
Do your best everyone.
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
[NANA]
All right, Takeru.
Get set.
[RIKU panting]
Dammit.
What's with Riku?
His pace is still unstable.
Three, two, one...
Go!
[gasps] Takeru, you're
moving too fast!
[RIKU panting]
That was close.
[TAKERU] You're still slowing
down toward the end.
[RIKU]
Yeah, I know.
[TAKERU]
This happens every time you run.
You've got to do
something about it.
[RIKU]
I said I know!
You saw how fast
Kakyoin's runners are!
If you wanna beat
them, then you--
[KYOSUKE]
Takeru.
There's no reason for you
to yell at him like that.
It's not as though
you're without faults.
When you charge into
the Takeover Zone,
you're hugging the
inside of the track.
Your impatience could
cause an accident.
[TAKERU exhales]
There's something I noticed
while watching you
two practicing.
You don't look at each other.
You look straight ahead,
like there's somebody
running in front of you.
[gasps]
[NANA]
You guys okay?
Sorry, I totally messed
up my timing.
[RIKU]
Oh, no, you did great!
For real, it wasn't you.
We've gotta--
[TAKERU]
Maintain that same timing.
Let's go again.
[NANA]
Why am I so distracted?
I have to try and concentrate.
I can't let my dad get to me.
[gasps]
[JOE]
Nana.
It's good to see you, Dad.
It's been a long time.
I hope you're doing well.
Yeah.
Just a little surprised
to see you, that's all.
I wasn't expecting
you to be here.
I'm just as surprised
to see you.
I had no idea you'd joined
Stride at your new school.
Nana.
[NANA]
Uh.
[JOE]
Join me at Kakyoin.
If you're serious about Stride,
then it's the best
place for you.
[NANA]
I dunno.
What does Honan have to offer
that you can't get at my school?
I chose Honan, cause I saw
a video of their Stride Club
competing and it blew me away.
They were more than a team,
they were like family.
I agree. There was
a time when Honan
seemed to have an
ideal Stride team.
But it didn't last. And now
they have different members,
so it'll never be the same.
I'm looking to create an ideal
team of my own at Kakyoin.
Here take this, I don't
wanna pressure you
but I'd love to have my
daughter join our club.
Hey Nana, are you ready to g--?
Oh, uh. Hello, Sir.
Let me know what you decide.
[HEATH]
All right, Riku's up first.
[NANA]
I've gotta stay focused.
I don't want the guys
getting hurt.
I can't stop thinking
about what he said.
An ideal Stride team.
Honan had one before.
[NANA]
And we can be one again!
Ready, Takeru?
Three, two, one... Go!
--[AYUMU] Uh-oh!
--[HOZUMI] Takeru!
Slow down!
[HEATH]
Watch out!
[crash]
[HEATH]
Are you guys all right?
[TAKERU]
Yeah, I'm fine.
[RIKU] Me, too. I grazed
him a little, that's all.
[NANA] I'm so sorry!
I made the call too soon!
No, you did fine;
we messed up!
[TAKERU]
Look, Yagami.
You've gotta keep a steady pace
going into the Takeover Zone.
What's your deal?!
Why are you always blaming
everything on me?!
I'm not blaming you.
I'm simply pointing
out a problem.
I get it, okay?!
You don't have to
keep "pointing it out"!
[TAKERU]
Shut up!
Can't you see that I'm
trying to help you?!
In Stride, one member's problem
affects the entire team!
[RIKU] Okay, then what
about your problems?
You're not the perfect runner
that you think you are, bro!
[TAKERU exhales]
Then tell me.
Tell me what all
my problems are.
And I'll work hard to fix them.
[RIKU] You think hard work
solves everything, don't you?
Well, some of us just
aren't as talented.
Please calm down.
I've given it my all.
But you still look down on me
'cause I can't run faster.
Who's looking down?
I'm right here,
looking straight at you.
[RIKU growls]
[TAKERU gasps]
Let go, Riku!
All right, break it up!
You're actin' like whiny brats!
And how 'bout you quit bein'
such a smart-ass, Takeru?
Tell you what,
let's switch gears
until everybody calms
down a little.
Let's move on to obstacles.
--[HOZUMI] Got it!
--[AYUMU] All right!
[AYUMU sighs]
It's friggin' hot!
I die!
Yeah. No joke.
I feel ya.
I wish we could cancel
tomorrow's practice.
Look, I don't wanna be here
on a Saturday either,
but the finals are
comin' up fast.
[AYUMU]
Since I'm not running at EOS
I should be exempt
from weekend practices.
Scratch that, I should be
exempt from all of them.
Wow, You've taken slacking
off to a new level.
[AYUMU]
Yay!
I just feel like
I'm missing out.
I wanna do summer stuff,
like go to the beach,
or a swimming pool,
or hang out with pretty
ladies in their bathing suits.
You know what I'm sayin Nana?
Uh! Uh, yeah.
It'll have to wait.
Remember, if one of us gets
hurt, you take our place.
Crap.
Like it or not,
you're one of us.
You're a Honan Stride runner
just as much as I am.
[AYUMU] I'm gonna buy five
authentic good luck charms
and have 'em shipped overnight.
[KYOSUKE]
Only five?
You might want to
purchase six of them
so you're covered as well.
[AYUMU]
I'm not worried about me...
Is there somethin' wrong?
[NANA]
Uh. Well, Yeah, kinda.
Everyone's working so hard
to prepare for the finals
and I wanna help. But I don't
know how as Relationer.
[HOZUMI]
Uh-oh.
I dunno what's going on
but it makes for a
stressful environment.
And Stride's supposed to be fun.
Yeah, I have no problem
correcting technique
but I don't know how
to handle this.
[HOZUMI]
No!
The extreme heat has everyone
at each other's throats,
what're we gonna do now?!
[AYUMU] My dear Hozumi!
Let me calm your fears!
This is an opportunity!
Really?
[AYUMU]
Just go with me on this one.
I have a plan!
[AYUMU]
Operation Fish in the Water!
Bright sunshine overhead!
[HOZUMI]
And sparkling blue water below!
[BOTH]
Who doesn't love the beach?!
[CHILDREN laughing]
Guys, that lame backdrop's
not really foolin' anybody.
[CHILD 9A]
Mm... Pee-pee!
[MOTHER 9A]
Oh no, you don't!
Come here.
Oh, I'm so sorry about that.
[HOZUMI chuckles]
This is why I wanted
to go to the beach
and not the stupid pool!
Me, too!
I wanted to play the
watermelon splitting game!
Look, I'm sorry, but
the beach is too far away.
We've got less than a month
left to train for finals.
[TAKERU]
I'm out.
I'm going back to
school to practice.
Well, we're going to stay here
and do some hardcore training.
[TAKERU gasps]
How "hardcore" are we talking?
Here we go.
You ready?
Heck, yeah! Let's do it!
[HOZUMI grunts]
[AYUMU] Time to link up!
Grab onto my wrist!
And you grab mine, too!
[HOZUMI]
Boosters!
[AYUMU]
Engage!
Ha. The wind is on their side.
Yeah, they're rockin' it.
Awesome!
We could never get this kinda
speed if we were goin' alone!
Nope, and that's precisely
why working as a team
is so important!
[AYUMU]
Together we...
[BOTH]
...can go over the rainbow!
Okay, so what'd you guys think?
Man, that last jump you did
over the edge was totally rad!
Taking advantage of the water
flow makes it too easy.
You barely had to
exert any force
but we should be pushing
our bodies while training.
Oh.
You're right. Good point.
The underlying message
didn't get through to them.
Which is weird 'cause
I thought the whole
"workin' together" thing
was pretty straightforward.
Maybe we should try
something sneakier.
I'm not sure subtlety is
the way to go, senpai.
[HEATH]
C'mon, I've got an idea.
[KYOSUKE]
Sure thing.
[NANA]
Uh. What's the plan?
[HOZUMI]
Three, two, one...
Go!
[KYOSUKE, HEATH grunt]
Wow! What a race!
And I betcha they're gonna stay
neck and neck the whole way!
They're using healthy
competition to push each other
to new limits they
never thought possible!
Yeah! Besides,
it's only natural for athletes
to wanna compete against
their teammates sometimes.
Right? A little rivalry's
good, isn't it?
[RIKU]
Huh? Uh. Yeah, I guess so.
[NANA] Uh... Oh!
What're you doin' over there?
I don't see how this could be
considered "hardcore" training.
Well uh... They're swimming?
It's a tie. Competing
with you is always fun.
You've really helped me
break out of my shell.
Hey, thanks, I've learned
a lot from our healthy rivalry,
it's even made me stronger.
If we keep it up we'll
be unstoppable, bro!
[BOTH grunt]
Huh?
All righty!
Now it's Takeru and Riku's turn!
[RIKU]
Huh?!
[HOZUMI laughs]
C'mon, no need to be nervous!
I don't wanna swim, I just
wanna chill by the pool.
[AYUMU] Remember, this is
about healthy competition,
so don't kill each other.
I'm not racing.
[ALL]
Uh...
[AYUMU] You've been talking
about training all day
and this is your chance,
swimming's a full-body
exercise so you'll be working
the same muscles
you use while running!
Forget it.
[TAKERU]
The truth is... I can't swim.
[HOZUMI] Why didn't you
tell us that sooner?
Good one, dude!
Got it! Here, Heath!
[HEATH]
And spike!
[TAKERU grunts]
[HEATH] Couldn't have
done it without you guys!
In volleyball, you have
to work together as a team.
You've got no choice.
Not if you wanna win
the game, anyway.
If we join forces I know that
we can kick the senpais' butts!
Here! Uh!
[RIKU]
All right! Nice bump!
[HEATH] Now all you gotta
do is set the ball, Riku.
[KYOSUKE] And then let
Takeru go in for the spike!
[AYUMU] No matter how
stubborn the players are,
everyone's gotta work
together to win the game.
That's the beauty of...
beach volleyball!
[RIKU grunts]
[HOZUMI]
I thought they almost had it!
[AYUMU] How could you go and
spike the ball like that?!
[NANA sighs]
Got it!
[HEATH sighs]
Jeez, how'd the first-years get
more physically fit than me?!
[KYOSUKE] Riku's the one
I find surprising.
I think our goal to teach them
the importance of teamwork
was a bust, they've proven
you can win without it.
[AYUMU] Okay everyone,
what flavors do you want?
I'll take the Blue Hawaii.
Strawberry for me, please.
[HOZUMI]
Melon for me.
[RIKU] Can you get me
a lemon one, please?
[AYUMU] Mm-hm. I think I'm
gonna go with sweet cream.
And you, Takeru?
[TAKERU] No, thanks.
I don't want the empty calories.
What about you?
Which one would you like?
I'll take this one, please.
The bucket of snow cone!
[AYUMU screams]
[SHOPKEEPER 9A]
Miss, are you sure about that?
It's too much for one person.
I've only ever seen a team
of grown men finish it.
They were sumo wrestlers.
Okay, then that
sounds perfect, Sir!
Hey, I don't know if this
is such a good idea.
If they don't play along
you're gonna be screwed.
[NANA] Yeah, I know but
I have to give it a try.
There's no turning back
once I get all fired up!
[HEATH]
Uh...
[NANA whimpering]
[KYOSUKE]
It's massive.
Yeah, I wouldn't even
call it a snow cone.
It's more like an iceberg.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
I'm gonna finish it and I can
do it myself if I have to!
You've got three minutes
to eat it. Nana, get set.
[NANA gasping]
[HOZUMI]
Three, two, one...
Go!
[NANA groaning]
Just eat as much as you
can and then give up.
[NANA groaning]
[NANA]
What're you doing?!
You're allowed to have a team
of up to three people, right?
Figured I'd give it a shot!
[RIKU groaning]
Here, let me take over!
[HEATH]
Man, he's really goin' at it!
He's shoveling it in but the
poor guy's still only halfway.
I dunno how much
more I can watch.
How much time do they have?
[HOZUMI]
Less than a minute!
[NANA]
Don't push yourself, Riku!
Give it to me!
I'm good. Thanks.
I'm almost... there.
[TAKERU]
Hand it over.
[RIKU]
You're jumpin' in?!
Whoa, he's drinkin' it!
[AYUMU]
He's swallowing it
before his mouth can communicate
the chill to his brain!
[HEATH] That doesn't sound too
healthy, if you ask me, bro.
[TAKERU grunts]
[AYUMU]
He bypassed the brain
but now the cold's
hitting his stomach!
[HEATH] Man, this sucks!
They're so close!
Only ten seconds left!
--[RIKU] Nice work, buddy!
--[HOZUMI] Nine!
But I'll take it from here!
[HOZUMI]
Six... five... four...
...three... two... one...
[CROWD cheering]
[SHOPKEEPER 9A]
You did it, kids.
You finished it!
[STRIDE CLUB cheering, laughing]
[AYUMU]
Way to go, Honan!
[CROWD cheers]
We make a pretty good team.
[TAKERU]
Uh.
[stomachs rumbling]
[sighs] Oh, well.
Least they finally
worked together.
Took us a little while
but we got the job done.
Well done, Nana.
You never let up on those two.
I knew they had to
break at some point.
Thanks for all of
your help, guys.
Now that they got the message
we just need to make sure
they never forget it.
What they went through today
will only make their
friendship stronger.
Honan Stride's back!
Watch out world!
[HEATH] All right, let's
head back and practice!
[AYUMU, HOZUMI]
What?!
[HEATH]
You heard me!
[NANA]
Takeru Get set!
Three!
Two!
One!
Go!
[NANA laughs]
[KYOSUKE]
That was near perfect.
[HOZUMI] Seriously, what a clean
Relation!
[RIKU]
I think we can do even better.
Yeah, Me, too.
Let's see if we can smooth out
the transition some more.
I thought that one
was spot on.
But let's try again.
[HEATH] Can we get some
practice time, too?!
[HOZUMI laughs]
[NANA]
Hi, Dad.
[JOE]
Well, hello, dear.
[NANA] I've been thinkin'
about your offer
to transfer to Kakyoin.
[JOE]
And?
[NANA]
You're right, Honan Stride
isn't a perfectly polished
team like yours is.
And honestly, we're
probably gonna face
a lot of challenges
because of that.
But I know if we work together
we can overcome any challenge
that comes our way.
They're not just my team,
they're like family.
So, thank you for the offer,
but I've decided I'm
gonna stay here.
Honan Stride is where I belong.
[JOE]
I understand.
I'm proud of you for sticking
with a team you believe in.
Give 'em all you got.
[NANA]
I will.
Oh, and Dad?
[JOE]
Mm?
I'll see you at the finals.
[RIKU]
Tomoe!
Sorry we're late senpai!
--[TAKERU] Yeah, Sorry.
--[HEATH] Where've you been?
[TAKERU, RIKU] There was
a line for the restroom.
[AYUMU] How dare you make
Heathagon, the Beast of Stride,
wait around for you?!
[DAN]
What're you talking about?
[AYUMU] Ooh!  Here's the other
ogre of the team, Danjiro!
Next on "Prinstride,"
"Mecha-Heathagon
vs. King Danjiro!"
It's the fight of
the century! Kaboom!