[RIKU panting]
[RIKU]
Tomoe!
[NANA]
Go!
[RIKU panting]
[HEATH]
Dang, he's fast.
That starting dash
of his is no joke, man.
If only he could keep his speed
up throughout the whole race.
You know?
[DAN] Good work,
Kohinata and Yagami.
You're done for the day.
[HOZUMI]
Yes, sir!
[RIKU gasping]
I can keep going!
Don't push yourself.
The last thing we need
is you getting hurt.
[panting]
I won't! I'm okay!
Go home and get some rest.
[NANA] I've never seen Riku
train so hard before.
He must be determined
to outrun his brother.
[DAN]
Nice, Kuga. You're done.
Keep in mind, Yagami.
The whole point of
interval training
is to boost your
cardiopulmonary function.
It's not to race.
Yes, sir.
[AYUMU] You gotta learn
to keep an even pace
if we wanna be the
Stride champions.
Yeah.
Thanks, buddy.
But, I probably shouldn't
give any advice.
Considering my last race.
Can you say, crash and burn?
[RIKU laughs]
[NANA]
Go!
[HOZUMI]
They're so fast!
I'm getting tired
just watching them.
[AYUMU] Do you mind if I
take a look at the stats?
Let's see...
I finished in 61 seconds,
Hozumi and Riku did 52,
Kyosuke 47,
and these two tied at...
...45 seconds?!
[HOZUMI] They must be
superhuman or something.
[RIKU gasping]
[exhales]
[RIKU]
Hey, Senpai?
Yeah, what's up?
I know you're done for the day
but will ya do a set with me?
I wanna run against someone,
like a real race.
[KYOSUKE]
Sure, let's do it.
[RIKU panting]
[RIKU]
It's not working.
I'm trying so hard, but it
doesn't matter how much I run.
I'm not getting any faster.
It's just like what
happened last time.
[RIKU gasps]
What do you want?
Your breathing is disrupted.
Catch your breath
before collapsing.
[TAKERU]
Your running is terrible.
[RIKU]
Uh.
[HOZUMI] Oh no, are they
gonna fight again?!
[AYUMU] I thought
the nightmare was over!
[HEATH] Takeru, there's
no need to be so harsh.
[RIKU]
It's okay.
He's right.
[HOZUMI] Hold up!
What just happened?!
There should be pigs flying
overhead any second now.
I dunno why but I always start
to slow down toward the end.
I gotta do something,
but... what?
Well, I've been looking over
the team's numbers.
And I don't think it
has anything to do
with your stamina.
Your times aren't bad.
I mean, your three-thousand
meter is slower than Takeru's
but not by much.
Your 400 meter's not great,
but that's probably
just 'cause you still have
some technique issues
you need to work on.
I have a feeling
there's something holding
you back emotionally.
[RIKU gasps]
We've only got ten days before
the EOS semi-finals
against Saisei.
We're gonna focus
on gettin' you past
whatever's throwin'
you off your game, okay?
So cheer up.
[DAN] Fujiwara, would
you mind helping Yagami
up his training regimen?
[RIKU] Uh... Yeah.
Thanks, but no thanks.
I can handle this by myself.
Uh!
Don't worry, I'll whip
you into shape.
Wow, they're actually
gonna work together!
It's great to see
them getting along
but who knows how
long it'll last
so let's get outta here.
[HEATH] All right guys,
that's it for today.
Let's do some stretchin'
to cool down.
--[HOZUMI] Sounds good!
--[AYUMU] On it!
I'm so hungry!
[NANA]
Wow, you've got a feast! Nice!
And there's more! Lookie here.
A Yagami Bakery Yakisoba Bun!
[NANA]
How can you eat all that?
My stomach's like
a bottomless pit.
I've got so many tasty treats
I dunno where to begin.
Lemme see. Meatball,
I choose you!
Put it down. Remember:
train first and eat later.
[RIKU]
Mm... Yeah, I know!
I gotta go run.
Kay, I'll keep your
lunch safe for you!
[RIKU panting]
[TAKERU] Your jaw's too tight,
and your arms are too loose.
You're close but your
upper body's unstable.
Let's try it again.
[RIKU]
Okay!
[HOZUMI]
Are we done yet?!
[HEATH] Yeah, I guess
that's enough for today.
Good job, you guys.
[AYUMU, HOZUMI panting]
You did it!
Knew you had it in you!
What did I tell you?
Runnin' outside ain't
so bad, is it?
[AYUMU] No, except for the
fact my feet are on fire
thanks to the ridiculously
hot pavement.
Aw. Don't be such a wimp.
This is nothin', the semi-finals
are in the middle of the day.
[AYUMU]
No way!
I think I'd rather pursue the
fine art of team management.
[HOZUMI]
Huh?
[NANA]
Fifty-six-point-eight.
Fifty-nine-point-six.
[RIKU panting]
Not again!
What's wrong with me?!
[NANA] He seems to be losing
focus while he's running.
That explains why his
times keep getting worse.
[TAKERU]
Get up.
Huh?
You're not done training yet.
You've gotta be kidding me!
Do you have any idea
how much I've run today?!
What, you're giving up already?
Of course not,
I just needed a quick break
to catch my breath.
I'm ready to go again,
how 'bout you?
You know it.
[RIKU] Hey, wait up, man!
Nana didn't make the call!
I'm worried Riku might be
pushing himself too hard.
For real, if he keeps this up
he's gonna wind up injured
before the match.
[RIKU panting]
[clattering]
[TAKERU] You've gotta stop
collapsing like that.
[RIKU panting]
Say something.
'Kay
[TAKERU]
I don't understand.
Why're you so slow?
Whoa, what did he say?
"Why're you so slow?"
Ouch.
[AYUMU]
Well, Takeru's never been one
to beat around the bush.
Maybe this'll be the kick in
the pants that Riku needs.
[RIKU grunting]
[RIKU]
I'm so tired.
But I have to keep up,
I have to run faster!
I can't do it.
He's too far ahead.
Why run anymore?
It's pointless.
I'll never catch up to him.
No matter how hard I try.
I'm always left behind.
[TOMOE] It's just like
what happened before, Riku.
[RIKU gasping]
[TOMOE]
I trained with you daily.
I pushed you to keep going
when things got tough,
but you gave up.
It's a shame.
'Cause you have so much talent.
If you would just try harder.
Just try harder.
Try harder.
--[beeping]
--[RIKU gasps]
[CLASSMATE 10A]
I'm goin' to the school store.
[CLASSMATE 10B] Run dude, you'll
miss out on the panda bread!
[TAKERU]
Ready?
Sorry man, not really
feelin' it today.
Let's go!
You're slowing down!
Pick up the pace!
Move it!
[TAKERU]
Sixty one point three.
You were lagging
at the end again,
but you had a slow start, too.
Three more and we'll
switch to obstacles.
How's that sound?
[RIKU]
I'm done.
That's all I can do today.
[TAKERU]
Seriously?!
But your form is improving.
We only have five days left
until the Saisei match.
I know it's tough,
but you have to try harder.
You can't give up now,
you've got talent, but you--
[TAKERU]
C'mon, you can't give up now--
[RIKU] Shut up!
I said I'm done, okay?!
[NANA]
Riku, wait!
We need to give the guy
some space right now.
[CLASSMATE 10C]
Ugh, summer school's lame!
[CLASSMATE 10D] No joke!
We barely get any vacation!
[RIKU]
Hey, Suzuki.
You headed to the school store?
Yeah, but your yakisoba bun's
way better than their food.
[RIKU]
I didn't get one today.
They're on sale so there
were none left for me.
You'd think they'd
save me one, right?
[SUZUKI laughs]
Yeah, for real.
Hey.
--[HOZUMI] Hiya Heath!
--[AYUMU] What's up, boss?
For today's practice we're
gonna work on obstacles
out in the field.
Is Riku absent?
[NANA]
No, he was in class earlier.
Well, that sucks.
[BOYS laughing]
[BOY 10C]
Got it!
[ASUMA]
Hey! What's up, bro?!
[RIKU grunts]
Asuma.
[ASUMA chuckles]
Mm?
I thought you'd be
more surprised.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm just havin' a
rough day, that's all.
[ASUMA] What're you doin'
out here by yourself?
[RIKU] Wait. Shouldn't
I be asking you that?
[ASUMA] Eh, Reiji asked
me to run an errand for him
and here I am.
What'd he want?
Some kinda local delicacy from
a bakery that's having a sale.
And they look pretty good, too.
Heard of Yakisoba Buns?
[RIKU]
Uh.
[laughs]
[ASUMA] So it is your family's
bakery, I thought so.
Yagami isn't a common last name.
[RIKU]
Uh.
Holy crap! This is delicious!
Yeah, I know, right?!
Our Yakisoba Buns are the
best in the whole world!
Hey so, what's up?
Don't you have practice today?
I'm trainin' solo.
Okay.
[BOYS laughing]
[ASUMA]
Tomoe Yagami.
[gasps]
[ASUMA]
I know this is probably
the last thing you
wanna hear right now,
but your brother's stupid fast.
I've seen videos of
him running before,
but watching him live
at the time trial
was terrifying, man.
He's, like, on a whole
different level.
I mean, that Amatsu Ida
guy's nothin' to laugh at,
but I've never seen anyone
run as fast as Tomoe can.
Trust me, I know how tough it is
living in your big
brother's shadow.
[RIKU]
He's always been fast.
I used to run in the same club
as him back in the day.
I remember he used to practice
harder than anybody.
I always admired his
dedication to Stride.
I thought if I worked hard
enough I could be just like him.
So I trained with him every day
hoping that I'd get faster.
But...
[RIKU]
There was this one day.
Practice was cancelled 'cause
of a storm, but nobody told him.
[RIKU] When Tomoe didn't
come home after school
I decided to go look for him.
The first place I checked
was where we trained.
[RIKU gasps]
I guess practice was cancelled
but nobody bothered to tell me.
[RIKU]
That's when it struck me.
I ran Stride 'cause
I thought it was fun,
but it was Tomoe's life.
And he had a talent
for it that I lacked.
Work as hard as I might,
I'd never be as fast as him.
Once I came to that realization,
running wasn't fun
for me anymore.
So I decided to quit Stride.
I see, but now you're
back with a vengeance.
I keep telling myself I'm
not who I was back then.
That I can run Stride
just for fun.
But then, Tomoe's team
showed up in Hokkaido.
And I watched him run again.
I realized that,
after all this time,
I'm still chasing his back.
I'm stuck.
I loved running Stride but now
that he's back I dunno anymore.
Look, If you love Stride,
don't let him ruin it for you.
Hey, I know!
Instead of worryin' about him
start running for yourself
and for your teammates!
[ASUMA]
Besides, ya can't quit,
I'm lookin' forward to racin'
you at the semi-finals.
[RIKU gasps]
Huh? It looks like
it's gonna rain.
I'd better get goin'.
[RIKU]
Yeah.
Thanks, Asuma, you actually
cheered me up a little.
No problem.
But I'm throwin' salt on
my team's game again.
[RIKU]
Salt? Whaddya mean?
[ASUMA groans] You seriously
gotta look that stuff up!
I'll see ya later!
[RIKU laughs]
[AYUMU panting]
Yay, I did it!
[NANA]
Way to go, Ayumu!
Your times keep getting
faster and faster!
[HEATH]
Nice work, guys!
Aw, crap.
Looks like it's about to pour.
That's it for today!
--[NANA] Yes, sir!
--[AYUMU] Hallelujah!
Hey man, You comin' in with us?
[TAKERU] No, I'm gonna go
practice on my own for a bit.
[AYUMU, HOZUMI, NANA]
Heh!
Okay. But don't overdo it!
[AYUMU] Let's hope he can
find Riku relatively fast.
Cause it's supposed
to get bad later.
[KYOSUKE]
A storm can be a good thing.
It's a sign of change.
[thunder rumbles]
[RIKU panting]
[RIKU]
Go away!
Can't you see I'm tryin'
to do my own thing here?
[TAKERU]
Well then don't mind me.
It's kinda hard to ignore you
when you run up behind me!
That was creepy,
even for you, bro!
[TAKERU]
Yeah, whatever.
You're just mad
that I passed you.
[RIKU panting]
Aw, it's raining!
[BOY 10A]
Let's go!
[BOY 10C]
Don't forget the ball!
[RIKU panting]
[TOMOE]
I guess.
It was cancelled
but nobody told me.
[RIKU] You've taken all
the fun out if it, Tomoe!
Look, I don't wanna
do Stride anymore!
I never wanted to.
You forced me.
[RIKU panting]
Just go ahead.
You don't have to wait for me.
[TOMOE]
I understand.
I'm sorry I pushed it on you.
[TAKERU]
Yagami.
I'd never leave you behind.
[gasps]
Let's go.
Okay. If that's what you want.
[RIKU]
Sure, running Stride is tough.
But...
[NANA]
Hey!
[HOZUMI laughs]
[AYUMU]
You're almost there!
--[HEATH] All right!
--[HOZUMI] You can do it!
[NANA]
Keep it up, you guys!
[TAKERU]
Race ya to the finish line!
[RIKU]
I love it!
[BOTH panting]
[NANA]
C'mon, Riku! You've got this!
[HOZUMI]
Let's go, Yagami, let's go!
[HEATH] You're so close, man!
Just a little farther!
Hooray! Go!
Leave Takeru in the dust!
Show him who's boss!
Final dash, bro!
[RIKU panting]
[RIKU]
I'm running for my teammates!
And I'm running...
...for myself!
He passed him!
[RIKU gasping, laughing]
[TAKERU panting]
[TAKERU]
C'mon, Yagami.
What'd I tell you?
You have to catch your breath
before you collapse.
You got it?
Yeah.
[panting] Way to go.
That last dash was good.
But next time, I'm gonna
run even faster.
[RIKU] Heh. That's cool,
do your worst.
Now that I've passed you
I won't lose again.
I'm gonna go cool off.
[RIKU]
Hey! Wait up!
Where do you think
you're goin'?!
Come back here, Takeru!
Asuma, how many of those
things have you eaten today?
[ASUMA]
Mm?
[sighs] Every Yakisoba bun
contains an average
of 300 kcals. I know
they're delicious
but you should really limit
yourself to two per day.
If you start gaining weight
it could slow you down
and then we'll never beat
Honan, much less Kakyoin.
You've got to learn to control
yourself when it comes to food.
[SHIZUMA]
Hm?
[AYUMU] Whoa! Media coverage
at the semi-finals is insane!
Whaddya say we take
over the airwaves?!
Yo, yo, yo! Honan Academy Shogi
Club is in the hizzouse!
Come and join the gang!
Shogi life, what?!
[HOZUMI]
We're here for Stride, dummy!
Next on "Prinstride,"
"Runners on the Shogi Board!"
Rook-King fork!