Let's say I did let
you live, right?
You would develop civilization
just like before.
Can you promise that
you won't do that?
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU]
The hell are you talking about?
I could promise anything
to stay alive.
No. You would never lie.
Not when it comes to science.
So will you promise me, here
and now, and for all eternity,
that you'll abandon science?
Because if you can make
that pledge, you can live.
And then I won't be forced
into killing you.
No, I can't. I can't do that.
Of course not. I knew
that would be your answer.
Just kill me in one blow.
Because leaving me
to suffer till I die
is both illogical
and inefficient.
Don't worry, Senku.
I'm going to sever
your cervical nerve.
It'll be instantaneous.
You'll be knocked unconscious
and die without suffering.
I won't miss.
[gasps]
[YUZURIHA]
Taiju.
[TAIJU gasps]
Something's wrong.
I gotta get back, now!
[TSUKASA]
Senku, I have a feeling
that if we had met each
other 3,700 years ago...
[ALL]
Huh?
[ALL chuckling]
[SENKU, TAIJU]
Huh?
[SENKU screams]
[yelling]
[TSUKASA]
...before all this...
...before the planet was
turned into a Stone World...
[TSUKASA] ...I think that
you might have been
my first real friend.
[thud, squelching]
[TAIJU screaming]
Senku!
[TAIJU screams]
Please! Answer me, Senku!
Open your eyes! Wake up
and say something!
C'mon. This can't be right.
There's no way!
Don't let it end
like this, Senku.
After everything you've
done, you can't just die!
Talk to me!
I gave him a painless
death. It's over.
I trust that as his friends,
you will give him
a proper burial.
[gasps]
[TSUKASA]
Even if Taiju wasn't a pacifist,
he'd never risk endangering
Yuzuriha by attacking me.
That was the power
dynamic between us.
But, Taiju, if Senku's death
sends you into a rage
and drives you to
attack me mindlessly...
...then I'll have
to kill you, too.
Please, don't lose your head.
What're you doing?
[TAIJU] It's fine,
Yuzuriha. Don't worry.
I'm still thinking clearly.
[TSUKASA]
Of course.
I have no choice but to fight.
Sorry, Yuzuriha.
But I can only hope--
[YUZURIHA]
No. It's okay, Taiju.
After all, the three of us
made each other a promise.
It'll all work out.
There's no doubt in my mind.
Yeah. Thanks a lot, Yuzuriha.
[TAIJU grunting]
[TAIJU screaming]
[TSUKASA]
Overhead? Why?
It must be a decoy.
Good try, but I won't
fall for it, Taiju.
No matter what you
do, you've lost.
[TAIJU] Tsukasa's worried
I'll attack him.
He won't dare take
his eyes off me!
And that... is why
she has a chance!
[YUZURIHA] Tsukasa thinks
I'm Taiju's weakness.
Someone he has to protect.
And in a primitive, stone world
like this one, it makes sense.
[YUZURIHA]
But it's like Senku told us...
[YUZURIHA, TAIJU] Science levels
the playing field for everyone!
[TSUKASA]
That's black powder!
[YUZURIHA] Senku didn't
leave us with nothing!
[TAIJU] We have science
to remember him by!
The three of us made a promise
to work together and stop you!
[TAIJU] Me, Yuzuriha,
and Senku as well...
...we're fighting
this battle together!
Goodbye, Tsukasa!
[TSUKASA] Taiju would
never attack anyone.
Knowing that, I think he
must've expected me
to come out of this unscathed.
[TAIJU]
Goodby, Tsukasa!
[TSUKASA]
So that's what he meant.
It's gonna be okay, Senku.
You said it yourself, remember?
If we're gonna run for it,
then we have to do it together!
I don't care what anyone says--
you're not dying on me!
I know you're alive!
We've only just started
bringing back civilization,
and you're not the kind of guy
to leave a job half done!
[TSUKASA]
What's the point of fleeing?
[TSUKASA] I know for a fact that
I severed his cervical nerve.
[TSUKASA] There's no
coming back from that.
Especially not in a Stone
World that has no medicine.
[TAIJU] I'm trying to give
him a heart massage,
but I have no idea
if I'm doing it right.
But I can't do nothing,
and this is all I can think of.
[TAIJU]
Wait! What about mouth to mouth?
Ah! Hold on a second!
I think we need to
keep his neck still!
Because that's where
Tsukasa hit him.
I'd been caught, and Senku
gave himself up for me.
Wait, you're saying he
sacrificed himself?
[STUDENT A] Check out
this psychology quiz.
"There's been a tragic accident,
and between your friend,
your lover, and yourself
only one of you can be saved."
Who would you choose?
Uhh.
I think I'd get stuck picking
between my friend and my lover.
[STUDENT A] Might pick yourself
in the heat of the moment.
How could anyone
make that choice?!
This quiz of yours
seems kinda nasty.
I choose everyone.
[ALL gasp]
[SENKU] I'd look for
a fundamental rule...
...that'd let me save all of us.
[YUZURIHA]
Guess that's the kind of answer
you'd expect from the
Science Club's president.
[TAIJU]
That's actually an option?
Well, it's my choice, too, then!
[STUDENT A] I think the point of
the question is more to reveal
who's most important to you.
[SENKU] That's ten billion
percent obvious.
Your book belongs in the trash.
[TAIJU] Senku wouldn't
go the suicide route.
He wouldn't sacrifice anyone.
He would stake the whole game
on the chance to save us all.
We have to figure out
what he was thinking.
If anyone can do it,
then it should be his friends!
He must've left us a hint!
His neck.
Back at the hot spring,
when I was caught,
Senku was drawing
attention to his neck.
I think that's where he wanted
Tsukasa to strike him.
[TAIJU]
You're right.
That thing he was doing,
it's not a habit he always had.
Why'd he keep touching
his neck and cracking it?
Was he trying to
tell us something?
[gasps]
[YUZURIHA] There's a little bit
of stone left on his neck!
Hold on.
When we removed the stone
that was left on your foot,
Senku told us something.
That when we "de-petrified,"
cracks were filled in
as part of the process.
Here, Taiju! The revival fluid!
[TAIJU]
Right.
[YUZURIHA] It might work
on Senku's neck, too!
There's a chance.
Yeah, when he's de-petrified,
his neck might be fixed as well.
The petrification's gone!
[screams]
Wake up, Senku!
I knew you'd live!
I knew you weren't gonna
let yourself be killed,
not in a place like this!
Senku, you're...
the star of hope.
For humanity.
For all of civilization!
So please... come back!
You have to wake up, Senku!
[SENKU]
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Heh.
All right.
I can make it past
800,000 seconds
without all-but losing
consciousness now.
Guess my brain's
finally adjusting.
[SENKU]
I've been frozen for
117,354,889,550 seconds.
[SENKU] So this is the
3,718th spring since I froze.
Starting in spring
is an absolute must
if I wanna survive.
[SENKU]
Okay. No time like the present.
Come on, me, get up.
Get up.
Get up, damn it!
Get up! Get up!
[SENKU breathing heavily]
[chuckling]
Yeah! I'm finally free!
[SENKU] Yeah. A flashy entrance
like that would've been fun.
[chuckles]
[SENKU]
And I'm ten billion percent sure
that's how my blockhead friend
Taiju would've done it.
My first objective is to
evaluate my surroundings.
I'll start with my own body.
It can give me clues that're
worth its weight in gold.
[SENKU] My initial location.
The position of my body.
Even the order in which these
mysterious stone fragments
fell off me.
I'm gonna keep every last piece
for when I'm ready
to investigate later.
--[rustling]
--[gasps]
[MONKEYS gibbering]
[MONKEY C]
Yo. Where you from?
Where's your monkey tribe?
[grunts]
[MONKEY C]
Dude's all smooth and shiny!
Gross! What kinda monkey
has skin like that?
[MONKEY A] He's got his
nasty peepee out, too!
[MONKEY B] Well, so do
all of us, but still!
[MONKEY C]
Gross!
Am I the first human
they've seen?
[SENKU] Doesn't look like
civilization survived.
This is a whole new world.
And from the looks of things,
I might be the first shiny
monkey to be born in it.
[chuckles]
[SENKU] This is
exhilarating. Get excited.
[SENKU] It's been
117,354,893,870 seconds now.
Huh. This is some
nasty mental math.
Especially when I factor
in the leap years.
Not to mention the
earth's rotation slows
by 17 millionths of
a second every year.
That hardly adds up
to anything, though.
[SENKU]
April 1st, 5738 A.D.
Though you could
call this Year Zero.
'Cause it all begins today!
Tch.
[chuckles]
Behold the power of the
smooth and shiny monkey.
My forebears had the
technology to reach space,
and I'll rebuild their
civilization from scratch.
[yelling]
[MONKEY C] He's been rubbing
that stick this whole time.
[MONKEY B]
That shiny monkey's a dumb-dumb.
[MONKEY C]
Let's go home.
[MONKEY B]
What a moron.
[SENKU] I'm neither
a meathead like Taiju,
nor an ultra-dextrous craft
club kid like Yuzuriha.
There's no way
I can start a fire
with nothing but a
primitive hand drill.
Not in Japan's humidity.
Heh.
[SENKU]
That's right.
This shiny monkey has
neither fangs nor claws.
All I can do is improvise,
one step at a time.
That's how
civilization advances.
[screams]
[MONKEY C] Why does he keep
smashing rocks like that?
[MONKEY B] That shiny monkey's
definitely a dumb-dumb.
[SENKU]
There's a trick to this,
but I'll only find it
through trial and error.
Maybe I should bash
the edges off in mid-air.
[SENKU] Or I could use
a solid foundation,
and aim right at the edge,
chipping at both pieces at once.
Can't forget that different
stones have different uses.
This colorful piece of chert
is the hardest rock around.
Which makes it the perfect
material to craft into a knife.
Study everything.
Try everything.
[chuckles]
I can unravel this plant
like string cheese.
[MONKEY C] It looks like
he's twisting it now.
[MONKEY B] I bet you his brain
is just as smooth as his skin.
[SENKU]
Surprisingly enough,
there are quite a few
animals that use tools.
Crows, otters,
orangutans, and more.
But out of all the
creatures in this world,
only one can make
use of science.
[SENKU] When cellulose
is heated through friction
and exposed to air, it rapidly
oxidizes, giving us...
[MONKEYS scream]
[SENKU]
...combustion!
[SENKU screams]
[growls]
[MONKEY B]
Huh?
[SENKU] Through persistence
and ingenuity,
I can take everything this
universe has to offer.
I'm the master of science!
[ALL gasping]
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU] Just realized I
never introduced myself.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
[MONKEY C]
Ah! What the hell is that?
[MONKEY B] The shiny monkey
isn't shiny anymore!
[SENKU]
You see,
I'm the only one of my kind
still walking this world.
I'm a human being.
[SENKU] I intend to build a
technological civilization
from scratch.
And this is where it all starts.