[SUIKA] Whoa! You can
see super far away!
[SUIKA gasps]
[SUIKA] The sun's coming up
really soon, you guys!
Careful not to look at it
through the telescope.
If those are the
right type of stones,
they should start to glow.
[ALL gasp]
Oh, wow. It looks like
a mountain of jewels.
Yeah, of course it does.
Because it is a
mountain of jewels.
[SENKU chuckles]
And this treasure hoard here
has our ultra-rare
metal inside it!
Ha. Call 'em whatever you want--
they're just kinda
heavy rocks to me.
I hope they're worth the fuss.
They'll definitely be worth it
when they help us beat Tsukasa.
These'll help us win the battle?
I get it.
They're weapons!
They've got enough weight to 'em
to really hurt somebody!
Sorry, Father. I don't
think that's what they--
Cut him some slack.
The older generation doesn't
understand some things.
[KOKUYO]
Huh?!
Look, we're up against
Tsukasa's army,
which is gonna be
crazy ong-stray.
But if we stick to the plan
and make cell phones
with these rocks,
we'll have a massive advantage
in the information war.
[KOHAKU] Yeah, I know,
but how much longer
is it going to take to
make these cell phones?
[GINRO] That's a good question,
'cause once spring comes,
their army's gonna
storm the village!
Ehh. We're not far
from our goal.
To explain things simply,
the vacuum tube's the heart
of the cell phone,
plastic's the skeleton, the
microphone's the vocal cord,
and the gold wire's the veins.
All we gotta do is put
those four parts together
and we'll have ourselves
a cell phone.
[OTHERS gasp]
[SENKU] It's been a marathon
of a science project,
but we're getting close
to the finish line.
Ha! Now it's time for us to make
our final sprint to the end!
The first thing we gotta
do is make filaments,l
which are essential
for vacuum tubes.
And they'll be made
outta tungsten.
The most heat-resistant metal
in the known universe
waiting inside this blue light.
Here's another question:
How exactly are we gonna
get it out of the stone?
Yeah, well, that is gonna
be pretty tough to pull off.
What the hell are you
doing?! Are you crazy?!
Huh? We're gettin' the stuff
outta these rocks, man.
If we smash 'em up first,
it'll be easy.
That totally works for me.
We'll be turning it
into powder, anyway.
You guys hear that?
What'd I tell ya?
[GINRO]
Uh! But you didn't know that!
[KOHAKU]
If you were wrong,
you'd have to go through
all that trouble again!
[KOKUYO]
Well, this is strange.
This isn't like him at all.
I've never actually seen
him offer to help before.
Did something happen
down in that cave?
[SENKU]
With me here, you get to see
all the ridiculously
awesome stuff
that humanity worked together
for two million years to build.
And I'll show you enough
to make your head spin.
Senku!
I don't care if you're
in charge anymore.
At least, not until we deal
with that Tsukasa guy.
Huh. Wonder what it was.
[MAGMA]
All done! So what's next?
I'll use my chemistry skills
on this powdered rock.
And when I'm finished with it,
it should have a similar
consistency to toothpaste.
Oh, right, more fun
chemistry stuff.
Never does me any good to
ask questions about it.
[SENKU] Then, we're gonna treat
the toothpaste with hydrogen
by warming it up in
a glass container
to get rid of any rust.
And we're done.
It has to reach a
thousand degrees,
but the hotter we make it,
the stronger the
tungsten'll turn out.
Ho-ho! We can just throw it
in our trusty furnace here!
It's nice to get an easy
step once in a while.
Have you two lost your minds?
Think what would happen
to a glass container
if you threw it into a
thousand-degree fire.
[BOTH gasp]
We have to make sure that
only the tungsten mixture
inside of the glass
container is getting hot.
So then we'll need to pinpoint
the heat on one spot.
But how exactly?
Let's split up the work--
time is short.
I can handle all of
the toothpaste-making
chemistry stuff.
Wait, then who's
gonna figure out
the pinpoint heating mechanism?
We don't have another scientist!
[gasps]
Come on.
You know everything you
need to make that happen.
You've gotta throw all
the science tricks
you've learned at it.
Heh.
Or do you need Professor Senku
to come and hold your hand?
Are you kidding with that?
Don't make me laugh.
I'm Chrome, you know!
And I'm smarter than hell!
I'm a scientist!
If you need some
help in your lab,
you'd better not come crying
about it to me, okay?
[SENKU] I got all the
lab stuff, no problem.
You're gonna have your hands
full leading the heating team.
You guys make me
a little jealous.
Since I was a boy, I've
always loved making things.
It was such a fun way
to spend my time.
I made all kinds of stuff,
like shields and bridges,
while other people just
stood back and stared.
Even in my old age,
I still get looked
at as a laborer.
Seeing you two working
together like this
has got me thinking
about how much
I'd like to have a crafting
buddy of my own.
[CHROME]
Hm?
But you're not building things
on your own anymore, are you?
You've got crafting buddies.
Hold on, I do? Who's that?
Us two.
Really?
Even though I'm almost 50
years older than you?
Of course. Why should age
matter at all? Who cares?
[yells]
[SENKU, CHROME scream]
[SENKU]
What the hell?
I've gotta say,
he certainly is gung-ho.
[SENKU] All right, modern man,
you're comin' with me.
I'll bet you know a little more
chemistry than the villagers.
I'm not so sure.
There are a stupid
number of steps,
so this could get
pretty complicated,
but I'll try to keep it simple.
Cook the powder in
sodium hydroxide,
add seashells,
hydrochloric acid,
and ammonia to crystallize it,
then bake it and mix with honey.
[gasps]
Yeah, okay, and I am reading you
loud and clear Professor Senku!
I'm using honey! Bake it
and add some honey.
That's about the gist
of it, that right?
[SENKU] Chrome would
be ten billion times
more helpful right now.
[GEN] No, I doubt anyone
could've kept up with all that.
You're the only person
who understands
this kind of stuff you know.
Look!
This has gotta be the perfect
tool for precision heating!
Ha! Chrome is pulling out
his special move again!
Quit showin' off.
That thing brings
back bad memories.
I'm not exactly
sure how much heat
that lens is going to produce.
To test out the temperature,
I've set up these metals
by heat resistance.
[SUIKA] It doesn't seem to be
doing anything to the lead,
and that's the
weakest one, right?
Maybe because it's winter.
It might work if we had
a little more sunlight.
You've gotta throw all
the science tricks
you've learned at it.
[gasps]
Our pinpoint heater needs fire.
And the cotton candy machine.
Let's throw that in, too!
Aw, man!
We're gonna need more
than just me and Suika.
But at least the lead's
startin' to melt down!
Awesome! There goes the
gold and silver, too!
Yeah! Way to go, battle team!
[MAGMA, KOHAKU yelling]
Iron is down!
Yeah! Gorilla team!
[KASEKI laughs]
We made it past a
thousand degrees!
It has to reach a
thousand degrees,
but the hotter we make it,
the stronger the
tungsten'll turn out.
We need more heat.
Let's throw in electricity!
[SENKU]
All right. It's finally done.
Tungsten toothpaste acquired!
So, heating team,
how's it goin'?
Great. We're just
about done here.
Huh? Not too shabby,
ya science user.
[SENKU screams]
What's with the jumbo
deluxe combo set?!
Come on, Senku. I'm doing
exactly what you told me.
Using every trick I've learned.
I didn't mean to go this far.
The thing's ugly as hell.
[chuckles]
[SENKU]
But to be honest,
this might actually be
the best solution.
So now, everybody's gonna
need to work together
to get this temperature
crazy high.
We're gonna squeeze out
a long, thin blob
of tungsten toothpaste.
Zapping water with electricity
produces hydrogen.
The hydrogen, with tons of heat,
will peel the rust
right off that stuff.
Here we go.
Few thousand degrees.
[ALL]
Let's heat this thing up!
[VILLAGERS gasping]
We've tamed the world's
most heat-resistant metal.
Which means now we have our
hands on tungsten filament!
[SENKU] With this, we have
everything that we need.
Aw, yeah! We're so close to
the finish I can taste it!
We might as well go in order!
I think we should start with
the cell phone's heart
and finish makin'
the darn vacuum tube.
But to get that part done,
it's gonna take some pretty
complicated glasswork.
I'm not entirely sure that
you're up to it, old man.
Oh, please.
Give me some credit.
I did make this ridiculously
challenging twisty doohickey
for ya earlier, didn't I?
So nothin' scares me now!
Well? Let me see
what you've got.
[yelps]
This device is known
as a Hickman pump.
It sucks air like you
wouldn't believe.
This baby is a level
ten billion vacuum!
You kinda sound
like you're doing
a vacuum cleaner commercial.
[SENKU]
Vacuum tubes are created
by removing as much air
inside as possible.
The pump we built before was
more like a level one prototype,
which worked for light bulbs.
But it won't give us enough
power for this job.
I don't know where to begin.
Is this even humanly possible?
In Senku's and my age,
people could build them,
but it was only the insanely
talented super craftsmen guys.
I know you're good, Kaseki,
but this is a different
era altogether,
so you shouldn't feel
too bad about it.
It'll never ork-way.
Is that true?
Well, yeah.
But why the hell
would a mentalist
know the first thing about it?
He's probably just
talking out of his ass
to get the old geezer fired up.
[KASEKI chuckles]
[KASEKI] It's fine. I don't
need you to inspire me.
It's the complicated stuff
that gets me fired up, anyway.
But in exchange... A favor.
That thing you did with Chrome,
I really want you to
do it with me, too.
You know. Seeing as the
two of us are buddies.
Oh, yeah!
You'll bang out this
vacuum tube, buddy,
there's no doubt about it.
Damn right! Watch me!
Ah! Hey, check it out, Senku.
I'm sure I'm the only
one who noticed,
but even though Old Man Kaseki's
acting like a little kid
begging for that high five,
he's really more concerned
with helping you out
with the big workload
you've got ahead of you.
[SENKU]
Yeah, any idiot could see that.
[SUIKA]
Hey, Senku?
So, is there something
we kids could do?
Yeah, there is, actually.
You guys can handle the wire.
[SUIKA]
Yay!
This means we're in!
We're all members of the
Kingdom of Science, too.
Us kids are going to make
the wire ourselves.
And we'll do it without
any help from Senku!
[KIDS]
Yeah!
All right. Are you ready,
chemistry team?
Because it's time for us
to make some plastic.
Yep!
I have no clue what that is
exactly, but I'm ready to learn!
Honestly, this is the
step on the road map
I was the most worried about.
Is it even possible to make
plastic in the Stone World?
I'm just saying, isn't it
made outta petroleum? Uh.
[KASEKI] Get over here,
Gen. You're with me.
You got me so fired up earlier
I've got no choice but
to work you to death!
Not air-fay!
[SENKU]
Uhh...
Who woulda thunk it?
The old guy's got a
soft spot for Gen.
For some reason.
[SENKU] I figured out
how to make our plastic.
First, we wanna simmer some wood
and boil the liquid
that comes out.
Pour that over some hot
copper, and then--
Hold on a second, Senku!
I'm already completely lost!
You heat it to extract some
liquid, heat that again,
and then heat that again?
What are we even doing?
We're modding the hell
out of it by adding
and removing crucial
ingredients.
Chemistry's all about
adding and subtracting.
And after that process,
we're left with this
stuff called formalin.
You can preserve
corpses with it.
[CHROME]
That stinks!
And what's the deal with you
pulling out these creepy
dead people chemicals
all the time?
Okay.
So now the only thing we need to
acquire is a ton of coal ash.
Because sodium hydroxide
plus formalin plus coal
ash makes bakelite,
which is the very first
man-made plastic.
It's perfect for this.
Oh, okay.
So I guess we're
gonna need to burn
a crazy amount of
coal, aren't we?
My hands are numb.
We're not gonna get much
work done like this.
This winter does seem like
an especially harsh one.
I'm worried some poor soul
is going to die from
the cold this year.
We need coal?
[SENKU] Yeah, like a
ridiculous amount of it.
It seems like just
the job for you guys.
Hold on, Ginro.
Where you going?
Oh, you know me! Off to train.
And I have to guard the village,
so I don't really have the
time to take this on, too.
I'll have to pass. Shucks.
The rules are the rules.
And the village chief's
orders are absolute.
Let me go, please!
This is gonna be so hard!
[KINRO]
I said, "Rules are rules"!
[KIDS gasp]
This thing makes the house
super warm and toasty!
We should make a nice
hot meal for everybody to eat.
[NATORI]
Mh-hm!
We have the time, since
the work's going faster.
[SENKU] Now then, the only
thing that we really need
are the ashes from the coal.
But you're more than welcome
to sit by the fire.
I'm impressed, Senku.
Huh?
I realize that the
things you're making
are for a completely
separate goal,
but our little village
is slowly becoming
a much better place to live.
It's true. That's
how science works.
It's just as simple as that.
[KOKUYO]
I must say,
you ended up being just
the man we needed
to lead our village
into the future.
Hold on. Zinc-carbon batteries?
Are we gonna use batteries
to finish the vacuum tubes?
The instructions and materials
are all listed there.
We'll use the manganese
from the caves.
Uh...
So you want me to
make them, do you?
[sighs]
We'll need 800, at the least.
Huh?! Are you crazy?!
Utal-bray.
I can lend a hand! No problem!
[thud]
Here's the wine
that you asked for.
You throwin' a party, or what?
Nuh-uh. Makin' some microphones.
They're the vocal cord.
Huh? Out of wine?
Yeah.
More precisely... we'll be
using these pink crystals
that are stuck all
over the lid here.
Then we'll cook some
of this seaweed,
mix it into hot water, and done.
Huh?! Which part of this stuff
is the gonna be the
"microphone" thingy?
Dunno, and what are all those
shiny rocks in there?
[SENKU]
They're Rochelle salts
and they turn sound
into electricity.
You can tack one of these
onto something lightweight,
like a plastic megaphone
for example,
and you've got yourself
a microphone.
The plastic hurdle's cleared!
The wire hurdle's cleared!
Vacuum tube hurdle's cleared!
Microphone's cleared!
[SENKU] The most powerful
weapon of modern warfare
is one that shoots voices
over infinite distances.
It's the birth of
the cell phone.
Oh, yeah!
[BOTH gasp]
Whoa!
[KASEKI laughs]
Yay!
[GEN chuckles]
So bad!
[chuckles]
And we were able to pull this
thing off before spring came.
[SENKU] The final battle
is coming soon.
We're up against Tsukasa,
so get ready, everyone.
[SENKU]
And of course, get excited.