[music playing]
[chuckles]
[VILLAGERS chattering]
[GAN'EN gasps]
[SENKU] This savory bowl
of gourmet science...
...is gonna buy me enough
manpower to make steel.
Foxtail millet ramen. Coming up!
[GAN'EN] I've never had anything
so chewy and amazingly yummy!
[chuckles]
We all know Gan'en has some
experience with eating, so...
Man, that's tasty!
A steaming stew of
slippery deliciousness!
Are you the man who made all
this incredible food for us?
The one called Senku?
So, what kinda
girls do you like?
The kind that can pump a ton
of oxygen into my furnace.
What kind of answer
is that? Really!
I mean, did the concept
of polite small talk
not exist during your time?
[CHROME]
Hey, Kinro, Ginro!
Don't pretend like you
don't wanna try it.
This ramen stuff
is insanely good!
[GINRO gasping]
We will not eat food
made with your sorcery!
Besides, a guard
accepting a gift
would clearly be in
violation, you know that!
Rules are rules!
Really? Then what have
you got in your hand?
I guess there's a special
exception for a golden spear?
Yeah, what gives, Kinro?!
[VILLAGERS chattering]
[JASPER]
Chief, it's about your daughter.
Kohaku is handing out strange
food to the villagers.
[KOKUYO]
Say what?
[JASPER]
Shall we go?
[KOKUYO]
Why would we?
To try it.
You believe I would do that?
[RURI] Kohaku, what are you
and that outsider really up to?
[SUIKA]
Here you go!
I've totally lost track of
who I've served already!
They're really eating it up.
Everyone's coming to get some.
Heh. They can have
all they want.
But they'll find out very soon
that the more ramen they eat,
the harder I'm gonna work 'em!
You really do make the
creepiest faces sometimes.
Ah. This ramen is making
me wickedly thirsty.
A cola would be great.
Cola?
Senku. You happen
to know that guy?
[SENKU]
No, I don't.
[CHROME] Hey, just eat it
before it gets all mushy.
[KOHAKU] Kinro. Ginro. I need
you to stop squabbling.
How come? Is there a--?
[gasps]
[KOHAKU]
I'll get right to the point.
There's trouble.
Better answer truthfully,
or I'll slit your throat
before you know what hit you.
Are you one of the long-haired
man's underlings?
[chuckles]
[GEN] Well, while I admittedly
don't mind the attention
of a cute little thing like you,
I believe you must've mistaken
me for somebody else.
[GEN sighs]
[GEN] I've not yet met
any "long-haired man."
I've been wandering
all on my lonesome
since breaking out of the stone.
I thought that you looked
strangely familiar somehow.
You're Asagiri Gen, right?
So you do know him!
[SENKU]
No. Never met him in my life.
He's a trashy magician
who wrote psychology books.
Read my work, have you?
How wonderful.
But that "trashy magician"
barb was cruel.
Please, call me a "mentalist."
Look, I apologize for taking
the ramen without asking.
So please, will you be kind
and lower your weapons?
My arms and legs are
trembling in fear,
and I'm worried I may spill
this heavenly bowl.
I got it! I don't mind
holding it for you!
[KOHAKU]
He's full of crap.
[GEN] I was all by myself and
searching for something to eat,
then my nose was
filled with nostalgia.
The scent of ramen.
[KOHAKU] I've seen scared guys
before, and he's not one.
And every word outta his
mouth is like feathery fluff.
...having an extremely
difficult time adapting.
[SENKU chuckles]
Yeah, sure, I'll take
your word for it, man.
But still, there's no such
thing as a free lunch.
You and everybody else
who ate the ramen
have got some work to do.
[screaming]
[ALL screaming]
We've upgraded the
blowing capability!
Iron furnace: Level two!
We're gonna have to take turns,
but I think it'll work!
Question for ya, Gen.
How are Taiju and Yuzuriha
doing these days?
[GEN]
Uhh...
Oh, so that's your game, yeah?
Work me into a state
of exhaustion
and fool me into fessing up?
You've got guts,
trying to pull a trick like that
on a renowned mentalist.
[GEN] There's no need
for you to worry.
Taiju's strength is
seemingly without end.
But you know that, right, Senku?
[KOHAKU] He's definitely
with that long-haired man!
Should I kill him?
Wait, you fool.
Okay, Gen.
You ten billion percent knew
I was trying to make you talk,
so why'd you
suddenly let it slip
that you're working
with Tsukasa?
Well, because once
I saw all of this,
the tides turned, as they say.
[GEN]
I have a simple task.
That is to confirm your
death beyond any doubt.
"Tsukasa, Senku
is still alive."
One little phrase, and your
fate would be sealed.
That was my initial plan.
But if you're able to finish
forging weapons made of iron,
there's no telling
who'd come out on top.
[gasps]
Whoa!
[SUIKA]
Wow!
[GEN] "All I found was a
tiny primitive village.
Seems Senku is no more."
One fraudulent report
would spare your life.
Does that sound good to you?
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU]
Actually, it's music to my ears,
and I'd really appreciate
you doing that.
[GEN] Don't go thinking I've
got some "moral compass."
I'm unbelievably shallow.
Give me a life
surrounded by hot girls
and I'm happy as a clam.
I couldn't care less if you
and that primate Tsukasa
live or die.
I'll be on the winning side,
no matter what I have to do.
What benefits me most?
Is it aligning with your
fledgling Kingdom of Science,
or perhaps Tsukasa's
Empire of Strength?
That is truly the
extent of my concern.
On one hand,
there's the scientific creations
and ramen and all that.
But hellish, back-breaking
work is just not my style.
On the other hand, Tsukasa's
settlement lacks science
and the food is rather plain.
But my work is easy.
And if I revive
a few hot celebs,
I could have the
harem of my dreams.
A harem? What's that?
I'm sorry. All I can say is
that it's not for children.
[SUIKA] Well, whatever it is,
ramen is probably way better!
Yeah. Ramen's nice, but
on a balmy day like this,
I think I'd rather side with
Tsukasa and what he can provide.
Asagiri Gen, was it?
I think the only two options for
a snake in the grass like you
are either locked up
or put in the ground!
Scary!
No.
If he doesn't go back
and give his report,
Tsukasa will come
looking for him
and we'll all be screwed.
[chuckles]
So relax, would you?
I've got a plan for this iron.
And once you feast your eyes on
what we're gonna make with it,
there's a ten billion percent
chance you'll choose
to join our Kingdom of Science.
Oh? What's that? Think you
can sway me with a sword?
How 'bout a generator?
A generator? Are you
freakin' kidding me?
No way you could pull that off!
[SENKU]
Nice, you have native copper.
[CHROME] Hey, that stuff's
way too pretty to destroy.
We'll melt it to make wire.
[CHROME] Damnit,
you're not even listening.
Now then, if only we
could get some lightning.
[JASPER] It's lightning,
the rage of the heavens!
[ARGO]
If it hits you, you're dead!
Make sure the women
and children are safe!
[JASPER]
Move! Quickly!
Looks like we're getting
our lightning.
Ha! It is the rainy
season, after all.
Ah! Can you believe
how lucky we are?
This isn't luck, it's
the worst-case scenario!
We are in no way prepared
to utilize this right now!
The generator will
run on lightning?
That's ridiculous.
Yes, of course.
Magnets. I can make a
generator if I have magnets.
[SUIKA] But we have the ones
we used to collect the sand.
The natural ones are way
too weak for what we need.
We'll catch lightning
with an iron rod,
and make a crazy-strong magnet
using the power of science!
I was gonna put up a bunch of
rods, as many as possible,
but we can't pass
up this opportunity.
We'll just have to run
with what we've got!
Heh. Pardon the pun, but we
gotta move fast as lightning!
Melt the copper!
There's lacquer coating
Kohaku's shield;
we could really use
some of that!
[SUIKA] I got a whole
jar of it right here!
Lacquer is a ridiculously
effective insulator.
Use it to coat the iron rod.
I'm confused.
Uh. I don't think you
should be doing that!
I've carved a channel in it!
[SENKU] Pour the melted
copper into the channel.
And after it solidifies,
wrap it up real tight
around the iron bar.
Hey, everybody, listen up!
The foreigner and his friends
have started destroying
the bridge!
Heh. So he's finally showing us
his true, evil colors, huh?
That's probably why the
gods are so angry with us.
They don't like that sorcery.
Ah, yeah!
All right. Time for them to die.
[gasps]
[CHROME]
This is bad! It's Magma!
[KOHAKU] He's not the kinda
guy who talks things over.
We're gonna have to fight!
If we go to war with the village
right now, it's game over!
I need to think fast!
[sighs]
Now this won't do.
I simply can't let myself get
killed because of you lot.
Fetch me some flowers, Suika.
Huh?
Instead of war, flowers.
[ALL]
Hm?
[GEN]
Ha!
What in the hell is this
guy holdin' flowers for?
Doesn't he know we're
lookin' for a fight?
Yeah!
Were you the one that made
the gods so angry? Heh.
Stepping up to me like this
takes more balls than brains.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
We're trying to use our sorcery
to stop this onslaught
of terror from above.
Quit talkin' outta your ass.
I don't wanna hear--
Allow me to show you.
[MANTLE, CARBO gasp]
They disappeared!
Did you see that?
[KOHAKU]
Wait a second.
So they really can't
see the flowers?
[SENKU] It's a trick
that I believe is called
the back palm.
Magicians do it all the
time with cards and stuff.
Hmph.
Not too shabby for
a complete fraud.
[MANTLE screaming]
Heh.
[GEN sighs]
[SENKU] It may sound nuts,
but it's doable.
There was a guy at NASA
called Wasilewski
who ran successful
experiments using lightning
to make powerful magnets.
[WASILEWSKI]
Wasilewski!
I just so happened to
find this bad boy
on top of that bald
mountain one day!
Well, Chrome,
I'd say that your ten
years of exploration
are really paying off now.
Oh, yeah. Pretty bad, right?
We're at the top of
the bald mountain!
[SENKU]
Perfect spot to catch lightning.
We couldn't ask for
a better place!
Set up the lightning
rod, quickly!
You see that?
I think they wanna make
a tower, should we--?
No way! You're just after a
silver spear, aren't you?
We came here to keep an eye
on them. Rules are rules, okay?
The lightning's close now.
Crap. There isn't enough time
to build real scaffolding.
Even so, we have to
get as high as we can.
If only there were
something long
that we could stick
into the ground.
[GINRO]
Uh?
No! Not happening!
This is my spear!
Guess you like it more
than you let on.
[KINRO screams]
[yells]
My spear!
[chuckles]
Well, take a look at that.
The lightning god descends.
[GEN laughs]
This is crazy, Senku.
Starting with nothing
in this barren Stone World.
You actually pulled it off.
Electricity is in play.
[SENKU]
Get excited, people.
Woohoo! We scored a
magnet for our generator!
Oh, no. Was your
golden spear destroyed?
I hope you can
forgive me, Kinro.
But it was kind of an emergency.
I'm sure Senku will make you
another one if you ask him.
Hey, Kinro! Where did that
special spear of yours go?
Gone forever, huh?
And you were so
protective of it, too.
I mean, you never even
let me borrow it once,
and yet here we are;
it's a real shame.
[GINRO groaning]
[SUIKA]
Uhh...
Senku, I think we may have
failed to create magnets.
[gasps]
They won't get anywhere
near each other.
Some force is
driving them apart!
Just switch one of their poles.
[SENKU yelps]
[KOHAKU, CHROME gasp]
[SUIKA]
Wow! They're so strong!
We can make it now, can't we?
That crazy-bad thing
you call electricity?
I'm curious, Senku. Are you
creating a thermal generator?
Or a wind turbine?
I don't suppose you're
going nuclear yet.
It'll be muscle powered.
I should've expected as much.
We'll hammer the
copper to stretch it,
cut it into a disk,
and grind it down.
Yo! Let's try and grind this
disk down with corundum.
It's one of the
baddest rocks I've got!
The second-strongest
mineral after diamond.
I really admire your
collection, Chrome.
I'd thought we'd coat the copper
wire with phosphoric acid,
but this lacquer
oughtta work just fine.
I've been racking my brain
trying to come up with
the perfect quip,
but I think I should just ask.
[SENKU]
What?
Why do you look like
a human marshmallow?
Lacquer poisoning.
[banging]
Ah, yeah!
[SENKU chuckles]
The Kingdom of Science advances.
[SENKU] Our dual-wield
hand crank generator
is now complete.
So do we need to spin
them both in unison?
That seems pretty challenging.
Not if two of us work together!
If they get outta sync,
it'll break down.
The timing has to be perfect.
Ugh. This has to be done right.
If only we knew a pair
who were perfectly
coordinated and energetic.
[ALL gasp]
So you came back again.
What do you want this time?
C'mon!
I'll let you guys check out
our badass science machine!
[KINRO]
Not interested.
[CHROME whines]
You've always been a
pretty stubborn guy,
but now it feels like
you're holding a grudge.
[SENKU chuckles]
He must still be upset
that we ruined the golden
spear I made for him.
Huh?
What now?
[GEN] Wow, electricity
sure is amazing!
Thanks, sorcery!
In our technological
civilization,
electricity lets us have
all sorts of nice things!
With our new generator,
we might even be able
to create and repair
gold- and silver-tipped spears.
Isn't that right, Senku?
Electrocoating is
pretty damn difficult.
Do you actually
know how to do it?
I don't have the faintest idea.
I was right about you.
Every word out of your mouth
really is just feathery fluff.
[GINRO, KINRO yelling]
They're a great team.
Perfectly in sync.
[SENKU chuckles]
Kinro and Ginro are mine now.
The Kingdom of Science is
building up a solid workforce.
But are they actually
generating electricity?
[SENKU] It's a
steam-roasted bamboo fiber.
[GEN]
Uh.
[KOHAKU]
Does it need to be that high up?
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU] Not really. But I
figure we might as well.
[gasps]
[GEN]
I see now.
He's using that bamboo fiber
to create an Edison light bulb.
I've never heard of
a bulb of light.
Chrome, does the
night scare you?
Well, yeah, because
everything gets dark.
Why do you ask?
[SENKU] Back in my day,
there was no darkness.
With old man Edison's
incandescent light bulb,
humanity beat back the night.
Conquering all
24 hours of the day.
Through the power of science,
mankind defeated the darkness.
And now we're gonna do it again.
For the first time
in 3,700 years,
the flame of science will burn.