[TAIJU]
Yuzuriha!
Sorry I'm late!
It's fine.
So what's going on, Taiju?
You wanted to talk to me?
[giggles]
[TAIJU] All this time,
I've been so scared
that if I tell her how
I really feel about her,
she could not want to
be my friend anymore.
[TAIJU]
It's like this, Yuzuriha.
All right. No turning back now!
[TAIJU] I've kept this inside
me for five years, and--
[gasps]
[TAIJU] Hold up,
what's that weird light?
[NARRATOR]
On that day,
every man, woman,
and child on Earth
instantly turned to stone.
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU]
Well, look who's finally awake.
Good morning, ya big oaf.
[chuckles]
It's October 5th
in the year 5738.
It has been 3,700 years.
[gasps]
How do you know what day it is?
You got some kinda
calendar, or what?
Huh? I figured it
out by counting.
It was the logical thing to do.
It took humanity over
two million years
to crawl out of the stone
age to the modern age.
We need to do that in a sprint.
I swear, I'm going to
take back the world.
Through science, I'll figure
out what happened to us,
and how we broke free.
I swear on my life,
I'll save you!
[TAIJU gasps]
I'm gonna beat fantasy with
science as my only weapon.
Oh, hell yeah. Get excited.
What do you think, man?
Who are we gonna
bring back first?
[SENKU]
Hmm.
Well, we're gonna revive
everybody sooner or later,
so it doesn't matter all that
much who we start with.
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU]
Although I suppose it would suck
if we happened to wake
up a murderer first.
I get ya.
[SENKU] I don't particularly
feel like choosing
who we revive first.
So, Taiju. It's all
on you, my friend.
[TAIJU gasps]
I appreciate that, pal.
I know who I'll pick.
I mean, it's obvious.
[TAIJU]
All right, I'm ready.
It's go time!
Let's pour that miracle water!
It's gonna turn her back
to normal again, right?
Yeah. I believe that it will.
I tried it on a piece
of broken stone
and it turned into
a hunk of dead flesh.
Try and have a little respect
for the dead, would ya?!
I did make the effort
to put them back together
first, obviously.
But it seems that once
someone has died,
reviving them is not an option.
I value their sacrifice.
Perhaps you should
pray for them.
[TAIJU]
Uh, right!
Rest in peace, rest in peace,
rest in peace, rest in peace...
[TAIJU]
I'm sorry, Yuzuriha.
I didn't mean to keep you
waiting for thousands of years.
But now, I'm gonna
bring you back to life.
Hold on, Senku! She's naked!
Don't look at her!
[TAIJU] We gotta wait!
We can't wake her up like this!
I know it's tough,
but would it kill you to try
to use some logic for once?
I think the Stone World's
kind of a special situation.
There's absolutely nobody
around to give a damn
if your butt's showing,
or even if your
dick's hanging out.
Yuzuriha does not have a dick!
You're missing the
point, you idiot!
We need to take her back to camp
and get some clothes
on her first.
Okay. But how heavy's
that statue, anyway?
You'd better not
be calling her fat!
Way to completely miss
the point again.
What I mean, is wouldn't it
be like ten billion times
more efficient to
just wake her up
and have her walk there with us?
I can't deal with all
this illogical thinking.
[snarling]
Hey, wait, you big oaf!
[TAIJU]
Huh?
[growls]
Why is there a lion
walking around Japan?!
Why do you think?!
It's gotta be descended from
a zoo animal, obviously!
The door must've been open
when the zookeeper
was turned to stone.
And without humans
to contain them,
all the herbivores
were likely on the menu!
Plus, once they got
out into the city,
I'm sure it was a pet buffet!
So that means, they're
literally the king of beasts!
The Stone World is brutal, and
we can't let ourselves forget:
Humans aren't at the top
of the food chain anymore!
[BOTH yell]
[roaring]
[TAIJU] Why haven't the lions
actually attacked us, yet?
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU] They've probably
never seen bipeds before.
I bet we look creepy as hell
to them, running on two legs.
[TAIJU] Yeah, we are the
only humans in the world.
[SENKU]
We definitely spooked 'em.
But they'll go in
for the kill soon.
Even if we get super lucky and
make it back to camp in time,
all we've got to fight
them with are spears.
Unfortunately, this was "game
over" from the very beginning.
[TAIJU yells]
[yelps]
You dying now is not
an option, Senku!
Your big, science-filled brain
is humanity's last hope!
Even if I gotta be lion
food, I'll save ya!
No way!
Use some logic for once, Taiju!
I'm the brains, and obviously
you're the brawn!
If humanity is gonna live on,
we both need to as well!
If we're gonna
make a run for it,
it's imperative
we do it together!
Yeah! I got it!
[SENKU] Besides, I know you've
never actually even hit anyone.
That's been true ever
since we were little.
[SENKU] You may be an athlete,
and strong as an ox,
but you're not a fighter!
[TAIJU]
Hey, if we can't outrun them,
I thought of something
we can do instead!
I found this guy earlier.
He was called "the strongest
primate high-schooler."
Shishio Tsukasa.
[TAIJU]
Sorry about this,
but right now, we need somebody
who can fight to help us.
If we can make our way
through this in one piece,
I promise, we'll
wake you up real--
Don't waste your breath,
let's just pour it on him.
[snarling]
[BOTH gasp]
[TAIJU]
Crap! We're surrounded!
This is it!
[cracking]
[TAIJU]
Sorry!
I know this isn't what
you wanna wake up to
after sleeping a
few thousand years.
[TSUKASA]
What's the situation?
[SENKU] Your whole body
is covered in stone.
There're lions from your
nine o'clock to your two.
Yeah, okay.
[SENKU gasps]
[TSUKASA] You can fill me in
on all the details later,
but I owe you.
So I'll make you this promise.
As long as we're together,
the two of you will not
be in danger again.
From now on, I'll take
care of all the fighting.
[TAIJU]
Yeah!
You hear that, Senku?
We had brains and brawn,
but now we've also got
brute force on the team!
We're just like the
three musketeers!
[chuckles]
I suppose we are,
but I have a nagging
feeling that the new guy
may be a little bit too strong.
How could that be a bad thing?
Like, don't we need
that kinda help?
What if it turns out
that he's actually
some evil, homicidal,
sex-crazed, wannabe tyrant?
Dude's so overpowered,
he just killed a lion
with his bare hands.
In a world where guns
haven't been invented,
he's ten billion
percent unstoppable.
[YUZURIHA]
Wow!
Come to the "primate," Yuzuriha.
Oh, no way! We can't
let that happen.
[TSUKASA]
Hey, guys.
You have anything I could
use to butcher this with?
A knife, or at least
something sharp
if that's all we've got.
Are you thinking about
eating that thing?
That's nasty!
[SENKU chuckles]
Well, it's not poisonous,
but it's super tough
and reeks of ammonia.
Not to mention it tastes bad.
When the hell did you eat lion?!
When I was in Africa
doing research on Ebola.
What kind of high-
school kid are you?!
[TSUKASA]
Although it was attacking us,
I took this noble
creature's life.
So... I wanna give back
to the circle of life
by putting all of it to use.
I owe it that much.
[yells]
That's so cool!
How 'bout that, Senku?
We just woke up a
legendary warrior
and he's like, actually
a solid dude, too!
[SENKU]
I hope you're right.
Well, the whole
"circle of life" thing
doesn't move me one millimeter.
But I have to agree about not
wasting meat or resources.
[TSUKASA] Interesting.
The two of you built this?
[SENKU]
Sure did.
Just hang in there a
little while longer, okay?
But I promise, we'll
get you fixed up.
We just need miracle water.
[TSUKASA]
Huh.
You've got a laboratory?
[TSUKASA]
Anyway, I'm Shishio Tsukasa.
Just call me Tsukasa.
I suppose family names don't
really mean much in this world.
I'm Senku, the brainy one behind
our scientific advancements.
Taiju, the simple one,
handles all of the grunt work.
I'm Taiju, the simple one.
It's true. Senku does do most
of the thinking around here.
What have you been surviving on?
[SENKU] Mostly wild
greens and mushrooms.
And once in a while,
we'll bag a rabbit for meat.
[TAIJU] Oh, man, lately
I've been dreaming about
eating so much meat
my belly explodes.
[TAIJU laughs]
[TSUKASA] Well, you two
won't have to survive
on just that anymore.
I'm here now.
[TSUKASA] I'll take on all
the fighting and the hunting.
Oh, wow! This is awesome!
Now that you guys
have me on your side,
you won't have to just dream
about filling your bellies.
[TAIJU]
Ah, I get it.
So if we just go ahead
and cook the food,
we won't need a
fridge to keep it in.
I'm not cooking these fish.
I'm using the aldehydes in
the smoke to kill the microbes.
In words that your feeble
brain can understand,
I'm smoking them.
With me and Senku
working together,
we should have plenty
of preserved food.
We can take the first step
towards civilization now.
So we're still on step zero?
[TAIJU]
Huh?
Hey, Tsukasa, what's wrong?
[yelling]
[BOTH gasp]
[TAIJU gasps]
Sorry if I startled you.
[TSUKASA] Just noticed this
person buried under that rock.
I said he was a solid
dude, didn't I?
[chuckles]
It's like having a superhero
on our team, huh?
[TAIJU groans]
My belly's so full!
Okay. It's time to take
a fun little pop quiz.
For a technological
civilization,
what's the most important
component to have?
Right answer will get
you ten billion points.
Well, it's gotta be...
something that's techy,
but what exactly?
Smartphones!
Oh, sure! Yeah!
Smartphones would be
great, wouldn't they?
We're not jumping ten billion
years into the future, dummy!
Maybe... iron?
Iron's pretty important,
but not at this stage.
There's something
far more crucial.
It's calcium carbonate.
[TAIJU]
Of course!
Once again, I have no idea
what you're saying!
[TSUKASA]
Do you mean lime?
[SENKU] Yep, let me
think of way to put it
that even someone like
Taiju could understand.
It's the stuff they use
to mark athletic fields.
Cool! So we're gonna have
to find a gym storage locker
and grab some whatever-
that-was carbonate?
Oh, sure! Yeah!
Let's just head to the gym!
Don't be such an idiot!
You think we'll find one
after 3,700 years?
[SENKU]
C'mon, Taiju, think.
You know those shells
that you've been using
to shave your big, oafish face?
If we pulverize them
into a powder,
we'll have plenty of calcium
carbonate in no time.
Yeah!
Looks like I'm needed for
some serious brawn duty!
[yelling]
[SENKU] Calcium carbonate
actually gets me excited.
Check it out!
There are four super useful
things you can do with it.
First is agriculture.
We can use it to blow away
the hydrogen ions in the soil,
and that'll be a major
upgrade for the farmland.
Second is construction.
Heat it up and mix it with
sand and you have mortar.
[TAIJU coughing]
[SENKU] Mortar's like a
less sophisticated cement.
We can use it to build
houses and furnaces.
Third is hygiene.
Gather calcium carbonate from
seaweed and blend it with oil
and the reaction makes soap.
[SENKU]
This world is brutal,
and getting sick
means game over.
But a little chunk that
gets rid of harmful germs
is a lifesaver in a
world without doctors.
You can call it "Doctor Stone."
[TSUKASA]
I gotta hand it to you, Senku.
You're pretty amazing.
[SENKU]
Hm?
I mean, you freed me
during a lion attack,
but you stayed calm
and spoke clearly.
I've never met anyone
like you before.
You truly have my respect.
For at least the last
ten billion years or so,
almost without exception,
a man who praises
another to his face
is either flirting or scheming.
[SENKU]
So what are you getting at?
It's not like that. I'm really
not doing either one of those.
I was just thinking,
if there's anybody
who could rebuild modern
civilization from scratch,
it's you.
Yeah. That's all I
was trying to say.
[TAIJU grunts]
So this is the kinda
stuff you gotta do
to build a civilization, huh?
That's right.
One step at a time.
The journey is a slow one,
that's for sure.
But we keep on getting closer.
Hey, so what was
that fourth thing?
You said there were four
uses for the seashells,
but you only told
us about three.
No, there're only three.
I said three earlier, didn't I?
[TAIJU]
Oh. Did you?
Man, my memory is
all screwed up.
[TAIJU laughing]
[snoring]
[TAIJU coughs]
[TAIJU]
Shells! Shells! Shells! Shells!
Shells! Shells! Shells!
[TSUKASA] We have so much
freedom in this Stone World.
Nobody is around to
claim that shells
are their personal property.
Or the ocean. Or the land.
[TSUKASA] A long time ago,
there was a poor boy
whose little sister was
going through surgery.
He collected seashells to
make a necklace for her
and help her feel better.
His sister loved
the Little Mermaid.
But along came an older man
who owned the fishing rights
to that part of the beach.
He reeked of booze.
[TSUKASA] The boy thought he was
collecting shells, but the man,
the man accused him
of stealing the shells,
and beat him so badly,
he was almost unrecognizable,
He was never able
to make his sister
feel like the Little Mermaid.
You do know what you
just did, don't you?
That may have looked
like a statue,
but we both know you
just killed a man.
[TSUKASA]
Of course I know.
Tell me something, Senku.
Are you planning to bring back
all the greedy,
black-hearted adults
who ruined the world
we came from?
Sure, they'll be overly
grateful to you
right after you help them out
but as soon as
civilization returns,
the rich and powerful
will say things like,
"This used to be my property,
so you'd better start
paying me rent."
Next, they'll try
to collect taxes.
They'll rob the
young people like us
of our future all over again.
We simply can't bring
that kind of world back.
We live in the Stone World now.
A paradise that hasn't
been ruined by greed.
I think we should only revive
the young and pure-hearted,
and make sure that we
keep this world natural
and not owned by anyone.
This is our chance
to purify humanity.
Don't you agree with me, Senku?
No, I don't. That speech didn't
move me one millimeter.
I'm the kinda guy who
absolutely loves technology.
I get excited by space and mechs
and Doraemon
and stuff like that.
I'm going use the
awesome power of science
to rescue every last person.