[CHALK barking]
I'm so happy to see you!
[CHROME]
Biggest hurdle cleared!
Sulfuric acid acquired!
Ah. This is so amazing!
We can finally make the
medicine and save Ruri's life!
We're still a few steps away.
You gotta have some patience.
You remember that crazy
roadmap to the drug, right?
I recall it being
incredibly long.
Heh. No sweat. We're close.
We have just about
every component
that we're gonna need now.
[ALL gasp]
[SENKU] And since most of
the materials are in place,
it's just a matter of lighting
up all the dark spots
on the roadmap, one by one.
Should be pretty easy, actually.
So why don't we light up
all of 'em up today?
It's time for a little mad
chemical cooking class.
So you'd better get excited!
[SENKU] First, we boil
the sulfuric acid,
and add a pinch of salt.
This glass thingy is weird.
It looks like there's a stick
in the middle of it.
You asked me to make this
bizarre doohickey and I did it!
I have no idea what you're
going to use it for,
but you went and got me excited!
[SENKU]
It's part of a dripping system.
[CHROME] We're catching the gas
coming out of the sulfuric acid
and salt mixture as it drips.
Hydrochloric acid acquired.
Hydrochloric?
It's a slightly
dangerous chemical.
Get this stuff in your eyes
and you'll go blind.
Next, we take the sinters
from the sulfuric acid spring,
which some call
"flowers of sulfur,"
boil 'em, throw 'em into
the hydrochloric acid
we just made, and...
Now we have chlorosulfuric acid.
Chlorosulfuric? Uh...
It's a super bad chemical.
Get this on your skin and you'll
turn into a skulking zombie.
[BOTH yelling]
That's good. Smells
like a swimming pool.
We'll separate the salt
water with electricity...
And we've acquired
sodium hydroxide.
Sodi... hydra?
It's an extremely bad chemical.
The yakuza use it to
melt enemy corpses.
[KOHAKU]
Oh. I get it now.
[SENKU]
Huh?
It makes you blind,
turns you into a zombie,
and melts your corpse.
Is that all?
Senku, you're gonna
make Ruri drink that?
[SENKU]
No one's drinking it!
We're just using it
to prepare the drug!
Relax, will ya? All the rest
of the chemicals are harmless.
Next up is ammonia.
Let's go!
[KOHAKU]
Where do you get that?
[gasps]
[BOTH sigh]
[SENKU]
Ammonia... acquired.
Do you really think
I'm gonna let you
force my sister to drink that?
[SENKU]
She's not drinking it!
We just need it to
prepare the drug!
All right, we're so
close to getting there.
We're down to the
last three items:
Acetic anhydride, sodium
bicarbonate, and anilin.
[SUIKA] Sounds like you're
casting some kind of spell.
But we need alcohol to make
those. That's the key here.
So if we can get our
hands on some booze,
we'll have the
ultimate cure-all.
A powerful sulfa drug.
[ALL gasp]
So let's make us
some alcohol then!
That's gonna take a
little time and energy.
Some more manpower
would be great.
Need booze? Funny
you mention it.
Because if you were
to be victorious
in the Grand Bout tomorrow,
the villagers will
give you more booze
than you could ever
hope to finish.
Wait, it's tomorrow? No way!
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU] The timing
couldn't be more perfect.
[GINRO yelps]
[CHROME]
Right.
If Kinro or Ginro wins,
we'll have alcohol,
and then practically
nothing can stop us
from making Ruri's medicine!
[SENKU]
Yeah.
Our team is gonna win the
Grand Bout, even if it kills us.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
[KOKUYO]
At last, the time is upon us.
Tomorrow, your husband, the new
village chief, will be chosen.
Are you ready for that?
Yes.
[KOKUYO]
Turquoise!
Are preparations for the Grand
Bout proceeding as planned?
Yes.
Well, I mean... the
preparations are in order,
but there is one thing.
Why is Kohaku allowed to
take part in this again?
You need to go and
tell her that she can't!
Anybody over 14 and
unmarried can enter.
The sacred rules governing the
Grand Bout can't be changed.
When those rules were written,
nobody expected a hard-headed
girl to compete!
Ugh. But I suppose we
should just let it be.
After all, a man who's
unable to defeat a woman
isn't fit to be the
village chief, anyway.
Chief, there's actually
one more small problem.
[KOKUYO]
Hmm?
Yet another contestant
has submitted their name.
You're gonna participate
in the Grand Bout, too?
And I was the one who signed
him up for the big battle!
Yep! Senku is over 14
and unmarried, isn't he?
That's right.
Plus, there's no rule that says
you have to be a
villager to participate.
[SENKU, GINRO chuckle]
[SUIKA]
This is kinda weird.
Since when have Senku
and Ginro been so close?
[KOHAKU] Well, they're birds
of the same devious feather.
No offense, Senku, but
you're not a capable fighter.
[SENKU chuckles]
I don't plan on
winning the thing.
My main goal is just to
tire out our opponents.
And not only that, if we happen
to go up against each other...
[GINRO]
Boop.
Oh, no, you sure got me good!
We move up without
breakin' a sweat!
So the more contestants
on our side, the better!
You see?
You're really gonna
rig the Grand Bout?
How dishonorable. Even for you.
Either way, although the goal
is worthy, rules are rules.
I won't throw my match.
I'll still fight fairly
and with honor.
[GINRO, SENKU]
Yeah, of course you will!
Everybody knows that you
have the best chance
at beating Magma in
a one-on-one fight.
So we're gonna need you
to save your energy
and make it to the top!
Exactly! Nobody's asking
you to cheat, Kinro.
Once you hit us, we're just
gonna cry out "mercy"
and the match'll be over.
No problem there, right?
[KINRO]
You're not convincing me
that this is the
right thing to do.
Hey! What do you
think about this?
Please, Kohaku. Surely you
don't agree with them!
Eh... Honestly?
If this can help
my sister survive,
then I'm left with
no other choice.
Ha. It's been close to half
a year since Senku arrived.
Now, finally...
This is the first time
I've set foot in the village.
Well, I'm here.
I take it that's the outsider?
The one foolish enough to
enter the Grand Bout?
Yes. His name is Senku.
[gasps]
[RURI]
It's what? Hold on.
Did I hear correctly that
this man's name is Senku?
It is. I assume you haven't
met him before. Have you?
[RURI] No, sir. Of course
I've never met him.
How could I have?
But yet... I do know him.
This Senku...
Could he be the one?
[BOTH gasp]
Wait, Ruri!
[RURI]
I've known him for years,
possibly even from long,
long ago in the past.
I've heard that
name all my life.
[RURI]
Your name is Senku, is it not?
And you're the village
priestess, Ruri. Heh.
So nice to finally
meet you in person.
Indeed.
I have a very important
question to ask you.
Tell me, please. Senku,
what is your surname?
Say what?
Surname?
[RURI] I mean, your family name.
The one that's passed--
Yeah. I know what you mean.
[SENKU] There's no tradition of
having surnames in this village,
so how does she know about them?
[RURI] Could it be
that you're... Ishi--
[RURI coughing]
[JASPER]
Priestess Ruri!
Stop there! Stay away from
the priestess, outsider!
[KOKUYO] Don't make her walk!
Carry her back immediately!
[TURQUOISE]
Are you all right?
I am.
I have about ten billion
questions for her as well.
I think she and I should
have a nice, long chat
after this Grand Bout
business is over.
[MAGMA laughing]
Now we're talkin'.
It looks as though I might not
have to go through the
trouble of killing her.
At this rate, she'll probably
keel over on our wedding night.
No, Magma! Anybody but you!
Well, look at that.
Chrome might actually have
some decent fighting
skills after all.
That's true.
Probably because he's been busy
poking that target
like a mad man!
[CHROME] I'm practicing hittin'
Magma's weak spot.
[GINRO]
His weak spot? You mean...
That's right! His junk!
[SUIKA yelps]
It's a sound strategy.
If we're trying to wear him
out in the early rounds,
then his testicles will be
an excellent target to strike.
My, Kohaku.
I know you have a reputation
as being somewhat of a tomboy,
but this strategy goes
well beyond that.
Some things should be
off-limits, you know.
I realize that I have
no chance of winning,
but if I can land a couple
of good hits on Magma.
I can wear him down
for the next person.
That's the best I can
do for our team!
He's right.
That means the order of matches
is going to be crucial.
[GINRO]
Rig the match! Rig the match!
Give us an order
that'll let us win...!
Yeah. I say to hell with
trying to have a fair fight.
The Kingdom of Science uses our
wits and cunning as weapons.
Our strategy is to game the
Grand Bout to work in our favor.
We'll rig it so that Kinro
gets to the top unscathed,
and pit him against
an exhausted Magma.
Which means it's best for us
if Kinro and Magma are
in separate blocks.
The quickest way would be if
I beat Magma in the first match.
That happens, it's smooth
sailing from there.
That's correct.
If you can take him
out early like that,
then we're good as gold.
[SUIKA] Since they're drawing
straws for the order,
all we can do is pray for luck.
Kohaku and Magma
start off together.
Kinro and Magma never
go against each other...
Is that a prayer or some
kinda tongue twister?
[SUIKA] Kinro and Magma
never go against each other.
Kohaku and Magma start...
They're drawing up the
brackets right now.
[SUIKA] Kohaku and Magma
start off together.
Kinro and Magma never
go against each other.
Kohaku and Magma
start off together!
Kinro and Magma never
go against each other!
The first round of the Grand
Bout will be between...
[JASPER]
...Kinro and Magma!
[GINRO]
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Seriously bad!
It's the exact opposite
of what I prayed for!
Damn it, how could we
have such rotten luck?
[SENKU chuckles]
Well, that's life.
[SUIKA]
Huh?
A scientist knows better than
to rely on luck or superstition.
Even if you're dealt
the worst hand,
you play every card you've got.
So we'll have to resort to
doping to win the Grand Bout.
Thus, I've developed
the Kingdom of Science's
special power-up drink!
[OTHER whimpering]
[KOHAKU] Great, another
suspicious chemical creation.
There some kinda bad
drug in that stuff?
[SENKU laughs]
Unfortunately,
it's perfectly safe.
It's a mixture made up of tea
leaves, honey, and sweet flag.
The caffeine speeds you up,
sweet flag keeps you cool,
and the honey jacks your
blood sugar way up.
It's the Stone World's
version of doping.
Did you really just
drink all of it?!
[GINRO] Ah! I didn't know
that was the whole supply!
What do you want me to do?
Because if you lose to Magma,
then that'll mean it'll be
completely up to me to beat him!
He even ate the raw ingredients.
Wow, yeah. There goes our
whole supply of sweet flag.
That's the grass, right?
The kind that grows
down by the river?
[SUIKA]
I'll go pick some more for us!
I may not be competing
in the Grand Bout,
but I can still make
myself useful!
[chuckles]
[GINRO]
Here's the plan.
Everything'll be just fine
as long as you make it to the
final match, you got that?
[MANTLE]
No! This is horrible!
Suika went to pick some herbs
and fell into the river!
I'm afraid the poor
thing's gonna drown!
Kohaku, you're the
fastest one here,
so you need to go down and
help her before it's too late!
It's ten billion percent obvious
he's lying through his teeth.
Eh?
No. I'm telling you
the truth, I swear.
I just happened to be walking
by the river when I saw her,
and then she fell in!
If you just happened to see
her fall into the river,
how did you know she was there
to pick herbs in
the first place?
Come back in ten billion years
if you really wanna
have a battle of wits
with the Kingdom of Science,
you slimy, pea-brained idiot.
I'm almost positive he's lying,
but there's a slim
chance that he's not.
I can't risk it
and let Suika die.
Yeah, well.
You realize you're our last line
of defense against Magma,
so if you bail on us now...
Look, I'm the fastest
out of all of us,
so I'm the only one
who can save her.
I know it's a little risky,
but I have to go see for myself!
[chuckles]
You're disgusting, Mantle.
A despicable person.
[GINRO, CHROME]
Kohaku!
No way! She's leaving us?
[JASPER]
Round one.
Kinro! Magma! Come forward!
[CHROME]
Hey, uh, Kohaku's not here.
She went to save Suika.
She competes in the third round.
If she hasn't returned by then,
she will be disqualified.
Damn it! Come on,
Kohaku. Hurry!
[MAGMA laughs]
Excellent work, Mantle.
Ah, yeah! I had to make sure
our problem was solved.
[MAGMA]
Now that Kohaku's gone,
there's no one who
can defeat me.
And I, Magma, will
get what I deserve.
Ruri and the entire
village will be mine.
Now, Kinro!
Surrender to me and I'll
make you my right-hand man.
I'll need a strong
fighter by my side,
as well as someone
who'll do my bidding.
Grovel at my feet
before the crowd.
Put on a show for everyone!
Do that, and I'll take it
as your pledge of loyalty.
[KINRO]
Listen, Magma.
Even if everything
you say is true,
I'd never kneel before you.
There are many schemes
in this Grand Bout,
but I can only fight honestly
and to the best of my abilities.
Besides, I'm not the
same man I was before.
[MAGMA laughs]
You've never once beaten me
in a match like this, Kinro,
so what's so different
about this time?
[KINRO] This time, I have
no choice but to win,
because my friends
are counting on me!
[JASPER]
Round one: Magma versus Kinro.
Begin!
You're motivated by
a lust for power.
But I... have bigger
reasons than that!
[KINRO yelling]
Wow, Kinro, when did
you get so strong?
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[GAN'EN] Kinro seems to be
holding his own against Magma.
He might actually win
this whole thing!
I gotta say, he's doing
ten billion times better
than I was expecting.
This is all thanks to the
training our battle team
had to go through.
Why the hell are you acting
so smug about it, Ginro?
--[GARNET, SAPPHIRE cheering]
--[MANTLE snickering]
[MANTLE] I've got our
backup plan right here.
[CHROME]
Hey, Mantle.
Jasper's our bad referee.
No way he's gonna let you
get away with that!
--[SENKU] You got this, Kinro!
--[CHROME] Take him down, Kinro!
[MANTLE]
Ah, yeah!
[chuckling]
I was just, uh...
Clack. Clack. Just clacking
these to cheer him on!
Nuts.
[MANTLE, CHROME gasp]
[SUIKA screaming]
What am I gonna do now?
Mantle tied me up so tight,
I don't know how I'm
gonna break outta this!
[gasps]
[yelling]
[SUIKA] I have to get back
to the others, quick!
[TITAN]
Magma took a big step back.
[GAN'EN] He always just goes
rushing in with brute force.
[CARBO]
He looks serious.
I've never seen him
like this before.
[KINRO] Not good. He's put
distance between us.
[VILLAGERS yelling]
[gasps]
[SUIKA] I know that look.
He's straining his eyes.
[gasps]
Oh, Suika!
You're back home safe!
So Mantle was lying
about you drowning.
What a little worm!
I think Kinro has the fuzzy
sickness in his eyes!
He's making faces
like I used to have to!
[MAGMA laughs]
Were ya tryin' to hit me
with that? Not even close!
[yells]
[MAGMA laughing]
Bad! He just wiped
the floor with him!
Kinro!
[KINRO]
I can barely move.
Is this it?
[KINRO]
No. Not yet.
It's too important
to give up now.
Uh. Suika?
What the hell do you think
you're doing up here?
[SUIKA]
I'm finally gonna really,
really make myself
useful for once!
[MAGMA laughs]
You don't give up, do ya, Kinro?
Think I like you even more now.
I actually want you
to be my henchman.
[KINRO yells]
[SUIKA] I'm gonna to use
the stairs to build up speed!
[MAGMA] Now, you'd better
start grovelin', boy!
[SUIKA yells]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Take the eyes of science! Kinro!
[ALL]
That makes him look so creepy!
[laughs]
Nice try, but that goofy
mask ain't gonna save ya!
[KINRO]
I can see.
This is the power of science!
Whoa! Holy crap!
It's close, but he's
dodging each attack!
Hey! What kinda stunt are
you tryin' to pull here?!
[yells]
I'm so grateful for science.
For Suika and for Senku!
[MAGMA screams]
[yells]
Learn this lesson, Magma.
If I'd had this gift of science
before... had this vision...
...I would've surpassed
you long ago.
[VILLAGERS cheering]