[NARRATOR]
On that day,
every man, woman,
and child on Earth
instantly turned to stone.
This is it, Senku.
My mind's made up!
I'm finally gonna do it!
After five long years,
I'm tellin' her how I feel!
[SENKU]
Wow. Fascinating.
I can't leave the lab right now,
but I promise to cheer
you on so vociferously,
my vocal cords'll snap.
Awesome! You mean it?
You rock, Senku!
No, you big oaf.
I won't project my voice even
one millimeter for your cause.
What? Come on, man!
Look, you've felt this
way for five years,
but never said anything?
I can't praise such
illogical behavior,
but I can give you
something logical as hell.
I've developed this drug
as a kind of "love potion."
It maxes out your
pheromone levels,
granting you a ten
billion percent chance
of winning her heart.
[gasps]
[TAIJU]
Thanks, but no thanks, Senku.
I gotta do this my way.
[door slams]
[STUDENT C]
Whoa, are you serious?
You made a love potion?
[SENKU]
Come on, use your brain.
It's gasoline.
I simply refined it from
plastic bottle caps.
Consider the molecular
structure of polyethylene.
It's just like a long
gasoline molecule
minus a few hydrocarbons.
You can tell by just looking.
[STUDENT E]
Well, I can't.
[STUDENT D]
Me, neither.
Yeah, but... If Taiju drank it,
wouldn't that've killed him?
[chuckles]
No, the odds of him drinking
that were ten billion to one.
He's dumb, but too strait-laced.
[TAIJU]
Yuzuriha!
Sorry I'm late!
It's fine.
So what's going on, Taiju?
You wanted to talk to me?
[giggles]
A hundred yen on heartbreak.
Three hundred on her
making him cry.
Five hundred on her
calling him a creep.
[SENKU] I bet ten thousand
that she's into him, too.
[GUYS]
Seriously?
[TAIJU] All this time,
I've been so scared
that if I tell her how
I really feel about her,
she could not want to
be my friend anymore.
But I can't keep it
a secret forever.
[TAIJU]
It's like this, Yuzuriha.
All right. No turning back now!
[TAIJU] I've kept this inside
me for five years, and--
[gasps]
[TAIJU] Hold up,
what's that weird light?
[TAIJU]
Quick! Grab on to the tree!
What the hell?
[GIRL A]
Why'd it get so dark?
--[MAN A] I can't move!
--[BOY A] I can't talk!
--[GIRL B] What's happening?
--[MAN B] Please! Help!
[MAN C]
It's the end of the world!
[WOMAN A]
My children!
[barking]
[GIRL C]
Mom! Dad!
Please, help me!
No. I'm scared.
Am I dying?
[yells]
[TAIJU]
I'm still alive!
I gotta stay focused
or else I'll fade out!
Wake up, Taiju!
Yuzuriha's smart.
I'm sure she probably got away.
But I can't die a coward!
I have to find her and tell
her exactly how I feel!
[howling]
[TAIJU] I've got the
willpower to survive!
I know I do!
This could go on for
weeks, or even months,
but still, no matter what,
I gotta let her know!
[TAIJU]
How many decades has it been?
Centuries? Millennia?
Well, I'm not giving up!
I'm gonna tell Yuzuriha
what my true feelings are.
I'm gonna survive this,
even if it kills me!
[cracking]
[gasps]
[screams]
[screaming]
I'm finally free! I can
move my body again!
[TAIJU]
Pieces of stone?
Oh, no.
So like, everyone went
through all that, too?
It's horrible.
How long have we been like this?
I'm sorry.
I really wish I could
do more to help you.
[TAIJU]
As long as the landscape
hasn't changed too much,
I should be able to
follow the river.
That'll lead me to
the tree... and to her.
[STUDENT A] Whoa, something
just fell over there.
[STUDENT B]
Is that a bird statue?
[STUDENT A]
There's so much detail.
I mean, check out those wings.
[STUDENT B]
It looks so real!
I think maybe it is real.
A friend of mine just
found one of these.
I saw the picture
he posted of it.
You poor little thing.
What happened?
Is it like some kinda disease
that made your skin harden up?
[YUZURIHA] Well, of course
the vet's office
wouldn't be open
before school hours.
Didn't really think
this one through, huh?
[TAIJU]
Crap, it's her!
[YUZURIHA] Not to mention that's
obviously a statue or something
and not a real bird, but you
still brought it to the vet.
You're so silly.
It's embarrassing.
[TAIJU] Of course, the moment
I do something stupid like this,
my crush shows up
outta nowhere.
Just my luck!
[TAIJU]
Uh? Why're you here?
[YUZURIHA] Well, because
I'm a big ol' dummy, too.
I found this little guy
and I wanted to see
if I could help him.
"Great minds," huh?
[TAIJU laughing]
[YUZURIHA]
Hey! Don't laugh at me!
You did the exact same thing!
Now we're both gonna
be late for school!
[TAIJU]
Yeah, whoops!
[TAIJU, YUZURIHA laughing]
Yuzuriha.
[TAIJU]
I could never forget that face.
Not even after
thousands of years.
I knew you were still alive.
I never lost hope.
And now...
I'm really proud of you!
And you're incredible,
too, tree!
You kept her safe
for this entire time!
Like you held onto
her. Thank you!
Sorry, but I just
couldn't protect you.
In fact, when you
really think about it,
you were actually the
one protecting me.
I was able to stay alive
because of you.
It's the truth.
You were my light
shining in the darkness
for hundreds, even
thousands of years.
And now, I can finally say it.
I started back then,
but I never got to finish.
So what I was gonna tell
you that day... is that...
...that I...
[TAIJU]
I've loved you...
...for hundreds and
thousands of years.
I swear on my life,
I'll save you!
Don't know how,
but I'll find a way.
Okay? So just wait--
Huh?
[TAIJU] "Follow the river
downstream, big oaf"?
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU]
Well, look who's finally awake.
Good morning, ya big oaf.
[TAIJU screams]
Oh, Senku! You're alive, too?!
Don't you dare hug me
while you're buck naked!
Hands off! I'm not joking!
[sighs]
It's October fifth,
in the year 5738.
You really slept in for
a hell of a long time.
I've been up and diligently
working my tail off
for the last six months.
Hold on. So it's been, like...
[SENKU]
It has been 3,700 years.
[gasps]
How do you know what day it is?
You got some kinda
calendar, or what?
Huh? I figured it
out by counting.
It was the logical thing to do.
[SENKU]
Four, five, six, seven, eight...
Damn, almost lost
consciousness again.
Seems to happen about every
800 thousand seconds.
Heh.
It's about as regular as my
bowel movements used to be.
I'll need to think and
count at the same time.
Run parallel processes.
One hundred-sixteen billion,
four hundred
twenty-seven million,
sixty-five thousand,
five hundred-thirty seconds.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven...
So that whole time you were
frozen, you just counted?
[SENKU] Even if I had willed
myself awake before then,
being out here stark-naked
with no supplies in winter
would've have meant game
over pretty damn quickly.
I realized I would have to start
things up in the springtime.
So keeping an extremely
precise account of the time
was an absolute must.
All right, we're here.
We need to put a pin in the
small talk and get to work.
Senku, you're tellin' me...
you did this on your own?
[SENKU] Until now,
I've been lacking manpower.
And coming up with the
bare minimum to survive
takes all my time.
If I'm gonna
rebuild civilization,
I'll need a muscle-y meathead
to do the grunt-work.
In other words, I've been
waiting for you, Taiju.
I was ten billion percent
sure you were still alive.
You were so hell bent on
confessing your love.
And for a guy as
stubborn as you,
even a few thousand
years wouldn't stop you
from making that happen.
You aren't that weak!
Yeah. Of course I'm not!
[TAIJU] All right, Senku, if you
can handle all the brainy stuff,
you can leave the heavy
lifting to me, no problem!
[SENKU] It took humanity
over two million years
to crawl out of the stone
age to the modern age.
We need to do that in a sprint.
I swear, I'm going to
take back the world.
Through science, I'll figure
out what happened to us,
and how we broke free.
[TAIJU] I swear,
I'm gonna save Yuzuriha!
[SENKU] We may be a couple
of high-school kids,
but we're gonna rebuild
civilization from the ground up.
You and I will be
like Adam and Eve.
Together, we'll bring life
back to this Stone World.
This is exhilarating.
Get excited.
That's definitely a
plus-sized haul, Taiju.
You have a real-life
cheat code for stamina?
[TAIJU yells]
[SENKU]
Amanita virosa, toxic.
Buna shimeji, safe.
Amanita muscaria, toxic.
If something looks like it's out
of a Mario game, pass it up.
Next. Mugwort, that's edible.
Wolf's bane. Are you
trying to poison us?
Oh, man! What the heck
did you season this with?
Just some salt that I
pulled out of the seawater.
A little pinch of it will make
almost anything palatable.
We can utilize it for
pickling food as well.
One of primitive man's greatest
discoveries, I'd say.
Thank you, Senku.
This is perfect!
I may not know all
the stuff that you do,
but I'm gonna bust my
back workin' for us!
[TAIJU yells]
[TAIJU] Time to check out
the other direction!
[TAIJU]
Whoa, these look like grapes.
Can we eat these, too?
There's one way to find
out. Get in my belly!
[TAIJU]
Hm?
I know I've seen that guy on TV.
He's called the "strongest
primate high-schooler."
Shishio Tsukasa.
Guess he couldn't
fight it, either.
[TAIJU gasps]
[TAIJU]
What's that?
Whoa!
Me and Senku haven't
been here yet,
so that means
someone else survived!
I gotta know who they are!
[SENKU]
It was me, idiot.
Oh, no way!
Are we the only ones
left, for real?
Like, the last
humans still alive?
[SENKU] We'll get more.
That's a top priority.
I mean, the two of us alone,
just a couple of dudes?
Can't "restart humanity"
if you catch my drift.
Yeah. That's true.
[SENKU]
Besides, why, after 3,700 years,
did we break free from
our petrified condition?
[TAIJU]
The stone rotted away?
[SENKU]
Well, something like that.
Say this strange mineral
had been corroded...
[chuckles]
Can you chalk up the timing
to mere random coincidence?
Six months apart is a
relative blip on the radar.
There's a reason why we both
reanimated so close together.
We drifted up near here.
It would make sense that this
cave factored in somehow.
See that? The stuff
trickling from overhead?
That's our miracle fluid,
made from bat guano.
Good ol' nitric acid.
No way! That's crazy!
What is that?
[SENKU]
I did anticipate that question.
But I'm not going to waste my
breath explaining it to you.
[TAIJU]
Let me guess.
You pour some of the
miracle stuff on it,
the stone breaks,
and the bird wakes up.
How I wish it were
so straightforward.
That would rule.
[SENKU] I've been working
like a madman on this project,
using every last method
I could think of.
[gasps]
[SENKU]
Over and over, again and again.
It's like something
from a fantasy world.
Is it all mineral?
Are there living
cells underneath?
I don't have the laboratory
for in-depth analysis.
So basically what
you're telling me is,
there are things even
science can't explain.
[SENKU chuckles]
There we go,
that tired old cliché.
Truth is, it never quite stands
up to the scientific method.
Science is often a slow process.
Some liquor might
speed things up.
[TAIJU]
Huh?
Combined with the nitric acid,
we could make something
nice and potent.
What's commonly known as nital,
which is an industrial-
strength etching agent.
[TAIJU]
What did you say we needed?
Huh? I said we could make nital.
It gets into the ferrite
grain boundary an--
No!
Don't confuse me with some
kinda "science talk."
I mean, the part about liquor.
Wine comes from grapes, yeah?
And that is a type
of alcohol, isn't it?
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU]
Not bad, you big oaf.
[SENKU groans]
[TAIJU yelling]
[SENKU]
Hm.
Yeah, we'll have you handle
all the neck-down work
from here on out.
It's just the logical choice.
[SENKU] Making wine is an
extremely simple process.
Crush your grapes or fruit,
put it in a container,
and stir it up every day
until it's ready to go.
Heh.
But if we tried this
back in our time,
we'd get arrested for
not having a license.
[SENKU]
It's been three weeks.
That should do the trick.
[TAIJU]
Thought of something.
Underage drinking's
a crime, too.
[SENKU chuckles]
Not a problem.
After all, we're both a
little over 3,700 years old.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
[TAIJU laughs]
Not bad. Way better
than expected.
Bet it's ten billion times worse
than what was on
the market, though.
That was so easy.
Just stomping grapes
and waiting around?
One step at a time, my friend.
Though I hate to say it,
our pace'll slow down.
This'll be a course in
"distilling wine for dummies."
Our goal is to acquire
some brandy.
[TAIJU] Distilling, huh?
No idea what that means.
I knew you'd say that.
It's heating, cooling,
and dripping.
That'll concentrate the alcohol.
Don't worry.
People back in
ancient Mesopotamia
were doing this with
clay pots in 3000 B.C.
And if they can do it,
then so can we!
Now get excited, Taiju.
Listen up, big oaf.
Lesson one:
It's not that there are things
science can't explain.
Not in the least.
[cracking]
[SENKU] There are rules behind
everything that happens.
Science is just the name for the
steady, pain-in-the-ass effort
that goes into finding
out what they are.
[TAIJU yells]
[screams]
[SENKU sighs]
I've been experimenting
for a year now.
It actually didn't take
as long as I'd imagined.
Heh. Slow and steady
wins the race.
I'm gonna beat fantasy with
science as my only weapon.
[SENKU]
Oh, yeah. Get excited.