[SENKU] When I first became
interested in science,
I read a biography
about Thomas Edison.
[SENKU] What the heck is
electricity, anyway?
[SENKU] Wow, so there are
only four fundamental forces
in the universe?
Gravitational...
Five plus three, equals...
[SENKU] ...and then "strong
force" and "weak force."
[SENKU chuckles]
That sounds ridiculously weird.
[SENKU]
So in the entire universe,
electricity is like,
the most essential power.
That gets me excited!
[SENKU] I was reborn
into a primitive world,
butt naked and completely alone.
But a year and four months
into my scientific journey...
[SENKU] ...I've reached the
essential power: Electricity.
[SENKU] I gotta say,
I'm off to a damn good start.
[GEN] Man, electricity
in the stone age!
It's hard to believe.
[GEN]
Right, Tsukasa?
[KOHAKU]
So you see, Suika,
the long-haired man, Tsukasa,
is the one who was
behind Senku's murder.
[SENKU chuckles]
Even though I'm still alive.
That guy's seriously bad news.
He wanted to stop
scientific progress,
and that's why he killed
Senku without hesitation.
Even though I'm still alive.
So if this Tsukasa is some
kinda violent bad guy,
and Gen has been
working with him,
that means Gen's a bad guy, too!
But isn't Gen also the person
who saved us from Magma?
Then he's a good guy!
[SENKU chuckles]
He's honestly not a good
guy or a bad guy.
He's nothing but a rat who's
only in it for himself.
It actually doesn't matter
to me if he's good or bad.
At the end of the day,
we need him to be an ally
of the Kingdom of Science.
We'll have him give a
bogus report to Tsukasa,
saying "Senku is
definitely dead."
That's the only possible hope
we have of winning this.
[CHROME]
Listen up, Gen!
I know you saw the
electricity! The light!
That's what badass science
at work looks like!
So why care about who wins?
Why even give a crap
whether Senku or Tsukasa
has the edge?
'Cause the Kingdom of
Science is obviously
the side that's more fun!
Oh, is that so? You are
the passionate type.
Too bad for you, I don't
really care about that.
I'm probably the most
superficial man on Earth.
All I consider is what's
beneficial to me.
[GEN]
Uh. Uhh...
What is this, some
kind of prank?
I'll have to have a word
with my manager.
They should understand
that I'm a mentalist.
Doing a show where I'm
the target of a prankster
goes against my image.
Welcome to the year 5739 A.D.
Though the year has changed,
you're still only 19.
Say what?
Hold on.
You were on the special
about psychological magic.
We did that gig together.
[GEN]
I believe you were called
the "strongest primate
high-schooler."
Shishio Tsukasa!
I've made a choice.
You and all of these statues
are among the people
who I believe should
be revived first.
I've gathered all of
you into one place.
[gasps]
Those dusty old fossils
who used to be in power
are even less necessary in
this natural world of stone.
But I see a massive amount
of potential in you, Gen.
[TSUKASA] There's something
I need you for,
and your skills as a mentalist
will be invaluable.
Follow them for me, and
get inside of their minds.
Perhaps I'm being
overly cautious,
but I want you to track
down this man Senku
and tell me if he's dead
or hiding out somewhere.
[GEN]
Who is Senku?
[TSUKASA] He was the
first of us to revive.
He used his knowledge of science
to create a formula to
undo the petrification.
That's how he revived me.
This man--his only desire
is to revive everyone,
no matter who they were.
He'll bring back the same
people who ruined our world,
and they'll make weapons.
He was the most
intelligent man alive,
and that's why I
killed him myself.
[gasps]
Who are...?
[GEN]
Why?
[KOHAKU]
What was that noise?
[BOTH gasp]
Holy crap, what
happened here?
Damn it. Looks like
he died instantly.
This is horrible!
Hang on a second!
[SENKU] He protected himself
with fake blood bags.
He's got these things
all over his body!
This is really freakin' bad!
I bet he did this
before he even came to
the village, just in case.
Tch. That's pretty
impressive, Gen.
You really are a magician
to your core.
Not to mention a showman.
[KOHAKU] Those bags may have
helped block the spear,
but he's still really beat up.
Damn it. We gotta
catch whoever did this.
First, we need to find out
who'd do such an awful thing.
[SENKU]
Huh?
[SUIKA]
I'm gonna investigate!
[SUIKA] Big news, guys!
I found out something huge!
Excellent work,
Great Detective Suika.
Do you mind tellin'
us what it is?
I figured out who
attacked Gen last night!
I know who killed him!
[KOHAKU]
Uh, you know, he's not dead.
[SENKU]
Well, so who was it?
[SUIKA]
It was...!
[laughing]
Now that I've killed
that sorcerer,
I'm the most powerful one!
Everyone should fear Magma!
I thought he'd put up
more of a fight,
but that was as easy as
taking a toy from a baby!
Oh, yeah! I bet it
was easy for you!
[MAGMA] Would've been better
to go on and kill Kohaku, too.
But that woman never seems
to let her guard down.
Well, I think that she's way
too strong to be a normal woman.
The only explanation has to
be some kinda sorcery.
[MAGMA laughs]
[MAGMA] But now that I've gotten
rid of her powerful ally,
she's just like every
other little girl.
[chuckles]
Though if she begs
me to spare her,
I wouldn't mind letting
her join her sister,
and both of them
can be my women.
[MANTLE] I don't know
who would be luckier.
You having both sisters,
or them having the great Magma!
[MAGMA, MANTLE laughing]
[SUIKA]
This is really bad news!
[MAGMA, MANTLE laughing]
It was Magma? That bastard!
I see.
When Magma came over here,
Gen made those flowers
vanish right before his eyes.
I imagine from his perspective,
Gen has to be the mysterious
foreign sorcerer
that I had tried to bring
into the village.
So Magma tried to murder Gen
because he mistook
him for Senku?
Heh.
What's more offensive
is Magma has the nerve
to go around saying that my
strength comes from sorcery!
Well, I always thought
you had the strength
of a gorilla because
you were one.
[CHROME]
Sorry, ma'am.
Got a question for ya, Kohaku.
Why would Magma be looking
for an opportunity to kill you?
It's probably because--
no, it's definitely
because of the Grand Bout.
Once every generation,
the village holds a big
martial arts battle.
It's a tradition called
the Grand Bout.
[SENKU] So that explains
the thing on the far island
that looks like an arena.
[KOHAKU] The last one
was several months ago,
on the day that my sister,
the village priestess Ruri,
came of age.
[KOHAKU]
Whoever won the Grand Bout
was supposed to marry her and
become the next village chief.
That's how my father became
the current village chief.
[MAGMA chuckles, yells]
[HAGANE groans]
[JASPER]
The winner is Magma!
Moving on to the final round.
Damn, man. Magma's an
unstoppable force of nature!
Oh, yeah!
[RURI coughing]
Ruri!
Hey, Ruri! Are you okay?
[TURQUOISE]
Stop right there!
You know you can't just casually
walk up to the priestess!
[CHROME gasps]
Ruri? Bet she's got one
more year, at most.
I don't want that
kinda hassle.
If she just went
ahead and croaked,
I could take over as chief
without having to deal with her.
I could make it look
like she drowned.
Everyone would
think her sickness
drove her to throw
herself off a cliff.
[yells]
[gasps]
Have mercy on me!
The winner of the
Grand Bout is Kohaku!
Magma, I cannot allow
you to marry Ruri!
A man like you doesn't even
deserve to be in her presence!
[MAGMA]
I get it now.
Kohaku joined the Grand
Bout just to get in my way!
Does anybody know what's
gonna happen now?
I mean, the rules do say
that whoever wins
is supposed to marry Ruri.
[GINRO gasps]
I guess that means
Ruri and Kohaku
will just have to marry
each other then!
That's super forbidden love!
[TURQUOISE]
Obviously not!
My word. What should we do now?
Who's going to marry
Priestess Ruri?
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU]
Hilarious.
I bet your old man disavowed
you after that little stunt.
Well, let's just say
that was the final straw
that broke his patience.
Kohaku's given the chief
a lotta headaches.
She's been that way
her whole life.
[KOHAKU]
Of course, the Grand Bout
ended up getting rescheduled.
There'll be another
one next month.
[CHROME] Are you saying the
real reason Magma killed Gen
is so he can win the Grand Bout?
[SUIKA] What?! Gen really
is dead? That's horrible!
[KOHAKU]
No, he's still alive.
Oh, man, it would be bad news
if Magma became the new chief.
[SENKU]
Yeah.
With a guy like Magma
in that position,
getting the medicine to
Ruri will prove to be
even more difficult
than it already is.
Heh. I see it as an opportunity.
If a man from the Kingdom of
Science were to beat Magma
and win the Grand Bout,
they'd marry Ruri and
become the chief.
That would fix everything.
It would mean more people
in the Kingdom of Science,
and make it easy to get
the medicine to Ruri.
Listen up, guys, I have an
important question for you.
What do you think about Ruri?
Do either one of you
want her to be your wife?
[KINRO, GINRO gasp]
Uh. I've never really
thought about it before.
Would I marry her?
I mean, Ruri is super pretty.
Kinda looks like
you, but better.
First off, she's way got
way bigger, I mean--
She's just so graceful and
cute, with big, round eyes!
There's more to a woman
than how she looks.
Is her appearance really
all you care about?
I had no idea you were
so shallow, Ginro.
Hey, you heard me.
I said... she had a bigger
amount of grace about her.
I have a very simple answer.
Guards don't have discussions.
The rules are the rules.
But listening to one
murmur to themselves
is not against the rules.
I've seen it myself. Senku's
definitely not an evil person.
[KINRO]
So do what you normally do.
Skip the details and
tell us what you want.
The only thing I want is
to save my sister's life.
[KINRO]
All right.
[GINRO] You don't have
to explain any further.
I understand.
Nope! Your attacks are
all way too shallow!
[KINRO screams]
[GINRO]
I think it's time for a break!
[KINRO]
Come on!
Let's get through three
more rounds, first!
Hold up.
[KOHAKU]
Hey, Chrome.
If you wanna know the truth,
I'd rather be training you.
But Kinro and Ginro
are the only ones
who really have a chance
of taking down Magma.
I'm sorry.
Yo, Chrome, the only reason
she's apologizing is because
the plan means that one of
those guys would marry Ruri,
even though we all know
you're in love with her!
Did you have to say that?
You're blunt,
but that was brutal.
[CHROME]
This place is amazing!
[RURI coughing]
[CHROME]
Hey, Ruri!
I'm okay.
You've always got a
little cough, don't you?
[RURI] Chrome, they told me
I'm never gonna get better.
[gasps]
[RURI] I'm not gonna live
to become an adult.
I can figure out
how to cure you!
I'll gather everything
I can find. I promise!
I know I'll make you
feel better someday.
Yeah. I'm totally
cool with that.
[CHROME] If we can create
something with science
that lets her live
a long, happy life,
that sounds good to me!
Because above all else, I'm
a genius scientist, aren't I?
[chuckles]
So you're finally
changing job titles
from sorcerer to scientist, huh?
[CHROME]
Yup! I'm not a sorcerer anymore!
Then let's leave the Grand
Bout stuff to the battle team,
while you and I,
on the science team,
get to work on the sulfa drug.
Hell yeah!
I'm planning on participating
in the Grand Bout.
The two brothers and I will be
the Kingdom of Science team.
We'll do whatever it takes
to keep Magma form winning.
Sounds good.
Is he all right?
He looks way worse.
I think he'll be fine,
but his recovery's gonna
take longer than we thought.
And that means...
Yeah.
It won't be long before Tsukasa
comes around lookin' for me,
and then kills me for real.
[inaudbile]
[GINRO]
I'm still sleepy.
Well, it's time to wake up.
We agreed to do training
in the morning
until we rotate on guard duty.
[CHROME]
This is bad!
Gen's not here!
He vanished somehow!
Yeah, well. It's obvious where
he went. Back to Tsukasa.
But why? Why sneak
out like that?
I bet that rat's gonna snitch.
He's gonna go and tell Tsukasa
that Senku is still alive!
Not good, Senku. We have
to try and stop him!
[gasps]
Wait, Tsukasa! It's me!
[GEN] I found a village.
Full of primitives.
[GEN]
They attacked me,
and I ended up getting a little
banged up in the process.
But I did manage to
find out about Senku.
We have to catch that
bastard, right now!
[SENKU]
No, stop!
What are you doing, Senku?
If we don't catch him,
it's game over for you!
I'm just saying, I think we
can let him be for now.
Look at it this way.
If Gen really didn't
have a millimeter
of interest in science,
he never would've cooperated
in the first place.
He made up his mind about
what side he was on
the moment I made electricity.
That's what got him.
But he's still a completely
superficial man to his core.
So he ran away
to give us a show.
[groans] You men.
Such a pain in the ass.
No matter what era.
[GEN] Ah. This ramen is
making me wickedly thirsty.
A cola would be great.
[GEN] Even in this Stone World
could you make one for me?
Just one cola?
Yeah. For sure. Nobody else can.
[GEN]
Senku... was gone.
No trace of him anywhere.
There's no doubt.
He's definitely not alive.
Whoa! So Gen's gonna join
the Kingdom of Science?
Yeah.
He'll come back before too long
and act like nothin' happened.
Heh.
Well, I guess that
was our first battle
against the Tsukasa Empire.
In the fight over Asagiri Gen,
the Kingdom of Science
claims victory!
[SUIKA] Gen turned out to
be a good guy after all!
[CHROME]
Yeah!
[SENKU] It's the world's
most flimsy alliance.
Bound by a single
bottle of cola.
[GEN] Man, this isn't
worth all the trouble.
For just one bottle of cola?
I hope it's ice cold. That's
the very least he could do.
Tch. So my next step is to
use my knowledge of science
to make him an ice cold cola.
And I would love
to have it ready
by the time he makes it back.