So what I heard is
Tsukasa's been looking
for him the whole time.
Yeah? Seriously?
So who is this guy?
[TSUKASA]
Welcome, Hyoga.
You're now 3,700 years
into the future.
In this brand new world,
your skills are needed.
And you will shine.
[GOZAN laughing]
I was thinkin' he was
gonna bring back
a real badass fighter,
but this guy looks like
a little toothpick!
Yeah, how's this shrimpy
dude gonna help us anyway?
[GOONS laughing]
Fight him and you'll understand.
Why don't you go ahead and spar?
Ha-ha. Are you sure?
We might end up killin' him.
I feel kinda bad for
the wittle guy.
He may still be sleepy
after his long nap!
[GOONS laughing]
[HYOGA]
I don't mind.
Oh, yeah?
[HYOGA] If I'm allowed to
use my preferred weapon,
I'll gladly take on
ten men by myself.
Huh.
[laughing]
Well, it's too late for
you to back out now!
[chuckles]
[GEN]
My, what impressive ills-skay.
[TSUKASA]
Heh. I apologize.
Seems there weren't enough men
for a proper warm-up
spar after your rest.
[HYOGA] It's not really
a matter of numbers.
The only proper fighter
here, by which I mean,
the only one I wouldn't
want to fight... is you.
You're the "strongest
primate high schooler,"
Shishio Tsukasa, after all.
I'm glad you've joined us.
Let me show you
around our new world.
As you see, nature's
bounty is generous.
We want for nothing.
The world was
like this for ages.
Well before human civilization.
It belonged to no one.
[TSUKASA] However, from the
moment you and I were born,
the old world hammered
a message into our heads.
"This world is not yours,
because there's not a single
square centimeter of land on it
that isn't already the property
of some rich old fool."
[MINAMI]
Yeah, it's true.
I worked myself ragged,
day in and day out,
only to give up most of my
money to someone else as rent.
Looking back on it,
that's just slavery.
The privileged elders
were ruthlessly exploiting
the impoverished young.
The old world worked by theft
and rampant corruption.
I'm a lot happier now
in this new world.
[chuckles]
Although part of that
is due to I was already
a super fan of Mr. Strongest
Primate, Tsukasa.
[EOM A]
Yo, we caught a big 'ol sucker!
[MINAMI laughs]
Check it out. Whaddaya
think about this?
[TSUKASA]
Oh. Excellent work.
I'm just happy we
were finally able...
[GEN]
Well, even in the old world,
Tsukasa was an extremely
charismatic fellow.
[TSUKASA]
I appreciate it.
[GEN] Take someone strong,
handsome, and soft-spoken,
give him a half-decent argument,
and it'll be prove awfully
difficult to talk anyone
into turning their back on him.
[TSUKASA] Hyoga, the way things
were 3,7000 years ago,
would you call that a utopia?
[HYOGA]
No.
[TSUKASA] Suppose those
in the privileged class
of the old world
were revived today.
And they obtained the
weapons of science
that make killing so easy.
What would happen?
[HYOGA] I imagine they'd
try to use those weapons
to recreate the pyramid
of wealth and influence
they once stood upon.
No one who has drank
of that sweet nectar
could be compelled
to abandon it.
Regardless, this world
has been reset.
It's in no condition to
support seven billion lives.
So there must be a culling.
[GEN] The two deadliest
warriors alive today,
and they're in total
agreement with each other.
[TSUKASA] Then it is up to the
young to create a new world
in harmony with nature.
The world of the past
must stay in the past.
There was... well, I'm hesitant
to call him a friend.
But there was a man named Senku
who had a superhuman
grasp of science.
He sought to revive
the old world.
Therefore... I had to kill
him with my own hands.
With no Senku, there
will be no science.
The corrupt human race
will be purified
and march together
into a new world.
[TSUKASA]
To accomplish that goal,
I'll stain my hands as
much as necessary.
What? You see that?
They cut right
through his spear!
Ah, damn it! We gotta run!
Oh, yeah!
[HYOGA]
Remarkable athleticism,
combined with coordinated
teamwork, and a dirty betrayal.
[GEN chuckles]
[HYOGA] Add to that
thee scientific knowledge
to create guns and
Japanese katanas.
You people seem to know
the proper way to do things.
[HYOGA] What would have
been more proper
was if you had realized
that all of this
was merely a distraction.
[gasps]
Ah. So that's really
why they came here.
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[CHROME]
This is bad! Fire!
[EN screams]
[UNMO]
Run!
[ARGO]
Head for the bridge! Hurry!
[gasps]
Jasper! Turquoise! I don't need
your protection right now!
Save the children!
--[JASPER] Of course!
--[TURQUOISE] Right!
[BOTH gasp]
It burned down.
[TURQUOISE]
Who is that?
[HOMURA]
A hindrance.
Get everyone to safety!
Another one?
[HYOGA] Say hello to
Homura, my right hand.
Unlike those mush-brained
macho men,
she can get things
done properly.
She's quite thorough.
[yells]
Her moves are incredible!
[VILLAGERS crying, muttering]
[KASEKI]
This is horrible.
Once a fire gets to
raging like this,
the wind coming down
off the mountain
will fan the flames out of
control, like a gust of death!
Everyone! We need to evacuate!
Hey, unless you wanna die,
you'd better forget
about the houses!
Get outta here right now!
[CHROME]
We can't go that way, either!
The bridge was burned down.
We have to get to
the science shed!
[GOZAN chuckles]
That was an awesome
move by Homura.
That's what they get for
makin' us look like fools.
[HYOGA] You'd look like
a fool regardless.
We set those fires to force
the villagers out into the open.
That much should be obvious
even to your mushy brain.
Say what?
[HYOGA]
We're dealing with people
so incredibly naive
and sentimental
that they wouldn't even
abandon a village guard.
Why the hell does that matter?
I know!
We're gonna snatch up
one of them little brats
that we smoked outta there
and use 'em as a hostage!
Yeah, that's a great idea!
[laughs]
There's no guarantee
they'll attack head-on.
Keep your eyes and ears
open for anything.
Uh, can we really
protect this many people?
Put all the children up in the
science shed! They'll be safer.
[GINRO]
Yeah! Right!
[GINRO screams]
[SENKU]
Grab water!
Come on now, hurry!
[SENKU] We gotta start dousing
it before it spreads!
It's gonna burn down!
Chrome spent his entire life
collecting those minerals,
and we spent months and months
building the lab together!
If we lose it,
it's all over for us.
The Kingdom of Science--
I've gotta protect it somehow!
[AKASHI]
Huh?
Look!
There's some dumb kid who
didn't get away in time!
[GOZAN] Oh, yeah! We found
ourselves a hostage, boys!
[HYOGA] She's so devoted
that she'd sacrifice herself
to help the others?
I certainly appreciate
her naiveté.
We only need one captive to win,
and this will be far easier
than attacking the home base
of those soldiers of science.
[SUIKA] Gotta run a little,
then hide a little.
Gotta get 'em far away from
the Kingdom of Science!
If I run upwind
towards the mountain,
they won't be able to smoke
me out with more fire!
[AKASHI grunts]
She's runnin' that
way, you guys!
What? Suika ran away?
I, uh, tried to stop her!
But she took off toward
the hot springs!
[KOHAKU]
Wait a sec.
I come here all the time to get
water from these hot springs.
[SENKU]
It gets dangerous up ahead.
The poison gases that form here,
the hydrogen sulfide and sulfur
dioxide, are heavier than air.
A powerful wind's blowing
in from the mountains.
[SENKU] There's something
strange about this wind.
I've got a really bad
feeling about this.
[GOZAN]
Just give up already!
[MORITO] When we catch this
brat, I say we break her legs!
[gasps]
[giggling]
[HOMURA]
This wind brings death.
[screams]
Suika! Climb up that tree!
[SUIKA]
Ah! Wh-What just happened?
[KOHAKU]
You don't need to worry.
The poison gas will
settle below us.
What? "Poison gas"? Uh.
[SENKU] Mother Nature is
neither friend nor foe.
Heh.
She's doesn't care
one way or another.
Hey, ya pipsqueak!
You were the one who made
all this poison gas, huh?
[SENKU]
Huh?
Yeah, damn right it was me!
That was a pretty dumbass move,
launching an attack on
the Kingdom of Science.
You never had a chance
against our modern weapons.
Now then, it's time
to head back.
Just breathe nice and slow,
Suika, you'll be fine.
[SUIKA]
Right! I'll do my best!
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU]
You guys can go back home
and suckle on
Mama Tsukasa's teat.
Of course, you'll have to wait
about ten billion seconds
for the gas to clear outta here.
[GOZAN]
Ugh. He's just screwin' with us.
No way we're waitin' that long!
[AKASHI]
Yeah, I mean it's not like
he could actually make poison
gas in the Stone World, right?
[HYOGA] Good point.
Let's deal with this properly.
We'll need to make sure the gas
is gone before we move.
This is a great opportunity.
You lot can finally perform
a job as you should,
despite your mushy brains.
[GOZAN screams]
[screaming]
[HYOGA] Well, look at that.
They actually died.
So those gas masks were
real, at the very least.
It would appear that
Senku and his allies
have a variety of metals and
chemicals under their control.
The Kingdom of Science
is quite a force.
We can always rebuild
our lost homes!
But our peoples'
lives are precious,
and we didn't lose a single one!
Which means Ishigami Village
has won this battle!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
Hey. I am so proud
of you, Suika.
[SUIKA giggles]
[KASEKI] But that was
pretty dang reckless.
[HYOGA] We'll have to crush
them with sheer numbers.
Tsukasa and I will lead
the charge, of course.
Backed up by the most
massive and powerful army
that our empire can muster.
[chuckles]
[VILLAGERS chattering]
So what's your next move?
You've managed to hide
for quite a while,
but they'll tell
Tsukasa you're alive.
Yeah, and I'm sure
he'll figure out
we can't produce the
gunpowder that quickly.
At least not enough to use guns.
Huh? What do you mean we can't?
Why would that be?
[SENKU]
It's like this.
The revival fluid
that Tsukasa's guys
have been cranking out is
actually pretty easy to make.
And yet, we still haven't
revived a single statue.
That's because we don't
have enough nitric acid.
Now we could make some
from dung or sea shells,
but we're short on both
time and materials.
Also, no nitric acid
means no gunpowder.
Tsukasa's smart enough to
figure that out on his own.
[chuckles]
We didn't have much gunpowder
saved to begin with
and now we're completely out.
You lost me the moment
you started talking about
that whatever-it-was acid.
Isn't there an easier way
to explain it to us?
[SENKU sighs]
Listen, even if we have guns,
he'll know that we
can't really use them.
And I'd say there's about a
ten billion percent chance
Tsukasa's gonna have a huge
army built up for the invasion.
The more time passes,
the more fighters
they have, after all.
Too bad we can't do
that with gunpowder.
[laughs]
Ah!
Well? So what're we gonna do?
Ah. I think it's
fairly obvious.
We'll just have to
attack them first.
With a ridiculously
awesome scientific toy.
[ALL gasp]
Ha! You've got the right idea!
Waiting puts us
at a disadvantage.
So our only choice
is to strike first!
[GINRO whimpering]
And to that end, we gotta start
building our new weapon.
Uh. So what kinda weapon
are you talking about?
[SENKU chuckles]
We've gone leaps and bounds,
but now it's time
for us to break out
the ultimate modern tech!
We've been recreating
scientific advancements
from as far back
as the stone age,
but we're finally getting
to something from my time.
What was truly the deciding
factor in modern conflicts.
The strongest weapon in two
million years of history.
Wait, you don't mean
nukes, do you?
Hell no.
There's something else that can
give one side a huge advantage.
I'm talking about
communications technology.
We're gonna make
cellular phones
with service even
in the Stone World.
[SUIKA]
Huh?
Cell...
...u..?
...lar?
[GEN]
Has he lost his mind?
Because he just said
something really crazy.
[MAGMA]
Huh? Cellular phones?
What're those? Are they fish?
[VILLAGERS chattering]
[VILLAGER B]
They work from a distance?
So you can have a
conversation with someone...
[SUIKA] ...even if
they're super far away?
Definitely sounds
like sorcery to me!
How could an idea that
crazy even possibly exist?
So bad! I've gotta
know how that works!
Me, too!
And that's gonna be our weapon?
Oh, you bet it will.
Communications can completely
turn the tide in a battle.
Look, suppose we
have a double agent
who leaks intel
to us in real time.
It's Gen reportin'.
Senku, the enemy is completely
wide open on the west side.
There's barely any guards
to speak of. Over.
[GEN]
It's Gen reportin'.
Senku, the enemy is completely
wide open on the west side.
There's barely any guards
to speak of. Over.
Now that's some excitin' intel!
We're gonna go nuts
on their western flank!
[SENKU] And if we coordinate
our efforts correctly,
we might take down the Tsukasa
Empire without bloodshed.
But who would we use
to be our double agent?
Ah?
We've already got our
mole over there.
[BOTH laugh]
[SENKU]
Two of 'em in fact.
Taiju and Yuzuriha.
[TAIJU]
Smartphones!
[SENKU]
Oh, sure, yeah.
Smartphones would be
great, wouldn't they?
[TAIJU]
Smartphones?
[SENKU]
You do love your smartphones.
[chuckles]
That big oaf was desperate to
get his hands on a smartphone
from the very beginning.
Now, he's finally
gonna get his wish.
[SENKU] Granted, this'll be
more like a regular phone,
not necessarily the smart kind.
[laughs]
We can do this!
That sulfa drug was a
hell of a lotta work,
but we made that
happen, didn't we?
No offense, guys,
but I don't think you
realize what he's saying.
This road map's full of things
that are impossible to get.
[SENKU chuckles]
Nothing is impossible, Gen.
No matter how far off
the goal may seem,
if you follow the steps,
you'll get there ten billion
percent of the time.
That's how science works.
[HYOGA] Every single one
of Gen's reports was a lie.
The village already has
considerable scientific power.
[HYOGA]
And what's more, Senku is alive.
[gasps]
[chuckles]