I think it's best if I
leave the village for now.
I'm an outsider, and I'm
not competing, so...
I bet our Kinro would
throw a fit if I didn't.
[KINRO, KASEKI grunt]
[GEN] I came here to have a
little chat with you, Senku,
but I'll be patient.
We can discuss your
end of the deal
after you've taken
over the village.
Sure.
[RURI
Oh, Chrome.
[GINRO]
Ruri--Priestess, I mean.
You're gonna have to
marry the winner, right?
Well, don't worry.
It's down to us three.
And Senku and I are just
gonna throw our matches.
So Chrome's already won.
Don't act so surprised.
It's pretty obvious.
I can tell that you've
been rooting for him.
Nice job figuring
out the difference
between convex
and concave, Chrome.
[RURI]
No.
As the priestess, I am
but a servant of the gods.
I cannot favor anyone.
I will simply marry
whoever wins.
Huh? Seriously?
That's weird, I coulda
sworn you-- Whoa, hang on!
Are you saying you don't
care who wins at all?
[RURI]
Uh! Well, um. Yes?
[JASPER] Learn to read between
the lines a little, Ginro.
What else is she supposed to say
when you flat out
ask her like that?
[GINRO]
Village chief Ginro!
[laughs]
[JASPER] We'll now begin match
two of the semi-finals.
Senku versus Ginro.
Contestants, come forward.
[yells]
[SENKU gasps]
What the hell has gotten
into you, Ginro?
Whaddya mean?
You heard the girl!
Ruri said she'd marry anyone!
That means even I could
be the village chief!
My time has come!
It's the era of Ginro!
No! You've gotta be kidding me!
What a scumbag!
[GINRO]
If I win and become the chief,
we'll all get to eat
ramen every single day!
And everyone gets a harem!
Just you wait,
I'm gonna turn this place
into the village of
all of our dreams!
[GIRLS groan]
[GINRO yells]
[GARNET]
Ugh. Please not him.
[TITAN]
Ginro... anyone but you, man.
[VILLAGERS] We can't let him
become the village chief.
We have to take him
down as soon as possible.
But how is Senku
supposed to do that?
[GINRO laughing]
Senku...
Our weapon is science,
so get in there and use it!
[BOTH gasp]
I guess I don't have
any other options.
Uh! You're gonna try to use
some crazy sorcery now?
Well, not if I get you first!
--[SENKU yells]
--[GINRO wheezes]
[RURI]
Ahh...
[KOKUYO]
He's clever, that one.
Senku, was it?
The winner is Senku!
[VILLAGER A]
Ginro's down!
[VILLAGER B] That means
Senku's going to the finals!
They're united in relief
that Ginro didn't win!
Yeah.
And now we can turn this village
into a Kingdom of Science.
And we... can save Ruri...
All right, it's the last round.
So now all that's left for me
to do is throw the match.
Then, Chrome, you'll marry Ruri
and become the village chief.
[laughs]
Happily ever after.
This couldn't be more perfect.
Now stop screwin'
around and get u--
Okay. He is completely
conked out.
Maybe the tension was
keeping him awake.
But once Ruri was safe,
it all went away.
Then does that mean...?
What happens?
So... do we get a final round?
[JASPER] The new village chief
and husband of the priestess...
...is the winner of the
Grand Bout, Senku!
[BOTH scream]
[gasps]
Huh?
[JASPER]
So...
[TURQUOISE]
What now?
Well, great. This just got a
hell of a lot more annoying.
So just to be clear,
if I were to marry Ruri,
then this entire village
is mine, is that right?
Then I guess I'll do it.
Ah! They're married now?
This is happening so fast!
Hold it, Senku! Where did
you even come from, huh?
You're an outsider! We can't
let you become our chief!
My, my. If it isn't the former
village chief himself!
To tell you the truth, I don't
have a millimeter of interest
in your lack of approval.
[VILLAGER B] Uhh... Who are
we supposed to side with?
[TURQUOISE]
We side with Kokuyo, obviously!
Do I really have to
spell it out for you?
[GARNET]
But the gods are watching,
and he did technically just win.
[SAPPHIRE]
Not to mention he's married
to the priestess now, too.
Object all you want to,
a win is a win.
So chop, chop!
Bring the winner his booze!
Can you not?
You sound like one
of those old drunkards
who can't get his fill!
[SAGAN]
Hm?
This pot's no good. All of
its turned into vinegar.
[SENKU]
I'll take it! We need that, too!
[RURI coughing]
Not again!
Ruri.
It's not that bad.
[SENKU] Looks like the clock
is seriously ticking now.
Heh.
We literally just finished
the Grand Bout,
but I guess it's
straight back to work.
Let's head back and
finish the sulfa--
[GENBU]
Hang on!
Where do you think you're goin'?
You're the guest of honor.
Yeah, have a drink with us!
To celebrate your marriage,
we're drinkin' the night away!
It's tradition around here!
Yeah? In that case...
[GAN'EN, GENBU, UNMO]
Huh?
...I want a divorce.
[VILLAGERS grunting]
They're divorced now?!
This is happening so fast!
[SENKU laughs]
We've scored a ton of
alcohol and vinegar!
Let's haul ass, citizens of
the Kingdom of Science!
[KASEKI]
Excuse me!
Since when am I a citizen
of the Kingdom of Science?
[KOHAKU] I'm sorry, Ruri!
I'll explain later!
Huh?
[JASPER] That guy's making
a mockery of our ways.
I'm still a little confused,
but I think I may
have just become
the first divorced
priestess ever.
Well? How's that, Chrome?
This is utter bullshit!
Capture that man, right now!
[KINRO]
Senku is no villain.
[KOKUYO]
Hm?
Please let him
explain for himself
what the sorcerers--
I mean, the scientists--
have been working on.
What they bet their lives
on for half a year.
What I've seen them do.
What's this?
The force from the waterfall is
making the bamboo spin around.
Ha-ha! And I nailed it
on my first attempt!
Pretty cool, huh? Are you
charmed by my talents, ladies?
[SENKU]
Impressive.
I usually botch my first few
attempts at building anything.
Thank you. But I wasn't
trying to charm you.
[GEN] So... what does
this allow us to make?
Well, I know it spins,
but what it's for, I dunno.
[SENKU chuckles]
Don't worry, you're
gonna find out tomorrow.
[KASEKI] I'll think I'll keep
an eye on it for a while.
I'd cry if my baby
were destroyed
by a piece of driftwood
or something.
Uh?
Hey, you! Want me to
stand guard by myself?
A weak old man like me?
You've got nothing better
to do. Stay and help!
[GEN] Huh?! I'd really
rather not, gramps.
Uh. Oh. Sure, I'll help you out.
[GEN]
"Weak old man"?
Wake up and smell
the ammonia, buddy.
We're gonna need you on
team science, let's go!
We don't have much time left.
All we have to do is put
everything together
and we're done.
By morning tomorrow,
we'll have it.
The cure-all sulfa drug.
Tomorrow?!
That quickly?!
[SENKU]
Fun with Making Sulfa Drugs.
Step one.
First, we're using a burnable
rock called coal to--
[CHROME]
Burnable rocks?
Got it. I've got plenty
of that stuff!
Uh.
[wheezes]
Yeah, I sorta figured we
must've used it all up
when we made iron.
That's bad!
[SENKU chuckles]
Don't worry about it.
If we need more ordinary
coal like what you had,
we'll just take a quick
trip up to the mountains.
But for now, we don't
even need the coal itself.
We need the coal tar that's
left after it's burned.
Just wash it with
hydrochloric acid,
then throw in ethyl acetate
made from alcohol and vinegar,
and we've got aniline.
Uh. Wait, wait, wait, slow down!
You lost me like
five sentences ago!
If that's all step one,
and we're done by tomorrow,
how many total steps are there?
Like three or four?
[SENKU]
Hmm... Oh, only 25, maybe?
Whoa. That's bad.
[inaudible]
I still have absolutely no
idea what this thing is.
Surely it wouldn't hurt to
take a quick peak inside.
[GEN]
Is it...?
Could you make one for me?
Just one cola?
Yeah. For sure.
Nobody else can.
[GEN] Careful now,
don't get your hopes up.
There's no way he's
that nice, right?
[GEN]
Senku!
What's this fizzy water for?
[GEN screams]
Did a bomb go off in here?
There's a lot of
collateral amage-day.
Just what have you
gotten up to this time?
[chuckles]
Nothin' special really.
Only mixin' stuff together.
Poured vinegar on burned shells,
extracted glacial acetic
acid using sulfuric acid,
turned it into ketene
in an iron pipe,
and put it back to make
acetic anhydride.
Uh. Oh. Very interesting.
So I tried to drip that acetic
anhydride into the aniline,
but I poured in way too much...
...and kaboom.
[GEN]
I see. Hence, the wreckage.
Mix the chlorosulfuric acid into
the acetanilide we just made
for para-acetamido-
benzene-sulfonyl chloride.
And then, throw in ammonia
to make para-acetamido-
benzene-sulfonic acid,
cook it in hydrochrolic
acid, 'nd get that.
I'm genuinely impressed you can
say that without stuttering.
Good job.
[SENKU]
Lastly, that carbonated water.
Oh, yes, I meant to ask.
I'm not expecting anything,
but is this for--?
Yeah. What else would it be for?
I have no earthly idea.
Mix it with sodium hydroxide
to make baking soda!
Baking soda. Yes,
right. That's it.
That's definitely
what I was thinking.
[SENKU]
Step 25, we wash this stuff
with our newly
acquired baking soda.
And then we sit back and wait.
This is it.
[CHROME] It took a long,
bad half-year.
It's sulfanilamide.
Or you could say...
the fruits of our labor.
The cure-all sulfa drug.
Yeah!
Yay!
[GINRO]
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
We finally have it.
And now Ruri will...
Hey. Don't start with
all your crying already.
Save it for when
she's actually better.
Who's crying? Not me!
[GEN] Unfortunately, I remain
barred from the village,
so I won't be able to come
and see Ruri take her medicine.
[SENKU chuckles]
Enjoy the solitude of
waiting back at the lab.
Gen helped us out so much,
it's a shame he can't come.
I feel bad for him.
[GEN] That's just the way
it is for rats like me.
[gasps]
Mecha Senku here
to spit some facts!
Carbonated water, cilantro,
lime, and honey caramel
are all the ingredients
you need to make cola,
if you can believe it!
You should try tossing some lime
zest onto crushed cilantro.
You'll be shocked at how much
it smells like good ol' cola!
[GEN]
Woo!
Hey. Don't worry, Ruri.
I promise you, this is the
powder of life, born from stone.
It's the cure-all of science!
It'll knock that sickness
right outta you!
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU] A mystery bug
versus the culmination
of two million years of
humanity's scientific endeavors.
[SENKU]
Time to get excited.
[SENKU] All right, I finally
get to see my patient.
Time to make a diagnosis.
Say "eee" loud and clear.
[KOHAKU grunts]
[JASPER groans]
Eeeee...
[SENKU]
Sounds like a bleating goat.
That's evidence that
there's fluid in her lungs.
[GEN]
I'll just come out and ask.
Why do you have that rat?
Maybe we're eating it?
It's incredible that's the first
thing that comes to your mind.
Trust me, rats aren't exactly
a part of my diet.
That's comforting to know.
Usually.
Ah, yes. "Usually." Great.
[SENKU chuckles]
[SENKU] They are a good
source of protein,
but we're not here for a meal.
This is an autopsy.
[SENKU] Red inflammation
all over the lungs.
So it's definitely a
bacterial infection.
And even the rats
are catching it.
We gotta narrow it down more.
[CHROME, KOHAKU]
Huh?
[SENKU] Even our cure-all
has its limits.
It's not ten billion
percent guaranteed
that it'll wipe out this
specific bacteria.
And in the worst case scenario,
if we're up against
tuberculosis,
then frankly, we don't
stand a chance in hell.
[SUIKA] Quick! You guys
gotta come with me!
It's Ruri! She's gotten worse!
Don't get up!
Just stay on your side like this
and try to breathe slowly.
It's never been this bad. Never.
I can't help but fear
the worst here.
She had that white powder,
and now this starts happening?
I knew not to trust them
and their sorcery medicine.
--[CHROME] Ruri, we're here!
--Just hang in there!
Uh, Senku?
Senku, you bastard!
This is all because
of that drug!
Father!
If you didn't give her that,
Ruri wouldn't have taken such
a drastic turn for the worse!
Yeah. You might be right.
[ALL gasp]
So you admit it.
[SENKU] The bacteria is
getting serious now.
It's making allies by
spreading its toxic genes
into all the harmless
bacteria around it.
It's the signature move of
the pneumococcus bacteria.
Which means that Ruri's
disease is... pneumonia.
And that's nothing to laugh at.
It's a deadly disease
with a kill count
in the hundreds of millions.
But... sulfa drugs absolutely
slaughter pneumococcus bacteria.
Which means that we won! With
the power of humanity's science!
Now that we know what it is,
we've got the upper hand.
All that's left is to pump her
full of more sulfa drugs.
Enough of your trickery!
[KOHAKU]
Father!
This is nothing like
the fraudulent sorcery
that you know.
It's science. The culmination
of human wisdom.
And I believe in it.
I trust and believe
in Senku, too.
That's right! So do I!
Not entirely sure why,
but I kind of do, too.
[SENKU chuckles]
I gotta say, it's a miracle
that Ruri managed to live to 18.
But if you stay clean
and keep warm,
the disease's progression
slows significantly.
[SENKU]
Turns out that hot spring water
that Kohaku hauled in every day
ended up helping her sister
a lot more than she knew.
Ruri.
Ruri!
[KOKUYO crying]
[inaudible]
I can't even remember how
many years it's been
since I've left the village
or been able to run!
[KOKUYO, TURQUOISE, JASPER gasp]
I know that rambunctiousness.
It must've actually run
in the family all along.
[KOKUYO]
Everyone!
As of now, this man
known as Senku
is pronounced the new chief
of Ishigami Village!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[SENKU]
Ishigami Village?
[RURI]
That's right Senku.
I know of you. I have
for a long, long time.
Since I was a child.
[RURI] Your full name...
is Ishigami Senku.