[baby laughs]
[cries]
[SWEALLOW] When you're
born with a curse,
it's only natural that
people come to fear you.
Even if those people
are your parents.
But it can't be helped when
everything you touch breaks.
[SWEALLOW] I tried to
pass my time by reading,
but the pages crumbled
as I turned them.
And no one ever bothered
to read to me.
Sometimes I wondered what would
happen if I used someone.
If I treated them like a tool.
[SWEALLOW]
The Clazzvali family
was one of the
richest in D'natia.
But before I knew it, we were
well on our way to ruin.
Hey, Shark.
Don't worry, I'm not
going to touch you.
[SWEALLOW]
It was when I lost my friend
that I finally began
to understand.
Even if I didn't touch
the things I cared about,
they were still gonna break.
[SWEALLOW] That had always
been the reality of my life.
[ULRIKA] I'd heard rumors
about their downfall,
though I never imagined...
But if he succeeds
in his mission,
he won't have to suffer anymore.
You mean because of his contract
with the Black Dragon.
I just hope his bad habit
doesn't come out.
What are you talking about?
[SWEALLOW] The name of this
island is Nil Kamui.
It's currently caught between
the ancient country of Kouran
and our homeland of D'natia
as we struggle for supremacy.
Empire Era 285, September.
[SWEALLOW]
Despite the ongoing conflict,
the great land of Kouran,
and our country of D'natia,
have come together to form
the Red Dragon expedition
along with Nil Kamui's
Revolutionary Army.
Which is where I
find myself now.
If all goes well, I will
be spared my cruel fate.
Come on!
Look at me!
Remember!
[screams]
[MALE RETURNED ONE A growling]
[groaning] I'm sorry.
I failed, my lord.
Don't give up!
You're part of the revolution,
you have to be strong!
[HIEN grunts]
[HIEN]
He's already revived.
For the sake of the
Child of Contract,
I will sacrifice anything
so that he may be king!
[HIEN grunts]
[HIEN]
That is my vow.
Let's see if four strikes will
be enough to make you fall.
Pò Shan!
[QI SHA TIAN LING] Oh, what
sweet nectar this is, Lou!
I've never before savored
such an exquisite soul!
I'm glad. I'd do anything
to please you.
Here goes.
Hear me, Izun! I beseech you!
As an imperial of this land,
I wish to help you!
[KA GRAVA gasps]
Ibuki!
[IBUKI yelps]
[gasps] Are you in there?
This isn't as bad as I thought.
Hey! What are you
all trying to do?
Well, Ibuki.
Sorry, Lord Ibuki,
wants us to buy some time
so he can try and save Izun.
But once a person becomes a
Returned One, it's all over.
There's no coming back.
He's no exception.
So what are you gonna do?
I will give my life to my lord.
It's his only chance
at beating this giant.
I hate to be the
one to tell you,
but there's no way he's
gonna go for that plan.
[LOU]
How pathetic!
I don't even need my
lord's power for this!
Feng Zhan!
[SWEALLOW grunts]
Amazing! I've never
seen such a skill!
[gasps]
[KA GRAVA]
Stand back, Ibuki!
[EYKHA gasps]
[SWEALLOW]
They're just kids.
They aren't ready for this.
It sucks.
But someone needs to be
there to protect them.
At least until it's
their time to break.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Oh, my. What is this?
My lord?
[HYAKKI WARRIORS gasp]
[ULRIKA]
What's happening?
Sir Sweallow has done
what he felt he had to.
[MERYL]
When he was ten years old,
he requested a Mixed One
as his personal servant.
Supposedly, they, along with
Bounded Ones, did not age.
And thus, they wouldn't break.
Or at least that's
what he thought.
[MERYL]
However,
the Mixed One was actually
brought in to be adopted
as a steward's daughter,
rather than just a retainer.
[SWEALLOW panting]
[MERYL]
A few years later,
she was the victim
of a kidnapping.
And was left on
the brink of death.
[BLACK DRAGON]
So that's what it is.
[BLACK DRAGON] I sensed
your peculiar phenomenon
and was drawn here before you.
Do you intend to save
this girl's life?
I have to!
[BLACK DRAGON]
Is that so?
Then I shall aid you by shifting
her wounds onto you.
[SWEALLOW whimpers]
[MERYL] Everything eventually
breaks down and dies.
He knows that, but
can't help himself.
It's such a bad habit.
Go, Val!
Izun!
[yelling]
[QI SHA TIAN LING] I will
take everything you have!
[laughs]
[IZUN grunting]
[LOU gasping]
[QI SHA TIAN LING laughs]
After all that,
it's still full of life!
[LOU] It would appear
that way! Don't worry.
For I will keep
you safe, my lord!
[LOU grunts]
Wait, Lou!
[IZUN yells]
Izun.
I'll free you from this pain
and go to my grave soon after.
If this keeps up, then
Eykha will kill Izun.
She'll be killing her friend.
It isn't right.
No one should have to do that!
[KA GRAVA grunts]
Look out!
Hien!
[KA GRAVA] It appears even he
has become a Returned One.
[HIEN grunts]
Can't be.
Not him!
[HIEN groaning, screams]
I beg you to take my life!
I'm sorry.
I'll grant your wish to be
offered to Red Dragon.
[HIEN grunts]
[gasps]
[HIEN]
Hurry up.
Use the dragon's
flame to end this!
[IBUKI]
Hien!
[KA GRAVA]
He's regained himself?
No, he was never a Returned
One to begin with!
But... Hien.
Your eyes!
What did you do?!
[HIEN] I knew if I
wasn't a Returned One,
you'd never be willing
to sacrifice me,
even though it's your only
hope of getting out of here.
Because your kindness
would cloud your judgment.
[IBUKI gasps]
[HIEN] You have to offer
me to Red Dragon...
before that giant
kills all of you.
Yes. Hear me, Red Dragon.
I've given you my pledge.
Now unleash your
flame to save us!
After all this time.
Through death, you will finally
be giving my life meaning again.
[IBUKI gasping]
Red Dragon! Hurry!
Give me your power!
Red Dragon!
Hien has given his life for you!
What more do you need?!
It's an equivalent!
I need you!
Why aren't you answering?!
[KA GRAVA]
Get ahold of yourself!
We can't stay here much longer!
What's wrong?
Why isn't the Dragon
Eye shining?
Of all times.
[SWEALLOW]
Simple.
His life isn't considered
to be of equal value.
Or at least, that's what I
think his silence means.
So you mean...
You're saying Hien's life
wasn't precious enough to me?
[KA GRAVA]
Wait. Where are you going?
Don't you guys
worry about it.
I'm gonna take
care of everything.
[SWEALLOW]
Talk about a mess.
This isn't how I wanted
things to go down.
I knew Hien couldn't
have been a Returned One.
The Returned Ones haven't moved
since I used the
Black Dragon's Scale.
But there's no way I can
tell them the truth.
That Hien's death,
that all of what's happening
now, is my sin to bear.
[MERYL]
Please don't touch anything.
[SWEALLOW]
C'mon, I just want a cup of tea!
That's a shame.
Seeing as how everything
in this mansion
has been seized by
the Sherbet Company,
I'm afraid that's
strictly forbidden.
You know, I really appreciate
that you're doing all of this.
You're just about the only
person who still supports
the bankrupt Clazzvali Family.
But then you are the creditor.
Not to change the
subject, sir.
But it's about time you
got to your meeting.
[SWEALLOW] Man, are you sure
I have to go to this thing?
[SWEALLOW]
Okay, fine. I'm on my way.
[BLACK DRAGON growls]
[gasps]
[BLACK DRAGON]
So that's what it is.
It would appear you carry a
curse of ruination with you.
[SWEALLOW] That's correct,
Black Dragon. And it's awful.
[BLACK DRAGON] Have you come
to ask me to remove it?
If it's possible, then yes.
As you might imagine,
it's just absurd trying
to live life this way.
The Red Dragon, from Nil Kamui,
has succumbed to madness
and lashed out in violence.
The Seven Dragons
cannot abide this.
The three countries
are launching an
expedition to find him.
You will join in their search,
and kill the red one.
[SWEALLOW]
And once I've done that,
you'll free me from
this stupid existence?
That is correct.
Now, if you agree,
we can use your scar
to seal our contract.
[exhales]
I got this from the last deal
I made, and it saved Meryl.
That's fine by me.
Then congratulations,
Sweallow Clazzvali.
I welcome you to the
Black Dragon Knights.
Okay, contract seal, release!
Herald the Black
Dragon's conquest!
[SWEALLOW] This was supposed
to be my trump card when I
finally came face-to-face
with Red Dragon.
But it's all I can do to
atone for what I've done.
Black Blade's Fury.
[yells]
[BLACK DRAGON]
My contract and your curse
are intertwined
with one another.
And when the unique powers
of humans and dragons
are brought together.
[SWEALLOW yells]
Izun!
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
I am familiar
with that particular
Black Dragon Knight skill.
However, his wielding of
it was rather unique.
It's appalling how
he ruins his swords
with such reckless abandon.
[QI SHA TIAN LING laughs]
It makes me wonder
what he'd do with me.
[LOU] My lord. How can
you even think that?
He wouldn't care what
condition you were left in
when he was done
with you, unlike me.
I will give you
everything that I am.
[EYKHA]
Are you all right?
You look okay.
I failed.
I wasn't able to kill him.
Ibuki?
Hien... is gone.
[KA GRAVA]
It would appear this is in fact
the item my friend left
behind as he implied.
Given our circumstances,
I believe it is a most apt
trophy for Sir Sweallow.
[SWEALLOW]
Mm... Uh.
[KA GRAVA]
According to legend,
dragons can only be
slain by other dragons.
[ULRIKA]
Yes?
Sorry to cut you off,
but something strange is
happening back in Haiga.
[KA GRAVA]
What could be wrong?
[clears throat] U-Uh.
Hello... Shaddy?
Thank goodness, Lord Ka Grava!
D'natia's bishop has come
to the city! It's bad!
[KA GRAVA] Can you send me an
image of the current events?
[SHADDY]
Yes, sir!
[ENUMAEL] Hear me,
citizens of Nil Kamui!
The one standing before you
is this country's true
imperial and heiress!
Your future and rightful king!
Lady Inori!
[gasps] Can't be!
Do you know her?
She's my...
little sister.
[NARRATOR]
Act Eight.
"Perfect Serenity."
Inori's sudden return
releases Ibuki from his fate.
With a life so cruel,
who would ever stand
in the way of that?