[SOLDIER 2A]
The legend is true?
[SOLDIER 2B]
Incredible.
[SOLDIER 2C] A Child of
Contract has finally appeared.
Yes, so we must protect him.
Until he rises to the throne.
We are the army to
restore freedom to Nil Kamui.
Please, use us as you will,
Child of Contract.
Fugaku...
Why did you make me
wear Ryugatou?
If you knew Kouran troops
would be at the market,
then that means...
Trust me, I didn't know
things would end like this.
But still, we needed the heir
to the throne to rise up and--
I don't want to be king,
and now Mashiro's
dead because of you!
No, you're
the one who killed her!
This scumbag's
no Child of Contract!
Ibuki... is just a murderer!
He killed my sister, Mashiro!
[IBUKI gasps]
[IBUKI] We hail from a
country known as Nil Kamui.
It is but a small island nation.
We were invaded by the great
ancient country of Kouran.
And in their avarice, a third
of our land was pillaged.
D'natia, an ally state
to the east,
was quick to defend settlements
where they had established
bases, but nothing more.
And like a sacrificial swine,
Nil Kamui's land was
carved and slowly devoured
by the two infiltrating powers.
Despite all of this,
our guardian deity,
the Red Dragon,
did not protect the land.
Imperial Era 3015, September.
When all was said and done,
the country was no longer ours.
[PATRONS cheering, chatting]
I'm not afraid of a Bounded
One like you, you hear?
Back in ancient times,
freaks like you weren't even
allowed to speak with humans!
Were you acquainted
with Mashiro?
Are you saying
that you knew my sister?
No. She wasn't
actually my real sister.
But still I...
You... liked her?
And now she's gone. Why?
[LOU]
My, how marvelous.
My Lord, you have the power
to soothe even the
most fearsome creatures.
[QI SHA TIAN LING] I thought
this island to be nothing
but an insignificant speck.
But it's turned out
to be quite interesting.
[KAI] She was the Child
of Contract's shrine maiden?
That's what I heard.
But wait, that means
Ibuki was at the castle, too.
I don't understand.
Why would he kill Mashiro, then?
Aren't the shrine maidens
supposed to serve the imperials
who came from the line of kings?
Mashiro once told me this.
[MASHIRO] Long ago, Red Dragon
made a solemn promise.
It would lend its blade if
the Child of Contract, the king,
made a suitable offering
to it in return.
Specifically, a bonded soul.
There are a number
of interpretations
as to what that means.
But I think it refers
to one who freely gives
everything to the king.
You exchange the life
of someone precious to you
to save your world from crisis.
[chuckles] What an
ingenious scheme that is.
[KAI] So because
she was a shrine maiden,
Mashiro offered her life
to Ibuki willingly?
Is that it?
[EYKHA] And she was eagerly
awaiting the arrival
of such a day.
But that--
[IBUKI]
That doesn't make it right.
[KAI]
Huh?
Kai, listen.
Red Dragon, he's gone crazy.
He's destroyed villages
all over the island.
[KAI] Are you trying
to say that's the reason
why Mashiro is dead?
[IBUKI]
Kai...
Is that your excuse now,
that you weren't
responsible for killing her
because Red Dragon's
gone insane?
[FUGAKU]
Lord Ibuki.
We must speak.
[FUGAKU] While this country went
without a king, the council,
or should I say,
the provisional government,
along with D'natia
and Kouran, usurped us.
Now is the time to
throw off the shackles
and reclaim our land.
But I'm not sure if
I've really become
a Child of Contract.
[FUGAKU] The abilities
you manifested to defeat
that Kouran commander.
There's no doubt they were
the power of Red Dragon.
We will follow you anywhere,
but we must move
somewhere safer tonight
and do so quickly.
Yes, I agree,
Kouran reinforcements
should be arriving by daybreak.
We must depart immediately.
[SWEALLOW]
Aw, come on now.
I just got here.
[HIEN]
Who are you?
Me? I'm just
a guy from D'natia.
"Just a guy?" Geez.
Hey, wait a minute.
You're that--
[SOLDIER 2A]
D'natia?
[SOLDIER 2B] You've got a lot of
nerve coming here, buddy!
[FUGAKU]
Sir Black Dragon Knight?
Yep, that's who I am,
Sweallow Clazzvali of
the Black Dragon Knights
at your service, friend. Hi.
[MERYL]
And I am Meryl Sherbet.
I am the official attendant
to Sir Sweallow.
The Black Dragon Knights.
They're powerful warriors
who have been imbued
with the power of Black Dragon,
the guardian deity of D'natia.
Out of that nation's force of
three hundred thousand,
it's said there are only thirty.
But it's hard to
believe he's one of them.
You think so? But why?
[MERYL] 'Cause you look
and act like an idiot.
Sheesh!
Why don't you tell me
what you really think, Meryl?
Sir Sweallow,
to what do we owe the
honor of your presence?
[SWEALLOW] Oh no,
the honor is all mine, Ibuki.
You're next in line
for this country's throne.
By the request of
Nil Kamui's council,
we would like to
bring you on as a member
of the Red Dragon expedition.
At least that's what I heard.
Yours truly was selected to be
a member of the expedition, too.
There's an expedition...
to find Red Dragon?
[SIMEON] I can't believe
you summoned me at this hour.
[KRAMA]
Forgive me, sir. I apologize.
However, I'm not
taking any chances
by letting this one out of here.
Welcome to my humble,
and I might add, filthy home.
[SETSUREN] It looks like
the current rulers
of Nil Kamui are here.
[SIMEON]
As are you, I see.
[KRAMA]
Agito,
Kouran's forces were attacked
by the revolutionary army.
[AGITO]
Ah yes, in town, correct?
Are you the one
who gave the orders?
Listen. The rumor
of Red Dragon going mad...
We have to confirm it.
Provoking a skirmish between
forces will cause confusion.
Have you forgotten
about our deal?
You know... Kouran. D'natia.
And the rebel army.
"Revolutionary" army.
[SETSUREN] The three powers
will send their elite
to form the expedition
for Red Dragon.
That was our agreement.
[AGITO] That's right,
but in order to bring Ibuki
onboard the expedition,
he required a little bit
of prodding first,
you understand?
[KRAMA] And to do that
you knowingly sacrificed
both Kouran and rebel forces?
It's okay.
We'll just treat this
as an isolated
and unfortunate accident.
But still, I won't let you
do such a thing again
until after the
expedition finds Red Dragon.
Are we clear?
[KOHKAKU]
"An unfortunate accident?"
I couldn't care less about
the combined expedition!
Need I remind you that
the rebel army attacked us?!
Why haven't you sent
us any reinforcements?!
Return at once.
I refuse to follow
such an order!
I am not returning until
I've reclaimed the Dragon Eye!
Hmph!
My Lady Kohkaku...
[KOHKAKU] Are you certain
that this Child of Contract
was the one who killed
Commander Kohretsu?
[MALE SHOP OWNER 1A]
Yes, and everyone is saying
it was by the power
of Red Dragon.
Though he's of royal lineage,
you say he lived
at an orphanage?
[MALE SHOP OWNER 1A]
He did, my lady.
He bought food from our stall
at the market several times.
I thank you for
this information.
Now that we've
given you what you want,
will you please
return our son to us?
[KOHKAKU]
Oh, right, him.
Yes, that handsome-looking boy
was your son, wasn't he?
I'm sorry, but you're too late.
[BOTH gasp]
You see, there's a
special Kouran spell
that allows one to
burn life onto a seal.
I used it to make your
son's life a part of me,
and now thanks to him,
I'm protected from harm.
[BOTH gasp]
[CHILD 2A]
Mom...!
So you see,
we need to find Red Dragon,
and with your new power
you could really
help us out, Ibuki,
so what do you say, are you in?
[SWEALLOW gasps]
[FUGAKU]
I say D'natia and Kouran,
two forces in conflict
over our conquered land,
forming an expedition out of
goodwill, is hard to believe.
[MERYL] Besides us, we've
heard there's a participant
from the
revolutionary army, too.
Well, that's news to me.
And if Kouran has a
representative, where are they?
Well, we're supposed to
meet them somewhere in town,
we just haven't
run into them yet.
They should be carrying
something like this.
Hey. Come on.
Put your sword down.
We're not from Kohran.
D'natia and Nil Kamui
have always been allies.
We're all long-term friends.
Right?
It seems you've
forgotten one small thing,
so make sure this gets through
that thick skull of yours, okay?
D'natia was indeed allied with
this island's royal family,
but when Kouran's forces
invaded Nil Kamui,
our country only
defended those towns
where our military bases
were stationed.
Oh, so then what
happened to the king?
He was assassinated
during the turmoil with Kouran
during the Seven Year War,
and after that,
Nil Kamui accepted a treaty
which signified
complete surrender.
[SWEALLOW]
Man...
That was a pretty
crappy move on our part.
Excuse me...
But listen. I, um...
[MALE SUBORDINATE 2A]
Everyone!
Kouran forces are
laying siege to the town!
[FUGAKU] So their
reinforcements have arrived.
[MALE SUBORDINATE 2A] No, it's
the remnant force from earlier!
[HIEN]
If that's all there is,
we can handle them on our own!
Who's with me?
--[SOLDIERS yelling]
--[IBUKI] Please, wait!
There are children in
the town who could get hurt!
It's pointless
to try and stop you.
Yeah, but I do have to say
it's sweet how well
you know me, Meryl.
[KAI]
Mashiro.
I said some
horrible things to Ibuki.
But now I...
[explosion]
--[ORPHANS screaming]
--[KOHKAKU laughing]
Hey, "Child of Contract,"
in case these flames
don't get your attention...
I bet the screams of these
pathetic little brats will!
[KAI gasps]
That way won't help them.
Hey, let me go!
I don't know you!
Do you know Ibuki?
[KAI]
Huh?
[LOU]
You know...
I hear he's able to
take the soul of someone
who's precious to him
and alter it into a weapon.
Perhaps that is the best way
you can save
those in danger.
Ibuki can use
my soul to help?
Hold nothing back
and go all out!
Now open the gates!
[SWEALLOW] No, if you do that,
a lot of you will die.
[FUGAKU] You have a plan,
Sir Dragon Knight?
[SWEALLOW]
Sure do.
It's the only way I can
think of to gain your trust.
And also... I don't want
to see any kids get killed.
Ain't that right, Meryl?
Is this a joke?
Only one rebel
against all of us?
[SOLDIER 2B]
I'm not sure he's a rebel.
I bet he can die like one!
[SWEALLOW]
Oh, well.
[yelling]
[SWEALLOW] My debt to Meryl just
keeps getting bigger and bigger.
That power! How did he do that?
[SOLDIER 2D]
Who cares? Charge!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Guess it can't be helped.
Tell me...
How does that happen?
Any instrument he
wields will fall apart.
That's his curse.
He was born with it.
[MERYL]
But the moment it does so,
that instrument is capable
of exerting all of its power.
[MERYL]
Now then...
I wonder how much all these
lost weapons are going to cost?
Wait, that explosion...
That's near the...!
[EYKHA]
Where are you going?
Fugaku asked you to stay here.
Your name is Eykha, right?
I beg you.
Beg me?
You're saying that
to a Bounded One?
Yes, I am.
Will you please let me
ride on your friend's back?
'Course you can.
[IBUKI] I knew it!
Is everyone still inside?
I'll distract her so you
can go and search for them.
[VAL growls]
[IBUKI]
Hey, guys!
Is anyone here?
--Ibuki!
--Please help us!
[IBUKI]
Thank goodness!
It'll be okay!
You're brave to
come back to save them.
No.
You're the one who's brave by
protecting them like this, Kai.
Thank you.
Yes! Bite it to pieces! Go!
I hold more than
one life, you wretch!
[ORPHANS screaming]
Eykha!
[KOHKAKU laughing]
Oh, no!
At this rate,
we'll all be killed!
We've gotta defeat her somehow.
[IBUKI]
I'll have to use that power.
Answer me! Red Dragon!
Ah, imperial.
So you once again desire
the flames that I possess?
[IBUKI] Since the pledge was
already enacted, yes!
I have paid your price.
Someone... who was
very precious to me!
[RED DRAGON]
Indeed.
Then summon forth your fire
and strike down my enemy!
[RED DRAGON]
If that is what you desire,
then you must offer me
an equivalent tribute.
[IBUKI]
Wait, but I already did that.
You don't mean...
[RED DRAGON]
One pledge, one life.
That is the cost of each
contract between us, imperial.
One pledge, one life?
Someone else has to die?
I won't let them!
Ibuki.
This time, it's my turn.
Kai, what are you saying?
Red Dragon's
tribute is the soul
of someone you're bonded to.
Friendship's a bond,
and you and I are friends,
so I could...
You want...?
Just kill me, Ibuki.
Like you did to Mashiro!
It's the only way you
can stop that monster!
Please, Kai, don't do this!
I won't let you!
I wasn't able to save Mashiro!
No one else dies for me!
You're a king, right?
Or at least you will be one day!
But your subjects there'll
die if you don't kill me!
I can't Kai. I won't.
Am I not good enough?
Will it not work because
we're not friends anymore?
No, Kai.
You are my friend.
[yells]
Ibuki!
[KOHKAKU] I can't believe
a cute little boy like you
is capable of
such terrifying power.
Now where is the Dragon Eye?
Found it!
Out of my way, runt!
No, Kai! Not you!
[RED DRAGON]
The pledge has been fulfilled.
But I didn't...!
Red Dragon! I wasn't
the one who killed Kai!
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
The Child of Contract was unable
to defend his friend.
In a sense, he abandoned him,
and that is akin to murder.
[LOU chuckles]
That's the reasoning
of a dragon, I guess.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Plus a soul that's willing
to lay down its life
is twice as sweet.
[LOU]
Indeed, my lord.
Oh, thank goodness.
[IBUKI]
Kai!
[KAI]
Red Dragon acknowledged it.
I am still a
precious friend to you.
I said a lot of
horrible things to you.
Sorry. I was just jealous
of you and Sis Mashiro.
[RED DRAGON] You may now
do as you desire, imperial.
[IBUKI]
I couldn't protect Kai.
That's the same thing
as killing him.
That's what you're telling me.
Isn't it, Red Dragon?
So somehow you've
fused with the Dragon Eye?
Steel Form, release!
I'll rip the Dragon Eye
and your heart out, boy!
Now...
I'm going to make you regret
that you were ever born!
[IBUKI, RED DRAGON] By the
oath between the Red Dragon
and the Child of Contract...
[IBUKI, RED DRAGON]
Perish!
[KOHKAKU screaming]
[SWEALLOW]
You're sure about this?
[IBUKI] Yes. I will
join your expedition.
I don't really
have another option.
If I stay here, I'll just
lose more people I care about.
[MERYL]
Huh?
[IBUKI]
Therefore...
I have to meet Red Dragon.
And when I do,
I'm going to return this power.
No, it's not a power,
but a curse!
[SWEALLOW]
Got it. Let's go then.
[IBUKI] Fugaku.
Take care of the children, okay?
[FUGAKU]
Ibuki!
[screaming noise]
Hold on, are you...?
Kouran's representative.
She must be.
[LOU] It's a pleasure
to meet you, Ibuki.
You know...
I'm hoping that we'll
become the best of friends.
[NARRATOR]
Act Three.
"Three as One."
The motive behind the
three countries seeking
to find Red Dragon
shrouds Ibuki's life
in both darkness and danger.
And now, the final player
takes a seat at the table.