[SOL]
Yes, that's correct, sir.
You were right.
I just verified it.
Judging by the armor
and body stature,
there's no doubt.
[KA GRAVA] It looks as though
we've been able to confirm
the body of whom we believe
to be Lady Ulrika.
[SIMEON]
"Believe to be"?
[KA GRAVA] Hm... Unfortunately,
the head remains missing.
There are few on this island
who possess the strength
to take down someone
like Lady Ulrika.
Yes, very few. It was likely
the work of Lou Chun Wah.
So, you finally admit it!
All of this deception
was Kouran's doing!
Look, I already told you. Lou
was acting on her own accord.
A likely story!
I swear, on my honor, as one
of the Six Greats of Kouran.
I am no liar!
[KA GRAVA] The combined
expedition is finished.
It's been disbanded.
[KA GRAVA ] In truth,
both D'natia and Kouran
sought for the extermination
of Red Dragon.
While the revolutionary
army prepared an alliance
with D'natia under
the veil of secrecy.
[KA GRAVA]
Nonetheless, Lady Ulrika
believed in the ideals
of the expedition.
[KA GRAVA] She believed
that Kouran and D'natia
would join hands
and work together
to save Nil Kamui's
guardian deity, Red Dragon.
[KA GRAVA]
Thus, as the final member
of the combined expedition, I,
Ka Grava Rai Fuu Gramstahl,
have an obligation to carry
on Lady Ulrika's will.
I swear, I will not
allow any conflict
between Kouran and D'natia
to occur in my presence!
[RED DRAGON roars]
[MISKA] Her ride is on the
house. Think of it as charity.
[SWEALLOW laughs]
[MERYL]
Setsuren, what a lovely name.
Thanks a lot.
So, you must be the
Sherbet Company person.
And that would make
big brother here,
the newest member of
the Black Dragon Knights.
Is that right?
And you?
Are you the daughter of some
wealthy merchant or something?
[SETSUREN]
Hm...
Sure. Let's go with that.
Ok. Ha, ha.
That concludes
our introductions.
Now then. There's something I
wanted to ask you, Sweallow.
Oh? Sure, what is it?
I was curious if you had found
what you were looking for
on this remote island.
Have any luck?
[MERYL gasps]
Well, it's true that I am
here in search of something.
But let me ask you,
do you happen to know
what that "something" is?
No. Not really.
But let's see, maybe it's
something that will...
never break?
[SWEALLOW gasps]
[SWEALLOW]
Yes, you're right.
No matter what I do, everything
that I try to keep precious
to me breaks, shatters
and falls apart.
No. It's more like I break
everything, precious or not.
How sad.
What if there was someone who
could live thousands of years
without a change in their
appearance? No aging.
Might that be the "something"
big brother was looking for?
[gasps]
I may be in a position
to give that "something"
to you, Sweallow.
[MERYL] What do you mean?
Just who are you?
[SWEALLOW]
Uh!
[MISKA]
Hey, everyone!
We're about to arrive in
the capital city of Shuka!
Interesting.
The beast isn't healing its
wounds as quickly as usual.
And, in turn, it's taking away
the life to which it's bonded.
Must be due to the Magic
Territory shift to D'natia.
Do you have any last words?
If I see Ibuki, I can relay any
message you may have for him.
I can't die.
Not like this, not yet.
Ibuki needs to--
He no longer desires
to become king.
He plans to help
his sister do so.
[EYKHA]
It doesn't matter.
Ibuki is going to be the king.
I have decided that
it has to happen.
Oh, I see.
I suggest you use this.
By doing so, the pain in your
body would be neutralized
through the use of
Kouran's magic.
Just know.
This wedge will only be able to
extend your life for a few days.
Would you like it?
Okay. It's all yours.
[gasps]
[KA GRAVA]
Tell me. Who is responsible
for expediting the
execution of Agito?
[KRAMA]
Kouran.
It's the condition that we gave
to attend the peace meeting.
[SWEALLOW]
Ka Grava!
Leader Simeon!
You have some nerve to
show your face here.
Having left without
any warning or notice.
Ha, ha. By the way,
will Lady Ulrika
be attending the peace meeting?
I see. So you
haven't heard yet.
We, uh... We've only
heard about Agito.
About the execution.
[KA GRAVA] Hm... Allow me
to introduce Sir Krama.
He's the representative of
the provisional government.
[KRAMA]
Sir Sweallow, was it?
Agito, who once led
the rebel army,
is being held prisoner
here in Shuka.
Recently, we discovered
he'd conspired
to place a false king named
Inori upon the throne.
For doing so, we've decided
to execute him without trial.
But, the people of Nil Kamui
support the revolutionary army.
[SETSUREN]
Not "revolutionary army."
More like "rebel army,"
big sister Meryl.
[SWEALLOW]
Setsuren? Sir Byakuei?
If it was that kid Ibuki,
I'd let him pro claim himself to
be the king without a problem.
But not Inori. You
know why, right?
[BYAKUEI] This is Kouran's
representative, Lady Setsuren.
--[SWEALLOW gasps]
--[MERYL] Representative?
Indeed. I'm also known as
the spiritual mother, Ling Mu.
But why would a leader such
as yourself come here?
[SIMEON]
You there. You know why.
Tell me where to
find Lou Chun Wah.
Sir Simeon? What are you--?
[SIMEON]
Where is she?!
This way. You may speak
directly with Agito in here.
What's the meaning
of this. Let me go.
[FUGAKU]
I'm sorry.
Agito asked to speak with
Lord Ibuki in private.
[BLENHEIM] I am a member of
the Emperor of D'natia's
personal order of cavaliers.
My name is Blenheim.
I need to question you
concerning the deaths
of Bishop Enumael and
the temple soldiers.
[SWEALLOW] If Agito is
going to be executed,
then Inori and Ibuki are most
certainly coming to Shuka.
[SETSUREN]
After which they'll summon forth
Red Dragon to save him.
[KA GRAVA]
Summon?
I believe Red Dragon went on
a rampage on its own accord.
How unlike you, great merchant.
Before it goes on its rampage,
a young girl is always sighted.
Or have you forgotten?
[KA GRAVA]
And that young girl is Inori?
Hey, big brother Sweallow.
If Red Dragon appears, would
you mind leaving it alone?
[gasps]
Why would I do that?
If we were to just ignore it,
this city would be
in a lot of trouble.
On the other hand, if big
brother Sweallow kills it,
the power of Red Dragon will
be absorbed by Black Dragon.
After all, Black Dragon and big
brother are bonded by contract.
That's a bit of a
problem for me.
I'm sure you understand why.
[KA GRAVA] If I recall, your
country once defeated a dragon
and built an advanced
civilization with its power.
Correct?
Why, yes!
I believe humans
should be the ones
to use the power of dragons.
So then, what does
Sir Sweallow get
in return for his compliance?
Didn't I mention that?
I know what big brother
wants, remember?
[gasps]
Yes. Something everlasting.
Something that
would never break.
[SETSUREN] I'm able to remain
in this youthful form
until the day I die. And I
can make it the same way
for your precious
someone, as well.
Change them into an existence
that can't be broken. Yes?
[SETSUREN] So how about
it? Why not ask him?
Say you want to stay as youthful
as you are today forever
to be with him. Okay?
If you do, maybe he'll
actually touch you.
[MERYL grunts]
[gasps]
I see.
[SWEALLOW]
That's my final answer. Líng Mu.
I can honestly say now that
I hold precious the concept
of how new things are
born into this world
with each thing
that breaks away.
[MERYL gasps]
If you want, whenever you
grow weary of this life,
I can try to break you.
Sweallow... Clazzvali.
[AGITO]
You've grown well, Ibuki.
Thank you for coming down here.
Hello, Teacher.
Agito.
[AGITO] There is something
you need to do before
you can become
king of Nil Kamui.
[IBUKI] Wait a minute, I thought
you wanted Inori to become king.
[gasps]
You must kill Inori...
with your own two hands.
That establishes your
right to become king.
[KNIGHTS yell]
[RETURNED ONES moan]
[KNIGHT C]
Whoa!
[KNIGHT B grunts]
Fugaku! What on earth
are you doing?!
This is all part
of Agito's plan.
Yes, that's right.
He informed us that very soon
you would come to this prison.
Consider it a plea bargain.
[INORI]
Agito. Of course, that's right.
Agito went and...
[IBUKI] Inori was cursed by
Red Dragon, just as I was!
She went insane because of it!
I only want to have Inori
back to how she was before!
Killing her is--
[AGITO]
You've got it wrong.
It was Inori who made
Red Dragon go mad.
She what?
Half a year ago, Inori was
hiding in a certain village.
But they discovered who
she was, and, in fear
of being chased by Kouran, the
villagers tried to kill her.
[INORI screams]
[screaming]
--[VILLAGERS yell]
--[INORI screams]
[AGITO]
Then, from within Inori...
[RED DRAGON roars]
[AGITO]
...Red Dragon appeared.
[RED DRAGON roars]
[INORI laughs]
[AGITO]
By the time we arrived,
Red Dragon was in the middle
of burning down the village
by Inori's command.
[AGITO] It was then that
I knew she had gone mad.
Red Dragon?
Agito! How could you?!
You killed Father and Mother?!
So you finally remembered!
The death of your parents,
the King and Queen.
The tragedy that took
place three years ago
wasn't because of Kouran.
I killed them!
Uh?!
[AGITO] The king was secretly
planning to gain a false form
of peace by offering Nil
Kamui to D'natia and Kouran.
That is not the kind
of country I desire!
That's why I killed the king!
Agito, no. It can't be...
[AGITO] But when I met
Inori at that village,
she smiled back at me.
The memory of what I
had done was gone.
That's when I knew.
She wasn't the same as
she had been before.
Don't worry, I won't
forget again.
Now, Red Dragon. Kill Agito!
[RED DRAGON roars]
[AGITO]
Ibuki! Kill Inori!
It's the only way
to stop Red Dragon.
This is your moment.
This is when you become
known as the king
who defeated Red
Dragon! [laughs]
[IBUKI]
Agito!
Fugaku!
[FUGAKU groaning]
[gasps]
[FUGAKU] Hurry... use
Red Dragon's power!
Uh!
That is, if you still see
me as your dear friend.
Of course you're
my friend, Fugaku!
[FUGAKU] Offer up my
life and stop Inori!
Hear me Red Dragon!
I need your power!
[INORI laughs] But Red
Dragon has approved of me.
That's why your voice won't
be heard, Dear Brother!
Now, come with me!
[IBUKI] Stop, Inori!
Fugaku is going to--!
[INORI]
Hmm. What shall I do?
Hey, how about I let him
live as a Returned One?
I mean, he is your precious
friend after all, right?
Ibuki!
[INORI]
Or, maybe not.
[IBUKI groaning]
Fukagu!
[RED DRAGON roars]
Ah-ha, there you are! I've
been searching everywhere.
Some of Simeon folks have
been looking for you.
Did you do something?
Who knows?
But forget that.
I heard that our Ling
Mu spoke with you.
Yeah. She told me to
leave Red Dragon alone.
I assume you're not
going to listen. Pity.
Honestly, I don't care who
defeats Red Dragon.
As long as, in the end,
Ibuki's curse is lifted.
Wouldn't it be better for
everyone if we joined forces?
[LOU]
That would defeat the purpose.
The life of that dragon is
intended solely for my lord.
[gasps]
Come on, is this
really what you want?
If we both use them, we'll
just be on equal footing
with our powers cancelling
each other out.
[LOU]
We aren't equal at all!
[MERYL grunts]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Now, Lou!
He still doesn't know about
Lady Ulrika's death!
[MERYL gasps]
[LOU screams]
[SWEALLOW]
I see. So then, Ulrika's dead.
[MERYL]
Things will always break.
That's something obvious to him.
Something he doesn't question.
To him, all living
things are precious.
But there's no time to look back
on that which is already broken.
[LOU growls]
Contract seal. Now release.
[BLACK DRAGON growls]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
It came. It finally arrived.
[KRAMA]
What the...?
What's going on?
[IBUKI]
Inori. What have you done?
[INORI] Today's going to be the
first day of our independence!
And very soon you and
I will bond as one!
Uh!
What are you talking about?
A king can do anything
they want, right?
Or have you forgotten?
[groaning]
[KA GRAVA]
I see.
So my old friend is being
controlled by Inori after all.
[RED DRAGON roars]
[SIMEON] I will release
the contract seal!
All those who are still
alive, leave at once!
And after all that talk
about making me king.
You're such a liar, D'natia!
Contract seal, now release!
Black Blade!
Is that all you've got?
Wow, how incredibly lame.
[IBUKI]
Careful, Simeon!
[RED DRAGON roars]
Heh. I'm the one to
defeat Red Dragon.
[gasps]
[SIMEON]
Black Dragon! I beseech you!
Grant me your two
divine protections!
Wait he has two contract seals?
[SIMEON growls, yells]
Hear me, Black Dragon!
[SIMEON growls]
Come, Dear Brother.
[IBUKI]
Do I really have to kill her?
Red Dragon. Answer me!
[IBUKI]
It won't say anything!
[INORI]
Don't worry.
[gasps]
Red Dragon is right
here with me.
[EYKHA]
Ibuki!
Eykha!
You don't have to dirty
your hands with this one,
because I'm your sword.
And I will strike!
[INORI groaning]
Eykha, no!
You're not my sword,
understand me? Listen.
You're the one I
care for the most!
[EYKHA gasps]
[INORI grunting]
[VAL growls]
[sighs]
[INORI] Did you forget?
Red Dragon is inside me.
Neither I nor Red Dragon
can be destroyed.
We're invincible.
Ibuki. Please,
listen to my song.
[gasps]
[KA GRAVA]
The Song of a Bonded One.
A magic that changes their life
force into their attack power.
So, she's prepared
to die then.
To give her life.
[singing]
--[singing continues]
--[VAL growls]
Come forth, Red Dragon! Ha!
Red Dragon won't give up.
It'll just keep reviving her.
[KA GRAVA]
So long as Inori still lives.
But no attacks will
be able to reach her
because of Red Dragon's
divine protection.
[laughs] Well, this
isn't looking too good.
My lord. I'll bring down
Red Dragon for you.
And now, I want you
to use my life....
Ibuki.
[IBUKI]
Something's changed.
I can't hear Red Dragon's
voice anymore. But...
Imperial Era 3015, November.
I've... decided.
[NARRATOR]
Act Twelve.
One Chance in a Million.
The city of Shuka burns,
consuming all with it.
Fulfill your desire,
Imperial! Meet with destiny!