[MASHIRO]
I'm sorry,
but this is all I have
to give you right now.
[EYKHA]
Thank you.
But, I cannot accept this as
I have no way to repay you.
Actually, you can do
something for me.
You're strong.
So I'd like you to help
me protect my friend.
Protect? What do you mean?
I'm talking about Ibuki.
With things being
the way they are,
I don't think I can protect
him all by myself.
[gasps]
All right, fine.
It's a promise.
Thank you so much, Eykha.
[IBUKI] The name of our
country is Nil Kamui.
It's a small island nation.
Three years have passed
since our land fell
to the great neighboring
nation of Kouran.
Our ally, D'natia,
maintained their distance,
and our guardian deity,
Red Dragon, went mad.
I lost everything in
this conflict known
as the Seven Year War.
Our castle, from which we
once ruled over the country,
my parents, my sister,
Inori, all of it.
Imperial Era 3015. October.
Nil Kamui is still not
under our control.
Forgive me for asking,
but didn't all your
family members die?
[IBUKI]
When the castle fell,
I was the only one in my
household to survive.
Or, so I'd believed. Till now.
[LOU]
Whatever the circumstance,
the next thing you should do
is meet with her face-to-face.
Lou! Are you okay?
[MERYL gasps]
I'm a member of
this expedition.
I won't die because of
something like this.
[KA GRAVA] We need to
get you treated, now!
[IBUKI]
Uh!
Ogani Volcano erupted?
[MERYL] But it showed
no signs of activity
during the investigation.
[KA GRAVA]
This is bad.
If this keeps up, the fort
is going to be in danger!
[SIMEON]
Open the gate!
Huh. Anyone recognize that guy?
Oh, come on! You
can't be serious!
That's Lord Simeon,
leader of the third corps!
Oh, yeah, of course!
I remember now! It
just slipped my mind.
Contract seal, release!
[SIMEON grunting]
[KA GRAVA]
He averted the lava flow!
Lord Simeon is a
powerful one, indeed.
Unbelievable.
[SIMEON]
Not even half the power
granted by Black Dragon should
have shown here on this island.
Dear Brother!
It's really you!
--[INORI grunts]
--Thank Goodness!
[IBUKI]
I... Inori?
I missed you so much.
Look at that!
Not really sure what to
do in these situations.
Yes, I know.
Meryl, are you crying?
[gasps] No, of course I'm not!
[IBUKI] I can't believe
it. It really is you!
[INORI]
Yes. It is.
I almost forgot!
There's someone I wanted
to introduce you to.
[gasps]
Ibuki.
Mashiro...?
[INORI]
I met her at Shuka.
I knew you'd want to see her,
so I brought her to you as
soon as I could, brother.
Hold on. Wasn't
she the one that--?
[MERYL grunts]
[EYKHA gasps]
Mashiro?
[IBUKI, INORI gasp]
Mashiro? No way.
We know Mashiro died.
And I've heard that
Inori died, as well.
[door opens]
[FUGAKU] On the contrary,
Lady Inori was alive.
By order of Agito,
I was the one who
brought Lady Inori here.
No way! You mean Agito was
sheltering her all along?
--Help!
--[FUGAKU] No, stop!
--They're still inside!
There's nothing we can
do for them anymore.
Kouran's army will be on top of
us in a moment, we have to go!
But we--! [gasps]
Agito!
I will save Lady Inori.
After some time had passed,
I visited Shuka's prison...
No, it can't be. Lady Inori?
If it's discovered that
both Imperials are alive,
Kouran would surely
move into action.
[AGITO]
It was necessary
to hide her away somewhere
until the time was ripe.
Fortunately, because
of the untimely loss
of General Kohkaku,
Kouran is currently lost
in a state of confusion.
[FUGAKU]
I was completely unaware.
[INORI] From now on, let's
fight these battles together.
[AGITO] We will make Inori our
king, and free this island.
But... but what about Ibuki?
[AGITO] It was heart-wrenching
deceiving you all, believe me.
But in the end,
everything was for the sake
of regaining our country.
I didn't know about any of that.
Agito put that much
thought into all of this?
Lady Inori would like
to meet with you again.
This time, at the embassy.
[IBUKI]
Understood. Count me in.
Wait. But what about Mashiro?
You killed her, didn't you?
[IBUKI]
Yes.
I killed her.
But...
Yes, it's strange.
I was only recently told of
how Lady Inori was alive.
You should speak with
Mashiro to settle this.
Oh, by the way, where's Hien?
[IBUKI] He's dead.
He gave his life for me.
[FUGAKU] I see. I'm sure
he went with honor.
[SWEALLOW]
Amazing. He actually did it.
Ka Grava built an
embassy for us.
[MERYL] Enjoy it while it lasts.
I'm sure it'll be in shambles
within the month with
you here, Sir Sweallow.
[ENUMAEL] Did you call for me,
Mister Ambassador?
Your Exellency.
I certainly did.
I was hoping you could
tell me more about Inori.
Who is she, really?
[ENUMAEL] She is the
true Child of Contract,
and the true ruler of Nil Kamui.
Our country will
protect Lady Inori
and help her regain the
dynasty she so truly deserves.
[SWEALLOW exhales]
So what you're saying
is that you'll end up
with a puppet government.
[ENUMAEL] I would prefer
that you acknowledge them
as being a sibling country led
by D'natia's grand teachings.
[SWEALLOW]
Is that so.
While on the subject, do you
think there's any chance
that Inori could
be a Returned One?
Come now, that's absurd.
Not too long ago, we
had the misfortune
of fighting the
walking dead.
And now we've learned
that an Imperial
that was initially reported to
be deceased has appeared.
Wouldn't that make
you suspicious?
Surely, you jest!
Why would we make such
a foolish assumption?
When Lady Inori came
under our protection
from the revolutionary army,
we conducted a very thorough
background check using magic,
specifically focusing
on the possibility
of her being a Returned One.
Of course, we found nothing.
I personally believe
she is quite suited
to lead the
dragon-revering savages.
After all, miracles are
adored by the ignorant.
Interesting assessment.
You know, you could
say the same thing
about the Black Dragon Knights.
[KA GRAVA]
It took some time,
but I have examined the
wedge of the Yellow Dragon.
Did you find that it
piqued your interest?
[KA GRAVA]
The magic we use
is affected by the magic
dwelling within each land,
also known as the country's
"State Magic Territory."
You could approach it as a
"home" or "away" concept,
but it seems as if this wedge
can tilt the balance
towards Kouran.
It looks like there's value
in working out a deal
with you after all.
[LOU]
Why of course there is.
Now then, arrange for
my artificial arm.
[KA GRAVA]
Understood.
The driving force behind
humans seems to be
how they use and
abuse one another.
All that remains for
them to figure out
is whether they can feel
good about doing so.
That being the case,
do you think that's
what gives meaning
toward a trusting
relationship?
[SHADDY] Is this really
okay, Lord Ka Grava?
[KA GRAVA] Regardless of D'natia
or Kouran, if the wedge is used,
the balance of Nil Kamui's State
Magic Territory will crumble.
The land will suffer, even
in relation to its magic.
That's why we need to stop
as much of this as we can
before it starts.
Lord Ka Grava.
Mm.
[KA GRAVA] I made a promise
to my wife before she died
that I would protect
the future of you kids.
I intend to keep that promise.
[FUGAKU] Good work.
You've guarded Ibuki well.
You can leave everything
else to us now.
Welcome, Dear Brother of mine.
[INORI laughs]
[KA GRAVA]
I wouldn't if I were you.
Even if you go now,
I doubt your thoughts
will get through to Ibuki.
I saw it. Mashiro
offered her life.
She should be dead
now as an equivalent.
[KA GRAVA] I'm in quite
the predicament,
as I've not yet witnessed
Ibuki's power for myself.
That's why you--!
[KA GRAVA] That's why I see
the value in confirming
your suspicion. Isn't that
what you had in mind?
You're the one who built
this embassy, right?
Tell me. Is there a
way to see inside?
[KA GRAVA]
Such an accusation!
Even I wouldn't
do something as--
[SHADDY]
I'll set it right up for you!
Yeah, I thought so.
My dearest brother.
You must have gone through
so much on your own.
And you, too.
You and I were born into
this world as twins.
And according to
ancient tradition,
I was determined to be
the king of our land.
[IBUKI]
Yes, I remember, Inori.
[INORI]
That is why...
there's nothing for
you to worry about.
That can't be!
The revolutionary army
fought to place Ibuki
on the throne of Nil Kamui.
[INORI laughs]
I can leave you alone for a bit
with Mashiro, if you like.
Uh! That's not...!
Hi, Ibuki.
I still can't believe
this is happening!
Mashiro, you're really alive!
It's all because
of Red Dragon!
He looks over us and
protects us! Listen!
Let's all live here in this
place together, okay?
Just the three of us!
You, me, and Mashiro!
I'll be the king, and Dear
Brother will help me!
I'm sure we'll make a
wonderful country together!
Our Emperor has given us orders
to guard Bishop
Enumael and Inori.
To achieve this, we must head
to the town of Haiga posthaste.
[ULRIKA] I sense
something troubling you.
Were you aware of that
girl Inori, Sir Simeon?
[SIMEON]
No, not at all.
The Bishop will be questioned
at length in regards to her.
If we leave, our mission
of stationing ourselves
here will obviously be--
[SIMEON]
Regarding that,
we have proper support
to fill our positions.
You may enter.
[door creaks]
Wait, I know that emblem.
We are the Emperor's
personal order of cavaliers.
We will gladly take over
here in Nil Kamui.
Thank you. I will be on a
mission, headed to Haiga.
I assign Tricolor
and Black Tongue
to handle the colonial
towns near the rear.
Ruby and Blenheim, you two
will head towards Shuka.
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
Come on, Ulrika.
Let's get moving.
[ULRIKA]
Sir!
[EYKHA]
What are you talking about?
Weren't you going to
be king of this island?
Everything's okay, Eykha.
After all, Mashiro's alive now.
[gasps]
[MASHIRO]
Just be a good king. Ibuki.
She's been alive
this whole time.
Don't you see?
I didn't kill her!
Ibuki, Mashiro wanted to
sacrifice herself for you.
Nothing's changed.
Just because she's alive
doesn't mean your
promise to her is gone.
You're the one who's going to
become king of this Island.
And I'm the sword that
will bring that about.
We've received numerous
reports from Shuka,
tales of Inori appearing and
taking Mashiro with her.
But the details of such
appearances are still unknown.
[KA GRAVA] Good work.
Thank you for your efforts.
We even made a grave for her.
I'm telling you, she's dead.
[KA GRAVA]
It's difficult to confirm death,
even for an experienced doctor.
There are instances of the dead
reviving after their burial.
[EYKHA] Not in this case. Ibuki
told me her heart was pierced.
[KA GRAVA] Or, maybe this
girl is just a stand-in.
It's also possible that she's
Mashiro's long lost twin.
Additionally, there doesn't
seem to be anything unusual
about her. She's just been
sitting there the whole time.
Sitting there?
[gasps]
[EYKHA]
This whole time.
Just sitting there, not eating,
not sleeping. No way.
Mashiro is a Returned One!
[KA GRAVA]
Hm...
And that means
Ibuki is in danger.
[KA GRAVA] What are the odds
of there being a Returned One
who retains their sanity?
Don't forget Izun!
[KA GRAVA] Circumstantial. That
alone isn't proof of anything.
[EYKHA]
I understand. Well then.
I'll just have to find
a way to get proof.
[EYKHA] I'm here as
Lord Ibuki's messenger.
I have a letter for Lady Inori's
waiting maid, Mashiro.
I see. No problem.
You want to see her
somewhere out of view, right?
Let me ask you something: do you
remember the first time we met?
I promised you that I would
protect Ibuki. Right?
You two were different
from the others.
You never threw rocks at
Bounded Ones like myself.
You both treated me like
a normal human being.
I'm sure Ibuki will spread
such feelings of kindness
and acceptance across
this entire island.
I'm bonded to Val here,
so I don't have many
years left to live.
But, I've decided to use
whatever remaining time I have
to protect Ibuki.
It's the same with you, right?
You offered your
life to Red Dragon
to help Ibuki become king.
That's the reason that he has
continued to keep your promise.
At the orphanage, he
saved all those children,
but he was forced to kill Kai.
In that moment I knew.
Ibuki was the one who should
become the king of this island.
[gasps]
Mashiro?
Ibuki.
[EYKHA]
Huh?
[EYKHA grunting]
[EYKHA] You don't remember
a thing, do you.
[MASHIRO]
Heh, heh.
I will protect Ibuki.
I'll die defending
my future king.
Enough! Stop smiling at me!
How dare you smile
using my friend's face!
[ENUMAEL] What in the world
is this business all about?!
I can't believe you
made me bring
this harmless waiting maid
all the way here for this!
[KA GRAVA] I'm terribly
sorry about that.
Where's Lady Inori?
[ENUMAEL]
Resting. As she should be.
[KA GRAVA] I see. Then let's
get started, shall we?
If you may, Eykha.
Eykha? What is this about?
It's Mashiro.
She's a Returned One.
[ENUMAEL]
What's this all of a sudden?
Is this Nil Kamui's
poor excuse for a joke?
[EYKHA]
Mashiro died once at Shuka.
But she came back to life.
That's what I thought.
She was killed by Ibuki.
Yet here she is. Good.
My memory's not
fleeting after all.
Hold on. You can see that
she's sitting right here.
It's true. And there are a
number of suspect things, but--
Look, she was saved by Lady
Inori's magic, nothing more.
I don't see the fuss.
[LOU]
Don't feel bad.
When I was first starting out,
I often thought I was killing
a person when in fact I was only
rendering them unconscious.
Turns out you have to behead
them to make sure.
[SWEALLOW] Uh, that's not what
we're talking about, Lou.
[ENUMAEL]
If you're going to accuse her
of being a Returned
One, then you should
at least show us
some form of proof.
[KA GRAVA] Well, Eykha?
I killed Mashiro
again last night.
[ALL gasp]
Right! Sure! And your point is?
She died by my hand
yesterday evening,
yet now she's here
in front of us.
She came back to life.
So she's--
[IBUKI]
Calm down! Take it easy!
[EYKHA]
Take her clothes off!
Ah, I see your plan. She
should have two scars.
One from when Ibuki killed her,
and another from when Eykha
killed her last night.
Wounds like that would
be hard to refute.
Come now! Don't be ridiculous!
That isn't proof of anything!
And aside from that,
making her take off her
clothes is outrageous!
[KA GRAVA]
Well, why don't we decide
after we take a look at this.
No. Impossible.
[KA GRAVA]
Those images were recorded
by Haiga's security system.
As you can surmise,
there is no human that can
survive what you just saw.
So, there's only one
reason as to why
she would be here
in front of us.
[IBUKI]
It can't be...
Mashiro is...
[KA GRAVA] I need not
explain the dangers
involved with a Returned One.
As one who oversees Haiga, I
can't let this go unnoticed.
[ENUMAEL]
N-No, but, wait...
[INORI] What's with all
the commotion, everyone?
Yes, Mashiro is indeed
a Returned One.
Are there any
problems with that?
Huh?
[FUGAKU]
Lady Inori?
That girl is someone
who is very precious
and important to
my dear Brother.
That is why...
...I brought Mashiro
back from the dead.
But... Inori.
[NARRATOR]
Chaos Dragon, Act 9. Winding.
The distorted and twisted heart
raises the curtain to
a stage of tragedy.
How will this play turn out?