[IBUKI] The beasts of
this forest are dying?
[FUGAKU]
Yes. Over the last few days,
they've all but
gone extinct.
It's possible that our State
Magic Territory is changing.
And if it is, then what you're
seeing is only the beginning.
Soon, the flow of water,
our crops and livestock,
and even the air we breathe
will be affected.
All this time, it was Inori
Agito wanted to ascend.
It's unforgivable.
Using you as a decoy.
[IBUKI]
Leave Agito to me.
For now, let's just
get to Shuka.
[INORI]
Oh! Thank goodness!
I was worried we'd
gotten separated!
Here. Don't ever let go
of me again, brother!
Excuse me, Bishop Enumael?
I can't seem to find
Inori anywhere.
Uh!
[SIMEON]
Sir Sweallow!
Please forgive me, I had
intended to meet you
sooner than this. Alas,
I was given urgent orders
to retrieve Bishop Enumael
and the Imperial.
We are to depart for
Shuka immediately.
Where's Ibuki?!
Why's this monster
in the embassy?!
[ULRIKA] She's a member of
the combined expedition.
As for Ibuki, he's the other
imperial. You can't find him?
[gasps] I want this facility
on lockdown now!
[BLENHEIM]
Sir!
[SWEALLOW]
What's goin' on?
Uh!
[ULRIKA] The name of
this island is Nil Kamui.
Three years ago, it was invaded
by the great ancient
country of Kouran.
Despite being Nil Kamui's ally,
our homeland of D'natia
maintained a neutral stance and
avoided the conflict entirely.
As the Seven Year War
came to a close,
the land returned
to a state of peace
under the rule of the
two foreign powers.
With D'natia monitoring
Kouran's occupation.
But even with the
current arrangement,
this country must one day
return to its rightful owners.
Holy Era 285, October.
Nil Kamui is about to be
engulfed in conflict once again.
[MERYL]
That's strange.
You said these were found next
to Bishop Enumael's body?
[ULRIKA]
That's correct. You see,
these are the remnants
of a Holy Spirit,
a seal that's given by the
church to protect its bearer.
I assume Sir Sweallow
never got one because
he has you as a partner,
so he wouldn't need
the extra care.
More like he never got one
because it's so valuable
that he'd just sell it.
Meanwhile, I'm worthless
and easy to abuse.
Have you ever stood so
close to a painting,
that you weren't able
to the whole thing?
[MERYL]
Uh?
You two are always together,
so you may not know it.
But really, you're
very precious to him.
So you're saying, Mashiro--
Uh. No. I mean, the Returned One
is responsible for
killing the bishop.
[KA GRAVA]
It would provide motivation
for Inori and the others
to suddenly disappear.
Well at least any implications
directed at Kouran
are now put to rest.
[BLENHEIM growls]
But it doesn't solve
the big issue.
Our two nations would attack
each other for any offense.
Which is just what Agito wants.
[SIMEON]
You're Byakuei,
"the Leader of
Ten-Thousand," correct?
You'll have to excuse
my forwardness,
but it is quite suspicious
that our bishop was killed
as you arrived in Haiga.
[BLENHEIM]
The timing is convenient.
[SWEALLOW]
Nah. That's a coincidence.
I'm tellin' ya,
he's not a bad...
[grunts] person.
I'm here for a reason.
Kouran's spiritual mother
wants a conference.
She sent me to arrange this.
Proper rule over Nil Kamui
needs to be established.
Kouran's legendary ruler
of three-thousand years
suddenly wants to
set up a meeting?
"Legendary"?! Not exactly.
But, yes, she's actually
in Shuka for this occasion.
[KA GRAVA]
I don't think it's appropriate
for this country's future
to be decided solely
by foreign nations.
[BYAKUEI] Your attendance
has also been requested,
Sir Ka Grava.
[KA GRAVA]
Hm...
Agito is clearly working
toward something.
Whatever it is, it involves
the imperial children as well.
And he's already manipulated
D'natia once before.
With everything that's going on,
we really don't need a
power struggle right now.
[SIMEON] Agreed. Once
I have received approval,
we will have the
meeting in Shuka.
[SWEALLOW]
Hold on a second!
We don't have time
for this stuff.
Have you forgotten about
the combined expedition?
[BYAKUEI] You mean the one that
united us with the revolution?
We believed if the three
factions came together
for a common goal, they
would find peace eventually.
But considering the
revolutionary army's
been going behind our
backs this whole time,
it makes it all meaningless.
[IBUKI] With everything
that's happened,
there's no way Kouran or D'natia
would approve of Inori as king.
So then...
[gasps]
Stay back!
Something's not right!
Go! Now!
[RETURNED ONES moaning]
[VAL growls]
Val, no! What's the matter?
You have to get up!
[INORI] You poor thing.
You're feeling run down, right?
More undead attendants.
Come on.
Those filthy outsiders
have tainted our
State Magic Territory.
It's slowly killing that
monster you're bonded to.
You see?
Undeniable proof. Right here.
Weakening the Red Dragon has
always been the true purpose
of the combined expedition,
and this was the
easiest way to do it.
It's not exactly irrational
after he lost control like that.
Or have you forgotten? He
attacked his own people!
Well, it's not like they didn't
have it coming to them.
The Red Dragon was disappointed.
The country he devoted his life
to protecting betrayed him,
after all. But what would
you know about that?
--[VAL growling]
--[RETURNED ONE A moans ]
[EYKHA grunts]
[gasps]
Hurry and take my life, Ibuki!
[INORI]
How sad.
You'll never become king!
Only Ibuki has the traits
necessary to rule!
[INORI]
I get it.
Your entire life is
dependent on my brother
ascending to the throne.
Only because he's
the rightful king.
No, it's because you're
a worthless Bounded One,
and you're out of time.
Once that monster of yours
dies, it's all over.
But if my brother used you
to unleash his flame,
it would mean your
life had value.
Then you could die happily,
because you gave everything in
service as your king's blade.
And it would prove
that he considered you
a precious friend.
Yeah. That's it.
Don't make me laugh.
I can't blame you for
falling madly in love
with my dear brother.
That's a lie!
But the truth is he'll never
return your feelings
because you're merely
an attendant to him.
Which is why he won't
sacrifice you.
A relationship like that
isn't worth anything
to the Red Dragon.
No. That's not why.
[INORI]
You understand?
No matter how it happens,
your death will be pitiful
and mean nothing!
[laughs]
You know what, brother?
You should just kill her.
It's all she has
to look forward--
That is enough!
Eykha. Go back to Ka Grava.
[EYKHA] You also refused to kill
me the last time I asked you to.
Is it because what
she said is true?
You think my life is worthless?
Eykha...
[EYKHA cries]
[IBUKI]
I'm sending you away
because I don't
consider you my blade.
[INORI chuckles]
[IBUKI] All I really
want is to protect you.
But I know I don't have
the right to do that.
Ibuki!
[LOU] This new arm
is quite impressive.
[KA GRAVA] That's the best
Wu Xhing Ti that Kouran makes.
It's the least I could provide
after what you've given me.
[LOU]
And what is this?
That would be
the Dragon's Claw.
[LOU]
If I had to guess,
I'd say that's our best hope in
the fight against Red Dragon.
[KA GRAVA]
Hm... It's rather unlike you
to show interest in someone
else's belongings.
You're right. How
unbecoming of me.
[SWEALLOW]
Hey, all right.
Looks like your operation
was a complete success.
You like it?
[SWEALLOW]
Uh. Yeah, sure. [clear throat]
So the combined expedition
was just a waste of time.
Because each country had
its own selfish goals
rather than interest
in working together.
Uh! But all that political
mumbo jumbo
doesn't have anything
to do with us.
Am I right?
Yes, you are. We were
given a mission
and we should see it
through to the end.
Then it's really up to us.
Indeed.
--Find and kill Red Dragon.
--We have to protect Ibuki.
[BOTH]
Mm?!
Sorry, I must have misheard.
What is it you
think we should do?
[SWEALLOW] Depending on how
the meeting in Shuka goes,
Ibuki could be in
serious danger.
We have to keep him safe.
[LOU] But the whole
purpose of the expedition
was to find Red Dragon.
Although... that was
always just a front.
In reality, you and I
were supposed to kill it.
I won't deny that.
And if we could pull off
getting rid of him, honestly,
my life would only be
better for having done so.
But if you were to ask
me whether I thought
doing something to make my
life better in exchange
for letting a kid's life
be ruined was worth it,
my answer would be no.
Truthfully speaking, I've never
been attached to anything
in my whole life.
And that applies to the
mission we were given, too.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
He is an enigma, isn't he, Lou?
However, if we
stay by his side,
I will be able to consume
both the Imperials
and the Black Dragon Knights.
[grunts] Watch yourself.
I'm pretty sure I've
told you this before,
I can't touch people
like it's no big deal.
[LOU]
Sir Sweallow.
I will kill Red Dragon if
it's the last thing I do.
I don't understand you, Lou.
What's the point in pursuing
this thing so doggedly
it practically becomes
a vendetta?
Just why?
--There's gotta be a reason.
--[LOU] That is akin to
asking me why my
heart beats within
my breast without provocation.
[SWEALLOW]
I think I understand.
You're my total opposite.
You get attached to anything
that's given to you.
Then again. It's not
like I didn't realize
that about you back
when we first met,
so it's not really surprising.
Truth be told,
I think I was hoping that
sentiment might rub off on me.
Guess I was expecting too much.
[LOU] Oh, I'm more than willing
to meet your expectations.
Right now's fine.
Here.
If you'd like...
[BYAKUEI] Lou Chun Wah. Am
I interrupting something?
[LOU] No, sir. Is there
anything I can do
housand?
for you, great Leader
of Ten
[BYAKUEI] Not quite. You have
a message from the Líng Mu.
[SWEALLOW groans]
[ULRIKA] Are you all
right, Sir Sweallow?
Oh, man, I swear this
isn't what it looks like!
I understand.
Uh!
It's all right. I know you're
planning to go help Ibuki,
even though it's going to
inhibit the possibility
of having your curse lifted.
Cat's outta the bag!
Did Meryl tell you
about this? Man!
--Uh!
--[ULRIKA gasps]
[ULRIKA] Are you sure this
is what you want to do?
You've suffered more
than anyone ever should.
Even as a child.
Yeah, maybe I have.
But that's exactly
why I can't stand by
and do nothing when I
know a child is suffering.
[ULRIKA whimpers]
Be careful.
[BYAKUEI]
What were you about to do?
Kill that Black Dragon
Knight in the open?
Would that be a problem?
[BYAKUEI] Well, it would give
some credence to the rumors.
The way I heard it, you became
a cold-blooded assassin
after you stole that
sword from a general
who had taken a liking to you.
[KOURAN GENERAL]
From what I was told,
it has something to
do with the Líng Mu.
The blade is so sharp that the
previous owner couldn't resist
the temptation of testing
it on his subordinates.
[laughs] Sounds like
a good idea to me!
[LOU gasps]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Would you like to be the one
to entertain me, my dear?
I will do anything
for you, my lord.
[KOURAN GENERAL screams]
[BYAKUEI]
Allegedly, you were charmed
by the sword and
became its slave.
Ha. I'm shocked you'd believe
something so ridiculous.
Honestly, General, you should
try to be more skeptical.
Regarding your message
from the Líng Mu...
[BYAKUEI] ...she said, "even
if you're the only one left.
You must take Red
Dragon's life."
[SWEALLOW]
Hey. Where's the Dragon's Claw?
[MERYL] We must've forgotten
it, but we can't go
back for it now. Or we'd have
to reveal where we're going.
[ULRIKA] That could be trouble.
What if Lou gets it?
Well, that's pretty unlikely.
I've never seen her
show any interest
in other people's stuff.
Better safe than sorry.
I'll handle making
sure it gets to Shuka.
That'd be great. But really--
[ULRIKA]
Sir Sweallow.
All I want is for
the people here
to live together in peace
without fear of discrimination.
To reach a point where
D'natia, Nil Kamui,
and Kouran aren't
struggling for power.
I'm afraid this makes me unfit
as a Black Dragon Knight.
[SWEALLOW]
You're wrong.
[ULRIKA] I had hoped
the combined expedition
would spearhead this
ideal as it progressed,
but that will never happen so
long as Lou Chun Wah
is a member! That
woman is pure evil.
[MERYL gasps]
Well that took a dark turn.
[ULRIKA]
Sorry about this.
We need to get sailing
pretty quick,
so we'll only need the
minimum crew and supplies.
[SHADDY] It's fine. We're more
than happy to help you out.
[SOL]
As for your special request...
I believe this is
what you wanted?
[ULRIKA]
Thank you.
[LOU]
The Dragon's Claw.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
This is all a ploy.
They appear to be
going separate ways,
but their destinations
are the same.
[exhales] I can do
this. It'll be fine.
There's nowhere you can run!
Your fate is sealed, Ulrika!
[ULRIKA]
Hmph.
Time to die!
[HYDRA growls]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Lou! The shadow!
[HYDRA growls]
[LOU]
A familiar?!
[HYDRA growls]
But how?!
Can't say I anticipated
the shadow monster.
[HYDRA growls]
[LOU gasps]
I can't sense its presence.
Damn it.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Be careful, Lou.
The Black Dragon's
element is "Darkness."
They can use the shadows
to their advantage.
Further, his power is
greatest at night.
If we do not hurry,
the sun will set on us.
And she'll have the upper
hand. Can't have that.
[HYDRA growling]
Contract seal... Release!
[ULRIKA] Bestow upon me the
power of the Black Dragon!
Die!
[LOU grunts]
[ULRIKA whimpers]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Well, well.
This comes as no
surprise to me.
After all, none can resist
your charm, my lord.
[ULRIKA gasping]
[LOU] You're so consumed
with desire for this sword,
you can't control
yourself. Right?
[ULRIKA gasping]
I offer to you, my lord,
Ulrika's very essence!
Feast upon this
Black Dragon Knight!
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
I accept!
[LOU grunts]
[ULRIKA gasps]
[QI SHA TIAN LING laughing]
My lord?
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
That light.
She's protected by
a Holy Spirit.
[LOU]
A what?
[HOLY SPIRIT screams]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
A type of seal
that can deflect a deadly blow.
However, it is sacrificed
in the process.
[LOU] Then she has more than
one life for us to take.
It seems the pain made
you regain yourself.
No matter, everyone
succumbs eventually.
You'll lust for my lord again.
That so? Then I'll just remind
myself how he hurt me!
[screams]
Unbelievable. Why are
you fighting so hard?
[ULRIKA
Attack!
[LOU gasps]
[HYDRA growls]
[ULRIKA] It takes a lot
more than simple trickery
to steal my heart!
You are nothing!
I've already seen the most
beautiful thing in this world!
Because he's fated to lose
everything he'll ever care for,
he willingly risks it all
to preserve the lives
of those around him.
And if his life is theirs,
then my life... is his!
It's not like he
can even touch you.
How pitiful to fall for someone
that you will never embrace.
[ULRIKA grunts]
[gasps]
[HYDRA growls]
[ULRIKA whimpers]
[LOU]
In case you were wondering,
the Magic Territory of this
ocean just shifted heavily
in Kouran's favor.
[HYDRA growls]
Seeing as you're from D'natia,
I imagine you're feeling rather
uncomfortable about now.
Even though there's
no hope left,
you're still willing to protect
your master to the very end.
How loyal.
[HYDRA growls]
[HYDRA groans]
There is nothing more
beautiful than my lord.
And he is eager to touch you.
Heh. Ha!
[ULRIKA screams]
[HOLY SPIRIT screams]
[ULRIKA]
Sweallow.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
It was all a ruse.
They must have sent
the Dragon's Claw ahead
through some other channel while
this ship served as a decoy.
So she sacrificed herself?
Oh. I see.
You gave everything you
had to be his Holy Spirit.
[NARRATOR]
Act eleven.
Pandemonium.
The fires of the
revolution burn as hot
as the Red Dragon's flames.
However, once the dragon
has chosen its prey,
nothing can escape
its infernal blaze.