[RED DRAGON roars]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Fly, Val!
[VAL roars]
[EYKHA] Red Dragon, why?!
Everyone believed in you!
That you'd fight alongside us
in the revolutionary army.
Instead... you attack us?
[RED DRAGON roars]
[EYKHA] Izun, a Bounded One
who shared a bond
with a great Stone Giant,
led the first expedition by
the Revolutionary Army.
Our fate was sealed the moment
he became the first to fall.
[STONE GIANT grunts]
[EYKHA]
Izun!
Izun! What are you doing?
Wait, stop this!
You don't have to die!
[STONE GIANT growls]
[RED DRAGON roars]
[EYKHA]
Trust me...
Red Dragon will not save us.
[gasps]
[IBUKI] We hail from a
country known as Nil Kamui.
It is but a small island nation.
We were invaded by the great
ancient country of Kohran.
And in their avarice, a third
of our land was pillaged.
D'natia, an ally
state to the east,
was quick to defend settlements
where they had established
bases, but nothing more.
And like a sacrificial swine,
Nil Kamui's land was carved
and slowly devoured by
the two infiltrating powers.
Amidst it all,
the island's Red Dragon deity
was suddenly
overcome with madness
and began razing villages,
killing indiscriminately.
Imperial Era 3015, September.
When all was said and done,
the country was no longer ours.
[KA GRAVA] As I said,
Red Dragon gave me a message.
He told me this back then,
and I now believe
I know what it means.
[RED DRAGON]
My dear friend.
A day will come when
I am greatly changed
from how you have known me.
No. It will be much
more dire I'm afraid.
[KA GRAVA]
What do you mean?
[RED DRAGON]
When it does,
go to Ogani Volcano.
That is likely the last place
I can maintain my sanity.
Or some semblance of it.
[KA GRAVA]
Red, are you trying to tell me
you'll leave something
there to be found?
[RED DRAGON growls]
[IBUKI]
Wait, that's all he said?
There wasn't anything more?
But this message...
Can we trust anything
that Red Dragon says?
[KA GRAVA]
It's what I was told.
I'll let all of you decide
whether you believe it or not.
Ugh.
[GAKUSHO]
Hey! So tell me, folks...
Where can a girl
get a bath around here?
Uh! General Gakusho?
[KA GRAVA]
A bath, you say?
Yeah, getting all my troops
stationed was pretty grueling,
so I'd like to take
a relaxing soak,
but, damn, this place
of yours is so big!
[SOL sighs]
Then follow me, General.
Come, I'll be happy
to show you the way.
[GAKUSHO] Oh, you're a
mixed one, and a cutie, too!
Stabby as well.
Ooh! Heh!
[MERYL] That's General Gakusho,
the Leader of One Thousand?
[doors rattle]
[SWEALLOW] Wow, Kouran
sure is diverse, isn't it?
Wait, so you want me to
speak with General Gakusho?
Yeah. About how both
of our forces
can coexist here in Haiga.
I do agree that's
an important topic.
But wouldn't that be your job
as ambassador, Sir Sweallow?
U-Um, well, yeah,
you see, about that...
[chuckles nervously]
What he means is he's just
recently arrived in Nil Kamui.
So you're more
knowledgeable than he is.
Um, yeah! What she said!
[ULRIKA giggles]
Plus, this just came together
on Ka Grava's whim.
Mm. Understood.
Do your best!
'Kay, Ulrika?
[sighs]
[ENUMAEL]
Sir Sweallow Clazzvali.
Yeah, that's me. And you are?
I'm Father Enumael Meschwitz,
bishop to the military
forces of D'Natia.
May I ask for a moment of your
time, Sir Black Dragon Knight?
Uh... Sure thing.
Ah, that's the ticket...
Hot damn, this bath is
really hitting the spot!
So... Do you have to be
in here with me right now?
We were informed this
bath is open to ladies,
only during these hours.
I mean I want some privacy.
[LOU]
Oh, come now, General Gakusho.
I do believe I know of
your particular "tastes."
I'd love to get to know each
other on a personal basis.
So... Would you be interested?
No! I'm here to finish
what Kohkaku started!
Wait, Kohkaku?
[GAKUSHO] She promoted me so her
death hit me quite hard
and I've heard a rumor that
she was slain by someone
from Kohran and not
by a rebel soldier.
Impossible! That can't be!
Lady Kohkaku had been planning
to find and exterminate
Red Dragon before the
combined expedition could.
With her now gone, I'm going
to carry out that plan
in her place.
Therefore, my main force
will be heading out
to Ogani Volcano tomorrow.
Sorry, but that's the way it is.
[ULRIKA] No, a bath
is not what I requested!
[SHADDY] But, ma'am, I was
instructed to bring you in here!
[ULRIKA] Wait! What are you
taking off my armor for?!
[SHADDY] I have to!
It'll rust if I don't!
[SHADDY grunting]
--[SHADDY] There!
--[ULRIKA gasps]
[GAKUSHO] So... I understand
you wanted to meet with me?
[ULRIKA]
Um, yes, General Gakusho,
but I was hoping to meet
somewhere more private.
'Ey, come on, now.
You can't get much more
private than a ladies' bath!
Normally, yes, but there
are others present here.
[GAKUSHO]
Oh, them?
You know they're part of the
combined expedition, right?
[ULRIKA]
You're allies of Sir Sweallow?
[EYKHA grunts]
Feel free to bare your soul
or anything else in here.
[ULRIKA whimpers]
Notification was sent
to both Kouran and D'natia.
All military action
was ordered withheld
until the expedition
finds Red Dragon.
So then why did you
attack Haiga?
[GAKUSHO] It was because
there was rumor that Ka Grava
was backing the
revolutionary army.
But it was just a
misunderstanding.
According to the
pact we just made,
D'natia and Kohran won't
conduct any battles in Haiga,
which means it
won't happen again.
So we're good now, 'kay?
Well, I guess that
concludes our meeting.
Ah... No, wait.
Huh?
[ULRIKA] When it come to
our countries' policies--
[GAKUSHO]
Let me stop you there.
I'm a soldier, not a--
--[IBUKI grunts]
--[GAKUSHO gasps]
Oh, no! I'm so sorry!
Aw, if it isn't
the little Imperial.
Little Imperial?
So, he's part of the
expedition, as well?
[grunts] Uh, excuse me.
But have either
of you seen Eykha?
Would you believe this
adorable little thing
came close to assassinating me?
[IBUKI gasps]
Yeah, but--!
That power...
If you really do have it,
you should never use it.
But then again...
Is there something
you want so bad
you'd be willing to lose
everything to gain it?
Um, I don't know.
[GAKUSHO]
Honest, aren't you?
General Gakusho...
All that hostility she
showed me earlier is gone now.
Well, Sir Sweallow,
just what are you going
to do with this thing?
[SWEALLOW] A power that can
paint everything in black, huh?
[ENUMAEL] This item is called
the "Black Dragon's Scale."
Whoa, really?
According to legend,
it was created by alchemists
using a scale that
came from Black Dragon,
the guardian deity of D'Natia.
The Black Dragon, huh?
In Nil Kamui, both the power
of the Black Dragon Knights
and the magic of Kohran
aren't nearly as effective
as they are in their
native homelands.
You've noticed this,
haven't you?
I have, and for the life of me,
I couldn't figure out why.
Ever since we got
to this country,
I haven't been as powerful
as I normally am.
Because this island is
under the influence
of Red Dragon's power.
However... that's done!
[BOTH gasp]
[ENUMAEL] With this powerful
scale that I offer to you,
Nil Kamui's magical balance can
shift to that of Black Dragon.
In fact, if used properly,
the entire island
can be placed under the
power of Black Dragon,
and by proxy, D'natia.
Every aspect of this island,
from its water to its crops
to all of its numerous living
creatures are harmonized
through Red Dragon's power.
If that is forcefully
changed, then--
That is something
a mere attendant
such as yourself
needn't be concerned with.
[MERYL sighs]
[ENUMAEL "If it can defeat Red
Dragon, then it must be used."
That was our Emperor's order.
So this is our trump card
to defeat Red Dragon?
[ENUMAEL]
Yes.
I have faith that
you will use it wisely,
and lead D'natia
to a bright future.
[IBUKI]
As for me...
...I'm going to Ogani Volcano.
[KA GRAVA] Then does that mean
you believe the information
that I related to your group?
[IBUKI] Yes. I do, and
that's why I need to get there
and see Red Dragon
as soon as possible.
I'm sorry, but I'll understand
if you don't come along, Eykha.
If that's your choice,
Ibuki, I'll come with you.
As will I, but what about
the rest of our band?
[gasps]
[SWEALLOW] If I have to use that
scale, then no, count me out.
[LOU] Will you be joining us,
Sir Black Dragon Knight?
[SWEALLOW] But you have
to go through the desert
to get to Ogani Volcano.
That's pretty dangerous!
[ULRIKA]
Yes, that's true.
However we'll escort them
to Fort Rosweisse
to keep them safe.
Wha--?! I mean,
of course we're going.
--Well, congratulations.
--Huh?
You've gained yet another
attractive companion.
Aw, knock it off, would ya?
[KA GRAVA]
Well then, it's settled.
Shaddy, Sol.
Can I leave the rest to you?
--Yesiree!
--Yes.
[LOU] Does that mean
you're going with us?
[KA GRAVA] Didn't I say
Red Dragon was my friend?
I can't turn my back
on a friend in need.
Besides, don't you folks
need supplies and provisions?
[gasps]
That's very kind of you, sir.
Plenty of dishware will be
required on this expedition
due to a certain someone,
so the Sherbet Company
will gladly provide that.
[SWEALLOW] Geez, way to
make me feel guilty, Meryl.
[MERYL, ULRIKA, LOU giggle]
[SWEALLOW] Is it okay to
leave General Gakusho behind
like this?
[LOU]
Actually, she left us behind.
[MERYL]
What?
[LOU] It seems she's already
on her way to Ogani Volcano.
[SWEALLOW]
Well, isn't that a coincidence?
She and I are both from Kouran,
but I can't understand
her thinking.
[EYKHA]
Where's Ibuki?
He's speaking to Ka Grava
about something.
Oh...
[IBUKI]
So, Ka Grava.
Were my father and all the
previous kings before him
granted this same power from
Red Dragon that I've described?
[KA GRAVA] Hmm, let me see
if I understand this:
your power lets you take one's
life with the flames
of Red Dragon, but to do so,
you must offer another one's
life to Red first, correct?
Yes, and the person
whose life is offered
is someone precious
to me, and so far,
it's always meant
the life of a friend.
[KA GRAVA]
Truth be told,
I've never heard of
such a thing before.
Well, what about Red Dragon
going insane?
Could that be why I've
been cursed like this?
[KA GRAVA]
Possibly, but history does note
a certain king of the dead.
[IBUKI]
Who was that?
[KA GRAVA] An Imperial who
possessed a disturbing power.
It allowed him to raise anyone
he killed from the dead,
and reanimate them
as a Returned One.
A Returned One?
So then you mean a member
of the living dead?
But... I thought those
things were just legends.
[KA GRAVA]
I've never encountered
any Returned Ones before.
But legend says that those
slain by the king of the dead
will always rise
as Returned Ones.
Gathered together, they will
form an army of the unliving.
[IBUKI] Is that a power that
Red Dragon granted as well?
[KA GRAVA] A dragon has the
power to revive someone
as many times as needed, and the
power to take someone's life.
So if I were to guess,
I would say yes,
since killing and reviving are
two sides of the same coin.
Well, if I had my way,
I would only want the power
to revive someone.
[SWEALLOW grunting]
[MISKA]
What are you doing?
That was supposed to be
two days' worth of water
for everybody!
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to cool off
a little since it's so hot out.
Leave it to Sir Sweallow to
put comfort over survival.
[KA GRAVA] Hmm, my Ka Grava car
has a little water stored
in reserve that we can use,
but I'm afraid it won't
last us very long.
Then I suggest that I go
ahead to find an oasis
where we can renew our supply.
Once I have, I'll rejoin you.
You'll be okay by yourself?
[LOU]
Yes. I'll be just fine alone.
[QI SHA TIAN LING] Exactly
where are you headed, Lou?
[LOU] To ensure no one else
gets to Red Dragon first.
He will be yours, my lord.
[MALE VILLAGER A groaning]
Um, what's with
the teeth-gnashing?
Well, ma'am. We're
not exactly sure yet,
but all who've fled the
areas around the volcano
are acting like him.
Returned Ones... Yes,
that's what those things were.
What else could walk
through the lava
as if it was nothing at all?!
[sobbing]
So Returned Ones, huh?
Do creatures like that
even really exist?
Question them and see if they
know anything about Red Dragon.
Right!
[gasps]
[GAKUSHO] You...
So that's why you're here.
I have no doubt that you
feel indebted to Kohkaku.
Even so, there's no way a
level-headed general like you
would go up against Red Dragon.
Unless, of course,
you had some secret weapon.
Huh. One derived from
Lady Kohkaku's work
and recently sent
from our homeland.
They call it the Gold Wedge.
[LOU]
Hmm...
It's quite marvelous.
According to my intel,
it will shift the balance
of this land's magic to Kouran.
What's more, the magic of
both D'Natia and Nil Kamui
will be severely
weakened as a result.
That means Red Dragon will, too.
My, my, what a frightening
item to possess.
[GAKUSHO]
If you want it, take it.
Very well, I will then.
[GAKUSHO] Wait.
There's something else
I wanna give you...
...your death.
As rumored, I see you
have no problem in killing
even your own people,
Lou Chun Wah!
I don't know what you've got
planned, but you made a mistake
by killing one
of my personal guards.
[gasps]
What a beautiful sword.
It's simply incredible.
Hand it over!
[LOU] Why do that when you
already have that rifle?
[gasps]
I don't want it anymore!
But what I do want
is that sword!
[QI SHA TIAN LING] It seems
the Leader of One Thousand
had a counter skill ready.
So she was able to
divert my strike a bit.
I doubt that she'll
divert this next one.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
No, don't bother, Lou.
She won't survive much longer.
Leave her paltry soul and keep
the female Black Dragon Knight
from getting away instead.
Black Dragon Knight?
Wait, you mean Ulrika?
[QI SHA TIAN LING] I'm sure her
soul will be even more
satisfying than this one's.
[LOU growls]
[GAKUSHO grunts]
[FEMALE SUBORDINATE A]
Lady Gakusho!
[FEMALE SUBORDINATE B]
What happened?!
Quick, summon the medics!
[GAKUSHO whimpers]
[FEMALE SUBORDINATE B] General?
What are you trying to say?
[SWEALLOW]
Fort Rosweisse is pretty close.
So the volcano
isn't far, either!
[MERYL] Sorry we lost
another knife, everyone.
Well, if it bothers
you that much,
then why don't you feed me?
No matter what
instrument he uses,
it seems to break
without fail, doesn't it?
Poor guy...
[SWEALLOW] I've actually
had to deal with it
ever since I was a little kid.
It's the price of my power.
You've had it for that long?
It seems like it causes you
an awful lot of trouble.
Don't you ever wanna
get rid of it?
Well... Yeah, I've thought about
how my life would be without it.
because sometimes
it feels like a curse.
Just like Sir Sweallow here,
you think your power
is a curse, too,
don't you, Ibuki?
Yes. I do.
So if I can find a way
to be done with it.
No, you can't be serious!
Don't waste such
a wonderful gift!
I can't really weigh
in here, because...
...I haven't seen Ibuki's power
in action or even heard much
about it, so maybe
one of you guys
can explain it
to me, like, Eykha?
Or maybe... Lou?
[ULRIKA]
Excuse me.
Duty requires us to hurry
ahead to Fort Rosweisse.
I'll leave Miska here with you.
[KA GRAVA] Yes, that's fine, but
tell us, did something happen?
[ULRIKA'S MALE SUBORDINATE A]
The Returned Ones.
--[KA GRAVA] Hmm?
--[IBUKI gasps]
[ULRIKA] Villagers who
live near the volcano
have fled to the fort.
They claim that Returned
Ones have appeared.
[MERYL] You're serious?
The risen dead of island legend?
[ULRIKA] Yes, and I believe
their claims are mistaken.
But I still have to
investigate them.
Bye.
[gasps]
[ELEPHANT trumpets]
[FEMALE SUBORDINATE A snarls]
[MISKA]
Stop it! I said... stop!
[FEMALE SUBORDINATE A grunts]
[FEMALE SUBORDINATE B grunts]
These soldiers...
Are they all Returned Ones?
[ELEPHANT trumpets]
You're kidding!
Ibuki! Sir Sweallow!
General Gakusho...?
It can't be...
[GAKUSHO rasping]
She's a Returned One?!
[IBUKI gasps]
[NARRATOR] Act Six.
Six Paths of Transmigration.
A young man placing faith
in his ideals offers his life
to Ibuki to avert a crisis.
And as Ibuki learns, reunions
are not always a blessing.