[IBUKI]
Agito!
I will save Lady Inori.
[IBUKI]
Agito! Be careful!
And please save her!
Where is Ibuki?
Where is my dear brother?
[SOLDIER A]
Man, look at this stuff!
I can't believe they
just left it all behind!
[SOLDIER B] I guess now that
their Child of Contract's dead,
Nil Kamui doesn't see
the value in much anymore.
After seven long years,
this war's finally over.
My father's gone.
Why is this happening to us?
[BOTH grunting]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[AGITO]
Time's running out.
I think you'd better leave.
But you're the one who
told us to come in here
and take what we want!
Well it's your lives
on the line.
Uh!
[SOLDIER B]
Will you hurry up?
Just forget that old box!
[SOLDIER A]
All right, fine!
[AGITO]
In that case, I'll take this.
These fools don't realize
they're passing up
Nil Kamui's greatest
treasure: the Dragon Eye.
There are supposed
to be two of these,
but the other was given to
Kouran's "spiritual mother"
at this war's inception.
[AGITO]
Princess?
Agito. Tell me!
Why have you done this?!
[HANDMAIDEN grunts]
[AGITO grunts]
[HANDMAIDEN groaning]
[INORI gasping]
Help me.
Brother.
You have to save me.
I need you.
[AGITO gasps]
[RED DRAGON]
Pledge yourself to me, Imperial.
Bond with me, and obtain
power for yourself.
[INORI]
Red Dragon called out to me.
And when I heard his words,
I realized I had been waiting
my whole life for that moment.
With that, I made my vow.
Just had to get me
in private to talk.
Well... Brother?
Is what you said before true?
[INORI] What, that
Mashiro's a Returned One?
Why would I lie about that?
Honestly, I was under
the impression you knew.
[IBUKI]
That's not what I'm asking!
I want to know how you were
able to do something like that.
[INORI]
Isn't that obvious?
This is the power Red
Dragon has given me.
You can raise the dead? Really?
[INORI] The ability to
take lives is a necessity
for a king's aide.
That's why you have it.
But the king is responsible
for deciding who lives.
So I was given power
worthy of that role.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[INORI] The name of our
country is Nil Kamui.
It's a small island nation.
Three years have passed
since our land fell
to the great neighboring
nation of Kohran.
Despite the conflict, neither
the allied State D'natia,
nor our guardian deity Red
Dragon bothered to defend us.
I lost everything
in this conflict
known as the Seven Year War.
Our castle.
My purity and innocence.
Even the brother
I love so dearly.
Imperial Era 3015, October.
Nil Kamui was ours once,
and it will be again soon.
Oh! How absolutely dreadful!
To be stuck in the same
room as a Returned One!
[MERYL] But Bishop, you've
been traveling with Mashiro
as Lady Inori's attendant
for a while now.
[ENUMAEL]
I've had more important concerns
than the condition of
the lady's equerry!
So mind your tone!
[SWEALLOW growls]
[ENUMAEL] And besides,
Inori is only under my care
because Agito handed
her off to me.
[KA GRAVA] Agito, as in the
leader of the revolution?
That's really surprising.
Kinda goes against what
the revolution stands for.
Considering they want
their independence back,
it's hard to believe they'd
actually ask D'natia for help.
He didn't have much choice
after he was imprisoned.
His only hope of
furthering our goals,
was in pursuing D'natia's
support toward our future king.
Which would thereby assure
an alliance with Nil Kamui.
And then together, they
could drive out Kohran
without upsetting the
internal power structure.
Right. That said,
even I wasn't aware of
what Mashiro really was.
[LOU]
I've heard that dragons
are capable of
reviving after death.
And if that is indeed
a matter of fact,
creating a Returned One could
be an extension of that skill.
Then, that would prove Inori has
been accepted by the dragon.
[INORI grunts]
[KA GRAVA groaning]
I can't believe
he's so paranoid,
he'd bug his own room!
[INORI giggles]
What was he thinking?
We wouldn't know?
Honestly, how rude.
[KA GRAVA sighs]
[IBUKI] It doesn't matter
if they listen in or not.
Because I won't keep a
secret from my friends.
[INORI]
And what about from me?
When we lost our home,
I was alone with no one to
turn to. So I ran by myself.
I did a lot of things I'm
not proud of to survive.
[IBUKI]
I'm sorry. Oh, Inori.
I wish that I had been
there to protect you.
[INORI]
The only person I trust
in this whole world
is you, my brother.
You have to feel the
same way about me!
Since you can't trust
the combined expedition.
But why?
[INORI] The only thing they care
about is destroying Red Dragon.
Because once he's dead,
they can finally take
control of Nil Kamui.
Are you going to let them take
our home again, brother?!
[EYKHA]
Ibuki!
[gasps] Are you all right?
[KA GRAVA] I take it you two
are finished speaking?
Yes. Now I'm certain
Mashiro is a Returned One.
You're saying Inori really
brought her back to life?
[ENUMAEL]
How absurd!
Who said you could do
such a terrible thing?
Now come along! We
need to have a talk!
[SWEALLOW]
That was fun.
He was sure quick to ditch
all that "my lady" talk.
It's sad, but
should be expected
considering we're merely
D'natia's puppet. Pardon me.
Anyway. Where do we
all go from here?
[EYKHA] First, I will
dispose of Mashiro.
You will not!
[gasps] Why?
Because... I have
to sort things out.
I'm sorry, but please
give me some time.
[SWEALLOW grunts]
[MERYL gasps]
What the hell?
It feels like my contract
seal is burning.
[knocking]
[MERYL] Sir Sweallow!
Are you all right?
[SWEALLOW groaning]
Sir Sweallow! Something's wrong.
[groaning]
[BLACK DRAGON]
Sweallow Clazzvali.
Hear me, cursed child.
Because of your efforts, Nil
Kamui is in a state of change.
The land is being painted black.
[SWEALLOW]
Well, that's what your scales
were supposed to do, right?
[BLACK DRAGON]
True.
It shall not be long before my
essence has consumed that land.
Then I will preside over it
in addition to my kingdom.
[SWEALLOW gasps]
[BLACK DRAGON] Of course,
in order for this to happen,
I must take possession of
the red one's power as well.
Thus, it would appear you still
have work left unfinished.
About that.
Once the State Magic
Territory becomes D'natia's,
what's going to happen then?
To Nil Kamui's people?
[BLACK DRAGON] The citizens
shall remain unharmed.
However, they will no longer
be capable of magic.
Furthermore, the bonding of
beasts and man shall cease.
As will the lives
of such creatures.
Impressive. That's supposed
to be a good thing?
As a token of my gratitude, I
shall bestow upon you a gift.
I refer to it as
the "Black Curtain".
For it will veil you from
any external danger.
[roars]
[SWEALLOW screams]
Sir Sweallow!
[panting]
Hey. Tell me. Did you feel that?
[MERYL]
It was Black Dragon.
But how's that possible
when we're in Nil Kamui?
What can I say?
When you're popular like me,
no one cares about distance.
I suspect he's not happy about
me trying to protect Ibuki.
Oh, no...
Look, if you're nervous, I won't
blame you for going back home--
[groans]
[groaning]
So useless.
[INORI]
Don't you understand
what I'm trying to
tell you, brother?
I never wanted to be
D'natia's puppet,
but we can use it
to our advantage.
If we rebel, the revolutionary
army will rise with us
and we can take
them by surprise!
Together, we can finally
reclaim our home!
[IBUKI] If I join you, what am
I supposed to tell the others?
What will it take
for you to get this?
They're our enemies.
We're going to
have to kill them.
Because, eventually, they're
going to try to kill you.
[IBUKI]
No way!
They wouldn't do that to me.
[BLACK DRAGON] Ah. I can
hear your cries, young one.
And though you are not my child,
I will answer your call.
[IBUKI]
Red Dragon?
I didn't call you!
[BLACK DRAGON] Though I am
one of the Seven Dragons,
you are mistaken
as to my identity.
Yet, despite my body
residing in D'natia,
you still hear my
thoughts clearly.
Black Dragon.
[BLACK DRAGON]
I know you yearn for your island
to be returned
to its former order.
That is something only those
of my country can accomplish.
How so?
[BLACK DRAGON]
Kouran wishes to subjugate you
and those of your land.
The revolutionary army fights
against their persecution.
No matter the outcome, the blood
of many will continue to pour.
That is not your wish.
If you align with us, I vow that
your citizens will be unharmed.
That can't be. No way!
[BLACK DRAGON]
Such an alliance
would also benefit you
personally. After all,
it would finally bring about the
end of your cursed existence.
[IBUKI]
Red Dragon's power.
How?!
[BLACK DRAGON] You are
familiar with the concept
of a "State Magic
Territory," yes?
At the moment, Nil Kamui's
is shifting dramatically
to match D'natia.
Upon its completion,
Red Dragon will lose
his dominance,
and you will at last be
freed from your suffering.
But why? Is Sweallow to blame?
[BLACK DRAGON chuckles]
The fate of your country rests
in your hands, Imperial!
[IBUKI screams]
[BLACK DRAGON roars]
[IBUKI]
Ah!
D'natia.
Kouran.
They all act like they
know what I should do.
But, how come none
of them have advice
for handling Mashiro?
Where is she?
[SOL]
That bald blowhard came back
and dragged her off with him.
Said they had to
interrogate her
and that she'd be restrained in
the embassy for the time being.
[IBUKI] And you didn't do
anything to stop him?!
[KA GRAVA] He reminded us
she's Inori's attendant.
It was out of our hands.
She's still Mashiro.
Even if she's a Returned One.
[LOU]
There's your kindness again.
Listen, I understand what
you're going through.
Feeling such devotion. Still.
Once something's gone, it can
never be like it was before.
Uh!
Loss is inevitable
as you get older.
But it's because
we can lose things,
that we consider them
precious to us.
[LOU]
Uh...
[SWEALLOW]
Hey, Ibuki!
We were looking for you!
Uh!
[IBUKI] Sweallow's
D'natia's representative.
[IBUKI grunts]
[SWEALLOW]
Hey! Where ya goin'?
[IBUKI grunts]
Whoa, now. Where's
the fire, kiddo?
Oh. Sorry, uh...
I'm being followed!
[BYAKUEI]
Uh?
Shoulda known. Leave it to
D'natia to bully some kid.
[SWEALLOW]
Well, when you put it that way,
it does look pretty bad.
[MERYL] Could you defend
your image for once?!
[BYAKUEI] I don't know
what's going on here,
and honestly I don't care.
There's no way I'm turning my
back on a kid who needs help.
That's great! Ya hear that?
This guy's an
upstanding citizen!
How can you say that when he's
picking a fight with you?
[ULRIKA]
Sir Sweallow!
[SWEALLOW]
What's wrong, Ulrika?
Wait, Ulrika Ledezma?
They're Black Dragon Knights!
[ULRIKA] You know full well we
have a peace treaty with Kouran.
So explain yourself.
[SWEALLOW]
No, listen, it's cool.
He's actually a good guy!
[MERYL] You don't know
anything about him!
[SWEALLOW]
Mm?
[KOURAN SOLDIER A]
Sir Byakuei!
[KOURAN SOLDIER B]
Where are you?!
Hey, over here!
Sorry, got lost in the crowd!
[laughs]
This guy's... Byakuei?
[BYAKUEI] Guess I should
have introduced myself.
Probably not the best
first impression
considering I'm Kohran's
new representative.
I was actually headed to
Rosweisse to meet you guys.
Wait. I'm lost.
This man is Sir Byakuei.
But he's more commonly known
as the Leader of Ten-Thousand.
A Great General of Kouran.
I have to meet
with him, so move!
[GATE KEEPER A]
I'm afraid I can't.
The Bishop wants no disruptions.
[IBUKI, RED DRAGON]
You will!
None shall stand in the way
of Nil Kamui's imperial!
[IBUKI] Mashiro!
It's me! Where are you?!
[gasps]
[INORI] Ka Grava's such a riot!
He's wiretapped this whole city!
[laughs]
[IBUKI] I was told they
were holding Mashiro here.
Yeah, but... It's no big deal.
What do you mean,
"it's no big deal"?!
If the bishop really wants to
make you king like he says,
there's no way he'll let
a Returned One live!
Even one so docile.
So what? He can kill
her if he wants to.
I'll bring her back to
life again every time.
By the way, that also means
you can use your power
without any fear
of repercussion.
Well? Go wild!
If you don't know
where to start,
I think you should
nix that girl Lou.
[gasps]
After all, that sword she wields
makes it impossible to
revive Returned Ones.
And I want to see
what you can do.
Your gift from Red Dragon must
be amazing, dear brother.
Too bad. I'm never
using that power again.
Besides, if I were to kill Lou,
you'd have both Sweallow
and Ka Grava to deal with.
[INORI] I don't see the problem,
we'll just kill them, too.
Besides, you know the
expedition only formed
because they wanted
to kill Red Dragon.
Oh, but if you're
particularly fond of them,
I can always bring them
back to life for you.
Inori.
Don't worry. I'm more
than used to it by now.
[RED DRAGON roars]
[INORI]
I get it. I understand.
You're doing all of this for me.
Because I have so much rage and
sorrow that I can't let out.
More. It's not enough.
Destroy it all!
Burn everything!
It's what they deserve
for watching idly
as my life was stolen from me!
They're just as guilty as
those who attacked us.
They should all be incinerated!
And from the ashes, we'll
bring back the people we like.
Then, once Nil Kamui is
full of Returned Ones,
we'll have a home that's
kind to us again.
[INORI laughs]
[IBUKI] She honestly believes
Red Dragon's rampage
was a tribute to her. Is his
madness controlling her, too?
At this rate, Inori might
actually kill us all.
[laughing continues]
[IBUKI]
I think you're right, Inori.
But we should go to
Shuka's prison first.
[INORI]
Huh?
[IBUKI] Seeing as D'natia
won't support us anymore.
If we're going to place
you on the throne,
we'll need to get
Agito out of jail.
You mean it?! Oh, brother!
I can't tell you how happy I am!
Yeah, me, too.
[IBUKI] This whole time,
the other expedition members
have been protecting me.
They've made so
many sacrifices.
I won't let anyone hurt them.
Not even you.
--[crash]
--[gasps]
[whimpers]
[FUGAKU]
Stay there, Ibuki.
[IBUKI]
What's going on in here?
Mashiro?
[gasping]
[knocking]
[SHADDY] Excuse, me!
I brought your dinner.
Are you in there?
[EYKHA]
So Ibuki hasn't come back yet?
No, I guess not.
[IBUKI]
Fugaku. Tell me what happened.
[FUGAKU]
All right. But it was awful.
Enumael was angry and
wouldn't stop slandering us.
He said we were all
savages and heretics,
and that he was going to
have Mashiro exterminated.
[FUGAKU]
I think all the commotion
unleashed something within.
Because that wasn't Mashiro.
[ENUMAEL GUARDS grunt]
[ENUMAEL gasps]
[MASHIRO grunts]
[ENUMAEL GUARDS yelp]
[MASHIRO laughs]
[ENUMAEL GUARD B groaning]
[MASHIRO yells]
[ENUMAEL whimpering]
[MASHIRO laughs]
Get away. Stop!
[ENUMAEL]
Holy spirit!
[FUGAKU]
Lady Inori watched in silence
as the bishop took
his last breath.
[INORI]
There you are!
Are you ready to
go now? To Shuka?
[IBUKI]
Not just yet. This first.
[INORI]
No. You two can talk later!
[FUGAKU]
Wait, what are you doing?
[INORI]
What's wrong, brother?
[IBUKI screams, cries]
But... Why?
You know that doesn't
accomplish anything.
I'll just bring her back.
[IBUKI]
Red Dragon.
[gasps]
[IBUKI]
You told me before,
I can offer you a Returned One
as long as the person
was important to me.
I will pledge Mashiro
to you again.
No matter what she
has become, her life
is still precious to
me! Do you accept?
[RED DRAGON] Indeed. I
acknowledge the equivalence.
You can't.
[IBUKI] By the oath
between the Red Dragon
and the Child of Contract...
Your body and soul will be
completely incinerated.
And you will never rise again!
Perish!
[IBUKI]
Mashiro.
Can you possibly remember
what the last thing
you said to me was?
Just be a good king, Ibuki.
I will.
I haven't forgotten.
[NARRATOR] Act ten.
Narrow Escape from Death
Even the pure intentions
of Lady Ulrika turn to lust
before Qi Sha
Tian Ling's gaze.
Only the holy spirit's
glimmering light
can protect her in
this darkest of hours.