[EYKHA]
Ibuki!
[IBUKI gasps]
You should have yelled
for me to help you!
Hold on a second!
That's Gakusho, not an enemy!
[GAKUSHO moans]
Please, stop!
Val. Again!
[VAL roars]
[EYKHA gasps]
But how? She's dead!
[ULRIKA] Are you absolutely
certain this was Gakusho's unit?
[SUBORDINATE A]
Based on their trajectory, yes.
I believe so.
What could've happened to them?
[SUBORDINATE B]
Ma'am!
We've discovered a survivor.
A Returned One! A Returned
One did this to us!
Our encampment has been
inundated with refugees
making similar claims, despite
how farfetched they sound.
That's actually why we're here.
All right, tell me.
Are the Returned Ones
coming from your village?
It's not just from within.
The wound on her neck
had to be fatal.
She was dead! Kouran's general!
[ULRIKA]
Wait a minute.
Someone managed to
kill Lady Gakusho?
[VILLAGER A]
But then she revived.
[ULRIKA]
As a Returned One?
[VILLAGER A] She started
killing everyone around her,
but then they all
resurrected as well.
Just like what happened before!
Just like back in my village!
Well, that's unexpected.
I've never heard of an
instance where those killed
by Returned Ones became
such themselves.
Nor I. But the
question now is:
where are they going?
Could it be...?
Uh!
[IBUKI] We hail from a country
known as Nil Kamui.
It is but a small island nation.
One day, we were invaded by the
great ancient country of Kouran.
And in their avarice, a third
of our land was pillaged.
D'natia, an ally
State to the east,
was quick to defend settlements
where they had established
bases, but nothing more.
And like a sacrificial swine,
Nil Kamui's land was carved
and slowly devoured
by the two infiltrating powers.
Amidst it all, the
Red Dragon deity
lashed out upon the people.
Soon after, the Returned Ones
of legend appeared as well.
Imperial Era 3015, September.
When all was said and done, the
country was no longer ours.
[IBUKI gasps]
[SWEALLOW]
You okay?
Wait is that...?
Is Gakusho up there?
What's happened to her?
[SWEALLOW grunts]
[KA GRAVA grunts]
Ibuki, are you unharmed?
[gasps]
[RETURNED ONES groaning]
[KA GRAVA] Hm. It would appear,
despite their present condition,
destroying their brains
is quite effective.
[SWEALLOW]
Ha! Thanks for the insight!
[SWEALLOW grunts]
--[IBUKI gasps]
--[KA GRAVA] Mm?
[KA GRAVA]
Now, might I recommend
we all make a hasty retreat?
[GAKUSHO moaning]
[IBUKI]
Gakusho!
[EYKHA]
Stay back!
[KA GRAVA]
What a surprise.
You have only known
Gakusho a short while,
yet you are awfully
invested in her wellbeing.
I owe her! She taught
me a lesson.
And renewed my resolve!
[KA GRAVA] But what is
before us now is not her.
Further, there are no records
claiming a Returned One
has ever regained itself after
the metamorphosis has occurred.
[IBUKI]
Uh...
[MERYL] That means there's
only one thing we can do.
We must find a way to help
her soul rest in peace.
No matter what.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
[VAL growls]
I can't accept just putting her
to rest until... I know why!
[GAKUSHO moans]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
How interesting.
It has such a unique flavor,
and yet, it is reminiscent
of a dragon.
[LOU]
So that means...
The Returned Ones
and Red Dragon...
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
...are most likely connected.
You need not worry, Lou.
Any foe that we dispatch
is incapable of reviving.
After all, whatever souls
may have remained
within those vessels
now reside in me.
[LOU]
Yes, my lord.
[EYKHA]
All we can be sure of
is that the wound on her neck
means she was murdered.
She was? Why?
[KA GRAVA]
The question is not "why,"
but "who could kill an
adversary such as Gakusho?"
[IBUKI]
Hear me. Red Dragon!
[IBUKI] The person before you
is someone precious to me.
She could have been my
friend in time. Tell me.
Would you accept
her as an offering?
[RED DRAGON ] Indeed. Do you
have need of my power, Imperial?
Yes, I do.
I need your flame to kill
the one who did this to her.
You're willing to sacrifice
what's left of Gakusho,
so you can avenge her?
Yes. That's the
best I can do now.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Oh-ho-ho.
Quite an interesting plan
that boy has devised.
The dragon's power,
is it really as
versatile as that?
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
The Returned Ones
are a byproduct of the Red
Dragon. Because of this,
I would wager he is already
aware of who killed Gakusho.
And that his flames
would easily find you.
Good to know.
Normally, I would
take that bet.
However, it would
likely prove difficult
to serve my lord if I
found myself incinerated.
[QI SHA TIAN LING laughs]
[RED DRAGON] My flames
will reach any target
regardless of their location.
Okay. Accept... my offer!
[LOU] Even at this range, I can
kill him using my Bai Bu Quan.
Sad that it had to come to
this, Child of Contract.
But I'm afraid you've
left me no other choice.
[SUBORDINATE D]
Lady Ulrika.
[ULRIKA]
What's the status?
[SUBORDINATE D] Ma'am, it
appears the Kouran woman
is staging a coup.
She's targeting the other
expedition members to kill--
[screams]
Soldier!
What is going on
out there? Tell me!
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Ironic.
You were so on guard
it made you vulnerable.
[GAKUSHO moaning]
[IBUKI gasps]
Please forgive my late
arrival, my lord.
Hien, you just... No.
I'm honored you remember
me. Have no fear.
Agito has given me orders to
act as your personal guard.
Good thing. To think Gakusho
would use the truce
as a cover to make an attempt
on our Child of Contract's life!
[IBUKI cries]
You fool!
Uh! What is the
matter, my lord?
How could you, Hien?
Gakusho was...
She was important to him.
What nonsense!
[HIEN]
Lord Ibuki. Please stand up.
We can't allow our people
to see you in this state.
Kneeling over the corpse
of a Kouiran General--
[EYKHA]
Stop it!
Having his best interest at
heart won't make you friends.
That's some nerve.
I am merely a loyal subject,
I would never overstep
those bounds!
[IBUKI cries]
[ULRIKA] Thank you all for
coming on such short notice.
[SWEALLOW] I hope
you guys don't mind,
but you're not gonna
be able to walk around
the fort unsupervised.
There's a lot of secret military
stuff here that we
can't let outsiders see.
[LOU]
Naturally.
[ULRIKA]
Lady Lou Chun Wah?
Yes?
[ULRIKA] I was wondering if you
had seen one of my subordinates.
He still hasn't returned
after the recent deployment.
[LOU] Curious. I was under
the impression D'natia
used something to
contact people far away,
not unlike our
Communication Seals?
He isn't responding.
That certainly is troubling.
However, I'm afraid I
don't know anything.
[KA GRAVA] You're saying there
were more Returned Ones
outside of Gakusho's unit?
[ULRIKA] Correct. The
foot of Ogani Volcano
is surrounded by
different villages.
Hordes of Returned Ones
began attacking them,
and not long after, those
who had fallen revived.
Any idea where the first
batch came from?
That might explain all this.
According to the few survivors,
The earliest raid was
conducted by beings
sporting revolutionary
army garb.
[HIEN] Are you trying to say
that we're the ones to blame?
[EYKHA]
Wait.
Were they the members
of the first expedition?
[ULRIKA]
It would appear so.
After all, word is one of your
battalions had approached
the volcano about a month ago.
[RED DRAGON roars]
[EYKHA] They rose as
Returned Ones? All of them?
[SWEALLOW] What's the deal
with this, Ka Grava?!
I mean, am I wrong, or
are we saying Red Dragon
is responsible for everything
that's going on here?
[KA GRAVA]
Perhaps.
Do you believe that we
should question his claim
of leaving something
behind at Ogani Volcano?
That doesn't change anything,
we still have to go.
There's something else.
As we speak, Simeon,
the Black Dragon Knights'
third corps leader,
is headed toward us.
[HIEN]
Wait, he's on his way here?
[LOU]
Huh.
[SWEALLOW]
That's great! But, uh...
Who is that again?
He leads the squadron
of soldiers our country
has deployed to this island.
Ranked third of the
Black Dragon Knights.
Oh, that's cool.
On the subject of rank,
uh... What's mine?
Why, you're the 30th, of course.
Dead last.
Uh...
Soon, everything will
be made right again
because Simeon will be
here to save the day.
You have a lot of
confidence in him.
Yes, I do. So now...
You can leave the
rest of this to us.
[ULRIKA] You're still set
on going to Ogani Volcano?
I have to. There's no way I
can just sit back and watch.
Not after what
happened to Gakusho.
Well then, at the very least,
you should allow my unit to
accompany you on the journey.
You'll still help us?
[ULRIKA] I consider
it my personal duty
to protect this island's
citizens and maintain order.
I can't turn a blind eye when
the people are in need.
[HIEN]
Lord Ibuki.
I've been told about the
power you now possess.
Hien.
I beg you, once Simeon
arrives, take my life.
You want me to use the dragon's
flame to kill him, don't you?
[HIEN]
Of course!
It will spark the fire of
revolution throughout the land!
My lord. We'll rid Nil
Kamui of occupation!
There is absolutely no way
I'm killing you or Simeon.
And it wouldn't
make a difference.
You don't know what you're
talking about, so forget it.
Nothing will happen if I hurt
you. It'd just be a waste.
No, it wouldn't.
As our lord, all the people of
our country are bound to you.
You can use us as offerings.
That's not the point, Hien!
Perhaps.
But kindness clouds
your judgment.
The Seven Year War
took my family.
Not even my little
sister survived.
And a part of me died
along with them.
But that's why I'm
the perfect sacrifice,
no one will mourn my death.
So if the Child of
Contract needed my life,
I would give it with pride.
You see? Please don't
hesitate on my behalf!
That's not why!
I hope I'm not
interrupting anything,
but our ride is
waiting for you two.
[IBUKI]
Right.
[HIEN] I should be used to
such disrespect from Kouran!
[LOU]
Sorry?
[HIEN]
Whether he acts like it or not,
Lord Ibuki is the
successor to the throne.
You will address him properly.
Oh, my, how could I
have been so rude?
So it's "Lord" Ibuki, yes?
Hey, Lord Ibuki?
Did Hien tell you
to call me that?
Please just ignore him.
Why, too much?
If you want, we can ease you
into it by calling you "sir."
[laughs]
[IBUKI]
Uh...
[SWEALLOW]
So Meryl told me
that you were planning
to kill Gakusho,
and that somehow
you'd be able to
destroy her murderer
because of it.
Well, technically
Red Dragon would.
I think I get it.
In exchange for the
life of someone else,
the Dragon grants you--
Perhaps it would be wise to drop
the subject, Sir Sweallow.
You've known about this
all along, huh, Lou?
Why, of course not!
It's such a frightening thought.
I agree.
Now I get why you
called it a curse.
You mind if I ask
you something else?
Do you really wanna rid
yourself of that power?
How can you afford to if
you're going to become king?
[gasps]
It's scary.
But something like that could
come in handy for a monarch.
Maybe, but that's not the
type of king I want to be.
I lost a friend recently.
She thought I could put an
end to people's sorrow.
I want to.
But with this power...
I can't.
Guess not.
Anyway.
I'm actually in favor of
you losing that ability
in the long run.
[LOU]
Of course you are.
A weapon like that is a
major threat to D'natia.
[SWEALLOW]
Ha! You think so?
[REVOLUTIONARY ARMY gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[ULRIKA] There was supposed
to be a village here.
[SWEALLOW] Looks like it's
just a big lava pit now.
[REVOLUTIONARY SOLDIER A]
Look!
[SWEALLOW]
Well, that's not a good sign.
[HIEN gasps]
[SWEALLOW]
Really not looking like
there's survivors
waiting for rescue.
Everyone! Let's go!
Hien! Hold on!
What are you doing?!
We will handle the
Returned Ones ourselves.
Continue on!
But that's suicide!
[RETURNED ONES moan]
[HIEN] This is how it has to be.
They're from the revolution.
Which makes them
our responsibility.
We'll help you!
You can't waste time!
So go!
And pray that our
fallen comrades
may finally rest in peace.
[HIEN]
Now, men. Attack!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[RETURNED ONES groan]
[SOLDIERS groan]
I, for one, think we
should appreciate
their most generous
martyrdom. After all,
we're supposed to find Red
Dragon, not fight dead things.
Not you... Izun.
Oh, no.
[MERYL] That's the giant
you told us about?
All right, everyone.
What's the plan?
I would like to take this
moment to remind you all
that leaving and letting
Simeon handle everything
is still a viable option.
[MERYL]
Sir Sweallow.
[SWEALLOW]
No, seriously, listen.
That thing is enormous!
There's not a chance in
hell that we can beat it!
Right. I absolutely agree
with you on this matter.
Even at the expense
of our mission,
we can't risk Ibuki
or Eykha's safety.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I meant!
[EYKHA]
I'm staying.
[SWEALLOW]
But why?
[EYKHA] Because I believe
Izun would want me
to free him from this
terrible existence.
[KA GRAVA] Additionally, just
in case you haven't noticed.
[SWEALLOW]
What is that?
[KA GRAVA] I believe it
is Red Dragon's talon.
[EYKHA] He engaged the
Red Dragon by himself
so Val and I could escape.
That's the only
reason we're alive.
[SWEALLOW] The claw must have
broken off in the battle.
[KA GRAVA]
Indeed.
It must also be what
my friend left behind.
[QI SHA TIAN LING] Oh...
This area is teeming with life!
Is it, my lord?
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Even in their present state,
the dragon's nail and that
colossus contain more life
energy than any normal person.
I've never experienced
anything like it!
[LOU]
What would you have me do?
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Feed me!
Yes, Lord.
[LOU]
All right, I have an idea.
We'll make a united attack
from two different angles.
I will cross the lava
to strike from behind.
[EYKHA] While we
attack from the front.
[IBUKI]
Before we do,
we have to make sure there's
no hope of saving Izun.
Only then will we fight.
Ibuki.
[IBUKI]
He's become a Returned One,
but that doesn't mean he's
completely lost control.
We have to know for certain
before we decide to kill him.
[EYKHA]
Understood.
You two. I'll need your help.
Are you with me?
Okay. I'll just try to slow
it down then. Good luck!
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Are you honestly humoring him?
No, but I need to
find a blind spot
so you may be hidden
while you feast.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
How thoughtful of you.
After all, it's always
nicer dining in privacy.
[VAL roars]
[SWEALLOW]
All right. Give it to me.
I'm sorry, sir, but I
think you've forgotten.
Forgive me as I
remind you, but...
this item will disrupt
the natural order of...
Ready?
If you're not too busy,
I think it's time that
we joined the others.
[SWEALLOW]
Actually, I'm afraid it's not.
I'm going, but I need you
to take care of Meryl.
And watch our backs
from a safe distance.
Uh? Don't take this
the wrong way,
but you're going
to need my help.
[SWEALLOW]
I know you're strong.
That's exactly why I'm
asking this of you.
And when we find we're
at the end of our rope,
you might have to save some of
us. Just get the kids out first.
[MERYL]
I guess in the end,
Sir Sweallow isn't
concerned about me at all.
The thing he's really worried
about losing is the future.
Hold on.
Are you trying to tell me you're
willing to give your life
for the expedition?
[SWEALLOW] Well, it's
the first time anyone's
asked me to do something
for them, y'know?
Wanna see it through.
One thing.
Under no circumstance can you
trust that Kohran woman, Lou.
[SWEALLOW]
Hmph. I'll be fine.
She's not the first girl who's
tried to pull a fast one on me.
Your master is quite
the good man.
I suppose he's all right...
for a good for nothing.
[NARRATOR]
Act Seven.
"Ups and Downs in Life."
Nothing lasts forever
in the test of time.
And as the embodiment
of that rule,
no one knows this better
than Sweallow Clazzvali.
Is it wrong to dream
of eternity?