[RED DRAGON growls]
[RED DRAGON roars]
[IBUKI]
Eykha!
Stop! That's enough!
[RED DRAGON roars]
Eykha!
Sorry I'm late! I got
here as fast as I could!
This thing is gonna work, right?
We can stop Red Dragon with it?
[SWEALLOW]
The Dragon's Claw.
I hope so, but I
do have my doubts.
Doubts? What do you mean?
As long as Inori's around, the
dragon will continue to revive.
So even if we manage to
defeat the dragon with this,
it'll all be for nothing.
But maybe doing so...
...is the key to bringing
Red Dragon back to sanity?
And if so, the person
who wields this weapon
should be someone
related to Red Dragon.
Meaning it can't be me.
[KA GRAVA]
Now wait a second.
Don't forget, Ulrika
sacrificed herself
to entrust the
Dragon's Claw to you.
[SWEALLOW] Maybe so, but
she's no longer with us.
There's only one person this
claw should be entrusted to.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Now, Lou!
The dragon!
Let me savor the supreme
life ruling this world!
Feed me its power!
[LOU]
Why, of course, my lord!
All our travels,
all our plans,
everything has been building
up to this very moment!
[INORI]
No way!
[RED DRAGON roars]
[LOU] The State Magic Territory
has shifted to that of Kouran!
With that, even Red Dragon
will lose its power!
One!
Two!
[RED DRAGON roars]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Ah! Yes! This is it, Lou!
Indeed, my lord.
[RED DRAGON roars]
[INORI]
How dare you!
All you outsiders
tainted Nil Kamui!
I'll make you suffer!
[RED DRAGON roars]
[CIVILIANS scream]
[KOURAN SOLDIER A] What
business do you have here,
Black Dragon knight?
[SWEALLOW]
U-Uh, uh. Hey, everybody!
I'm here to--
[BYAKUEI] Hold your fire!
Stand down and make way!
Greetings, Sweallow.
What do you need?
[SWEALLOW]
Ah, Byakuei.
I was wondering if
the Qilin Chuán
could possibly be launched?
Who told you about that?
Either way, deploying it
doesn't happen so easily.
Ka Grava and I came up with
a plan that implements it.
What kind of plan?
[SWEALLOW]
Heh.
Either you listen,
or I fight you and force you
to hear what I have to say.
It's your call.
[gasps] Fine. Let me hear it.
[LOU]
Seventy-one!
Seventy-two!
Seventy-Three!
--[LOU laughs]
--[RED DRAGON roars]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
You're wonderful, Lou!
Marvelous! The greatest
user there is!
[LOU]
Ah! Thank you, my lord.
[RED DRAGON roars]
[IBUKI]
Eykha.
Lou, are...
are you all right?
I'm going to kill Red
Dragon, no matter what.
And I won't let anyone
get in my way!
[gasps]
[BYAKUEI sighs]
So, it seems Lou
has changed the Magic Territory.
[SWEALLOW] That's actually
why I wanted to borrow
the Qilin Chuán. Now that
the State Magic Territory
has shifted in favor
of Kouran's power,
our best chance against
Red Dragon has come.
[MERYL] We know this is
an absurd request, but...
Won't you please consider it?
By order of Líng Mu, the
Qilin Chuán will be used
for the purpose of aiding
in Kouran's escape.
[MERYL, SWEALLOW sigh]
[BYAKUEI] But, I can't abandon
citizens in danger and in need,
even if they are of
another country.
[MERYL]
Then?!
There's a first time
for everything.
Like disobeying...
a direct order.
[BYAKUEI] In the name
of the heavenly Lord.
I request for the dispatch
of the Qilin Chuán!
Encantation Jí jí rú lú lìng!
[BOTH gasp]
[SETSUREN] Hm. Is he
actually planning to ram
the Qilin Chuán into
Red Dragon? Ridiculous.
Foolish Kouran.
I'm sure this involved Ka Grava.
[IBUKI]
Eykha!
Where are you?!
Hear me, Red Dragon!
Hear my words as
the Child of Contract!
[RED DRAGON]
Child of Contract.
[IBUKI gasping]
[RED DRAGON] The despair
your sibling bears is darker
than dark itself and her flames
of wrath are burning strong.
Even the pangs of
my consciousness
are about to be
swallowed by her anger.
[RED DRAGON roars]
Wait, that's...!
[SWEALLOW] Ibuki! This
is the Dragon's Claw!
[MERYL grunts]
[SWEALLOW] You're the one
who should be using it.
I'm counting on you!
[MERYL]
Do you think he'll understand
the meaning of that claw?
[SWEALLOW]
All we can do now...
is just believe that he will.
But now, even if Red Dragon
regains its sanity,
in order to truly defeat
Inori, Ibuki will still--
Oh, he has his equivalences.
There's Ka Grava, Lou,
and myself, as well.
Out here on this
field of battle,
there are many that
he holds precious.
What in the world
are you saying?
[RED DRAGON roars]
[SWEALLOW grunting]
[MERYL gasps]
[MERYL]
Quick! Use the Black Curtain!
Protect yourself!
[SWEALLOW] I can only use
that barrier once a day.
I need to save it until the end!
This is no time to be stingy!
You may not get to the end!
--Unbelievable!
--[SWEALLOW laughs]
[SWEALLOW] Ibuki. I know
you're going to struggle now
and beyond that. Please.
Let me help you just
a little bit more.
We are friends, after all.
[IBUKI]
Val!
Eykha! Eykha!
Come on, answer me!
Say something! Don't give up!
[IBUKI cries]
[IBUKI]
Eykha.
My travels began when I met you.
You're not my sword. Not at all.
You're precious to me.
I won't let this happen.
I won't let you die!
[EYKHA]
I... Ibuki.
[IBUKI]
Uh! Eykha!
[EYKHA] Listen to me.
My life is about to end.
So with what little
time I have left,
I want to use it for you, Ibuki.
[gasps] No, you can't!
I'll fix this, I promise.
Wait here for me.
[EYKHA]
Ibuki.
[RED DRAGON roars]
Red Dragon.
You will hear me.
[INORI]
Hello there, Dear Brother.
[IBUKI] I'm sorry I
couldn't protect you.
But we need to put an
end to this already.
This is not the
behavior of a king.
A king does whatever
a king wants to do.
Dear Brother.
Inori!
If you die and become
a Returned One,
then you'll go back
to being the kind,
wonderful brother
I used to like.
What a plan! Why didn't
I figure that out before?
It's just ingenious, right?
[IBUKI gasps]
[INORI]
Incinerate him!
[RED DRAGON roars]
Uh!
Ka Grava! What are you doing?!
[KA GRAVA laughs]
Whatever I can.
I'm pretty sturdy, you know.
I... I can't control it!
Whoa! Hold on!
What are you doing?!
Whatever I use falls apart.
But at the very moment
that happens,
I can draw out all of its power.
And that goes for everything,
even a warship like this.
Ah! No! Please!
My clan put over 100 years
into the building of this ship!
[SWEALLOW] If it breaks,
then make it again!
What?!
New things are only born into
this world out of destruction!
[BYAKUEI] You're planning
to expend this ship
just for that one moment?
That's the sin we
as humans hold.
The price that we have to pay.
Hm? Wait. Now I get it.
I think that's what my curse has
been about this entire time.
[BYAKUEI growls]
Damn it!
I am going to punch you later!
Fine! Let's do this!
[SWEALLOW]
Byakuei!
Huh?!
I believe we need to actually
survive in order for you
to be properly punched, Sir
Sweallow. So make it happen.
Good point, Meryl.
[SWEALLOW yells]
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Before the Black Dragon knight
gets in the way of our plan,
let me drink Red Dragon's
life bone dry.
Sound good, Lou?
No, my lord. Not yet.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Hmm?
Sweallow!
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Wait, Lou!
Now is the time
to kill Red Dragon!
Actually, now is the time
for me to defeat him!
That's Lou? What is she up to?
[ALL grunting]
[MERYL]
You're almost there!
[SWEALLOW yells]
[SWEALLOW gasps]
Hey there, Lou!
What the--?
[MERYL gasps]
I thought you were all about
defeating Red Dragon!
[LOU]
I am.
But first, I'm
going to kill you.
What I stand for
would be tainted
if I simply let you walk away!
I won't allow that to happen!
[SWEALLOW]
That's quite an honor!
Unfortunately, you've come
a little bit too late.
[RED DRAGON roars]
[LOU]
Sweallow!
Contract seal, release!
Try this on for size!
Ha!
[SWEALLOW grunts]
[LOU screams]
[gasps]
[SWEALLOW grunts]
[MERYL]
Sir Sweallow, no!
[LOU]
Sweallow!
[MERYL]
Uh.
Get out of my way!
Black Dragon! I call
upon the Black Curtain!
[MERYL gasping]
[SWEALLOW groans]
[MERYL gasps]
[LOU]
Uh! [laughing]
[MERYL]
Sir Sweallow!
[BYAKUEI grunting]
[KA GRAVA]
And that's that. Now, then.
It's my turn, Ibuki.
You mean you were
planning this all along?
[KA GRAVA]
Listen to me.
Your words should
reach Red Dragon now.
[IBUKI gasps]
[INORI]
What are you saying?!
Seems you've forgotten:
Red Dragon is immortal!
[VAL roars]
Eykha!
Val, why? Why did you...?
[EYKHA]
Remember? I want to...
be your sword until
my very last breath.
No, please!
That's the last thing I want!
[IBUKI]
Wait... maybe...
[BOTH gasp]
Hear me, Red Dragon!
Answer my call!
Reclaim your soul and your
place as Nil Kamui's guardian!
You've recovered me from
my madness, it would seem.
You have my gratitude.
You truly are the
king of Nil Kamui.
What is it you desire?
I have traveled long and
far for the opportunity
to return this curse to you.
[RED DRAGON]
Curse?
You wish to return to me the
power granted from our contract?
[IBUKI] No. Right now,
I need this power.
And because of that,
I'll live with this curse
as long as I have to.
But I do still desperately
want to sever
this sad chain of events.
If so, then offer
me the equivalence.
My equivalence, huh?
All right.
I will offer you the life of
the one I hold most precious.
But, I want you to keep
a promise for me.
[RED DRAGON roars]
[INORI] How dare that
monster! Red Dragon!
Use your power!
Burn them all to ashes!
[RED DRAGON]
Uh-uh.
Huh?! What's the matter?! Huh?
Uh!
I've noticed throughout
my travels
that Lou, Ka Grava,
Sweallow, and Eykha
all shared one thing in common,
they've sacrificed
many precious things.
[IBUKI] Losing things
forced us to move forward.
But, I didn't want
to lose anything.
I tried my best not
to take anyone's life
or lose anything precious.
But I've learned that...
by doing so, I've simply lived
while taking something
precious from someone else.
I've made my choice.
I know what I must protect.
And who I have to sacrifice.
[KA GRAVA] The time has
come, Ibuki. Now, do it!
[IBUKI] I will offer Eykha's
life to Red Dragon.
[gasps] Mm.
[KA GRAVA]
Ibuki!
Eykha.
I understand.
[INORI]
No! Stop, Dear Brother!
Don't do it!
Red Dragon! I order
you to destroy them!
[RED DRAGON grunts]
[INORI whimpers]
[IBUKI]
Listen to me, Eykha.
[EYKHA]
Mm.
[IBUKI] I'm going to do
something horrible to you.
You probably won't
forgive me for this.
[EYKHA]
Ibuki.
It's okay.
[IBUKI]
Even then, I will protect you.
[EYKH groans]
Inori! I promise you!
How could you?
I refuse to repeat the horrible
things you went through!
No.
[IBUKI] I'll make a
country without sorrow!
Brother, please. Don't do this!
[INORI screams]
Sleep, Inori. Good night.
My Dear... Brother.
Not too bad of an ending at all.
I will reward you for all
your deeds in these matters.
[SWEALLOW]
Uh, if you're thinkin' about
lifting my curse, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
[BLACK DRAGON]
Oh?
[SWEALLOW] This "curse" of
breaking in order to create,
is something that we
as humans must bear.
And so I want to see exactly
what the future holds in store.
[MERYL cries]
[SWEALLOW grunting]
Uh! Sir Sweallow.
Uh? Well, looks like
I'm not done here yet.
Black Dragon still wants
me to live, it would seem.
[MERYL sobs]
[SWEALLOW gasps]
You...
[cries] ...low life!
[SWEALLOW yelps]
Ouch!
--[MERYL] Horrible!
--[SWEALLOW groaning]
--Selfish!
--Low life!
--[SWEALLOW groaning]
[LOU]
Huh?
[LOU gasps]
[QI SHA TIAN LING] It looks like
we can have fun again, Lou.
Indeed, my lord. [laughs]
[BYAKUEI] Our spiritual
mother has reviewed
and sanctioned Nil Kamui's
proposed new system.
[SIMEON] We were finally
able to receive approval
from our country as well.
And now we can focus
on its restoration.
[BYAKUEI] So. With that,
may we consider it final
that both D'natia and
Kouran officially
approve of the new king?
Yes. There are no objections
from the council.
Now then, I believe it's time
to bring in the new king-to-be.
[smack]
Uh. I'm sorry.
But, Ibuki has requested
that we briefly delay
the crowning ceremony.
Okay, then I will
offer you the life
of the one I hold most precious.
But I want you to keep
a promise for me.
I want you to take
a part of the life
that Val has remaining
and give it to Eykha.
Can you do that?
[RED DRAGON] I can.
But doing so would mean
that two lives that
were once separate
will come together as one anew.
Even if she gains a new life,
her soul will not be
the same as before,
both in memory and in mind.
Knowing that this
would be the outcome,
do you still wish to proceed?
Both Eykha and Val have
little time left to live.
If I offer Eykha
as a sacrifice,
I can protect her.
Even if it turns out
that Eykha won't be
the same person
I know right now.
I want her to live!
Last of the Dragon Shrine
Maidens. Arise and awaken.
I have bestowed upon
you a new body and soul.
[EYKHA]
How odd. I feel like...
Like I need to see someone?
Then trust your feelings and go.
I know.
[IBUKI panting]
[EYKHA] That I'll travel
with you again someday.