You want to be... my friend?
I do.
You may call me Lou Chun Wah.
A pleasure, yes?
Sure it is.
And your name's Ibuki?
I believe you're also a member
of the Red Dragon expedition.
[SWEALLOW]
Now I get it. Hi there.
So I guess you must be the
missing member of our party.
[IBUKI] We hail from a
country known as Nil Kamui.
It is but a small island nation.
We were invaded by the great
ancient country of Kouran.
And in their avarice, a third
of our land was pillaged.
D'natia, an ally
state to the east,
was quick to defend settlements
where they had established
bases, but nothing more.
And like a sacrificial swine,
Nil Kamui's land
was carved and slowly devoured
by the two infiltrating powers.
Despite all of this,
our guardian deity,
the Red Dragon,
did not protect the land.
Imperial Era 3015, September.
When all was said and done,
the country was no longer ours.
[SWEALLOW]
All right!
Now that we're all here,
it's time to begin
the combined expedition!
Tomorrow, we'll be packing
up and leaving Shuka.
We'll then be traveling to
the independent city of Haiga,
where there's a guy
who knows the Red Dragon!
Did I get all that right?
Surprisingly, you did.
I was expecting you
to forget most of it.
[SWEALLOW]
Well, my mind is pretty sharp.
Now. Who's hungry?
If we're going to be spending
a lot of time together,
we should all get
to know each other!
And what better way to open up
than grabbing a hot meal
before going on an adventure?
I'm sorry.
There's something
that requires my attention.
But please feel free
to go into town without me.
We must also refuse.
I don't think it
would be appropriate
for us to act
so informally yet.
If you'll excuse us.
I'd be more than happy
to join you for dinner.
[SWEALLOW chuckles]
I guess that
worked in your favor.
You must be so thrilled.
Meryl, it's not like I'm trying
to get to know her
personally or anything.
It's for the good
of the mission.
[laughs]
You understand, right?
Oh, yes, absolutely.
[SWEALLOW] And what'd be
extra good for the mission
is you digging
into her background
while I keep her entertained.
[sighs]
Fine. I'll see what I can do.
Good luck.
[SWEALLOW]
One more thing.
Could you maybe
lend me some money,
so I'll be able to pay?
[MERYL]
Enjoy your time out on the town.
[IBUKI]
Mashiro and Kai.
Please rest in peace.
Fugaku has gone
to report to Agito.
Agito?
The leader of
the revolutionary army.
And I have been
appointed your escort.
Wait. There's a whole army?
[SWEALLOW]
Can I ask you something?
It's about that big box.
It looks really important,
so what is it?
Your weapon?
[LOU]
Not exactly.
It's so much more than that.
The object inside
is my very life.
It transcends weaponry.
Guess that means it's something
you can't use carelessly.
So it must be an heirloom
or a keepsake then, right?
Why is what's in my
box of such interest to you?
Oh, it's not!
[chuckles]
See...
The thing about me is,
I can never keep a tool
or a weapon for very long.
When I use an item
like that, sometimes...
Okay. Just about every time,
the thing falls apart
as soon as I'm done using it.
Yes, I see that.
I've never gotten
sentimental about an item
in my entire life.
I guess that's
why I was so intrigued
by the way you
talk about that thing.
It's a foreign concept to me.
Sorry if I was being too nosy.
People don't always choose
which tools they get to use.
The tools are the ones
who choose their users.
[SWEALLOW]
Wait, so...
Are you trying to tell me
your weapon chose you?
[LOU] Why does that notion
seem to surprise you so?
Have you never been chosen?
That would suggest items
don't like you very much.
[WHISPERING, CRYING]
[SWEALLOW] I never
thought about it like that.
Wow. Huh.
[EYKHA] So you're the one
who runs this store, Meryl?
[MERYL]
Yes.
It's actually a branch
of the Sherbet Company,
but I'm the one who manages it.
Wait, how can that be
when you're so busy
attending to Sweallow?
It's not really
that complicated.
Actually, it's simple.
You see, I maintain
Sir Sweallow's assets.
To keep him from
going bankrupt again.
Done!
I'll have the rest of the
luggage couriered for us.
Let's grab a bite
before we head back, okay?
That's a good idea--
I'm sorry. I can't.
I'll return to
the inn on my own.
[door closes]
[DRUNK 3A]
Well, it's like I always say:
"Sometimes ya gotta--"
[grunts]
What the--? Hey!
[DRUNK 3B]
Better let it go.
That girl's a Bounded One.
Messin' with her'll
pro'lly cost ya yer life.
But if it makes ya feel better,
ya won't see her again.
Their kind never live long
bein' tied to monsters.
[DRUNK 3A]
Still...
Her owner could've
at least thrown her
in a pen or something!
[laughs]
[trumpets]
What a cry!
Are we really
riding those things?
Yes, we are.
How about that!
We'll be traveling in style
on those Gadanans!
Right, Ibuki?
I suppose so.
What was that?
I mean...
Was it something I said?
Perhaps he's not as excited
about joining the
expedition as you are.
No one's forcing him to go.
he joined of his own volition.
But never mind that,
where are we going again?
Have you already forgotten
what you said yesterday?
Well, I said a lot
of things yesterday!
[MERYL] Right now,
we're here in the town of Shuka.
As you should know,
our destination
is Haiga to the south.
It's a neutral city and
said to be the home of someone
who knows the
Red Dragon personally.
This someone is Ka Grava,
more commonly known as
"the Undead Merchant."
As it happens,
Ka Grava owns Haiga.
And if that's not enough,
ercent
he supposedly owns five
of the world's total capital
on top of that.
He's our only lead to
the Red Dragon's whereabouts.
Any information he has
could be vital to our cause.
Well, it looks like we're set.
You ready, Miska?
Sure. You can count on me.
All right.
Then our combined
expedition departs now!
[FUGAKU] Aren't you
the least bit concerned
that joining forces
with Kouran and D'natia
will only preserve their power?
[AGITO] So long as Ibuki
is a member of this
"combined expedition,"
Kouran has no reason
to make an attempt on his life.
Which works in our favor,
as it gives us time
to finalize our plans.
How can you be so sure?
Because once the
expedition is on its way,
our young lord will be
drawn to the Red Dragon.
It won't be long before he's
brought back to his roots.
Try to have a little
more faith in the boy.
Everything is going
to work out just fine.
[FUGAKU]
Sir.
[chuckling]
Now then...
Seeing as the dragon's
flames are so hungry,
who will they consume next?
[IBUKI] The Red Dragon's really
responsible for all of this?
I must find a way
to make things right.
[IBUKI yells]
[PIG MONSTER growling]
[EYKHA]
Val!
[IBUKI]
Eykha!
Run! Now!
Your friend...
He's hurt.
What if you need help?
[EYKHA]
Just get out of here!
Behind you!
[IBUKI]
Eykha...
[EYKHA] The next time
you're in danger,
you need to raise your voice.
It is my responsibility
to ensure your safety.
Why, because Agito
said you had to?
Yes, I am.
Will you please let me
ride on your friend's back?
That's not the only reason.
I'm sorry.
Meryl, quit being so paranoid.
She isn't just
marrying me for my money--
What the--?!
Oops, hope I didn't
wake you, Sir Sweallow.
[SWEALLOW]
'Course not.
You're as quiet as a mouse.
Sorry, but I thought
you'd be interested
to read my findings on Lou.
Here.
'Kay. Let's see...
"Lou is an assassin
in Kouran's secret society.
A highly skilled member
of the Eight Claw Clan."
Agh. Gimme a break.
Why'd that have
to be her profession?
And now we're stuck
on this expedition with her.
So, what now?
We're almost
in Kouran territory.
If we want to take action,
now's our best chance.
Yeah, I know that.
There's not much time.
But it's not like
she's caused us trouble,
so we shouldn't
get ahead of ourselves.
Besides...
It's not like we
have much room to talk.
We have our
own orders to follow.
And the Black Dragon
was awfully specific.
[MERYL]
Kill the Red Dragon at any cost.
[QI SHA TIAN LING] I must say,
this island has proven
full of worthy prey
to feast upon.
[LOU]
Yes, my lord.
And, given time,
I will present to you
the finest of courses.
The Child of Contract,
and the Black Dragon knight.
Then at the end of it all...
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
...The Red Dragon itself.
[yawns]
[SWEALLOW]
So...
I guess this means we're all
gonna be staying here tonight?
[MERYL] Well, Jinrai
serves as headquarters
for Kouran's occupation forces.
Seeing as Lou
is out doing recon,
we should at least
wait for her to get back.
[SWEALLOW]
I suppose.
Hey, Ibuki.
How about you take
this meal out to Eykha?
Why me?
Well, because,
I thought she'd like it more
if it came from
a friend, y'know?
Maybe.
[IBUKI]
But I'm not her friend.
Are you hungry?
I brought your food.
Thank you, but I'm fine
eating whatever Val gets.
You eat that?
But why? You're a human.
[EYKHA] That's not
what other people say.
They think I'm less than human
because I'm bound to a monster.
To them I'm a tool.
I fill a purpose
until I'm discarded.
That's wrong.
No one should ever
be treated that way.
[EYKHA]
Mashiro used to say that, too.
But it's not like
Bounded Ones live long anyway.
Yeah, but...
Let me tell you
a story from when I first
joined the revolution.
[MASHIRO] I'm sorry, but this is
all I can give you right now.
[EYKHA]
Thank you.
But I cannot accept this
as I have no way to repay you.
Actually, you can
do something for me.
You're strong.
So I'd like you to help me
protect my friend.
The friend she spoke of...
It was you, so I will
protect you, just as she asked.
[IBUKI]
But you shouldn't.
Because I'm the one
who killed Mashiro.
[EYKHA]
That may be so,
but she accepted
her role as a sacrifice.
The Red Dragon
required your friend.
Then I don't need friends!
I can't go through that.
Not again!
[QI SHA TIAN LING] So Kouran's
forces have surrounded Haiga.
This may complicate matters.
[LOU] I believe it's of
no concern, my lord.
Not while I'm
part of the expedition.
What's this? Oh, my.
[REMNANT SOLDIER 3A]
Lou Chun Wah.
Give yourself up.
We've come to take vengeance
for the fallen Lady Kohkaku.
[REMNANT SOLDIER 3B] Regardless
of any secret assignment
you may be on,
your treason is unforgivable!
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
What perfect timing.
I was starting to
feel the pangs of hunger.
Delicious!
No point in letting a meal go
when it presents itself to you
so adamantly.
[LOU laughs]
[gasps]
What's the matter?
You should feel privileged
to serve my master!
[QI SHA TIAN LING laughs]
It's so beautiful!
I know. It's mine!
At last, there's a blade worthy
of being wielded by me!
You're wrong.
The only one worthy here is me.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
Ah! That was satisfying.
I am happy to be
of service, my lord.
[FEMALE ADJUTANT 3A]
Lady Gakusho.
Despite our efforts,
Haiga still has ample supplies.
And if that's not bad enough,
our own resources are dwindling.
Well, we have
been staked out here
for about a month now.
We'd better figure out something
before D'natia decides to get
involved, or we are so screwed.
[FEMALE ADJUTANT 3B]
There aren't a lot of options.
We have to take Haiga
before then.
[GAKUSHO]
Yeah.
If only because
there's a debt to be paid!
That merchant won't
be "undead" much longer.
They've been completely
surrounded as far as I can see.
How come?
I thought Haiga was neutral.
Yes, but the
intel I've procured
seems to suggest that
they've been secretly funding
the revolutionary army.
That's not the worst of it.
I have information.
Apparently D'natia forces
are on their way here
led by Lady Ulrika,
and once they arrive,
the city will
become a battlefield.
It's only a matter of time.
And our country's desire
to keep up appearances
won't help any.
[MERYL]
I'm not done.
According to the map,
the Undead Merchant's manor
is located near the coastline.
So it's fortified
by natural defense.
[SWEALLOW] Which means we'll
need one heck of a plan
to stand a chance
of getting inside.
We can wait for the conflict
between D'natia and
Kouran's forces to flare up,
and in the chaos,
make our way into the city.
How about a little
less death and destruction?
Then I suggest we
use our company ties
to negotiate our way through
the business structure.
If that were an option,
Kouran would have resolved
its issue peacefully by now.
Okay. Fine. Infiltration.
Just leave everything to me.
I'll take care of it.
[IBUKI]
Wait!
I know I might slow you down,
but please take me with you.
You want to go?
I do!
The Undead Merchant is said to
be a close friend to Red Dragon.
And since I'm an imperial
tied to the Dragon,
he'll listen to me.
He has to!
All right.
You can come with me this time.
After all, what kind
of friend would I be
if I didn't let you try?
We're really more
like acquaintances...
[LOU chuckles]
[IBUKI] I have to meet Red
Dragon as soon as possible.
It's my only hope
of preventing others
from being dragged
into this misery.
--[LOU] Here.
--[IBUKI] What are you doing?
--Ready?
--Oh, no!
Please put me down,
I can do it myself!
I beg you! Lou!
You should calm down.
You'll bite your tongue off.
This place...
[LOU]
It is quite unique.
I believe it is intended to be
the lord of the manor's study.
This is very strange.
It doesn't feel as if
anyone lives here at all.
[IBUKI]
Uh, hey, Lou?
Did you see something
moving over there?
[LOU]
Not that I noticed.
Look, there!
[LOU]
Oh?
[IBUKI]
I thought I saw...
Now, Ibuki.
You should know better
than to play tricks on adults.
[IBUKI yells]
[VOICE] Good morning,
I don't believe we have met.
I am Ka Grava Rai Fuu Gramstahl.
So he's the one.
You're the Undead Merchant?
[KA GRAVA]
Yes. That I am.
How would you like
to join me for breakfast?
Doesn't that sound pleasant?
[NARRATOR]
Act four. "Amid Enemies."
Haiga is on the brink
of being consumed by warfare.
But despite his anguish,
Ibuki must once again make
a choice for life or death.
Who can he save,
and what measures must he take
to protect them?