[IBUKI yells]
[VOICE] Good morning,
I don't believe we have met.
I am Ka Grava Rai Fuu Gramstahl.
So he's the one.
You're the Undead Merchant?
[KA GRAVA]
Yes. That I am.
How would you like to
join me for breakfast?
Doesn't that sound pleasant?
[LOU] Could you
keep it down, please?
You're giving me a headache.
Even with your Wu Xing Ti,
my fists are capable of
destroying you from the inside.
[IBUKI]
W-Wait a second! Please!
We're here to speak with you
about Red Dragon.
[IBUKI] We hail from a country
known as Nil Kamui.
It is but a small island nation.
We were invaded by the great
ancient country of Kouran.
And in their avarice, a third
of our land was pillaged.
D'natia, an ally state
to the east,
was quick to defend settlements
where they had established
bases, but nothing more.
And like a sacrificial swine,
Nil Kamui's land was carved
and slowly devoured by
the two infiltrating powers.
Despite all of this,
our guardian deity,
the Red Dragon,
did not protect the land.
Imperial Era 3015, September.
When all was said and done,
the country was no longer ours.
And who might you be?
Huh? Oh, come now.
Can't you at least
make an educated guess?
Hi, there!
My name is Shaddy,
and this is Sol!
Nice to meet you!
We were sent here to greet you
by order of Lord Ka Grava.
So are you both
Bounded Ones?
Well, Shaddy is.
Sol is a
human-monster half-breed.
He's a mixed one.
[EYKHA] The Undead Merchant
sends a Bounded One
and a Mixed One
as his messengers?
[SHADDY]
Yep!
Lord Ka Grava
treats everyone equally,
without judgment
or discrimination.
[SWEALLOW]
Is that so...
Enough with all this
prattling chit-chat.
The Kouran forces
surrounding the city
could find us
at any moment.
We need to get moving.
Uh... sorry about him.
He's always like this.
Right then. Let's head
to the city, shall we?
Sounds good to me.
[FEMALE ADJUTANT B] I apologize
for the intrusion, Miss.
I hope you have
a really good reason
for disturbing
my slumber like this.
What's going on?
[FEMALE ADJUTANT B]
Well... you see...
Ka Grava...
[GAKUSHO]
Was asleep?!
[FEMALE ADJUTANT B]
Yes, ma'am! Take a look.
[CROWD cheering]
[GAKUSHO] You mean to say
that during the one month
we surrounded him...
That tin can was actually
just sleeping the whole time?!
[CROWD cheering]
[KA GRAVA]
Ta-da!
[SHADDY]
Lord Ka Grava!
Our guests have arrived!
[KA GRAVA]
Oh!
So you're members of the
combined expedition, yes?
Welcome! Climb aboard!
We can have a
nice chat at my manor!
[GAKUSHO] So you finally
show up, do you.
Today is the day
I take my vengeance.
Nobody makes a fool of me!
[whirring noise]
[CROWD screaming]
I did it!
I killed Ka Grava,
once and for all!
Now to march in
and crush Haiga by force!
We must act quickly
before D'natia intervenes!
[FEMALE ADJUTANT 3B]
Right!
[MACHINE beeps]
Just look at what
they've done to you.
That overhaul
took an entire month!
[SOL]
Lend a hand, Shaddy.
[SHADDY]
Alley-oop!
[KA GRAVA]
Yes, much better!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
I must say,
Gakusho has quite a taste
for aiming at my
most costly part!
Wait, Gakusho?
As in the Kouran general?
[KA GRAVA]
The very same!
She was hailed as
being a master sniper
during the Seven-Year War.
Despite my selling her
guns and gunpowder,
she seems to have quite
the grudge against me.
There's no sense
in having all these guns
if we don't have the gunpowder
to actually use them!
The price of
gunpowder keeps rising,
not only in Nil Kamui,
but our country, as well!
I've no doubt Ka Grava
is behind it.
He's cornering the market!
That sneaky bastard!
He sold us the weapons
for dirt cheap
knowing that he'd bleed us
dry for the gunpowder!
[crashing noise]
Retreat! Move!
[FEMALE ADJUTANT 3B]
Yes, ma'am!
That tin can will
pay dearly for this.
[KA GRAVA chuckles]
[MERYL] She believes
you're supplying funds
to the revolutionary army.
Kouran's forces will lay siege
to this city because of it.
[KA GRAVA]
Hm...
Keeping Haiga's neutral position
is going to be difficult
in this situation.
This is the current image
of Haiga's main gate.
[LOU] Looks like the
pride of their military,
the steam tank brigade
is in position.
They aren't fooling around.
[KA GRAVA] Yes. Knowing
that D'natia is closing in,
it would appear that they're
going on the offensive.
Oh, I know!
Once the battle begins,
we can draw D'natia's forces in.
Confusion will arise
among both sides.
When it does,
we'll seize that opportunity
and assassinate
both their leaders!
[LOU chuckles]
Wow. Isn't that kinda...?
I feel the simplest approach
is the best approach here.
No! Wait!
We need to find a way
to prevent all of this
without hurting anyone!
For example...?
[IBUKI] Well, why not
try speaking with them
one more time?
Come on, Ibuki.
It's a little too late for that,
don't you think?
[LOU]
Not at all!
I agree!
I think it's a fine idea!
I'm sure we can
get them to listen!
[KA GRAVA]
Hm...
Well, how about
this then, Ibuki?
If you're able to avoid this
conflict through negotiation,
then I will acknowledge
you as being worthy
to hear the message
from Red Dragon.
Hello, Ka Grava?
You're still there, aren't you?
[KA GRAVA]
Oh! Lou!
What can I do for you?
[LOU] I hope you'll
forgive the intrusion,
but I have some information
on Ibuki to share.
[KA GRAVA]
Oh?
He holds strange
and mysterious powers
as a Child of Contract.
Yes.
I know for a fact
that he has the power
to kill anyone in front of him
in exchange for
another one's life.
[KA GRAVA]
Ah...
Is that why you
so suddenly supported
Ibuki's face-to-face
meeting idea?
Intriguing.
That's a harsh way
to negotiate, though.
How things turn out
is still for him to decide.
[IBUKI] I'll go even
if I have to go alone.
[KA GRAVA]
Oh, I won't hear of it!
Such a burden is too much for
one to carry by one's self.
[EYKHA]
Then I will accompany him.
[KA GRAVA]
Here. Take this with you.
[IBUKI]
What is it?
[KA GRAVA] It's my letter
of apology to Gakusho.
[IBUKI]
Apology?
[KA GRAVA] Yes, an apology
for the one month
that I've been asleep.
Whatever the case may be,
if an imperial delivers
this letter of apology,
I'm sure that she'll at least
read it and hear you out.
I'd like to avoid war, as well.
I wish you the best
of luck with negotiations
and in finding
a way through to do so.
[IBUKI]
Thanks!
[KA GRAVA laughs]
Look at you! All fired up!
That's the spirit, Ibuki!
That's the spirit!
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
I see.
So this is what you were hoping
and preparing for, isn't it Lou.
[LOU]
Yes.
If he uses
that ability again,
we may be able to determine
the true extent of the power
Red Dragon has bestowed on him.
We'll use this opportunity
to investigate them thoroughly.
[QI SHA TIAN LING laughs]
[FEMALE SPEAR SOLIDER 4A]
Lou Chun Wah.
This is as far as you will go.
[LOU]
Come on!
I'm the one who
guided them here!
All right, all right,
I get it!
Just remember:
I'll save you no matter what.
Nothing is going
to make me abandon my friend.
Are we clear?
I should be going.
I've heard that
Ka Grava's messenger
is a descendant
of the imperials.
but all I see is a kid.
Is that the sword?
[GAKUSHO] There. Now we'll
have a little privacy.
Come on inside.
[FEMALE ADJUTANT 3B]
We insist that you enter alone.
I'll be here
waiting for you.
Remember that.
[SWEALLOW] Exchanging
formalities with superiors
isn't really my thing.
They scare me!
[MERYL]
Oh, hush up with that!
Anyway, we have to do our part.
We need to buy
as much time as possible
while Ibuki is busy
with negotiations.
[SWEALLOW sighs]
[MERYL] I'm the one
who should be sighing here.
[SWEALLOW]
Hello?
Sorry, but we're looking
for someone in particular.
Does anyone know where
we can find Lady Ulrika?
You're looking at her.
Greetings,
Sir Sweallow Clazzvalli.
Ulrika Ledezma.
Acting subleader
for the third corps
of the Black Dragon Knights.
[giggles]
I'm the leader
of One-Thousand.
General Seisha of Kouran.
You may call me Gakusho.
And I'm Ibuki.
I bring you a letter
of great importance
from Ka Grava Rai
Fuu Grahmstahl.
[GAKUSHO]
Is that so...
I believe it's a
letter of apology--
Ka Grava's a fool!
Wait, what are you doing?
All right, that's
enough of this farce.
I only agreed to
this meeting with you
because you're an imperial.
Do you really intend to
attack the city of Haiga?
Well, of course I do.
I need to crush the source of
the revolutionary army's funds.
[IBUKI]
Even if that's true,
you'd be killing
innocent people!
I've lost a lot
of comrades myself
dealing with this.
Even my former caretaker
General Kohkaku.
[IBUKI gasps]
[GAKUSHO] This will even
things out a bit, kiddo.
[KA GRAVA] I wonder if Ibuki
has figured it out by now.
Gakusho has no intention
of even reading my letter.
She's in no way willing
to talk things out.
So in other other words, he--
[LOU] ...only has
one choice he can make.
If Ibuki wants to
put a stop to this war,
he must kill Gakusho.
[QI SHA TIAN LING]
With her out of the way,
the soldiers that remain
and D'natia's forces
won't be fighting in Haiga.
[LOU chuckles]
So that's it?
You don't have anything else
up your sleeve?
Really, "Mister Imperial"?
[IBUKI]
Ka Grava and the others knew
that this was going to happen
from the beginning!
Is killing her
really my only choice?
In order to do that,
I'd have to offer up another one
of my friends to the dragon!
But that's... It's just--
What's with that
look on your face?!
Eykha!
Ibuki!
That other brat?
You savages are
completely out of your minds!
[EYKHA]
Please shoot me.
[GAKUSHO]
Huh?
Use that weapon
and shoot me.
Eykha, are you...?
For her.
It'll be just like what
happened to Lady Kohkaku.
The dragon will destroy her.
[GAKUSHO]
What? What did she say?
Hurry!
Shoot me and kill me.
In order to kill Gakusho.
But you're--
You're not my friend.
It would be meaningless!
Only killing me
will determine that.
Wait!
If she dies, I'll die?
Is that what the deal is?
That's how they were able
to defeat the General?
[KA GRAVA] Gakusho is aware
of General Kohkaku's
untimely demise.
That will lead her
into believing
the power that Ibuki holds.
So doubt engenders doubt
in this case?
Is that it?
[IBUKI]
What should I do?
[RED DRAGON]
Do you seek power, imperial?
Wait, no!
[RED DRAGON] If my flames
are what you desire,
then you must offer me
an equivalent.
[EYKHA]
Ibuki...
I won't do it!
I don't want to kill anyone,
understand?
Killing others...
it never solves anything!
[GAKUSHO]
He's completely serious.
He honestly thinks
he can kill me.
Ibuki!
[IBUKI]
No... There has to be a way!
Ka Grava?
Would you just look at
what they've done to you?
That overhaul took a month!
Bastard!
He sold us the weapons cheap
just to bleed us dry!
[KA GRAVA] It's my letter
of apology to Gakusho.
All right, that's
enough of this farce.
[IBUKI]
I see!
She thinks Ka Grava died
when she shot him.
So if I let her know that
he's actually still alive,
it may lead me
to another choice!
General Gakusho!
Please! I beseech you!
Take a moment
to read that letter!
It was written recently
by Ka Grava himself!
Ka Grava is still alive!
He what?!
[GAKUSHO]
No way...
Even if he's some machine,
I put a bullet
right through his head!
Wait...
Maybe he is undead,
like his name implies.
[IBUKI]
It would only take a moment!
Please, if you want
to save yourself,
put down your weapon
and listen to me!
[GAKUSHO]
What now?
If Ka Grava is alive,
there may still be room
for negotiation.
But...
[IBUKI] After she reads
the letter, then what?
What's to negotiate?
If it doesn't work, I'll end up
killing Eykha and Gakusho!
The letter. Bring it.
[FEMALE ADJUTANT 3B]
Uh... right!
[GAKUSHO] The stamp looks
authentic, all right.
But...
[laughs]
Okay, I see how it is.
That shrewd bastard.
No use conducting a war
after seeing this.
Uh, so then...
You accept his apology?
Apology?
[laughs]
He sent us a peace treaty!
And I've got no complaints with
the conditions he's offered.
Really?
[GAKUSHO]
Send a message to our forces!
Haiga has accepted
all of our demands!
From this point forward,
we will enter Haiga
as an occupation force!
Be warned that all rioters
are gonna be
drilled with holes by me!
[CROWD cheers]
[LOU] Ka Grava.
He must have set up something.
[IBUKI]
During my sleep...
[KA GRAVA]
No, during my overhaul,
an unfortunate misunderstanding
has occurred.
For that, I apologize.
It was definitely
not my intention
to dismiss your advancement.
Regrettably,
the government of Haiga
will stop any further
resistance and accept abidance
under the rules
of Kouran's security.
Along with the costs involved
with being stationed here,
I will provide concessions
as expected.
I look forward to your
sound and right decision.
[IBUKI]
"Being stationed"?
[GAKUSHO]
That's right.
I don't mind fighting
for a good cause,
but killing and plundering
isn't really my thing.
I admit, I do have a personal
grudge against Ka Grava.
But... For now,
I'll forget about all that.
Oh, good.
Well, if you'll excuse us.
[GAKUSHO]
Just a moment, Ibuki.
[IBUKI]
Huh?
At least I know now
that you're not like all the
other spineless savages.
[IBUKI]
Huh?
That's because
he is going to be
king of Nil Kamui.
If that's the case,
then you'll make
for a tough opponent!
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
[KA GRAVA]
Speaking strictly of results,
killing Gakusho or
sealing the negotiations
by having her
read that letter...
Those were the only
two choices you had
from the very beginning.
The latter choice was
very difficult to achieve,
given the situation.
Yet, even when
you were at a loss,
you never gave up on your ideal,
right to the very end.
Ibuki.
I acknowledge you as a person
worthy of imparting
my knowledge to.
[IBUKI]
But...
What I did led to Haiga
being occupied by Kouran.
[KA GRAVA] I'm merely
having them stationed here
for military purposes.
Additionally, Kouran won't be
the only one stationed here.
[IBUKI]
Huh?
[KA GRAVA] D'natia's ambassador
should be arriving here shortly.
[IBUKI]
Who is this ambassador?
[KA GRAVA] Oh, someone you
are very well acquainted with.
[IBUKI]
Sweallow?
By bringing in both forces,
the balance of power
between Kouran and D'natia
can be kept.
I guess we were collectively
manipulated by you
this entire time, weren't we.
[KA GRAVA] This is just
a temporary solution.
Their forces led me to
surrender Haiga's position
as an independent city.
[KA GRAVA]
This is fact.
That's about all a petty
merchant like me can do.
Now then, would you mind
gathering everyone together?
As promised,
I'll talk about Red Dragon.
Sure!
[KA GRAVA]
And unbeknownst to you,
I have a standing
promise with Red Dragon.
It is, "To help the imperial
that would, one day,
come in search of me."
Tell me something.
Why didn't you kill me?
Is it because
I'm not your friend?
Or is it because
I am your friend?
[EYKHA]
Either way...
I consider you my friend, Ibuki.
Thanks for that.
[KA GRAVA]
Now then, as promised.
Red Dragon, was it?
I have a message from him.
A message from Red Dragon?
[KA GRAVA]
But before I get into that,
we need to listen
to Eykha's story.
[EYKHA]
My story?
[KA GRAVA]
Yes.
About the revolutionary army's
first expedition.
The one that was destroyed
while attempting to hunt down
the then-crazed Red Dragon.
[BOTH gasp]
Eykha...
Yes, that's right.
I didn't talk about that.
Honestly.
I probably just wanted to
forget that it ever happened.
[EYKHA] Izun was the leader
of the first expedition,
and a Bounded One who
was bonded to a Stone Giant.
Initially, he thought that he
could talk with Red Dragon.
Persuade him.
[RED DRAGON roars]
[ARMY gasps, yells]
[ALL scream]
[EYKHA]
That's... That's Red Dragon?
[NARRATOR]
Act Five. "In A Fog."
The undead, revived and
returning from the abyss,
stand in the way of those
seeking Red Dragon.
Is there no place one can
gain happiness in this world?