Sorry 'bout
this... Ginza.
Well, look who scored
himself an invite
to the "Wedding
of the Century."
We're closed...
Oh, you...
Long time no sale.
Yeah well...
I got a rush
order for ya, pal.
Father...
What have you done
with the contributions
that were in
the building fund?
Our parishioners trusted us
to spend that money
restoring the church!
Tell me... How in the name
of God do you explain this?
Electricity...
It is the guiding
force of all life.
Electricity giveith life,
and it taketh away.
And now that I have
its holy power I am God!
That's blasphemy...!
Just tell me how we're supposed
to pay for the repairs!
I will not restore a house of
worship unfit to worship me.
Father...
What is wrong wi-
"They shall know that
I am the Lord thy god...
when I shall lay my
vengeance upon them!"
From the ashes of this pyre
shall rise a temple
far more worthy a
testament to my glory!
Now there's a face
I haven't seen in a while.
Saiga!
You've come back
to me at last--
Wha--?
I need your help Bob...
I have to get the
girl back from him.
Are you...
serious?
Yeah... Because
Kagura needs me.
Or rather... I guess
the truth is I need her...
She fills my thoughts...
my dreams...
Since I first saw her
through my lens.
I just didn't realize
it until she was gone.
Saiga, you,
poor, tragic man.
You can only fall in love behind
the safety of your camera.
Ginza almost killed
me back there...
Maybe she's right-- What's
a guy like me doing running
around with a child?
Far be it from me
to cast judgment
on anyone else's tastes.
Whatever happens
between a man and a woman
or a man and a man
or, hell, even
a man and a goat--
do what you like...
But a grown man and a young girl
is something very different...
I don't think it's the
best for either of you --
sooner or later she'll
break out of her shell
and step out into
the world as a woman...
Her hormones
will kick into gear,
and she'll need more than
just a "good friend."
She'll be surrounded
by young studs
with, tight butts
and rock hard...
Wait,
where was I...?
Oh yeah. You however,
will just be old.
Yeah.
You're only settin' yourself
up for heartbreak, darlin'.
When she's twenty and you're
ancient, she'll leave your ass.
I honestly don't care.
None of that
even matters--
shit I'd be happy
to see her turn twenty.
She doesn't
have long to live.
What?
But for her...
To spend the rest of her days
as a plaything for those sick,
twisted--
I can not
let that happen.
So, Mr. Privacy finally
emerges from the shadows.
Soon every paparazzo
in town's gonna be able
to snap his ugly mug.
Togoshi here--
what can I do ya for...?
Saiga is that you...?
I thought you'd dropped off
the face of the earth...
Eh...?
What ceremony?
You don't mean the Suitengu
wedding tomorrow...?
Mister Prime Minister,
was the Cabinet acting
under your authority
when they decided
to ease up on
corporate restrictions?
Again, no comment.
Before we talk
business--
what sort
of representation
will we have at the
wedding this afternoon?
I'm sending my secretary...
She loves to get dressed up.
Gentlemen we're talking about
the Tennozu Group's heiress...
marrying the man
who controls
our extracurricular
activities...
Can we risk
appearing so blasé?
Does anyone else find
something a tad...
unseemly about
this young Turk?
If there is something
unsavory going on,
our attendance could generate
public backlash down the line.
However...
This debate may be rendered
moot once the Prime Minister
shares the first item
on his agenda for today.
It may indeed.
Care to enlighten us?
Gentlemen I propose we take
steps to bring Suitengu's club
under state control.
We'll establish a secret
committee to oversee it--
siphoning operating expenses
from the federal budget.
Very intriguing...
Then I suppose...
Of course, as Parliament our
admission to the new State-
run club will be
free of charge.
We all know how problematic
it can be raising
those membership dues
without also raising
the wife's suspicions.
Excellent idea,
Mr. Prime Minister!
Thank you.
All those in favor?
It's unanimous, then.
We've finally succeeded in
cultivating the hormone
from Kagura's
genetic makeup.
Excellent... By all means,
Doctor, move on to pase two.
Kagura...
My beautiful soul mate who
shares this cursed affliction.
Siblings of a sort,
yet like parent and child.
And now we shall be
man and wife as well...
so this corrupt world
may be reborn anew.
Pardon me, sir...
Let me be the first to
offer my congratulations.
I've brought you the
current list of RSVPs.
As expected the politicians
are all sending their proxies...
Cautious as always...
Oh well. We have more
than enough glitterati
attending to garner
the nation's attention.
And if my presence is
validated by the public,
this ceremony will have
served its purpose.
The paperwork...?
The marriage license...
All the documents for
transfer of assets...
Everything is here.
That's rather conservative
attire for a wedding.
It is still a
time of mourning.
Are you not happy
now working for me?
I consider it the
greatest honor.
Have these
filed immediately.
Yes sir.
Kagura...
Captain, thank God you're
awake-- how do you feel?
Like shit.
Mister Saiga called and said
you were in the hospital...
But he didn't tell me
what happened to you.
I'm standing outside the church
where, in just a few moments,
the wedding of
Kagura Tennozu,
daughter of the
late Shinsen Tennozu
and heiress
to her fortune,
is slated to commence
in a fashion befitting
one of the wealthiest
women in the country...
The red carpet arrivals
are already underway,
as nobody would dare be late for
the social event of the season.
Take me there.
He won't miss that.
Finally I command
a church...
that is a worthy
tribute to my power!
Shouldn't Tsujido
be here by now?
Probably.
And now... Goddess on high
who is to be my bride...
I beseech you,
reveal yourself!
Hey, Captain...
Oh it's you...
What're you doing here?
Got a tip
something newsworthy
might actually
happen here today.
You don't say...
Choji Suitengu...
Do you take this woman
to be your wife,
for better or worse,
for richer or poorer,
in sickness and in health,
'til death do you part?
I do.
And Kagura Tennozu...
Do you take this man to be your
husband, for better or worse,..
Yurigaoka?
Yeah he's here
I saw him come in...
What...?!
Son of a...
You have to say "I do"...
My darling...
She doesn't
have to do shit!
First you kill
her mother, and now,
in a last-ditch effort
to take over her empire...
You wanna acquire
this poor girl
like she's just
another commodity?
As if your backward idealism
wasn't a give-away...
I clearly recognize
your voice...
Tatsumi Saiga.
Saiga?
Hold on! That guy
ain't Yurigaoka!
Stop right there!
What the holy hell?!
Sounded like a bomb!
What are you,
mannequins?
In the news biz, this
is what we call "news!"
Somebody run a live
feed to the networks!
Get the lead out!
Uh... okay...
That guy...
who is he again?
Quit jerkin' off
over there and move!
You people may not be
wearing the same masks today,
but I still recognize you
all from the Club...
Therefore... you should
recognize me too,
and you know what happens
when I press this shutter.
Suitengu!
Step away from the girl!
You want her for
your own sick pleasure?
What I want is for you to stay
the fuck away from that girl!
Go ahead. Take a picture--
I dare you..
But know this...
It'll be your last.
God damn--
Go ahead...
Suitengu...!
Let the whole
country see...
see what you
really are!
Saiga!
Well what're
you afraid of...?
That all the cockroaches are
going to go scampering back
into the shadows...?
'Cause you know...
that exposure spells the
end of every vermin in here!
This can't be...
I'm a... movie star
for Christ's sake!
Saiga!
Now you get to watch
me leave with the girl.
What a cruel fate...
That my glorious cathedral
would be christened
under such unholy
circumstances!
Suitengu my son...
I will rain divine retrobution
down upon these sinners!
Mister Suitengu!
Can you tell us what
happened in there?
How would you characterize
the relationship
between that man
and your bride?
Is Miss Tennozu
a runaway bride?
She's yet to be seen!
No need for concern...
I've moved her somewhere safe
and private until our honeymoon.
Tatsumi Saiga...
I will destroy you.
I have a marriage license that
needs to be filed right away.
Gladly.
Oh, it's...
Still unclear at this time...
exactly what happened
inside that church today...
I don't have all day.
Oh. Consider it done.
Then it's official.
Kagura's
a married woman.
Come on Kagura!
Wake up...!
It's all right.
You're with me now.
Sai-ga...?
Verily Lord,
unyielding Voltage
is the cross I bear...
Mister Saiga!!
It's good
to have you back.
Where are we?
The church... Outside.
That's right...!
They tried to force me
to marry Mr. Suitengu...!
But I knew it--
I knew you'd come save me!
Then let's go.
Okay!
I will not allow it!
The Wrath of God shall
sear your mortal flesh...
Now... it is time
to confess your sins.
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah...
I think so...
Good...
that jolt wasn't
intended for you --
it was for your cameras.
For electricity
is divine truth.
Electricity is
the blood of God!
Now prostrate yourselves
and prepare to repent.
But first I've got
some truth for you.
True pros never switched to
digital or point-and-shoot.
Our cameras are
entirely mechanical.
Means they've got no
circuits to short.
With you for a subject
it seems a bit redundant
to use a flash...
Almost!
Hey...!
Need a lift?!
Nice ride...!
Kagura... Ready?
Uh-huh!
Blasphemy!
May lightning strike you
for your sins against me!
Holy fuck!!!
My Wrath against you
shall not be quenched!
Kagura!
Saiga!
Everything okay?
Yeah.
After all we've been
through we're right back
where we started.
But things are
different this time...
'Cause now
we're free too.
Yeah.
A mermaid beckons
from the water's edge.
Her tongue for a pair
of land-walking legs.
Will her watery kiss
lure the wayward prince
to the deep abyss?
Life ain't a fairy
tale, princess.