Saiga...
Kagura, dear.
I'm the woodsman,
not the wolf.
I'm sorry,
I can't let anybody in!
I know you've been
through a lot...
That's why I'm here,
to protect--
No...!
You have a gun.
I saw it.
It's 'cause
I'm a cop, Kagura.
I don't believe you!
Listen, Saiga's
a friend of mine.
He told me you'd
be waiting here.
We've taken him into
protective custody.
No one else is
gonna touch him.
Captain Hibari Ginza.
New Metropolitan Police.
Now you're gonna be a
good girl and go home ...
Aren't you?
But your mother
needs you, hon...
Haven't you heard what
happened while you been gone?
What?
I'm Police Chief Ekoda...
I have a statement regarding
Shinsen Tennozu's condition...
As you know,
Ms. Tennozu collapsed
outside her home this morning.
Paramedics responded swiftly,
but Ms. Tennozu has yet
to regain consciousness
and remains in
critical condition.
Oh my God,
Mother--!
Word around town is
it was friction
between you and your mom
that made you run
away from home...
But the fact is, she's the
only the real family you've got.
You're her blood--
she bore you,
and that matters--
I don't care how much
you hate her right now...
You can tell me it's
none of my business...
But if she dies and
you're not there...
you'll regret it for
the rest of your life.
Besides, going home now
may be your only chance
to save Saiga
from kidnapping charges.
Somehow I don't think
prison's his style.
So tell me...
What was going on with you
and Saiga through all this--
what kind of relationship
did you two have?
Relationship?
Look, I'm a cop and you're
a minor, I have to ask.
We got laws against
certain things, ya know.
Laws?
Against what?
Stuff you learn
in health class--
birds, bees, bad places--
come on, you
know what I mean.
It's not like that...
He never touched me.
It's better than that.
What I share with
him is in the heart.
Do you know my
mother's condition?
She's here, ma'am.
Mother--
Well...
What's going on...?
That news story
said you were sick...
Sorry to worry you, dear...
But I'm certain I'll live
much longer than you.
Welcome home,
Kagura...
We're so relieved...
You were gone
such a long time.
It's perfectly normal
for a child your age
to want to expand
her horizons...
But do you really think it was
fair to worry your mother so?
Mother...
Don't trust him...
You don't understand...
He--
You disgraceful whore...
Manipulating that damned
fool into kidnapping you...
with your
young little cunt!
We have to remember,
Miss Tennozu...
Your daughter is
not well now...
It's her condition that
makes her so irrational...
She needs treatment
at a proper facilty,
to make sure
she won't stray again.
Ah, hell.
Ginza, wait!
Please! It was a trick!
Don't look at me
to save you...
You thieving little cat!
You said you'd...
protect me...
No, let go!
Get off of me!
Thank you, Captain.
You do good work.
Ginza, why?
I held up my
end of the bargain,
so I'll be taking
my bounty, as agreed.
No! Saiga, wake up!
You know it was a
real bitch piecing
that fake news
report together...
I hope you don't plan
to go back on your word.
I admire a brave woman...
You won't be followed.
'Preciate it.
How could you do this--
you said you came to help!
Little word
of advice, kid,
next time someone
shows up at your door--
the wolf always lies.
You can't take him
from me, please!
Is that supposed
to be funny...?
You listen to me...
Saiga is all mine...
And nobody steals from
me and gets away with it!
No...!
You don't understand!
Please!
Don't leave me here!
I won't survive
without him!
Saiga! Get your
hands off me!
I can't go to back
to this!! I can't! Stop!
I leave the rest to you.
No! What are you
doing to me?
Please, let me go!
Calm down little one,
we're here to help you...
You're sick, and it's
affecting your thoughts.
We're going to make
everything better.
No, get away!
Just relax.
Nice, deep breaths...
It'll be okay...
Trust us, you'll see...
Thank god. She hasn't
begun menstruating yet.
Inject her with the
hormone inhibitor!
Hurry!
Oh yes...
Do you know how long
we've waited for this day?
Come on,
come on! Faster!
I'm gonna win, you filthy
little whore, let's go!
That's right, baby,
keep it trucking...
One dirty little hoof at a time!
Go!
You're falling behind!
Come on!
Giddyup, bitch, giddyup!
You like getting
spanked, don't you?
That's what a
slut like you needs!
Move!
Yeah, keep it movin'!
Almost there!
Don't give up now,
you naughty little cooze!
Very close race,
gentlemen.
Clearly,
I won that one.
Like hell...!
I won!
Miserable whore!
You know what happens
to losing horses?
Number one by a nose.
No...
It's a tie.
Yeah!
Dinner's on me
tonight, bitches!
Here ya go sluts!
Enough for everyone!
It appears you've
won big tonight.
It's just a way
to pass the time...
However...
These activities alone are
hardly enough to satisfy.
I understand...
And I realize I've kept you
gentlemen waiting far too long,
but the Club is
scheduled to reopen soon.
That is good news...
But it's clear the Club is
just a part of your strategy.
All of these "gifts"
you shower us with
are obviously a lead-
in to something bigger.
Am I so transparent?
Let's cut to the chase,
Suitengu...
Ponies are fun, but
Miss Tennozu is the horse
we want to ride...
It's time to grab
hold of her reins.
-- The problem's Taizo Senri--
He clings to her
like the heir apparent
and she won't make any financial
move without his consent.
We can't reach him--
he has no interest
in wine or women--
just his god-
damned pond.
How does a wet blanket like
him become such a hero
in financial circles...?
If you ask me it's a sign of the
economy's impending collapse.
Measures have
already been taken.
You and your esteemed
colleagues rule the political,
industrial and
financial worlds...
With your help
the Tennozu Group
will become
Triple-Crown champion,
bringing riches to us all...
Let me thank you now,
in Shinsen Tennozu's name.
You know it's a real pity
we couldn't deal with her
in person tonight...
I always have
enjoyed her ass.
Pretend these
girls are her...
I'm sure she'll
like the gesture.
Oh...?
Is that right...?
Well, Shinsen...
Are you having fun now?
Now I got the worst
sense of smell around ...
But I could still
smell that...
So with your nose it
must've been killing you.
The smell of decay...
Old sweat
and stale cigars...
I can withstand
any stench
as long as it
benefits our business.
You're a model employee.
I don't know what Suitengu is up
to but it seems kind of risky...
Should he really be trusting
those wrinkle-dicks?
His nose is
even more sensitive
to the smell
of money than mine...
All we have to do
is believe in him,
and go where he leads us.
You've certainly gone too
far this time, haven't you?
What does that mean?
The Tennozu Group
is past its growth phase--
I thought you understood.
Any further expansion
at this stage
will only lead
to destruction,
like the great
empires of the past
that over-extended
their borders,
leaving themselves so
vulnerable they collapsed.
You've talked in the past
of me ruling Japan...
Maybe you should
explain your strategy,
because you clearly see
something I don't.
Forgive my ignorance.
Are you mad at me now?
Furious, at myself.
Because I no longer know
what you think of me.
What are you
talking about?
All of this...
Everything I've done,
I've done to make you happy
so one day you'd take me
as your husband......
But I'm too much of a fool
to even get that right.
Suitengu, ...
I feel I'm a captive
of my own decorum.
Like I need to do something rash
to show you how I truly feel.
Suitengu,
what are you doing?
We're together--
nothing else matters!
Please...
be my wife.
Suitengu,
you do go overboard.
But I can't say
I don't enjoy it.
It is nice
to feel again...
Good day,
Madam President.
We received a call
from Taizo Senri's home
while you were gone.
Senri's home?
Yes ma'am... I'm sorry
to tell you this...
But they said there's been an
accident at his lake house...
He's passed away.
Senri, Chairman
of the Federation
of Economic
Organizations, has died...
sending shockwaves through
the Japanese economy.
Hey I knew him...
He was one of Miss
Tennozu's advisors.
Uh-huh. And Yuichiro
Ashikaga's friend--
he's the one who brought the
original investors together.
So now that he's dead...
The Tennozu Group could lose
most of its financial backers...
So... That's what
Suitengu's after.
He's planning
to challenge them all.
Let's go.
Where?
To meet the next V.I.P...
Then go after Saiga.
What, again?
Forget about earlier--
Suitengu hasn't cancelled
his orders yet...
Wait!
Hey...
Yurigaoka!
Over here!
Why...? Why am I not
good enough for you?
She's just a kid...
And I'm not
losing you to her...
Hell...
I'm your girl.
Don't you know that?
Having fun?
Director...!
I'm sorry...
Well...
Can't blame you...
I come here myself.
Did you hear about
Mister Suitengu?
Apparently he and Miss Tennozu
are going to be married.
No... Mother and that
horrible Mr. Suitengu??
How can she?
Doesn't she know
what he is?
With the world
on her shoulders,
a girl runs in despair.
And where she ends up
will forever change
the face of Tokyo.
They say life
moves in circles.
And with the doomsday god
about to rear its head,
it's good to know
where you've been.