There was a man on that
barstool last night
smoking like a freight
train-- who was he?
Look around...
It's a bar...
There were a lot
of men smoking...
most of 'em like it
was goin' out of style.
I told you I don't
know who he is...
What're ya doin'...?
That's some perfectly
good whiskey!
Fuck! Fuck!
Okay!
The guy you're lookin' for's
a photographer, named Saiga!
Now grab that extinguisher
and put me the fuck out!
"Tatsumi Saiga... renowned
freelance photographer.
He made his name documenting
the wars of Africa, Asia
and the Middle East.
His images are at once
vibrant and haunting,
stirring the souls of all those
who lay eyes upon them...
And this humble reporter
surely cannot be the only
one left wondering...
how the Pulitzer could have
eluded him for so long."
Tatsumi...
Saiga.
A war photographer eh?
Yes... He's in Tokyo now
toiling away in obscurity.
Surely he couldn't have
been on that battlefield...
I'm having his place
watched around the clock,
but he's yet to return.
Should we attempt to lure
Mister Saiga back home?
There'd be no point...
A man like him can't
be seduced with money.
The roll of film
he left behind...
Have it developed.
I want to see his work.
Yes, sir.
They really called
the police? That's bad!
Why? I didn't get
the ticket...
Creepy!
Total hentai.
I'll bet he's going up
there to buy some panties.
Yeah the ones
you just sold!
Manager, you got
any fresh ones?
Maybe something
in a blonde...
What the hell...?
So we meet again...
Interesting hobby
you got here...
Senator.
You -
you're that--
Where... am I?
Awake at last.
The tawdry fetish
of a Senator...
A trashy enough shot'll
cover my rent for a year...
Soon they'll all
know your secret.
You bastard-- what is
the meaning of this??
Voters'll kick your
ass outta the House...
and then your wife
will do the same.
No...! What do you
want from me?!
Saw you leaving the
hotel that night--
were you there
when your colleague
in the Health Ministry
was decapitated?
Did you pop his head off?
Of course not...! I only went
to Nakano's room because...
Mister Suitengu told--
"Mister Suitengu"?
Why don'tcha tell me all
about your secret boss...
and that underground club
of his you belong to.
No...
I can't.
Wha-- What... the hell
kinda camera is that?!
You tell me--
ever since I dropped in
on your twisted club...
it's had a lot more flash...
So how 'bout you
start talking?
If I talk...
I'm a dead man,
soon as I leave!
If you don't, you're
a dead man now.
Hold on-- I'll talk I'll talk
just put that damn camera down!
One night, at an otherwise
unmemorable cocktail party,
a stranger approached
me out of the blue.
This man, Suitengu, knew
all about my "proclivities."
He told me there was a club
that catered to people like me.
The first few visits
would be gratis
and if I liked
what I saw,
I could pay annual
membership dues...
and receive services well
worth the exorbitant fee.
Frankly I was shocked...
These were people not even
I could brush shoulders
with in the outside world.
All the highest
of the high were there--
the nation's movers
and shakers.
And this club was the one place
they could gather together,
in tacit agreement
of secrecy,
while forging a
network of power.
That's when I realized--
those who weren't in this club
could never climb to the top.
It was just another
wrung on the ladder.
And it served a purpose.
The heavier the
responsibility,
the heavier the stress...
Every man has latent hungers
that yearn to be fed...
This club is a necessary evil.
Those in power need somewhere to
release those urges most of all!
So you're telling me orgies
are what keep the wheels
of this country turning...?
Do you even hear the shit
that's coming out of your mouth?
Now, tell me
about the ritual.
Does it have anything
to do with me
turning into whatever
it is I've become?
I don't... I don't know,
I'm not a VIP...
They're the only club members
allowed to attend the rituals.
But I've heard...
when the Goddess
bestows her blessing
you experience supreme bliss...
and your deepest
desire is fulfilled.
Blessing of the Goddess ...
I swear, that's all I
know about the ritual...!
But take my advice...
If you value your life
even the slightest bit
don't get involved
with that club!
The place is flooding!
Please, you gotta take
these cuffs off me!
Hurry!
Oh, thank God!
Ah, it slipped!
Hey, where you going?
You can't just...
Don't get involved, huh...?
A little late for that.
She has awoken
your potential,
and turned your deepest
desire into reality.
I'll die if I have to stay!
It's back--
I wanna take photos...
Shot after shot
after shot...!
I may be on a
treacherous path,
but I will follow
it to the end!
Hey, excuse me, girls.
Can I take your picture?
Oh, please...
Forgive me...
I haven't even
introduced myself yet-
I'm a photographer...
For Tokyo Girl magazine.
Have you seen it?
Only like every month!
Yeah, I got a subscription.
We're looking for models
for next month's issue
and I think you've
got the look. Interested?
Hell yeah, we are!
Sorry girls, your dreams
of fame'll have to wait.
I know better than to
carry a loaded camera.
All right, give it to me.
Yeah, play with your hair.
Yeah, just like that.
Okay, now you: smile!
Gorgeous...
Man you two are pros!
You go to St. Ignatius
right...?
You wouldn't happen
to know a girl there
by the name of
Kagura Tennozu?
Well yeah, of course.
She's a celebutante.
Yeah I shot her
the other day...
I need to get some
retakes on her.
Good luck finding
her at school.
She hasn't been
around in days.
Huh... You know why?
No, not really...
I heard her mom's paying our
teacher for private lessons.
Seriously?
Private tutoring
at home, huh?
Good afternoon...
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Beg your pardon... but
where is Miss Wakaba?
Well regrettably...
Miss Wakaba got a little tied
up in the classroom so...
I'll be filling in
as substitute today.
No bugs in here.
Excuse me...
I'd like to make a personal
call if you please.
Uhhh... I've brewed some
fresh tea for you.
Door's open.
So, Chief, any word on that
underground fire in Roppongi?
Well...
the boys over in arson say
it could be weeks-months
even-before repairs
are finished down there.
When's this go public?
There's a press conference
tomorrow afternoon.
Means there's still
a few hours
to sell my East
Kanto Internet stock
and buy up shares
of Tojo Electric.
They're gonna be up to their
asses in no-bid contracts soon
as this gets out.
Just a memo to myself...
So... whadda ya want
from me Chief?
Uh... Would staying...
behind your desk be
too much to ask of you?
I see...
You don't want me on the
streets-- is that how it is?
No, no...
It's just that...
when you leave the
office--people...
they tend to get hurt...
And when people get hurt
they tend to get lawyers.
So, you didn't
lose my number...
You must really
want something bad.
Actually, I just want
to return a favor...
That double homicide,
the Roppongi fire,
the shooting in Odaiba...
If you listen to me...
You should be able to round up
all the suspects at once,
and get all
the credit for it.
Well... When you put it like
that, I can't afford not to.
Does this mean
you're going out?!
Hey sugar...
wanna have some fun?
Shit.
You must be lookin' for a man,
'cause you ain't gonna find
a better woman than me!
See anything yet?
Nada...
You think this guy's dense
enough to come back home?
That's not your concern...
Just keep watching--
is that clear?
Crystal.
Oh, yeah...
Right there...
Yeah that's it...
Mister Slotnik
you naughty boy,
you've been overworking
your pelvic muscles!
Come one, come all.
Door's open!
Jesus Christ...
All right, all right.
You know how to open
a door don't you?
Just put your hand on
the knob and twist...
It's just like...
You... you that crazy bitch
who's stalking Saiga.
You can go yank
yourself Yankee...
and while you're at it...
you can give us...
your apartment.
Why me?
Is it him?
Can't see-- damn
blinds are in the way.
Gather up the men.
Odd. I haven't
picked up his scent.
Miss Kagura... it's time
for your tutoring session.
I think I've seen
enough of Miss Wakaba.
Actually Miss Wakaba
isn't here today...
but a Mister Saiga
has come in her place.
Mister Saiga?
Hi Kagura... Are you ready
for your lesson?
This way.
I've come for you.
Who are you?
Take a guess.
Tatsumi Saiga...
Photographer...
Someone who knows freedom.
You've done your homework.
So what are you going to
teach me today Mister Saiga?
How to be free of course...
You coming?
Yes!
Close your eyes for me.
I take it you guys
are the perps...
Pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
For the record that
was self-defense.
Freeze!
Self-defense!
Sounds like a war
zone up there!
Pigs must'a ambushed 'em!
Damn it, he set us up!
Mister Saiga... how do we
get out of here?
You just leave that to me.
I will need to borrow this.
Good wind.
Keep your eyes closed
and hold on tight.
Um, yeah.
Son of a bitch...
How dare you keep
humiliating me?
I see... Perfect.
Tonight... You two shall have
an exclusive audience...
you shall see my true dance!
You all right?
Heck, yeah!
Divine Goddess... it's not
like you to shy away.
Who are you-- I've never
seen you before in my life.
You're one of them.
Yes, like you,
I've had the pleasure
of the Goddess' blessing.
Mister Saiga...
what was that?
I'll explain later...
Right now I'm gonna
distract him...
That's when you
make a break for it.
But then what?
Under that billboard?
Yeah, wait for me
under the billboard
we saw from the buoy...
I'll come for you.
I promise. Now go!
Okay.
What?!
Your aim's a little
off, cameraman.
It was you...! You're the
one who killed Nakano!
You're familiar
with my work?
Oh, now that didn't work!
What kinda...
twisted freak are you?
One who has
transcended humanity.
I grasped at the light that
shines within her heart,
and plucked true bliss.
A man with pleasure
does not mind his chains.
His desires fulfilled,
he walks gladly through hell.
Am I so different from you?
You are...
'Cause I...
I never wanted
this power!
You wouldn't have the power
if you didn't want it.
Your desire is to steal
life with your lens.
It's just too bad you'll
die before capturing me,
the ultimate subject.
See, while I've enjoyed
our pas de deux,
it's come time
for the coda.
Even a Euphoric will perish
if his head is taken off...
So I shall twist off yours
like I did the rest.
Thanks for the tip.
What do you know...?
My desire was fulfilled.
How does this nobody keep
slipping through our fingers?
I've got our best men setting
a trap for him as we speak.
Here...
The photographs he took.
He has quite an eye.
Saiga!
Sorry to...
keep you waiting.
Saiga...!
I'm all right kid...
Forget about it.
When the sun goes down,
the city becomes a playground
where assassins roam.
And with the snap
of their fingers,
their darkest desires
come to life.
Meanwhile, the rest of us make
do with the treasures we've got.