I can't... I can't
see anything...
My eyes...
Is this it?
I've got to...
I've got
to shoot her.
Please help me!
Is anyone out there?!
Anyone...?!
Let me out of here...!
Somebody! Please!
(Oh please some)body get
me out of this place!
Kagura!
Kagura, can you
hear me? Kagura!
Doctor, is that you...?!
Doctor Ryogoku?!
Not so loud.
I don't know
what's going on here,
but it's probably best
not to draw attention.
But Doctor...
I've been thumbing through
Professor Nishiya's journal.
There are notes
in here...
Detailed notes
regarding the research
he did on you
and your condition.
About me?
Yes. And it's confirmed
a lot of my theories.
I was hoping I might find
some way to save you.
But there's something
I still can't seem to grasp.
That...
journal...
That journal is me,
isn't it...?
All the secrets...
My whole life I've been
wondering who I really am...
But now I... I'm really
going to die, aren't I?
For so long...
that's what I wanted.
But now that I'm
actually facing death
I want nothing more
than to survive...
With Saiga...
he helped me see that
I could live and be free.
I want to live...
I wanna live
to see Saiga again.
Oh good, I'm so glad
you're up, Captain.
Chief...?!
What the fuck
is going on?!
Shouldn't I be asking you
what you're doing here...?
Of course, who am I to question
the sublime hand of fate
that brought you and your
"knockout pair" into my home
to join my
private collection?
Collection...?
You mean...
This fucked up
shit is your doing?
Whatcha think...?
Beautiful aren't they...?
Don't worry, I saved
a nice bit of real estate
for your stems,
Captain...
The perfect place, right between
my wife's and daughter's!
Goddamn...! You mutilated
your own wife and kid?!
You sick fuck!
You make it sound
like a bad thing,
when I did it
purely out of love.
This way I stay close to them
for as long as I live,
and they always
stay beautiful...
Well at least their
legs stay beautiful!
What does an elite club
like Suitengu's even want
with a lowly
nothing like you?
Ah, so that's
what brought you here...?
They welcome all public
officials with open arms.
Course, the
Superintendent-General
of Metro Police
is my uncle...
But that's enough
gossiping...
Those legs aren't going
to saw off themselves.
Stay away!
Please don't struggle my sweet!
They all struggle...
But it'd be
a real travesty
if I were to damage
those perfect legs.
How could I forget
the most important part?
Lotion!
Play it smart,
Chief...
if you kill me, you're
gonna find yourself smack
in the middle of a
massive shit storm!
How's that?
Before I came here I got hold
of the Club's membership list.
And guess whose name
was printed right there
in black and white...
If I don't get back soon...
I've arranged for that list to
go to the brass and the media.
Oh is that all, you really
had me worried for a second...
Did you even bother to look
at some of the other names,
Captain...?
The head of the
National Police
and my dear uncle, the
Superintendent- General...?
As for the media,
our members own
every major newspaper
and broadcast
outlet in Japan.
Hell, even the Prime
Minister's a member!
In fact, the Club's
reopening tonight!
I couldn't be
more excited!
And... Kamiya's got
a big announcement
to make at the ceremony.
Of course you'll be
dead by then
so what the fuck
do you care?
Now the lotion...
it works wonders...
It'll make your skin as
smooth as silk stockings.
Plus it helps you relax,
and the aroma's intoxicating.
But best of all, it contains
Drop of the Goddess!
Drop of what...?
What the hell is that?
The special ingredient
added to every one of the
Tennozu Group's new products.
The "magic potion" that's
been liberating everyone
of their inhibitions
as of late...
Oh sure some people
have gone a bit crazy...
but that's a small price to pay
for unleashing our desires...
No...!
Get off me!
Get off...!
Get off now!
Why my dear,
sweet Captain.
That is entirely
the point.
Get off!
Damn it...
Goddamn it...
What was that?
Is somebody out there?
I've got a gun...
Saiga?!
Sweet baby Jesus!
Guess the Chief wasn't
dickin' around, was he?
They're all here...
Directors, Deputy Chiefs,
Security Police...
What the fuck's wrong
with this country?
Welcome to the grand
reopening of our Club...
This is truly a
special evening!
Please partake
of our fine elixirs
and feast upon the sumptuous
dishes prepared by our chefs.
That's it...!
Kagura I found it!
I found a way to
save your life!
Kagura!
Pardon me, sir.
Welcome Goddess.
Please, come in.
I trust that you
slept well last night?
Aren't you ...
Kamiya, yes...
You seem surprised
to see me...
Since yesterday you've been
a guest in my residence.
Mr. Prime Minister...
why have you--?
Please, won't you
have a seat...?
I apologize for the manner
in which you were brought here.
However, it was of the utmost
importance that I see you;
to apprise you of your
current situation.
What is this...?
What am I here for?!
With all you've been through
you must be famished...
I'll explain everything
to you as we enjoy
a hearty breakfast,
Goddess.
Now come,
have a seat.
Oh, everything looks
delicious, doesn't it?
The dishes on the table are
like power in this country...
Spread out before me,
and all within my reach.
I'm not ashamed to say
I derive boundless pleasure
from each little bite.
And as the man at the head
of this nation's table,
I intend to
devour it all.
I'm sorry, sir, but
I don't feel like eating...
Now please tell me
what you want from me.
Why have you brought--
You mustn't let this
banquet go to waste!
You have lost entirely too much
weight while on the run, dear...
You have to eat something
to get your energy up.
Go on...
Food is more than
mere sustenance.
It is culture-
it is art...!
And only the chosen few
are given the chance
to appreciate and indulge
in such epicurean delights...
And no one is more
deserving than you, Goddess.
What's the matter,
dear Goddess...?
That soup is full
of collagen...
It's good
for your complexion.
Let me out
of here now!
Patience my
beautiful child...
As soon as you finish
eating this fine breakfast
we shall leave...
And head to the Club.
Why would you--...?
I'm never going back
to that place, never!
I'm afraid you have no
say in the matter...
Recently the Tennozu Group
has been brought
under federal control...
Meaning that the Club
is hereby a public entity.
In which case,
I suppose one could say you
are now a servant
of the people...
Just like yours truly!
You won't get
away with this!
Oh I'll eliminate anyone
who gets in my way...
I've dispatched an elite
squad to do just that.
Relax. There's no love lost
between you and Suitengu?
So... let's enjoy
the rest of our meal
while we wait
for the good news.
All right boys, we're storming
the Tennozu Building.
Suitengu's gotta be
holed up in there.
Fuck me!
How much ya think's
in this shit hole?
Sit... We're not
finished eating yet!
I can't eat this...!
And I don't care what you say...
I won't ... I won't
go back to that Club...!
The only place I'm going
is wherever Saiga is.
That pest?
He's dead.
Forget him...
Now hurry up and eat...
you naughty girl, you!
You're lying, he can't
be dead...! He can't...
Hurry up and eat,
Goddess,
the time
for feasting is now!
Bravo, gentlemen.
I'm flattered I warrant
such a distinguished
welcoming committee...
Prime Minister Kamiya can
be a bold man at times....
A crack squadron,
to be sure...
It's too bad none of you have
any actual combat experience...
I just wish you could've
been in that jungle--
seen what I saw...
Fire!
Oh, Saiga...!
Thank God you're awake...!
C- can you even
tell who I am?
Yeah, Bob...
I can see...
But you kept saying
"I can't see-- I can't see...
" Somethin' wrong with
those gorgeous eyes?
Guess you can call
that one more I owe ya.
Oh pish posh--
don't be silly...
Makes me feel good
takin' care of you.
'At's sweet, but...
No moving!
I gotta go.
Kagura's in trouble--
'cause of me.
Don't be ridiculous...!
You're staying right
here with me...
Doctor Bob's
orders, honey!
Bob, I...
When's it stop?
How much suffering'll
be enough for you two?
Just look at you...!
I wanted you both
to have a fairytale ending,
and that's the truth...
Why do you think,
against my better judgment,
I did everything
I could to help?
But what good did it do?
For you...?
For that girl?
No, you're wrong...
about us...
Wake up...!
Will you...?
It's all over!
Back there...
I had a dream.
I dreamt I took Kagura's
picture and killed her...
It was so goddamned
real it was scary...
And then I
realized that,
when I'm with her...
all I feel is fear!
Saiga, you--
This isn't
about love, Bob...
It's something more...
If I can't find a way to save
her, I can't go on living!
And it goes a lot deeper
than just me and her now...
Too many people
have died...
This whole country's
been sold to the wolves!
Just promise me one
fuckin' thing...
That you'll come
back to me alive.
Thanks for
everything, Bob.
Shouldn't Kamiya
be here?
Don't worry, he'll be arriving
with the Goddess soon.
And the Ambassadors, too...
If we can seduce
foreign diplomats now,
it'll be easier asking
for favors down the road.
Professor...
Nishiya...
Uh, sir...
What do you want?
Is it time already?
What? No, sir...
It's just...
there's a bit
of a problem.
The squad infiltrated
the Tennozu Building,
but we seem to have lost
contact with them.
What the hell?!
That's gotta be...
Keep the change!
I'm coming for you...
Kagura.
The time has come for
you to remember the beginning
of our sordid story...
Prime Minister.
Time to go.
That shocking day that
lies hidden in your heart.
The dark memory that haunts
the deepest recesses
of your mind...
Sooner or later,
it all boils to the surface.
And all you can do,
is let it come.