Defense Minister Fukushima,
Finance Minister Yumoto.
Thank you so much for coming
to our little factory
on the sea this evening.
We've arranged
a first-rate tour.
Right this way,
gentlemen.
It's a damn
fine factory.
All this, hidden
inside a tanker.
Ingenious.
Yes... So it that
our magic elixir?
I've been thinking of calling
it "Drop of the Goddess."
Got a nice ring to it.
The formula has already
been added to all
of the Tennozu
Group's products.
It's not quite up to par with
the girl's Euphoria stimulant...
But it is highly addictive...
even a small dose reduces
serotonin in the brain.
Serotonin?
That's a hormone,
isn't it?
It's a neurotransmitter
that regulates
the amount of dopamine and
norepinephrine in the brain--
the chemicals
responsible for desire.
When serotonin
levels are low,
people become unable to control
the most basic animal cravings.
Put simply, it will return
people to their primitive roots,
making them
ideal consumers...
and creating great
fortune for us all.
Thanks to your changes to the
Pharmaceutical Affairs Law,
the Tennozu Group's drug
companies now own the market,
and these products will
reach every shelf...
while your recent corporate
deregulations have allowed to us
to expand our financial empire
in ways few dreamed possible.
From the Prime Minister
down the chain,
all of you
loyal Club members --
as well as your
family businesses--
will become
top shareholders
in each of the
Tennozu Group's firms.
Healthy dividends await,
you can be sure.
We'll take care of raising
funds for the next phase...
In terms of investments
it's far beyond the Bank
of Japan's normal limits...
But I've already
cleared it personally
with the bank's governor.
This has been a risky
maneuver for all of us...
These legislative
changes have stirred up
a firestorm in the media--
especially the drug law--
and we expect big returns.
You know, gentlemen,
we could always spin off
part of the Tennozu Group
into a public corporation...
And thus transfer most of
the early financial burden
to the national debt.
Don't get ahead of
yourself, Suitengu.
Just do your job, and leave
the politics to the politicians.
Please sirs,
pardon my insolence.
This was a damned bold step
on your part, you know,
offering us such a sizeable cut
of the Tennozu Group's profits
in order to make this
plan of yours happen.
"Bold?" No, I'm simply
looking to the future...
My dreams go far
beyond riches.
You don't say...
Gentlemen-- to the development
of our great country.
And prosperity
for all of us.
I gathered
all I could!
I pulled strings,
groveled on my knees!
I maxed out every possible
line of credit, I swear!
Yet you're still short
twenty million yen.
That's money you
spent at the Club.
But I've given you
everything!
The stock in my company,
the deed to this house!
Mister Suitengu, please!
Twenty million yen!
That's pocket change
for someone like you!
The state of my
financial affairs
should be the least
of your concerns...
At this point,
I'm certain you know the rules
of doing
business with me.
There's a reason life
insurance policies
are a membership
requirement.
I'm begging you...!
Please reconsider!
I have a family--
children!
Mai, don't come in here--
go back to your room!
I'll give you...
this...
That's nice,
sweetheart...
But it's play money--
we can't take that.
How old are you?
Your daughter just
bought your life.
Let him go.
How's it coming?
Man, this is a bitch...
Do we honestly gotta get
every single boxload counted
by the end of the day?
It's the semiannual audit--
you know how it works...
How's Sasazuka?
Every time he crunches
numbers he gets that grin--
If I didn't know better I'd
think he was jerking off.
He knows numbers
like I know smells.
If I get a whiff of
someone's urine,
I can tell where they've been,
what they were eating--
even how they felt
while they pissed...
Smell has its own language--
it excites me in a way
nothing else can.
Were I to venture a guess,
I'd imagine crunching numbers
gets him off in
the same fashion.
It's been
a hell of a term
compared to the
normal receipts.....
And I know who we
have to thank...
So this is it.
What is this?
Who would have thought...
In a madhouse
like this...
I'd finally find
my subject.
What are you waiting for?
Take him away from the
Goddess, immediately!
He stole my ritual...
I've come for you.
Who are you?
Take a guess.
Tatsumi Saiga...
Photographer...
Someone who knows freedom.
You've done homework.
So what are you going to
teach me today Mister Saiga?
How to be free
of course... You coming?
Yes!
Keep your eyes closed
and hold on tight.
Um, yeah.
You wouldn't have the power
if you didn't want it.
Your desire is to steal
life with your lens...
Even a Euphoric will perish
if his head is taken off...
So I shall twist off
yours like I did the rest.
Thanks for the tip.
What do you know?
My desire was fulfilled.
Smile.
Make sure you
catch my good side.
Go to hell.
It didn't focus...
What a pity.
Simon...!
You filthy whore...!
Get out of here!
You won't get off just
'cause you're a freak!
Madam Koganei...
You played a risky hand,
but now it's time to collect.
Please help me...
I'll repay you!
You know a clouded
diamond has no value.
Gather the pieces,
and sell them off.
We have to profit
from her somehow...
What the hell is that thing
and why is it in my house?
Stay back, Doc!
You're just like
the rest of 'em...
Not right in the head.
'Kay, so...
How much you
suckers wanna bet...
that lucky bastard's bangin'
divine pussy right now?
Shows how much you know...
That's never going
to happen with them.
Why not?
Quite simply, a Euphoric
needs something very different
to get off.
I believe that's more
than fair compensation...
for the photograph you
took of Miss Kagura.
Photograph?
What are you
talking about?
See for yourself...
It turned out
quite nicely.
Can't say I care
much for the rest.
Okay that's enough;
I don't want to get caught...
What are you doing?
Come any closer and
I'll kill myself, I swear!
Okay please, don't do it...
You're too important--
They'd kill me if
anything happened to you!
All right... Then you're gonna
have to do what I say.
Mother, run!
He's one of them--
he's a monster!
You should have been
happy with me.
In all the time we shared,
you were always
in the left arm
of the man you loved.
Let her go!
Mother, no!
Don't leave me!
Listen to me...
You were wrong...
That night fifteen years ago
my father did come for you,
he was just late- -he got
there right after you left!
The owners told me!
Father never
deserted you!
He loved you!
Mother no--
you can't leave me now--
if you go away
I'll be all alone!
Well I take it this
means the wedding's off.
No. Just a small
change in cast.
With Shinsen gone, all the
Tennozu Group's assets
go to her daughter...
There will be
a marriage tonight,
and Kagura
will be my bride.
It's got me...
Saiga...!
Use your camera!
It's the only way-- you
have to take us both out!
Ginza!
Just...
do it...
I can't.
And Kagura Tennozu...
Do you take this man to be your
husband, for better or worse,..
Yurigaoka? Yeah he's
here I saw him come in...
You have to say "I do"...
My darling...
She doesn't have
to do shit!
Now you get to watch
me leave with the girl.
Mister Saiga!
It's good
to have you back.
Where are we?
The church.
Outside.
That's right...!
They tried to force me
to marry Mr. Suitengu...!
But I knew it! I knew
you'd come save me!
Then let's go.
Okay!
I will not allow it!
The wrath of God shall
sear your mortal flesh.
Now, it is time
to confess your sins.
With you for a subject it
seems a bit redundant
to use a flash...
Almost!
Kagura? Ready?
Uh-huh!
I have a marriage license that
needs to be filed right away.
Gladly.
Oh, it's...
Still unclear
at this time...
exactly what happened
inside that church today...
I don't have all day.
Oh. Consider it done.
Then it's official.
Kagura is
a married woman.
Well done.
Thank you, sir.
One more thing.
Add this
to the balance.
I can't do that...
It's not real money.
Of course sir,
please excuse me...
I'll add it
in immediately.
Repaired,
as you asked.
I've been meaning
to ask you, Saiga.
That song you're
always whistling...
What's the name of it?
Don't know...
It's just something
I picked up...
Out on the battlefield,
when I was a war photographer.
I heard it eight years ago.
I'd been sent to this
island to cover a raid
by a special forces unit.
There were rumors of secret
experiments going on there,
some weapon that had been
forbidden by an arms treaty.
I thought it'd
be my big scoop.
I guess I was wrong.
There was a explosion,
the whole unit was wiped out.
I got hit, bad.
When I woke up,
I was buried alive.
I scraped for hours,
trying to get to the top.
But it was no use.
I had given up.
I was just about
ready to die....
that's when I heard
that song,
coming from someone
trapped nearby.
We were both too badly
injured to say anything,
but he kept playing
his music box...
Over,
and over again.
I don't know if he was trying
to give me stength to hold on...
Or if he was just trying
to keep his own sanity.
Maybe it was both.
Do you know what
happened to him?
I did some checking later,
but whatever happened
on that island was classified
top secret by the military.
I couldn't find out his name,
what he looked like,
or even if he
was still alive.
But one thing
I know for sure.
He and that song
saved my life.
It's a nice thought...
That he's out there and
you might find him someday.
I guess.
Could that be it...?
Could that be when
I became a carrier?
All that's left
are tears of blood,
called forth by the winds
of nostalgia...
He can hear the music
box playing that same,
haunting song...
Until an explosion
rips through the air,
and all the
music is gone.