Here we are,
Madam Koganei.
Please,
have a seat.
This diamond just
arrived from South Africa--
you're the first
to see it.
My...
Go ahead.
Pick it up.
A full ten carats
with stunning clarity--
almost completely
flawless...
a true marvel.
I've never seen
anything quite like it.
I immediately
thought of you.
It is brilliant...
Any questions?
No...
I'll take it.
Wonderful! Would you like
to discuss a setting?
Madam...! My god,
what are you doing?
"Whore of Diamonds" Who knew
you could be so clumsy...?
You let my daughter be abducted
right in front of your eyes?
My sincerest apologies...
I have no one to blame
for this but myself.
If you could be the one
to punish me, Miss Tennozu,
I would be most grateful.
That's your plan?
Gambling I won't have the heart
to shoot my plaything?
You'll bring Kagura
back home safely, won't you,
before this
gets out of hand?
And you'll make
sure the man dies?
Yes ma'am...
You may tend
to your legs
but not until you've
gone between mine.
Dinner is served.
Just don't burn yourself...
S'not much, but they were fresh
out of the twelve-course meals.
It was either
this or cold cuts.
Thought this
would keep you warm.
Thank you, Saiga,
smells good!
Let me guess.
I should've gone
with the cold cuts?
No, not at all...!
They're perfect!
I'm just surprised--
I've never had instant
noodles before!
Hang on a sec--
you're a teenager and you've
never had a cup of ramen?
Well no--
but I have always
wanted to try it!
O-kay...
Yeah, hello.
Saiga! Oh, thank god!
Are you okay?
Yes, Bob, I'm fine.
Well our building's
become a hornet's nest,
and they're
all looking for you!
Listen, I don't know what
kind of trouble you're in,
but my sister runs
a little club in Kitasenju--
the Show Pub.
She said you could hide
there for a while--
no problem!
Thanks.
The party crowd
is just heading home now--
it's going
to be bumper-to-bumper
going this direction...
This is bad.
Hey what the hell man?
Move your fucking truck!
What'd you say...? Huh?
Man, not her.
You're lucky
I'm on the clock.
These guys
are unbelievable--
they've roadblocked
the whole street
so they can search
every damn car for you...
We'll just have
to kill some time
until the morning
rush hour starts,
and then pray we can slip
by with the commuters
in the subway system.
Okay...
But if we walk...
Oh right,
you need shoes...
And a different wardrobe
wouldn't hurt either.
This outfit
is embarrassing.
Relax-- it's to help you
blend in with the crowd.
Wait...
Come this way.
Good. I don't
think they saw us.
Looks safe enough.
Here.
Oh...
Thank you.
What...?
Uh... Um... Saiga!
Never taken a
train either, huh?
There's so many people.
Hang in there-- most
of 'em will get off soon.
So why were you
laughing back there?
I don't know...
'Cause the man in front of us
was tickling me with his hand.
Damnit...!
That was a pervert!
Speak up next time!
Hello...?
Madam Koganei,
you home?
Can't believe she
doesn't have a phone...
What the--?
Hey... Everything here
is tagged for auction...
Wonder what that's all about.
We were sent to find
Madam Koganei--
the rest is
not our business.
Ah, don't
be such a prude.
Now that's how you
shit with class.
I thought Madam
Koganei had kids?
Hell if I know.
Sorry to keep you
gentlemen waiting.
Oh, hope we didn't
scare you, madam-
Mister Suitengu
wants your help.
Well... We should
get going, then.
Can't blame her
for being tired...
Look at me, on the run with an
abused, sheltered teenage girl.
What the hell
am I thinking?
This stop,
Kitasenju Station.
This is the end of the line.
Please exit the train.
This place is weird--
it's so dirty.
Stop looking 'round
like a tourist, will ya?
Oh... Sorry.
This is it.
Not there either, huh...?
Yes yes, I understand--
I'll call you back shortly.
We've secured all the main
roads and station terminals
that lead outside
of the city...
but we still
haven't caught them...
Means they're either still
hiding somewhere close...
or they...
Excuse me, sir?
I'm trying to get to Ameyoko--
could you point me there?
Oh yeah you
mean the market?
Just keep going a few blocks
down until you-- what?
Hey, what
are you doing?
Ah, god!
God, let go of me!...
Yes, that's it...
You have Kagura's scent.
Where were you when you
put your hands on her?
A pretty girl--about 15--
with long brown hair.
On the subway!
The Hibiya Line!
The subway? Damn it!
Now I'll have to search
that entire track!
How come
no one's here?
It's a late-night
type of club--
the employees
are probably asleep.
Anyways... I'm hoping we
can lay low here, for a while.
You think Mister Suitengu
will stop looking
if he doesn't
find me soon?
I highly doubt it.
Yeah... me too.
Listen, while we're
on that topic...
I know this isn't easy...
But for our sake...
Our safety...
Anything you can remember
about what happened to you,
in those underground
rituals--
I need to know.
Okay...
I'm sorry...
I just... I...
Hey... It's all right...
Just forget it...
We can worry about
all that later, okay?
Hey, you like Karaoke,
don't you...? Sing something.
We could both
use a diversion.
What's Karaoke?
It's like singing your
favorite song in the shower...
No pressure to be good,
and you can pick what you want.
Oh...
I like hymns...
Like they sing at church.
Church hymns ...?
Yeah, it's been a while.
Well, hello.
You must be the "special
customers" Bob phoned me about.
Yeah, so that makes you,
um, Bob's "sister"?
What?
One hell of a lay...
Stop the car.
Is something wrong,
Madam...?
You're not feeling
car-sick, are you?
Just put your
foot on the brake.
Can I... help you?
What an exquisite
diamond you have.
Come, let me look at it--
one girl to another.
Okay...
It's lovely...
Hey...! What are you
doing you freak??
What the--?!
Let's go...
Only a cheap diamond
made to look expensive.
Damn it lady,
that's fucked up!
Stop the car...!
Stop it! Now!
What do you think?
I don't know-- sure as hell
can't let her do that again.
I need more...
You cocksuckers,
I need more diamonds!
No funny stuff!
Just dump the
rocks in the bag!
Take what you want--
just don't hurt us!
An old-fashioned stick up--
I'm getting nostalgic.
Yeah, the first job I ever took
was a jewelry store heist...
Gave my mom
a necklace.
She was so proud.
Sure...
The madam kind of
reminds me of my mom,
y'know, when she
was younger.
Mmm, delicious.
Yes, there's no mistake...
This is where
Miss Kagura got off.
Oh, come on, sugar,
you can be honest--
we're all friends here.
What's the story between you
and that hot hunk o' beef?
What do you mean?
Is he your sugar daddy?
My what?
Don't be stupid...
You know that can't be it...
Ooh...! He's your
teacher right?
And you've fallen
hopelessly in love...
The forbidden passion between
a teacher and his pupil...!
You're eloping, aren't you?
No, no, it's nothing
romantic like that...
They're a daughter and
step-father, that's my bet.
Boo-- scary!
Yeah, enough with
the childhood memories!
No, it's nothing
like that-- really.
But you did run
away with him right?
Yes.
Then you're free now,
that's all that matters!
I am?
Well aren't you?
You tell me.
I'm not sure yet,
actually...
What about all of you--
are you free?
Well there's no way
that I am...!
Not with the old balls-and-chain
still stuck to me!
Well then hurry up
and get rid of it!
Why do you think
I'm working so hard?
Maybe if you didn't work hard,
you'd get better tips.
Sorry about their
crudeness Kagura...
They couldn't be clean if
they were raised in a bath.
Oh no... I really
don't mind at all--
everyone seems to have
so much fun here.
Oooh...! This girl is so
adorable I can't stand it!
I want to make her
my little sister!
Hands off, Yashiro!
The big sister title
belongs to me!
Don't you mean
big brother?
Speak for yourself.
Can it...! You haven't even
asked what she thinks...!
You're probably scaring
the poor girl silly!
No, I think it's great--
I don't have any real siblings.
Good... Then in
that case, it's decided!
From this day forward, you can
be a little sister to all of us!
Yay!
All right, Kagura!
Welcome to the family!
Wonderful!
Yoo-hoo "Simon"...
Where's that whiskey
and water...?
Chop, chop! Our customers
need their drinks!
Yeah, yeah...
I'm coming.
I guess no one hides
for free.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Show Pub David!
And now,
it's Sexy Showtime!
So...! Let's
get kinky, girls!
Take it off!
I'm not gonna
regret this!
Oh yeah!
I must've lost my mind.
I was expecting you
over an hour ago.
We had to take
a little detour.
Madam... The night finds
you more radiant than ever.
Thank you!
Are you happy...?
That's a worthy frame.
Oh, just take her
picture already...
After all...
She is quite lovely.
What a stupid irony.
Finally find a subject,
and I can't take the shot.
You sure that cute little
heiress is hanging around
in a dump like this?
Yes... There's no doubt.
Yeah! Bravo! Encore!
Now, for our finale...
Young Kagura
will sing for us!
What?
Yeah! Alright!
Let's go...! We can't
keep your audience waiting!
Wait, I--
She's here.
Don't be shy, sweetie--
go for broke!
We'll be right behind
you the whole time!
Okay.
Hurry up and sing!
Yeah, we'll cheer no
matter how bad you are!
Show us what you got!
♪ Amazing grace,
♪ How sweet the sound,
♪ That saved a
wretch like me...
♪ I once was lost,
♪ But now am found,
♪ Was blind, but now I see...
♪ T'was grace that taught
my heart to fear,
♪ And grace my fears--
Beautifully sung Goddess--
you gave me chills...
You've had
your adventure...
Now it's time
to come home.
Oh, yeah!
Take it off, honey!
There's a carnivore in the
room with skin like diamonds.
Cold, hard,
and impossible to bruise.
In this city, greed
can take you like madness,
until all you want
to do is feed.
But you can't weigh
love by the carat.