Kagura...
You asshole...
What've you done
with Kagura?
What good will it do you
to know that, Mister Saiga?
You'll never see
the Goddess's smile again.
You're just like the rest of
Suitengu's little lap dogs...
I'll fuckin'
kill you, too.
Vulgar Suitengu.
He was the conductor's baton
that started the march.
But we have our
own momentum now.
Matters have evolved far
beyond crude solo acts.
What the hell
does that mean?
Nothing a trivial man like you
should concern himself with.
Joe...
And now the music
I promised.
The song of parting.
Think of the Goddess...
and die!
This is it!
The perfect feeling!
The heightened senses!
The vibration!
Damn...
I can feel it!
Your soul
is vibrating too!
Don't leave yet,
there's still more!
That was
just the overture.
Now comes
the good part!
Vibrations, huh?
That's what
emotions are.
Tangible pulsing,
shaking your bones!
Fear! Fury!
Sorrow! Joy!
And by creating vibrations,
humans can express themselves!
So let's have it!
You and I!
A session of souls!
You can't
run from me.
There's still more!
This is it,
Saiga!
Do you feel
it pulsing?
The ultimate sensation
of sight and sound!
Damn it.
My eyes!
Saiga is in there,
isn't he?
Hey, wait!
Come back!
Ah, fuck.
They can't be...!
Toda!
Sakuragi!
Oizumi!
Come on... Joe!
Hang in there, kid...!
You can't be dead...!
You're just
a damn kid...!
Joe! Joe!!
Saiga...!
He's gone.
What the fuck
happened here?
This city is falling apart and
you cops haven't done shit...!
So we took matters
into our own hands...!
They were respectable men and
women, pillars of the community,
sacrificing to fight
the vultures
who are preying
on this country!
And this
is the result?
This is some
sort of list.
The Prime Minister's
name is on it,
along with most
of his cabinet members.
It's probably the
club membership list
that Joe had been
talking about.
Club? You mean the one
Suitengu's been running?
That's right...
We were gonna present it at
the next legislative assembly
and cause a shitstorm
that not even
the ball-less mass media
could dance around...
But now...
Hell, I can't believe
they're all dead!
Oh, god!
They were
Japan's last hope...
That fucker!
Hey, wait!
Come on.
Don't quit on me yet.
Good morning,
citizens!
This is your incumbent
representative to Parliament,
Seiji Ochiai!
I want to thank you all for your
years of enthusiastic support!
You know election
day is approaching,
so I've come out
to make a final bid
for your endorsement
at the polls...
If re-elected, I promise to see
the pseudo-intellectuals,
pseudo-journalists,
pseudo-feminists,
and all other
public enemies,
purged from our
beautiful streets!
I will work to build a new,
stronger nation,
dedicated to those
upstanding citizens
who are true hedonists.
Thank you,
thank you all very much!
Your stirring
cheers of support
will help build
the Japan of tomorrow!
I wish my opponent,
candidate Saiga,
the best of luck.
What's the
meaning of this?
Why are you treating me
like I'm one of them?
I demand to see
Ochiai immediately!
He said if I did my part,
I could have Kagura for my work!
Where the hell have
you taken us, anyway?
Professor Nishiya!
What kind of game
have you been playing...?
Were you lying to us...?
From the start?
Oh no...
That means Saiga...
Where are you
people taking us?
How could they
do this to me?
I was promised that I would have
both of them for my research!
He can't get
away with this...
I won't let him!
Hey!
Professor!
Stay where you are...
All of you!
This is
sulfuric acid...
If I spill this, it'll eat
the flesh right off her bones!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
I won't be delayed
any longer!
I have to move forward
with my research!
None of you understand the
importance of this discovery!
I'm warning you!
Don't come
any closer!
Please! Stop!
You're better
than this, Nishiya!
Use your head!
There's no one
left to interfere.
Sulfuric acid was
a good bluff, wasn't it?
Want to know what
was really in there?
A culture of the virus
I extracted from Saiga.
I've just turned
myself into a carrier.
All I need now is to be
exposed to your bodily fluids.
Stop it...!
Just stay away from me!
I need to discover
for myself...
I know the virus changes
the body by reconfiguring DNA,
templating to
subconscious desires.
But what's the connection
between the virus
and the subconcious?
What?
No!
Just cooperate.
It's in the name
of science!
Get offa' me...!
No! Stop!
I have to see it work,
for the sake of my research!
We don't have
any choice...!
I need your catalyst to
activate the virus in me!
No!
I'm sacrificing too,
experimenting on myself...!
Now just give me powers
like you gave Saiga!
They'll probably manage
to break the door down soon,
but don't worry:
This should
only take a minute.
You might
even enjoy it!
No!!!
It's okay now, Kagura.
I've got you.
Don't touch me!
Get away!
Calm down, Kagura,
it's me.
Dr. yogoku...
You're okay now.
If you're smart you won't
give us any more trouble.
We'll be good.
Saiga...
Candidate Saiga
did his best,
but lost the election
in a landslide.
But don't be discouraged,
photographer.
You still have your
meaningless journalism career
to fall back on.
Pretty bold for a man who
got his start in the papers.
Ridiculous!
I'm Representative Ochiai!
Member of Parliament!
A man of import!
I'm no scum-sucking
media lapdog!
Journalists and
activists are useless.
What does a camera take?
Pictures, not action!
What did the White
Eagles accomplish?
Talk, not change!
They coulda done a lot
if you hadn't betrayed them.
I didn't betray.
I only led them
to their natural end.
See, when I joined Parliament,
I realized a vital truth.
Authority belongs to those
of us with the power
to shape history.
Those who oppose us are destined
to be crushed in our wake.
Journalists are
merely spectators,
describing the world
we create.
Sounds like fascist nonsense...
That's crap!
Oh, I assure you,
it is mankind's only truth...
The strong seize power and
earn the right to rule ...
While the weak simply
moan and take pictures.
Did your photographs
ever change the world?
Did they lessen the number
of struggles, and wars?
Through your lens,
you saw the world's pain.
Why didn't
you save them?
Lift a weapon, instead
of pressing the shutter?
I know why. You wanted to
capture that decisive moment!
You craved the fame--
the glory...!
And you called it
"journalism," "justice."
But in reality,
it was just a delusion.
No. You don't know
shit...! I...
That's not--
That's not who I am!
It's okay,
Mister Saiga...
Take your petty,
self-serving pictures,
and claim it's
for a greater good.
The powerful...
The authority
of the nation
will protect your
freedom of the press.
We will preserve you
and your hypocrisy,
because freedom cannot
exist without authority.
Do you truly believe freedom
and civil rights exist
independent
of authority?
Look at the Goddess,
freedom incarnate.
Right now, the Prime Minister,
symbol of authority,
is keeping her safe.
Kagura...
Son of a bitch.
Now, now, photographer,
you mustn't run.
This is one of those epic
moments you love to exploit.
A train full
of commuters.
I wonder how many will
die because of you?
Oh no, you've
dropped your camera.
But that's the most
important part, isn't it?
Go on, pick it up,
take your pictures!
See what difference
they make!
You are going to die.
Amid the glory,
the praise... the hypocrisy.
I've taken pictures
of what I wanted...
Glory and praise had
nothing to do with it!
Nor did it matter that
your subjects were dying.
Or that
you're dying now!
Now you
listen to me!
Here's somethin' any good
war photographer knows...
"If your pictures
aren't good enough...
you're not
close enough."
Yes, Saiga,
I feel it!
Good vibrations!
Licadonia?
They'd been given asylum
in the Licadonian Embassy.
Unfortunately, it seems they've
since been moved elsewhere.
Ochiai's work.
I believe so.
I've tried
contacting him,
but his people say
he can't be reached.
So the old maverick has
finally made his move.
And the man gripping
his reigns...
Kamiya himself.
The Prime Minister, sir?
How goes
our other project?
Rather well, sir.
We've nearly
completed liquidation
of all Tennozu
Group assets.
This evening will mark
the Club's grand reopening...
Be sure to notify
all of our members.
Sir.
The Last Supper
can finally begin.
My God, it's
what I thought.
Saiga...
Mannequin legs?
Fuck!
Not nice, Captain.
I really don't like
uninvited guests.
Damn you!
You're the
fucking chief...
How could you--
That was unlawful entry...
Self defense,
to use your phrase.
You may have noticed,
I'm not the tallest man.
And while I can't
say it's been easy,
it's always given me
the perfect view.
Your legs, Captain.
You have the most
fantastic pair.
Powerful, and long.
Just between us, I've wanted
to add them to my collection
for a long time, ever
since you joined the force!
But to think you'd
bring them to me.
Just walk them right in...
It's a dream come true.
Ka... Kagura...
Wounded hearts that
call out to each other--
even from afar...
As the deadline
approaches,
an insatiable hunger
is revealed...
And an explosion lights the
fires of the final contest.