There's nothing in here about
what happened at the church.
Despite all those reporters
standing right there...
Musta been bought off...
Shit, even the press in
this country is corrupt.
Something
tells me, though;
Suitengu won't
be so quick to forget.
I drink maybe I've had
too much to think...
Cap'n.
Saiga...
you asshole...
Next stop...
Omiya...
Omiya.
Where are
we going... Saiga?
Nevermind...
I don't care as
long as you're here.
Wow! The sea!
When I was a child,
The Little Mermaid was
my favorite storybook.
Hate to break it to ya
but you're still a child.
The Little Mermaid
lived under the sea...
and when she turned fifteen,
she was allowed to swim to
the surface for the first time,
and see the world above,
as she'd always dreamed.
And that's when she saw a
handsome prince on a ship
and fell in love with him.
Sorry kid... but
I'm no handsome prince.
You're really funny
sometimes Saiga...
That was just
a fairy tale.
She don't look
like no hitman.
She was in a film a few years
back-- made a big splash.
She's an actress?
She only did the one movie.
Just got another update
from the coppers...
They were last spotted
headed up north.
What, is she some kinda
fuckin' mute , too?
Fuck if I know.
The Little Mermaid lost
her beautiful voice.
She desired human legs,
so she could be with
her beloved prince...
The Sea Witch gave the Mermaid
what she desired,
but took away
her voice in exchange.
What have I lost
in exchange for this?
Oh Mother...!
Kagura...?
Kagura,
you're burning up!
Why didn't you say
something to me?
How long have you
had this fever?
I'm going to get
you some help, okay,
you just need
to hold on...
She's gone...
Mother's gone...
Miharu Tsurumaki...
When she was five, her mother
attempted a murder-suicide.
Only got it half-right,
though... Miharu lived.
Since then...
she hasn't uttered a word.
It wasn't her first
scare, either...
Her mother had dragged her
into the sea many times before.
Time and again,
she nearly drowned.
Poor kid--
That's fucked up.
There are plenty
of men who'll take pity
on a downtrodden
beauty like her...
Thanks to them she's
never missed a meal.
Can a fragile broad like
her really handle him?
Don't be misled, that is
the face of death itself.
I finally managed
to finagle us a car.
It's a hunk of junk,
but it'll have to do.
There's s'posed to be an inn
way up in the hills...
We're gonna have to lay
low some place off
the beaten
path for now...
Think you can hang
on 'til we get there?
Don't worry
about me... I'm fine.
You're definitely
not fine...!
I can feel the heat coming off
your forehead from here.
So do you still
have a headache?
My mother must be really
upset with me right now.
It's not fair that
I'm still alive and she's...
But none of that
matters, does it?
As long as I've got you
by my side... even if I die...
Don't finish that sentence!
Quit with the dying crap...!
You're still just a child!
Don't get angry...
I'm not getting angry!
Look at you.
Saiga you've been acting
weird around me all day ...
Please tell me what
I did to make you so mad.
Why'd you even bother
coming to save me
if all I do
is make you miserable?
I'm sorry... It's not you
that I'm mad at.
I guess I'm just not cut out
for this parenting crap...
I mean I don't know if
I should give you medicine...
Or if that'll make
you sick or worse or--
I just don't know.
I'm sorry,...
I'm so immature.
Hey, if anybody's being
immature here... it's me.
Best I can hope to do...
is to go on
holdin' Kagura's hand
through the end of her
way too short life...
Well, at least until this
curse claims me, too...
The two of us, marching
towards our deaths,
like a god damned
double suicide.
I think I figured out
what your deal is...
Yeah, well try
not to talk...
You should rest.
Okay spit it out.
Well at first I thought...
you were like this
amazing superhero...
But...
turns out...
you're just
really awkward.
So I'm awkward, huh?
Go back to sleep, Kagura.
Thick fog...
Hey lady...! You might wanna
watch where you're goin'!
Are you out here
all by yourself?
Can't talk can you?
Hey... do I know
you from somewhere?
'cause I just can't kick
this feeling that...
I've seen you
before but I don't--
Look, I'd love to help you out
but now is not a good time.
Sorry I can't
give you a lift.
Look, if you keep followin' this
road, you'll reach a town...
Get someone there
to help you. I--
Hey!
Wait, where
you taking me?!
Was there something
out here, or--?
Let... go 'a me!
What the hell
is goin' on here?
That kiss was
as cold as ice.
It's hot...
So hot...
Your fever's
actin' up again...
Want me to crack
open a window?
Please...
That's strange...
So cold...
What's wrong?
There's a woman...
She just appeared
outta nowhere...
Where?
There...
Is she a ghost?
A ghost...
Of course...
Saiga...
I'm scared...
There's no such thing...
I've seen too many people
die in my lifetime...
and not a one of
'em ever came back.
Ghosts only exist in
fairy tales and movies.
I remember one movie
with a ghost in it...
Saw it years ago.
And it was that woman.
The director cast some
mute actress in the role
since the ghost
had no lines
and he thought it'd make
her seem more otherworldly.
You think that
actress is here?
Let's go.
Yeah, I remember now.
The rumors.
How the director
was screwing her,
and when things went sour
he tried to kill them both.
Only, she survived and cashed
in with a huge insurance payout.
One after the other, Miharu
wrapped her men in her arms
and dragged them
into the sea...
And every time, she's
emerged the sole survivor.
So you're sayin' this
murder-suicide shit's
like her gimmick?
I think she sees the water
as a surrogate
for her dead mother's
embrace...
only place she can go to
silence the guilt of living.
Saiga... something's
not right about this fog.
'cause there's
something in the fog.
In the fog?
Whatever it is it's
definitely not a ghost.
What is it?!
Whatever happens--
stay in the car!
Damn it. Lens
is all fogged up.
Saiga...!
Saiga!
A mermaid?
So...
Is this how I die...?
Guess there are
worse ways to go...
I'm sorry, sweetie,
but it's all too much...
Mommy has to leave you.
Mommy please
stop crying.
We could go
together again.
Take me with you.
At last...
I can be with her...
What's with the downpour
all of a sudden?
It's like--
glowin'...
It smells like Miharu.
She used too much power--
evaporated into the atmosphere.
I suppose her
wish was granted.
Kagura...!
Don't die on me!
It's not your time!
Please... I thought you'd
figured out by now...
it'll take alot more than
just that to kill me.
You're right...
You're too strong to die...
Too strong.
I was wrong just to
give up and accept it...
I swear, I will find
a way to fix you.
I will never...
let you die!
You see...
just awkward.
It's accounting time
for the corporate beast,
and even the most violent
exchanges must be valued,
and inked in the books.
What are the costs
of your actions?
And were they worth it?
What price can you
put on a human life?