Kamu pemerintah?
(Satema) kamu!
(Demura)!
You almost took a bullet.
You alright?
Guess so...
Goddamn pervert...
You got a freaking hard-on.
That was the moment
I first woke up.
When I caught every man's
destiny on a strip of celluloid,
thirty five millimeters wide.
So how the hell
did I wind up here?
There's serious opposition
in your own party
about this revised
Pharmaceutical Affairs Law!
Will you comment
on your announcement
at the cabinet meeting?
How many arms did
you have to twist?
All right...
Clear a path-- the Prime
Minister's a busy man.
Please Mr. Prime Minister,
give us a headline!
Why are you pushing
this through so quickly?
What are you--...?
Get that camera out of here!
What a boring subject...
But it pays my bills.
It's been over a decade
since the Bubble War,
when the global
economy burst,
and the insiders who held
the needle pulled out early,
then swooped in like
vultures to eat the remains
at a fraction
of the cost.
You know the drill.
The rich got richer, and
the poor were out of luck.
Welcome to Tokyo, the city
where all the winners
came to jerk
each other off.
If you've got money,
you can buy anything
your sick mind
can dream up.
If you don't, you just
try not to get crushed
beneath the wheels.
In a city like this,
there's not a single thing
worth the cost of my film.
Damn it...!
That performance was abysmal!
It wasn't me at all!
No, the real dance...
The real me is ...!
Who are you?
I met with you
earlier this week --
I'm Miss Kokubunji ...
If you recall,
you promised you'd see
my daughter dance today.
She's very talented--
we're hoping you'll
take her under your wing.
Very well,
let's see her dance.
Go on, Kozue.
Ye-Yes ma'am.
No, no,
that's all wrong...!
Look how stiff
your arms are!
Stretch your body!
Be like rubber!
Stop!
More! You're
not even trying!
You're hurting me!
Mr. Shirogane!
Let go of her, please!
Somebody! Somebody
call an ambulance!
Hardly worth my time.
Yes?
Well, hello...
What can I do
for you Mr. Suitengu?
Sounds lovely...
I haven't danced
enough tonight.
Saiga-babe, you're
getting expensive.
The public safety authorities
don't come cheap.
I didn't ask you
to bail me out, Ginza.
I never do.
You're impossible.
By the way, you familiar
with a politican named Nakano?
Sure, he's that Health
and Welfare Minister
who's raising Cain over this
Pharmaceutical Reform Bill.
That's right, tiger.
And apparently he
doesn't feel too safe.
He just asked for a big
bump in police security.
Startin' to think
the guy's in trouble...
Son of a--...
A "thank you"
would've been nice.
Now then,
where were we?
Ah yes,
the money...
See I'm running
a little short this month,
cost of living and all.
So why don't you open
your wallet a bit wider,
and I'll forget
I saw these.
Deal?
Shit...
Just 'cause you got a badge
don't mean you can extort me!
Damn you!
For the record, boys,
that was self-defense.
Bitch ass--!
Don't make me
self-defense you, too.
This feel I've longed
for... This aroma...
This flexibility...!
Finally!.
I can be the real me!
What the--?
Take him down!
What?
Please, spare me!
Let's make a deal...!
I swear, we'll give
you anything you want!
Councillor Okubo...
Strange...
Hell of a way to go.
Looks like their heads were
twisted around in a vice.
Always the first on the scene.
I don't know how you do it.
Now get out before
I arrest you.
Right on the mark
this time, wasn't I...?
You get so excited
when you're looking
through that lens.
You're such a pervert.
Stop it...
We're working.
I told you, baby doll, you don't
have to worry about that...
I'm pulling down
enough for us both--
I'll take care of you.
Tempting, Ginza.
But no thanks.
Hey!
Well in that case
I'll need collateral...
You can have your little toy
back when you come to my place.
Come on, Ginza.
Stop joking around.
Who's joking...? I've got
serious needs, Saiga...
And since you've been
stripped of your passport,
you've got a
short list of options.
Can't leave the country,
can't leave me.
Try it,
and I'll kill you.
Hey, Saiga.
Saiga!
Wait!
Let me guess, Bob. Your
boyfriend dumped you again??
No! I dumped him...!
Fucking bastard...
he was messing around
with another guy!
Oh, no.
Not Jimmy.
No! Charlie...!
Oh please, won't you
take me in and comfort me?!
Sorry, Bob...
Same-sex marriage
isn't legal in Japan.
Saiga!
Nice try, Ginza.
Nakano and Kawaguchi.
Former Health, Labor
and Welfare Minister
and Director of the
Drug Administration,
massacred while in private talks
in a heavily guarded hotel.
That makes five, now.
They all opposed
the Drug Reform Bill,
and they've
all turned up dead.
That's right...
Heavy stuff...
Obviously someone
big's pulling the strings.
No doubt...
So what do you say
we find the puppeteer?
Ever heard anything
about the Roppongi Club?
Only rumors. Some kind
of secret society--
Open solely
to the ultra-rich,
and offering the
kind of debauchery
that would
make Nero proud.
That's the one...
As long as its members
shell out the cash,
the club claims it can satisfy
any desire imaginable...
legal or otherwise.
And you think these
pleasure-brokers are connected
to the murders, somehow?
That's what we're
going to find out.
Last week's hit was
the Vice-Minister of HLW...
My guys have been
investigating a car
that was inadvertently
photographed near the scene.
Turns out, the car belongs
to Roppongi Development,
a subsidiary
of the Tennozu Group.
The Tennozu Group...?
You mean the ones
who built that
big-ass skyscraper
in the Roppongi district?
That's right...
Real Estate...
Construction...
Information...
The Tennozu Group
does it all...
They've been buying up every
piece of the market they can,
and it's made 'em one
hell of a profit machine.
Some say as Tennozu goes,
so goes the Japanese economy.
At the top of it all
is Lady Shinsen Tennozu,
who runs the conglomerate
like its unchallenged queen.
This is her number two,
her right hand man...
Director of Roppongi
Development, Choji Suitengu.
And rumor has it
he's the man in control
of the Roppongi Club,
as well.
This photo's crap.
I don't know
about that...
Mr. Suitengu's
a private man--
never shows his
face in public...
That's the only pic
we've ever gotten of him--
Tabloids'd
pay a fortune...
But you see
the challenge here.
This club's like an urban
legend around Tokyo.
No hard facts,
no real clues...
That photo's the closest
thing I have to a lead.
Nonsense. You got
all the clues you need.
Next stop, Saiga...
Saiga Station...
All aboard!
Awfully light drink
for you, Saiga.
Don't tell me you're
going to meetings, now.
Don't piss yourself.
I'm still on the clock.
Just dumb luck this
seat has a perfect view.
Photographing a high official
in his private office.
You're asking for it.
I'm just watching.
Think that matters to them?
By the way, what's
with the poster?
I'm seeing it everywhere.
And I hear you
took the picture.
I don't do ads,
you know that.
It's a picture
I shot way back.
Someone wanted to use it,
and I was hard on cash.
Aren't we all...
Well, this is my stop.
See you 'round..
Just watch your
step on the way out.
The other day I was cleaning
that storage compartment,
and the floor gave out.
A hole big enough
to climb through...
We got holes all over
this district now,
thanks to that damn
"Geo Front" program.
You should move down there.
Make it a subway bar.
Ah hell...
Asshole...
Here goes nothing...
I love it when I'm right...
Damn it.
Now what...?
Wait a minute.
If my bearings are right...
Nex--
Back already... What's up,
you forget something?
Just transferring
to the subway line...
Oh, hey... Can you move my
car if you see any cops?
Thanks.
An air duct...
Deep enough...
All Luxury cars...
Must be the place.
Should be a
memorable night.
Yes. I heard there's going
to be a divine ritual.
Hey... Long time no see.
How'd you get here??
Sleep tight.
Son of a bitch.
An actual subway.
An entire underground system
built solely for them,
so not even the members
know where they end up.
Quite a production...
Must be one
hell of a club.
To the winner
the spoils, right?
Unbelievable...
How could they
build something
like this right under
the streets of Tokyo?
So this is it.
And Ginza
calls me perverse.
I recognize them all,
too, even with the masks.
Politicians,
celebrities, CEOs...
Suitengu...
Damn it. Which way?
Lost him.
This place is a maze.
What is this?
Ladies and gentlemen, valuable
patrons of the Roppongi Club...
Welcome to a night of
decadence and desire.
There you are...
Tonight we have a man who seeks
the blessings of the Goddess,
and fulfillment
of his deepest want.
And like all who climb
the steps of her altar,
he is willing to put
his life on the line...
Will his anointment
bring ultimate pleasure,
or a pitiful death...?
Initiant,
are you prepared?
Pleasure is
the only truth...
The driving force from
which all life derives...
Without it we have no purpose,
and can only wait for death.
Goddess on high...!
Please give this
brave man your blessing!
Who would have thought...
In a madhouse
like this...
I'd finally
find my subject.
Grab him!
Taking a picture
inside these walls
is an unforgivable taboo...
Any true member knows that.
And what do we do with
intruders, patrons?
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
No...! No!
What are you
waiting for?
Take him away from
the Goddess, immediately!
He stole it...!
That was supposed
to be mine!
Kagura...
what have you done?
The Syndrome wasted
on a low-life like him...
Death to the intruder!
At once!
Only one thing's for sure.
The world doesn't
run on love or mercy.
It runs on greed.
And everyone has their price.
It's a place where not even
an innocent child
is safe from being turned
into a money machine.