That same nightmare again...
Eight-thirty five?
But I set the alarm
before I went to sleep.
Why on earth are you
still in bed, Kagura?
Did you oversleep again?
Sorry, Mother...
Good morning.
You had better get a move on,
or you'll be late for school...
And I'm sorry...
but you missed breakfast.
Yes, ma'am.
Where did it go?
What's the matter now?
My school uniform,
it's missing...
I know I hung it
here last night.
Well clearly you didn't.
Maybe it was just a dream.
How'd it get there?
Hurry, Kagura. You don't
have time to dawdle.
Yes, ma'am.
Look at you,
running in the house...
What has happened
to your manners?
Young lady, you really should
develop better work habits,
like preparing for the day
before you go to bed at night.
Yes ma'am.
Have a good day.
Our sunshine emerges.
The day can begin.
Oh, good morning.
Good morning...
Is everything all right?
You look a little
under the weather.
Oh, she's perfectly
fine, Suitengu...
Silly girl just overslept
and missed breakfast.
You know how she
loves her sleep.
Good morning, Miss Tennozu,
good to see you...
I'm sorry to hear
that, Kagura.
You should wake up earlier--
growing girls need to eat.
Pardon me, Kagura...
I've packed your lunch.
There's no need...
I've already prepared
a special lunch
for my daughter
on my own...
Here.
Thank you.
A loving mother's
home cooked meal.
Can't get any better
than that, can you?
Good morning, Kagura.
Good morning.
Ushigome...
Ma'am?
Why don't you take this
other lunch for yourself?
Grateful
as always, ma'am.
Kagura seems to be
trimming down a bit.
You think?
It's hard to believe.
She eats like a pig
whenever she gets the chance.
I think she's
a beautiful girl.
Takes after her mother.
She's disgusting,
is what she is.
Shiny hair,
perfect skin.
And not even the
hint of a wrinkle...
It's like watching the canvas
of some master painter,
becoming more
beautiful every day.
It's enough to make
a mother sick...
I feel like she's gaining
what I'm losing, Suitengu...
Like she's a parasite,
absorbing my very essence.
That's simply untrue.
She's an unripe grape,
and you, a full-bodied wine.
You've always been
good at compliments.
What can I say, Miss Tennozu?
You're the woman of my dreams.
I do love to hear those
words fall from your mouth.
Yet you still insist we have
to wait to share our passion
with the world?
I'm beginning to think
you have other reasons.
Maybe you love
Kagura, instead?
Don't be silly.
It's not like I have
a Lolita complex.
I'm committed to upholding
my responsibility:
Taking care of all your...
smoke and mirrors...
And a relationship with you
would put me in the spotlight...
My dirty dealings could tarnish
the Tennozu Group's name.
We'll just have to wait until
your dream is realized, my love,
and Japan belongs to you.
While you're here,
Suitengu...
I understand the chief
cabinet secretary
is enjoying
your club very much.
An important gathering place
for important people...
Whatever you're doing...
you'd better keep it up.
Until next time,
Miss Tennozu.
Good morning,
Madam President.
So I've heard.
The Governor of Tokyo has been
waiting to speak with you.
Begging for campaign
money, no doubt.
Hey, Kagura...
You're always eating
lunch by yourself--
Why don't you
join us for once?
Yeah right... I, for one,
would be interested to see
what kind of food the heir
to the Tennozu Group brings.
Stop it...
You see!
Yeah, I knew there was
something freakish about her!
No wait...
I can explain...
I-- Kagura?
Are you okay?
Are you feeling
any better, Kagura?
Miss Wakaba...
It's all right.
You don't have to get up.
You... have a mild
case of anemia.
Have you been
eating enough?
I'm your teacher,
I care about you--
I need you
to be honest.
The other girls say you
bring an empty lunch box
to school every day.
I... I'm on a diet,
that's all.
I know
that's not true.
You're not the type
who would starve yourself,
even if there are
problems at home...
Now I want you
to eat this, okay?
Yes-- yes ma'am...
Thank you, Miss Wakaba...
Oh you poor thing...
I should've known...
Your stomach's
gotten so weak.
Maybe I shouldn't be asking,
Kagura, but I need to know...
Is your mother abusing you?
Is she not letting you eat?
I suspected as much...
That settles it,
I'll speak with her today...!
I don't care
how rich she is
or how important her business
dealings are to this city.
She has a
responsibility to you.
She's a horrible mother
for treating her own daughter
in this way.
And now, an update
on the murder
of former Health
Minister Nakano...
We're running out
of space here.
Yeah, business
must be booming.
We'll need
another warehouse.
What the hell?
Lucky for you there's
still two-thirds intact...
If a single bill goes missing,
Suitengu will know.
You can guess
what happens then.
I'm sorry sir...
We'll kill every rat we see.
My philosophy exactly...
Oh, and there'll be one
more delivery today.
Shit!
I'm still short!
Gotta be some change
in here somewhere...
God damn... it...!
C'mon...!
Hey, Dad...
I need a soccer ball!
Buy me one!
Shut up...!
Can't you see I'm busy?!
Now get out!
Well give me some
money and I will!
Come on, everyone
else has one!
Your allowance--
Give it back!
I'll pay you
double next week!
Yeah right, I already
spent it, okay...!
Ah, this is why mom left,
'cause you're such
a freaking cheap-skate!
I don't have time
for this shit! Get out!
Come on, there's
gotta be something...
Gotcha!
Yes...
Payment in full...
We've counted
several times.
Mister Otsuka...
Your requital is three hundred
million, nothing less.
I'm telling you,
it's a mistake!
There must be something
wrong with the machine!
I counted--
I know I had it all!
Don't give us excuses...
There are no discounts
for membership fees--
you pay us in full!
If you cannot present
the full amount in cash
by this date and hour, you will
surrender all of your assets
to the Tennozu Group,
without exception.
That was our agreement,
Mister Otsuka,
which includes the proceeds
on your life insurance policy.
But I did have
enough, I swear!
C'mon. Let's go.
No...! Please,
just count it again!
Don't be a sore loser,
Mister Otsuka.
You had a hell
of a good time, pal.
No reason
to regret it now.
Don't worry about
changing your will.
We'll take care
of everything.
Wait, damn it!
Please!
This is a mistake!
Look, count it!
Count it! Just count it
one more time!
You bastards!
I swear!
I had enough!
You were living
beyond your means,
trying to sit
at the big kids' table.
You've got no one
to blame but yourself.
No! Don't kill me,
please, I have a son!
Quit strugglin'.
Just think
of something pretty.
Hey kid...
A word of advice...
In this country, lives can be
bought and sold on a whim...
Should you deem it
necessary to take my life,
I suggest you make a lot of
money and come buy it from me.
I just got off the phone
with your mother, Kagura...
She's agreed to speak with me,
so I'll head over there now
and smooth things out
before you get home.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll demand
an explanation,
and let her know you
can't be treated like this.
Things are going to change
for you, I promise.
Excuse me?
I hate to ask,
but could I possibly borrow
some money from you?
Borrow some money, ma'am?
Yes sir... I'd like to buy
something to eat somewhere.
Sorry, no can do,
little lady.
I'm neither allowed to stop this
car nor to give you any money...
Your mother was quite specific
with her instructions.
Hello, I'm home.
Someone's
in my bedroom...
Miss... Wakaba?
Kagura...
I'm glad
we had this talk.
As promised,
you may leave here
with all the money
you can carry...
But your
clothes stay here.
Miss Wakaba, why?
Kagura, please,
pick that up for me.
Hurry, damn it!
Looks like
a busy afternoon.
I was tutoring her teacher...
A simple study in economics.
When you're at the top
everything has a price tag.
A valuable lesson.
Speaking of lessons, Kagura,
it's time for your
piano practice.
I've come to take you
to your instructor's house.
Suitengu...
How is the little
girl in that photograph
able to smile like that?
Who knows... I don't often
ponder the well being
of third world
inhabitants.
Maybe she found
some bread.
She's poor, but in a way,
at least she's free.
Freedom,?
I never pegged you
as a romantic, Kagura...
But unfortunately, people must
pay for their freedom here,
and it usually comes rented
on a short-term lease...
With mortgages, taxes,
the cost of living,
the poor are never free.
They suffer with meager scraps
of money their whole lives,
miserable prisoners of a society
built to massage the rich.
That's what this
country is about.
If that's true, then
I want to escape!
To somewhere far away!
I'm scared
I'm losing my mind...!
I have these
terrible nightmares,
almost every night!
I'm so afraid!
They're only dreams, your mind's
way of confronting a world
that can be a truly
frightening place...
That's why you're being
given the finest academic
and cultural educations--
to rise above it--
to reach your potential and
succeed your mother one day.
Concentrate!
I'm sorry, sir...
It's just... that smell...
It's starting
to get to me.
Try it-- try it all again,
from the beginning.
Yes, sir.
I can't go on.
When I see those
hands of hers
I lose my patience!
How can I work like this?
I need new hands-- fresh,
beautiful, graceful hands!
You see?
My sweet Angel's arms
are already decaying!
Ugh. He could at least
try to preserve her.
Please forgive me,
Angel! Forgive me!
Don't worry, Maestro,
the Club is gathering tonight.
I assure you, you'll
have your new arms.
You mean it--
a new pair??
Yes...
We're holding a Divine
Ritual for the VIPs,
a few casualties are
always part of the bill.
Kagura... It's time for the
world to see the real you.
Who... am I...?
What... am I?
Kill!
Kill! Kill!
Can you help me...?
Take me away from
this terrible place...!
Please...!
What are you waiting for?
Take him away from the
Goddess, immediately!
Kagura, what
have you done...?
This vermin can't possibly
carry the Euphoria Factor.
Death to the intruder,
at once!
Without warning, I was
snatched from my hollow void ,
by a girl who gave me
power beyond imagination.
Now my bizarre fascination, once
hidden deep within my psyche,
is staring me straight
in the face.