Officer!
Mind tellin' me
why the hell you're all
just standin' around?
Technically that's
federal land,
we haven't gotten
clearance to step in yet.
What are you
talkin' about?
Our superiors haven't
given us any orders at all.
The Prime Minister's house
has been attacked...!
Where's the SDF?
They shoulda been
called in by now!
We've tried them, but they
don't have orders, either.
Across the board, none of
the higher-ups can be found.
What, did they fall into
a fuckin' black hole...?
There's gotta be somebody,
uh, the D-Defense Minister!
Or the Deputy
Prime Minister!
If they're important
enough to give orders,
you're not gonna find 'em.
Captain Ginza!
How the hell do ya
know that...?
Hey!
Saiga!
You two!
Hands up!
Not so fast.
Captain Ginza,
New Metro P.D...
These guys aren't suspects,
they're with me...
You go on inside
and look for survivors.
Weren't you listening?
We don't have
authorization for that.
Forget your goddamn
authorization...
The whole place
is a blood bath...
Now do the job you're paid for
and try to save some lives!
If you got a badge,
come with us!
Yes, sir!
Jesus, what
happened in there?
Kamiya's dead.
Suitengu killed him.
What?
Tell me you at least
got some pictures.
Sorry,
no such luck.
That isn't like you.
Give him a break, old man, don't
you know what his camera doe--
Drop it.
You! Get your gear.
We're goin' in.
Tell me you're gonna
get a scoop out of this.
You're damn straight, a full
exposé on how the mighty fall.
Gotta avenge Joe's
death somehow.
Come on. Let's get
you outta here.
What is this?
Who the hell is this guy?
Choji Suitengu, CEO
of the Tennozu Group.
I see. The manager of
the secret club in question?
That's not all.
He seems to be the beast
that wiped out our Special
Forces eight years ago,
when they were
secretly deployed
to neutralize
a bio-weapons lab,
after our treaties
made it too risky.
Uh-huh... So he's a,
he's a leftover
from the living
weapons project
we funded in
collaboration with Japan.
I was briefed on
it this morning.
He's managed to stay under
our radar all this time.
Mr. President, we must
eliminate him. Right now.
I agree in principle, sir.
But we've lost contact with
the Japanese government.
Our hands are tied.
We don't need the Japanese
government's approval...
Let our diplomats deal
with the clean up.
However... The United
Nations Resolution--
This situation calls for
immediate action...
We're not dealing
with a human...
We'll make up
reasons later.
Say there was a bio-terror
threat in the heart of Tokyo
and we saved the day...
You've seen the video.
Deploy soldiers, and
they'll just become
more sacrificial lambs.
We're not going to use troops
to exterminate this monster.
Right now he's holed up
in a skyscraper,
and our ships already
have the coordinates.
If we act now,
we can kill him quickly
and minimize casualties.
At the same time,
we can show the world
our military dominance.
And think about it.
It's the perfect opportunity
to sell our new arms to Japan.
Well hell.
I'm on board.
So, it's decided then?
"Moral America
Rescues Corrupt Japan,"
that's one heck
of a spin job,
considering
what we're about to do.
I don't know how you
stayed on your feet
with those wounds, pal...
But with the way
your body heals,
you should be up and
runnin' before too long.
Don't even try it.
Why don't you tie
him to the bed?
I can lend you my cuffs,
but bandages oughtta work.
Ginza... I appreciate
you being here,
but don't you have
bigger fish to fry?
Speaking of... Where have you
been all this time, Captain...?
I've been trying to--...
Last night the Chief's
house burned down...
They-- they found
his body inside.
Yeah. Tough break.
Wait.
You already knew?
Of course.
I killed him.
What?!
I saw the manifest
for that secret club,
and the prick's
name was on it...
I went to grill
him about it,
and he had a whole
fucking room full of legs
from women
he'd butchered.
He killed his wife and
kid and he almost got me.
Every politician and offical
who's worth a shit
went to that
Club last night.
The doors are sealed, so they're
prob'ly still stuck inside.
But that means Japan's without a
working government right now...
And the attack on the
Prime Minister's house--
my god, is this what
Suitengu had planned?
You think Suitengu's done
all this to stage a coup?
Hello, Bob's Massage
Parlor, this is Bob...
Who did you say?
Saiga's boss?...
Huh?
Turn on what news?
--interrupt today's
regular programming
to bring you
a special news report...
Yotsuya, are you there?
Yes I am, Trisha, with
a serious development.
We've received
a press release
from the Emergency Crisis
Management Committee.
They've ordered a full,
mandatory evacuation
of Tokyo's Minato Ward,
effective immediately.
I repeat...
It's a full, mandatory
evacuation of the Minato Ward...
All residents and anyone
currently within the area
are required to vacate
without delay...
Evacuees should
leave quickly but calmly,
take only
what they can carry,
and follow all directions
given by the SDF.
Okay, I'm watching...
So what the hell
does this mean?
The Japanese government couldn't
have ordered this evacuation...
Everyone with that
authority's gone.
Someone's pulling
the strings...
But...
Who could--?
The Americans, god damn it,
I'd bet my career on it.
They've taken
advantage of the chaos,
and infiltrated
Emergency Management.
There's only one reason
they'd order an evac.
And that's a
military assault.
This country's knee
deep in it now, Saiga.
You guys'd better get your
asses outta here, quick.
The Self-Defense force
and the police
will be directing traffic
along all major exit routes.
Evacuees should cooperate
with the officials,
and help those in the area
with limited mobility...
Once again, all residents
must vacate immediately,
Saiga!
You'll get yourself
killed...! Saiga!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Anarchy...
Thought
I'd seen it all...
Attention,
all citizens.
This is the
Self-Defense force.
This area
must be vacated.
Evacuation centers
have been readied
for you outside
the Minato Ward.
You will be safe there.
Please proceed
calmly, but quickly,
in a courteous
and orderly fashion.
Evacuation
is not a choice.
You must leave now.
Back to you, Yotsuya.
Can you tell us anything about
the cause for this evacuation?
The administration
has still not released
any official statement...
But our sources tell us
that the explosions
at the Prime Minister's
home this morning
were caused by
military-grade weapons...
It is widely speculated this
evacuation has something to do
with that incident.
Am I to understand this is
possibly an act of terrorism?
Hey, let's go!
Saiga, wait!
So what I hoped
for wasn't true.
I wasn't a child born
out of love, after all.
You and I are human, my dear,
but not completely...
We are guinea pigs, ushered
along by the whims of fate...
And no matter how hard we
push against its current,
we cannot escape
our destiny...
Even if we did keep scraping
along and find a way to survive,
it would only be a life
of misery and pain...
Like Yui had.
She was only five
when it happened...
When we were hauled away.
At least I had Saiga to show
me the kind of freedom you
and your sister
never had.
Despite all the unsavory
things I've done,
whenever I looked at you,
Yui was there...
Deep, beneath it all.
Saiga... What the hell
are you doing?
Suitengu's planning
to die tonight
and he's gonna
take Kagura with him.
You won't stop him...
You'll just lose what
sight you have left.
You're prob'ly
right, Doc,
but I'll be damned if that's
gonna stop me from trying.
This-- everything
I've done--
it's been my choice.
Ever since that
first snap of the shutter
after my powers
were awoken,
I could feel I was on a
road that would end me...
If I truly hated it,
I would've stopped...
But for as long
as I can remember
photography's been like
breathing to me...
Without it I'll suffocate
in all this filth.
If my eyes are really
gonna quit on me,
I wanna be on the front
lines when it happens...
I want the last thing
I see to be through a lens.
When you do get
Kagura back,
bring her
straight to me.
I found the answer in
Nishiya's journal...
They've kept her from
having her first period
because the hormone
change in her body
could reverse the
syndrome's effects--
that's how
it was designed.
You mean, you could
save her life?
I'm holding you
to that, Doc...
I promise I'll
get her out alive.
Get yourself
out alive, too.
Where are you
slinking off to, Tiger...?
Blind as you are...
Wanna take a guess?
I'm not stupid enough to think
I can talk you out of it...
So I guess I'll suck it
up and take you there.
Ginza, you--...
I went to that club
last night...
And it hit me...
This country's elite
only care about excess.
They're fucked
beyond belief. But...
I'm the same...
Just on a smaller scale...
Playing the system
to grab whatever I can,
doing it all for the money
or a good piece of ass...
Tell you the truth
I'm sick of myself...
Disgusted by the
things I've done...
And I'm tired of
livin' on empty...
I wanna do something
that means a shit.
Too easy.
I told you he'd come.
Let's do this.
Hold up. I got a handle
on these fuckers. You go up.
Ginza...
Now which one of you
wants some self-defense?
Now it gets good.
Those trigger-happy idiots...
They have no clue what they're
getting themselves into.
That music.
Son of a bitch.
So it was you...
With the music box on
that island years ago.
And that's where you contracted
the carrier virus as well.
Tatsumi Saiga,
I knew you'd come...
Your destiny and
mine are intertwined.
Mystery solved.
I finally see what
you've been up to.
With the power you had,
you could have easily killed
Shinsen and Kamiya long ago,
and had your revenge.
But you waited,
biding your time.
And this is why.
I have six hundred trillion
yen in cash here...
Including stocks and bonds,
it's triple that amount.
Tonight it will
all turn to ash,
and the Tennozu
Group will crumble...
The Bank of Japan and every
major company in the nation
have invested far more than
is legal in the Tennozu Group,
and far more than they
can afford to lose.
When this money disappears,
the entire country
will go bankrupt.
That's your true revenge...?
A total financial collapse?
If I had merely killed
Shinsen and Kamiya
what difference
would that have made...?
No one would have
missed them...
They would have only been
replaced by new heads,
while the Hydra
continued to thrive.
You see, Saiga, on the
battlefield I realized
the true object
of my vengeance --
the one that orphaned
me and my sister.
It was society itself--
a culture of greed...
Built from the
souls of mankind.
You're talking about
fighting a system, an idea...
But it's people-- human beings
you're making pay the price!
I should've died
on that battlefield,
with the rest of my squad.
Then I wouldn't've had to
experience any of the suffering
that greeted me
when I returned to Japan.
But now this life...
The life my sister
willed me to lead,
can finally reach its end.
If you believe that,
what the hell was
my purpose for surviving?
When I was trapped
in that rubble...
Hearing that music was
the reason I held on.
If you think you were kept
alive for your sister's revenge,
then in a way
she saved me, too.
So why?
Maybe I'm here to keep you and
Kagura from being destroyed
by all this shit.
If you're here for Kagura,
you've come too late.
There was a billboard
on the waterfront
with a simple question.
One I'm still not
sure how to answer.
Every story needs a
final page, and trust me,
this one comes with a bang.