Next time try standing up
for me, you little prick!
Nice one.
Is this urgent?
Representative Ochiai.
It's me, Saiga...
I've decided...
I'm gonna offer my
testimony at Parliament...
But Kagura stays out...
Help her...
Move her out
of the country
where she can get the
treatment that she needs.
And I want you to send
Dr. yogoku with her.
You have a good heart...
And the last thing I want
is to see her suffer...
You've got a deal...
I'll make plans to get Kagura
out as soon as possible.
I'll owe you for this.
It's Tokyo.
Everybody owes.
But you can
even the trade.
With you on board,
the revolution can begin.
I want everyone
to meet tomorrow.
Everyone?
The Order of the
White Eagles...
You don't know it, but we've
all been waiting for you...
You are the last
White Eagle, Mr. Saiga.
Me?
I wish I could raise
a glass with you now,
but we'll have to wait
for tomorrow.
I've got a
lot of work to do,
if we're going
to pull this off.
I won't be
sleeping tonight.
Tell me about it.
Something wrong?
Hey, Captain!
Glad you finally made--
Have you been drinking?
Oh, jeez, Captain,
that is foul!
What is it?
How should I know...?
Smells like something crawled
in your mouth and died.
The crime.
Oh... Right... Looks like
another random attack...
It's the fifth one this
week, and no explanations.
Dragged my ass down here
'cause I thought you had
somethin' interesting for me.
Would you like
to take a look...?
It's a real mess...
Multiple stab wounds...
I don't understand
what's happening.
Random murders,
robberies...
Fighting on every block...
We're lookin' at the highest
spike in violent crime in years.
Maybe everyone else
is as bored as me?
This is serious.
I can show you the numbers.
And even weirder, these guys
aren't repeat offenders.
They're all just
regular people.
It's like the entire
city's gone mad on cue...
What if there's
something big behind this,
something the brass
can't even fathom?
Captain, wait...
Where are you going?
Back to where I was before
you called, rookie...
I'm gettin'
shit-faced...
I am done bustin' my ass for a
city that doesn't give a fuck...
'Sides, rich girls
don't hafta work.
And this bitch just
made a fortune.
On stocks?!
See ya.
You invested in the
Tennozu Group, didn't you...?
Well I hope you feel
good about yourself,
swimming in
your dirty money!
Feel good about myself...?
How the hell could I?
Saiga...
Where are you...?
Are you still
babysitting that child?
Yeah,
I feel great.
Kagura...
Saiga...
We're a pair,
aren't we...?
Well, ladies first.
There something
you wanna say?
Saiga... I want to testify--
at the Parliament hearing.
I want us both to testify.
How did you hear--...
Forget it...! You're not
going near that place!
Why can't I?
You just don't get it...
It's dangerous-- If we show up
at Parliament together,
we'll be sitting ducks
for Suitengu...
And I'm not going
to take that risk.
I don't care... It's better
than us getting separated!
I said no... If that's all you
came to say you can go now.
But Saiga... You said from
now on we'd stay together...
You promised me that.
I didn't mean it.
Kagura...
Trust me... There are things
you don't understand.
Like the sort of things
Professor Nishiya could tell me?
What's that supposed
to mean...?
Ah, hell...
What did he
say to you?
I don't want to be
away from you...
Please, Saiga...
Whatever time
I do have left...
I want to spend
it with you.
God damn it!
I should break
his fuckin' neck!
I'm glad
he told me...
I'm not afraid
of dying...
It's you I'm
worried about...
your eyes!
Kagura...
Saiga, wait!
Hey, buddy...
Don't tell me you're
drinking alone tonight.
Old habit.
I could go for
a drink myself.
Guess that's better'n
another slap in the face.
You uh...
You saw that didja?
Nothin' to be ashamed of,
I just got one of my own.
A girl hit you, too?
Hang on a minute,
aren't you--...?
Nah... What am I saying,
you couldn't be him.
All right, you want a drinking
buddy, I'm here for ya, man!
We're like members
of the same club!
If you say so.
Kampai!
Hey, I didn't
get your name.
Everyone calls me Joe...
So what's yours?
I'm uh...
I'm just another good-
for-nothin' loser like you.
It's funny, when I
first saw you outside
I thought you were
this amazing guy.
I heard of him through
this club I joined,
full of the most
awesome people...
I'm not even in the same
league as them to be honest...
I'm half expecting them
to wise up and boot me out.
I tend to have trouble
with authority myself.
Yeah, right? But these people,
you gotta respect them.
They're working really hard
to turn this country around.
Yeah, good luck.
Joe... Who are you,
really?
It's like
you said earlier...
Just a good-
for-nothin' loser...
Born without courage...
So I drink instead.
I've been there.
People think Japan's
peaceful now.
But we're still at war.
Only instead of rifles,
we kill each other
with great big wads of cash.
I've spent my whole life
ducking from danger...
If there's a way
for somebody
like me to put an
end to this war...
Then I'd happily give
my life to that cause.
You got a good face, Joe.
I mean... You're
a total dumbass...
But you're a...
good guy.
Tell that
to my girlfriend.
I talk big... But the
fact is, I'm afraid...
When it comes to taking
risks, I just run and hide.
Any tips
for a chicken-shit?
My advice...?
This country went way
beyond fixing years ago...
Fuck it.
Why should I care?
I'm using Ochiai and his friends
just like he's using me.
Fuck it, huh?
Yeah, and forget about
that martyrous bullshit...
It's a joke...
Things get bad,
run away.
Sound advice...
Except that's not
what Saiga would do.
That's the guy's name...
The one I mistook
you for, I mean...
I've never actually met him,
just saw his picture once...
But I heard about him
from someone I respect...
He said, "Saiga would run
straight into battle
to get the shot he wanted.
That's the kinda
guy he is."
Even today...
He's still fearless...
What makes a guy
like that tick?
Who knows...
Maybe he's trying to save
some damsel in distress.
Cool... That would make
him even more heroic.
Ya think so?
Well if she's hot!
Hey. Closing time, Joe.
Face worth the film...
Who knew I'd find that again.
Saiga!
I'm sorry
about yesterday.
Me too...
We have a meeting with
the White Eagles today
to prepare us for
the official hearing.
It's safer if we
take two cars.
I'll be in the first car...
But the Doc'll be here soon
to ride along with you...
Okay?
Okay!
Kagura...
I won't let you die...
I promise... We're
gonna live-- Both of us.
'Kay...
Saiga.
Forgive me, Kagura.
I swear, this is the last
time I'll ever lie to you.
Christ... You never
give up, do you...?
I haven't heard
from Saiga, I swear.
For all I know
he's dead.
Considering the shape
this city's in,
a detective like you shouldn't
be wasting your time ...
In case
ya hadn't noticed,
we're in the middle
of a god damned crime spree.
Saiga's all that's
important to me.
Saiga, it's me... There's been
a little change in the plan...
You go on ahead... I think
I'm gonna be a bit late.
Gotcha.
Something come up?
Bit of trouble on my tail.
Eh, nothing
I can't handle.
See ya there.
Wait... Would there
happen to be a young guy
in this
White Eagles club...?
Well meaning,
he goes by Joe...?
Yeah! That'd
be Joji Kitazawa.
Good man.
He's a Cub, but the kid's
got some definite promise
as a journalist...
You could say I've taken
him under my wing.
So you're the one...
The man Joe said
he respected...
Who'da thought?
What the hell's that
supposed to mean?
I'm the most
respectable prick alive.
Now that
you mention it,
the kid reminds me of you
when you started.
Full of ideals, looking
to take some risks.
Startin' to feel like
I might pull this off.
Hey, if there's still people
like him left in this country,
people who believe in
something bigger
than what they can stuff
in their pockets,
maybe I could turn
things around.
Maybe I could
out-play Kamiya;
hell, take down
Suitengu, too.
Mister Saiga...
I'm so glad you've come!
Let me introduce you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I present the last White Eagle!
Doctor...? Just how far
away is Saiga's meeting?
Kagura...
I'm sorry...
But I'm actually taking
you to the airport.
But, Doctor!
Saiga's waiting for me!
I'm just doing what
he asked, Kagura...
He wants to keep you safe.
No! You have to let me
out of this car!
I'm sorry,
I can't do that.
Exscuse me...
Madam...
Is Joji Kitazawa
gonna be here today?
Oh... So you've
already heard about him?
Look, I know it's a bad topic
for your first meeting...
But Ochiai gave
us some news...
He has reason to believe
there's someone in the group
feeding information
to Kamiya's people.
Are you saying you
think Joe's a spy?
Well no...
I mean we haven't been able
to prove anything yet...
But there's something
off about him,
he isn't like
the rest of us.
Fair enough...
But he doesn't come off
as a traitor.
Saiga!
Joe!
So, you realized
it was me...
When did you
figure it out?
When I hit my head
on the barstool.
I'm hoping you'll take a
photograph of me someday...
"Joe the Drunk."
Nah, I'd call it
"Slap-Happy Joe."
Sorry I made
such an ass of myself...
Not the first impression
I'd have hoped for ...
But still...
I'm lucky I guess...
I got to meet you without
all the pretense...
And after our discussion
I made up my mind.
I'm confident I can
give this to you.
You'll know what
to do with it.
My God!
Every single member
of Suitengu's club.
One of the members
they murdered
for outstanding debts left that
behind, as a sort of revenge.
Last night...
This was your big risk.
There's something else...
Ochiai... Your name's
on that list.
As a VIP.
He's a traitor?
He can't be...
But he's our leader...
You bastard...
Damn it...!
You are risking
your life!
All right, Ochiai...
Time for some answers.
My god... You were the one
betraying us this whole time?
The head of our own group,
reporting to Kamiya's faction?!
At last.
All the key
players are here.
My final obstacles.
You can't imagine how long I've
waited for this day to come...
I'm so pleased.
This is it,
White Eagles...
This is your end...
Allow me to play you some
music befitting the occasion.
Can you hear it?
Can you hear the overture?
Don't waste our time!
This is no joke!
We want answers, Ochiai!
Ah, you're not
really listening!
You mustn't use
just your ears,
you must listen
with your souls!
Joe, run!
Poor fools. You don't
appreciate true art.
You don't know what
real pleasure is.
You really thought
I was your comrade,
that I shared your
naïve goals for change?
Let me show you...
This is the
true revolution!!
Thought I'd lost ya.
Shut up and
take me to him.
Joe...
Joe...!
Hey!
Damn you.
Why the hell'd
you do it?
What'd I tell you...?
If things get bad, run,
don't be a fucking martyr!
Mister Saiga. What a
surprise to find you alive.
Clearly, you're
not one of them.
The old guard,
the human weak.
No, you're like me.
You're a
fucking monster.
And so are you.
Now, if you'll humor me,
I'd like to play a more
appropriate song...
A ballad of parting...
Listen to it well,
my friend,
while you picture
the girl you love.
Kagura...?
You son of a bitch!
What have you
done with her?
Another two-faced
politician.
Another betrayal.
Another obstacle between
the girl and her freedom...
And a surging
wave that shakes
to the very core
of those who believe.