Oh, good God!
What the fuck
is goin' on?!
Suitengu!
Suitengu?
He's wasting his time...
and ammo, this whole
building is bulletproof.
The bird is down.
I repeat,
the bird is down.
Hold off on
the police...
Let us clean up
here first.
How the hell is that son
of a bitch still alive?!
It appears as though
you're all there.
Suitengu!
Deputy...
Defense Minister...
and all you other
Cabinet members...
I do hope you're
enjoying the show.
Damn you...!
Don't you realize
what you're doing here...?
This is an act
of treason!
Don't worry yourself
over my fate.
Just enjoy to the fullest your
final moments at the Club.
Final moments?
What the hell
does that mean?
Suitengu...!
Answer me!
No good!
The door's locked!
And with that the Club is
completely locked down.
This blows.
Can't believe the son of
a bitch is really gone.
Yes...
But sir...
What's this for?
This is your
last assignment--
The time has come
for me to let you go.
There are those
in the government
who intend
to eliminate me...
From this point on, the fight
is between them and me alone.
I can't ask you
to join me.
There will soon be
nowhere in this country...
or in the world
for that matter,
where I will belong.
Only Kagura and I
shall remain here,
to face our fates.
You've all worked hard for me
and've been incredibly loyal...
You have my
sincerest gratitude.
Well boys,
this is where I get off...
Though it has
been quite a ride.
I'm staying put.
You can take my
share if you want.
You fuckin' serious?
Tsujido...
You stick around here,
and they'll fuckin'
slaughter your ass!
What can I say, ever since we
met, I've admired his scent...
And regardless, I've been
living on borrowed time
since that day.
You know, fuck it...
Take mine, too.
Makabe?!
Long time ago I promised
myself I wouldn't go out
'til I was on top...
And somehow, I doubt I'm
ever gonna get any higher
than where I'm at now.
Ah come on...! So this is how
you assholes honor Suitengu?
By ignoring his
last fuckin' wishes?
He told us
to run, right?
Ain't it up to the
three of us to live?
So we can go and tell the world
all the great shit he done?
Niihari...
I think that's a task
you were born to perform.
We'll meet again,
if the fates allow.
Cocksuckers...
Try not to
get dead.
Let's go, Makabe...
This time we save him.
Kagura...!
Kagura!
Away from the door!
Doc,
is that you?
Saiga...! Thank God,
you're still alive.
Kagura...!
Where is she...?
Isn't she with you?!
They took her somewhere...
So tell me... where
the hell are we, anyway?
The Prime
Minister's mansion.
The what?
Stop it!
You have no reason to be
afraid in here, Goddess.
This office is
completely secure...
My men will
take care of...
that horrible Suitengu.
As long as I'm here
with you, my child...
you've nothing to fear,
I won't let anyone hurt you.
Now... why don't we
make our way to the Club
so we can continue
our meal in peace...?
I've asked them to prepare
all the finest delicacies.
But first, just
one more lovely taste
of your delicious
fingers, hmm?
No...!
Stay away from me!
Kagura!
Saiga!
Ah yes,
I recognize you...
You're that photographer...
You called me "a boring subject"
if I recall correctly.
Wow, you remember me,
I'm all tingly inside.
I've heard about
your unique talent...
But do you honestly dare snap
that shutter of yours at me...
the esteemed Prime
Minister of Japan?
Now then....
How shall I prepare you,
my little appetizer?
Suitengu!
Why isn't anyone who's
supposed to be dead dead?!
So Suitengu...
You responsible for that
pile of bodies out there...?
Just how many lives
are you gonna take?
All the people I've killed
in this country were guilty...
Guilty of being blinded
by their unending avarice.
The only innocent
blood on my hands...
is from a distant
battlefield long ago.
In that previous
existence...
I ended
countless lives...
Innocent, harmless,
unselfish...
People who had never
done any wrong by me...
Just so I could cling
to my own miserable life.
Just so I could
survive... Kamiya...
and claim
my vengeance on you.
Vengeance, what are
you talking about?
Do you not recognize...
this visage...?
Fifteen years ago when you
were Secretary of Finance...
you sold me abroad--
Have you forgotten
Takeshi Ueno?
Ueno...?
My God, you're that young
whelp from all those years ago?
Good morning,
young man.
And to you as well,
young lady.
What a shame!
Truly an unfortunate
turn of events.
Who are you?
I don't know
if you're aware,
but your father was
in quite a bit of debt.
He was?
Oh, yes. And rather
late on his payments.
So, you lived
to tell...
In a manner of speaking--
I was mortally wounded
during battle...
But, Kagura...
thanks to the research
performed by your father...
I was reborn...
Your true father was
Doctor Kazuki Odawara,
a brilliant scientist...
Some twenty years ago...
he was enlisted by the
Japanese government...
which had been
invited by an ally...
To participate
in a joint project
developing biological weapons
for use in polar warfare.
Biological weapons...
But then...
an international treaty banned
all research of that nature...
Fearing reprisals, the nations
involved sought to destroy
all evidence of the project.
But Odawara's research
was secretly passed on
in two people.
One of them was me,
the carrier...
The other was you,
Kagura...
There is a substance coursing
through your bodily fluids
that has the power to
activate the viral syndrome,
and create Euphorics.
I spread the virus
as I saw fit,
and then used your
talents at my club
to ascend the ranks of
power in this country.
All for this day.
Too bad then, that as of
today you're through...
The Club is set
to become state-run...
and the Tennozu Group
will be sold to foreigners...
The Cabinet already
made it so...
And our will is the
will of the people.
Don't you just
love democracy?
And this is the true face of our
country's Prime Minister...
How appropriate.
W-- Wait...
Suitengu...!
Your sister, I know
where your little sister is ...
If you kill me now...
there's no way
you'll ever find her!
Yui is still alive?
That's right...
And I know where...!
I'm the only one
who still knows!
A nice attempt...
But my sister has been
with me for some time now.
Get out of the way!
Move it!
Clear the street!
Ano kamu?
(shouts in Tagalog)
Paki ibigay
ang pera sa akin.
Give me...
money...
Okane...
kudasai...
Money... money...
money...
Give me money--
cash only.
Yui...
Are those your
sister's remains...?
Gimme, Suitengu, gimme!
Let me be the one to devour it--
I want her inside me!
Yui... now you and
I will be together...
until I can join you.
Tell you what,
Suitengu...
we got off on the
wrong foot, okay...?
How 'bout I put the Club
back in your hands...?
Or I know!
How would you like a
cushy Cabinet post?
Name it,
it's yours!
I think not.
No wait...!
Let's talk!
Kagura...
Come with me.
Fuck!
Saiga!
Please, Suitengu,
leave him alone!
Kagura...
if you do as I say,
I will spare
this man's life.
Ah, c'mon... what use do
you have for Kagura now,
why not just let
the poor girl go?
She and I are needed
to end this tragedy...
But after that we
have no place...
We're cursed aberrations,
living plagues upon
the earth...
Had I died on
that battlefield...
and had you
not been born...
countless deaths would
have been prevented.
If I had
never been born?
That's right.
You should never have
been allowed to exist.
Kagura...! Don't listen
to a goddamn word he says!
Oh, god!
Suitengu... Promise me
you'll let him live.
Kagura!
Let's go...
Right now.
Thank you, Saiga...
Don't forget me.
Kagura...
Kagura!
The cruel morning dawns,
the end looming on the horizon,
ready to rise like
a waiting sun.
What happens to a nation
when its leaders are gone?
Someone always steps
in to fill the void.