Death to the
intruder, at once!
He stole my ritual...
He stole my kiss!
He has to suffer!
It cannot be forgiven!
It should be my
right to kill him!
Kill him!
Yeah!
God damn it...!
This man is a Euphoric!
Bastard!
What the hell...?
My camera did that?
Unbelievable.
He's a natural carrier?
Detain that man!
And get Kagura to safety!
Yes sir.
Hey, girl.
Can you hear me?
Hey!
I've got their scent--
they're in Area B.
Ugh, dizzy. I've
lost too much blood.
Stop! Do you want
to kill her too??
I'm willing to let
you live, stranger...
Just give Kagura
back to us.
Kagura...?
I thought she was
your Divine Goddess.
In any case, she's obviously
an important part
of this fucked-up
operation...
So I'll take that to mean
I'm traveling safer
as long as she's with me.
Have you found them?
I'm sorry, sir,
but he's using her
as a hostage and he got away.
I think he's headed towards
the water purification plant.
Damn it-- what's going
on in this place...?
... It's gotta
be this camera...
There's no
mistaking that...
What the hell?
I should be dead.
But I'm healing.
Maybe it's not the camera.
Maybe it's me.
This way!
Hurry!
What am I
doing here...?
And who are you...?
Why am I--
What does this mean??
You tell me--
Stay away...!
What's happened to me?
That's my question...
My camera...
My body-- what the
fuck's going on here?
What are you
talking about?
Perhaps I should
answer that.
Kagura has used
her talents on you...
She has awoken
your potential,
and turned your deepest
desire into reality.
What do you mean,
"deepest desire?"
Mister Suitengu?
Yes, Kagura, it's me.
There's no need to worry.
I've come
to take you home.
But...
I don't understand...
How did I get here?
Why am I wearing this...
this costume?
I've seen it before...
It's the same costume
I've worn every night,
in those terrible dreams...!
Could it be...
Could it be real?
Did I really do those
disgusting things?
Of course not...
It's all in your head...
You're dreaming right now...
In the morning you'll awake
and tell me all about it.
Nice story...
But enough
of this bullshit--
What did you mean by her
fulfilling my desire?
How?
Kagura...
Come along now.
The things I remember...
What happened in here...
If everything those men
did to me in my dreams...
Is true...
I...
I can't...
Oh god...
No, wait!
Tsujido...
Have speedboats ready
at Shibaura Dock!
Quite a performance,
you have to admit...
He dropped this
in the hall.
"Explo-tography"...
No wait...
"Snap-Shooting"
--that has a better ring.
A unique ability.
I may call on your help,
should the situation
demand it...
Master Shirogane...
Of course...
Anything to ensure
the Club's survival.
You all right?
Don't touch me...!
I didn't ask you
to save me...!
You should have
just let me drown.
I wanted to...
You're too young
for thoughts like that.
Please,
let go of me...!
How can I live if those
nightmares really happened...?
I have to die!
Don't say that!
You see that girl?
Her whole village
was wiped out
in a war she couldn't
hope to understand.
Still... She found
a reason to keep living.
But how...?
How can she smile,
after all that pain?
Because she's free.
Free?
Free to live, and dream,
without worrying about
what she doesn't have.
That's just an illusion.
Don't ever talk so lightly
about dying again.
Take me away.
To somewhere far off, where
nobody can ever find me...!
I'm a prisoner here--
I can't take it any more...!
Please save me!
I'll die
if I have to stay!
There!
Straight ahead!
Damn it...
Take a deep breath.
Don't let go of me!
No! Let me go!
Don't take me back there!
Yes sir, we have Kagura,
safe and sound...
He's still underwater...
Right...
We'll bring her back now.
Okay, second team,
you keep searching...
'til sun-up
if you have to...
I want that man dead!
NO!!
Damn it...
She has awoken
your potential,
and turned your deepest
desire into reality.
So that's it...?
That's my deepest
god-damned desire--
to kill with
my own thirty-five?
That's so fucked up!
You comin' after me--
now that's a pleasant
role reversal,.
Your clothes're all ripped.
You been foolin' around with
dangerous elements again, Tiger?
Guess so.
We have a subterranean fire
in the Roppongi District.
All units--
Here...
That is what you
came for, isn't it?
A girl who can't
fuck without her gun,
and a guy
who can't get it up
without starin'
through a camera...
Don't we just make
the perfect couple..
Now come on, babe...
Give it to me
hard and slow,
I want to feel you
all the way through.
I don't think I can.
What...?!
You better not've
met another woman...
And if I have?
I'll kill you.
Saiga!
Jesus Christ...
I am not here to play
your goddamn nurse!
Thank you for receiving
us, Mrs. Morishita.
It's awfully early.
What do you want?
I'm afraid we're the bearers
of the most unfortunate
sort of news, madam...
Late last night your
husband passed away.
What did you say?
There was an accident
at our Club.
What club?
I hope we can settle
this amicably.
We've come to compensate
you for your loss.
You bastards...
You honestly think you can
pay for my husband's life
with your pocketbooks?
Now.
What's the
meaning of this?
Who are these men??
Three billion yen,
altogether.
Three billion?
The market value of his life,
by our calculation...
He was an older man,
well past his prime...
Planning for your son
run in his place
in the next
parliamentary elections.
Actually, his tragic death
should help your son
capture the sympathies
of the people...
I'd say it's more than
enough, Mrs. Morishita.
Or would you rather we leak
that photo to the press,
and destroy his
reputation as well?
His loser son is
a member too, correct?
Yes.
Get him into debt, then
seize the entire estate.
This is bad news.
I understand.
And I'm terribly sorry.
But the truth
of what happened
will never be reported
by the media.
We're in better
shape than you think.
Yes, but Morishita
was a Cabinet Minister.
I'm aware of that...
But the man was only
appointed as a figurehead...
The agendas that really matter
won't be affected at all.
Even so...
that means we now have
two legislative vacancies...
Our party could easily
lose those seats
in the special
elections.
The Tennozu Group will
finance all your campaigns,
one hundred percent.
Cut to the chase--
what about the Club?
We'll have to close
it for a while.
Close...?
That won't work.
Don't worry. I've already
instructed Suitengu to...
take care of you
in the interim.
Let's hope so...
I've explained things
to all our regular members--
they're not happy,
but they can be handled.
I sincerely apologize again
for this disgrace, Miss Tennozu.
Perhaps you
can enlighten me.
What was my daughter
doing there?
She stopped by
for a short performance,
at her piano
instructor's request.
I assure you, she has
no knowledge of the Club.
That's all...? It's not
because you love her
and have laid
your hands on her?
Never, my lady.
Just remember what
will happen if you do...
Finally awake?
Mister Suitengu...
Where am I?
Don't worry,
you're at home...
In one of the
mansion's back rooms.
But why?
For your safety...
You were tossing and turning in
your bed for hours last night...
You began sleepwalking, and we
were afraid you'd get hurt...
Your mother wants you
to recuperate here.
Sleepwalking...?
Mister Suitengu,
you're not saying everything
that happened last night was
just another nightmare, are you?
Well I'm afraid I don't know
what you're referring to Kagura,
but you were
home all night.
No, it can't be!
What about that man?
What happened to him?
What about what man?
That photographer
who saved my life!
You mean someone
from your dreams...?
Well... You'd best call on
Lord Morpheus for that one...
As for things in this
world, call on your maid.
Mister Suitengu,
wait! Please!
Let me out of here!
I'm awake now!
You don't have
to keep me like this!
Tell me you've found him.
No...
Not yet, sir.
And why not?
My best men are on it.
We'll get him.
Please let me out...!
You have to...!
Don't make me
stay in this cage!
Someone, help!
Don't make me
stay here!
Help me...
Be free...
What time's the
press conference?
2 p.m., sir.
God damn it! They don't want it
to the make the evening paper!
Ah hell, we'll
run an extra!
Yes, sir.
Son of a--
Saiga?
What're you doing
in my office?
I needed some information
on the Tennozu Group.
And how did
you sign on?
Your password was taped to
the back of your desk drawer.
Have you heard
the big news?
About what?...
where inside legislators
are scrambling to react
to the sudden deaths
of two of their own,
news that has
sent shockwaves
throughout a government
already in disarray.
Most notably,
the death of Education and
Science Minister Morishita--
And that's just
the start of it--
a number of high-profile
entertainers
and corporate executives
passed away last night,
with causes of death ranging
from household accidents
to cirrhosis
of the liver.
And none of the families
are letting the press get
within a hundred meters.
It doesn't make sense.
I don't suppose you know
anything about it...?
Have any luck with the
Roppongi Club last night?
I'd say they've
been put on hiatus.
Hiatus?!
What is it?
The picture you mentioned
is in this magazine.
I hope it helps.
Thank you.
Call if you need
anything else.
This is it...
"Photo by
Tatsumi Saiga,
Renowned War
Photojournalist."
That's him!
You are real...
You're not some figment of
my imagination, like he said.
To somewhere far off, where
nobody can ever find me...!
I'm a prisoner here--
I can't take it any more...!
Please save me!
I'll die if I have to stay!
So that's where
they keep you...
How fitting...
A lighthouse, in an
otherwise hopeless sea.
An innocent girl
asked for help,
and I'd be a
monster not to try.
I'm not the only one in this
city who's been changed
by the goddess' kiss.
What happens when two
warped desires collide?