That kind of power...
I can't believe you
could get it from her.
You planning to take her
back home anytime soon?
No, that's the last
thing she needs...
Pretty abusive
environment there.
In my view...
The best thing I can do
for that girl and myself...
is keep looking...
find out what's going on
with our bodies,
and bet back
to normal again.
You know, Saiga...
I can take care of
that part for you.
The finding out anyway.
I took the liberty of sending
your blood to the university lab
I was telling you about
where I used to do research...
When it comes to DNA
they're the best,
and if they can't
figure it out no one can...
Listen...
It's just a theory, but I'm
thinking the tumor in her brain
may be less a symptom of her
curse than the cause of it.
Thanks, Doc...
but I've already endangered
you way too much as it is.
Shut the hell up--
being around you two
has been a real blessing ...
I haven't felt this
young in years.
All I'm in danger of
is being happy again.
Call me in a week...
I should have results then.
Okay.
Uh, Captain?
Sorry, but why am I here?
'Cause I called
for you, rookie.
Yes but... why...
did you call for me, ?
'Cause this is
your office now,
and I thought the least
you could do is show up.
What?! My office...? I work the
crime lab-- remember?
As you can see,
all of my men are playing
hooky in the hospital.
So I asked the brass
for reinforcements.
You're them.
No...! That's crazy--
I can't work out
in the field...!
I mean, outside of training I've
never even handled a pistol!
Funny...
Figured a guy like you's
got all kinds of practice
holding his own pistol.
Okay, fine...!
Tell you the truth
I've always dreamed
of making detective one day...
Just wait'll the boys
in ballistics hear!!
Jesus, try not to crap
yourself with excitement...
I don't have time
for dry-cleaning.
So... what are we
workin' on now, Captain?
One hell of a puzzle.
A pile of politicians
and celebs turn up dead
all across town...
A massive fire...
And the sudden disappearance
of Tatsumi Saiga.
Wait, Mr. Saiga disappeared?
While he was sniffing around a
certain top-secret social club.
So what's the connection?
All that shit just
happened to go down
on one fuckin' night...?!
Doesn't that seem odd to you?
Every one of these jerks
dies of unrelated causes
in unrelated locations??
Bullshit!
This isn't
some coincidence...
They were all part of the
same incident, same place.
Someplace where famous people
get to hobnob with each other...
I see...! It's that club
you were talkin' about...!
And Mister Saiga saw something
there he wasn't supposed to!
That'd certainly connect all
these "unrelated" cases...
But we don't have
any hard evidence...
Guess we'll have
to go make some.
I'm here to see
number eleven.
Hello beautiful,
welcome to the stir...
How about you
crawl on in here
and we make this visit
a conjugal one?
Some other time...
Right now I'm
busting you out.
Uh, Captain, I'm not sure
this is such a good idea.
Where are you
taking me hot stuff...?
District attorney...?
Grisly crime scene?
Mister Suitengu's office.
You can't do that!
I'm serious...!
You have no idea
what he'll do to me...
Yeah but what kind
of guest would I be
if I showed up
empty-handed?
That hurts...!
Let go of me!
Let them through.
Afternoon...
Got a few cases I'm workin'
on, and-- funny story...
they all led me to you.
I had a feeling that
eventually a police presence
would turn up around here.
Should I take that as a
confession the secret club's
behind all the stiffs
I keep finding?
If it's secret
how would I know?
Spare me your
bullshit asshole...!
I know you've been
hunting down Tatsumi Saiga...
And now you're gonna tell
me where the fuck he is...
Of course I'm willing to
give you something in return.
This is the
wannabe crime lord
who tried moving
in on your turf...
You'd prob'ly like to
take care of him on your own.
I can arrange that.
You crazy bitch!
Somebody should lock you up!
Interesting.
I'm sure your photographer
friend would be disappointed
that you think so very
little of him, Detective.
Because "very little"
is about all this
two-bit hustler is worth.
Seems you don't know Mr. aiga
as well as the rumors claim.
Oh that's perfect...
What the fuck?!
Now even you're tellin'
me I don't know the guy...
If you need dating advice,
we can do it another time...
We're done here.
God damn it, you stupid
jackass son of a bitch!
'Course a miserable piece
of trash like you
isn't worth the grease
in Saiga's hair!
Captain, get a
hold of yourself!
Back off!
There's not a soul
in this world
who cares for that
bastard more than me...!
Saiga is the air I breathe!
He's my life!
Jesus Christ, I don't
even know this Saiga guy!
How's your headache
doin' now...? Feel okay?
Much better.
What's wrong?
It's nothing...
My eyes are gettin'
a little tired, that's all.
Hey listen...
There some place in particular
you're itchin' to go?
We gotta keep movin'
for a week,
so we might as well
move to somewhere.
Must be plenty of places
you've always wanted to see.
Now that you mention it...
There is... one place.
Who the's girl?
My mother when she
was a young woman.
And the guy?
I don't know...
That's what I
hope to find out.
It's a nice picture...
Who gave it to you?
It was sent to me out of the
blue about four years ago...
I've tried to ask my
mother about it, but...
whenever I bring up the
past, she gets angry...
So I just had to wait.
Bessho Onsen Spa...
That's in Nagano.
From what I know of it,
the life of Shinsen Tennozu
has always been
shrouded in mystery...
She came out of nowhere to take
the modeling world by storm.
Her distinct look caused
an uproar, but then,
as suddenly as she'd
emerged, she was gone...
leaving the runway to become the
mistress of Yuichiro Ashikaga,
a giant in
financial circles...
Upon his death...
the grieving widow
restructured the Ashikaga group
under the Tennozu name,
and thus her dynasty was born.
Could this child's disease
have been passed down
from her mother?
Something stinks...
No that's not
what I meant kid.
Yeah but I do
smell kinda bad...
I've been in the same
clothes for days.
Guess we're both
a little ripe...
How about
we make a detour?
Awesome...! I've always dreamed
of coming to a place like this!
Go ahead-- you can have
whatever you want.
Thanks!
But you have to help me pick,
'cause you have the good eye.
You're a photographer,
after all!
Yeah... the fashion
thing's not really my scene--
uh!
Look, it's
just like yours!
Well, I'm taken care of--
now we get to shop for you!
That's okay...
Come on don't be shy...
You look great!!
You sure...? Don't
think it's really me...
What is it?
You have a call coming
in from the mansion...
Madam Gotokuji is not having
one of her better days.
Patch her through.
Shinsen...!
Shinsen! I need to see
the doctor-- you have to help--
I just know something dreadful
is going to happen to me!!
Shinsen...!
Shinsen,
where are you?!
Whatever is the matter...
President?
I'm not speaking to you--
bring me Shinsen!!
Come now-- don't you
recognize me...?
I'm here.
I am Shinsen.
You're lying...!
Bring the real Shinsen
to me you beast!
Lies...!
It's all lies!
I assure you, I am Shinsen.
Assure all you want, but you
are not the Shinsen I know...
Take a look... Now this--
this is Shinsen.
What an ugly child.
Oh no... Can't you see
this girl is a rare gem...?
Polish up her rough edges
and she's sure to become
an unrivaled beauty...
I have an uncanny eye
for this sort of thing.
But Madame President...
that child has already
blossomed into a butterfly.
Shinsen...?!
Shinsen,
is that really you ?!
Look at these wrinkles...
We must hurry and get you
to the doctor at once!
You know, that doctor with
the blemish on his left hand...
I think you fancy
him, don't you?
I did...
But that was another
lifetime ago.
Ah yes... It's
coming back to me now...
The woman pictured is
Shinsen Tennozu, right??
So you remember her
coming out here?
Most definitely...
How could I forget...?
Quite a bit
happened that trip...
Now then... you
must be her daughter.
Yes.
Any clue who that guy
standing next to her
in the picture might've
been, ma'am...?
Oh... forgive me...
I'm her uncle...
I'm a big-time lawyer
back in Tokyo, um...
These rags are just my
traveling clothes...
I'm here to clear up a
question of succession.
Oh... is that so?
Yes, so any information
you may have...
Please, even if you're
uncomfortable discussing it...
if it has anything to do
with where I came from...
Bear in mind...
all of this occurred about
fifteen years ago now...
Miss Tennozu
often came to our spa,
with this gentleman
at her side.
Was he her boyfriend?
Well, I don't like to pry,
but it certainly
appeared that way.
And then...?
From what I could
gather at the time,
they had arranged
to meet here that week...
but he didn't make it...
Miss Tennozu waited
around for a few days,
but eventually, she returned
to Tokyo, all alone.
He stood her up...?
My poor mother.
So this mystery guy--
He never showed?
Actually... he did
arrive at our door...
Tragically just hours
after Miss Tennozu left.
When he discovered
she'd already gone,
he seemed so...
devastated.
He left that
photograph behind,
the one my father mailed
to you four years ago...
But I don't know why he didn't
mail this at the same time--
the man wanted Shinsen's
child to have it, too.
Do you know...
where that man is now?
I'm afraid I do.
A few days later,
his body was found
at the bottom of a ravine...
The police neglected to do
a thorough investigation,
simply writing it off
as the accidental death
of an unidentified man.
My father and I decided
it was best not
to notify Miss Tennozu...
We'd read in the paper
about her marriage
to that wealthy businessman
shortly after her
return to Tokyo...
What good could have
come from telling her?
You still have the guest
register from back then?
Ah yes...
here he is.
Kazuki Odawara.
Jeez, Saiga...! I'm not your
goddamned errand boy...!
Where are you, anyway?
You get the info
I asked for, or not?
Yeah, I got it...
Bacterial Research
Lab One Fifty-Two.
An old Army installation
for experimenting
with biological warfare.
But it's been shut
down for 15 years.
As for that Odawara
you asked about,
he was a licensed physician up
until fifteen years ago.
His specialty was
genetic cures.
Bacterial research and
genetic cures-- some combo...
What about this modeling
agency Shinsen was with?
Gotokuji Promotions...?
The president vanished
fifteen years ago
and the company
went under...
That's funny.
All this crap happened
fifteen years ago...!
Hey, this wouldn't
have anything to do
with that club you were
lookin' into, would it...?
Saiga, you there--?
One of them exited
the car at this spot...
and headed
for the station.
The doctor.
And then... Saiga and the
Goddess went this way.
You sure
about that boss?
Every passing day Miss Kagura's
scent grows more pungent...
It's obviously been several days
since the Goddess's last bath.
This feels great...
It's like
I've been reborn.
Yeah...
You know, I read
in a book one time...
When large birds
like that mate,
they choose
one partner for life.
It's a nice thought, isn't
it...? Seems pure, somehow...
The way
nature intended.
That song...
I picked it up from
a guy, long time ago.
I think I remember...
hearing that
somewhere before.
They've left Izu
and are headed west.
West huh...?
Interesting...
The man's no fool.
It appears he's
taking her to Nagano.
Nagano?
We've wasted too
much time on this...
I'm ready to see
results...
I think I'll go
out there myself.
In your condition...?
What do you think
you can accomplish?
My injuries aren't
so severe...
I need to see this through,
Miss Tennozu, as a man...
But true to my word...
once everything has been settled
and the club has reopened,
my body will be happily at
your disposal once again...
Just so we're clear, you're
going to bring Kagura home
and remain my
personal plaything?
Of course.
So be it...
But before you
go chasing her...
I'd like some reassurances
that I'm the one
you'd rather get
your hands on.
How does your left hand
always please me so?
I swear, I'm tellin'
ya the truth...!
This sparkly, naked
broad comes in,
slicing everything she
can reach into pieces...!
And then this bartender
with the camera
and this really cute girl
who was up on stage singin'
some church song...
They ran off together
hand in hand.
You sure that's what you
saw you pathetic lush?!
Yeah... That bitch was
some kinda monster...
She broke my last bottle.
Damn you, Saiga...
Running around
with some girl...
Looks delicious!
Not too shabby is it...?
To good health...
Cheers!
You know...
I'm really glad I got
to talk to that lady
and hear about my
mother's past...
To think there was a time
when she loved someone enough
to consider
eloping with him.
You see... I've always been told
I was conceived for money,
a pact my mother made
to get her fortune...
I knew she never
loved my father...
There wasn't much
to love about him.
I thought that was why my
mom always looked at me
with so much hatred
in her eyes...
But don't you think
I look an awful lot
like that man
in the picture?
I hope so.
I want to be the daughter
that she had with the
man she once loved.
I like the sound of that.
I think you're right, kid...
Your mother still thinks
about that man a lot.
Each year, her child grew
to look more and more
like the lover who
deserted her...
And she couldn't
deal with that.
'Kay, so... How much you
suckers wanna bet...
that lucky bastard's bangin'
divine pussy right now?
Shows how much you know...
That's never going
to happen with them.
Why not?
Quite simply, a Euphoric needs
something very different
to get off.
If only I could...
Temptation lurks
around every corner.
The desire to do that
which we know is wrong.
Sometimes the fruit
of vice can be tempting,
but the cost -
innocence - too high.
Large sums of money
and giant wings unfurl.