Launching missiles into Tokyo
without any provocation...
Do they think Japan'll
just take this lying down?
But the truth is,
we can't respond.
Suitengu killed
the Prime Minister,
and all our top
officials are missing...
What the hell's going to
happen to this country now?
Suitengu...!
Open this gate!
You think you can get
away with this, you fuck?!
Our top story: the recently
evacuated Minato Ward
has come under
missile attack.
We have still not received
any official statement
from the
administration.
But in light of the assault
on the Prime Minister's
home this morning...
Many speculate this operation
is a counterattack...
against some unidentified
terrorist force.
Panic has set in on the
streets of the capital,
with citizens demanding answers
from their government.
Oh, shit!
I can't believe it!
You piece of shit...!
What did you do with her?!
Kagura has chosen
to accept her fate,
and that's all
you need to know.
You see, I was never a
believer in destiny before...
Before Yui died
in my arms...
But then I met Kagura
for the first time...
I learned she possessed within
her the same power as I...
And my views changed.
It was too perfect
for coincidence.
I was being led
to my true end.
Kagura and I were fated
to drown this lost
nation in Euphoria.
Get over yourself.
You used Kagura for your
own personal vendetta!
True, my blood
debts were paid.
But what did I
do to get there?
I merely nudged
the backs of those
already headed
toward self- destruction.
Because destruction
is the only end
for those twisted
by desire and greed.
Be it a nation, or lost
individuals like you and me.
So, what? You're
saying all that's left
for us is
to curl up and die?
Exactly...
Once the plan is done,
I'll die with the rest.
You're wrong...
I know the real reason
you're eager to die...
Because you feel guilty
for killing your sister
when you couldn't handle
what she'd become.
You looked at Kagura,
and all you could
see was Yui...
Cause it made you
feel better thinking
you were working
with her to get revenge.
But it's not her.
Kagura is not your sister!
Give her the freedom
she deserves.
You'll have
to take her from me...
By force!
This whole place
is comin' apart...!
Why're you boys all
suicidal for that prick?!
His afterimage.
Every person emits light,
and some burn
brighter than others.
When you've been standing
next to someone like him,
he burns into your retina,
so even when he's gone,
he's all you see.
This is the fate of people
who stare into the sun,
like Makabe and me...
On the day we first
met Suitengu...
We got burned.
Fighting for a man
you love...
Yeah, I can relate.
Behold your demise.
Damn...
Caught me off
guard... You okay?
Thanks to you.
Makabe!
We had a helluva
run, Tsujido...
Take care of the rest...
Makabe!
Makabe...
Let's do this
the easy way.
I really don't wanna
hafta kill you...
Leave now, nice n' quiet,
and I won't follow.
Fuckin' hell,
you're one of them, too?!
Damn it...
Damn fool...
Had your chance...
Kagura...
Elevator still works.
Least somethin's
goin' right.
Ginza...!
Saiga! Glad to see
you're not dead!
Yeah, you too...
Y'seen Kagura?
Nothin' yet, just
got here myself.
Not yet...
I'm not finished.
Kagura!
Can you hear me?
Say something!
Oh God, no...!
Kagura...!
Talk to me!
Open your eyes.
Please!
S--Saiga ...
Kagura... I thought
you were dead...
Now come on...
Let's go...
Can you stand...?
I've got some good news...
Doc found the answer,
he knows how to save you now.
I don't wanna be
saved, Saiga...
Forget me.
How could you--?
This whole thing
was my fault...
I created all of those
horrible monsters...
But if I had
never been born...
a lot of people
would still be alive.
Don't talk like
that, Kagura...
None of that was your
fault, you hear me...?!
From now on, all you have
to do is live your own life!
I've made up my mind...
What Suitengu said
about me was right,
it's my destiny to die
in this building with him...
Don't worry about me...
It's more important
that you live.
That's insane...!
You haven't lived half
as long as me...!
Forget about destiny...
Grow, see the world...!
Then you can act like you
know what's best for you!
I wanna thank you, Saiga...
I'm so glad I got
to meet you...
It may not have
been very long...
But I'd never felt
happiness like that before.
You think dying will
solve everything...?
Well, what about
my feelings...?
The feelings
I have for you?
I told you I'd make
you free, Kagura...
How will I keep
my promise?
But Saiga...
I love you.
Don't you know that?
Please go
on living.
For me.
Saiga!
Ginza... Take Kagura
and get outta here.
Make sure she's safe...
Let Doc help her,
then leave Japan...
Go somewhere no
one'll ever find her.
It's time for me
to end things with him.
Saiga...
I know I've got no right
to ask you to do this ...
But you're the only one
I have left I can turn to.
You are such
a fucking loser.
I won't let
her be rescued.
Then we got a little
problem to work out...
here and now.
Let's go, kid!
No, I won't leave him
again...! I'm staying!
If I can't be with him
I don't wanna live at all!
You have no idea how much
I'd enjoy helping you
with that deathwish,
little girl...
All of that shit Saiga
said to you just now...
You think it was
easy for me to hear
that when he should have
said it to me instead...?!
I wanna kill you...!
I wanna paint that wall
with your god damn brains!
I'm sorry.
But'cha know...?
I still have some pride,
and I'm trying to turn
things around here.
Saiga asked me to
take care of you...
If I let you die, I really
will be a lost fucking cause!
I won't let you die.
I won't.
I've got too much
self respect for that.
Is this it?
My limit?
This next shot
could be my last.
Shit!
That you,
Suitengu...?
Just like the
beginning, huh...?
You're even playing
the same old song.
Figures we'd have
such an ironic end.
Full circle,
and all that crap.
Now go on,
kill me.
I can't see anymore.
Why did I leave him?
I'm such a
fuckin' idiot.
Saiga!!
Suitengu's blown
himself up, Mr. President.
You can stop
the operation.
So it's done...
Now we'll have our
businesses buy out
all the Tennozu Group companies
and then call it a day.
Yes, sir. We've already made all
the necessary arrangements.
Sir, wait a minute!
We've got a problem.
According to the reports
I've just received,
approximately
eight trillion dollars
invested by the Tennozu
Group has gone missing!
Missing?!
There's more-- apparently
the Bank of Japan
has another ten trillion
invested in the Tennozu Group
that was converted to cash!
Oh, God-- you're not saying
Suitengu would've blown up
all that money, are you?!
If he has done that...
Japan will go bankrupt!
But sir, Japan is already
over twenty trillion dollars
in the red!
Holy hell... If Japan
does go belly up...
Forty trillion dollars'll
just disappear
in the international
markets!
We gotta do something 'fore
all them markets open today...!
Or else there is gonna
be a financial panic!
Too late, Mr. President,
the New York Exchange
is opening right now!
Oh, my dear God!
Saiga...
What...?
That's all money...
Hello...?
This is Bob speaking...
Saiga, honey...!
Is that actually you...?!
Sweet Jesus we thought
you were dead--
Hey, Saiga,
it's Doc here...
Where are you?
Don't know.
My eyes gave out on me.
Seem to be on a
rooftop somewhere.
There's a fire.
Hot as hell.
Just sit tight...
I'm not sure how yet...
But we're coming
to find you.
C'mon...! I can get
a police helicopter for us!
Out of the way!
Rescuers coming through!
I've gone over it
in my head a thousand times,
and I have no idea
why Suitengu saved my life.
But he got his revenge.
This country was
plunged into bankruptcy --
the collapse heard
'round the world.
They called it
the Roppongi Crisis,
and it turned
everything upside down.
What do you mean
this is all you got,
you limp-dicked
son-of-a-bitch?!
You're trying to make a
fool of me on my own turf?
I don't care
how much they're worth,
I only take repayment
in gold Euros!
I wouldn't wipe
my ass with those!
You got one week...
Don't disappoint me.
I won't sir...
Well when
it comes to money,
you're still as ruthless
as ever, Mr. President.
What can I say, I'm
a man with a dream...
I'm gonna need me
a crapload o' cash,
so's I can build three
towers downtown
so damn tall,
they block out the sun...
The tallest one,
smack in the middle,
I'll name the
Suitengu Building...
And then, the ones
on either side,
I'm gonna call the Tsujido
Tower and Makabe Plaza.
Now that's a dream that's
fuckin' worth somethin'.
What's wrong?
Nothin'...
Must be seeing things...
Hey, let's boogie.
What the frig is this?
It's out of focus!
Saiga could take
better pictures--
even in the shape
he's in now!
Don't you think you're
exaggerating just a bit, sir?
Hell no...! You give him
the lighting conditions
and the distance to the subject,
he'll take far better pictures
than every miserable
halfwit on my payroll...!
A real professional can feel
the shot in his bones...!
Christ, what're you, new...?
How long has it been
since you started working
for me anyway, kid?...
Um... About five years
I guess...
So...! I gotta lead
to check...! See ya!
Hey...! I'm not
done yellin' atcha!
Next stop,
Shiina station.
Thanks.
Tell Saiga I'm finally
gonna be starting up my bar
again at night,
and I'm saving
a seat for him.
Yeah, you got it.
I'm sure he'll be
glad to hear it.
Take it easy.
Shiina,
now departing!
And... One, two...
One, two...
Come on, ladies,
it's opening night!
Let's get those
legs up in the air!
Um...
excuse me...
I've been looking for Saiga,
you know where he is?
You mean Simon?
Have you tried
Bob's Parlor?
Yeah, it was the
first place I checked,
but nobody's answering.
Huh... Well isn't
that bizarre...
Oh, you know, they're
probably up on the roof!
Up on the roof?
There you are...
What on earth are you guys
doing all the way up here?
Hey there, rookie.
Dude, you can't call
me rookie anymore...
I've been at this
for five years...
Is Saiga taking pictures?
Comes up here every day...
And each time he takes exactly
one photograph of the city.
It's a crazy little irony,
don't you think...?
The man had to go
completely blind
before he finally
realized a way
to take pictures
that make him happy.
So is there a reason
for your visit?
Oh... Yeah Ginza
sent me a postcard
and I thought
I'd share...
She says she and the
Doc are in Africa now.
Still havin' trouble
with that one.
I mean, Ginza hooking
up with Dr. Ryogoku?!
How do you see
that coming?
Can it, loverboy!
Or I'll find a
place to stick this.
Oy, that woman's a
handful and a half.
But she doesn't mention
anything about Kagura here.
No, but as far as I know,
she's still with them...
And last I heard, they were
actually getting along.
'Bout time.
I've come home.