Who knew it would
come to this...
You are devastated
by her passing...
And so am I.
Come, dear...
Our fractured souls will
find strength in each other.
No!!!
Yes...
Saiga will...
Your photographer
will soon be dead,--
no one can
save you now.
The only one reflected
in your eyes...
will be me...
The man who will
be your husband.
Hey boss, I'm not trying
to be a wet blanket...
But ain't marrying girls
her age against the law--
I mean when you
file the application
they'll probably
try to arrest you.
Then we'll just change
her birth certificate.
Oh, hey Captain...
Word of advice Tiger:
forget that Club exists.
It's none of your
business, Ginza.
So what...?
You gonna kill yourself over
that little girl...?
Huh?
A man your age with
a girl like her...
There's a word
for that...
Sick.
If I'm such a damn deviant,
leave me alone--
forget about me.
Fat chance...
I'll keep you locked in a cell
forever if it keeps you alive...
and safe from
that monster...
I know all about it.
What is it you
think you know?
I know some kinda monster
covered in tattoos
came to my place
last night...
He was lookin'
for you.
Tattoos, huh?
They want you dead...!
Stay away from that Club!
And that fucking child!
Hey... You fixed
your camera...
Nice work.
You might wanna
stand back.
What?
Stand back!
Holy shit...
Careful Ginza,
monsters are everywhere.
Hold it.
What was that?
What happened to you?
Been wondering
that myself...
That's where
I'm heading now--
test results
should be in..
Results from what?
Bum a smoke?
Sure, if you
like menthol.
So that was real?
And here I was thinkin'
comic books were fiction...
Silly me.
Suicide?
Yes.
Mister Suitengu...
Correct me if I'm mistaken,
but I believe the plan was
for you to marry Shinsen
so you could take charge
of Tennozu's assets yourself.
Yes, enlighten me...
How do you intend
to share the profits
you guaranteed us
if they're not
in your control?
Rest assured...
The heart of my plan
has not changed ...
I will
soon be married,
with full control
of the Tennozu Group,
and all promises
will be kept.
You plan
to marry a corpse?
Allow me to
introduce to you...
My new fiancée.
The Goddess??
This is Kagura Tennozu.
Is this some kind
of a joke, Suitengu?
You just want to keep
the Goddess as your own.
That's bullshit!
I won't allow it!
Shinsen has willed
everything to her...
It was done to prevent me
taking control of the Group
if she died.
This marriage will
solve that problem.
But I assure you it is
merely a business formality.
Kagura will remain
your Goddess...
In every way.
Miss...? Are you
having car trouble?
Let's just say
I played a bluffing game
with my fuel
gauge and lost.
I'd be happy to run you
to the nearest gas station,
if you like.
It's you...
I knew it...
You're Ran Yurigaoka,
the aesthetician.
Why yes...
In the flesh.
Care for a free
evaluation?...
Wonderful...
Now lean your seat back
and try to relax for me.
Oh... Okay...
Your skin is lovely...
But with my therapeutic touch
I can make it even better...
Free its potential...
Just close your eyes,
and let go.
Oh my god...
That feels incredible...
Describe it for me.
I don't know...
It feels...
like my skin is melting...
Oh... How are
you doing that?
It feels like needles...
Give in to the pleasure...
Let the stimulation improve
the flow of blood to your skin.
Oh yes you're right...
I feel it...
It's like I read--
you're so gentle my
whole body's tingling...
Can I open
my eyes now?
By all means.
I was mistaken...
Doesn't match
your skin at all.
An amusing detour...
Hey, Saiga.
And who's this?
Captain Hibari Ginza...
New Metropolitan
Police...
I'm Saiga's
girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
You got your hands
full, don'tcha?
So what's
the news, Doc?
You got something for me?
Sure do...
Come on, the
Professor's waiting.
Here we are...
Come in.
Doctor Nishiya...
I brought the guy whose
cells you've been testing.
It's a real pleasure!
I've been waiting
all day for this...
The hell's
wrong with you?!
Okay...
Self-defense time.
I'm so sorry,
I just wanted to test him,
I swear!
Test?
Please, just let
me examine the wound...
Forgive me...
I just had
to see for myself.
Astonishing!
What in the hell?
The rapid regeneration of
cells in the damaged area,
It's like nothing
I've ever seen...
It's like...
A vampire...
And you know what
a vampire is.
A vampire?
Yes.
A vampire bite dramaticly
alters human physiology,
granting new strengths
and weaknesses.
You're saying I'm gonna
start growing fangs now?
God, no... Vampires
are things of fantasy...
Still...
It's a helpful frame of
reference when trying to explain
what's happened to you,
because if you think of it
that way it isn't
too hard to grasp...
Please,
come take a look...
Modern Vampire Fiction has
become quite sophisticated.
Some authors have even
begun linking vampirism
to being infected
with a retovirus.
Quite true
in your case.
This is a map of
your DNA, Mister Saiga.
Mostly ordinary..
But take a look at this.
It's a virus.
A virus attacking
at the DNA level?
It's not unheard of.
There are a number
of natural viruses
that can latch
onto DNA...
But this virus...
It rewrites
the base sequence --
making fundamental
genetic changes.
And it is fast.
That's hard to believe.
You've seen it work...
My theory is when I cut his
hand the virus changed
the surrounding cells into
TS cells, then multiplied them,
repairing the damage--
all in response to a
subconscious impulse.
Like symbiosis...
but the virus actually
responds to his brain ...
and then makes changes
to the DNA sequence...
Imagine the implications
The Carrier would only have
to imagine what he wants,
and his whole genetic
code could be rewritten.
Anything's possible...
He could want
to become a fish
and the virus
might make it happen...
Of course it's all
theory at this point...
If I were to try and
present these findings now,
I'd be the laughing stock
of the scientific community.
You're tellin' me everything
I take a picture of explodes
because my subconscious told
the virus it's what I want?
I know it sounds strange...
But yes, that's
most likely it.--
Of course I won't know for
sure until I've had more time
to study it.
So he contracted
this virus from Kagura--
is that what you're saying?
Well... Actually,
I ran her blood sample,
but her DNA doesn't contain
any sign of the virus.
Her sample was a
diffrent mystery.
It contained a strange
substance I couldn't identify.
And here's the kicker.
When I introduced Mister
Saiga's virus
into another subjects's DNA,
nothing happened.
But when I introduced
the substance from Kagura,
the virus sprang to life,
reproducing like crazy.
I ran some tests on
this mystery catalyst.
I found it significantly lowers
serotonin levels in the brain.
Seratonin
suppresses dopamine,
inhibiting desire.
So without it--
Skip to the end,
Professor...
What's the cure...?
For me and the girl?
There's just no way of
knowing at this point...
But there's
still hope--
I need to
keep studying you,
to get to the core
of what this virus is
and how we can use it...
it's the discovery
of the century!
Sorry, pal, but I don't
have time to play lab rat...
But thanks for the chat..
Mister Saiga, have you
noticed anything wrong?
With your eye,
perhaps?
I told you...
Like a vampire, these changes
give you weaknesses, too.
The mutated cells
degenerate over time.
The more you
use the abilities,
the more quickly
the cells will die.
If you don't let me help
you, you will go blind...
You may even die.
Please stay.
I'm really sorry, Saiga...
I know it's not what
you wanted to hear.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, yeah...
Had a question for you...
You familiar with a "Bacterial
Research Lab One Fifty-Two?"...
Defunct bio-weapon facility--
it was built before
the second world war.
Huh-uh... You think
it's got something to do
with what's going on now?
Possibly...
This catalyst Kagura has...
I think it was
engineered at that place.
Really...?
Say no more...
I'll look into it.
And take care of yourself...
Don't strain that eye.
Yeah, I'll be in touch, Doc.
Your condition is the result
of a latent virus
activated by a catalyst
present in the girl's saliva.
Latent virus...?
What do you mean?
In order for the Euphoria
Factor to be triggered,
you must've already
been a carrier...
I don't know
how you came by it,
but the virus was there in your
cells the night you were kissed.
I caught it somewhere,
before I met her...
Which battlefield?
Where?
Saiga...
Now back to the
day's lead story...
Corporate icon
Shinsen Tennozu...
President of the Tennozu Group
was found dead in her home
this morning...
In keeping with Ms. Tennozu's
final wishes...
described in an
emotional suicide note
found at the scene...
A wedding will
be held tomorrow
between her daughter
and Choji Suitengu,
one of her company's
top directors.
Bullshit...!
That can't be right...
Don't you get it...?
She must have found out
Suitengu was cheating on her...
Losing your man to
your own daughter.
I'd probably
kill myself, too.
You're wrong.
Don't act like Kagura's
some symbol of purity...
Like anything innocent
could live in a place
as screwed up as this...
And you know
she put out.
That's not true.
Yeah keep denying
it all you want...
I don't give a shit what
you did with that child...
Because I'm here to make
sure you never see her again.
Come back!
I'll shoot!
Damn it Saiga,
this is real easy...
Lose the camera,
forget about the girl...
Just walk away
and you live!
You keep
your eyesight...!
We could be together again,
like before...
I swear,
I'll try harder...!
Please, Saiga...
We could be happy!
I made an oath to
set that girl free.
And I'm sticking to it.
Made an oath...?
What the fuck...?
What are you,
a five year-old
on a playground?
God damn it, why won't
you just talk to me!
I'm sorry...
Not what
I'm looking for!
Move!
Saiga!
At long last we meet.
Saiga...!
Get in!
Damn... He just
doesn't give up.
Oh fuck me...
Prick...
No, don't!
No choice.
You will both suffer for
what you've done to my skin.
Stop it!
Are you fucking insane?
You'll just get worse.
You'll get swept back in,
and go back to that girl!
Look, I'll do
what I have to do.
What does that cunt
have that I don't?
Well for one thing...
the Divine Goddess has
infinitely healthier skin
than a washed-up whore
like you, Captain.
Go to hell.
But you needn't worry
your poor, jealous heart.
Because Saiga is never going
to see the Goddess again.
He is going
to die right here!
Please, Captain...
Don't harm my skin again...
It's of a vastly higher
quality than yours.
You son of a--
Where is he?
Saiga...
I fucked up...
Don't move...
Ooh. It looks good
on you, Captain.
It's got me...
Saiga...!
Use your camera!
It's the only way-- you
have to take us both out!
Aarrgh!
Ginza!
Just...
do it...
I can't!
Hurry!
I can't.
At long last,
you are home...
Goddess...
Where you can shine
in all your glory.
It's the marriage
of the century,
and all the pretty faces
are putting on nice heels
and fancy ties...
But while Tokyo's
politicians plan a move
on their little club,
I'm gonna show up
for a coup of my own.