Your sister's one hell of
guy, Bob. I owe you both.
Forget it...
You're family now too.
Oh, I brought
what you asked for.
Those bastard goons turned
your apartment upside down,
but most of your camera
stuff was still there.
Killers tend not to have
much use for camera gear.
So that's the girl?
Heir to the Tennozu Group?
That's her. Saiga,
I'm worried for you...
Those guys have their
hands in everything--
politics, the police,
organized crime...
Why don't you
just send her away
and go back to taking
pictures, like you used to?
It's too late for that.
I'm in too deep.
Such beautiful teeth...
Like rows of pearls, nestled
in a warm and fertile oyster.
All they need is some tender
love, and a healthy polish.
Oh yes,
that's better...
Okay, Doc.
Fun's over...
It's time we discuss
how you'll pay us back--
for her and the rest.
See you next time.
What the fuck
was that, Chief?!
Why the fuck'd they
all get released?
We had them by
the balls you idiot...!
Illegal Possession of
Firearms-- and they walk??
They didn't walk they were
just processed quickly...!
The judge paroled them
with suspended sentences,
since it was their first
offense, so we had no choice!
You're telling
me they were tried
and sentenced
in three days??
Well, yes! I know it's
unusual, but it happened!
And I was ordered not to
get involved in the case!
And you just swallowed the
command with a big happy gulp...
Do you have any desire to
protect this city at all?
I have a mortgage--
that's what I have!
car payments, my daughter's
tuition, just leave me alone!
You're really making this a
lot harder than it has to be.
Now either you
spill your guts,
or I start spilling
them for you.
My guys ain't exactly
the top of the food chain--
they just told us to bring the
photographer, Saiga, to 'em...
I don't know nuthin'
else, damn it-- I swear!
What about Saiga--
where is he now?
I don't know-- last I heard
he ain't been caught.
You just qualified
for self-defense.
What in the world
is going on?
His apartment
getting ransacked.
The underground fire.
And the midnight
shooting in Odaiba.
Someone powerful
has stepped in,
and made it seem
like none of it happened.
But Saiga knew...
And now he's been
erased, too...
No matter who I ask,
or where I look,
I can't find him.
What the hell
is going on??
Saiga...
Where have you gone??
Have at it...
Detective,
what are you doing?
I've got some film
I need developed, pronto.
That's gotta be
a thousand rolls!
Yeah, and?
Wow! It's so
beautiful...!
Where are we?
We're outside
of Shimoda...
You've learned
about that, right...?
Japan's first port open
to ships from the West.
Really...? You seem to know
about everything, Mr. Saiga.
I bet you've been
all over the world?
Yeah.
I never have.
In fact, I've never been
outside of Tokyo until now.
I used to dream about
places like this, though.
Never left Tokyo?
My god. Don't schools take
kids on field-trips anymore?
Yes. But I've never
been allowed to go.
And my family never went
on any trips, either.
You see, my family's
kind of strange.
My mother hates me,
and I don't know why.
Hey... You remember
that first night
when we were floating
on that buoy...?
As far as I know,
that's the first time
I'd ever left
Japan's shores.
What's wrong?
Sorry, it's just...
It's just a headache.
You gonna be all right?
Yeah, I should be.
I think I just need to lie back
like this for a little while.
I see. Well
I'm glad you told me now.
As it so happens, the guy we're
on our way to see is a doctor...
I was planning to have him
check us both out anyway--
we can just add
that to the list.
This is my fault...
I'm so sorry.
Drop the bag of
guilt, Kagura...
It's not yours to carry.
Yeah.
Tsujido.
It's that big shot from
the Traffic Department.
They're headed south on
the Tomei Expressway.
Our cameras caught them as
they took the Gotemba Center
exit onto Route 246.
By the way, any news
on the club reopening?
It won't be long...
And you have my word,
the moment it does open,
you'll get free admission...
In gratitude for your help.
They're on the Izu Peninsula.
We'll rendezvous there.
Roger that.
Good news, Doc. You're
about to get a new patient.
You got a good nose, sir.
But it's still no match
for their high-tech toys.
If I could smell
every fetid thing
that was happening
in this city,
I would have lost
my mind a long time ago.
Hello?
Hey Doc, you in here?
Guess not...
Yeah, go ahead and sign
in... I'll be right up.
Hope you're cheap.
War photographers don't
make dick these days...
War photog--?
Well I'll be damned.
So you're closing down
the ol' clinic, huh?
That's correct,
I've decided to re-enlist
with one of the
medical N.P.O.s.
You dragging
your wife along?
She passed on ...
'bout three months ago.
It was cancer
that took her,
it must have been eating
her away for months--
by the time I got back
to Japan it was too late...
And you know through
the entire ordeal...
she never once laid
the obvious blame.
What a god-damned
pitiful story.
I'm an M.D., and I didn't
even know she was sick.
So sorry to hear that, Doc.
I hate telling people--
feels like I could choke on
all the undeserved sympathy...
But anyhow... What brings
you to my clinic? --
Don't tell me you just came to
show off your young girlfriend.
I can't give you
details, honestly...
But I was hoping you could
run a few tests on us both...
Blood work...
CAT-Scans...
Even DNA, if possible.
DNA...? X-Rays are about
all I can do out here...
You'd have to go into
one of the major hospitals
if you want
testing like that.
I was hoping you could use
some of your connections for me.
Okay.
How could I say
no to you, Saiga?
I've done work with a
hospital not far from here.
I'll give 'em a call.
You're the best
there is, Doc.
Done yet?
I've worked all day, and
I've hardly made a dent.
These photographs...
They're Tatsumi Saiga's,
aren't they?
He was at your
last crime scene.
What? You know of him?
Of course. Anyone does,
who's serious about photography.
His images are so potent.
Like he fits the whole history
of the world in every frame.
It's a world
I can hardly imagine,
but he stares
it in the face.
Doctor?
Since you're his friend...
Would you mind telling
me more about him?
Saiga?
Yes, anything you
know would be helpful.
I want to learn where he
came from... Who he is.
Truth is, for as long
as I've known him...
I don't know
much about him.
Honestly, I can
only remember one time
when he talked about himself,
and his past...
It was over ten years ago,
on a chaotic newsroom floor...
A young man came in to see me
with a cut-and-dry offer--
he'd pay his own way
to the frontlines,
as long as we paid
him market price
for the photos
he sent back.
That's how I met Saiga.
At the time I was
fighting with the public,
protesting the war in one
of the more radical weeklies...
I suppose that's how
the kid found out about me.
So what's your answer?
You gonna take my deal...?
Or aren't you?
You get that in by tonight's
deadline, damn it...!
No bull!!
Why on earth you wanna
go to a place like that?
I'm a photographer......
It's my life...
And I want to give
my life to its pursuit,
the way Capa,
and Sawada did.
I was dumbstruck.
Here was a young man
not only willing,
but wanting to risk
his life for a cause.
In this shit-hole world
where the only values
come on price tags,
he was a breed
I thought was extinct.
And then, less than
two weeks later...
We got his first rolls
from the battlefield,
and again I was
knocked off my feet.
He was literally risking
everything out there...
Wandering the frontlines
day after day
for a snapshot of truth.
He was unbelievably
reckless, sure...
But his pictures struck
a chord with the public...
He was a household name.
Pleased to meet
you, Mr. Saiga...
I heard you're going on a
search-and-destroy mission...
Oh, yeah...
I'm Sid...
With the U.S. News Service.
Hello, Sid...
Pleasure's mine...
Though I guess
I can't get my scoop...
Now that you're here.
I'm going to take advantage
of your good fortune...
People talk
about your unit...
Say it always
comes back alive.
Everybody at base camp is just
superstitious, that's all...
Trust me, nothing is
certain in this place.
I just don't get it...
It's one thing to go to war with
a gun and join in the fight...
But charging into battle
armed with a camera--
what the hell's
the point of that?
Maybe this doesn't make sense,
from a cop's perspective.
But a war photographer
is looking for something
more abstract than the win/loss
columns on a general's desk.
It's not about their
lives, or glory.
It's about the work
they leave behind.
Putting a face
on the war...
Is their presence going to
change the battle's outcome?
Not a chance in hell.
Shit...
Showtime!
They save no lives,
and take no lives--
endangering no one else
but themselves.
Through showers of bullets,
exploding grenades,
even fields littered with
mines, they charge ahead.
You ain't getting
there before me.
Hey!
And they drop
like flies.
War photography's an
investment of sorts--
in the immediate sense the
work doesn't matter at all...
But later on, when it reaches
the public back home
through the newspapers...
Or years afterward, when
people's memories begin to fade,
that's when the
pictures really shine...
They become windows
to that moment in history.
People like us can stand
with the photographer
on that battlefield,
and try to make sense of the
mess we got ourselves in--
or in the very least,
acknowledge the horror of it.
All done.
Okay.
Such an overwhelming
life story...
I can't imagine what
it's been like for him.
No. I doubt anyone
who hasn't been there,
in the heat of battle,
really can...
It changes a person.
You become
accustomed to it.
To seeing the dead.
Your body and soul wear down
from the endless trauma,
until something inside
you just shuts off.
Eventually his luck ran out.
He suffered critical injuries,
and was barely saved by
an NPO Doctor named Ryogoku
who found Saiga wasting away
in a crude foreign hospital...
After that I pulled some
strings and forced him
to come back to Japan.
See... I thought it was
in his best interest,
but it's a decision
I've come to regret.
Regret?
Ever since he got off that
plane, his eyes have been dead.
The battlefield was the
one place he was alive.
Looks like the power
depends on the lens,
and its focal distance...
She has awoken
your potential,
and turned your deepest
desire into reality.
So, what kind of
investigation is this?
The none-of-your-business kind.
I should tell you...
He was looking into
a certain... secret club.
Secret club, eh?
Damn you, Saiga.
Are your eyes dead
to me now, too?
Stop.
Hello, Miss Kagura.
I've found you.
Let's talk in here.
He's such a good boy...
Does she have any family?
Not really...
They're... estranged...
Why, is there something
wrong with her?
Well...
Then I guess you're
the one I need to tell.
There, you see it?
A dark spot on her brain.
Odds are that's a tumor.
And it's a large one, too...
It looks to be pressing
against her parietal lobe...
The location makes
removal impossible.
Meaning...?
There's nothing we can do...
I'll be blunt, Saiga--
she probably has
six months, at best.
How do you live by the
ticking of a clock?
Do you count
each pendulum swing,
or try to pretend
you hear nothing at all?
There's a doctor in the dark,
anxious for a second opinion.
And when the sounds
of the piano die,
the mountain
will begin to slide.