[KAZUMA]
Hi, friends. How is everyone?
Here I am, stuck in
a strange world,
forced to go to school
with these freaks.
And it totally rules!
Hey, you guys?
Yeah?
I'm starting to suspect that
we might be in Valhalla.
I agree.
Have you ever seen
such beautiful girls?
Surely not in the Empire.
No way. Never.
Perhaps we're finally being
rewarded for our efforts.
The years of suffering
on the battlefield.
Let's have fun! The time
for celebration is here!
[COCYTUS] Drop and give
me a thousand pushups.
[BOYS grunting]
[WEISS]
Why is this happening to us?
[NEUMANN]
What'd we do?
[COCYTUS] As members
of the gym committee,
you must be the example
of fitness for everyone.
[DARKNESS pants]
That all you boys got?
This doesn't even count
as exercise. Not in my book!
[COCYTUS]
Impressive, great example.
Agreed. Really great.
Yeah. She's not even
getting tired.
Well, sure, but that's
not quite what I meant.
[WEISS]
Huh?
I mean, just look at them.
[DARKNESS continues panting]
[WEISS] Yeah, keep going.
Work those things out.
[NEUMANN] Yeah. Or maybe
just bust them out instead.
[DARKNESS]
I can sense them ogling me.
It's like they're molesting
me with their eyes!
Those men, staring at my body,
imagining all the depraved
things they'd do to me.
They're like a pack of wolves!
What will happen to me if
they decide to try something?
My arms will be too
tired to defend myself,
and I'll be completely
at their mercy!
What will happen
to me then, huh?!
[COCYTUS]
I feel like I missed something.
What scumbags.
Got that right.
[SUBARU] Hey, there, sis!
Working hard or hardly working?
[SUBARU gasps]
Who could look that miserable
while they're setting
up for a barbecue?
They're supposed to be fun.
You've got it wrong.
I like barbecues.
I'm the furthest thing
from miserable,
and this workload
is a piece of cake.
--Go be wrong somewhere else.
--[SUBARU] Don't lie!
You're miserable!
Okay, are you
even working, Barusu?
Oh, sorry, do you see any
animals on this field trip
that need looking after?
Thought not. So, instead,
I'm checking in with the
humans to see who needs help.
You mean hassling people.
As usual, you've just proven
you're a useless waste of space.
I knew you were gonna say that.
--[VISHA] Pardon.
--[SUBARU] Huh?
Your name is Subaru, right?
No, no. Barusu.
Natsuki Subaru?
Correct. Barusu.
[SUBARU]
Will you stop?
Can't you see you're
confusing the poor girl?
[KAZUMA yells]
[KAZUMA]
My eyes! My eyes!
That's what you get for staring
at girls in their swimsuits
like a perv. Your job is
to enforce the rules,
not break them yourself.
But, that was just mean!
[KAZUMA chuckles]
Stealth. A useful skill.
And now... I peep.
Summer is my favorite.
[DEMIURGE] What exactly
do you think you're doing?
[KAZUMA]
Uh?
And, flash!
My eyes! My eyes!
You didn't have to blind me
for peeping on the ladies!
Thank you for your cooperation.
[KAZUMA]
Will you listen to me?
My pleasure. I'm just glad
you were so swift to act.
Saved the day.
Oh, don't be foolish. I couldn't
have done it without your help.
Ains is lucky to have a
subordinate like you.
[KAZUMA] I feel kinda
like I'm intruding.
[REM] I don't think
anyone is coming.
Indeed, you may be right.
[REM] Oh, is something
the matter?
No! Everything's bouncing
along just fine!
[SUBARU]
This is delicious!
[RAM]
Of course it is.
[DARKNESS] Wow!
She really nailed that melon!
[KAZUMA]
Ha, ha!
[BOYS grunt]
[ROSWAAL]
And now, friends, it's time!
Everybody's gonna
test their courage!
Draw names from
this box to find out
who you'll be paired up with.
It can't be. It can't be!
'Kay, group one, it's your turn.
Yeah! Let's do this, ladies!
Hey! Stop trying to
boss everyone around.
or have you forgotten
that's my job.
I've been alive a whole
lot longer than you could
ever imagine,
stupid human.
[GRANTZ]
It's going well so far.
But. I'm not...
[GRANTZ] Thanks for being
such an angel, Mare.
Shut up! I'm not a lady!
[GRANTZ]
Huh?
[BEATRICE, MEGUMIN]
[ROSWAAL] That's enough
lollygagging, move it please!
Nicely done. You barely
seemed scared at all.
Of course we weren't scared.
The moment Ains and I got
assigned to different teams,
the exercise became
totally pointless.
That may be true for you, but
you can't speak for the others.
I mean. Not to be rude,
but our old world was a whole
lot scarier than this forest.
Well. It wasn't
our world, per se.
The Major was actually
the scariest part of it.
Captain, don't! You're the
one who said it, not me!
You sure? I think it was you.
Did not! Stop lying!
[TANYA sneezes]
Huh? Got a cold?
'Course not.
Oh, well, then, maybe
somebody's talking about you.
Hey, listen, you guys.
[SUBARU, TANYA]
Huh?
[AINS] This again?
I'd really appreciate it
if you'd just let it go and stop
trying to pick fights with me.
[AQUA]
Ugh, please, I'm not!
[AINS]
Hm?
[AQUA] I'm curious:
you're all from Earth, right?
[ALL gasp]
Wait, How'd you
figure that out?
I can just tell.
Kazuma is from Earth, too.
I'm the one who brought
him to his new world
in the first place.
[gasps] Would you mind
repeating that last bit, please?
[AQUA] You see.
I am a deity, a goddess.
I sent Kazuma to his world,
the one we were in before this,
to defeat the Demon King, so,
hope that clears things up?
You said you're a deity?
--[TANYA growls]
--[AQUA] That's right.
Again, a goddess.
[SUBARU]
Seriously?
[TANYA]
It was you.
[AQUA]
Huh?
You're the infamous
Being X, my enemy!
[TANYA yells]
[ROSWAAL]
Oh?
[ALL gasping]
Subaru, no!
[AINS]
Tanya, wait! Stop it! Please!
[TANYA] Don't try and
get in my way, Ains.
Tanya, you're really
starting to scare me!
Oh, frightening you, am I?
A god like Being X
getting scared?
Well, that's just pathetic.
[AQUA] You keep saying that
"Being X" thing, but I ha--
Shut your mouth! Do you realize
what a stupid fraud you are?
[SUBARU] Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, calm down!
I don't know what's going on,
but can you please
be reasonable?
What is your problem, sir?
You'd better stay out of my way!
Tanya, come on!
Look, I have no knowledge of
what happened in your world,
but I have a sneaking
feeling you're misplacing
your anger here.
[AINS]
I actually agree with him.
Take a step back
and think about it.
Do you really think Being X,
the god, or the self-proclaimed
god that sent you to your
world is the same entity
that's in front of you now?
[gasps]
[AQUA whimpers]
You do have a point.
They're nothing alike.
[SUBARU]
You see?
[TANYA sighs] Okay. I guess
there are people from all
kinds of different worlds
together in this one.
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
[AQUA]
Uh, sure.
[TANYA] I guess I get a little
hyper-sensitive when people
call themselves deities.
Why are you just getting
all worked up now?
I've been saying I was
a goddess since day one!
[TANYA]
Eh?
[AQUA]
Huh?
Uh...
[AINS]
Yeah, haven't you heard her?
Huh? Uh... She never
seemed very goddess-like.
So, maybe it just took a while
for the information to sink in.
I see. Maybe.
That's really insulting!
[TANYA] If I lose my cool around
every self-proclaimed goddess
that comes along, I must
have a lot more work
to do than I thought.
That's mean, too!
[ALBEDO]
Lord Ains! My Lord Ains!
[AINS]
Oh, there you are.
We all witnessed a powerful
magical explosion
that felt exactly
like an earthquake.
Mind sharing to the
group what happened?
[AINS]
Well, you see, uh...
I'm embarrassed to admit
I lost my composure.
Thanks to Ains and
Subaru's wisdom,
I was able to regain
control of myself.
I'm sorry for causing trouble.
I'm working through some stuff.
Well, as long as everyone
is safe, it's all right.
But you should control
your magic force.
You knocked a couple
people out cold.
[sighs] Amateurs! You all
lack mental discipline!
No, I think it has more to do
with the fact that those dudes
know exactly what you
can be like when you get all
bent out of shape.
They're traumatized.
Oh, you have a point there.
That's still a sign of weakness!
[SUBARU]
You're ruthless!
I really am a goddess!
But nobody ever
believes what I say!
Then, when someone did seem to
believe it, they got mad at me!
Yeah, okay. But you're actually
just an archpriestess who tells
people she's a goddess
when she's really not.
Come on!
[SUBARU]
He's pretty ruthless, too!
[KAZUMA]
Oh, I misspoke.
[AINS]
If we were on Yggdrasil,
her power would exceed
eighth tier magic.
Few can summon
that kind of might.
But that man took it in the
face and still remained
standing afterwards.
[AQUA]
You know I'm a real goddess!
Just stop lying and
admit it to yourself!
[AINS] What kind of
intense mental stress
must this man be accustomed to?