[MOMONGA] Uh. Did she
bring me here to talk,
or just glare at me?
[grunts]
[MOMONGA]
I'm the lord of Death!
Master of the Great
Tomb of Nazarick!
I will not be intimidated!
[AINS] You wanted to
discuss something. What is it?
[TANYA]
Tell me...
[AINS gasps]
[TANYA] You're that bastard,
Being X, aren't you?
[AINS]
Huh?
Being X you say?
You're not some regular schmuck.
You've got that powerful
aura around you.
And that nightmarish face.
So, cut the crap and admit
you're the wannabe god, Being X!
[AINS] Wait. What are
you talking about?
You tossed me into a
hellish world of war,
but I guess that wasn't
enough for you, was it?
Couldn't get your jollies
until you sent this little girl
back to school, huh?
Is this some sick joke?
[AINS]
Wait one moment!
For what?
[AINS] Let me ask you something.
Are you originally from Earth?
Japan, to be more specific?
[gasps]
[ALBEDO growls]
[ERICH] Now, can anybody tell
me what the author may have
been thinking when he
wrote this second...
Uh. Albedo? Is that black
cloud you're wearing new?
Now don't work
yourself in a tizzy.
Lord Ains is not
exactly the type of man
who chases little girls
around, you know.
You're totally
missing the point!
Lord Ains is
simply irresistible.
Those red eyes and studly horns.
I'm sure she fell madly in love
with him the instant
he walked in the room,
I mean how can you not?
[REM]
I know!
I get you. For real!
[ALBEDO sighs]
Wait. Are the two
of you friends,
or am I missing something?
[SHALLTEAR] I fail to see
how you're alike in any way.
[ALBEDO]
Someday, even you...
[ERICH] Are any of them even
paying attention to me?
Hold on. You're saying you're
in the same situation as I am?
[AINS] Yes. Though I
was transported,
and you've got some
reincarnation thing going on.
Sorry I was being rude,
but I'm sure you can imagine
why I'd have no idea
you were actually human.
Think nothing of it.
For the record,
you don't exactly look like
your typical salaryman, either.
[TANYA]
No, I don't.
Salaryman. That's a
title I haven't heard
in a very long time.
You really should've told me you
were from another world sooner.
I wouldn't have called you such
a horrible thing as Being X,
at least.
[AINS]
Well, to be perfectly honest.
I didn't think anyone
would believe me.
I know just how you feel.
[school bell rings]
[ALBEDO gasps]
Oh, Lord Ains!
[AURA, SHALLTEAR]
See you later!
[ERICH gasps]
[VISHA grunts]
Sorry! But I have to go, too!
[door clatters]
[sighs] Don't forget we're
having a talent show.
It'll be held tomorrow
morning after class.
[ERICH] The performers have not
yet been chosen, so you should
all come prepared to
showcase your "talents".
[COCYTUS] Sir. Can you
tell us why exactly
we're being ordered
to do such a thing?
Well, uh. To quote
Mister Roswaal,
"Wouldn't that be fun?"
His opinion, not mine.
[RAM]
That settles it.
[COCYTUS]
Does it, now?
Yes. Teachers make
the rules. It's settled.
[COCYTUS]
But. Is it settled?
It's settled, now!
Interesting.
Did you actually learn
something from all that?
[AINS]
So, do you enjoy coffee?
Oh, I love it. Back
in Japan, I would--
[VISHA]
Major! Major!
Hi. Uh...
Yes? What is it?
Well, ma'am. School's over for
the day, so I came to fetch you.
And I thought we might head
over to the market and get some
of those croquettes you're
so fond of, they're on sale!
[TANYA sighs] It seems
the reason we're here
and who brought us to this world
will remain a mystery for now.
But, at least...
[AINS]
At least what?
The food's divine.
Best I've ever had.
Well, it was nice talking
to you, Ains Ooal Gown.
Let's do it again sometime.
[AINS]
Yes. I'd like that.
[VISHA] I'm a little
surprised the two of you
got along so well.
[TANYA]
What's that supposed to mean?
[VISHA] Maybe I should
have said, "impressed."
[AINS] This world is full
of culinary delights, eh?
[MOMONGA]
Damnit, I wish I could eat!
[ALBEDO growls]
[TANYA]
Good morning to you, colonel.
Excuse me, teacher!
Top of the morning
to you, teacher!
[ERICH]
Uh... Yeah, good morning.
[ERICH] I didn't know Major
von Degurechaff could smile.
A monster like her,
grinning ear to ear.
It chills my blood.
I realize things
are different here,
but that is totally bizarre.
[AINS] I hope the day
finds you well, teacher.
[ERICH]
Uh, yes, and same to you, Ains.
Yeah. This world holds
creatures far more terrifying
than demonic girls.
[SUBARU pants]
Sorry for the hold up.
Didn't mean to make you wait.
It's fine. I didn't want
to leave without you.
Appreciate that. We gotta
haul ass, or we'll be tardy!
Let's kick it up a notch!
Right!
[SUBARU]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hold on, there's no freaking
way I could keep up with you!
[REM] Well, then I'll just
have to carry you there.
[REM grunts]
[SUBARU]
This is a lot faster.
But still, I'm feeling way less
like a man and more like a baby.
I think this suits
you perfectly,
and it really gives you
the look of a nobleman.
That's nice, but I don't see
any other guys being schlepped
around by their lady friends.
Oh, there's one!
Kazuma? I know we're running
late, but this seems silly.
I mean, do I have to carry you?
I would argue you do.
'Cause this is the fastest way
we can travel with
our current party.
I don't have the same ability
for high speed as you do,
so here we are.
Yeah, but don't you think
this is just a little
emasculating for you?
[KAZUMA] I think getting
carried around by some buff
crusader chick makes
me look more manly.
[DARKNESS gasps]
[KAZUMA, DARKNESS]
Huh?
[SUBARU, KAZUMA groan]
[SUBARU] Ya know,
go ahead and put me down.
Oh, okay.
Ya know, go ahead
and put me down.
Yeah, okay.
[ALL groan]
[SUBARU, KAZUMA] What's up?
Oh crap, that means we're tardy!
[SUBARU] Faster! Faster! Faster!
Faster! Faster! Faster! Faster!
[KAZUMA pants]
[shouts]
Natsuki. You're late!
[SUBARU]
No!
[ERICH] And you, young man!
You're also late!
[KAZUMA yells]
Hey, your name's
Kazuma, isn't it?
Yep. That's me.
Last name Satou?
Yeah. That's what they call me.
[SUBARU]
So, were you...?
Wait. I've got the
same question for you.
[BOTH] So, were you... Randomly
summoned to some other world?
Say what?
What'd you say?
I knew it from the very first
time I heard your name
during that class intro.
It was the dope tracksuit
for me. I had one.
Wore it when I was reincarnated.
It's the quintessential
outfit for the man
who never leaves his room.
I left my room a lot actually.
[ERICH] Hey, less talkity
and more buckety.
[KAZUMA] So, you know that trope
when a character reincarnates,
and they get some
broken superpower?
Oh yeah, for sure.
Way too powered up.
Can't even stop winning!
That's how it goes, uh-huh.
Turns out in reality,
it's nothing like that at all.
Yeah, don't I know it.
So I gotta beat
this "Devil King."
Now they say I can have some
"awesome power or weapon"
ya know?
But that turns out to be some
useless lush of a goddess.
Get this, my party?
A chatterbox mage, who can
only use one spell a day!
And a crusader who
can't hit a damn thing!
We had no coin, and had to
sleep in a stinky ol' stable!
I'm telling ya man, it was
a freaking beating.
I met this half-elf chick
and had to help her
with a buncha stuff.
We live in a mansion, though.
We've got these twin
demon maids with us.
And this snarky-ass loli,
whose hair is like a couple
of power drills. Ha, ha...
[gasps]
Wait...
[SUBARU]
Huh?
What the hell, bruh?
Now don't get the wrong idea.
Rem does have a
major thing for me.
Oh. Rem's uh, the stacked twin,
the one with the blue hair.
Wait, say what?
Thing is, Me and Emilia,
that's the half-elf chick,
We're totally the OTP!
[KAZUMA]
This freaking guy!
Yeah. Guess we both have it
pretty rough don't we?
I got it rough and
you got it cushy!
You're surrounded by girls?
And you live in luxury?
It's rough 'cause your
crush doesn't like you?
That's it! You're my enemy!
You harem-having
whiny baby bitch!
I'm your enemy?
We both died and went
into another world,
but I happened to get the
crappy one? It's not fair!
[SUBARU] Hmph, I didn't
die before I got there.