[ROSWAAL] Seeing how well you've
all adapted to your school life
makes me very happy. So far,
we've touched on the rules,
and learned everyone's names.
So without further delay.
It's time for us to decide
who will be our class reppy!
Not only will we choose our
reppy, but the vice-reppy too.
[ALBEDO]
Sir!
Do you have a question,
Miss Albedo?
I just want to say Lord Ains
should clearly be hailed
as class alpha!
[AQUA]
Nope! No way! Not gonna happen!
I refuse to be represented
by some scary, evil,
undead monster!
Ooh, does that mean you'll
be volunteering, Miss Aqua?
[AQUA] Yes, it does!
I mean, it only makes sense!
This class needs a leader
who's truly divine, like me!
[ALBEDO] You're even uglier
when your mouth is moving.
[AQUA]
Huh?!
I mean, really. The thought
of an ugly, crazy,
screeching harpy like you
repping us. Utter nonsense.
I may be a lot of things,
but I'm not ugly!
Hey Kazuma!
Yeah, yeah, that's my name.
That succubus over there
is being a big ol' meanie!
[DARKNESS]
Please, Aqua.
What she said barely
counts as an insult.
You need a lesson in true shame.
[KAZUMA]
That'll be a hard nope from me!
So, we have two names up for
the position, Ains and Aqua.
Is there anybody else?
[TANYA exhales]
[TANYA] I think trying to
represent this freakshow
would be just about as insane as
going back to the front lines.
No way in hell I'm throwing
my name in the ring.
[EMILIA] Oh, Mister Roswaal.
Me. I volunteer, too.
Yes. I think this class
should be a place
where we can all be friends.
I'll vote for ya! And I know
everybody else will too!
Alright, teach! Let's do
this thing! Let's vote!
[ROSWAAL]
We'll be drawing names.
[SUBARU]
Oh, we will?
Well, I will.
Um, hello. My name's Emilia,
your new class rep.
It's a great honor.
I'll do my very best.
[SUBARU chuckles]
That's quite a smug
look you have there,
especially since
you've done nothing.
[ALBEDO growls]
I will not accept this!
We're led by a stammering child,
while the powerful and sexy
Lord Ains is
second in command?
I'm sorry you feel that way.
But the process was
open and fair, so...
It's wrong. And that
homely girl is vice rep?
Don't insult me!
For the record, I'm not even
interested in "old boney"!
And I have no desire to
be the vice-rep, either!
Well. Seems we have an
open slot for vice-rep,
don't we now?
[BOTH gasp]
[SHALLTEAR] I'd be more
than happy to volunteer
for the role.
Hold on a minute!
I would be honored to serve
alongside our glorious
Lord Ains!
Uh. I would too.
[AINS]
Calm down, everyone!
It's insane.
[NEUMANN]
Hm?
The skeleton... has a harem.
Yeah.
But not us. Makes me sad.
[NEUMANN]
Yeah.
I'm actually pretty jealous.
[WEISS] An Imperial Soldier
should never broadcast
desires like that.
So are you saying
you're not jealous, then?
I guess you could say that.
But it would be a lie.
--[GRANTZ] You too, huh?
--[NEUMANN] Samesies.
Why do the men in our battalion
have to be so obvious
about everything?
Huh?
Well, in my opinion, having
strong desires like that
can be pretty helpful
on the battlefield.
You really think so?
[TANYA]
I really do.
[VISHA]
Hm!
[SUBARU] I guess in every world
there are little girls going on
about stuff they
don't understand.
Your inner thoughts are just
as idiotic as your words,
I suppose.
[ROSWAAL] Okay, that's quite
enough of that!
I know you could go
on like this forever.
So instead, I'm just going
to draw more names.
[AINS] Yes, I support this move!
Let's do it that way!
[ALL]
Lord!
Oh, wow, that was quick!
Hell yeah!
[ALL groan]
[ROSWAAL]
It's settled.
These will be your teams, for a
little while at least, okay?
Whoa? Really?
That's my team, huh?
I've never even talked
to those people, ya know.
[ROSWAAL] Well, talking is a
great way to turn a stranger
into a friend, so lucky you!
They're splitting us up.
But still, this could be
a great opportunity.
Opportunity?
[DEMIURGE]
Take a closer look at this list.
Seems the guardians have
been equally divided.
[SHALLTEAR] True, but what
point are you trying to make?
Lord Ains gave us clear orders.
We're to follow the rules of
this school life for the moment.
But we must consider
what the "for the moment"
part means, exactly.
[AINS]
Hm?
Our main goal. And this has been
stated repeatedly by Lord Ains,
is still world domination.
We wouldn't want to put
that aim in jeopardy.
As we're in an
uncertain environment.
Our wise lord wants us to
gather intelligence on the
assembled factions, and use
our findings against them.
[AINS]
Huh?
Why am I on the
animal care team?
[DEMIURGE] So you see, this is
a chance to show Lord Ains
the degree to which
we serve him.
Our obedience to him and our
absolute adherence to his
primary objective is
being put to the test.
[COCYTUS] So to serve our Lord,
we must faithfully execute
our duties on our
respective committees?
[DEMIURGE]
That's correct.
--[AINS] Huh?!
--[SHALLTEAR] Understood!
In order to please my
Lord and Master,
I will be the best damn nurse
this world has ever seen!
[ROSWAAL]
Hello, Beatrice!
Is something
troubling you, dear?
You and I need to have
a little chat, Roswaal.
That would be "Mister Roswaal."
You really believe that
you can get away with
that rigged drawing, I suppose.
[ROSWAAL] I don't know
what you mean by "rigged."
Whatever it is you're planning,
I want to know all the details.
Is that so? Planning anything
would be a waste of my time.
Stop being cryptic and
tell me what it is!
I'm being honest.
In the end, we all have to act
out the parts we were given.
That goes for you,
that goes for me...
Hey! Hold on, Roswaal!
You get back here!
[KAZUMA]
Hey, Mom. Hey, Dad.
It's Kazuma It's been a while,
but things have been nutty.
Dying was bad enough, but then
I was alive again and
partnered up with some useless
goddess in a weird world
full of crazy people.
But now, I find myself
in another world.
And in this one I'm a student.
I know, I know.
I used to play hooky and
wouldn't go to class, even when
you begged me to, so I'm just
as surprised as you guys are,
trust me.
But I gotta say, the weirdest
thing about this school...
How come nobody here
is an actual student?
Why is the place so crazy?!
What's wrong with you?
Speak up, Kazuma Satou.
[KAZUMA] I'm stuck here
with an evil little girl.
And some guy who may
literally be the devil!
Yeah? And you think lying
on the floor will help?
I can't get up for some reason!
[DEMIURGE]
Hm. My command spell
doesn't seem to work
as intended here.
Kneel before us!
What the--?
[TANYA]
Hm?
Kick, kick, kick, kick...
[DEMIURGE] There is something
rather complicated about the
power balance in this world.
Now back on your feet!
[KAZUMA] Ugh. Whoa.
What just happened?
Are you sick, boy?
If you're feeling ill,
perhaps you should lie
back down for a little bit.
Yeah, I think I
just might, honestly.
[TANYA]
Unacceptable.
We'll never get anything
done at this rate. Stand up!
What'd you just say?
I clearly said, "stand up!"
[KAZUMA groans]
[DEMIURGE] This human girl has
the power to command others?
This isn't some kind of jokey,
slice of life world we're in.
At least, not if I can help it!
[DEMIURGE]
Ah!
Rules first! We need
to establish order!
Freedom will be secondary!
Yes, I agree whole-heartedly!
We'll need to come up with a
strict list of rules to follow.
Yeah. And the more of them
there are, the better.
You know...
...I think you and I are
going to get along famously.
Ains has excellent
taste in allies.
That's kind of you. And I must
say, I'm beginning to see why
he holds you in
such high regard.
Oh, and by the way...
[KAZUMA]
Mom, Dad, I'm sorry about this,
but I think I'm never coming
back to school again!
[COCYTUS] If there
are no objections,
I will assume the role of
gym committee leader.
Makes sense. You do strike me
as the strongest one here.
Oh yeah.
So, what are we doing?
Binding our bodies and
hanging from the rafters?
Or forcefully thrusting
ourselves deep
in the throat of a giant toad?
[COCYTUS]
Young lady.
You angry? You deadly
looking metal mantis man?
[COCYTUS]
What did you just call me?
You have four arms for
a reason, don't you?
So you can pin down my arms
and legs at the same time.
You'll hold me tight and say,
"You're totally helpless,
now aren't you?"
"Scream all you want,
no one cares."
But I'll try to resist!
Then your frosty breath will
give my entire body chills.
All of the sensitive
parts especially.
Oh my god! I can't handle it,
so soft and chilly!
[COCYTUS]
Such an odd young lady.
What's going on with her?
Daddy issues?
Easy, Darkness. You're scaring
our friend, Cocytus.
You! You dare call
yourself a man?
You'll side with the monster,
and while he holds me down,
you'll savage me with those
strong, unforgiving eyebrows!
What is wrong with you?
Don't know, but your brows
are freaking her out.
Seems so.
[gasps]
Take me!
The wheels of reincarnation
have begun to spin. Heh!