[EMILIA sighs]
[EMILIA]
This is so hard.
[PUCK]
Good work today, Lia.
I bet it must be pretty
tough having to be the
representative of all of those
weirdos in your class, huh?
[EMILIA]
Yeah, it's not easy.
Although you do seem
happier than usual lately.
[EMILIA]
Well.
I feel lucky because everyone
in class is so unique.
I'm not sure that "unique,"
is the right word,
but I get what
you're saying.
It's kind of nice, actually.
I'm not known as "that
silver-haired half-elf" here.
Yeah.
There's a lot I
don't understand.
Like where we are,
or how this all happened.
Though I get the feeling Roswaal
knows what's going on.
But still. I want to do whatever
I can with this opportunity.
[PUCK]
Good!
It might be difficult.
Mm. Honestly, I know it will be.
But you know what?
I'll give it my best try!
Well, no matter what
you decide to do,
you know I've got your
back all the way!
That's sweet. Thanks, Puck!
[PUCK chuckles]
By the way.
[PUCK]
Huh?
Oh, it's just. I think I really
like going to school.
I'm having fun!
[REM] I'm curious.
How's animal duty treating you?
Yeah, the truth is,
it's kinda nutty.
Oh really? How so?
Well...
[SUBARU]
This guy, is a tiny bit bigger
than the Djungarian
hamsters I'm used to.
I don't believe it. So familiar
with my species, you are?
Yeah, but the ones I've
encountered were a little,
and by that I mean,
a lot different.
[HAMSUKE] A very similar
sentiment my lord did express.
[SUBARU] I have a hard
time understanding you
when you're nomming
on my head, ya know?
[AURA]
Cut it out, Hamsuke!
My animal instincts just took
over and chew on him I did!
Sorry, Subaru!
Whoa, you're all bloody!
I'm fine. I guess him chewing
only on me makes me special.
You know better than that!
Yes but for some reason
whenever I see him,
the excitement takes
over me, it does.
High fives work, too! Or is
chewing on someone's head
the way your kind
likes to say hello?
[HAMSUKE] Extremely ashamed
of myself, I am.
[SUBARU] Then maybe you
should stop chewing on me!
So yeah, it's nutty.
[REM]
We must go slay that monster!
Whoa, slow your
roll there slugger!
Besides, Rozzy told us not
to start fights, remember?
Forget about it.
Anyway, how's your gig going?
Well, since I'm basically
the school nurse,
I don't really have
all that much to do
unless somebody gets
sick or injured.
[gasps]
Subaru!
[SUBARU]
Huh?
Why didn't you come to me
for help when that evil monster
attacked you?
Oh. I didn't want you to worry.
Next time that happens,
you come straight to me!
To be honest, I'm not really
planning on letting that
happen again, so...
Hey.
You got any crazy stories of
stuff going down in the library?
Not much happens there,
I suppose.
I just end up reading
books all day.
[SUBARU]
That sounds right up your alley.
It's just fine by me.
If I were forced to spend time
with those other lunatics
in class, I'd become
one myself, I suppose.
Oh. But I thought you had
somebody else working with you,
is that right?
Mare, if I recall correctly.
That's true, I suppose.
Yeah, she's fine.
Coming from you,
that's practically a
gushing compliment.
There's nothing really
remarkable about her.
But I will say, she makes
me feel so relaxed.
Uh! Um, hey. Uh...
Yes, what is it?
Well, this book I'm reading
is pretty good, is all.
[BEATRICE]
I'll read it later, I suppose.
[MARE gasps, giggles]
Are ya tryin' to tell us
you made a little friend?
That's precious.
I'm not saying that at all!
You had to make me upset!
So typical.
[MARE] Can you slow down
a little for me, please?
Come on. Why don't you
just hurry up instead?
Hey! What's up, guys?
How's it going?
Wow, I guess you're always
loud and annoying, huh?
Yeah, it's just one more
extraordinary thing about me!
The fact you're proud of that
is kinda impressive, actually!
By the way, how's your
Hamsuke bite?
Oh, that? Just peachy!
[AURA]
Good to hear!
Anyway, I gotta go feed the
big guy, so I'll see ya later!
Cool! Fill him up!
Give him so much he
won't wanna snack on me
when it's my turn
to check on him!
[AURA] Yeah, okay, I got it!
I'll make sure to leave
just enough space
in his belly for you!
Hey!
Oh. Lovely morning, isn't it?
Indeed it is, I suppose.
Well, okay, I guess I'll
be talking to you later.
Not so fast. If you're
going to open the library,
I suppose I'll go with you.
[MARE]
Okay!
What's up with you?
Nothing. I was just thinking
this is kind of fun.
It is, kinda.
Hey, Rem.
Emilia came to school pretty
early this morning didn't she?
Yes.
She said that she had something
rather important to do.
[SUBARU]
That's weird.
[REM]
Rather odd.
[MEGUMIN]
Good morning!
Alright, let's give
it our best today!
Now here's a song that's sure
to get your blood pumping!
It's called, "Piercing Howl!
Coal Black Storm!"
[GRANTZ]
No! That's horrible! Here!
[MEGUMIN]
What do you know about music?
Just because you don't have the
artistic sense to understand it,
doesn't mean that
it's not good!
[REM gasps] I just remembered
something I have to do
in the nurse's office.
You go on to class,
and I'll see you there.
Cool.
What's up, you guys?
Never fear,
Subaru Natsuki's here!
Hey, Emilia! You all
look deep in thought.
We are.
You know, I spent a lot of
time thinking yesterday.
School should be fun.
I want every one of us to have
a good time while we're here.
[SUBARU]
Makes sense.
And so... I thought...
...that we should all do some
kind of fun activity together.
What do you think.
Is it a good idea?
Well, I trust in
your judgment, so yeah.
Let's do something fun!
I'll be more than happy to help.
Thank you. That's sweet.
Sure! But, uh.
Are those guys... into "fun?"
[AINS]
Hello. I am Ains Ooal Gown.
Please, call me Ains.
Oh. Ains, huh?
Lord Ains to you!
[SUBARU gasps]
[AINS]
Relax, Albedo.
Please forgive me.
[AINS]
Sorry about that.
Now, regarding Emilia's plan.
I think it's an excellent idea.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[AINS] We may not know why
we're here, but here we are.
I suppose you could
say the situation
makes us comrades, in a sense.
Comrades?
[AINS] There's a strong
argument to be made that
getting to know each other would
only help us reach our goal.
[MOMONGA] I used to do a lot
of fun stuff with my guild.
I mean, not IRL, of course.
[AINS] I agree that it
would be beneficial,
and bring the team together.
What say you, Albedo?
You're as wise as
you are handsome.
I'll gladly defer to
your wishes, my lord.
If you think we should go
along with her plan, so do I.
Alright then, Ains. Let's do it!
That's lord Ains!
Sorry.
[AINS]
Albedo!
[SUBARU]
It's weird,
but I feel like he's
from my world, somehow.
Anyway, it won't hurt
to get along with him.
[AINS] I'll call you Subaru,
so we're even.
Does that work for you, Subaru?
[SUBARU]
Yeah, totally.
This is great! You're getting
along wonderfully!
Well, I wouldn't go and pick
out a wedding gift for us yet,
but this is a pretty good start.
[AINS]
Hm?
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[AINS]
Excuse me.
[ALBEDO gasps]
If you need to fondle a chest,
I'm right here you know?
[AINS]
Hmm...
[SUBARU]
Uh, wait. I...
[AINS]
Forgive the intrusion.
I just noticed something
and had to investigate.
Guess I can cross "having a
skeleton touch my chest"
off my bucket list, now.
That was scary.
[AINS laughs] Well, that was
the first time I've done that
without crushing
the person's heart!
[AINS, SUBARU laugh]
That's not even funny!
Oh my. You're as thick
as thieves, eh?
Listen carefully,
because I have some news
that I know you will adore.
[ALL]
Huh?
We'll be having an excursion,
or I suppose in school, it's
what you'd call a field trip?
Are you serious?
Yes. And what better
place is there
to get to know each other
more intimately than a beach?
There'll be fun and sun!
Really? We've barely just
gotten past introductions
at this point. Don't you think
that's jumping the gun a bit?
Oh silly. Youth goes
by so quickly. Poof!
Yeah, that kinda makes sense.
Not how I would
phrase it, but...
[AINS]
Hm...
Emilia, why don't we organize
an activity while we're away
on this so-called "field trip?"
You want to organize
an activity?
[AINS]
Yes. That's what I said.
I think we should hold an
offsite event in which the
entire class can participate.
That's a wonderful idea!
Once again,
you're so right, my lord!
I wonder what exactly we'll do.
Hm. I'll try to
think of something.
Thanks Ains. Good work!
She may be smiling
at someone else,
but I still think
Emilia's a real angel.
For short: "E. R. A."
I'm sorry. Was that supposed
to make sense, or..?
[ALBEDO]
Sounded like gibberish to me.
[ROSWAAL] I suppose I
can leave it to the kids
for the time being.
Best... of... luck!