[TANYA] Greetings to my
beloved Fatherland.
And to all the backwards
territories surrounding it.
At the moment, I am currently
engaged in what could be called
"academic pursuits."
[sighs]
[TANYA] Yes, this is
exactly what I wanted!
A stable, civilized,
non-threatening life
in the rear echelon.
I've found myself in a setting
centered on learning.
One that has nothing
to do with war.
However... Though my current
station may sound peaceful,
when I look around,
I have to wonder what
the hell is going on.
The battlefield is chaotic,
but at least it makes sense.
What's more, General Rudersdorf
is serving as the principal,
and General Zettour
is our vice-principal?
Then there's the clownish,
yodeling fool in front.
Come to think of it, this world
may be even more confusing
than that hellish nightmare
I was sent to before.
But still...
[ALBEDO growls]
[ROSWAAL]
Your name is Albedo, yes?
[ALBEDO]
Hm?
Don't even try it.
I don't believe you have the
authority to give me orders!
Please, try to remember
it's very important
that we all get along here.
We don't want any
problems now, do we?
Although it is a
rhetorical question,
the answer is still
an emphatic, "no, sir."
I see now, that's how it is.
You see what's how what is?
Mister Roswaal seems to
be outlining the rules
we're to follow.
He's implying any behavior
that would jeopardize our quote,
unquote, "school life" is taboo.
I hear you talking,
but it's all noise to me.
Then perhaps this will help.
We're trapped in this world.
And some force is compelling
us to pretend we're students.
[SHALLTEAR]
Hm...
[MOMONGA]
Oh man, really?
Our liege understood
this situation
from the very beginning.
[MOMONGA] I didn't know
it from the beginning!
Hell, I still don't have a clue!
[AINS] An astute observation,
Demiurge. It's like that.
It is, indeed.
[AINS]
Yes. That thing.
Indeed, it is.
[MOMONGA]
What thing?
[AINS] We get it,
but everyone except you and I,
don't seem to grasp that thing.
So you must explain it to them.
As you wish.
Let us just assume that this
world is covered by some type of
barrier which has a compulsory
effect on those within.
There are no further
details at the moment.
But I'd wager that engaging in
any action deemed threatening
to the balance here could bar
us from returning home.
[MOMONGA]
Oh, so that's the thing.
[COCYTUS]
Which is why you demanded
we refrain from combat.
[AINS] Uh, ahem. Yes, correct.
Well done, Demiurge.
No. I should have realized
this much sooner. Forgive me.
[AINS] Even the wisest
in Nazarick needs time
to process such things.
[TANYA]
I have to admit,
what the lackey is saying seems
to make a little bit of sense.
I suppose for the time being,
I'll have to operate
under these parameters.
Major! Major Degurechaff!
[TANYA]
Huh?
I received this communique.
[TANYA]
Let's see.
"Our class will be holding a
talent show. This mandatory
activity will let us get to
know each other better."
What is this nonsense?
[EMILIA]
Hey, Subaru?
What kind of talents are
you supposed to showcase
at a talent show?
[SUBARU] Hm... Entertaining
little party tricks, I guess.
Crap like that.
What are party tricks?
[SUBARU]
Ya know, something you can do,
that maybe other people can't.
Talent is in the name.
Then perhaps you should show
off your uncanny ability
to fail at life?
Can you say anything without
taking a personal shot at me?
[RAM] If you could do something
else, we'd know by now.
Man, don't write me
off like that.
I may have a hidden talent
that is so freakin' awesome,
it'll blow you away.
[RAM]
Nope.
Hey now!
[PUCK]
But you know,
if Subaru does have some
amazing secret talent,
I'd honestly love to see it.
[SUBARU] Don't talk with your
mouth full, it's gross.
What I wouldn't give to learn
about all your biggest secrets.
I'm curious as well.
I wonder what you can do.
Ooh, you ladies are in for it!
Just when you think you might
know everything about me.
I'll whip something out
that'll knock your
frilly little socks off!
Stop nomming, will ya?
My talents are quite obvious.
I have no need to present them.
[BOTH gasp]
You realize a photograph
would last longer?
Of course. I'm sorry,
little girl. Truly.
Not nearly as sorry as you'll be
if you continue addressing me
as "little girl". In fact,
don't address me at all.
My friend here is no good
with kids. Excuse him.
[BEATRICE grunts] Were you all
trained to be insufferable,
or is that just
a coincidence?
[BEATRICE growls]
[WEISS gasps]
What did you do to
that little girl?
It seems like you've upset her.
Nothing, sir. We've been
extremely polite.
Are you sure?
She looked rather irate.
You know, captain. It's always
something with those types.
Am I right?
Yeah, like a certain
battalion commander, eh?
Damn straight.
[KOENIG, NUEMANN chuckle]
I see. I'll be sure to include
that in my next report
to the commander.
[KOENIG]
Captain, if she heard that,
she'd use my balls
for target practice.
[NUEMANN]
Yup.
[KOENIG, WEISS laugh]
[grunts] Roswaal's definitely
got some explaining to do.
Surely he'll tell me what's
going on if I demand it!
Roswaal in here, I suppose?
[ERICH] Uh... Oh uh,
your name is Beatrice,
if I'm not mistaken?
Yes, that's correct. And who
in the hell might you be?
[ERICH] Well, first,
you shouldn't talk
to your teachers like that.
I haven't agreed to
be your student!
Besides, I've come here to have
a word with Roswaal. Not you.
So, where is he?
[ERICH grunts]
Now Beatrice, you must not
talk to any teacher like that.
Like it or not, you and all
the others are students.
Here for the express purpose of
experiencing school life.
Therefore, you need to start
behaving like students.
[BEATRICE grumbles]
[ERICH]
You understand?
I get it. I suppose.
Tell Mister Roswaal that
Betty came by to see him,
if you would please.
Much better. I shall
pass that along.
Now, lunch break's almost over.
Please return to your classroom.
You don't need to tell
me what to do. Hmph!
[sighs] Was I coming across
too harshly? Perhaps.
But no matter how she may look,
I can't let my guard down.
After all. I know firsthand
there are monsters who
walk this world in the
form of little girls.
[TANYA sneezes]
Do you have a cold?
No.
[AQUA]
Goddess bless you!
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
So what's her deal?
[VISHA chuckles nervously]
Show a little gratitude,
would ya?
Wait. Do ya understand
why I said that?
Check it. When someone
sneezes, you say,
"God, bless you."
But I'm a goddess, see?
[TANYA]
God bless you?
God. God?
Did she have to say it?
That word makes my blood boil.
I can't not think about
that bastard, "Being X."
[TANYA gasps]
Wait. That one. Is he?
[AINS]
Hm?
[TANYA]
We need to talk.
[MOMONGA]
What? Why me?
Got it? Come to the park
by the school after class.
[AINS] Why? I'm more than
willing to converse here.
It's private. There are
too many eyes and ears.
[ALBEDO growls]
Say what?
You want to talk
to my Lord Ains?
We all know what you
really want, bimbo!
[AINS]
Calm down, Albedo.
No. If this hussy
wants to mount you,
I swear that I will
slap her silly!
I'll pulverize her!
I'll rip out her hair!
"Slap her silly"
kinda sounds like the type
of thing Meelee would say.
[AINS]
Albedo, she's just a child!
I don't give a damn about
her gender, race, or age.
Have you seen yourself?
Your sex appeal penetrates
the whole spectrum.
[AINS]
Besides, we've just met.
[REM]
That doesn't matter at all!
Stay out of it, okay?
You can fall in love. Even with
someone you've just met.
[growls]
This little maid
knows what's up!
I mean, I've only known
Subaru for a short while.
[ALBEDO] I don't know what
a "Subaru" is, but okay.
It's this guy right here.
He's very important to me.
And you're saying that without
anyone forcing you to.
[ALBEDO] I think you and I
have some things in common.
[REM] Sorry for not
introducing myself...
[TANYA]
Why don't we go now instead?
[AINS]
Very well.
[REM]
Yes, nice to meet you.
[ALBEDO gasps]
No! Lord Ains is gone!
Move, you scum!
Class is starting now!
[ALBEDO grunts]
That floozy!