[EMILIA] Hm! Today is field day.
Let's do our best!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ALL chattering]
[YUNYUN]
I finally found you!
[ALL]
Huh?
[KAZUMA]
Whoa, it's Yunyun!
Megumin, our duel
goes down today!
Now who is this chick?
She a friend of yours?
I've never seen her before.
She's clearly delusional.
[YUNYUN] How could you
just forget who I am?
We've been rivals
our entire lives!
So. What do you want, huh?
Oh, yeah. Um... Ahem.
You think you're hot stuff,
well I've got news for you.
Class three will win
and you'll lose.
[KAZUMA]
So there's a class three? Huh!
Yunyun.
[YUNYUN]
Yeah?
You're gonna win? Tell me this.
What exactly happens at a
field day thing like this?
[YUNYUN gasps]
You and all of your friends
in the class work together to
compete in different kinds of--
So where are these
"friends in class" you speak of?
You don't seem to have any.
Oh yes, I do!
They're just, uh...
They decided to send me
out to pick up some, uh...
...yakisoba sandwiches
so we can eat together!
Oh, come on! Just admit
you're alone, would ya'?
Sorry, but I have
some questions.
[GROUP]
Huh?
It's just. Why'd they
send you? It seems weird.
Are they making you buy it?
[SUBARU]
Emilia-pro tip. Just stop.
[FELT]
What's going on, dude?
[ALL]
Huh?
[SUBARU] Hey, it's Felt!
And, ugh, Julius.
I hate to break it to ya,
but you're all gonna be eating
class one's dust today!
"Ugh?" That's how you greet me?
Come now. Let us try to conduct
ourselves like true knights.
I kinda already wanna
crotch punch this dude.
Kinda his superpower.
I humbly beg forgiveness,
Lord Ains.
When I initially agreed
to enter this contest,
I had no idea we'd be
facing as adversaries.
[AINS]
Pay it no mind.
Although your purpose
as the Pleiades,
my combat maids, is to shield
me from harm in our world.
We now find ourselves in another
world, and on opposite sides.
I won't ask you to hold back.
To be clear,
I will say this battle is
nothing more than a farce.
Regardless, we must
strive for excellence
no matter the situation.
[AUREOLE] I appreciate
your encouragement, My Lord.
[MOMONGA]
It's like the team fights we did
in the guild way back when.
[AUREOLE] You should
be aware of something.
[AINS]
Hm.
Our class... has a
particular member
that you definitely
need to watch out for.
[AINS]
That would be Reinhard, yes?
I've heard tell of his
incredible abilities.
[AUREOLE] Yes. I'm sure he's
no match for you, My Lord,
but I wanted you
to be forewarned.
[AINS] Thank you.
I'll be watching him.
[GRANTZ] Okay, now a word
from the students.
[KAZUMA] Wait, why is
she the one up there?
[EMILIA] Well, she kind
of insisted on it.
Attention, everyone!
Hear my words!
The dark cloud of oppression
has been lifted as if--
[DEMIURGE]
Is everybody okay?
[BEATRICE]
This is the easy part.
[AURA]
The awesome part!
[VISHA grunts]
[AUREOLE]
Excellent.
[REM]
Shalltear. what's the matter?
[GRANTZ]
Wait!
[ALBEDO]
I wait for no man.
[RAM]
Same!
[ALL gasp]
[COCYTUS]
Good game.
[REINHARD] That's my divine
"tug of war" protection.
[SUBARU] No way!
That can't be a real thing!
I'll use "steal" and boom,
all your balls are belong to us.
Why didn't it work on 'em?
[REINHARD] That's my divine,
"no stealing" protection.
[SUBARU]
Okay, that one might be real!
[AINS]
We're still trailing class one.
That guy! Could he
be more infuriating?
I warned you, didn't I?
Reinhard's on a
whole other level.
[ROSWAAL] Seems like you're
in a bit of jam here, class.
[SUBARU]
Oh, it's Mister Rozzie.
You can all unfurrow your brows,
the cavalry match is
your second chance.
Victory can still be yours.
[CZ] In the final game
of today's event...
...the winner will receive
one hundred million points.
See?
[ALL] Then why did we do
all that other stuff?
I have full faith that you will
claim victory once more,
My Lord.
[AINS]
Mm. We will not lose.
Good luck. You can do this!
Yes. I'll show them what an
imperial solider can do.
You've got this.
I believe in you.
Be careful. Don't push
yourself to hard.
Hey, don't worry, okay?
[MEGUMIN] You'll probably
just get in the way,
but please try not drag the
other guys down too much.
[DARKNESS] Kazuma, go out
there like a horse,
flailing in the mud.
Maybe you'll get stepped on,
like a piece of trash
on the ground.
Ooh, now I'm starting
to get jealous!
[AQUA]
Well, I'm tired.
So don't keep wasting our
time and wrap this up.
Would saying,
"good luck" kill ya?
Okay guys, let's go!
[JULIUS, REINHARD, CHRIS]
Right!
[KAZUMA]
Hang on. Where's class three?
Is it just Yunyun
all by herself?
Quite staring off
into space! Look alive!
Sorry!
Are you ready! On to victory!
[KAZUMA, AINS, SUBARU]
Yeah!
[KAZUMA, SUBARU pant]
You really surprised me, dude.
I appreciate that!
Now if you'd surprise
me by giving us a win,
I'd appreciate that even more.
Sorry, Subaru.
You have to realize that
is simply not an option.
You can't escape the
stink of failure.
You should know that.
[YUNYUN pants]
[MEGUMIN]
Yunyun?
[YUNYUN]
Yeah?
How come you're not with all
your "friends" in class three?
Earlier you swore that
you had a bunch of them.
Of course I do!
There's no one else in your
class even participating today.
I'm starting to believe
there is no class three,
and you just made up the
whole thing for some reason.
[COCYTUS]
Shut up.
Let's face it, there's no way
we'll win a straight-up fight,
but maybe we can split them up
and deal with them one-on-one.
Hey, Ains.
[AINS]
Hm.
[SUBARU]
Can you handle Reinhard?
[AINS] That's quite the
responsibility. I won't fail!
Right, sounds like a plan.
[CZ] Now, an announcement
that's sure to shock you.
Joining us for this last event,
will be a team made up by
our teachers. Don't forget,
this round is worth
one-hundred million points.
So whoever wins this,
will be the ultimate
victors of field day.
[SUBARU]
Mister Rozzie?!
Hi.
[KAZUMA]
Vanir?!
What's wrong?
Has this sudden change
filled your heart with
overwhelming dread?
[TANYA]
Mr. Rerugen?
Why me? This is hell.
[MOMONGA] Oh man, I was
afraid he'd show up here.
[AINS]
Pandora's Actor!
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Father!
[KAZUMA, TANYA, SUBARU]
Father?
[AINS]
No!
You understand now, kids?
There is only one road to
victory, and that is through us!
[AINS]
But you're our teacher.
You can't just work with us
to help us get back home?
[ROSWAAL] Think of this
as a lesson, a final exam!
Give us all you've got
and don't dare hold back!
Not a fan of this.
To have one's duel
interrupted in such a way.
This knight takes great umbrage.
Well. I think we're all
on the same page here.
Yeah. Hey, Reinhard!
I know where you're going.
Subaru. I suggest an alliance
between our classes.
Let's combine our strengths.
[ALL gasp]
[FELT]
Don't get the wrong idea.
First we'll team up
to beat the teachers,
then we'll be free to duke
it out between ourselves!
[SUBARU]
Whoa.
[CHRIS] Okay, Kazuma.
You with me?
I'm counting on you!
Oh, well uh, yeah! I'm in!
Guys, let's do this!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[AQUA grunts]
What's the matter?
Just kinda starting to feel
like my position's in jeopardy.
[AURA, MARE chuckle]
[ROSWAAL] Hmm, we seem to be
in quite a pickle, boys.
These teams are both chock
full of big, brazen souls.
I suppose we'll just have
to kick it up a notch,
and show these children that
we're not just playing around.
Come forth,
my faithful servants!
[KAZUMA] Watch out, those things
will explode on you!
[AINS] I don't care! We'll go
straight for our target!
Greater teleportation!
\Got you now!
[PANDORA'S ACTOR gasps]
Lord Ains!
Must we, as father and son,
come to blows like this?
[ALBEDO]
You are not his son!
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Transform!
[ERICH gasps]
[AINS]
Greater Teleportation!
[ALL gasp]
And now, we've got you!
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
Julius!
Unleash Al Clauselia!
[ERICH grunts]
That light is so bright!
[CHRIS]
Bind!
[gasps]
I got one, you guys!
[KAZUMA]
Thanks, Chris!
[ROSWAAL]
Oh no!
[CHRIS gasps]
Well done class! A real
show of teamwork at work!
I had no doubt that our brave
students would charge headlong
at their enemy! So full of fire!
So sure of their victory!
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] But! If you
think this fight is over,
I admonish you rapscallions
to think again!
[TEACHERS]
Formation Quartet! Go!
[TANYA] Is that even allowed?
And FYI, that is a trio!
Alright. Today's ultimate
battle starts now!
[VANIR laughs]
[ERICH] Hey, will you please
stop that? Thank you! Quit it!
I'll admit guys,
that's too much.
Tell me something.
Yeah?
Do you feel kinda sorry for
Mister Rerugen, or no?
I wouldn't wanna be him.
[KURT]
Interesting.
Seems the teachers are
at a slight disadvantage.
It does. Shall we
send it in, then?
Send it in? Let's see how
the students handle this.
Won't be easy.
[HANS]
Pushing the button.
[ALL gasp, yelp]
Careful, Lord Ains!
Hey! Wait!
What the hell is that?
No way!
[DARKNESS, MEGUMIN]
The mobile fortress.
Not the (bleep) Destroyer!
[ROSWAAL] And now. Time for the
main event, boys and girls!