[ROSWAAL] If we're to have a
harmonious school life together,
we'll first need to
establish the rules, 'kay?
You'll all be sharing this
classroom as fellow students,
so it's important that
everybody plays nice.
So, Roz, hey.
I'm your teacher.
So, uh, Mister Roz.
Why the hell are we here?
To experience school life.
Oh, yeah. Good ol' school life!
Where boys become men!
And girls blossom
into full-grown women!
So then why is this classroom
packed with these freaks
that probably shouldn't even be
allowed anywhere near a school?
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
It would appear the first
lesson you need to learn
is that you should never
judge a book by its cover.
You better hope that
they don't judge you
by the way you look.
[SUBARU]
Don't start with me.
--[AINS clears throat]
--You think we all belong here?
[AINS] So if I
understand the situation,
what you're trying to tell us
is we've been assembled here
to make it through
this trial together,
as part of some kind
of "school life"--
that's our objective?
You've just hit a
bull's-eye. Spot on!
[AINS]
What if I refuse?
Refusal is simply not an option.
Because violating the rules...
...means you will be
punished accordingly.
[KAZUMA]
Hmm...
Is something the matter?
Eh, that guy.
[DARKNESS]
Hm?
[MEGUMIN] Oh, he's wearing the
same stupid looking outfit
you used to wear.
I thought I looked pretty cool.
[REM]
Excuse me, Subaru.
Yeah. What's up?
That boy over there,
he seems to be extremely
interested in you.
[SUBARU]
Hm?
[KAZUMA]
Uh.
Tell me. What did
you do this time?
So, we're doing the ol'
"blame Subaru" bit, are we?
I know for a fact
I didn't do anything.
Now, listen up, everybody, okay?
It's time to tell your
classmates just who you are.
Subaru, let's begin
with you, eh?
[SUBARU]
No prob.
[SUBARU breathes deeply]
My name's Subaru Natsuki.
If I'm not the most clueless,
I'm the brokest one here!
Nice to meet you guys!
It's comforting to see
that no matter
what world we happen to be in,
nobody thinks you're funny.
Just couldn't resist
the dig, could ya?!
[ROSWAAL] Will the next
person speak up, please?
Yes!
Hi. My name is Emilia.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
And my name's Puck,
spirit extraordinaire.
Lia-- Um, that's just
what I call her.
Anyway, mess with Lia,
you're dealing with me!
Now don't be so over protective.
[AINS]
Hmm...
[MOMONGA]
A spirit and an elf--
No. More like a half-elf.
Assuming their races are similar
to what's in Yggdrasil.
I'm Ram.
And this is my
little sister Rem.
Hello. Nice to meet you all.
My name is Beatrice.
Can't say it's nice to meet
any of you, I suppose.
And I suppose, you'll
never make any friends
with that crappy attitude.
If you think I care, you're
a bigger idiot than I thought.
You really get under...
Is it possible to
be that unpleasant?
[VISHA chuckles nervously]
Very well then.
I believe it's my turn.
[VISHA]
Huh?
Attention!
Uh... Imperial 203rd Aerial
Mage Battalion Commander,
Major Tanya von Degurechaff.
I'm First Lieutenant,
Viktoriya Ivanova Serebryakov.
Reporting!
Matheus Johann Weiss! Reporting!
Wilibald Koenig. Reporting.
Rhiner Neumann! Reporting.
Warren Grantz! Reporting.
Uhh... are they from
some kinda war world?
[MOMONGA] Uhh... are they
from some kinda war world?
[SUBARU] Whoa, that girl
reminds me of you, Beako!
Gotta be nice to her.
Stop treating me like a toddler!
I'm older than
you are, remember?
And I don't have to be nice to
anybody if I don't feel like it!
[SUBARU]
Whatever.
[AQUA]
Ooh! Me! It's my turn, right?
[clears throat]
I stand before you as the
omnipotent goddess of wa--
Just call her Aqua, okay?
[AQUA]
Huh?
I'm Kazuma. She's Meg.
Ignore that one.
What the hell's wrong with you?!
I was just starting
my awesome introduction
and you had to go
and step all over it!
How dare you!
As the greatest of
the crimson demons,
this is my time to shine!
He said to "ignore that one."
"That one..."
Like some useless object!
Oh, so you're ignoring
all of us, now?!
Oh, my.
[AQUA] I guess you're
just a huge jerk...
Well, the only
one left is you.
[AQUA] Do I really not get
to finish my introduction?!
Ahh! This sucks!
[AINS sighs]
[AINS] Hopefully, the
achievement is worth
the nuisance of this
"school life" level.
I'll go first.
[AINS] Behold. I am Lord of
the Great Tomb of Nazarick:
The Mighty Ains Ooal Gown!
[ALBEDO groans]
[AINS]
Uh...
[ROSWAAL]
Oh my, what's wrong, young lady?
Are we feeling a
little "fainty" today?
You've got the wrong idea!
Did you not see
Lord Ains just now?!
Did his greatness not awaken
something deep
within your loins?
Oh my goodness. Well...
T.M.I.
So, let's get back to your
introduction later, shall we?
--Okay, class.
--Not so fast!
[ROSWAAL]
Hmm?!
My lord spoke and so shall I!
You will know every
one of our names.
Everyone. Identify
yourselves, now!
[GROUP]
Right!
I am the guardian of the first,
second, and third floors.
Shalltear Bloodfallen.
[COCYTUS] Guardian of
the fifth floor. Cocytus.
Guardian of the sixth floor.
Aura Bella Fiora.
Sixth floor. Mare Bello Fiore!
Seventh floor guardian.
Demiurge.
And I hold the
position of overseer
of the Nazarick Floor Guardians.
I'm Albedo.
[SUBARU]
Uhh...
[TANYA grumbles]
How delightful.
It seems we have
quite the variety
of colorful students here,
don't we, class?
[MOMONGA] Jeez, the undead
aren't supposed to get tired,
but damn.
[AINS]
I'm exhausted.
[MOMONGA]
So, here I am in another world.
I have the same body
I did in the last one.
Still, something
feels different.
[grunts]
[AINS]
What do you want?
Listen!
Undead and your creepy cronies,
I don't know what world this is
or what we're even doing here,
but no matter what
dump world this is,
it's my sacred duty as a god
to make sure your kind isn't
free to roam however you please!
[AINS]
A god, is that so?
Oh, yeah! You're welcome.
For I, goddess of
the order of Axis,
and the goddess
of water, Aqua...
...shall personally send all
of you on to your next lives!
[AQUA yelps]
[AINS gasps]
The Hell?
Starting a fight on
the first day of school
is not "being best"!
Come on! Can't you see
it's an undead?
And it's with
a demon, a vampire,
and whatever the
hell that thing is!
They're totes evil!
So what else is a goddess
supposed to do, huh?!
--Turn undead!
--No, Aqua, don't do it!
[AINS] I'm not worried.
That's a low-level spell.
[screaming]
[MOMONGA] How the hell
can it pack so much punch?
[groans]
Oh, no! That spell
didn't work on him?!
[AQUA yelps]
Kazuma! You didn't
have to hit me, ya know!
[KAZUMA]
Well, I think I did.
Kazuma, can't you tell that
I'm obviously not done here?
We can't just leave now!
What if this is another
quest and taking them out
--Hey. Sorry.
--is what we're supposed to do?
[AINS]
It's... fine.
[AQUA]
I'll get you, undead!
Mark my words,
I'll banish you from this world
if it's the last thing I do!
Ugh! This isn't over,
you hear me?!
[AINS]
A goddess who can make
even a hundredth-level
like me feel pain,
walking around with a human
who can just punch her
like it's nothing...
Whatever world this is,
it has some serious
power balance issues!
[bell rings]
[ROSWAAL]
Pay attention, everyone.
Miss Aqua was violent towards
one of her new
friends yesterday.
That means she's in big trouble.
Why am I being punished?
It was all their fault.
Yo. What's shakin',
water goddess?
You told on me, didn't you?
No wonder you were
a lonely dweeb
that didn't have any
friends in real life!
Nobody likes a tattle-tale.
Get away from me, you freak!
[SUBARU snores]
[AQUA]
Everybody, leave me alone!
[KURT]
So, tell us.
How are the new students doing?
They're fascinating,
I must say.
Ah. Unfortunately, they've
yet to really open up.
I see. Then why don't
we try "that"?
Ah, yes. "That."