[KAZUMA grunts]
[AQUA sobs]
Hold it! We should check out the
stuff we got from that quest!
Ugh, we can do that later!
Do you want me walking
around like this?
I'm covered in stinky
giant-toad slime!
You practically
live in toad slime.
Probably shouldn't
say that out loud.
Damn right you shouldn't!
Don't forget I'm a goddess,
I should look immaculate
and smell divine. Not reek worse
than some shut-in NEET like you!
Hey! I am not some shut in NEET!
You don't wanna hear it,
but if you hadn't run ahead,
you wouldn't be gross,
so don't get mad at me
'cause you were out there acting
like the goddess of stupidity.
[AQUA gasps]
What did you call me?
Does nobody even care
that Kazuma's...
Uh. What's this?
[ALBEDO] So our plan for now
is to manipulate the Kingdom
of Re-Estize from the shadows.
While simultaneously
forming an alliance with
the Baharuth empire.
Once we balance
these two operations,
we'll achieve our ultimate goal.
Making the Sorcerer Kingdom
of Ains Ooal Gown
a global superpower.
Seated in the Great
Tomb of Nazarick.
[AINS] I admire
your ambition, Albedo.
[DEMIURGE]
Lord Ains.
[AINS]
What is it, Demiurge?
Well, my lord. I have
a matter of interest.
[AINS] Then by all means,
enlighten us.
It seems...
...there've been rumors of a
strange phenomenon occurring
within the very
walls of Nazarick.
[AINS]
A "strange phenomenon" you say?
[DEMIURGE] Yes. I've yet to
witness this anomaly myself,
but as I've heard it told,
a small box suddenly
appeared out of nowhere.
But as its sole adornment
is a simple button,
I have deduced that it's
some type of device.
[AINS]
Could it be a weapon
planted by one of
our adversaries?
[DEMIURGE] At the risk of
sounding overconfident.
I cannot envision
any of our rivals
entering Nazarick undetected.
[AINS]
Understood.
But there are many things
outside your imagination.
We must consider
any possibilities
for its origin and use.
[AINS]
Alert all of Nazarick.
If any of these "mystery"
buttons are found.
Use caution in handling them.
If someone finds one,
use the message spell
to share its location.
Then follow our
"trap-disarming" protocol.
[ALL]
Lord!
[AINS] Of course. I'd imagine
you would take those same steps
without me needing to tell you.
Your words honor us, my lord.
[MOMONGA] Is it really a trap?
I mean, it seems so obvious.
Like something a kid
would come up with.
You'd have to be pretty stupid
to just press a random button
if you didn't know what it did.
That's a total noob move.
C'mon, just let me
push the thing!
I'll be super delicate
and careful...!
[KAZUMA] We need to find out
what the hell it is, first!
Vanir definitely needs to
check this thing out, okay?
I must say,
Kazuma's correct on this.
[KAZUMA]
Thanks, Megumin!
I knew you crimson demons
were supposed to be smart.
Glad you've got--
Although, if you're wondering
if we should push the button,
which may change our destiny...
Yes! Absolutely!
[KAZUMA]
Are you crazy?!
[DARKNESS, MEGUMIN]
Huh?
Um... this... seems bad.
Aw damnit, you shoulda
listened to me!
[gasps] What kind of
humiliation awaits me?
Will I be tied up and sold away?
To a dank, dark dungeon
and used as some handsy
savage's plaything?
[KAZUMA]
Stop being so giddy, Darkness!
[MEGUMIN chuckles]
And you'd better not be
smirking right now, got me?
[AQUA shouts]
What's happening?
The world's getting
all weird and squiggly!
Everything's melting!
[KAZUMA]
Shut up, you idiot!
[AINS]
Hm.
Is something wrong, my lord?
[AINS] No, it's nothing
I'm sure. Carry on.
[ALBEDO] Hm. Now, we need
to devise the most effective
strategy for forging
this alliance...
[MOMONGA]
Something definitely feels off.
[ALBEDO] In the last war they
shared in our glorious victory,
but many of their knights have
begun to desert their ranks
because they fear Lord Ains.
That unease is threatening the
emperor's hold on power...
[AINS yells]
[schoolbell rings]
[AINS]
So. Where are we?
Not sure.
But I do have a feeling that
we're not in Nazarick anymore.
[MOMONGA]
Oh man.
Don't tell me I'm stuck
in some other other world!
[AQUA]
Excuse me!
[AINS]
Hm?
I really hate to
bother you folks,
but do you know where we are?
[AINS]
Hm?!
[AQUA]
Yikes.
Did I get sent back?
Seems like it...
[AQUA] Hey! Kazuma, get your
head outta the clouds!
Look over there!
That's definitely an undead!
A big one!
They're all so
terrible and ugly.
Ah! It's only a matter of
time before they get their
disgusting paws all over us.
[MEGUMIN chuckles]
Never fear,
for I possess the most powerful
attack ever known, my expl--
[KAZUMA]
Will you hang on a second?
I can't think straight with
all your jibber jabbering!
[MEGUMIN] Stop thinking
and start doing.
Or get out of my way!
[DARKNESS] No! Let me go,
I can offer my body--
[AQUA]
If they're undead,
surely the power of a goddess's
holy punch will smite them.
[KAZUMA yells] Would you just
shut the hell up already?!
Listen up students!
Class begins immediately!
[TANYA] What's going on?
Where the hell am I?
Think back.
I was born into a world of
science and reason, after all.
A society that understood
fortune favored the bold
and the ambitious. I was a
successful businessman.
I earned my place at the
top of the food chain.
But a vindictive entity
known as "Being X"
forced me to be reborn
as an absolute weakling.
A little girl thrust
into a world that didn't
trust in science.
Instead, life was
dictated by magic
and the constant
falling of bombs!
And then, I was forced
to test out a new
computation jewel made by
that crazy old scientist.
[TANYA screams]
[SCHUGEL] What are you doing?
Do something or it will explode!
Press the button for the
jewel expansion, you fool!
But this piece of junk
doesn't look at all
like it did in the
manual you gave me.
This is an upgraded version
of the Elenium Type-97!
That masterpiece you're
wearing is the future!
[TANYA]
Listen crackpot!
How am I supposed to know
which button is which
if they're almost right
next to each other?
You're design sucks!
What are you talking about,
you little brat?
There's only one
button on the unit!
[TANYA]
Huh?
Your brain is more damaged than
I thought! I'm holding two!
My god, have you
actually gone mad?
Oh, because you're one to talk!
Push the damn button!
That's an order!
An. O. R. D. E, R!
Geez.
There's nothing worse than
working for the government.
One word from the higher-ups
and you're completely
stripped of your human rights.
Fine, then. I know what to do.
If I don't know
which one's which,
I'll have to push both of them!
[bell rings]
[TANYA]
And just like that, here I am.
[TANYA] At first glance it
looks like my old world, but...
[VISHA yelps]
[AQUA] I don't understand
why you just followed...
[TANYA] These guys look like
they fell out of an RPG.
They've got really crappy
equipment for adventurers.
[GRANTZ, WILIBALD gasp]
[TANYA] These characters
aren't even human.
Should I assume this
another trick by that
self-proclaimed god, Being X?
Or is some other
power at work here?
[EMILIA] I don't believe we
should be running in the halls
--[TANYA] Huh?
--in such a manner.
[RAM]
Well, if you don't like it,
you should blame stupid Barusu!
[BEATRICE] You should, but I
don't suppose he'll apologize.
[SUBARU] It's not my
fault you lazy bums
couldn't wake up on time!
[REM]
Subaru, are you okay?
[SUBARU]
Yeah.
I mean, I had to literally
go through hell to get here.
And being in school was
awkward and weird for me,
but let's just try to ignore
everything else for now.
And maybe we can enjoy
being somewhere,
where everything's
not out to kill us.
[SUBARU chuckles]
And this is what we run into?
[MOMONGA]
Oh geez, there's more of 'em.
Lord Ains. I think we
should slaughter them
[AINS] Not yet. First, we need
to gather some intel.
Understood my lord.
I think... this is
gonna really suck.
[AQUA]
Don't worry!
Remember you have a goddess
on your side, after all.
I'll handle it.
[KAZUMA] Yeah, well that's
not gonna make it any better!
If this is some new trial
Being X came up with,
then I accept it.
Do you hear me?
Whatever you're planning, I'll
wreck it and have my revenge!
Um, Major? Are you okay?
Well, I'm worried.
I can't say I care for
the look of these people.
That's it. There's too
little information.
Go on and sacrifice yourself.
[SUBARU] How else do we
gauge their kill power?
There's no need.
It would be my pleasure
to protect the both of you.
Hey, Subaru.
[SUBARU]
Hm?
I think. This might
be a good opportunity
to make new friends.
You never fail to see the
bright side of any situation,
just like an angel!
[KURT exhales]
So now that they have
all been assembled,
their school life
can finally begin.