[ROSWAAL]
Field day is coming, everybody!
[SUBARU] Mr. Ros-chi, we
literally just had a field trip
for that test of courage,
and now it's time for field day?
Like, I don't understand
the schedule.
[ROSWAAL]
Huh? You don't get it, do you?
This entire world is bizarre,
and you pick the schedule
to be confused about?
Sure, it's weird, but still--
Now, now.
Let's not get bogged down
with all the minutiae--
just work together and win!
And what exactly
is the incentive here?
[ROSWAAL]
Let me see...
As I recall, the prize is
returning to your home world.
--[gasping]
--[ROSWAAL] But don't quote me!
How can we work together
if we're in competition?
I mean, we're the only
ones here, as far as I know.
It's not like
there's another cla--
--[ROSWAAL] But, there is...
--Huh?
There's another classroom
--right next door, you see!
--[gasps]
[SUBARU gasps]
Huh?!
[SUBARU]
Wh-- Is that Reinhard?
[VANIR laughs] You there,
with the nasty stink face!
Huh?
While I do enjoy watching
your eyes bulge out
of your head in astonishment,
I would greatly appreciate it
if you wouldn't
disrupt my instruction.
Who the hell is that freak show?
Right, back to class.
We've got much more to learn
before the day is done!
[SUBARU] Call me crazy, but I
swear this wasn't here before.
[AINS]
Do you remember it?
No. I know it didn't
exist before today.
[ROSWAAL] There's no
choice but to accept it.
After all, that's
how this world works.
[school bell chimes]
[SUBARU]
So, yeah, we're calling them
"Class 1" now, apparently.
I recognized some of
them from my last world.
[AINS] Yes, my combat maids,
the Pleiades, were in there.
"Combat maids," eh?
Don't you think that's
a little much, dude?
[AINS] This from the
guy with demon maids
hanging off him most the time.
At least we know
something about
our field day enemy.
After all, the class appears
to consist of a handful
of familiar people from
our respective worlds.
Therefore, the situation here
is not totally fixed--
rather, it seems to be
--somewhat in a state of flux.
--[AINS] Yes.
All right. We must
win the field day.
The mystery of Class 1
is irrelevant.
Winning is all that matters.
[AINS] Correct. That is, if what
Mister Roswaal said is true,
and we do get to return
to our home worlds
if we win the field day.
[SUBARU]
So, this means...
...if we want to
get out of here...
...we have to beat Class 1.
Question, Ains.
How does their
strength match up?
[AINS]
I will say this.
The Pleiades will be
easy to defeat.
I am not sure about
the others, though.
Subaru, what do you know?
[SUBARU]
Well, um, I have some bad news
about that guy you just saw.
Reinhard is his name.
The goofy one with the red hair?
Sadly, he's probably the
strongest person in my world.
--[AINS] Hmm...
--[TANYA groans]
[SUBARU] Where I come from,
there's this kind of overpowered
ability called
"divine protection."
Maybe you've heard of it.
But that dude's got
the skill in spades.
[AINS]
Divine protection?
Seems different from
the skills and martial arts
that exist in my world.
What specific types of divine
protection does he have?
Oh, man, where do I start?
He automatically
dodges any attack
he's never seen before,
and he automatically dodges
pretty much all
other attacks, too.
There's also a rumor
that, if he dies,
he can just come back to life.
Auto-dodge for long-range
attacks, and 100% accuracy
for all ranged attacks.
Total immunity to shamanic
spells, buffs, and debuffs.
--And elemental attacks...
--[AINS] Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
If he auto-dodges first attacks,
and attacks he's never seen--
so, all attacks, really--
and he can come back to life,
how exactly are you
supposed to beat him?
Hell if I know.
And also, he's got
a "Riding" divine protection?
Does that mean there's
no possible way for us
to win the final round?
[GROUP]
Hmm...
--[AQUA yelps]
--[GROUP] Hmm?
Wait, Chris? What in
the world are you doing here?
How the heck am I
supposed to know?
[gasps]
Darkness!
Whoa, Chris! What's going on?
I'm not sure!
I was minding my own business,
when all of a sudden--
Bam, I got summoned
to this world!
Is that what happened to you?
Well, uh, yeah, we just
kinda woke up here.
Oh, right, so...
I have some bad news.
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
In this world, if you die,
you can't be revived
for some reason.
So be careful.
Seriously?
[CHRIS]
Seriously.
That's the worst news
I've heard in a while, Chris!
Why isn't Eris doing something
about the situation, huh?
Uh, actually...
Eris can't really do anything
about it, unfortunately. So...
Huh...? Hold on, why are you so
eager to come to her defense?
--[CHRIS growls]
--Funny thing about Eris...
I suddenly feel very
uncomfortable and don't really
--want to talk about her, 'kay?
--Come on, Aqua!
You know I am a member
of the Eris Faith,
so shut up before you
insult my goddess!
Darkness, please.
You know there are no good
goddesses with fake boobs!
Ah-choo!
Oh, are you feeling all right?
Ooh, Somebody out there
must be gossiping about the fact
that Shalltear's boobs are fake.
I don't speak dumb,
what'd you say?
[wails]
Uh, anyway, we may be rivals,
but thought you should know.
It's the truth.
When you die, you can't
be brought back to life.
So, like, all I'm saying is,
be careful, okay?
Something wrong?
[SUBARU]
Nothing.
[SUBARU] Does this mean that
my "Return by Death" spell
won't work?
In my old world, I just went
back to the last save point.
But if that's not
the case in this world,
bad news for me.
If I die, it's over.
Though, to be fair,
I hated dying in the old world.
[TANYA]
Hmm?
[SUBARU] Yikes, I said one
of the quiet parts out loud.
I should be more careful
what I say here.
Or, I could do a test.
[SUBARU] Humor me for
a second and cover your ears.
Huh?
When I die, I--
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
Bad idea.
At least I'm not dead!
[SUBARU] But I still had
to suffer the penalty.
Huh?
[AURA] I'm really sorry
about this, Lord Ains!
[AINS] What exactly are
those two doing here?
I sincerely apologize
for the intrusion, sir.
They got all excited
out of nowhere
and just started
running this way.
[AINS]
Yes, but, why?
I, uh, have a
feeling that might've
been my fault, actually.
[TANYA]
Uh?
I've got this ability
that has the side effect
of attracting mabeasts.
But I had no idea it could
work on the undead, too.
That's cool.
[AINS]
Is it some kind of curse?
[SUBARU]
Yeah, it is.
It appears we both have problems
with annoying curses, huh?
[SUBARU]
Both of us?
I'd love to hear more about
that, but first things first--
Can you please get this
Bad Hamster to stop
gnawing on my noggin?
[AINS]
So, as you can see,
if we all really want to go
back to our worlds, we must do
everything we possibly can
to win the field day.
[KAZUMA]
I vote no.
I'm actually happier
here than my home world.
So, I have no incentive to win.
That's so typical.
Of course you would say that.
We want to go home.
Yeah, jeez, Kazuma!
Have you forgotten that you
still need to go back home
and defeat the Demon King?
There's no way I can
defeat the Demon King,
so why can't I just stay
here where it's safe,
--doing what I want?!
--[COCYTUS] Impossible.
Uh?
[COCYTUS] You're in the
presence of Lord Ains.
Defeat will not be permitted.
[KAZUMA]
I mean, good point, I guess?
[TANYA]
Yeah, I agree.
No one ever charges
into battle with
the intention of losing the war.
If we're going to participate
in this field day,
we should give it
everything we've got.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, Subaru.
Let's try to win this thing!
Then I'll try
my hardest, too,
if only for my brother's sake.
[PUCK laughs]
Do your best so
I don't have to, Barusu.
One of us is a lazy,
good-for-nothing bum.
But the rest of us will fight!
[EMILIA gasps]
[KAZUMA]
Ugh, fine. If I have to.
I'll work my hardest to
make sure my classmates win
the field day--
Is something you'll
never hear from my mouth!
Please, not a chance in hell!
I'm lazy!
That's a core value
I will never compromise!
Kazuma! You're a bigger
scumbag than I thought!
Yeah, and I take
great pride in that.
[TANYA]
Shut your mouth.
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
Although, I respect
your consistent values.
If you're unwilling to put forth
any effort of your own accord,
then we'll help you.
A little hard work can fix that.
The 203rd Aerial Mage Battalion
will instruct you.
Our special training course
will surely transform you into
--the ultimate super soldier!
--Wait, what? What's that mean?
Captain Wiess!
Yes, at your service!
Hold on, what are
the shovels for?
[screams
Take this! And this,
and this! And this!
[KAZUMA yelping]
That's right, keep running!
You gonna cry?
I hope so, 'cause that
way we can all laugh
at the diaper baby!
So, am I doing this right?
Yeah, great job. Thanks a lot.
We've got a ways to go, though.
Looks like you've still
got a lot of energy left!
Excellent! I thought you
were lazy, what happened?
He might be
starting to slow down.
Maybe it's time to take
things to a new level?
'Kay, I'll hit him
with something special.
Take that!
[KAZUMA screamin]
I can't contain myself.
I have to help!
--Explosion!
--[KAZUMA] Don't do it, Megumin!
[KAZUMA screams]
[ALL groaning]
Hey, sis, doesn't
that look like fun?
Heck yeah, for sure!
Well, then, it's official--
I'm terrified of her.
[AINS] That's a testament
to your intelligence.
I agree.
I mean, this is quite a ruckus.
Just so you know,
nobody says "ruckus" anymore.
[KAZUMA] Will you guys cut
the crap and make her stop?!