[ROSWAAL]
Okay, students.
Let's get this talent show
underway now, shall we?
Inside this box are papers
with everyone's names.
I'll draw them one by one,
and when your name is called,
come up and show us
what makes you special!
Let's see...!
Mister Rerugen!
Huh?
But, Mister Roswaal.
I'm no student, why do
I have to participate?
[COCYTUS]
Remember.
You said yourself that Mister
Roswaal said "that it'd be fun?"
So that settles it, then!
[COCYTUS exhales]
We are all trying to be
friendly here, now aren't we?
So why don't you be
little Mister Icebreaker
and help kick off the show!
[groans]
[ERICH] I am Erich von Rerugen.
TA of class two A.
And for my talent today,
I shall sing for you
the song of my people!
[TANYA gasps]
[ERICH singing in
foreign language]
You see this Kazuma?
I'm Kazuma and I'm seeing this.
He's humiliating
himself up there.
[KAZUMA]
Sure is.
[DARKNESS] The humans
and non-humans alike.
Everyone is looking
at him with disgust.
[KAZUMA]
Poor guy.
[DARKNESS]
There's no question!
At this very moment,
he is the most disgraced,
most embarrassed
creature on the planet!
[KAZUMA]
Uh. This sounds familiar.
[ERICH] Can I stop?
I'm dying up here!
[sighs] If only everybody
would look at me that way.
With those eyes that say,
"How can you even stand
to live with yourself?"
[RAM grunts]
[singing continues]
[ERICH]
Kill me...
[ROSWAAL]
Next, who will it be?
Oh my. Subaru, you're up.
[SUBARU]
Oh yeah! Awesome!
This rules.
'Cause I don't know how I could
do any worse than that dude.
That was bad.
But I can't honestly imagine
you can do anything better.
Predictably taking yet
another dig at me. It's cool.
You'll change your tune after
you witness my amazing talent.
Oh, that was breathtaking!
I haven't even done it yet.
Okay! I'm holding in my hand...
...plain ol string.
Look closely and you'll see
there are no cuts and no knots.
Ah-ha, but watch this and...
a little more of this.
And...
Tokyo Tower!
Lame.
No! I knew it was
gonna be boring!
No way. I loved it, Subaru!
I have no idea what
you made, but still...
[ROSWAAL]
Who do we have up now?
Rem. I hope you're ready!
[REM]
Sure!
Huh?
[REM shouts]
[ERICH yells]
[COCYTUS]
Impressive.
She has a tremendous amount
of skill with that weapon.
And remarkable strength.
But of course. Rem's an expert.
[REM] Thank you, but I'm still
not as good as you, sister.
[COCYTUS] Interesting.
Could the pink-haired one
possess even stronger
abilities in combat?
So cold!
[TANYA growls]
Everybody's really amazing, huh?
[TANYA]
I get it.
Seems the point of this exercise
is to demonstrate our
strength to the other groups.
I've been able to communicate
with the leader of the most
intimidating one, but I
can't let my guard down.
From the look of things,
We're not the strongest by far.
So it would be foolish
to show them our limits.
It would only lead to
them challenging us.
Sir!
[TANYA] Good. At least he
won't do anything stupid.
I'm Matheus Johann Weiss.
Two hundred third
aerial mage battalion!
I have no particular talent
to perform, so I'll just...
...show you something
I'm very proud of!
Interference spell!
[WEISS yells]
[VISHA gasps]
[TANYA grunts] I'm sorry
you all had to see that.
[MOMONGA]
Glad we talked,
but I definitely don't want
to get on her bad side.
Will Miss Darkness
take the stage, please?
Uh, well the thing is,
I can't really do it alone.
So, can somebody from
the class give me a hand?
[GRANTZ]
Me! I'd be happy to help!
[TANYA] Why is he so
eager to volunteer?
[VISHA]
No idea.
[DARKNESS] Uh... Actually,
my talent is my pain threshold.
Yeah. I can endure
most anything.
So, this man.
This strong man, will punish
me with the whip
and together we will
demonstrate my resilience
to pain and humiliation.
[GRANTZ gasps]
Now, come on, soldier,
show no mercy.
Strike me with that whip,
'cause I know you love to!
Wha-- I've never hit you!
A soldier or scumbag?
[COCYTUS] I find him to be a
disgrace to the warrior ethic.
He's a scumbag, sister
Wait, No! Hear me out--
[SUBARU] Now listen up, pal!
Dunno what your deal is,
But you gotta start
respecting women, okay?
Hey man, that's not me! Right?
[KOENIG, NUEMANN grunt]
Please don't look away!
Sorry Lieutenant Grantz.
[GRANTZ]
Huh?
But you're a scumbag.
[GRANTZ groans]
Come on, now.
Do your worst on me.
Wait. I have an idea.
Oh yeah! You should have
your friend join in
and the two of you
can swap turns!
I can take it, I promise
I've handled much more,
and I deserve all the punishment
you can dish out on me!
Leave me outta this,
ya crazy lady!
[RAM]
He never fails to disgust me.
[COCYTUS] They're both unworthy
of being called warriors.
[REM]
Oh, Subaru's just complicated.
[SUBARU]
Leave me outta this!
[KAZUMA]
I'm sorry she's like this.
We're not all perverts.
I promise!
[DARKNESS, KAZUMA]
IseQuar!
Next is Aqua!
[groans]
What's your problem huh?
Just do, "Nature's Beauty".
That's like, your go-to!
Kazuma, we've talked
about this.
I'm not some kind of dog that
does tricks on command.
[ROSWAAL]
Hm. Well, that's a problem!
Huh? Hey, would it be okay
if I did some magic?
[ROSWAAL] Yes. The point is
to show us something special
that you can do,
so it's your call!
Oh heck yeah!
This is really special!
A spell fit for a
goddess like me!
I call it "Sacred Turn Undead!"
[KAZUMA] Don't zap
our classmates, dummy!
[AQUA yelps]
It's not fair!
Why do I have to be stuck in
here with a demon and the rest
of these wretched creatures?
I am Goddess, ya know?
Ah, very well done, indeed.
Seems Aqua's talent is a
husband-and-wife comedy routine!
--[AQUA] Hang on!
--[KAZUMA] Wait a second!
[AQUA, KAZUMA]
IseQuar!
[ROSWAAL] Class, our time
is running short!
I wish we could
fit everybody in,
but we can only
squeeze two more!
So who wants to go,
hands up high!
[KAZUMA] Darkness completely
humiliated us.
[DARKNESS swoons]
[KAZUMA]
Aqua made us look like idiots.
[AQUA]
Huh?
[KAZUMA] So please don't
make this worse, Megumin.
[MEGUMIN]
Hmph. Oh, ye of little faith.
This is perfect.
The path to redemption
is laid out before us!
[KAZUMA] The problem is,
you don't have a hidden talent.
[MEGUMIN]
I do.
[KAZUMA]
Do not.
I do, too!
[KAZUMA]
Yeah? Well, what is it?
[MEGUMIN] Explosion magic.
The most powerful, most feared,
most deadly spell
in all the land!
[MEGUMIN, KAZUMA]
IseQuar!
[ROSWAAL] Now, since we don't
do boom-boom in the classroom,
I have a target here
for your fiery pleasure.
I'm not so sure about
blowing up a bronze statue,
but I guess it
will have to do.
Sir, is this a good idea?
Because she really is crazy.
And her explosion spell
is a real powerhouse!
[AINS]
Hmm.
[KAZUMA]
Uh?
[AINS] My curiosity is
all the more piqued.
[MEGUMIN] Well, I have no
doubt you undead guys
are gonna love this one!
Behold the raw power
of Megumin, the crimson demon!
O blackest darkness
shrouded in light.
O frenzied blade clad in night.
Reveal the source
of thine origin.
I summon the root of
thy fearsome power!
[ALL gasp]
[MEGUMIN] Strike my foe...
with Explosion!
[MEGUMIN sighs]
I really needed that. Yeah.
That spell was quite impressive.
It actually lived up to
all of the hyperbole.
A fitting grand finale
if I dare say.
[AINS]
Not just yet!
Is that so?
[AINS]
It was an incredible spell.
I'm fortunate to have borne
witness to its brilliance.
However, I would like to take
this opportunity to share my
own talent with all
of you gathered here.
Oh? What'll you do?
[AINS]
Let me think. Hm...
[MOMONGA]
Back in my salaryman life,
I had to watch a talent
show thing like this once.
It was at a New Year's Eve party
for a really horrible client.
A lot of people took turns,
but there was one thing
that people were talking about
for weeks and weeks afterwards.
Whoa! That's crazy!
All those magic circles!
I feel this will be the
most amazing by far!
[AINS shouts]
[ALL grunt]
[COCYTUS]
Can it be?
[MARE gasps]
[AURA]
It's awesome, Lord Ains!
[COCYTUS] To create a weather
phenomenon, is incredible.
[DEMIURGE]
Amazing! Well done, my Lord!
[SHALLTEAR] One of the many
reasons Ains Ooal Gown
reigns supreme!
[ALBEDO] Yes, naturally.
As he should.
[DARKNESS]
Oh my!
[MEGUMIN] Um, can somebody
please help me up?
I think my nose is
going to freeze off.
[AQUA]
Well, that wasn't bad.
I mean, I have
seen better, but...
[KAZUMA] Cocytus looks a
lot like the Winter Shogun.
[AQUA] No! I almost
forgot about that guy!
[TANYA]
Very nice work, Ains.
[NUEMANN]
Grantz! Lieutenant Grantz!
[WEISS]
What's with him?
[KOENIG] He's out and
foaming at the mouth.
[VISHA] Bet he's having
flashbacks to winter combat
on the training grounds.
[TANYA chuckles]
--[BEATRICE groans]
--[RAM] I'm freezing.
[SUBARU chuckles]
[REM] Subaru, how about a sip
of something to warm you up?
[SUBARU] I think we'd get
in too much trouble.
[EMILIA sighs]
[PUCK]
This feels pretty great, Lia!
[EMILIA]
Wonderful!
[SUBARU chuckles]
[AINS chuckles]