[SUBARU]
What the hell is that beast?
[KAZUMA]
Destroyer, the mobile fortress.
It's an ancient superweapon,
that even scares the
pants off the Demon King!
[TANYA]
That sounds terrifying.
Hey, wait.
Is it really part of the game,
or can we just ignore the thing?
[AINS] I'm afraid we'll
have to deal with it.
[KAZUMA, SUBARU gasp]
Look at its head!
Are you kidding me?
[ROSWAAL]
This matter is no joke!
So, you ready? We hereby
commence with round two, now!
[ROSWAAL chuckles]
If I were you, I would
definitely start running!
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Father!
You are such an
amazing role model!
I will try my best to live
up to your expectations!
This will make you proud!
Just watch!
[MINIONS laugh]
[VANIR laughs] This must be
quite a nuisance for you!
But your frustration is
incredibly delicious!
Look up there!
Never fear!
[CHRIS gasps]
[SUBARU]
Huh?
We're boned, guys.
Let's give up.
We'd be punished harder
for giving up than for losing,
don't you think?
Yeah, you're right.
[gasps] I may be able to use
"steal" to grab that headband.
[TANYA]
"Steal"?
It's faster to show ya!
Steal!
[KAZUMA gasps]
How about them? Steal!
[TANYA] Just stop,
you're embarrassing yourself.
[KAZUMA]
What?
I promise it has never
bombed this hard before.
Are you just pulling my leg?
No, I'm totally serious.
My luck has always been the
only stat that's worth a damn.
[CHRIS]
Kazuma!
It doesn't matter. This new
world changes your stats.
The rules from our old
world don't apply.
[KAZUMA] Remember when
I stole your undies?
Did you have to tell everybody?
We're clearly up
against the final boss,
and one-shot magic never
works on those guys.
[ROSWAAL]
Better get moving.
You do realize we're not
playing freeze tag, don't you?
[ALL shout]
[FELT grunts]
Listen up.
Huh?
Let's try this.
Hm?
We should choose
different targets.
That's really not such a
bad idea. Who'll it be?
We'll handle the small
group of teachers.
--And you can take on the big--
--[SUBARU] Wait!
[REINHARD]
Hm?
That's clearly the
more powerful enemy!
You all act like a
bunch of hot shots,
so shouldn't you
take the lead?
I'm sorry. It's just my divine
"let somebody else take
the spotlight" protection.
Oh, you are so
full of it, man!
There's no way in hell
that's actually a thing!
Stop whining, ya big baby!
It's time to nut up, or shut up!
Show us what you can do!
You heard her guys. Let's go!
Show 'em how we do things!
Skill... "Bind"!
Oh, my...
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] I don't
believe that an attack like this
will slow us down
in the slightest.
[CHRIS]
Fine with me.
[ALL]
Mm?
It'll make things way
more fun when we fight ya!
Huh?
Hey. Best of luck to you.
[SUBARU]
What?! Hang on!
[ALL grunt]
Right.
[AINS] So. How should
we approach this battle?
Can we determine its weak point?
There's none.
That was fast.
It's true.
[TANYA growls] Would it kill
you to try to strategize
for just a second?
[KAZUMA]
No use.
Question, Ains.
[AINS]
Hm.
You're a "Lord of Death",
aren't you?
Does that mean you can summon
a bunch of undead and stuff?
[AINS]
Yes, I can.
Awesome! Then let me--
Watch out!
[ALL yell]
Protective Core!
[TANYA shouts]
It won't hold him!
[AINS] Tanya, have you
forgotten who I am?
[gasps]
[AINS] I am the mighty
Ains Ooal Gown!
By strength, and sheer force of
will, I have earned my titles.
Lord of the Great Tomb of
Nazarick, The Sorcerer-King,
and vice-representative
of this class!
Body of Effulgent Beryl!
[TANYA, SUBARU gasp]
[SHALLTEAR, ALBEDO gasp]
Amazing.
Why are you standing over
here with us, Mister Rerugen?
Excellent work, Ains.
Nicely done. I'm impressed.
[AINS, TANYA chuckle]
[AINS]
Mm...
Now.
[ALL gasp]
I have a really bad
feeling about this!
[AINS]
The next part...
This is gonna suck
for us, right?
[AINS] I leave the rest to the
three of you! Claim our victory!
[AINS]
Godspeed.
But I cannot forget my own
unfinished business here.
Undead Army!
[AINS] I call upon you
to keep this world safe!
[ALL gasp]
[AQUA] Not loving the undead
creeping around to "protect" me.
They actually seem
really sweet to me.
I've never felt less
safe in my whole life.
Hang on, why are there
so many around me?
[MOMONGA] There was reason you
asked me to do this, right?
I've done my part. The rest
is in your hands, Subaru.
So, what's our next
move gonna be?
A decapitation strike.
Huh?
I'll fly directly over it
and grab that head band.
Game over.
Wait, if that thing hits us with
its death ray, we're toast.
[TANYA grunts]
Don't worry about it, man.
Huh?
I'll just create a
little distraction.
You're willing to
take that risk?
Yeah! Okay. Listen up, Kazuma.
Use your "stealth"
to get her close.
That's crazy!
You don't get to come
back to life in this world.
Yeah. I know.
It's scary, but we gotta make
big moves occasionally.
Huh?
And to be honest with you,
coming back kinda
sucks sometimes.
It's hard to explain,
but trust me.
[KAZUMA, TANYA]
Huh?
[KAZUMA]
Oh no, it's targeting us!
[SUBARU]
And that's why...
[KAZUMA]
That's why what?
Why I won't lose. I'm risking
my life here, it's true.
But that won't stop me!
[KAZUMA, TANYA groan]
Good thing I can bench press...
One hundred seventy-six pounds!
[BOTH yell]
Subaru!
I'm okay! Just grab
that head band!
Oh, no!
Aw, don't worry. He'll be fine.
Huh?
I know it. But you gotta
believe in him, too.
Better cover your
ears, everybody!
Not like they can
hear me, anyway.
I die! And come back to...
Well, I'm back. So what now?
There's all of those undead!
[AINS]
What the hell?
Subaru...
[KAZUMA grunts]
[KAZUMA] And a snipe,
and a snipe, and a snipe...
[TANYA]
You're actually pretty amazing.
[KAZUMA]
And a snipe--
You think so?
And a snipe.
Then why doncha try...
...being a little...
And a snipe.
...nicer to me?!
Huh?!
[TANYA]
Hm! Yeah, I'll work on that.
Thank you! This is the last one!
And a snipe.
All right! That's about
all I can do for you now.
'Kay. Thanks for everything.
Oh, by the way.
What's up?
My good luck stat is
pretty amazing, too.
Yeah? That's the opposite
of my situation.
It's cool. I know
it'll all work out.
Well. I'm off.
'Kay. Best of lu--
[KAZUMA yells]
Aw, man! Why is this
happening to me?
I just wanna go home and take
a bath, but I'll... steal!
[TANYA grunts]
[KAZUMA laughs] What'd I say?
My luck is off the charts!
[KAZUMA gasps]
Yeah. That's no lie.
If we were in my world,
I'd force you to join
the Imperial army.
Since we're here,
I suppose I'll just have to put
an end to this farce myself.
[TANYA]
Lord. In you there is truth.
I pray that you
reveal a path to me.
I know you work in
mysterious ways...
...but do it now!
[TANYA yells]
[ALL chattering]
[SUBARU]
Hey!
They didn't let us go home,
it was all just a big lie!
I said that you could
"maybe" go home, remember?
And one's words
do matter, right?
Well. I'll be fine either way.
Say what? We still gotta beat
the demon king, ya know?
[MEGUMIN chuckles]
No matter what world we're in,
I'm gonna keep on
doing my thing!
It's humbling here.
I could get used to that.
Seriously?
Come on.
You're not really having too
bad of a time here, are ya?
Yeah, right.
I know that some people
are into peace,
but I really don't
want to lose my edge.
Major?
I'm sure that this is just
another one of that bastard's
tests for me. He's trying
to make me die of shock!
Say what?
This sucks, if you
ask me. So unfair.
It doesn't surprise
me at all.
Saw it coming, I suppose.
[EMILIA] You know, It's strange.
Regardless,
I'm still having fun!
[REM] Me too.
Everyday's a new adventure.
You're right. It's not so bad.
[MOMONGA]
I agree, it's not bad at all.
What's more, every day
we've been here,
the floor guardians have
become more independent.
[sighs]
[MOMONGA]
When you think of it that way...
[AINS] ...maybe this no-good
world isn't half bad.
[ROSWAAL]
Oh, one more thing.
[ALL]
Huh?
I nearly forgot to mention
something rather important,
that you'll all love!
We will soon be playing host to
some new transfer students!
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[TANYA]
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
[AINS]
Eh?!
[ROSWAAL]
Come in, please!