"It's taking part that counts."
These words became famous after
the father of the modern Olympics,
Baron Pierre de Coubertin, used them in a speech.
But some say the quote is frequently misused,
and is used as a coercion tool to force participation.
Yet, there are countless situations in
society where it's a waste to even show up.
If it's taking part that counts,
then taking part in the side that
doesn't take part should also count, right?
If everything can be chalked up to experience,
then the experience of experiencing
nothing should be worth just as much.
Huh?
The fact is, the simple act of not
getting experience could be just as priceless.
Jeez, there he goes again...
Considering he's so convincing despite the
ridiculous "logic" he spews, it's really pretty pathetic.
Wait a sec. I'm not to blame here.
That's on society!
Now this is what I call real teamwork!
All right then, let's do this!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Yay!
Yay...
Hm...
What do you think we should do about this?
Oh, do you mean this?
Trans Chiba Email Counseling.
This is the newest aspect of our club's work.
"I'm looking for ideas to make
our athletic festival more exciting.
Also, it's my last one, so I want to win!"
Ugh. That time of the year already?
God, I seriously hated the competitive class relays.
All that unexplained pressure...
Yeah, well, I couldn't run very
fast, so it was hard for me too.
I forgot, there was always that guy...
Anytime that a classmate would start to fall behind,
the soccer player Nagayama, would rage out.
Who is that? Why'd you even say his name?!
Well, I hated that guy.
Though I'm pretty sure he hated me right back.
And also, the girl who didn't want to take the baton.
Why would she say, "I can't believe this!"
When she was the next one after me?
So cold...
Uh, no, she's just...
I believe you know the answer perfectly
well so there's no need to comment.
Usually, when girls act reluctant
like that, she probably means it.
Well that sounds like a comment.
You should probably look up "comment."
You know what else happens at athletic festivals?
Oh boy, you have more?
I do! When you're one person short, and you
have to do gymnastic formations with the teacher.
Because you don't even have enough for a fan formation.
I pity the parents who had to see their kid do that.
Come in.
Ah! I've come to the right place
for the Service Club, haven't I?
I sent an email earlier about the athletic
festival, but I didn't get a reply, so I came in person.
So this email came from...
Yeah, that's probably the one I sent over.
I want to make the athletic festival
as exciting as the cultural festival!
You did such a great job last time,
please help Yukinoshita and... Hmm...
Oh, uh...
Hikigaya. It's Hikigaya!
Oh, yes, Hikigaya! And you're...
Uh, actually I'm Yuigahama.
He's Hikigaya.
I'm sorry. I don't know why, but
I've gotten so bad at remembering names.
Oh, don't worry about it. Hikigaya's a professional
when it comes to not having his name remembered by anyone.
I don't want to hear that kind of stuff from you.
You're not wrong, but still.
Then it's okay, right?
You're also good at erasing your own presence.
It's like a superpower.
No, that isn't true, Hikki!
You're in the classroom alone a
lot, so you actually do stand out more!
Does that even count as a defense?
So, uh, Hikigaya...
Ah... Y-yes?
Hikigaya, right? 'Kay, I've got it now!
You worked hard on the cultural festival, too!
I know I can count on you!
Sure.
Just hold on a second.
You can definitely forget about that one, so
why don't you just tell us more about your request.
Oh, that's right!
I need help in coming up with the boys' and
girls' featured events at the athletic festival.
Featured events? 'Kay...
Come to think of it, what were
the featured events last year?
Now that you mention it, I don't remember.
Well you do know they say that people block
out memories that are too painful for them.
My athletic past is not just some dark moment in time.
Besides, if it were that easy to forget,
I wouldn't still bear the scars of trauma.
You know, I actually don't remember last year's either.
That's because they're always so dull.
I want to do something different
with some flair this year.
That makes sense...
Now I understand why you need us.
How soon do you need our ideas?
Now that you mention it, we're actually having
a committee meeting down the hall and
could use your help. Could you join us?
Are you talking about right now?
Ah! What team are you guys on?
Every class in the school has been taken and split in
half to make up the two teams, so I'd like to make sure.
I'm on the red team, what about you?
I'm red.
Me too.
Same here.
We're all on the same team!
Okay we must get out there and
do our best to win this thing!
Yay!
Hey, looks like you managed to secure some new members.
I did. And it went exactly as you said it would.
So you're the one behind this little scheme then, huh?
I was getting so bored watching
the same athletic festival.
It just repeats every year.
I'm looking forward to something more fun.
You sound like you're playing around...
I find it interesting that you're in
charge of the athletic festival, too.
Ah, yes...
These kinds of jobs tend to fall
to the young teachers around here.
And mark my words kids, I am the young one. Very young.
She said it twice to show how important that point is...
Okay, Shiromeguri, let's start the meeting.
Great. On our agenda today is
featured events for the festival.
We need to come up with some strong ideas!
Raise your hand if you have a suggestion!
Over here!
Yes, Yuigahama!
What about doing a club relay race?
If you do that, people who aren't members of a
club don't get to participate. They'll complain.
Any others? Let's keep them coming!
Yes, Yukinoshita!
How about a nice, orthodox, bread-eating contest?
I'm afraid the students who prefer rice will complain.
I didn't know the bread versus rice debate was so serious.
Well let's just regroup and keep trying. Who's next?
Hah!
Yes, Yuigahama!
Let's do a scavenger hunt!
We need to be sensitive to all the students
who are suffering under their parent's debts...
All we're doing is being sensitive...
Everyone's so nitpicky these days.
There are so many regulations to uphold.
Anyway, let's keep thinking!
You guys over there need to be throwing out ideas, too!
This has turned into a word association game.
Why don't they just use Magical something-or-other?
Is that it on ideas?
They're far more lacking in
ideas than I originally thought.
No matter what we pick, our ideas
are scrapped for insensitivity...
It was a bit much to expect us to come up with ideas.
What do we do now?
We find the right person for the job?
Well that sure is a valuable perspective there, Hikigaya.
It's typical for organizations to pull this stuff.
Milk people until they're completely dry.
But yet, they'll never see a pay raise.
You said it! I totally hear that!
Ms. Hiratsuka, I don't think that
you're supposed to agree with that.
It's pointless for unfit people
to try too hard at something.
It's better to call someone who's a pro in the field.
In other words, you're saying that the
club should go ahead and renounce this request?
Workshare, that's what I'm talking about.
Like a job rotation. You know, outsourcing. Get it?
I'm not sure what that means, but it sounds good.
I'm just impressed you came up with so many terms
that mean the same thing. I guess it's in how you say it.
But it's also important that we
have faith in this, right, guys?
Well, see there you go, then.
Yuigahama.
Yeah?
Ah?
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
You got it. I'll go give them a call now.
Uh, those are our resources?
So, why'd you call me here, Yui?
Aherm, aherm, ahem. Same question as my left.
Well, the thing is...
I see! The Universe!
You want us to come up with thrilling
events that will go down in history?
And they should be exciting, right?
It doesn't matter how they're exciting, though, does it?
Uh...
Okay, no problem! I'll think of something!
You can also count on Yoshiteru!
Thank you guys so much!
This is shaping up to be a lot of fun thanks to you guys!
Hang on, we have plenty more still left to do.
Huh? Don't forget, we're only halfway
through the request that you sent to us.
Oh yeah! While we're at it, we gotta win too!
Yeah! Let's do this!
Go! Keep it up!
Ah?
And now, as the athletic festival nears
its end, the white team has dominated so far.
Our own Hayama Hayato has been a major source of points,
giving our team the advantage throughout each event.
However...
Don't forget, this is still anyone's battle!
And now, what we've all been waiting for,
the main event that's the Chiba Girls'
Mock Cavalry Battle! Also known as Chibattle!
Hey, are you sure this is okay?
Listen up!
Long ago, a battle took place right here
in Chiba between the Satomi and Hojo clans.
This magnificent event was
created with that battle in mind.
That's great but I think this area was underwater then...
Huh? What's with those outfits?
Believe me, that's what I want to know as well.
This is really embarrassing.
Well, it's a battle, after all.
The captains should always be wearing armor!
Right, but we're not actually...
Hold still.
These are very special battle costumes that have
been produced by me and made all by hand by Sakisaki!
Don't call me "Sakisaki"!
Wow, you guys sure get along well.
Why are they Western style?
Good point. Shouldn't they be more samurai?
You know why. This is what we like.
All right! Let's go take the lead!
Yay!
We get 30 points if we win this event, right?
And if the boys beat their next
event, that means we might actually win.
Telling me that doesn't really help me here...
Don't worry, we'll keep our promise.
Yep!
I wouldn't exactly call a one-sided
declaration a promise. But whatever.
And the horses and riders for both teams have assembled.
The team that knocks down the
most riders from the other team wins!
All right, folks! The Chibattle
has begun and as you can see...
I'm so psyched!
Let's go!
Good game, everyone!
Yui!
Ah! She's after me!
Wait, look!
It appears there's a clash of
captains on the other side, too!
Miura versus Yukinoshita!
Oh, an air throw?
Is she actually Master Asia? Is she going to die at dawn?
Remarkable skill! The red team wins!
Huh?
Good job, girls.
Go take care of the rest.
It's all yours, Hikki!
That's easy for you to say...
And for our next festival event,
we have the boys' Pole Topple.
For something Ebina came up with,
this one seems pretty normal so far.
All those sweaty boys fighting
and grappling over a big pole...
It's so obscene!
Huh?
Ah! Oh, Hachiman!
Hey, Totsuka. What's the deal with that outfit?
Uh, apparently, athletic club presidents
are supposed to be captains, so, uh...
So, do you think I really look weird?
Uh!
You look great! Uh, not weird at all!
No, not weird at all!
This must be love!
Oh, I think I just witnessed the moment
when someone fell in love for the first time.
We will begin by introducing the captains of each team!
For the white team, the soccer
club president, Hayato Hayama!
And for the red team, the tennis club president,
Saika Totsuka!
Zaimokuza, I think I've worked out a plan.
Oh, yeah? Well let us hear it then.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Yes! I've got it!
Just leave it to me, Boss!
Listen up, men!
Your supreme commander is here!
Uh, hi, I'm the team captain, Saika Totsuka.
Now, let's get out there and do our best!
We only have one enemy! And
that's Hayato Hayama! Okay, guys?!
Do you want that good-looking creep to
run away with our well-deserved victory?!
Well, I don't! I seriously don't want that!
I don't want to feel pathetic anymore!
I don't want to smile convulsively every time he
glances my way and speaks to me, as he's floating by!
I don't want to shut up and
give him the right of way anymore!
And how about you guys?!
Sure...
In that case, we must win!
Now is the time to awaken!
Let's stand up, citizens!
So tell me, was that performance to your liking?
Sure, that works for me.
It was so creepy, nobody could miss it.
C-creepy?
The plan is ready to go.
And now, all that's left...
And so, the game has finally begun! A boys'
game of boys' Pole Topple, by boys for boys!
We've got both seme and uke mixed deliciously together!
The white team has come out
strong launching a preemptive attack!
I'm really sorry about that...
It's my pleasure. Let me take him down for you, Captain!
Ah...
Thanks for that!
Guys? Are you okay?
There's so much cuteness...
All the guys on the red team are complete idiots.
Hmm...
I have not one shred of regret in my life!
How sad!
What the hell do you think he's doing down there?
As usual, he's being a total pain in the ass.
Although, with him drawing everyone's attention,
now I get to finally do my job.
I can't feel my hand!
Not yet...
It's not time yet!
And this is my skill.
Carefully cultivated through my many years spent alone...
Stealth Hikki.
Hey. I thought you'd be coming.
Hayama...
Nice wrap. You get a head injury earlier?
I've always got a bit of a headache, you know.
So, Zaimokuza, was it?
Using him as a decoy to get this far was a good plan...
But really...
there's no way I wouldn't have had a mark on you.
Don't think too highly of me, there.
Don't hold it against me.
But I'm going to fight your
grandstand play with team play.
You know that's what they call tyranny of the majority.
That just sounds evil. It's just numbers-based.
Hmph.
Give up?
No way...
Zaimokuza!
Gotcha!
If you're gonna fight with numbers,
then we're gonna fight you with weight!
Decoy for a decoy?!
We're in trouble! Get 'em, guys!
You won't be able to get past us!
Just come and try it if you can!
We're gonna get you!
Zaimokuza...
Crusher!
Hachiman!
You're amazing, Hachiman!
We did it! We won! We won!
I can't believe we lost.
Yeah, I never expected to lose on a foul.
If only someone hadn't done such a lousy
alteration on his headband, we'd have won.
I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't think anyone was watching me.
No, people do watch you!
She's right. Even I wondered what you were gonna
do when you took that bandage out of your pocket.
Wait, you were watching him, too?
Ah? I just happened to see it...
Can you guys please stop watching me?
Wait, calm down. Meguri was
really happy with the outcome!
Still, it's actually quite frustrating
to lose an athletics festival.
I didn't know that before.
Yeah! We'll win next year!
You're right. We'll win it next year.
You don't know if we'll be on the same team next year.
You always say stuff like that...
That's true. Hikigaya seems
like he'd enjoy being the enemy.
You've become more motivated?!
I'm excited already!
The festival after the festival is over...
And everything after that is a festival.
Some things can't be redone,
but whether we laugh or cry, our days carry on,
and our high school lives will end.
Thus, their festival will never end.