What? No... Y-you've got it all wrong.
You've heard of flexible management attendance, right?
As a man who strives to become an elite, I was just...
You told me your goal was to be a stay-at-home-dad,
and that you prefer to "work smarter, not harder."
Ugh! W-well, you know...
the concept of lateness being
evil is wrong in the first place...
Oh? I'll hear you out before I hit you.
The police don't mobilize until after an incident happens,
and it's standard for heroes to show up late.
But would anyone condemn them just for being late?
So, speaking paradoxically, lateness is justice...
Wait, please don't hit me, Miss! I was only kidding.
Oh?
I mean, for real...
There are just too many problem children in this class.
Are you practicing "flexible management
attendance," too, Miss Kawasaki?
Huh?
Black lace...
Are you stupid?
Hm?
Hmm...
Now it's Yukinon's turn to ask a question.
This one's a Japanese question.
They want you to complete the following idiom.
"When the wind blows..."
Hmm...
The Keio line stops running?
What is this, Trans Chiba Ultra Quiz?
"Yuigahama, you're thinking of, "...these days,
more trains just move slower instead of stopping."
Answer: "the carpenter gets rich."
Now for a geography question.
Two local specialties of Chiba.
Miso peanuts... Boiled peanuts?
You think peanuts are all this prefecture has to offer?
Oh, hey! Well, hello there, Hikki!
I thought it was some weirdo
just talking to me out of nowhere.
So you were invited to the study group, too?
Uh... What's with that face of,
"Oh God, we totally didn't invite him"?
Sorry, but you weren't invited to this study group.
Do you need something?
You shouldn't ask for answers in ways
that are only intended to hurt people.
Hm? What's that?
What? Oh, yeah. It's info on summer courses.
Whoa! You're already studying for exams, huh?
Isn't everyone studying for their exams?
I mean, it's almost time for college.
Plus, I'm trying to get a scholarship for a prep school.
"A scholar's hip"? He said "scholarship."
These days, prep schools are granting
tuition waivers for students with good grades.
If I get that, and get tuition money
from my parents, that money will be mine.
That's fraud. What a cheap trick to pull.
It's not hurting anyone. What's the problem?
Big Brother! Huh?
Komachi? What are you doing here?
My friend was asking me for some advice.
Hm.
Nice to meetcha!
My name's Komachi.
Thanks for looking out for my brother.
It's a pleasure to meet you. I'm his classmate, Totsuka.
Wow, you're really a cutie! Right, Brother?
Sure, except he's a guy.
Oh stop... You quit being such a silly billy!
Wait, really?
Y-yeah.
Promise.. I'm a real boy.
Oh, hi! Nice to meet you! I'm
Hikki's classmate, Yui Yuigahama.
Oh, cool! Pleasure.
Are you finished?
Nice to meet you. I'm Yukinoshita.
I'm not Hikigaya's classmate, nor am I one of his friends.
I'm truly sorry to say, but...
I think I'm considered an acquaintance, maybe?
Why sorry, and why say it like a question?
So, uh...
I'm Taishi Kawasaki.
I'm at the same cram school as Hikigaya,
and like you guys, my sister
is a second year at Soubu High.
Her name is Saki Kawasaki.
Huh?
Black lace?
Oh! You mean Kawasaki?
She's kinda scary-looking.
Aren't you friends with her?
Well, I've talked with her, but...
You know, you really shouldn't ask a
girl that, it can be hard to answer.
In fact, I don't think I've actually ever seen Kawasaki
acting friendly with anyone in class.
Not only that, but it seems like Taishi's sister
has developed some bad behavior lately,
like coming home late and stuff,
so he brought me here for us to try and figure out
how to get his old sister back to him.
When did you notice all this starting for her?
Only recently. And after she got into Soubu High.
In middle school, she acted really serious...
and she was considerate.
I see...
So she changed after being put
in the same class as Hikigaya?
Why did you just say that like I'm the reason behind this?
Am I some kind of pathogen?
I didn't say that.
Aren't you being a bit paranoid, Hikigaya-coccus?
You did say it. You just called me a germ.
I misspoke.
It's Hikigaya-coccus! Tag!
But I had a shield up this whole time!
Shields aren't able to keep out Hikigaya germs!
Hikigaya-cocci must be damn powerful
if they can go through shields.
Wait, so how late does she come home, anyway?
I mean, I get home late, too.
Well... like, after 5 AM.
But that's basically morning.
Don't your parents say anything to her?
Both my parents work.
I also have a younger brother and sister,
but they don't really say anything to my big sis.
Family circumstances, then?
Every family does have their problems.
Huh?
I understand.
Are you planning to do something?
Taishi is the brother of a
student at our school, Saki Kawasaki,
and since she is the one he has come seeking advice for,
I believe this falls within
the category of Service Club work.
Huh?
I've been thinking, and I believe
that, rather than coercing her,
it would be for the best if
Kawasaki fixed the problem herself.
You're probably right with that. So, what do we do, then?
Have you heard of animal therapy?
So, what are your intentions with my cat?
I think by having her interact with a cat
it will hopefully bring out Kawasaki's gentle side.
If her heart is moved, then she's sure to take him home.
She's not some old-school juvenile delinquent.
I went ahead and assigned roles for each of us.
Now everyone take your positions.
Meow. Meow.
Meow.
What are you doing, weirdo?
What do you mean?
Uh, you were just talking to
Kamakura like she was going...
More importantly, I believe I ordered you to stand by.
Are you unable to do a task?
I thought I came up with something
finally appropriate to your low level,
but I didn't realize I'd have to stoop even lower.
I can tell by the look in her eyes that
she'll kill me if I try to talk back...
Komachi, what's up?
Hi, Brother? This is Taishi. Hikigaya just told me...
You have no right in calling me
your brother, like that. Understand?
Hey, why'd you hang up?
I'm busy. I'm waiting for your sister.
Well, it's about that plan...
My, uh, my sister's allergic to cats.
Even if she can't talk to her parents
because they're too close to her,
maybe she can talk to another adult about it.
Right?
Kawasaki.
Hm?
Need me for something?
I hear you've been getting home late recently.
What are you doing, and where?
Who gave you that information?
I can't go revealing my clients' secrets.
Just answer my question.
What does it matter where I go?
It's not like I'm bothering anyone.
It might start to bother someone real soon.
You're only in high school right now.
Haven't you thought about how
your parents might feel about this?
Wait a minute.
How would you even know? It's
not like you've ever been a parent.
Ah?
Aren't you single?
If I were you, I would be more worried about
your own future than trying to look into mine.
Like getting married.
Oh no... Poor Teacher.
I'm going home.
Someone just marry her already. Seriously.
If changing made her worse, then it'd make
sense that if she changes again, she'll get better.
Yeah, but how can we change her?
There's only one thing that
will always make a girl change!
You know?
Love...
O... 'Kay...
Long day?
You look tired. Do you have work now?
You know you shouldn't wear yourself out.
Thanks for all your concern.
You know...
Hm?
You don't always have to act so tough around everyone.
Yeah, whatever you say, dude.
Uh...
I feel like I've been rejected...
Uh... No... Good job.
It's not nice to laugh at someone!
Oh no, it's okay. It doesn't bother me.
Hm?
I'm not your damn brother, all right?
What are you even talking about,
of course you're my big brother.
Anyway, Taishi said his sister just
got a phone call from some weird place!
Huh?
So, what he's saying is that she received a phone
call from the owner of a place called "Angel" something?
Yeah.
And when they searched around for stores in Chiba
city that are open till morning with "Angel" in the name,
they only came across two.
And one of those is this place?
I'm embarrassed to say...
but I don't know much about maid cafe.
What are they like?
I don't know much about them, either,
so I decided to invite someone who does.
Ahem!
My time has come at last to assist you!
Seriously?
It was you who invited me! Why are you making that face?!
I was just thinking it's gonna be a pain to deal with you.
Then just follow me quietly!
To where we can just sit back
and have the maids pamper us.
Huh?
They'll pamper us?
What's wrong with you?
You're starting to creep me out now.
Anyway, isn't this the kind of place that only guys go?
What are we supposed to do while in there?
It looks like women are welcome, too.
Meowlcome back, master! Arf!
Oh! Sorry to keep you waiting...
M-Master.
Well, does it look okay?
Wow! You look so cute, Yuigahama!
Right, Hachiman?
U-uh, yeah...
Really? You think so?
Hah! You're only cosplaying as
a maid, your soul isn't into it!
I would rather see you...
Wh-what?
Master!
Whoa! Yukinon, no way!
That looks great on you! You look gorgeous!
Thank you. Now then, it appears Kawasaki isn't here.
You checked already?
Her name wasn't on the shift chart.
Considering her employer called her at
home, I don't think she'd be using an alias.
That's odd...
What's odd?
A sullen girl like her working in secret...
"Meow, meow! Welcome back, master!"
"Hey, what are you doing here?!"
That's obviously how it's destined to turn out!
What? None of that made sense.
Let's just go to the second place.
The top floor of the Hotel Royal Ochre, "Angel Ladder."
A stairway to Heaven?
S-sorry for the wait.
Where are the other two?
Said they didn't have anything to meet the dress code.
I see.
Check these outfits!
Yukinon has lots of fancy dresses like
these in her closet, and she lives alone!
Seriously, who even are you?
You exaggerate. I only have clothes like
these because they're called for on occasion.
Most people never have those kinds of occasions.
Whoa!
You kiddin'? Is this for real? It's amazing.
Stop gawking like that. Stand up
straight and stick out your chest.
Pull in your chin.
Hm?
Kawasaki?
Sorry, sir, do I know you?
I don't believe we've met before.
Only you, Hikigaya, would be in the same
class as someone and them not know your face.
Yukinoshita?
H-hi!
Yuigahama.
So he's from Soubu High, too?
Yeah.
Well? What are you doing here?
Don't tell me you're on a date with this guy.
Certainly not. If you're talking about the
object on my right, that's not even a funny joke.
Do you think you could possibly stop being so mean
to me when you're busy arguing with somebody else?
Your little brother's worried about you.
He says that you've been coming home late, recently.
I thought people had been fussing over me.
So it was because of you guys.
I don't know what Taishi told you,
but you don't have to worry about me.
Stay out of it.
Cinderella's spell wears off
right as the clock strikes midnight,
but I guess your spell wears off about now.
Hm?
If my spell's wearing off, doesn't that
only mean there's a happy ending for me?
I don't know if that's in the cards, Little Mermaid.
Unfortunately I believe a
terrible ending is waiting for you.
Hey, what exactly are they talking about?
People our age can't work past curfew.
So Yukinoshita's saying she suspects
Kawasaki is lying about her age.
Oh... Then why not say that instead?
You have no intention of quitting?
Hm? No.
That's just not right, Kawasaki...
I like to pull some part-time work when I'm short on
money, too, but I would never lie about my age to do it.
It's not... look, I just need money.
Yeah, we get that, but you're pushing it...
Says the guy who says he wants
to "work smarter, not harder."
You heard that? Life isn't so light. I'm not
working for money just to go spend and play around.
Don't lump me in with those idiots.
You guys all strut around and talk like your big,
but can you three help me out with any money?
I'd like to see you all try and shoulder
the debt that my parents can't pay off?
Well, if you really need it...
Stop right there, Yuigahama. If you
keep talking you'll only give in to her.
Hey... Yukino, isn't your father a prefectural member?
Someone who's got it as easy
as you could never understand me.
Hey now!
Yukinon's family has nothing
to do with any of this, ya hear?!
Then my family has nothing to do with this stuff, either.
M-maybe not, but what about... Yukinon's...
I only knocked over a glass is all.
It's nothing for you to worry about. Just let it go.
I think it's time for us to leave.
Kawasaki. I want to talk to you about Taishi.
Give me some time tomorrow.
5:30 at the WcD's.
Why?
I'll tell you "why" when I see you.
Later.
Hold on!
There's not enough money here.
They didn't cover my part of the bill?
Son of a...
Taishi...
What are you doing here at this hour?
I should be asking you that.
Tell me, what have you been doing out all night?
It's none of your business.
Kawasaki, let me take a guess why you're working
so much and the reason you need the extra money now.
Taishi, has anything changed
since you started back middle school?
Yeah, I started going to cram school as well.
I get it. She wanted to pay her brother's tuition...
Wrong.
What?
When he started attending cram school in April,
the Kawasaki family had already
reached a solution regarding his tuition.
That sounds about right. After all, he's not the
only kid out there who has to pay tuition for school.
We go to a college prep school, so a lot of students
start thinking about college by their second year.
That's when they start giving serious
thought to taking summer courses.
Ah!
Big Sis...
I told you, you didn't need to know where I was at night.
I want to go to college, and I don't
want to be a burden to you and our parents.
Um, can I say something?
So yeah, our parents both work
and aren't around a lot, too.
When I was little, I hated coming home
and finding nobody at home, so I ran away.
And it was my brother, not my parents, who came after me.
And, ever since then, he's been getting home
before I do so that I never have to be alone.
I'm eternally grateful to him for that.
I thought Hikigaya went home early
because he has no friends to hang out with.
Hey, how did you know?
What are you, Yukipedia?
Oh, no, I mean I totally realize that, as well,
but I'd say my explanation is worth
more points, don't' you think? Huh?
So what are you trying to say with that?
I simply mean that just like you
don't want to be a burden to your family,
Taishi doesn't want to become a
burden to his big sister, either.
It'd make me happy as a fellow
younger sibling if you'd understand that.
Well, that's pretty much it.
So, um, Kawasaki...
Have you heard of scholarships?
Is that what it's like to have siblings?
Depends on the siblings you have.
You could also call them the
closest stranger in your life.
Oh, yes... I understand that all too well.
Oh, that's right. So you did get to meet her after all?
Huh? What are you on about?
You know, the girl with the desserts! Good for you!
To think you got to meet a cute girl
like Yui all because you broke a bone.
What did she just say?
Yuigahama is the girl who brought the desserts?
The owner of the dog I saved on
the day of our entrance ceremony?
What's the matter, Big Brother?
Nothing. Want to buy some bread on the way home?
Mm-hmm!
This concludes our workplace observation. You may go now.
Hikki!
You're late! They all went to the restaurant already!
Well, aren't you going, as well?
Huh? Oh... No, I was waiting for you to come down.
I mean, I'd feel bad leaving you behind and all.
You're a really nice person, Yuigahama.
But listen, you don't have to worry about me anymore.
Huh?
It was a total fluke that I saved your dog, you know.
Even if I hadn't gotten into that accident,
I probably still would've been alone.
You don't need to feel bad about that.
Sorry. I guess I made you worry about me.
But you don't have to anymore.
If that's why you're being nice...
then just stop it.
Oh, no... Well, I mean...
It's not really like that at all, Hikki...
Yuigahama is as nice as they come.
She'll probably stay that way to the end.
Hm?
Ah... Hm.
Jerk.
I hate nice girls.
If they so much as say hello, it stays on my mind.
If they return my texts, my heart races.
The day one calls me, I know I'll
look at my call history and grin.
But I know in my heart that's just them being nice.
People who are nice to me are also nice to everyone else.
I almost end up forgetting that.
If the truth is cruel, then lies must be kind.
That's why kindness is a lie.
I gave up on always expecting it, always mistaking it,
and even hoping for it.
Someone who's been alone for so long
doesn't fall for the same trick twice.
I'm a veteran.
I'm the best there is when it comes to losing.
And that's why I'll always...
hate nice girls.
I did have some hope for that girl...
It's not as if Yuigahama has quit...
If she doesn't come, then it's the same thing.
I never found out what Yuigahama
likes, or even what her hobbies are.
What kind of friend am I?
Oh... Sorry. I guess I got a little carried away.
I want to tell you properly.
You don't have to concern yourself with me anymore.
So it's over now, right?
Jerk...
Next time: "His Beginning With Her Finally Ends."