It is in the nature of animals to live in groups.
Hm?
Carnivores maintain a hierarchy.
Those who don't become the alpha must
shoulder that stress their entire lives.
Heh.
Whoa! For real? What is this?!
That is so cool, dude!
And herbivores surely feel the dilemma of
sacrificing their peers in order to
survive attacks from their natural enemies.
This is totally awesome!
Can I borrow it for a sec?
Uh, yeah... Sure.
This is why living in groups is
of no benefit to the individual.
As such, I choose to take the path of
the bear, which never lives in groups.
Bears are known for being solitary creatures
that feel no insecurity in having to living alone.
Better yet, they get to hibernate.
How awesome is that?
If I were to be reborn, I would
definitely want to be a bear.
You gave some serious props to bears.
I thought you were supposed
to be a modern Japanese teacher.
I'm supposed to give you "life guidance."
That's why the biology teacher
told me to assign this theme.
So, which part of this is about
"the ecology of wild animals"?
It's a powerful antithesis on
the social habits of wild animals.
Seriously, cut the crap.
You make it sound like living
in groups is some sort of sin.
But you live alone yourself,
and are, in fact, single, so...
Anyway, did that request for help go well?
Yeah, well... she seemed satisfied with our services.
Um, speaking of...
What's with that showdown you talked about the other day?
Oh, that thing?
Don't you worry about it.
I'll be passing my own one-sided judgment on the outcome.
It's all locked up in here.
Oh, and by the way,
what's your opinion of Yukino?
Hm?
Don't like her.
I see.
She's a very bright student, if you ask me.
But, those who have more than others
carry their own burdens in their own way.
She's actually very sweet.
Sweet and sometimes, she's right.
But the rest of the world is neither sweet nor right.
Must be hard for her.
You're both such troubling kids...
It just makes me worried that you'll
have trouble adapting to society.
It makes me want to bring you together in one place.
What is that room, a sanatorium?
Yeah, maybe!
But I think you kids are fun to watch together.
So maybe I just want to keep you two close by.
Normally, I have the best place to eat lunch
alone, without having to worry about people...
But when it's raining like this, I have nowhere to go.
Aww, Hayato...
I can't go today. I have my club.
Couldn't you skip just for one day?
There's a great deal on double
scoops at Forty-One Flavors today.
I want a chocolate and chocolat one.
Those are both chocolate!
Yeah, he's right.
They're totally different! And I'm really hungry!
Sorry, I'll have to pass.
Besides that, you'll live to
regret it if you eat too much.
Yeah, well I don't gain weight, no matter how much I eat.
Yeah, you totally look like a super model, Yumiko!
Your legs are gorgeous!
So anyway, I just, uh...
You think so?
But that Yukinoshita girl looks
even more amazing, doesn't she?
Yeah, that Yukinon sure is amazing...
"Yukinon"?
Oh, well, you're way more glamorous, Yumiko!
Oh, why not? I can go with you after my club.
Okay, Hayato. Send me a text.
Damn, that looks really rough.
Are they a feudal society or what?
If you have to kiss up to
people that much to feel complete,
I'd rather fly solo forever.
Well, I, uh...
I've got somewhere to go during lunch.
Yeah? Good.
Then could you pick up some of that lemon tea I like?
Silly me forgot to bring a drink today.
Uh, but the problem is I won't
be back here until fifth period...
I'll be gone for all of lunch, so I
don't know if I can possibly bring it...
Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
You know you haven't been very sociable lately, Yui.
Well, you might just have to say
it's kind of out of my hands for now...
I hate to let personal matters take me away, but...
That doesn't tell me anything. Just say it straight.
We're friends, aren't we?
Sorry.
I told you, "sorry" doesn't cut it.
There's something you want to say, isn't there?
Idiotic.
Go ahead, tear down your own friend.
It's not like I have any desire to actually help her out,
but when I see a girl I know
looking like she's about to cry,
my stomach twists up and nothing tastes good.
Besides, it's my job to get attacked by people, not hers.
I can't just let her take crap like that.
Hey, how about...
Back off!
H-how about I go and get myself
something cold to drink right now!
Or maybe I'll just sit down instead.
There.
Oh, yeah?
Let me say this for your sake.
That indecisive attitude of
yours is really getting annoying.
Sorry...
That again?
All you've been doing is apologizing.
You're apologizing to the wrong person, Yuigahama.
Listen, Yuigahama...
If you're going to invite me yourself
and then not even bother to show,
I have to wonder what that says about you.
If you're going to be late, isn't it
common courtesy to at least text me?
Oh, sorry!
Please forgive me, but I don't have your cell number.
Oh, right. Then I guess it's not entirely your fault.
I'm sorry. I'll let it go this time around.
Hey, wait a minute!
You and I are not finished talking this out!
Talking?
You consider what you're doing having a conversation, wow.
It appeared to me like you were
just forcing your opinions on her.
Huh?!
I'm sorry I didn't understand.
I'm not well-versed in the
ecosystem you all seem to live in.
Sorry. I thought you were an ape trying to intimidate me.
It's fine if you want to play king
of the mountain and try to look tough,
but please keep it confined to your own territory.
Your bluff will soon rub off, just like your cheap makeup.
Huh? What are you talking about? That makes no sense.
Okay, okay...
That's enough, Yukinoshita.
You, too, Yumiko.
Hmph!
I'll go on ahead, okay?
Ah?
Right! Thank you! I'm coming.
I'm gonna go get a drink.
Yeah, me, too! Later!
I think I'll go to the restroom...
Oh, I need to go take care of that!
I'll have to ride this big wave, too.
If the mood gets any more serious
in here, I'll suffocate and die.
Thank you for that, Hikki...
I mean, for standing up for me back there.
Huh?
Hm?
I'm sorry. It's just...
I feel uneasy when I don't go along.
Like, I end up trying to read the room or something.
I've always been like that, you know?
When we played house, I wanted to be the mother,
but if someone else wanted to do it, I'd be the dog.
It might be because I grew up in a housing complex.
I have no idea what you're trying to babble on about.
You're right. I'm not really sure I know either...
But, um, watching Hikki and Yukinon made me think...
They say what they think and
pick up on each other's moods,
and they seem to have fun
without trying to match each other.
They just seem right.
So I thought, maybe I was wrong to try
so hard to get along with everyone else.
I mean, Hikki is totally reclusive, right?
He pretends to sleep during breaks and
laughs while he reads books, and it's so creepy.
Heh. I thought you only did that in the club.
Didn't know you did that weird laugh in class, too.
Well, that really is creepy, so you should probably stop.
If you'd noticed it, then say something.
No way. I don't want to talk to you
when you're being all creepy like that.
And, well... that's the whole story.
I mean it's not that I don't like you or anything, Yumiko.
So, um, do you think we can still try to be friends?
Well... Sure.
I guess we can.
Sorry. Thank you.
Perfect... she can actually say it.
What are you doing here, Hikki?
Were you listening?
L-listening to what?
You were!
Eavesdropper! Creepy! Stalker! Pervert! Super creepy!
You're seriously way too creepy for your own good!
Why don't you learn a little restraint.
Huh? Why should I show any restraint now?
Whose fault do you think it is, moron?
What does she mean, "whose fault"?
Obviously...
It's Yukinoshita's, right?
Huh?
What are you doing?
Would you not sneak up on us like that?
Fine, sorry.
So, what are you doing?
There's someone suspicious in the club room.
What?
Imagine finally meeting you here.
I've waited so long for this,
Hachiman Hikigaya!
Do you know this person?
No way. Even if I knew him, I wouldn't.
Don't tell me you've forgotten the face of your partner.
I'm disgusted with you, Hachiman!
He says he's your partner, Hikki.
That's right, partner!
I know you have to remember
all those hellish times we went through
and the suffering we endured together.
I might've been paired up with him in gym or something.
Hmph! A most evil custom, indeed.
Find someone to pair up with, they say?
I am a man who could perish at any time.
I am not one to just make friends with!
What do you want, Zaimokuza?
Wait, so you do know this weirdo!
Well?
I am the Kengo Shogun,
Yoshiteru Zaimokuza!
So this friend of yours wants
something from you, I take it?
I told you he's not my friend.
That's right. I have no friends in this place!
Seriously. Not a one. None.
Anyway, Hachiman!
This is the Service Club, right?
Huh?
Yes, this is the Service Club.
I thought as much!
If the advice Ms. Hiratsuka gave me was correct, then,
you have a bound and sacred
duty to grant me my wish, Hachiman.
To think, after centuries, our bond
is still that of master and servant.
Could it be the guidance of Hachiman Daibosatsu?
The Service Club wasn't put in place
for granting yours or anyone's wishes.
We are only here so we can help people.
Th-then, Hachiman, please lend me your assistance!
As I recall, our bond is that of pure equals.
Let us strive once more to conquer
this hedonistic world to our liking!
What happened to our master-servant relationship?
Ahem! Ahem!
Come now, such trivial things
matter not between you and me.
I shall... forgive...
Why are you looking at me?
Hikigaya, a moment.
What exactly does that guy mean by "Kengo Shogun"?
That's a delusion of grandeur.
"Delusion of grandeur"?
A delusion of grandeur is...
So, he's not actually sick, per se.
I don't get it...
So, you're telling me he's basically just
acting out a setting he's created for himself?
That's about right... And...
Just because he happens to have the same name,
he's apparently convinced that
he's the thirteenth Muromachi shogun,
Ashikaga Yoshiteru.
So then why does he regard you as his partner?
Probably because my name is
the same as Hachiman Daibosatsu,
the Bodhisattva revered by Seiwa Genji.
I'm surprised. You're well-informed.
I guess.
Well, at least he's basing his setting on
actual history than on some fantasy in his head.
There are people worse than him?
Yep.
Purely for my own reference, what others are there?
If you don't know, the first seven gods of this world,
which includes the three creator deities:
The emperor Galan, war goddess Methica,
and protector Heartia, as well as-
Uh, you're pretty smooth with leading
questions. It's kinda freaking me out.
I almost went into way too much detail.
I wasn't trying to lead you into anything.
So creepy.
Well, you know...
I may have been like that once before, but not anymore.
I don't make up stupid fantasies anymore.
And I've graduated from cosplaying.
I'm not keeping spiritual world
diaries or government reports.
The only thing I still write is a
list of people I'll never forgive.
Yukinon, run!
I think I understand.
Your request is you want us to
heal this mental illness, right?
You are gravely mistaken. I have come here to
request that you grant my wish, as per your agreement!
It is the most noble of-
I'm the one who is speaking to you right now.
You need turn and look at people when they speak to you.
Well, good heavens-
And stop talking like that.
You're awesome, Yukinon!
Anyway, you'd like us to cure you of this illness, right?
Uh, I really wouldn't call it an illness...
Hey, don't be so-Huh?
Is this...
A manuscript for a novel?
Indeed!
That is a manuscript for a light novel.
I am thinking of submitting it
to a certain newcomer contest,
but no friends, means no opinions.
Please read it.
That was dreadful.
He told us something really sad without a second thought.
Aren't there sites you can submit these to?
Just post it there.
I can't do that. Those people are ruthless!
I would die if they criticized it too harshly.
Your heart needs to toughen up.
But you know...
She would probably be way more ruthless
than any place you would find online.
The foundation of this story is spatial
rupture... that which they call Dimension Driver!
In the end, it grants the world
parliament access to the akashic records...
Hachiman. Hachiman!
Huh? Oh. Sounds lame.
Now, hold on. Relax, Hachiman. Listen.
The heroine also has the hammer of
the gods, Gungnir Hammer! And it...
Ah!
Good morning, Hikki!
Hey, you're not very energetic today.
Hell, you know. After reading that thing...
Actually, I want to know why you're
so energetic after reading that.
Huh? Oh, y-you're so right!
Yeah, I'm starting to feel really sleepy...
You didn't bother to read it, did you?
Hm?
Good work.
Oh...
I'm surprised.
When I look upon your face,
my sleepiness is gone instantly.
I was too close to being deceived
by her looks and losing my mind there.
Wish I could put this woman to sleep forever.
Now then, let me hear your thoughts about my novel.
I apologize, but I don't understand
this sort of thing very well.
No matter. I wanted to hear the opinions of ordinary folk!
Say whatever you need to.
Fine.
It was quite terrible. Reading it was actually painful.
It was unspeakably tedious.
For my own reference, might I ask what part
of it you found to be so terrible and tedious?
First, the grammar is atrocious.
Why use inverse word order?
Do you not know how to use particles?
Did you not learn it in grade school?
I used a style that would
sound more familiar to readers...
Shouldn't you achieve a minimal mastery
of Japanese before you attempt that?
And the improper uses of furigana.
"Chikara" is not a possible
alternate reading of "nouryoku."
Let me ask you this...
Where does the "nightmare" in this
"Bloody Nightmare Slasher" come from?
You've got it wrong!
In modern battles, the use of
furigana adds a unique touch to-
Why does the heroine take off her clothes here?
There's no need for it at all. I'm not amused.
But without elements like that...
Could you not force others to
read a story that isn't complete?
Get some common sense before
attempting to show off literary talent.
Don't you think that's enough damage now?
You don't want to criticize him all at once.
I'm not finished just yet, but alright.
Well, I guess Yuigahama is next.
Yea... Oh, yeah...
So, you know a lot of... difficult kanji.
O-okay, Hikki!
H-Hachiman... You understand it, right?
So, what was that a ripoff of?
What?! A ripoff?!
How could you say such a thing? I'm a true original!
You're a blithering idiot.
What the...
Well, what's important are the illustrations.
Don't worry too much about the story for now.
Zaimokuza...
Will you read my work again?
Does he like pain?
After everything we said, you still want more?
Of course. Indeed, your criticism was harsh.
But it still made me happy.
Having someone else read the work I wrote for pleasure and
being able to hear their thoughts on it is a good thing.
I look forward to it.
Fine then. We'll read it again.
Farewell for now!
When I write something new, I'll bring it to you!
Yeah.
What he has isn't just a delusion of grandeur.
He's got full-fledged writer's fever.
He wants to write because he has something to write about.
If he can move someone's heart
with that, then all the better.
That's what writer's fever is.
Zaimokuza doesn't need to change.
Go!
Barrier!
Except maybe for that creepy side of his.
Good work.
My hip... my hip!
Hachiman...
What amazing artists are popular lately?
You're getting ahead of yourself.
Think about that after you win.
If it sells well, and gets
animated maybe I'll marry an actress?
Forget about that stuff right now. Just write, okay?
If it sells well, you think I
could have wild parties every night?
You're not gonna have wild parties!
Get your head out of the clouds!
If you don't mind, Hikigaya...
would you join our tennis club?
I'd have them run until they die, then swing
until they die, then practice until they die, perhaps?
Sai! Are you okay?
Will you hurry up? I wanna play tennis already.
Our forces are too overwhelming!
Game!
Mow them down!
You got me. That really was a magic serve.
Next time: "Sometimes the God
of Rom-Coms Does Nice Things."