Wow...
That article is about as intelligent
as the tree stump it was printed from.
What part of this do you relate to?
Oh, seriously!
Hey, it's time.
And wipe your mouth off first.
Huh? Is it jammed?
I wasn't aware your mouth was an automatic rifle.
You do know that's not what "jammed" means, right?
You know, Big Brother... sometimes I
have no clue what you're talking about.
That's your own fau...
Clean up for me, okay?
Younger sisters are strange beings.
However cute she may be, I feel nothing.
Her underwear is nothing more than cloth to me.
That's what a real little sister is like.
Huh?
Let's go!
This brat...
Don't go get in a wreck again,
okay? Remember, I'm riding with you.
What, it's okay to get in a wreck if I'm by myself?
Big Brother, sometimes you zone out with this
dead fish look in your eyes, and it really worries me.
Hey, I could give myself a lot
of points for that one, couldn't I?
I got into an accident on my first day of
high school, and she'll never let me live it down.
I got too excited about the start of my new life...
so I left home a whole hour early...
Huh?
and ended up hospitalized with a fracture.
That was when I knew I'd always be alone in my new school.
By the way...
After that wreck, the dog's owner came
over to say thanks for saving her dog.
She brought you desserts! They were really good.
And I never got to eat any of them, did I?
Tee-hee!
God, she's so annoying.
But the girl who brought the desserts goes to
your school, so you've probably met her already.
She said that she would thank you at school.
Why didn't you tell me this back then?
Well, didn't you get her name then?
I forgot it.
Oh! We're at my school!
Well it looks like I'm off then!
Thanks again, Big Brother! See ya!
Uh... Huh?
Oh, Big Brother!
Such an idiot.
"People in ancient times
believed that to work was to lose.
Manual labor requires high risk to earn high returns.
Therefore, my decision to start a family without
working is appropriate, and in fact, entirely justifiable.
This is why I have decided that
requesting my home be the workplace
for a stay-at-home dad, is
perfect for my career observation."
Guh!
You know what I'm about to say...
Do you not?
I'll rewrite it! Don't hit me!
You better believe it! And here I
was thinking you had changed a bit.
Hasn't your time in the Service
Club influenced your attitude at all?
I always say my motto is, "Stick to your guns."
If you don't want to get shot by my Annihilating Second
Bullet, you'd better shut your mouth while you still can.
Just try and spare me the Exterminating Last Bullet...
Hmph. Glad you're catching on fast, Hikigaya.
Anyway, you will resubmit your application survey.
Also, I forgot to tell you, but students will
attend this workplace observation in groups of three.
You can team up with whoever you
want, just make sure to come prepared.
I don't want random people from my
class coming into my house at all.
I take it you still intend on
"observing" your own home, huh?
Seriously...
You didn't see her?
See who?
Hey! You!
What's with you?
Since you hadn't shown up to the club room
in a reasonable time, you had to be looked for.
By Yuigahama, that is.
You don't have to use inverse word order
to stress that it wasn't you. I'm well aware.
I even went around asking people, you know.
And they were all, "Hikigaya? Who's that?"
That made it really difficult for me to find you!
W-well, sorry about that.
Thanks... not like I minded or anything.
So... like... maybe...
Hm?
G-give me your number!
'Cause I shouldn't have to run around looking
like a fool looking for you! It's distressing!
I mean I don't want people knowing I'm looking...
for you, that is...
That's fine with me, I guess.
You want me to type it?
Also, I'm amazed you can just hand
over your phone like this to someone.
You're typing really fast.
It's normal.
I bet your fingers are only weak 'cause you
don't have any friends to text back and forth with.
Well, that's rude.
I'll have you know that I texted
with a girl in middle school.
No way...
Hey! That was my phone!
Oh...
I was just having a hard time
imagining you texting a girl!
Listen, moron. It went down like this...
When we were changing classes
and everyone was exchanging numbers,
I took out my phone and looked around...
Thank you. Oh?
Do you want to exchange phone numbers?
You might as well say I was
popular enough for her to ask me that.
Well... Huh...
Sometimes kindness is cruel, isn't it?
Don't pity me.
I did text her as a matter of fact.
What kind of girl was this brave middle schooler?
She was a health nut and very refined if you must know.
She was such a devout health nut, in fact,
that when I texted her at seven in the evening,
she would always respond in the morning saying,
"Sorry, I was asleep. See you at school."
Hm... That means that...
She pretended she was asleep to ignore your text.
Hikigaya, don't avert your eyes from the truth.
Accept the reality.
I know what the reality is, you little fool.
Hell, I could probably write a Hikipedia article on it.
This looks like the sender line of a spam message!
Huh?
Something wrong?
What? No, nothing's wrong. It's just...
I got a weird message on my
phone. It's surprising, is all.
Hikigaya, if you don't want to
end up in court at some point,
you should refrain from sending such vulgar messages.
You just assume it's sexually charged, huh?
And I'm the culprit.
Let's see the proof you have!
I think your words are proof enough in this matter.
Guh!
There are certain lines the criminals always say.
"Where's the proof in all this?"
"Impressive deduction skills. You should
really write crime novels for a living."
"I'm not comfortable being in same room as a killer."
Really? That sounds more like the victim.
It's basically a death flag.
Is that what you think?
No, I don't think Hikki's the culprit for this one.
Why do you say that?
Hmm... I guess because...
it was about people that are in my class.
So Hikki would have nothing to do with it!
Except I'm in the same class as you...
Oh, I see.
Then, Hikigaya can't be the culprit, now can he?
She considered that to be valid evidence...
Well, these things are bound to come up now and then.
But I just don't worry about it that's all.
Huh?
Uh, hey... I wanted to ask a favor...
This is where the Service Club meets, right?
I instinctively admitted defeat again...
Ms. Hiratsuka said this was the place to
go to if I had a problem that needed fixing.
So... Man...
I had a hard time getting out of my club meeting.
We don't need to hear your story.
You came here to ask us for something...
Hayato Hayama?
Oh, yeah, about that...
Oh, that weird message...
"Tobe is a delinquent from Inage.
Staking out West High kids at the arcade.
Yamato dates three girls at once. He's total scum.
Ooka takes out rival schools' aces with rough play."
A chain mail, huh?
Since this started going around, it's
been really awkward with everyone in class.
And it makes me mad to see someone writing
this awful stuff about all my friends...
Oh, but I'm not interested in finding out who did this.
I wanna settle this thing peacefully.
Can you help me?
Hmm...
There it is...
Special technique: The Zone!
Allow me to explain.
The Zone is an inherent skill that only those
who live truly fulfilling lives may possess.
Its most prominent characteristic is
its ability to put a situation in order.
Because they are fulfilled in real life,
they are kind even to people who are often scorned.
One might call it a unique atmosphere
belonging to good people with strong charisma.
I see, so you want us to get the situation under control.
Hm. Yeah, that's about right.
Then, we'll need to find the
person who put out the message.
Hm. I'm counting... What?
But why? You don't have to do that.
Chain mail...
A despicable action that
tramples upon the dignity of others.
Their intention is to hurt those people...
while at the same time making sure
their own identities are never known.
In order stop this disease effectively,
it must be eliminated at the root.
Source: My own...
Your own experience?
Killed it at the root, then?
At any rate, people like that
must be thoroughly destroyed.
That's my way.
I will find the one who did this.
I believe a single word can stop them.
I'll let you decide what to do with them after that.
Is that all right with you?
Sure, that's fine by me...
When did you notice that the messages started to show?
It was last weekend, wasn't it? Yeah.
Something happen in your class, huh, Yuigahama, Hayama?
Nothing in particular that I know of...
Hm. Yeah, it was the same as always.
For the sake of asking, and you?
What is that supposed to mean?
Last weekend, huh?
So it was pretty recent that this started...
Workplace observation will be in groups of three.
Workplace observation?
Oh! That's it!
It's because we're being split into groups!
Hm?
I think I know who's doing it!
Could you explain?
Some people can't be grouped in events like this.
It can really affect their relationship afterward.
These people can get pretty sensitive.
Our workplace observation is done in groups of three,
so with a group of four friends, one's out.
He'd kick someone out so as not to be excluded.
So, I would think for starters, we can
assume that one of those three is the culprit.
W-wait just a minute.
I don't want to go about thinking that
any of my friends would be the culprit.
That message said bad things about all three.
I don't think any of them did it.
Are you stupid?
Everyone knows the culprit just did that so
he wouldn't be suspected as the instigator.
And, in fact, if it were me doing it,
I would pick the one person to not say
bad things about, so I could frame him.
You know you're absolutely terrible, Hikki.
Call me a smooth criminal.
Okay then, why don't you start
telling me about your three friends?
Hm... I admit...
Tobe often looks like a bad guy,
but he's the most easygoing and cheers people up.
He's the most proactive when stuff like this happens.
He's a good guy!
So he's a class clown who isn't
good at anything but making a scene.
Hm? What's the matter? Go on.
Uh, Yamato is really level-headed
and a super good listener.
He does things at his own pace and
puts people at ease. He's a good guy!
So you're saying that he's dense and indecisive. Next.
Ooka is really great with people! He's good-natured
and always helping someone out when they're in trouble.
He's a good...
Reader of people's moods like a weathervane. Yeah?
Any one of these people could be the culprit.
What Hayama has said doesn't
really give me much to go on, exactly.
What do you two think of the three suspects we have?
Huh? That's a bit hard for me to say, really...
I don't really know those guys enough to judge yet.
Then, would you mind looking into them for me?
Hm. Sure...
Sorry.
I understand it's not a pleasant thing to do.
I'll do it.
Huh?
It's not like I care what the
rest of the class thinks of me.
Plus, finding fault in people is one of my 108 talents.
Then I guess I won't expect too much.
I'll do it, too then!
I can't just leave this to Hikki, after all!
Besides, I can't ignore a
request coming from you, Yukinon!
Oh?
I'll do my best!
You sure are good friends.
Those two are, yes.
I meant you, too, Hikitani.
What is he talking about?
There's no Hikitani in this club.
Huh?
Okay then, for now, you don't have to do anything.
Well, that's a big load off.
What are you going to do, anyway?
I'll see what the girls have to say.
After all, girls know more about
how everyone in the class gets along.
And if I bring up someone they dislike,
then they'll get all into it
and tell me all kinds of stuff.
Girl talk is super scary...
Anyway, as I've said, I've got
this, so don't worry about it!
Well, if I tried to question any people, the
punchline would be them asking, "Who are you?"
It's all yours.
Great!
Okay!
Huh?
Yeah, so like, Tobe, Ooka, and Yamato,
they're acting kinda weird lately, huh?
What do you think is going on there?
That's getting straight to the point...
I don't remember you being
the type to say stuff like that?
Huh?
You know, that probably wasn't one of your smartest ideas.
You shouldn't being saying damaging
stuff like that about your good friends.
Oh no! That's not what I meant...
It's just been on my mind lately.
Really? Then do you have a crush on one of them?
What?! Absolutely not!
I mean, there is someone on my mind, but that's just a...
You have a crush on someone?
Come on, tell me who it is! I'll help!
I told you, that's not it at all!
I just wanted to know what kind of relationship they have!
I hear you.
So that's been on your mind, as well?
I feel the same way.
Yeah! Like, it seems awkward or something, right?
Personally I think... but seriously...
Tobi's definitely the uke!
Huh?
And Yamato is the seme, and Ooka is the inviting uke!
There's definitely something going on in that triangle!
One things for sure!
All three of them are totally after Hayato!
Am I right or what?!
All three stepping aside for the sake of their friends!
That has to be it!
You know what, girl, you're way cuter when
you're quiet, Ebina, so learn to blend in.
And wipe the blood from your nose.
Sorry! I couldn't find anything out!
Well, you were doing several
things wrong right from the beginning.
I'll do it next.
Do what next? What do you mean?
You're going to go ask around?
No. I'm gonna watch.
Huh?
I will now disclose one of my
108 talents: Human Observation.
Only about 30% of human communication is language.
The other 70% is gathering information
from eye movements and other subtle gestures.
In other words, I can actually achieve 70% of
communication while remaining alone and silent.
Right? Never mind.
Hm?
Good morning!
I want you to make miso soup for me every morning.
What? Why's that?
Uh, nothing. Ignore me. I was half asleep.
Did you want something?
Have you decided on your group for the work thing?
Have you?
Who me?
I, um, I've already decided. Yeah.
I figured. Totsuka's in the tennis club.
With all the connections he has there, it's
not surprising if he has friends in this class.
As for me, on the other hand...
Now that I think about it...
Actually, scratch that, I don't even have to
think about it. I don't have any guy friends.
Um, really?
You know, I'm a boy, right, Hikigaya.
Does he really think we can be called "friends"?
Friends are like, well, for instance...
Did you decide where you were going yet?
Yeah, man. I think either media
or maybe foreign investments.
Damn, dude! You're really looking
ahead towards your future, huh?!
But I guess we should be at our age.
It seems I totally respect my parents nowadays.
So gonna be serious from now on, are ya?
Whoa, dude! But we can't ever forget
our boyish hearts and devilish good looks!
Maybe friendship is all about being able to
talk to each other about your youth like that.
I could never do it, though. I'd burst out laughing.
They call each other by their first names, as if they're
saying this is proof that they're friends or something.
Saika...
Huh?
Uh, sorry... Forget I ever...
I'm so happy!
That's the first time you've called me by my first name.
What the hell?
Then can I perhaps call you "Hikki"?
That would be a no.
Well, then... Hachiman?
Oh. Say that three times.
Hachiman...
Hachiman?
Hachiman!
Are you even listening?!
Wait! What?
Oh! What were we talking about?
What is it?
Sorry... I just wondered if you'd found anything out.
Not yet.
Ah!
Something the matter?
I've solved all the mysteries within.
Well? Did you figure something out?
I don't know who the culprit is,
but I did figure out one thing about them.
That group of three is considered Hayama's group.
Huh? Why are you even saying that?
Uh... What do you mean?
Sorry, I said that all wrong.
I mean, they only hang out for Hayama's sake.
I don't think that's right...
Hayama, tell me have you ever seen those
three hang out together without you being around?
Well, no, I haven't...
When it's just the three of them,
they don't really get along at all.
In simpler terms, then,
Hayama is the one considered to be their friend,
whereas the other three guys, they're
just seen as friends of a friend.
Oh, I totally get that now.
When the person who keeps the
conversation going isn't there, it's awkward.
You don't know what to do, so
you start messing with your phone.
Hm...
Let's just assume what you say is true on all accounts.
It still only reinforces their motive to bring one down.
If we can't pin down the culprit,
the issue will never be fully resolved.
Hayama, if you want, I think I can
solve this mess you've gotten into.
I know a way those three can become friends...
and without searching for the culprit.
Not only that, but without anyone
having to resort to fighting each other.
Wanna know how?
Hm? By the way, like we were talking about before...
Can I sit here?
Hm?
You settled it all so peacefully. I appreciate it.
It's not like I really had to do anything.
The truth is, I didn't do a thing.
I just thought I'd drag Hayama
down the road to being alone.
The reason those three looked like they wanted to fight...
was because they all wanted to be with Hayama.
So all you have to do is remove the cause.
In other words, take Hayama out of the picture.
I tell you what, they sure were surprised
when I said I wouldn't team up with them.
But... I hope this will be a chance for
them to become friends and not depend on me.
That'd be nice.
Honestly, being this nice must
be some kind of demented illness.
Hey, man, you don't have a group yet, right?
Want to team up?
What is he, an American?
O-okay.
Damn it, that made me respond like an American...
Ow, man...
Totsuka, what's with you?
What about me? Hachiman!
What? What do you mean?
But, uh, you said you already had your te-
I meant, I decided right from the start
that I was going to group up with you!
There. Thanks for that.
At least you get my name right when you write it...
Hachiman!
Huh?
What day should we go?
Is this what other people call "friends"?
I'm gonna go wherever you go, Hayato.
No way! Hayama, you're going there?
I think I'll go there, too!
Hayato, you're so awesome!
I'm going!
Me, too!
Well... it's one of those things that
can disappear anywhere, and anytime.
But it seems like Taishi's sister
has developed some bad behavior lately.
Are you stupid?
Black lace?
In other words, she changed after
being put in the same class as Hikigaya?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Master.
I'm sorry, who were you again?
Meow. Meow!
Okay, none of that made sense.
Next time: "Once Again, He Turns
Back on the Path from Whence He Came."