Youth is a lie. It is nothing but evil.
Check this one out!
Heh.
Those who look to rejoice in their youth
deceive themselves and those around them,
accepting in full the circumstances that devour them.
Here.
In the face of the great and reverend word "youth,"
they will twist any common interpretation
or accepted notion out of recognition.
In their minds, lies, secrets, sins, and even failure
are nothing more than the "spice of youth."
If failure is truly the designated mark of one's youth...
Hey, is that you?
then would it not be considered abnormal for one
not in his youth to still fail at befriending anyone?
Come on, let's go!
But I'm sure none of them would admit to that being true.
They only define "youth" to their own benefit.
In conclusion, I leave you with this:
All you fools who delight in youth...
drop dead.
You're the one who needs to drop dead.
Look, Hikigaya,
can you tell me what the
assignment was I gave you in class?
Well, you wanted us to write an essay
about looking back on our high school days.
And how exactly did that lead you
to turn in this smart-ass essay to me?
What is this? How did that theme result in this?
Well...
Seriously...
Look at you...
You have eyes like a dead fish.
Do I look that rich in omega-3s?
It makes me sound pretty smart.
I'm being serious.
Uh, but I am looking back on my
high school days, just like you said!
Isn't that how we kids think? I mean, at least nowadays.
You brat... Just cut the crap, okay?
You just call me brat?
Well, I guess I could understand how
someone your age would think that I'm a-
Didn't anyone ever teach you
that you never talk about a woman's age?
I'm sorry about that. I'll rewrite-Huh?
I think you had better come with me.
Huh?
Oh...
Hello, Ms. Hiratsuka.
I believe I asked for you to knock before entering.
Even when I do bother to knock, you never deign to answer.
That's because you always come in
before I have a chance to respond.
And this?
Who's the space case?
Guh!
Oh crap, I know who this girl is.
International liberal arts, class J.
The class is 90% girls, since
they score higher than average,
and most know it to be a "very colorful" class.
And the one with the most color of the lot...
is Yukino Yukinoshita.
Everyone at this school knows her.
He wants to join your club.
Uh, Hachiman Hikigaya. Class 2-F.
So, um...
What do you mean, I want to join?
Suck it up.
I'm making you join this club as
punishment for your smart-ass essay.
You will give me no arguments,
protests, questions, or backtalk.
So then, I'm sure you can see by now, his
personality is as rotten as the look in his eyes.
This makes him a pathetic soul who is perpetually lonely.
I want this club to fix his contrary, solitary nature.
That's my request.
I must decline.
Just looking at the ulterior motives behind
that lewd gaze of his makes me fear for my life.
I am not looking at those modest breasts of hers.
Seriously, I'm not.
Don't worry. He's a decent guy
with a good grasp on risk and return
and he has a need for self-preservation.
He wouldn't dare do anything
worthy of criminal punishment.
Trust me, this thug attitude is an act.
I'd rather you just say that I can
make rational decisions for myself...
Thug attitude? But of course.
She's not even listening, and she's convinced!
Well, if it's your request, then I
can't very well refuse, now can I?
I'll allow him to join.
Perfect.
Good luck, Yukinoshita!
Uh, what?
Come on, are you serious? What just happened?!
A bittersweet memory suddenly came back to me.
Can we just stay friends for now?
Forget being friends. After that, we never spoke again.
I mean, seriously, romantic comedies
don't actually happen in my life.
Someone as rigorously trained as me would
never get caught in a rom-com trap like this.
Girls only take interest in attractive guys
and indulge in impure relationships.
In other words, they're my enemies.
Do you mind if we just stay friends for now?
Being hated is the fastest way for
me to avoid feeling like that again.
So, in lieu of pleasantries, I
decided to intimidate Yukinoshita.
Uh...
Quit standing there and just sit down.
Huh? Uh, right! Sorry.
Problem?
Uh, it's just...
I'm pretty confused about all this.
What kind of club is this supposed to be?
Try and give it a guess.
Literary club?
Oh? Why you say that?
Well that's easy, this room has no
particular backdrop and no special equipment.
Plus, you've been reading a book this whole time.
You're wrong.
Then what type of club is it?
So, what I'm doing here right
now is this club's exact activity.
Then I give up. I have no clue.
Hikigaya, how long has it been
since you spoke with a girl?
Guh!
I believe it was two years ago, in June.
God, it's so hot today, right?
More like humid, I would say.
Huh?
Well, yeah...
A compassionate few donate their
time... to those who are less fortunate.
Society calls it "volunteer work."
We extend a helping hand to those in need.
That is what this club does.
This is the Service Club. I welcome you.
And as I have been asked, I will fulfill my duty.
I will come to fix that little problem of yours.
Show some gratitude.
Are you serious?
My problem?
So you know, I'm damn efficient in my own special way.
I was third on the Japanese ability test.
And I'm pretty good-looking.
Ignoring that I have no friends or
girlfriend, I'm in a pretty high league!
In a way, it's impressive you
can say all that so confidently.
You're weird. I'm already creeped out.
Shut up! You're the weirdo!
Based on my observations so far,
it seems the loneliness that plagues you
is simply a direct result of your
stupid pride and contrary sensitivity.
As for your appearance, beauty
is in the eye of the beholder.
In other words, as of right
now, only what I say is correct.
Your opinion's ridiculous,
but it feels like you're making some sense.
Now, that completes this conversation simulation test.
What?!
If you can actually converse
with a beautiful girl like me,
then I believe you will be able
to talk with most anyone else.
So, do you think I have I fixed you a bit?
Just so you know, it's not like I
can't talk to people or anything.
I just don't make pointless small talk.
So, you see, I don't need to be "fixed."
Well I believe you're at a level that
will make living in society difficult for you.
I'm coming in, Yukinoshita.
I said knock...
Yeah, sorry.
Sounds like you're having some trouble
rectifying our little friend here, huh?
It's because he isn't aware he has a problem.
No, it's not.
What in the hell?
Why is everyone always telling me to change? I
don't want other people trying to tell me who to be.
That's how you run from your problems, isn't it?
Changing is a way of running
from your problems, too, isn't it?
Why can't you just accept someone for
who they are and what's in their past?
That won't...
'Cause that's not gonna solve anyone's worries...
nor will it save anyone.
Just relax, you guys.
You might not know,
but it's a time-honored shonen manga custom to
try and settle conflicting opinions with a showdown.
What are you even talking about?
I want there to be a showdown... to see
which one of you can do the most acts of service!
You're way too intense...
Well then, how about we let the winner
make the loser do anything they want.
By "anything," does she mean what
I think she means by "anything"?!
I must decline. Doing so with him as my
opponent would make me fear for my life.
That's sexist!
Sexy stuff is not the only thing guys like me think about!
We also think about... world peace?
Actually, I don't think about much else...
I guess even Yukinoshita has her fears.
I never thought I would say this...
but are you that afraid you'll lose?
Fine then. I cannot believe I'm
falling for such cheap provocation,
but I will accept.
Then that's that!
Don't I get a say in this?
Huh?
Well, hello again.
I didn't think you'd come back.
Are you a masochist, then?
No.
A stalker, then?
Why are you assuming that I'm harboring
some sort of illicit feelings for you?
So, you don't?
No!
Your overconfidence is weird, even to me.
Let me guess... you don't have any friends?
Well, then first why don't you explain to me where
the definition of "friend" begins and where it ends-
Please, say no more. That's exactly
something someone would say with no friends.
Because I'd say that.
You seem like a likable girl, so then how
can you have no friends? What's your problem?
Yeah there's no way you could understand.
I've always been considered really pretty...
Guh!
So any guy who has gotten close to
me has done so with ulterior motives.
How can people like you say you're lonely?
You're a disgrace to lonely people everywhere.
If everyone actually had liked me,
perhaps then I would have been alright.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
In grade school, my indoor shoes were
taken and hidden from me about sixty times.
Fifty of those times were done by other girls.
And it was all thanks to them that I had to
take my indoor shoes and my recorder home every day.
Sounds like you had a rough time.
Yes, it was rough.
It was because I'm pretty.
Ah...
But then, it can't be helped, can it?
Although, nobody can be considered perfect.
People are weak, they're ugly, they
get jealous and try to bring others down.
Oddly enough, the better you
are, the harder it is to live.
Don't you think that's wrong somehow?
But I can and will change it...
and all the people within this world.
You're putting too much effort into a crazy cause.
Oh, you think so?
Well, I think it's better than your
efforts to dry up and fade into nothing.
You know, I hate the way you
accept your weakness as a positive...
It's stupid.
Yukinoshita carries the pain of
someone who has more than others.
It shouldn't be too hard to hide that
and go through life lying to everyone.
After all, that's what people do in this world.
But Yukinoshita doesn't do that.
She would never lie to herself.
"I'm sure she and I are alike in some way."
I couldn't help thinking that, in spite of myself.
Even the silence in that moment felt comfortable...
like it belonged.
I felt like my heart inside me was wanting
to race faster than even the second hand...
itching to press forward.
Then...
Then she and I...
Hey, Yukinoshita...
If you want, I'll be...
your frien-
Yeah, that's not gonna happen, sorry.
What? But I wasn't even finished telling you what I...
Come in.
E-excuse me!
So, Ms. Hiratsuka sent me here...
Wha... What is Hikki doing in this room?!
Well, um... I'm a member of this club.
Wait, is "Hikki" supposed to be me?
Also, who is she?
Yui Yuigahama of class 2-F, correct?
Well, have a seat.
Wow! You actually know who I am?
I bet you've memorized the name of every student.
Not so. If you remember, I didn't know who you were.
How could I forget?
You don't have to feel bad.
I can only blame the weakness of my heart for
wanting to avert my eyes from your existence.
Are you trying to make me feel better?
No, I'm being sarcastic.
This club...
looks like a lot of fun!
And, Hikki, you're sure talking a lot.
Huh? Uh, no, sorry! What I meant to say is...
You're just totally different
from the way you are in class.
I mean, you usually act sort of weird and creepy.
You little slut.
What?! Who are you calling a slut?! I'm still a virgin-
Oh! Uh, ah! Never mind!
It's really nothing to be embarrassed about.
What I mean is that... you...
What are you saying?!
I'm a second-year! It's super embarrassing!
Shouldn't you be a little girlier than this?
Such values are pointless.
I don't know, saying something like
"girlier" sounds pretty slutty to me.
Stop it! Calling someone a slut is so
not cool! You're such a creep, Hikki!
Calling someone a slut has nothing to do with creepiness.
Stop calling me Hikki, slut.
Wha... Huh?
You are so damn creepy!
I can't believe you would say that!
What? Cookies?
Apparently our friend here would like
to make homemade cookies for someone.
But she's not very confident, so she wants our help.
This is her request.
Uh, why don't you ask your friends to help you with this?
Y-yeah, well, I...
I don't really want any of them to know.
And it's just that it'd be...
weird acting serious with them.
I guess... I see.
And besides, I heard from Ms. Hiratsuka...
that this club is supposed to
grant students' wishes, right?
Not quite. The Service Club only assists people.
We don't just give fish to starving people. We
teach them how to fish so they can be independent.
Th-that's kinda amazing.
That's crooked. Can't you even
manage to put on an apron correctly?
Sorry. Thanks.
And? What am I supposed to do here?
You can taste them and offer your opinions.
How in the world can someone
really mess up so much and so often?
It looks kind of like the charcoal
they sell at the hardware store.
I feel like the royal tester.
I didn't put poison in it!
It might be poisonous, though.
We won't die, right?
Well, let's think on how to improve this.
How about, "Yuigahama never cooks again"?
That's how you're planning to solve things?!
Maybe you're right, then...
I suppose I'm not cut out for cooking.
I guess I just don't have... the talent needed.
The only solution is to try harder.
Yuigahama, you just said you
don't have any talent, correct?
Uh...
Try changing your perception.
People who don't apply even minimal effort have
no right to go around and envy those with talent.
Unsuccessful people are unsuccessful because they can't
imagine the effort that successful people have invested.
Yeah... But lately, everyone
says they don't even cook like this.
This just isn't who we are...
Could you find it within yourself to
stop trying to match everyone around you?
It's terribly annoying.
Aren't you embarrassed waiting for others to tell you
why you're awkward, clumsy, or foolish? I mean, come on.
You're...
You're so cool...
Huh?!
You don't say anything superficial.
Actually... that's kind of cool, you know?
W-were you even listening to me?
I believe I was being rather harsh to you...
Yeah, your words were kind of harsh and all,
but I felt that's how you actually feel.
All I've ever done is just try to be like everyone else.
Sorry! Next time, I'll do it right!
Teach her the right way. Show her what to do.
I'll give you a demonstration. Do exactly as I do.
Mm!
Totally different...
How am I supposed to make you understand?
I don't get it. Why are you guys
trying to make cookies that taste good?
Huh?
What are you saying?
Come back to this room in about ten minutes.
I'll show you some real handmade
cookies you've never experienced before.
Now it's my turn in the showdown.
These are what you call "real" handmade cookies?
These things don't taste very good!
You think so? Sorry. I'll toss them.
W-wait a second! You don't
have to go and toss them all out!
I mean, they're really not that terrible!
Yeah? Well, these are the bad cookies you made, actually.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Here's a relevant little story I
once heard about a friend of a friend.
There was a girl he knew who'd tell
him everything that happened to her.
"I thou-I mean, he thought," This must
mean she likes me! I've got it made!"
So he made up his mind, and he asked her.
Hey, so who is it that you like
in our school? Just his initials!
Huh?!
H...
"H"?!
That's my initial... Is it me?!
What are you talking about?
You're being creepy. Would you stop?
Wait a minute.
So that's a personal experience of yours?
Hey, now! I told you, it was a friend of a friend!
Oh, please. And just what are we
supposed to take from that anyway?
I don't know.
I guess that guys are just simple and stuff.
They'll get the wrong idea if you so much as talk to them,
and they'll be happy just to
get handmade cookies from you.
So they don't have to taste good.
They don't taste good? Well, shut up!
As long as he knows you tried your very best,
wouldn't that make him like you?
I would think that's the response you're looking for.
Is that how it's supposed to work?
Would it work on you, Hikki?
Huh? Sure, it'd work great on me.
And stop calling me "Hikki," okay?
So, what are you going to do, Yuigahama?
Yeah, I think that I'm going
to go ahead and try it my way.
Thanks, again, Yukinoshita!
Did we really do the right thing?
Did we handle Yuigahama's request?
What are you yakking about?
I think if you really want to
improve yourself in some way,
you should go out there and
try to challenge your own limits.
And maybe that would have probably benefitted
Yuigahama most in the end, don't you think?
Your efforts will never betray you.
But they can always come betray your dreams.
Huh?
Not all dreams will come true through effort.
Actually, most of them won't even come true.
But if you tried your best, you can take solace in that.
That's self-satisfaction.
You're naive. It's creepy.
Hm?
Hello, guys!
You need something?
What? Am I no longer welcome to come in here?
Yukinoshita, do you hate me?
But why?
I wouldn't say I hate you.
You're just not my type.
That means the same thing in girl-speak, you know!
So, did you need something?
This is thanks for the other day.
I made cookies!
But I'm not really hungry...
Man, it's pretty fun once you give it a try!
Maybe I'll try making a boxed lunch next time.
Oh, and, Yukinon, let's eat
lunch in the club room together!
No, thanks... I like to eat my lunch
alone, so I think I'll pass on that offer.
And "Yukinon" creeps me out, so don't-
Also, Yukinon, I'm free after school,
so I'll help with the club! It'll be fun!
Yeah, this is, what would you call it? To say thanks!
Are you listening? Yuigahama?
Hikki!
Hm?
Ah! Huh?
I just want to show... my thanks.
You helped me just as much last week.
Well, this sure looks like something ominous.
It feels like some kind of bad omen...
but I'll accept it with gratitude.
And stop calling me "Hikki."
That indecisive attitude of
yours is really getting annoying.
Sorry. I thought you were an ape trying to intimidate me.
I am disgusted with you, Hachiman!
That's just a delusion of grandeur.
Delusion of grandeur?
Yukinon, run!
I think I understand.
You'd like us to cure you of this illness, right?
I am the Kengo Shogun, Yoshiteru Zaimokuza!
Next time: "All People Surely Have Their Own Worries."