The wind... It's really picking up out there.
Yeah.
Sure is.
What... the hell?
Are you confused about something here?
Since it's time for you to get to your next class,
and everyone was dragging their
feet on selecting committee members...
I just moved it along and picked you.
It's your own fault for sleeping so
soundly through your long homeroom period.
Yeah, but that's because, uh...
Move along. Can't start class with you up here.
You need to choose the rest after school.
So who wants to be the female representative?
Show of hands.
If this isn't decided, we'll use rock-paper-scissors...
What?
Is there a lot of hard work involved?
It's not usually a lot of hard
work if you do it right, but...
the female representative might
have it a bit tougher this time around.
Sorry, I'm the male rep, four eyes.
Hmm...
Honestly, it would be a big help if you decided to do it.
You're popular, after all. I think you'd be perfect.
Thanks for the compliment, but I'm not really all that...
Hey, Yui, I think you should do it.
Sounds like a nice time to me.
Two good friends planning such
an event together sounds so fun!
Huh?!
Uh, I already told you it's not like that...
Well actually, Yui's supposed flag down
customers with me, so she can't be our rep.
Oh, isn't that convenient?
Flagging down customers is important, too.
That's right! Flagging down customers is important!
Wait, I'm flagging down customers?!
So, uh, what you're saying is
you want someone that's popular
but also has good leadership skills, is that correct?
I think Sagami should do it, then.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
I think Sagami would do a good job.
What? No way! Me? I don't think I could do it!
Hey, now... You might fool them, but you
can't fool this first-rate refusal appraiser.
When a girl turns down something for real,
her eyes look colder and she's practically expressionless.
Seriously, not in this lifetime.
That's what they say.
They're so scary, you think your heart
will freeze solid, and you just want to die.
Pretty please? Could you do it for us?
Uh...
Well, if nobody else wants to take
the role, then I guess I have to do it.
But really, you guys, me?
The cultural festival planning committee
is now called to its first session.
My name is Meguri Shiromeguri.
And I am your current student council president.
Okay, so let's get right to work by
first electing our committee chairman.
Does anyone want to run for the position?
Um... You're Yukinoshita, aren't you?
Yes.
I knew it! You're Haru's sister, aren't you?
She was the planning committee chairman, too.
That festival was so great, it went
down in history as one of the best ever!
As Haru's sister, I bet you'd
be just as good she was, right?
I'll do my best as a committee member, thank you.
Ah...
Oh...
Uh...
Huh?
Ah...
If no one really wants to do it...
I could take on the chairmain's position.
Really?! You're, uh...
Minami Sagami from class 2-F.
I don't know just yet if I'll be
any good at being a leader, but...
I am kind of interested in that sort of thing...
I guess what I'm saying is I'd like to use
the cultural festival as an opportunity to grow.
That's great!
And why do we get the pleasure of having to help you grow?
So, if we have no other
candidates, are we okay with Sagami?
I just ended up becoming the committee chairman!
You're fine.
Don't worry, Sagami, I know you can do it.
And we'll help!
That's right, we will!
Thanks, guys, though I think I might
have said some really embarrassing stuff!
Oh, no way! You were great!
Huh?
You know, I was a little surprised
to hear you were on the committee team.
Well, I suppose... I can see why.
I would actually find it way more surprising if you
were the one who joined the planning committee, Yui.
That'd totally be out of character, right?!
Hey.
What about me? I was half forced into it.
I see.
Huh?
So, doesn't the committee meet every day?
I guess that means I'll probably have to start
helping with the class projects from now on...
Yeah, I won't be able to come
to the club for a while, either.
This is perfect timing.
So I've been thinking...
and wanted us to discuss this issue today.
In my opinion, we should suspend club
activities until the cultural festival is over.
That makes sense to me.
Yeah, I guess... After all...
You should focus on the cultural festival until it's over.
Well then, I suppose we're done for today.
Okay.
We're sorry to interrupt you.
Ms. Hiratsuka told me before we came...
But I didn't know you guys were in the Service Club!
What a surprise this is!
Do you need something?
As you know, I took on the role
of planning committee chairman.
The problem is I'm not very confident...
So I would like your help to improve.
Your goal of personal growth...
I believe that your request for confidence
building somewhat deviates from your goal.
You're right about that, but I think the worst
thing to do would be to cause problems for everyone else.
I don't want to mess up, you know?
Besides, I think that working with someone
to achieve something is considered growth too.
So, to summarize, you're asking
me to help you, is that right?
Ah! That's it!
Oh? Then that sounds good to me.
Huh?
Since I'm on the planning committee as well.
I'll provide whatever help I can within that realm.
Wow, you will? Thank you so much!
All right!
I thought we were halting Service Club.
This is something I'm doing personally.
It's not something you two need to worry about.
But, usually...
This is how I do things.
Besides, I have a fair understanding of
the cultural festival planning committee.
It would just be more efficient
for me to do it this on my own.
Efficient, huh?
Well, I don't feel good about this at all!
Dammit, I just... I just...
Wait up. So what on Earth is wrong with you now?
I don't know! Gah!
It's just, something feels off about this!
It's Yukinon. She usually isn't like that!
I guess you could be right.
Same goes for you!
To be honest, I don't really feel
comfortable with what Sagami is doing either.
And then with Yukinon agreeing to her request...
and trying to be nice to her...
I think I might actually like Yukinon
a whole lot more more than I thought.
Wow, did not know that you were a member of that team.
No! I didn't mean it that way!
You promised, remember? You said
you'd help Yukinon if there's trouble!
Well, I will if I can...
You will? I already feel better.
I'm not sure I like being trusted so unconditionally.
Okay, I'm gonna head off to class now.
Good luck with everything!
Let's begin the meeting everyone.
Publicity, why don't you start
us all off with your report.
For the posters announcing the
festival, I'd say we're halfway done.
Oh, really? Sounds like it's going well!
No, that's a bit slow.
Huh?
Do you know where you're gonna hang them?
What about the festival homepage, have you updated that?
Uh, not yet...
Okay. Well, please hurry. The posters can wait.
However, prospective students and their
parents check the school homepage regularly,
so it's important that it reflects current activities.
O-okay.
Sagami, moving on.
O-oh...
Okay then, volunteer coordinator go ahead.
Yes, uh... We currently have
ten volunteer groups participating.
Wow, it's gone up! Must be the Regional award.
Okay, next...
Is that within the school only?
Have you approached any locals yet?
As long as we're emphasizing our connection with local
residents, we must avoid a decline in their participation.
And please remember, submit a time table,
Summarizing the allotment of stage time
as well as staff assignments at the time of the opening.
Wow, you're so amazing!
Just what I expected from Haru's sister!
She's like a chairman.
Uh, no, don't confuse me with her...
I think she should just do it all.
Okay, up next is general records.
Be sure to submit the festival day schedule
as well as any equipment requests.
What... the hell?
Need an explanation?
Heh!
No way. I can't do it.
What?! Listen, if there was a Hayama
& Hachiman manga, it'd be a must-buy!
In fact, it's a must-gay!
What the hell is she talking about?
The scene opens with the prince making a move
on the sulky pilot with his warm innocent words...
Swoon!
Isn't that the whole appeal of this story?!
It's not that kind of story.
You're gonna piss off the French.
Well, I'm on the planning committee.
He's right. You need rehearsals
and stuff to put on a musical.
This really doesn't seem very realistic.
Oh, yeah... That's too bad...
Hey, how about this?
Maybe just take the whole thing and reconsider the story.
Like, who is the prince!
So that was really his goal...
Hmph!
It loses some of the sulky factor,
but this should work nicely.
So you're saying I still have to be in this thing...
Oh! That sulky attitude is perfect!
So, the only thing left to figure out are the costumes.
Ah, don't worry! We have Kawasaki!
Huh? You mean me?
I know about you!
You're the girl who's always altering
your uniforms and blazers, aren't you?
I can also tell your scrunchie's handmade!
It's made by hand, by me...
I can also use a sewing machine too.
Welcome aboard!
This seems like it's going to be really hard for me...
Do you think I'm a good fit?
I think you'll be perfect.
Totsuka...
Oh, well, see you later, Hachiman.
Sure.
Guess I'll just have to do my part.
That's too funny!
Sorry, I thought it was a good idea!
Especially since we don't have enough local volunteers,
I figured this was a good solution.
Did you know that in her third year,
your sister volunteered to play in a band?!
Ms. Hiratsuka was even a part of it!
It was so amazing...
I'm aware of that. I was watching.
Oh, stop the reminiscing, Meguri,
we were just having a bit of fun.
You don't mind this, do you, Yukino?
I'm just wanting to make sure I do
everything I can for my adorable little sister.
Ah!
You can do whatever you want.
It's not my place to decide.
What do you mean?
I thought you were the planning committee's chairman.
Then who is the chairman?
Sorry I'm late!
I stopped in to check on my class and got delayed a bit!
Haruno, this is our current chairman.
Oh, hi! I'm Sagami.
Hmm...
The festival planning committee chairman was
late because she was checking on her class, hmm?
Uh, I was...
I think that is exactly how the chairman should be!
Someone who can really enjoy the cultural festival
to the fullest is best qualified to be the chairman.
Ah, thank you for saying that!
Sure! So I have a favor to ask of you, chairman.
I really want to participate as a festival volunteer.
But Yukino brushed me off...
That'd be great! We're actually short on volunteers.
Yay! Thanks so much!
So does this take care of connecting with the locals?
Oh hey, it's Hikigaya!
Ya-hello there!
Well, I'm a little surprised. I didn't
think you were the type to join stuff like this.
Yeah... that's kinda what I thought too.
But speaking of surprises,
wouldn't you say the same
thing might apply to your sister?
No, I expect her to do this sort of thing.
I mean, it must be hard for her to hang around the club
since I was the planning
committee chairman back in the day.
She has plenty of reasons for
wanting to be a part of this.
Hey, everyone, can I have your attention?
So, I've been giving this a lot of thought.
I believe a planning committee should
also be about enjoying the festival.
Like, we can't make other people have fun
if we're not having fun ourselves, right?
I think we're making good progress with our plans,
and doing a good job keeping up in our classes.
With that, I think we should
slow down our work pace just a bit.
Sagami, I don't think you're
looking at this the right way.
We should be working ahead so we'll have a buffer-
Yeah, everyone worked too hard on their
parts back when I was the chairman, as well.
Yukinoshita...
I don't know what happened between you and your sister,
but shouldn't we learn from those who came before us?
You should put your own feelings
aside and consider everyone else.
Wow, you sure seem to know what to say!
Right?
Hmph.
These, too, please.
Seems Sagami's suggestion was wrong.
I'm thinking I probably should've turned it down.
Sorry about this.
We're just going to have to share the work
amongst everyone or we won't finish in time.
Excuse me.
I'm here to submit a volunteer application.
Applications go in the back.
Okay, thanks.
Hm?
Do you have enough help here?
I'm not exactly sure where things stand overall.
We already have our hands full
just managing our own posts.
What do you mean your posts?
My post is general records.
Oh... Makes sense.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
But from what I can see here,
it looks like Yukinoshita is doing most of the work.
It's just more efficient this way.
Yeah, but you're about to fall apart.
You should really rely on others before it comes to that.
I'll want to help.
I can handle the volunteer coordination.
Just call me the volunteer representative. Sound good?
He's actually right, you know...
You've gotta be able to rely on others sometimes.
At times like this, even Haru would...
Neither Hayama nor Meguri are incorrect,
but they're also not entirely correct in this situation.
They're great. I'm moved.
What heartwarming camaraderie.
But is doing things alone really a bad thing?
Collaboration isn't a guarantee.
So why should someone who's always
worked hard on their own be denied?
I can't allow that to happen here.
I...
Maybe relying on others is important,
but relying on others is all you
people ever wanna do around here.
Oh! Well, more specifically I was talking about me, okay?
I mean like, people who come and just
feel they can dump all their work on me.
I don't get to relax, and I know that can't be helped...
Therefore...
I don't think it'd be fair to let
anyone else here take it easy either.
Ok then, you're really terrible.
Hey, I can help you too.
It does look like a lot of the
record keeping has shifted to you.
I'll rethink the workload allocations.
As for relying on the help of others,
Shiromeguri has made her thoughts clear.
I gratefully accept it.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Great! We're almost there!
Push hard, and do our best!
Sorry I'm late, everyone!
Oh, hi, Hayama! What are you doing here?
Oh, hey there. So, were you off with the class just now?
Yeah, I was!
Sagami.
Ah?
These need your approval.
I've already gone through them
all and corrected the errors.
Okay. Thanks.
Actually, I'll just give you
my seal, so you can stamp them.
I want to delegate this to you. Here.
Okay...
No problem. I'll go ahead and
do all the approving from now on.
The day goes by so fast when you're having so much fun!
Thanks for your hard work, everyone!
Yeah! Thank you, everyone!
Huh? That's not the normal noises I usually hear in there.
You actually sound tired.
Hm? Hey, Hikigaya,
do you know where Yukinon is?
No.
Yukinoshita is out. She called in sick today.
Huh?
I didn't understand anything!
I shouldn't have been deceived by his words.
It's just that he smelled so
nice, and he was always shining.
You couldn't help it. You're still so young.
You just didn't know how to love him yet.
Buh! Gah!
Next time: "And So the Curtain on Each Stage Rises,
and the Festival is Festivaling as Hard as It Can."