It's already been a week...
It was a total fluke that I saved your dog, you know.
Even if I hadn't gotten into that
accident, I probably still would've been alone.
If that's why you're being nice... then just stop it.
Why did it turn out like this?
Jerk.
Wait! Sable!
It's so hot...
Hm?
Hey.
Uh... hey.
Okay. Super cool.
I've managed a complete reset.
By resetting our relationship
like this, I regain my inner peace,
and Yuigahama is free from her sense of obligation,
so she can return to her fulfilling daily life.
This definitely wasn't the wrong choice.
No, I know it's the right one.
So this whole matter is said and done with.
We just have to reset and go back to our respective lives.
You can't reset life, but you
can reset human relationships.
Source: My own experience.
I haven't contacted any of my
classmates from middle school-
Wait, that wasn't a reset. That was a delete.
So, something happen with you and Yuigahama?
Nope, nothing.
I don't think Yuigahama would stop coming
here if nothing happened between you two.
Did you have a fight?
No, we didn't... I don't think so.
Anyway, we couldn't have...
fighting is something you do
with people you're friends with.
So it wasn't so much a fight as...
A dispute?
Nope, but that doesn't sound too far off.
Then, maybe a war?
That's completely wrong... and further off.
An annihilation.
Were you even listening? You're further.
Different opinions... Is that about right?
Something like that.
Well... Nothing we can do then.
What, Yuigahama's not here again?
Do you not know how to knock?
And here I was holding in some hope for that girl...
Um, Teacher, did you want something from us?
That's right, Hikigaya! I certainly do.
I think we should make that showdown a battle royale.
A battle royale? Just the two of us?
You can go ahead and recruit new members if you need to.
Doesn't look like Yuigahama's returning.
It's not as if Yuigahama has just quit...
Not coming to the club is quitting.
No need to waste time on any unmotivated members.
Anyone who doesn't attend can leave.
U-um... Can I leave?
I have neither motivation nor discipline.
Huh?
I-I didn't think so.
Anyway, thanks to Yuigahama,
I now know that a club is more
active when it has more members.
Here's an opportunity.
You're to go out there and actively recruit at least one
new member with both motivation and discipline by Monday.
Got it?
You can...
start now.
Yeah, this is tyranny.
Perish the thought.
I'm only trying to help in my own special way.
Ms. Hiratsuka, I just want to confirm...
You want us to increase our membership, right?
That's right, Yukinoshita.
I wish you luck.
How does she think we're
supposed to increase our membership?
I have an idea of someone who might just be interested.
Who? Totsuka?
Totsuka? Totsuka, right?
Yuigahama.
Huh? But isn't she quitting?
If she quits, then she just has to join again.
Ms. Hiratsuka said we only need to
increase our membership, not who we bring in.
Will she come back that easily?
When someone leaves, they usually just don't come back.
The date June 18th... ring any bells?
No...
It's Yuigahama's birthday. I think.
Her email address has 0618 in it.
But you've never actually asked her about it?
Gotta love those communication skills...
Hmph.
The point is, I want to do something for her birthday.
Even if Yuigahama doesn't decide
to come back to the Service Club,
I want to show her my gratitude for helping us out.
I see.
Hey, Hikigaya...
Yeah?
Th-that is... well, um...
Uh...
W-would you please go out with me?
What?
I'm sorry to make you come and hang
out with me on one of our days off.
No problem! I want to be able to buy
a birthday present for Yui, as well.
And it's gonna be fun to go out with you!
Okay, let's be efficient about this.
I'll go that way.
Then I guess I'll head over that way and have a look.
Okay, Komachi, then you go over there...
Stop!
My god. What the hell are you doing? That hurts!
Since we're all here, why don't we go together?
Then we can give each other advice!
Sound like a plan?
But then we won't have a chance to make it to every store.
Not to worry.
My sound shopping judgment tells
me that based on Yui's tastes... Ah?
As long as we hit everything in this
area, we shouldn't have any problems!
Komachi, you meant around this area, right?
Hm? What? Did you see where she went?
Hello?
Hey, where are you?
Huh? Oh...
I totally forgot that there
was some stuff I wanted to buy.
You're the one who said we should all go together!
I didn't realize your brain was
already starting to go downhill.
As your brother, I'm a little shocked.
Jeez, you really can't take a hint, huh?
What do you mean, "can't take a hint"?
Nevermind.
I'll probably take like five hours to finish!
I'll go home by myself if I have to.
Good luck, you two!
H-hey! What the...
How does good luck help with
buying any of this stuff? Idiot.
Yukinoshita?
Eh?
What did Komachi have to say?
Oh... Uh...
She said there's something she wanted to buy.
And that she's leaving everything to us.
Well, we did bring her here on one of her days off.
We've got no right to complain about this.
Let's just figure something out on our own.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Hey, you think I look that suspicious?
I don't think it's you, per se.
It just looks like men are
viewed with suspicion in this area.
Doesn't look like there's anything I can do here, anyway.
I'll be over here.
Wait.
Hm?
Are you leaving this all to me, then?
Not to brag or anything here,
but my standards are quite a bit different
from those of regular high school girls.
So you do realize it...
So, um, well...
I would appreciate your help with finding something.
I've given a gift to a girl
before, and been rejected, of course,
but I've never actually bought anything for one.
Yeah, but I can't go into these stores...
I guess we've no other choice.
Try not to put too much distance between us.
What the hell does that mean?
Do I have to spell it out for you?
If all you can do with the air is breathe it, then any
air conditioner out there is way more advanced than you.
Ah...
She has a point.
It'd be damn convenient if those
things could read the air, too.
I'm saying that... just for today...
I hereby give you express permission
to treat me as you would your girlfriend.
Nice way to try and talk down to me.
You've got a problem with it?
Nope, none in particular.
What? Um... what?
It's nothing to be that surprised about.
I have absolutely no interest in being
her boyfriend, but Yukinoshita doesn't lie.
We'd definitely be pretending, no doubt
about that, so nobody would get the wrong idea.
I was certain you would dislike the idea immensely.
Nah, I don't really have any reason to not like it.
But... I thought you'd probably hate it.
No, I don't really mind at all.
As long as there's nobody around who knows who we are,
then there's no need to worry
about anyone getting the wrong idea.
I can't leave things like this with him...
I guess I really should go talk to him about this.
I didn't even have the chance to give him the cookies...
Huh?
Ahh!
You're not shopping for office supplies.
If you pick out clothes based on their
durability, you'll never settle on anything.
Come on now... I doubt seriously she looks
for defensive properties in her clothing.
I can't help it.
The material and stitching are
the only things I know how to judge.
I never bothered to find out what Yuigahama likes...
or even what her hobbies are.
What kind of friend am I?
Don't see why you'd need to know.
If you pretended to know me based
on offhand info, I'd be pissed.
Like giving a Chiba resident
peanuts from some other prefecture.
That comparison was too Chiba-based to make sense.
It's like giving wine to a sommelier
when you know nothing about wine.
I see...
If it's like that...
Well then?
I don't know how to answer that...
except to say it looks good on you.
You think so? Thank you.
But I didn't mean me. I was asking
you how it would work for Yuigahama.
I don't know about that.
It seems to me that Yuigahama would prefer stuff
that's more frilly and somewhat stupid-looking?
That's a harsh way to put it.
It's so accurate, I don't know how to respond.
I'll take this.
Yeah, sounds good to me.
Well, anything does. You're getting that, too?
Huh? Yukino?
Ah! I can't believe it's really is you!
It's Nee...
Huh? Who's Nee? What?!
I'm Yukino's older sister, Haruno.
What's your name?
Oh... Hikigaya.
That so? Well...
So you're Hikigaya, huh?
Well, nice to meet you!
How long have you two been going out?
Come on, why don't you just tell me?
We're in the same grade is all.
Aww...
I'm telling you I'm not her boyfriend.
Look... you're getting all serious there!
If you make Yukino cry, I'll never forgive you, got it?
Th-that hurts!
She's too close! Too close! Too close!
And... she smells good...
All right... that's quite enough, Nee.
No... Sorry...
I guess I got a little carried away for a minute there.
Yukino can be a very delicate girl at times,
so be nice to my little sis, okay?
Ah? Sorry, did I do something to make you uncomfortable?
Oh, you know, um... my ears are sensitive...
Hikigaya, don't reveal your fetishes
to strange older girls you've just met.
Or you can't complain if they try to sue you.
Hikigaya, you're so hilarious!
Are you finished yet? If you have no
business with me, we'll be leaving now.
Hikigaya, if you actually start dating, let's grab tea!
Your big sister really is something.
Everyone who meets her says the same thing.
I suppose it's rare finding someone as perfect as she.
Everyone likes to sing her praises.
Huh?
That doesn't sound like it's so different from you.
Is that a roundabout brag?
Hm?
When I said she's something, I meant...
Well, it's almost like she's
wearing a powered exoskeleton.
She has the whole package, really.
She's friendly, always smiling, and conversational.
Truly any guy's ideal woman.
But ideals are ideals.
They're not real. So it seems kind of fake.
Coming from you... it's... not surprising
you can actually see through that.
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
If you would like. It's a rave review.
What?
A dog...
Hm?
H-Hikigaya...
Ah!
Whoa...
Hey, where's your owner, pup?
Are you running loose?
What's with this dog?
You're a little too friendly...
Is this...
I'm sorry!
Was Sable bothering you two?
Oh, Yuigahama...
Huh? What?! Hikki and Yukinon?
But... wh-why are you two together?
What now? Uh... No reason...
Uh, nevermind!
No worries. It's nothing!
You're out together on our day off.
It's obvious what this is...
I see... Why didn't I notice before?
I mean... Reading the room is the one thing I'm good at...
She's definitely getting the wrong idea about us...
Well, I guess I'll be getting on my way now.
Yuigahama.
I want to talk to you about the two of us.
Would you maybe be free to come to the club room Monday?
Ah...
I'm not sure I really wanna hear the story...
I don't think it would do much
good for me to hear it now...
I mean, there's really nothing I can do about it.
You know, being the way that I am, I
couldn't say it the way one is supposed to...
But I want to be able to tell
you properly, if you'll allow me.
Okay?
What exactly are you doing? Ah!
Ahh! H-Hikki!
Well, uh, you know... the air just felt so good out here!
Come on, let's go.
Hm?
Yuigahama...
Oh, y-yahello, Yukinon.
Ah! Um, so... Yeah...
Y-you you wanted to talk to me about you and Hikki, right?
Yes.
I wanted to talk to you about our future...
Oh! No! Please! You didn't have to
worry about my feelings in all of this!
I mean, yeah, I was surprised and all, but it's more
like I want to celebrate and congratulate, you know!
Y-you already figured it out...
I want to congratulate you properly.
Also, I'm grateful to you for helping with...
Oh, stop it!
I didn't do anything that you should be grateful for.
I haven't done anything...
But still, I'm forever grateful to you.
Congratulations doesn't always have
to be about something you did, right?
That's all I want to do.
Fine... Sure.
I get the feeling they're not quite on the same page...
So with that... I...
I don't think I want to hear any more.
Yuigahama, I think you're getting the wrong idea here.
W-wait a minute!
So you guys aren't actually
sneaking around and dating each other?
Of course we're not dating!
Yuigahama, even I manage to get angry sometimes.
Besides, there's no way he's even capable
of having a proper relationship with a girl.
He can't even handle relationships with regular people.
Stop. I don't need to waste
my time on those relationships.
If a girl called me crying in the middle
of the night, I'd dump her then and there.
Sorry... Huh?
Our time to congratulate you has run out.
And I even made you a cake and everything...
A cake? Why a cake?
"Why a cake?"
I called you here today because I
wanted to celebrate your birthday with you.
Huh? What?
You haven't been coming to the club
recently, so it was also a sort of a bonus.
And, well... I guess you'd say a token of thanks.
Is that a present?
Yukinon!
Yeah, well, it's not like I'm the only
one who brought you something today...
Hm?
I never thought you'd have one for me, too, Hikki.
That's a surprise.
It's been a little weird, huh? Since the other day...
Sorry. It's not because it's your birthday.
Huh?
I mean, can we all just forget this just happened now?
The fact that I happened to save your dog,
and the fact that you were nice to me because of that.
All of it.
It's not like I helped you specifically
just so as to get gratitude out of you,
so there's no need for you to
feel indebted to me specifically.
But, well, you know...
I want to return the kindness you gave me.
This makes us even.
You don't have to concern yourself with me.
In other this is over now, right?
Why do you think of it that
way... as just pity or being nice?
I never once thought of you in that way, ever.
I guess I just... well...
I'm... just not sure, it's too complicated.
I thought it would be much simpler than all this...
There's nothing complicated about it.
Hikigaya has no recollection of helping you,
and you have no recollection of showing him pity.
You were mistaken from the start.
So I think Hikigaya's idea of ending
all of this turmoil is the right idea.
But I don't want it to be over...
not now... not ever...
Silly.
If it's over, all you have to do is start again.
Neither of you has done anything wrong.
What?
Even if one of you is the
savior and the other is the saved,
you're both victims equally.
Only the one who's done wrong
should be viewed as the aggressor here.
If neither of you were wrong,
there was no need to fight in the first place.
So... The two of you can make
a proper start now, as of today.
Now, I need to go inform Ms. Hiratsuka
that we've recruited a member to our club.
So, can I open that?
Knock yourself out.
Hey, how does it look?
Uh, wait. That's for your dog...
Huh? You should have said so, you dumb jerk wad!
Oh, forget this! I'm going to go see Ms. Hiratsuka!
Thank you... idiot.
Hikigaya, I need to speak to you immediately
concerning the Service Club's summer activities.
Please call me back.
Come on, are you still sleeping?
I've tried to call and email you several times.
You've actually seen them, haven't you?
You have, haven't you?
You're scary. You're scaring the crap outta me.
Next time: "Anyway, Getting No Rest
Over Summer Break. Just Isn't Right."