Big Brother!
Oh, hey, Komachi. Did you come here alone?
I did! But the only reason I came was to see you!
I'd sure give myself a lot of points for that one!
Where are Yui and Yukino hanging out?
Yuigahama's in our classroom, but Yukinoshita...
No clue, really.
So why are you out here and not in your classroom?
Shouldn't you be?
I am but a solitary, wandering soul.
I have no desire for a place to belong!
Wow, aren't you cool... What are you really doing?
I'm working.
What?! My own big brother? Working?!
That makes me so very happy!
Though, I admit it's a little strange...
Like my brother has left for some far-off place!
I'm not sure how to feel...
Well, actually, I call it work, but in reality
it's like I'm the lowest of the underlings.
Well, that I can see!
Okay, then I'm gonna go look around now.
See ya, Bro!
Ah?
Huh?
Oh?
Were you working?
Yeah, can't you tell by looking?
Why do you think I asked you?
So, what about you?
On my way to a meeting before the closing ceremony.
Oh, man! We've gotta hurry or
there won't be any seats left!
What's that?
You'll see soon enough.
Huh?
She's amazing.
It's a bit weird to hear you complimenting her.
Is it?
Despite appearances, I have
quite a high opinion of my sister.
When I was young I wanted to be just like her.
I think you're fine the way you are. Don't change.
Huh?
Sagami's missing?
She is. We've not been able to reach her on her cell.
This is a problem.
Without her, we can't hold the closing ceremony.
Worst case, we replace her?
It's actually more difficult than that.
Even if we found someone and managed
to get through the closing comments,
Sagami is still the only one here who knows the
voting results for the excellency and regional awards.
Why don't you just make up the results for the awards.
It's not like the vote counts ever go over well.
Hikigaya...
We definitely can't do that.
Put off the award presentations for another day, then?
That's the worst case scenario.
The regional award is kind of pointless
if it's not presented here today.
Something wrong?
I see...
Hmm...
What if we added another song to our performance?
Could you really do that?
Yeah.
Yumiko,
can you play and sing one more song?
Are you serious, Hayama? One more?!
No way! I can't! I'm totally on edge here!
Hmph. Pretty please?
Thanks for this.
Don't thank me, 'cause I'm not doing it for you!
Hmph!
The previous act just ended! Come on!
For real?
Oh, God...
This is so wrong.
I've posted online in a few different places.
If anyone has seen her, they should let me know soon.
I appreciate it.
Heh, no worries.
Even so, if we take the stage now,
we can only stall for 10 minutes.
Someone needs to find her quick.
Yeah...
I can go look around for her.
You won't find her by looking around randomly.
What you need to do is pick one place that
you can get to and back within 15 minutes.
Hey, Hikigaya,
do you think if I were able to buy you another 10 minutes,
could you find her?
Don't know. That's all I can tell you now.
But you didn't say it was impossible.
That's good enough for now.
Haruno, I need your help.
Wow.
Okay. I'm shocked. You know this is the
first time you've actually asked for my help.
So, I will actually accept your request.
"Request"? Don't go getting the wrong idea here.
This is an order as a planning committee member.
Oh? And is there a penalty if I
defy your order, Little Sister?
It's not like you can actually go
and take down my festival display now.
Will you run and go tell the teacher?
There's no penalty, but there is a benefit.
What kind?
The kind that says I will owe you a favor.
How you perceive that is entirely up to you.
Ohh...
Well, Yukino, you've certainly grown up.
No. You're wrong. I've always been like this.
Have you not been watching me
all this time? It was obvious.
Heh!
What's funny?
Nothing.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
This is the kind of person Yukino Yukinoshita is.
Well? What do you plan to do?
Fill in the gap.
Oh? You sure do come up with some fun ideas.
We do have all the members here, and all.
So, which song is it?
I think I can still play the
song I played with you before.
Meguri?
Oh yes! Don't worry about me!
Now we just need a vocalist.
Yuigahama...
Will you do us the honors and sing?
You'd be great.
Oh, well, uh... I'm not sure I can...
I might just make things worse...
But...
I've been waiting for ages for you to ask me.
Thanks, Yui.
Mm-hmm! To be honest, I only
vagooly remember the lyrics.
Please don't expect too much.
I think the word you're saying is "vaguely."
That mistake of yours has me a little worried now.
What the heck, Yukinon?! That was mean of you!
Hikigaya...
Please find her.
You can do it, Hikki!
The one thing someone who's lost
their own place really wants...
is for someone to find a new place they can feel safe.
She wants to be found, so she's here at school.
And in a place where she can be seen.
Where is she?
There's not much time.
I need to narrow down my options.
It is I!
Zaimokuza, where would you usually hang
out at school when you want to be alone?
What's all this, out of the clear blue sky?
I'm hanging up.
Wait! Wait! Please! The nurse's office, or
the balcony! I'm in the library a lot, too!
Also, the top of the annex tower!
Ah! Uh...
You know the closing ceremony's about to start?
Hasn't it started already?
Should've. And it normally would have.
But they're doing all they possibly can to stall.
Oh? And who exactly is doing that?
Well, Miura, Yukinoshita, and some others.
Then why doesn't Yukinoshita just do it?
She might as well just do everything!
Huh? That's beside the point, Sagami!
As you know you're the only one that
has the voting results, among other things.
Fine! Then why don't you just take back the results?!
The request Yukinoshita accepted was to have
Sagami fulfill the duties of the committee chairman.
If I just take back the voting results,
I'd be denying all the work that Yukinoshita has done.
What I need to do
is get Sagami to take her place on stage as the chairman.
Also, I need to give her the
glory of the chairman position,
along with a healthy dose of frustration and regret.
To accomplish that,
I only have to tell Sagami
exactly what she wants to hear.
But, unfortunately, I'm incapable of that.
Huh? Ah?
Hayama?
We couldn't get in touch, so we got worried.
We were asking around for you and
someone had seen you climbing the stairs.
Let's hurry back.
Everyone's waiting for you. 'Kay?
Yeah, he's right.
Everyone's worried about you.
Yeah, but going back now isn't going to help anything.
Don't worry about that. Everyone's waiting.
Please, come back with us!
No way, I caused so much trouble for everyone.
I can't face them...
It's okay. Everyone only wishes the
best for you and totally supports you.
Yukinoshita always saw things through her way.
So I'll do this my way.
Face it head-on, fair and square,
in the lowest, nastiest, most servile way I can.
It's okay. Let's go.
I'm just the worst...
Yeah, you are kind of the worst.
Sagami, in my opinion, I think
you want people to fawn over you.
You do this stuff because you want attention.
Even now, you just wanted them to say "That's not true."
Of course, nobody treated you like the real chairman.
What are you saying?
You really just wanted to be like Yukinoshita, didn't you?
You wanted to be acknowledged
and sought after, like she is.
You wanted people to depend on you.
So that's why you instantly pushed
the title of chairman onto her.
You wanted to confirm your superiority
by putting the label on someone else
and looking down your nose at them.
That's what you really meant by "growth."
I'm pretty sure everyone's noticed.
I don't really even know that much about you at all...
but, jeez, even I can see it.
You see nothing. Don't talk like we're the same.
We are the same.
And the best part is we're seen as the lowest of the low.
I mean, just think about it.
I have like zero interest in you as a person,
yet found you before anyone else did.
In other words...
Does that mean nobody was seriously looking for you, then?
You realize it, don't you?
That you're nothing more than...
Hikigaya, just shut up already.
Heh.
Hayama, don't bother. It doesn't matter!
He's not worth it. Let's just go, okay?
Come on, then.
Who was that jerk? Talk about harsh!
What a creep, talking like he knows everything.
He has no right to say you're like him.
Tell me, how's this your "go to" solution?
Thank you!
Encore! Encore! Encore!
This, uh...
This year's cultural festival
is unlike any other in history.
Among all this excitement...
Hey, it'll be okay.
You know you'd have been fine if that
guy hadn't said those things to you.
It threw you off, didn't it?
Hikitani can be such a mean jerk!
He was kinda like that over the summer, too!
I guess. He's been known to say some pretty harsh things.
Hayama is such a nice guy...
Isn't he so sexy coming to Hikitani's defense?!
Yesterday's enemy is today's boyfriend...
Seriously, Ebina, can't you act more like us?!
Here, your nose is bleeding. Blow.
Hm?
Ya-hello!
Oh wow, Hikigaya, you're the greatest there is!
I've heard all about your heroism from the others.
I love that kind of stuff, but
it's kinda wasted on Yukino, though.
Right? Isn't that so, Shizu?
First, your idea for the slogan,
now this thing with Sagami...
Somehow your efforts always seem to
find a way to play a part in the end.
But I don't feel like I can honestly praise you for it.
Hikigaya, you know you don't always have to put yourself
out there as the enemy in order to help someone else.
What's the difference? It's not
like any of this really gets to me.
Not true. Even if you're used to
hurting it doesn't have to be like this,
It's time you opened your eyes
and see that there are people around you
who hurt when they see that you're hurting.
Understand?
That's all I have to say.
'Kay.
Huh?
Hm?
Oh, hey. What's up...
most hated person in the school?
Are you picking a fight with me?
What about the after-party? You not going?
Don't ask questions you already know the answer to.
Tell me, how does it feel being genuinely hated?
Heh, having my presence acknowledged is a good thing.
Right?
I don't know if I should be surprised or disgusted.
You're really a strange one, you know?
But there is one thing I don't dislike about you.
Your awareness of your own weakness.
Yeah, I don't really dislike it, either.
Actually, that's kind of my favorite aspect of myself.
So, what are you doing here?
I'm just trying to fill out my career plan sheet.
I didn't really have time to work on it
while we were preparing for the festival.
So, what's your reason for being here?
I need to put my reports together.
I wanted to do it in a place that's
quiet where I could concentrate.
Oh... I guess we think a lot alike, don't we?
Well, we don't really have many options.
It's just convergent evolution of loners.
But it in no way means you and I are alike.
Hm...
Nope. She and I aren't the least bit alike.
Then again, that could be why our conversations
always feel fresh and comfortable.
Is that why, though?
After repeating the question, the answer I was led to
has turned out to be true.
So... So are she and I...
Hey, Yukinoshita...
Could we...
I'm sorry, but that's not happening.
Gah! Why wouldn't you let me at least finish my thought?
Haven't I already told you?
It's just impossible for you and I to be friends, okay?
Are you serious?
I am. I never tell a lie.
Well, it doesn't matter to me if you lie.
I lie all the time.
Who cares if you know something, but say you don't?
Forcing something out of someone
without permission is worse.
I wasn't lying then.
I mean, at that point I really didn't know you at all.
However, I'm pretty sure I do now though.
Guh!
Oh, you think so?
Yes, I do.
Ya-hello!
Such a great job with the festival!
Let's go to the night-after party!
Not going.
What is a night-after party, anyway?
You don't even know, and you refused?!
The night-after party is, well... it's, uh...
It's kinda like a regular after-party, but bigger?
Don't you think you should know if you're inviting us?
Let's see, judging from the name, it sounds like
it would be the opposite of a night-before party.
That's it! Yeah! Hayato and his
buddies booked a club near the station.
Said to invite everyone we know!
Well that was nice of them.
Well you should go and join them,
He'll-look-better-with-ya?
Hey! Don't casually say my name wrong!
And who you talking about, 'cause it's not
Hayama, 'cause I don't want to make him look good.
We don't get to do this often. Let's just go.
Thanks, but I'll pass.
Even if I went, I'd be sitting in a corner the whole time.
I'd feel kinda bad for destroying
the festive atmosphere for everyone.
He's right. Besides, the night-after party
isn't sponsored by the planning committee.
So I don't see much reason for me to attend.
Aww, let's just go!
Wait, what are you doing in here, anyway?
I'm doing reports.
Doing my career plan.
Oh... Well then I'll just wait until you're finished!
Wait just a minute, Yui, we never said we were gonna go...
You don't get much of a chance to redo things in life.
Even a stupid act like this will eventually be lost.
And I sit here and think about how...
I might actually regret that loss one day...
Don't treat my athletic past like a dark moment in time.
God, I hated the competitive class relays.
Yeah, well, I couldn't run very
fast, so it was hard for me too.
Okay, we must get out there
and do our best to win this thing!
I am young, after all.
Don't call me "Sakisaki"!
Ahem, ahem, ahem.
Oh, Hachiman!
Same question as my left.
We need to come up with some strong ideas!
Stand up, citizens!
Next time: "Thus, Their Festival Will Never End."