Come on, wake up. Wake up, Hachiman.
Wha...? What?!
Is this a "morning after"
scene? Is this the morning after?!
You're finally awake.
Morning af...
Everyone else left already.
You'd better hurry, or you'll miss breakfast.
Oh, yeah. I'm at that camp, aren't I?
I'm betting you don't have a
regular routine in the summer.
Yeah, I don't...
You're also not getting any exercise, are you?
Let's play tennis sometime!
Yeah sure, okay. Just drop me
a line whenever you wanna play.
Great! I will...
So it looks to me like I'm gonna...
need to get your phone number then, aren't I?
I've only ever used my phone as an
alarm clock with built-in time killers,
and now it's finally going to
have Totsuka's phone number...
Hey, Hachiman, why are you crying?
Let me send you a test message.
It's me, Saika.
Good morning, Hachiman! This is my first text to you.
Hope to hear from you soon!
Hachiman?!
What's wrong? Are you okay?!
Listen up, today's plan...
Tonight, we've got a test of courage and a campfire party.
The kids have free time during the day,
so use that time to get everything ready.
Great, a campfire party.
That's where you do folk dances!
Like that alien-summoning "Bentora Bentora" dance!
I believe you're thinking of the "Oklahoma mixer."
How did you even mix those two words up?
I can see how it would happen.
The people doing it are basically aliens anyways.
Hachiman, that's a mean thing to say.
I didn't mean it that way.
I have my reasons for saying that.
When I went to a campfire dance in grade school...
We don't actually have to hold hands, do we?
All the other girls did what she did,
so I was the only boy doing an air Oklahoma mixer.
Hikigaya, your eyes look dead.
I'm thinking that makes you perfect to play a monster.
Scaring kids with the test of courage, huh?
There are some monster costumes laid out over there.
Divvy them up and get to it.
Okay.
Hyah!
Stacking logs alone like this is like playing Jenga.
But much better.
Huh? You can play Jenga alone?
What? You don't?
That's finally done.
See? Stacking the blocks alone
is what makes Jenga fun, right?
Isn't that right?
It isn't, is it?
Hot...
Hot... Hm?
That looks refreshing.
That's cold!
Oh, hey look who it is!
Yoo-hoo, Big Brother! Why don't you come join us?
Um... Hikki?
What are you guys doing out here?
And why are you in your swimsuits?
Ms. Hiratsuka said we could come
play in the river since it's so hot...
True, but more importantly, this is my new swimsuit!
Look!
Well? Tell me what you think of it!
Hmm? Let me think here for a minute...
It's the cutest in the world.
You didn't even try...
Okay, what do you think of Yui's, huh?
Komachi!
Uh, well, uh...
Well, you know, she...
Looks really good. It suits you.
You think so? Th-thanks Hikki...
Damn. My eyes are naturally drawn in her direction.
Is this the unibreastal law of gravitation?
Leave it to Sir Isaac Newtit.
What's this? Apologizing to the river?
No...
What, you're down here, too, Hikigaya?
Ms. Hiratsuka... Wow, you do an excellent job of
passing for someone in their thirties when you really...
I'm still in my thirties, dammit!
Oh, so you don't go to Akihabara?
No, no! I go to Ikebukuro! Totally different!
For one, it's a completely different kind of place!
Akihabara is on the right side of
the Yamanote line... Making it uke!
I win...
Hey, so, considering your older sister, I believe
you can expect good things from those genes of yours.
What does my sister have to do with anything?
You shouldn't worry about it, Yukino.
They're not what makes a girl special.
And besides, everyone's different,
so don't listen to him. I've got your back!
Right... Thanks, I guess.
Sister? My genes? Special?
I'm different?
Oh!
Whatever, it's not like any of
that superficial stuff bothers me.
If certain outward characteristics determine a person's
worth, in my opinion, that should all be relative.
The overall balance should be considered, not just...
Yukinoshita, there's no need for you to give up just yet.
I wish I was out there splashing Saika...
Hey.
Why are you sitting alone?
I didn't know to bring my swimsuit. And you?
We apparently have free time today.
When I went back to my room after
breakfast there was no one around.
Hm...
Hey, Rumi, you wanna come hang out in the water with us?
Okay...
I have a question for you...
Ask away.
Do you have any friends you knew in grade school?
I don't. And I don't really think anyone does.
It's fine to let them be. Once they
graduate, you'll never see any of them again.
Huh?
That's just you, Hikki.
I haven't seen mine since then.
You know, Rumi, these two are a couple of special cases.
And tell me what's wrong with that?
All it means is we're "special."
Makes us sound superior.
Here, it only means "weird."
Yuigahama...
Huh?
How many of your friends from grade
school do you still hang out with?
Uh... hmm, let's see, maybe one or two...
And how many kids were in your grade?
About thirty kids in three classes.
Ok then, so that means the percentage that
remained your friends five years after your graduation
is only three to six percent.
See there, even a beauty whose friends
with everyone has a low percentage.
I'm a beauty?
Yuigahama, that wasn't exactly a compliment.
Look here. Most people aren't really
friends with everyone, usually just a few.
Split Yui's percentage by a
generous 25% and you barely have 1%.
No more than a typical margin
of error. It doesn't even count.
You know the saying, "Rounding
up only helps 5 and hurts 4."
Yes, but it might help to make
things easier if you think 1% is enough.
Being friends with everyone can be tiring, after all.
But my mom doesn't think that way.
She always asks me if I'm
getting along well with my friends.
She even told me to take lots of pictures
at camp with this new camera she gave me.
I see...
And so, I feel like an insect that's
beneath everyone when they're busy ignoring me.
I know it kind of sucks.
I feel pathetic... but that's how it is...
So there's no changing it now.
Why's that?
I turned my back on them. So
we can't continue being friends.
Even if I could...
Things might end up like this again at any moment.
So, I should leave things as they are...
So that's it.
She's given up completely.
It's said that if you change, the world changes with you,
but that's not true.
When people judge others, it's with
prejudice and existing impressions.
People who are alone are pressured to stay alone.
If they work hard to stand out,
others only use that to hurt them.
It's lousy, but that's how kids operate.
You don't wanna feel pathetic?
No.
Hope you have fun with the test of courage.
Huh? Ah!
Hikki, what's up? Hikki?
Question:
The world does not change.
One can change oneself.
How, then, does one change?
Answer:
Become the god of a new world.
She said we're to be monsters
for the test of courage, right?
What's with these cheap-looking costumes?
O, Gods who are up in heaven, I beg
you to send down your bridge to me!
That's needlessly realistic.
I can do traditional Japanese folklore stuff, too!
Douman! Seiman!
Do you think wizards can be counted as monsters?
I mean, I guess, in a broad sense.
But this isn't scary...
Oh, don't you worry about that, you're scary.
Seriously scary.
I'm scared I'm going to end up
going straight down the Totsuka route.
Hey, Big Brother, look at me!
Ta-da!
What are you, a cat monster?
I think... I'm not totally sure, but it's
super cute, so I figured I'd just go with it!
Why are you inspecting it?
It looks really good on you.
Yay! Thank you, Yukino!
Well you look ridiculously good in a kimono.
Just like the Yuki Onna.
And you look really good as a
zombie there, very realistic.
Those dead eyes of yours are worthy of Hollywood.
I'm not in makeup and I haven't changed yet, thank you.
So, you're looking awfully busy over there.
Huh... Oh hey, Hikki... Do I look okay? Scary?
So if it looked the slightest
bit terrible on you, I'd tell you.
In fact, I was even prepared to make fun of you, too.
And now I'm not even able to do that.
Huh? Um, so... Oh!
You could just give me an honest compliment, jerk!
My big brother is such a weirdo...
I was just trying to pay you a compliment.
So, what should we do about the problem at hand?
I think Rumi might just have to go and talk to the others.
I honestly think they'll just keep
giving her a hard time if she does that.
What if she talks to them individually?
It'll be the same... Even if they're nice to her
face, they'll start doing it behind her back again.
You need to know that girls are
scarier than you think, Hayato.
Seriously? Talk about scary.
Hey, I have an idea that just might work.
So that means probably not much of one.
Just hear me out.
We're gonna be running a test of courage,
so we've gotta use it to our advantage.
Use it how, though?
If you've got problems with human relationships,
if you destroy the relationships
themselves, the problems are gone.
Nobody will fight or argue if they're out there all alone.
Okay, so you guys get to go next!
So you need to go out and find the talisman
at the shrine deep in these scary woods.
Grr! I'm going to eat you!
I feel really stupid doing this...
It's just about time.
Hm? Ah...
Whoa, uh, it's just me.
Huh?
Oh hey, it's... you?
Your eyes looked so dead, I thought you were a ghost.
Is that so, huh?
So, how is the plan going?
That's the starting signal.
Okay, at last, it's finally your turn now!
Oh, it's Hikka's friends.
Look at them out here dressed all normal.
So lame!
This stupid test of courage isn't scary at all.
You guys sure are dumb for high schoolers!
Huh? What's with the lack of respect, girls?
Aren't you brats getting a little full of yourselves?
It's not like we're actually your friends
or anything, so you can't talk to us that way.
Now, didn't one of you just totally make fun of us?
Who's responsible?
We're really sorry...
I asked you who said it, didn't I?
Are you looking down on us? Little girls!
I say we take 'em out now.
I mean, isn't it our job to teach
these entitled brats manners after all?
Hey, Hayama, would you mind
terribly if I took these brats out?
How 'bout this? Half of you are free to leave now.
However, the other half are gonna stay right here.
You can decide amongst yourselves who's gonna stay.
We're so sorry!
I didn't ask you to apologize.
I said half of you will stay here.
So choose.
Well did you not hear Hayama or are you
gonna pretend he didn't ask you a question?
Then I guess you better make
it quick! So are you gonna stay?!
Tsurumi... You stay behind.
Yeah, stay.
Yeah.
What happens next is what you're after, right?
We start to destroy the relationships around Rumi Tsurumi.
When humans feel truly scared,
they can't think about anyone else.
They try to save themselves, even
if it means sacrificing someone else.
Once that ugly truth is exposed,
they can't be friends again.
We just have to break up their
little group in a certain way.
But you don't think that's really
going to solve the actual problem, do you?
No, I don't. But it should cancel it out, right?
Only strong people think it's bad to run away from things.
It's not always your own fault, though.
The world, our society, people around us...
There are plenty of times when someone else is to blame.
Saying "I can change myself" is just admitting defeat,
it's only done so one can adapt to this
cold, cruel world and become its slave.
That phrase is no more than a pretty way to
dress up the fact that you're deceiving yourself.
So that's how you think about things...
I think I'm beginning to understand
why she worries about you so much.
"She"...?
Okay, let's go with that.
But I'm betting on the possibility that
they'll all band together to solve it themselves.
I think they're good kids at heart.
'Kay, we need two more. Make it quick.
It was Yuka that said those bad things...
It's her fault! Yuka started it!
I did not! Hitomi started it!
I didn't say anything! It's not my fault!
Mori's attitude was the problem!
What?!
You always do that. Even to our Teacher.
That has absolutely nothing to do with this!
Everyone, stop, let's apologize so we can move on!
What I hate the most are girls who think
they can cry their way out of a situation.
We'll give you thirty seconds
to choose the other two.
And you know what'll happen if you tattle!
I'll remember who all of you all are!
You're down to twenty seconds.
I think Yuka should stay!
I agree! Yuka, you stay!
I'm with them, too!
Huh?!
Go on, go!
Hey! Don't push me!
Yuka!
I'm sorry, but we have no choice!
Okay, one more.
Ten... nine... eight...
Now, all we have to do is jump out and say "Gotcha!"
Wait!
Why'd you do that?
Is that... Huh?
Four... three... two... one...
Hey!
Hm?
This way! Hurry!
M-my eyes...
What the hell was that?
Was that a camera flash?
Wait a minute, does that mean
Rumi actually saved all of them?
I suppose deep down they were friends after all...
If you're not able to get along without putting someone
else down in the process, it can't be real friendship.
You're right. I guess it can't.
But then...
If she knew it was fake,
and still wanted to reach out to them,
then I guess her friendship must be real.
That was a dangerous bridge you crossed.
One misstep, and there could've been a big problem here.
Yeah... Sorry about that.
I'm not accusing you.
In fact, I think you did well for the short time you had.
Even though my methods were pretty terrible?
True. You kind of are a pretty terrible person.
I was talking about my methods here.
Why must you feel the need to criticize me?
Well, you're terrible for
coming up with a method like that.
But maybe... it's because you're so terrible, that
you can get close to people who've hit rock bottom.
It's a good trait to have.
Well, that was a lousy compliment.
No "thank you" for you, I see.
Hm? Well, it's not like I
really did anything good tonight.
Getting rid of that clique will make her life much easier.
They won't be able to gang up on her.
Regardless of your horrible method,
it seems your plan actually worked.
Shocker.
So...
Even if nobody thanks you for it,
I think it's alright if something
good happens from this whole experience.
Sorry for the wait!
Here! Sparklers!
Yukinon! Look!
Hey, watch it with those things.
Yay!
Hm?
Sorry I made you play such a rough part out there.
I actually didn't mind.
In fact, I don't really feel bad about it.
Except...
It made me remember something from a while ago...
when I saw something similar happening
and didn't do anything about it.
Hey, what do you think it would've been
like if we'd gone to the same grade school?
Well, I'm guessing your school
would've just had one more lonely kid.
Personally, I think a lot of
things would've ended up differently.
But still, I don't think...
we could've actually been friend's way back then.
I'm just kidding.
Good work, everyone.
Camp isn't over until you're home safe!
Be careful on your way back.
Okay, dismissed!
Komachi, let's do some shopping on the way home.
Aye aye, sir.
Hey, Yukino, why don't you come with us?
Hm?
Hey! What's up, Lil Sis?
What the...
You've been away from home far too long, Yukino!
I was worried about you so I came to get you myself.
Oh hey, it's Hikigaya!
Was this a date? Oh, I bet it was, you silly boy!
I told you, we're not like that!
Hey, you're making Hikki uncomfortable!
Wait, are you Hikigaya's girlfriend?
No! No way! I'm his classmate, Yui Yuigahama.
Classmate?
Yep! Oh, thank goodness!
I was starting to think of what I should
do if you were getting in Yukino's way!
You better not lay a hand on
Hikigaya. He belongs only to Yukino!
No, I do not. No, he does not.
See? They're in perfect sync!
Haruno, don't you think that's enough now?
Good to see you, Shizu.
I've told you not to call me that.
Teacher, you know Haruno?
She used to be my student.
So, you mean...
Well, Yukino, let's get going.
You know mom is waiting for us.
Huh?
Sorry, I must decline your invitation.
I can't go with you.
What? Okay...
Goodbye.
Hey, I'll see you later, Hikigaya!
Tsuzuki, we can go now.
Hey, was that car the...
Eh, who knows? Big fancy black cars
all look the same to someone like me.
I was too focused on the pain.
Plus, I can't be bothered to
remember every car that I see.
I said that even though I knew better.
The truth is, I recognized it the moment I saw it.
I didn't get to see Yukino Yukinoshita
again for the rest of summer break.
It just happened that way. Don't expect it.
I know, but for me I just wanna know more.
I just wish I knew you better.
I really want us all to be closer.
If something's wrong I want us to help each other!
And then...
Then...
I mean, I'm pretty sure that I'd...
Next time: "For the Third Time, He Turns
Back on the Path from Whence He Came."