[KING COLD]
Hmm...
[SAIYANS murmuring]
[GINE gasps]
[BEETS] Damn it!
Watch where you’re flying!
[KING VEGETA growls]
[SAIYAN GENERAL A]
Ridiculous!
[SAIYAN GENERAL B]
Is that the whole force?
[MAJORDOMO] The great King Cold
has now arrived, your majesty.
I’d say that’s pretty obvious.
[SAIYAN COURTIER A grunts]
[gasping]
[GINYU FORCE grunts]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[KING COLD] It’s been a
long time, King Vegeta.
It’s an honor to have you here,
Great King Cold.
This is my son. Frieza,
meet the Saiyan king.
[FRIEZA]
Mmm...
[KING VEGETA grunts]
Oh, yes.
Uh. It’s a pleasure to
meet you, Lord Frieza.
Welcome.
I believe you’ll find that
the pleasure is all mine.
[KING COLD chuckles]
[KING COLD] Anyway, I’ll get
straight to the point.
I’m retiring‐‐
effective immediately.
From this moment on, Frieza
will be your commander.
In other words, the Cold Force
has now become the Frieza Force.
Uh! Does that mean...?
Nothing’s changing.
The Saiyans will simply
continue to serve us
by following Frieza’s orders.
I suppose I should warn
you of one difference.
You’ll find that my son
has as short temper
and is even more
cold‐hearted than I am.
[laughs] Hello, monkeys.
I have such high
expectations for you.
For your sake, I hope
you live up to them.
[KING VEGETA gasping]
To commemorate my rise to power,
I brought along new combat items
to aid you in your servitude.
These devices are
called Scouters.
You’ll find they’re far
more compact and powerful
than the sadly outdated
surveillance Scout Scopes
you’ve been using until now.
They also function
as communicators.
The displays should be familiar.
They show your target’s
position and battle power
just like the older
scopes used to‐‐ Uh...
Oh dear...
It appears that
a number of Saiyans
currently have weapons
trained on us.
[KING VEGETA gasping]
Let’s see, the Saiyan
hiding in that tower
has a battle power of... 2,000.
That’s quite an
impressive number. Ha!
[SAIYAN GENERALS gasping]
[FRIEZA]
I assume you get the picture.
They’re useful, are they not?
[KING VEGETA grunting]
I’ll leave 500 units behind
as a gift for your troops.
If you don’t think that’s
enough, feel free to complain.
I believe we’re done here.
[KING VEGETA growling]
[KING VEGETA laughs]
He’s growing bigger and
stronger with every day.
My son, my pride and joy.
The latent battle power
within you is astonishing.
It is you who will
rule the universe.
That monster Frieza
thinks the Saiyans
will serve him without question.
But he’ll fall to us!
I look forward to watching you
grow into a vicious king.
Huh? Who is this child?
What is he doing in
the same room as my son?
[MOROKO gasps]
Your Majesty!
This is Broly.
He is the child
of Colonel Paragus.
[KING VEGETA] This nursery
is reserved for exceptional
children who’ll become
Saiyan elites,
not some low‐ranking baby
taken off the street.
Explain yourselves.
Yes, of course, Your Majesty.
You see, we found that
his latent abilities
are exceptionally high.
You dare to suggest
that this commoner
has a rating that’s on
par with my son’s?!
Well, sir, I‐‐
Whenever we analyzed Broly
his power level actually
far exceeded your son’s.
What you’re saying
isn’t possible.
The prince’s rating broke
every record in Saiyan history.
Give me that.
[BROLY cries]
[BROLY screaming]
[KING VEGETA yelps]
[KING VEGETA grunts]
I’m terribly sorry. The gauge
appears to have shorted out.
We’ll get a new one immediately.
[NION]
I’m sending for one now.
[MOROKO gasps]
Upon further inspection,
his rating is less than
half of his original number.
We’ve had a handful of anomalous
readings in the nursery lately.
His must have been due
to a device malfunction.
That being said, even if we
do ignore the previous data,
Broly’s latent abilities
are quite remarkable.
[KING VEGETA growls]
And once he receives training,
he will grow to be an
outstanding warrior.
He’ll be a powerful
asset to our forces.
[NION]
He could even end up being
the legendary Super Saiyan.
[SAIYAN GUARD A]
Paragus. You can’t!
[PARAGUS]
Get out of my way!
That’s far enough.
Please, forgive me
for barging in.
I... understand you plan
to send Broly away.
I’m told his pod will be
destined for an outlying world.
[KING VEGETA]
That’s correct.
[PARAGUS] That’s a fate meant
for a lower‐class warrior.
Not my son.
On the contrary,
what better way is there
to prove that your son
is a truly powerful warrior
than by conquering an unclaimed
planet on his own?
After all, that’s what
Saiyans have always done.
We subjugate valuable worlds and
sell them to the highest bidder.
[PARAGUS] But his destination
is the planetoid Vampa.
It’s an inhospitable world
devoid of intelligent life.
I don’t see how we could make
much of a profit on it.
The truth of the matter
is that your son Broly’s
latent abilities are
abnormally elevated.
I’d go so far as
to call him a freak.
Someday, that power
will likely end up
driving him completely insane.
When that time comes,
he’ll be a danger
not just to the planet Vegeta,
but the entire universe.
[KING VEGETA]
Be grateful that I’m exiling him
to a faraway world and not
simply ending his life.
[PARAGUS]
No. This isn’t right.
[gasps]
You... You’re jealous!
Because Broly’s latent abilities
surpass that of the prince’s,
don’t they? You’re trying
to exile my son!
Say another word and
I will have your tongue.
Then kill the both of you.
Besides, you’re too late.
He’s gone.
I had the pod launched
before you got here.
[PARAGUS]
Move it!
[SAIYAN FLIGHT STAFF A]
Hey, sir.
This area is for authorized
personal only.
[BEETS]
Huh?! What are you‐‐?
You don’t have
permission to launch this.
[SAIYAN FLIGHT STAFF B]
Watch out!
[SAIYAN CONTROL TOWER A]
Return here at once. I repeat...
[BEETS]
Please. We have to go back.
[PARAGUS] I can’t do that.
I have to save my son.
King Vegeta has
always been too proud
of his child’s exceptional
latent abilities.
The fool can’t stand the fact
that my son is almost
the same age as the prince,
but far exceeds his power level.
He won’t get away with this.
The pod’s destination
is some remote location
I’ve never seen before.
[PARAGUS] Yes, apparently
it’s a planetoid called Vampa
that orbits around Star 94.
[BEETS]
But, why send him there?
We don’t know of any inhabited
planets in that area.
[PARAGUS] The king’s goal
isn’t to conquer the system‐‐
it’s to get rid of my son.
But I’ll make sure that Broly
survives, no matter what.
[BEETS]
Okay.
I understand, but...
[PARAGUS]
Don’t worry, Beets.
Once I rescue Broly, we’ll go
live on some other world
where I can train him myself.
After you drop us off,
you can head back to
Planet Vegeta if you like.
[BEETS]
You aren’t coming back yourself?
No, of course not. If I did,
I would just be executed.
I’ll raise Broly to be a
mighty warrior on my own.
And some day,
I’ll have my revenge
against King Vegeta!
♪
[BEETS]
So... This is Vampa, huh.
My calculations say
the pod should have
arrived here two days ago.
Please be alive, Broly.
I’m coming to save you.
He should be in this area.
[BEETS groans]
It was calmer when we
were in the light.
Can’t we land back there?
It’d be easier
to bring her down.
[PARAGUS]
No. This is closer.
We have to find him quickly.
Come on!
[BEETS]
Wait, you need me to go?
[PARAGUS] Yes. I can’t exactly
have you takin’ off without me
while I’m searching for him.
[BEETS]
I wouldn’t do that. I swear.
You can trust me.
[PARAGUS]
Yeah. As if there’s such a thing
as a trustworthy Saiyan.
[BEETS]
I heard there’s an updated model
of those Scout Scopes
floating around.
Our new leader, King Cold’s son,
supposedly brought them for us.
[PARAGUS]
I know.
[BEETS] Word is this Frieza guy
is supposed to be impressive.
But brutal.
[PARAGUS]
Makes no difference to me now.
[rumbling]
[BEETS]
You hear something?
[rumbling continues]
[PARAGUS]
Huh?!
[BEETS gasps]
[VAMPA BEETLES A roars]
[BEETS, PARAGUS grunt]
[VAMPA BEETLES grunting]
[BEETS whimpers]
What are these things?!
I shouldn’t even be out here.
I’m not a soldier, dammit.
Looks like the daylight drove
away those storms at least.
Sure is hot now, though.
Is that a planet or a satellite?
Certainly looks like a moon.
[PARAGUS]
Don’t stare at it for too long.
You’ll become a Great Ape.
[BEETS gasps]
Oh. Right.
I’ve never actually turned
into a Great Ape before.
[PARAGUS]
Well that’s for the best.
You’d lose all
sense of yourself.
The only time to rely on that
is when you’re cornered
with no other way out.
[PARAGUS]
Huh? What is this?
[BEETS]
The terrain is soft here.
And this grass is really thick.
[BEETS]
Uh! Those bugs...
It looks as though they’re
drinking something
from straight out of the ground.
[BEETS gasps]
[PARAGUS]
What’s happening?
[BEETS screams]
[roars]
That wasn’t grassland‐‐
it was fur.
Some kind of giant beast.
Those insect creatures
must survive by
sucking its blood
like parasites.
And in turn, they serve
as food themselves.
[BEETS]
Ugh. This planet is disgusting.
Uh. Uh!
The pod! I think I
see it over there!
[PARAGUS]
He’s not here.
Where could he have gone?
I hope he wasn’t eaten
by one of these things.
Huh.
[PARAGUS]
Follow me!
[BEETS]
Oh my god, it stinks.
Are you sure this is
the right place?
‐‐[beeping]
‐‐[BEETS gasps]
[PARAGUS gasping]
[PARAGUS]
Broly!
You took down a monster and
then ate its leg, didn’t you?
That’s my boy.
[BEETS]
Uh! So, this is your son.
His battle power is 920?
That’s higher than
I am right now!
[PARAGUS]
Even if he is a gifted child
with an impressive battle power,
he couldn’t have defeated this
monster at his current level.
[BROLY screaming]
So that’s it. Looks
like his battle suit
has been stretched out
and torn in places.
He must’ve stared at the moon
and turned into a Great Ape.
Let’s just hurry and get
away from this world.
[PARAGUS] Felt like we took
some damage coming in...
[BEETS gasps]
Oh, no, no, no, no.
[PARAGUS]
What is it?
[BEETS] The main floater
is cracked! We’re done for.
[PARAGUS]
You mean... You can’t fix it?
[BEETS]
Absolutely not.
And without a new floater,
we’re stranded.
[PARAGUS] What? There’s got
to be something we can do.
[BEETS] At this point,
we can’t even radio for help.
Not that it would come.
[PARAGUS] There’s enough
food and water for ten days.
[BEETS] Do you really
think anyone will find us
before we start to starve?
I knew we shouldn’t have
crash landed like that.
I told you so!
[PARAGUS] There is one sure
way for us to conserve food.
[BEETS whimpers]
[BEETS yelps]
[thud]
[LEEK]
Bardock.
Bardock!
What is it?
[LEEK] We’ve almost arrived
at Planet Vegeta.
Feels good to be home, huh?
[BARDOCK]
Yeah.
[LEEK] What do you
figure this is about?
Must be important if Frieza
ordered all the
Saiyans to assemble.
Maybe the bastard has some
big plan he needs us for.
Your Scouter’s on.
Watch your mouth.
[LEEK gasps]
That’s right!
Hey, look at that!
Seems like the party may
have started without us.
Frieza’s already here?
Uh.
[BARDOCK]
Yeah, that’s his ship.
[LEEK] I wonder why he’s
still waiting up here
when he could’ve landed already.
[BARDOCK]
Something about this is strange.
If he wanted to talk to his men,
he could’ve just used the radio
and saved everyone
a whole lot of time.
And if he’s got
new weapons for us,
there’s no reason we need
to pick them up together.
I’ve got a bad
feeling about this.
None of it makes any sense.
[LEEK]
Come on.
What do you mean
a "bad feeling"?
[BARDOCK]
Look. We conquer planets
and then sell them
to whoever will pay us.
That’s how the Saiyans
made our fortunes,
how we’ve always existed.
But then... Frieza’s
father, King Cold,
made us serve under him,
forcing our people into slavery.
Reaping the benefits
of our work.
[LEEK] That was a pretty
long time ago, though.
[BARDOCK]
Sure, but all this time
we’ve never been happy
working together, have we?
[LEEK]
That’s true.
I can’t think of any
Saiyan who likes Frieza.
Yeah, and I’m betting
he probably feels
the same way about us.
[LEEK]
What?
[BARDOCK] The Frieza Force
has grown extremely large.
They could probably
get by even without us
annoying Saiyans around.
[door hisses]
[LEEK]
Wait. Hold on.
You’re not suggesting
that Frieza’s
planning to exterminate us.
It’s a possibility. Am I right?
Uh... Come on,
quit playing, Bardock.
[TARO]
Yo. It’s good to see ya.
Didn’t think you’d
make it back alive.
Shut up.
Any idea why we got the order
to return home so fast?
It beats me. Maybe they
found a fortified world
they need all of our help with.
One so protected, it’ll take
every Saiyan alive to conquer.
That must be it! And here
you had me all worried!
Oh, and Bardock.
Frieza’s people have
been askin’ around
about the Super Saiyan lately.
Not sure what that’s about.
What do you mean
the "Super Saiyan"?
Like the one in the legend?
That’s it!
[KIKONO]
Regarding the Super Saiyan...
A‐And the Super Saiyan God.
We’ve researched
them extensively,
but they appear
to be only myths.
[FRIEZA]
Ah, wonderful.
I expected as much.
But I can’t afford the least
bit of anxiety right now,
so I had to be sure.
Not that they’d be a problem.
So, then. Are you
cancelling the attack?
[laughing] You are hilarious!
Not after I went
through the trouble
of assembling all these monkeys.
It’s a perfect plan to
get rid of the Saiyans.
Planet and all.
Wouldn’t you agree?
[SAIYAN A]
Welcome home.
Good to see ya, Bardock!
[BARDOCK]
You too.
What’s wrong?
No warm welcome, Gine?
Bardock, you’re here!
Things sure are crazy
around town today.
Yeah. It’s not that often
everyone comes back.
[BARDOCK]
Where’s Raditz?
Off world. He’s in
the military now,
teamed up with Prince Vegeta
on some planet.
I seriously doubt they’ll
make it back for this.
Wow, Prince Vegeta, huh?
I wouldn’t wanna be stuck
on a ship with that one.
How is Kakarot doing?
Is he still in
a nursing capsule?
He is. It’s just about time
to let him out, though.
You should see him. Come on.
[BARDOCK]
Still small, huh?
[GINE] I think he may
be a late bloomer.
He looks just like you,
though, don’t you think?
He certainly has his father’s
hair, for better or worse.
[GINE laughs]
[BARDOCK] After dark, I’m going
to steal a pod for him.
[GINE]
Huh?
[BARDOCK] We’re going to send
our son to another world.
Huh?! You’ve gotta be kidding!
Gine. I’m serious.
Have you gone insane? Why would
we abandon our son like that?
He hasn’t even learned
how to talk yet!
With his latent abilities,
he’s destined to be sent away.
Probably somewhere horrible.
So, we’re going
to see to it that
he at least grows up
on a decent planet.
No. He’s far too young for that.
I don’t think we can afford
to wait much longer.
And what does that mean?!
Because of Frieza.
I think that he’s afraid of
the legendary Super Saiyan
appearing one day.
Hold on, the Super Saiyan?
But, that’s only...
That’s just a children’s
fairy tale, Bardock!
I know.
The problem is, I think he’s
still bothered by the legend.
And I can’t imagine he’d
want to take any chances.
[gasps]
I get the feeling that death
is on its way for us.
[GOKU cries]
[GINE]
Is there another option?
Let’s think about this.
[BARDOCK]
No, it’s the only choice.
If I turn out to be wrong,
I’ll go and rescue him.
‐‐[banging]
‐‐[GOKU cries]
In that case,
why don’t the three of us
run off somewhere together?
We can’t. They’d use
their damn Scouters
and be able to track
us down in no time.
Bardock...
Why are you going through
so much trouble?
It’s not like a Saiyan man
to worry about his children.
So what’s gotten into you?
[BARDOCK]
I don’t know.
Maybe it’s because I’m
constantly fighting, destroying.
And I’d actually like to
save something for once.
Especially someone
who was judged to be
a lower‐class warrior.
Like my Kakarot.
[GOKU cries]
[BARDOCK] I’ve programmed this
to head to a distant planet
called Earth. The people on
that world have low power levels
and aren’t
technologically advanced.
I think he’ll be able
to do well there, Gine.
Good thing is, it’s not an
extremely valuable world,
so I’m hoping it won’t even show
up on the Frieza Force’s radar.
If your father is wrong
about this then
we’ll come and
get you immediately.
Listen, son. You do what it
takes to survive, got it?
We’ll see you really soon.
[BARDOCK]
Goodbye.
Don’t forget us, Kakarot!
[cries]
[KIKONO]
But without the Saiyans
our fighting force will
be drastically reduced.
Almost by half.
[FRIEZA] My troops will
still be able to get by.
These barbarians pretend
to be submissive,
but they’re dangerous.
They could bare their fangs
against us at any time.
Uhh...
[FRIEZA]
They are, after all,
a species completely
comprised of warriors.
It’s always best to put
a sleeping beast down
before it can be awakened.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[yells]
Huh?
[SAIYANS murmuring]
[yells]
[BARDOCK yelling]
[BARDOCK screams]
I, for one, feel so
much better now.
[SAIYAN B]
Did you hear that?!
Somethin’ wrong?
We got a message from
the Frieza Force.
A meteor collided with
Planet Vegeta, and...
‐‐What?!
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
Uh! Our whole world
was obliterated!
Uh. Impossible!
That means most of the Saiyan
race was completely wiped out.
[SAIYAN C] But how? They
should have detected
the approaching meteor!
Well I guess we’re
pretty lucky, aren’t we?
It’s a good thing we
decided to ignore
Frieza’s order to head home.
Now I’ll never get
to be King Vegeta.
[gasps]
[NAPPA] Vegeta, you have
a brother, don’t you?
Oh, yeah, I wonder if
he got blown up, too.
Heh. Not that it matters.
And you had a brother as well?
Yeah, but he was just gonna
be a lower‐class warrior.
He was still at home sleeping
in a nursing capsule.
A disgrace.
Wait. I think Mom said she
sent Kakarot off the planet
in a pod though.
Oh well, I couldn’t
care any less.
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
[GOKU, VEGETA grunt]
[yells]
[yelling]
[BULMA laughs]
[WHIS laughing]
It’s delicious!
Ah, the food. The air.
I must say, this cottage
truly is fantastic.
Don’t you agree, Bulma?
It is nice, isn’t it?
[coos]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA]
Heh.
[GOKU chuckles]
[BULMA] We had the place
built a few years ago.
The island is deserted,
and around 1,000 miles south
of West City, so it’s perfect.
Out here the boys can cut loose
without hurting anything.
[laughs]
The last thing we need is for
them to destroy half of the city
while sparring with each other.
[VEGETA yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[growls]
Keep it down, will you?!
Learn to fight quietly!
I’m trying to nap!
[WHIS]
Tell me, Goku.
Why do you seek even greater
strength than you have already?
Wait, wait, don’t tell me.
Do you want to become
a Destroyer God?
[GOKU gulps]
What was that.
Don’t think I’ll take this
threat lying down.
No, that’s not it!
Why would I just want
to sit around all day?
Okay, that was uncalled for.
[GOKU] The Tournament
of Power opened my eyes.
You saw those fighters.
There’s no way can I stay at
the same level I’m at right now.
They got me all fired up!
[grunting, yells]
[WHIS]
Oh!
The tournament’s barely over
and you’ve already got
your sights set on
other universes?
You’re as big of a fool
as ever, Kakarot.
Well then what
about you, Vegeta,
why do you seek more strength
despite your current
power level?
To fight Frieza!
Because you...
You decided to bring back
that devil, you dumbass!
Of all the people you could
have returned back to life!
Hey, calm down.
If it weren’t for Frieza, we and
the rest of the Seventh Universe
might not even be here anymore.
Wait, seriously, is that true?
Yeah. He helped us
save everybody.
You idiot!
He only did that because he
was looking out for himself.
[VEGETA] You remember how
much stronger Frieza was
when he came back to Earth.
What happens when he
achieves a newer form?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Wait, are you saying he
might even get more powerful
and come to try and
beat us again?
There’s no doubt about it.
Huh. I dunno.
I mean, we’re the ones who
brought him back to life.
[VEGETA growls]
You idiot!
Do you really believe
that monster thinks
he owes us anything?!
Hey, how many times are you
gonna call me an idiot today?
[VEGETA growls]
As many times as I need to!
Idiot!
[ringing]
Huh. Wonder what he wants.
Hey, Mom!
[BULMA]
What’s up?
Sorry, but it looks like someone
broke into your laboratory.
What? Was anything stolen?
Oh, right, I’ll check
the security camera.
Let’s see...
[TRUNKS] Aw, man, they swiped
the Dragon Balls you collected,
and the Dragon Radar!
[BULMA growls]
They took what?!
[ALL yelp]
How many times have I told you?
The lab needs much
better security.
[TRUNKS]
You know what, Mom?
I recognize the clothes
the burglars were wearing.
They kinda look like
those outfits that Dad had
back in the day.
[VEGETA, BULMA]
What the‐‐?
Clean it up, ’kay?
Bye.
[VEGETA]
The culprits were Frieza’s men.
He specifically used people
with lower battle powers
so we wouldn’t be
able to detect them.
That thieving monster.
He’s relentless when it
comes to those Dragon Balls.
I wonder...
What kind of wish could he
be after at this point?
He can’t wish for anything
outside of Shenron’s power,
so it’s not like he can ask
to be made stronger.
At least not by much.
It’s obvious what
he’ll be asking for.
He wants to live forever.
[GOKU]
Yeah, but...
But dying is pointless
if you end up just losing.
[VEGETA grunts]
You’re missing the big picture.
It’s still possible Frieza
will surpass us one day!
You really think so?
[VEGETA growling]
I only had six Dragon Balls
stashed in my lab.
I bet they’re probably
headed for the last one.
Lucky for you,
I know where it is.
So where is it?
On the ice continent.
I’m not a fan of the cold,
so I was putting off
tracking it down.
We’d better go after it, huh?
[BULMA] Mm‐hm. Would you
like to come along, too?
It’s nap time. I’ll stay here.
Come now.
Don’t you think it sounds like
we could have a fun time?
Anything good to eat out there?
Not unless you consider
snow a delicacy.
Well, count me out.
Yay! Here.
[laughs]
[BULMA]
Thanks, Uncle Beerus!
Goodbye. Don’t have
too much fun!
Hey! I’m a Destroyer God,
not a babysitter!
The temperature
on the ice continent
will be below freezing.
We’ll have to stop and buy
some cold‐weather gear.
Hey, Bulma, why were
you collecting
the Dragon Balls anyway?
[BULMA grumbles]
That’s none of your business.
Ah. Come on, tell us!
[BULMA grumbles]
[BULMA] I was gonna make
myself look younger, okay?
Just by, like, five years.
You were gonna summon Shenron
just because you look so old?
You shut your mouth!
A Saiyan wouldn’t understand
how important this is!
[VEGETA grunts]
But why stop at only
five years, Bulma?
You could make it
an even decade.
Because that much of a change
would be totally obvious.
I know exactly what
people’d say.
"Oh, Bulma, what a surprise!
Your skin is so smooth,
not a line to be seen.
You look ten years younger.
Come on, spill it,
who’s your surgeon."
I won’t have it.
Oh, I understand.
You’ve already been using the
Dragon Balls for that, huh?
‐‐[GOKU laughs]
‐‐[BULMA growls]
[screaming]
[laughing]
[VEGETA grunts]
Heh.
[KIKONO]
Lord Frieza.
Not only did Vegeta’s wife
have the Dragon Radar,
she’d already collected
six of the Dragon Balls
which are now in our possession!
Our search team is currently
heading to the site
of the final ball, which should
be recovered very soon.
Well, that is truly
marvelous news, Kikono.
So... Should we fire
up the engines
and head toward Earth
to claim your treasure?
Not yet. We’ll wait until
the seventh Dragon Ball
is irreversibly ours.
It would be foolish to rush
there and arrive so early.
Even without Scouters,
the Saiyans would
be able to recognize
my high battle power as we
approached their planet.
Uh. Of course, my lord.
[FRIEZA]
And you’ve already written down
how to make the wish, correct?
[KIKONO] That’s right.
And in great detail.
Uh... By the way‐‐
Go on, out with it;
what is your concern?
[KIKONO] Oh, u‐uh,
nothing. I‐It’s just...
Since we’re so close to
gathering the Dragon Balls,
I was wondering if you’d
give me a hint about what
incredibly wise wish you’ll be
making once we’re on Earth.
Will it be to have
an immortal body
like you’ve mentioned
to us before?
[laughing]
No, no, that’s not it.
Huh?
I realized something when I
was trapped in Earth’s hell
hanging from a tree
unable to move.
Not being able to die
would likely result
in unending misery.
[KIKONO]
Then, perhaps, uh, I don’t know.
To never take damage again.
Or something?
[FRIEZA] Hm... Now why would I
want to make the game so boring?
Wrong again.
Um...
So what could you want?
[laughing] You’ll never
be able to guess.
Oh, but I can.
You’re going to wish to
grow taller, aren’t you?
[FRIEZA gasps]
[KIKONO]
Huh?! Uh! No. Berryblue, don’t!
You can’t say that to him!
There are so many
soldiers who’ve called
Lord Frieza a pipsqueak.
Of course, our commander
eliminated all of them.
Very wisely deduced,
my subordinate.
That is indeed my wish.
Really? [gulps]
That was actually
the right answer?
I trust I won’t have to worry
about you telling anyone else.
Of course not, my lord.
What I want is...
...to increase my height
by five full centimeters.
Huh...? Please forgive me.
If that’s the case,
couldn’t you simply go back
to your second transformation?
Wouldn’t you be
sufficiently tall then?
Don’t be a fool.
I would like to be taller in
my normal form you ninny.
And of course, my golden one.
Obviously.
But why only five centimeters?
Any more than that
would be too noticeable.
Don’t you understand?!
[KIKONO]
Uh! Not entirely.
I want it to look like
I’m still growing.
That this is natural!
[KIKONO]
Yes. Of course...
...my lord.
[CHEELAI]
This is pointless,
there’s no one out here.
Not to mention there aren’t that
many people with a battle power
of over 1,000 to begin with.
Our orders are to recruit
as many warriors as we can
to rebuild the force,
and that means exploring places
in the far reaches of
the universe, like this.
[CHEELAI] What, the Frieza Force
isn’t big enough already?
[LEMO]
Yeah, well, Rumor has it
they weren’t fighting
hard enough,
so Lord Frieza killed
all of ’em to make a point.
[CHEELAI]
Tch.
[LEMO] So, Cheelai. Why did
you join the Frieza Force?
I stole a galactic
patrol spaceship
and this is how I’m
stayin’ a free woman.
Hey, no one’ll touch me
if they know I’m part
of the Frieza Force.
A shifty one, huh?
Aw, thanks.
You’ve been in the force most
of your life, right, Lemo?
You must’ve met Lord Frieza
in all that time.
[LEMO]
Eh, I’m not a soldier‐type,
so I’ve only ever seen him
on the video monitors.
I hear he’s tiny.
[LEMO grunts] Don’t ever
say anything like that again
if you wanna live.
He’s killed for far less.
Yeah, yeah, I got ya.
[LEMO]
He once melted a lieutenant
just because he had bad breath.
[CHEELAI] Well, if he’s putting
women and old men to work
Frieza must be hurting
pretty bad for new recruits.
[LEMO]
Who’re you calling old?
[beeping]
[CHEELAI]
What’s that?
[LEMO]
Hm... A distress signal.
And it looks like
an old frequency
the Frieza Force used to use.
[CHEELAI] It’s coming from
that world over there.
[LEMO] If we rescue them, maybe
we’ll end up getting a bonus!
[CHEELAI]
Ha! A big one.
[LEMO]
Exactly. Let’s get down there.
[PARAGUS panting]
Don’t see anyone.
[CHEELAI]
Let’s beat it.
Hold on. I’ll use my Scouter.
Don’t go!
Are you with the Frieza Force?
[PARAGUS groaning]
Hold on a sec. Is that a tail?
You don’t mean to
tell me we found
an actual Saiyan way out here.
Wait, seriously?
Yes. My name is Paragus.
I’m a member of
the Frieza Force.
So that distress
signal came from...?
That was me. My spaceship
was damaged years ago.
I’d almost given up hope
that we’d ever make it off
this cursed planet.
But finally, someone
has come for us.
[CHEELAI]
Battle power of 4,200?
Perfect!
[LEMO]
So, are you alone?
[PARAGUS]
No, there’s one other‐‐
[stomping]
[LEMO, CHEELAI gasping]
[LEMO, CHEELAI scream]
Broly!
Yes, yes. Very good, son.
This is Broly.
[gasps] Impossible!
[LEMO]
What’s wrong?
It’s‐‐ His battle
power is like...
...the scanner can’t
even measure it!
No way!
Can’t be right, these are
state‐of‐the‐art devices‐‐
Ha, ha! Hop in
the ship, friends,
Frieza’s gonna lose it
when he meets you two.
So, uh, what are you
called again, creeper?
I’m Broly.
You want one of these to eat?
They’re not bad! Try this one.
Hey, wait! At least let me
take off the wrapper first.
[sniffs]
[PARAGUS]
It’s food, son.
[CHEELAI gasps]
[laughing]
See, I told ya it was good.
Wow, not even a "thanks"?
[PARAGUS]
Remember your manners, Broly.
Thank you very much.
I am grateful.
Why so formal?
Maybe just try a "thank you."
[gasps]
I thank you.
That’s close.
[BERRYBLUE] I’ve brought the men
in question, Lord Frieza.
Oh!
[FRIEZA]
How interesting.
Are you really Saiyans?
Yet that one doesn’t
appear to have a tail.
No, sir.
Whenever he transformed
into a Great Ape
he unfortunately lost all
control over his actions.
He became a danger
to himself, and to me,
which is why I chose
to cut off his tail.
And has this mighty
warrior lost his mind
and exploded since then?
[PARAGUS] Yes, sir.
But on the rarest occasions.
[FRIEZA] You’re saying
this could still happen?
You brought danger to my ship.
Please, there’s no need
to worry, I swear.
Were that to happen...
...I can control him using
this remote device,
which pumps a bolt of
electricity through his body.
It’s not a strong current,
but it allows me to rein
him in when he acts out.
[FRIEZA]
Fascinating.
And what is your name, Saiyan?
Please, sir, f‐forgive Broly.
[FRIEZA]
It would seem you still have
a tremendous amount of
untapped battle power.
I’ve trained the boy well,
and I’m certain he can be
of great use to you and
your troops, Lord Frieza.
This is indeed an
unexpected bounty.
Berryblue, please offer a
worthy reward to the two
who found these Saiyans
and brought them here.
‐‐[LEMO] It’s a fortune!
‐‐[CHEELAI] Whoa...
[CHEELAI, LEMO] Thank you
for your generosity, sir!
[FRIEZA] I’m told you were
trapped together on that awful,
barren planet for
quite some time.
[PARAGUS]
That’s correct.
And are you aware that your
home world, Planet Vegeta,
was regrettably destroyed
by an unexpected meteor?
Yes, sir. I’ve been briefed
on the fate of my planet.
But, if I may be blunt,
I do not mourn for it.
At all.
Is that because you
never got your revenge?
[FRIEZA] Paragus. Did you
know that King Vegeta’s son,
Vegeta the Fourth,
is still alive?
Flourishing, even.
His son? Prince Vegeta?
Of course he would survive!
Those arrogant
bastards must pay!
Their line should have ended.
[FRIEZA]
Please, allow me to lend a hand
and help your vengeance
come to pass.
Come Berryblue. Show these two
to their new quarters so
they may get tidied up.
They’ll need some new
battle uniforms, as well.
Yes, Lord.
[FRIEZA] Hm... I had not planned
on fighting the Saiyans
this time around. However...
...this is proving to be far
too interesting to pass up.
[laughing]
[door hisses]
[CHEELAI]
Hey‐o!
You’re lookin’ much better.
Come and eat with us, guys.
Say, Broly. Where’s
your battle uniform?
[BROLY]
No good.
It’s hard to move in.
Eh, it’s not that bad
once you get used to it.
But, do what makes
you happy, I guess.
[CHEELAI] Ugh. You should
really ditch that fur
around your waist
though. It’s dirty.
And it’s stinks.
Seriously, when was
the last time you wa‐‐
It stays on!
[yelps]
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?
Okay, I get it, that gross pelt
is actually something
important to you.
The fur is... special.
Broly, we’re here
to eat, not speak.
Don’t waste your energy.
Seriously?
You won’t even let him talk?!
I’d appreciate it if you
minded your own business.
Say what?!
Why don’t we calm down?
Hey. You must be new.
Aren’tcha?
Hm? It can’t be
much fun hangin’ out
with these puny losers though.
I’m the only warrior
aboard this ship
who’s worth spendin’ time with.
Why don’t you come sit
with me, sweet thing?
[BROLY growls]
[DAIGEN]
Whaddaya say?
Tch. Get your filthy hands
off me, I’m not interested.
[DAIGEN]
Huh?
You heard her, big guy.
How ’bout I buy ya
a drink instead.
Stay outta this, shorty.
Come on lady, I’m done askin’.
[PARAGUS]
Stand down, Broly.
[DAIGEN]
Hey, what do you want?
Got a problem with me?
I do.
Big mistake!
[DAIGEN grunting]
Dammit!
[DAIGEN yelps, chokes]
[PARAGUS]
Broly!
[BROLY growls]
[BROLY yells]
[DAIGEN groaning]
[BROLY screaming]
[CHEELAI gasps]
[screaming]
[BROLY groans]
[CHEELAI]
Are you okay?
You!
He’s your son!
How could you do that to him?!
[PARAGUS]
If I hadn’t stop him,
he might have killed
that buffoon.
That’s your fault.
You’re the one who
raised him to be this way!
We may be in your debt,
but you don’t know anything
about us, woman.
From now on, you don’t
come near my son.
[BERRYBLUE]
Excuse me, Paragus.
Lord Frieza would
like an audience.
It would be an honor‐‐
we’ll go to him right away.
Broly!
I’m afraid he only wishes
to speak to you.
Of course, yes,
if that’s what he wants.
Broly, I’ll be right back.
Stay here and shut up.
Used to think my
old man was a creep,
but this guy’s even worse.
[CHEELAI laughs]
What’s so funny?
Heh, heh. Ahh...?
Is that‐‐? You little thief.
Here’s what I think
about shock treatment.
By the way, thanks for
the help earlier.
[LEMO]
Yeah, I get it.
You must be thirsty.
Give it here.
This’ll be easier.
[BROLY]
What is this?
[CHEELAI]
Huh? Ordinary water.
You can’t expect me to believe
you’ve never had water before.
[CHEELAI]
Hm?
[LEMO gasping]
[exhales]
That was good "water."
[BROLY]
This is Ba’s ear.
Oh, you mean the fur
that I was asking about.
[BROLY] Me and Ba got
along well back home.
Ba was a big animal‐‐a giant.
And more fearsome than
most beasts on Vampa.
I named Ba after the sound the
creature would make sometimes.
It was scary when it got mad.
But I got over that.
And I started to train
by avoiding Ba’s teeth.
We became like friends.
We became like... good friends.
So this monster was the
first friend you ever made?
Yeah, but my dad didn’t
like that one bit.
He said that being friends with
Ba wasn’t training, but playing.
So then...
...Dad shot Ba’s ear off with a
gun, making it angry with him.
And me.
After that,
Ba was never the same again.
That’s why I decided
to keep Ba’s ear.
To remember when
we were friends.
That’s more than I’ve ever
heard you speak, Broly.
Yeah, and it happened to be
the most innocent story
I’ve heard around here
in a long time.
You can’t seriously be
that pure and naive.
I’ll betcha you don’t even
like all that fighting
your father makes you do, huh?
[LEMO]
If I had to guess,
I’d say Paragus saw you
had some real talent,
then made you focus on becoming
a warrior against your will.
[CHEELAI]
That man is no good.
He only thinks of you as a
powerful weapon he can use,
not as an actual person. Right?
You’re just a tool he’ll
use to get his vengeance.
Probably.
I gotta say,
your old man is awful.
You know, you don’t
have to do everything
that guy tells you to do.
It’s not right for you to
say bad things about him.
He is my dad.
[FRIEZA SOLDIER A] It should be
around here somewhere.
[BOTH gasping]
[FRIEZA SOLDIER A] You weakling.
Hurry and pull me up!
I’m tryin’!
The hell you been eatin’?
[gasps]
[FRIEZA SOLDIER A]
Huh?
Right there! We’ve got it!
[FRIEZA] The planet we’re
heading to is called Earth.
We’ll find Vegeta and
the other Saiyan there.
I would like to see
Broly’s power in action
against these two.
I assure you his strength
is remarkable,
you won’t be disappointed.
The prince will pay for
what his father did to us.
I’ll make you an offer.
You’re welcome to do whatever
you please with Prince Vegeta.
But the other one, Goku, is mine
and mine alone to destroy.
You and Broly will leave
his death up to me!
You’re very well acquainted
with the desire for revenge,
so you’ll understand that I want
Goku’s blood on my hands.
[PARAGUS]
Huh? As you wish, sir.
Lord Frieza! They’ve done it!
We’ve collected
the seven Dragon Balls!
Oh! And with such
perfect timing!
[BULMA]
Hm? [gasps]
Look! Down there! Frieza’s men!
Oh great. Have they already
beaten us to the last one?
[FRIEZA SOLDIER B] That aircraft
looks like it could be trouble.
You don’t suppose they’re those
Saiyans Kikono warned us about.
[GOKU]
Heh, heh!
Whoo! Now this is cold!
[BULMA] You don’t seem
to be bothered by it, Whis.
Ah, no, I find the vacuum
of space far chillier.
[FRIEZA SOLDIER A]
Crap. Not good!
The Scouter’s
readings have spiked!
Come on stupid.
We’re gettin’ outta here.
[ALL]
Hm?
[SOLDIERS scream]
You’re finished, guys.
Open up and give us back
the Dragon Balls!
What are we
supposed to do now?
Isn’t it obvious? If we don’t
give ’em back, we’re goners!
Just look at that death stare.
[FRIEZA SOLDIER B] But, like,
if we do give them back,
Lord Frieza will murder us.
[FRIEZA SOLDIER A]
Oh, no! He’s on his way.
[FRIEZA grunts]
Well, here he comes.
He always likes a big entrance.
[VEGETA]
Hmm?
What is that?
It’s not Frieza,
that’s for sure.
There’s someone else.
And his power is crazy.
[FRIEZA SOLIDERS scream]
[VEGETA]
Hm?
Kakarot, the two behind
him are Saiyans.
[PARAGUS]
Huh?! That’s Vegeta.
I’m sure of it.
[PARAGUS]
He looks just like the king.
[GOKU]
Frieza!
What are you doing here?
I’m positive you
already know.
I’ll soon have a wish granted,
thanks to the Dragon Balls.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[CHEELAI] Uh, what are those
glowing floaty things he’s got?
Beats me. Looks like
they all know, though.
Hey, you!
Give us those Dragon Balls
back and leave right now!
It appears we may have
a larger problem.
Huh?
You might call it the blessing
and the curse of a warrior race.
[GOKU]
So who are those two?
Friends of yours?
These are the newest
enlistees to the Frieza Force.
Allow me to introduce my
servants‐‐Broly and his father.
[PARAGUS]
I am Paragus.
I’m sure you’ll get along.
As you’ve noticed,
they’re Saiyans‐‐
from your annihilated
home world.
I’ve never seen them before.
[FRIEZA] I understand that
when you were quite young
your father did a
great disservice
to Paragus and Broly here.
Condemning the poor boy
to a repugnant world.
They were trapped there until
my people rescued them,
so you can imagine what rage
burns within their soul.
Tell me one thing.
[GOKU]
What’s "repugnant" mean?
[ALL]
Uh!
[FRIEZA]
Mm!
It refers to something
incredibly miserable.
Oh, that makes sense.
Cool. Thanks.
Such a moron...
[growling]
I swear you will pay,
Vegeta. Dearly.
[VEGETA]
Hm?
The sins of your father
are on your head, Prince!
[growls]
[VEGETA]
Don’t be ridiculous.
This isn’t my business.
[GOKU] He doesn’t have
anything to do with this!
Come on, we’re all Saiyans here.
We should try to get along.
[BROLY growls]
Shall we begin?
[growling]
It would seem he can’t wait
to get a piece of them.
Very well, then.
Show me how powerful this
boy of yours really is.
It would be my pleasure.
This is our chance, my son.
Attack!
[yells]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[BROLY yells]
You’re not half bad.
This might end up being
a pretty good warmup.
[yells]
[BROLY yells]
[VEGETA]
He’s fast.
He must have studied
how to use his power.
[VEGETA yells]
It looks like Prince Vegeta
is a skilled fighter
in his own right.
These Saiyans have certainly
been through their fair share
of battles over the years.
Of course, your son seems
adept at brawling himself.
And yet, Broly has
never actually fought
another person, correct?
[PARAGUS] Only during
training matches with me.
[FRIEZA] But fighting against
someone of your power level is
practically meaningless.
[FRIEZA]
Not to worry.
It’s obvious that
he’s quick to adapt.
[VEGETA yells]
[BROLY yells]
Don’t let up! Broly!
[BROLY, VEGETA grunting]
This is gettin’ annoying.
[BROLY growls]
[yelling]
[PARAGUS gasps]
What did he just do?
Hold on. Can Broly not
turn into a Super Saiyan?
That’s certainly
a disappointment.
What? A Super Saiyan?
Like the legend?
That’s a myth!
[BROLY growls]
[yells]
[BROLY groans]
[BROLY grunting]
[BROLY yells]
[VEGETA yells]
Where the hell did
you come from?
[BROLY growls]
[BROLY yells]
[VEGETA] Damn it.
He’s learning as he fights!
[BROLY yelling]
[BROLY, VEGETA grunting]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU]
This guy’s awesome!
He’s holding his own while
still in his base form!
Ha, ha!
[VEGETA grunts]
[BROLY groans]
[gasps]
[BROLY groaning]
[BROLY yelling]
[BROLY groans]
[BROLY screams]
I never imagined Prince Vegeta
would be such a
formidable opponent.
What’s the matter?
Has your son reached his limit?
I... believe so.
Well, that’s unfortunate.
In that case,
we’ll consider this fight over.
Yes, sir.
[BROLY grunting]
What is he doing?
[BROLY growls]
It’s over!
Broly, you’re not
to engage anymore!
Stand down and come back!
Get on the ship!
[BROLY growling]
Damn that boy.
No... No!
The remote control.
It should be here.
Broly! I command you to
get back here now, son!
[BROLY groaning]
You’ll listen to your father.
Do you hear me?!
[BROLY screams]
What a waste.
Uh! Don’t do this, Vegeta!
[BROLY screams]
Uh...
[BROLY grunting]
[yells]
What’s going on?!
Have you ever see a Saiyan
like this before?
Please tell me you brought a few
senzu beans with you, Kakarot.
[GOKU]
Uh. No. I forgot.
I think this is going to be
harder than we thought.
[BROLY yelling]
[BROLY growling]
[yells]
[GOKU yelps]
Oh crap!
If that had hit the ground, who
knows what it would have done!
[VEGETA growls]
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Vegeta!
[BROLY yells]
[VEGETA gasps]
Where did this come from?
I’m... not sure.
It looks as though he’s managed
to transform somehow
and take on the incredible
strength the Saiyans
have whenever they
become Great Apes.
Only he’s remaining
in his human form,
retaining his speed and agility.
And is there a downside?
Maybe. A big one.
Huh?
[exhales] He can’t control it.
He’s lost all sense
of who or what he is.
[yells]
[grunts]
[BROLY growling]
[GOKU]
Hey. You!
It’s about time I got
a chance to fight.
[BROLY growling]
[GOKU grunting]
[BROLY growls]
[yells]
[BROLY growling]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[BROLY grunting]
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU screams]
[BROLY yelling]
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU screams]
[BROLY yelling]
[yells]
[BROLY gasps]
[GOKU yells]
[BROLY yelling]
[GOKU groans]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU groaning]
[yelling]
[GOKU chuckles]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU]
Hmph!
[yells]
[BROLY yelling]
Hey, take it easy.
[yells]
[yelling]
[BROLY yells]
Ah!
[BROLY groaning]
You’ve got a lot to learn.
Here on Earth, we like to live
together in peace and harmony.
[BROLY grunting]
[yells]
Although, that’s not
always been the case.
Hmph. We’ve had our fair share
of enemies, trust me.
[BROLY groaning]
[GOKU] But I don’t think
that you’re one of them.
For some reason,
I can just tell.
[BROLY grunting]
[gasps]
[GOKU]
You can stop fighting.
You don’t have to listen to
what the others tell you to do.
[KIKONO, PARAGUS gasp]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[yelling continues]
[gasping]
[BROLY yells]
[yells]
[BROLY grunts]
[BULMA screams]
[ALL gasping]
[KIKONO] Lord Frieza,
perhaps we should get the ship
out of the battle zone?
Yes, I suppose that
would be for the best.
[yells]
[KIKONO] We’ll take care
of the Dragon Balls.
Don’t you worry!
Okay, then. I am enjoying
his performance.
But for your sake, I hope Broly
keeps putting on a good show.
[yells]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU yelling]
[yells]
[BOTH grunting]
[BROLY yelling]
[gasping]
I can’t believe how
incredible Broly is!
It’s insane.
But, still... It’s not right.
They treat him like a slave.
[yelling]
Poor guy. His dad’s forcing him.
Yeah...
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU yelps]
[CHEELAI]
Disgusting.
Paragus taking an innocent kid
and raising him to be
a cold‐blooded savage.
Now he’s snapped‐‐
the guy’s broken.
I wish there was a way
we could help him.
[yelling]
No, no. If this keeps up...
...Broly will be killed.
I‐I can’t let that happen.
Then it’ll be all over.
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU grunts, yells]
[GOKU groaning]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU screaming]
[screams]
[yells]
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU gasping]
[BROLY grunting]
[yells]
Well, well, well. It appears
I might not get an opportunity
to kill that monkey after all.
[BROLY yelling]
‐‐[BROLY yelling]
‐‐[GOKU groans]
Goku!
[GOKU]
Uh?!
[PICCOLO]
What’s happening out there?
That isn’t just Frieza’s
power that I’m sensing.
[GOKU groans]
Yeah, you got that right...
Seems like you may have your
hands full with this one.
[GOKU groaning]
[coughs] Yeah, he’s strong.
[PICCOLO]
Strong is an understatement.
I wish I could help. Thing is...
...I’m worried I might
just get in the way.
[GOKU] Stand by for now‐‐
we may need you.
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU]
If things get out of control,
I’ll use Instant Transmission
to go to you.
[BROLY chuckles]
[GOKU groans]
[panting]
[PICCOLO] If you honestly
think it’ll come to that,
he must be one hell of a foe.
Good luck, Goku.
[GOKU]
All right, Piccolo.
Gotta go.
[GOKU grunts]
[grunting]
[yells]
[yelling]
[grunts]
[BROLY, GOKU grunting]
[yells]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU]
Huh?
[BROLY yelling]
[PARAGUS screams]
[BROLY]
Huh?
[GOKU yelling]
No. It can’t be.
What King Vegeta said might...
...might actually
have been the truth.
Broly’s a danger to us all.
[BROLY groans]
[screaming]
This doesn’t look good.
Do you think he’s really
finished this time?
I’m afraid so.
I’m not so sure.
Shall we put him
to a little test?
[whimpering]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[PARAGUS groans]
Ahem.
Broly, look!
It’s such a tragedy!
[GOKU, BROLY grunting]
[FRIEZA]
Do you hear me?!
[BROLY]
Huh?
It’s your father!
He was killed by a
stray energy blast!
[BROLY gasping]
[BROLY groaning]
[BROLY screams]
[yelling]
Yes, there it is!
Show me your power!
[BROLY yells]
[BROLY growling]
[yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yells]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA]
What a lovely sight.
That was the anger
I wanted to see.
[VEGETA growls]
What the hell are you
waiting for, Kakarot?
Stop dawdling!
It’s pretty obvious you’re not
going to defeat him by yourself.
[GOKU]
I hate to admit it,
but I think you’re right.
[VEGETA yells]
[GOKU, VEGETA yell]
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
[BROLY yells]
[GOKU]
Let’s go, Vegeta!
[VEGETA]
I’m way ahead of you!
Galick...
Kamehame...
[GOKU, VEGETA]
Ha!
[BROLY growls]
[GOKU]
Have fun, Frieza!
[FRIEZA whimpers]
What are you doing?!
I am the mighty Lord Frieza.
[BROLY yelling]
[GOKU]
Vegeta! Quick!
Come with me!
[VEGETA]
Huh? What for?
[GOKU, VEGETA groan]
[VEGETA]
Perfect landing...
Hey! What in the name of
the multiverse is going on?
[GOKU groans]
[VEGETA]
Tch. Let go of me!
Don’t worry, I’ll explain
everything later.
Got any senzu beans, Piccolo?
[PICCOLO]
No luck, Goku. I’m out.
[GOKU]
Uh... Aw.
Hey, Vegeta.
Do you know the
Fusion technique?
Yeah, now that you mention it,
I’ve heard Trunks talk
about that before.
Uh! When you do an absurd
dance and join together?
Uh huh. You know, Fusion Ha.
Okay?
[VEGETA]
Nonsense!
As if I’d ever merge
myself with a fool!
Come on, it’s only
for 30 minutes.
Plus, we joined together before
with the Potara earrings.
But we don’t have
any of those now,
so fusion’s the only chance
we have to beat this guy.
[VEGETA]
There has to be some other way!
At least tell me
there’s a method
that doesn’t require
these stupid dance moves!
[GOKU]
It’s the only way to win,
so you have to
swallow your pride
or the Earth will be done for.
[VEGETA] Hmph. Then I guess
the Earth is done for.
You’re saying you’re
okay with letting Bulla
and your darling Bulma die?
Don’t you dare try and
guilt me into this, dammit.
[grumbling]
All right, fine.
Hurry up and teach it to me.
[BROLY yells]
[FRIEZA groaning]
[FRIEZA grunting]
[FRIEZA yells]
Uh?
[FRIEZA]
You dare make me exert myself?
To put effort into a fight?
Then I will teach you a lesson.
Behold! This is Golden Frieza.
The last thing
you will ever see!
[GOKU, PICCOLO]
Fu... sion!
Ha!
This couldn’t be any
more embarrassing.
So now you know how it works!
We don’t have much time.
Hurry up, let’s practice it now.
What’s wrong, Vegeta?
I think I’d rather
have Broly kill me.
So... stupid...
[VEGETA, GOKU]
Fu... sion!
Ha!
[PICCOLO grunts]
Heh, heh! Nobody’s
stronger than me now!
It’s no good, your
fingers didn’t match up.
Try it again in 30 minutes.
[FRIEZA groaning]
[screaming]
[GOKU, VEGETA]
Fu... sion!
Ha!
[sighs]
Your alignment is pathetic.
The angles were completely off.
Another 30 minutes.
[BROLY yells]
[FRIEZA groans]
[VEGETA, GOKU]
Fu... sion!
Ha!
[PICCOLO grunts]
It’s about time!
Now get out there
and defeat him!
Oh, uh...
What should we... call you?
Huh? Using the Potaras,
it was "Vegetto," wasn’t it?
Okay, then. How about, um...
Forget it! Hurry and go.
[GOKU, VEGETA]
Now, hold on a sec.
Having a name would definitely
make us sound much cooler.
This time it’ll be, Gokuga?
Vegugo? Um...
How about Gogeta? Hmph.
[BROLY grunting, screams]
[FRIEZA groaning]
Look at this.
Your battle power
is astonishing!
[FRIEZA]
Hm! Who do you think you are?
[GOGETA]
Hmph. We are Gogeta.
Kakarot and Vegeta have merged
together to take Broly down.
You’ve what...?
[GOGETA]
You were dead a long time,
so you wouldn’t know
about this technique.
Our two strengths aren’t
just added together‐‐
they’re significantly magnified.
[FRIEZA]
Wha‐‐? Not fair!
You stay right there, Frieza.
We’ll deal with you later.
[gasps]
[BROLY grunting]
That was a close call.
[BROLY yells]
Oh, my.
Don’t worry, we’ll handle
this from now on, Whis.
[BROLY grunts]
[WHIS]
Well, would you look at that.
Seems you two can work together.
[gasps] They did
the fusion thing!
[GOGETA]
Hmph.
[BROLY growls]
Go!
[BROLY yells]
[yells]
[GOGETA chuckles]
Now it’s our turn.
[GOGETA, BROLY yelling]
[BROLY groans]
[GOGETA grunts]
[GOGETA yelling]
[BROLY grunting]
[BROLY yells]
[BROLY, GOGETA yelling]
[BROLY yelling]
[BROLY groans]
[GOGETA, BROLY yelling]
[GOGETA]
Uh. What the...?
[BROLY, GOGETA grunting]
[BROLY growling]
[yells]
[GOGETA grunts]
[BROLY, GOGETA grunting]
[yells]
[GOGETA yelling]
[BROLY groans]
[GOGETA yells]
[BROLY yelling]
[BROLY, GOGETA grunt]
[BROLY grunts]
[screaming]
[GOGETA chuckles]
If they keep fighting,
Broly’s gonna be killed!
Damn his father.
He turned him into this.
In his heart, Broly’s
just a confused boy.
I can’t sit around
and let him die.
He’s a pure, kindhearted Saiyan
whose only friend in the
universe was an animal.
We can’t let this be his end!
Hurry, Lemo,
we don’t have much time!
[LEMO gasping]
[BROLY yelling]
[yells]
[GOGETA growls, yells]
[BROLY yells]
[GOGETA yells]
[BROLY groaning]
[GOGETA yelling]
[BROLY screams]
[GOGETA chuckles]
Uh...?
Wha‐‐? No!
I shall grant you any one wish
that is within my power.
[CHEELAI]
Okay. What do we say next?
Hurry up with it.
[KIKONO whimpers]
[LEMO]
Don’t even think about it.
Fine, then. I’ll shoot.
No, no, please don’t!
I’ll read it now.
It says, "Just say whatever
you want to wish for."
That’s all?
I thought it’d be harder.
[CHEELAI]
All right, listen up, Dragon!
[BROLY groaning]
[BROLY yelling]
[GOGETA yells]
[BROLY groans]
[BROLY yells]
[BROLY growls, yells]
[GOGETA grunting]
[GOGETA yells]
[BROLY groans]
[BROLY growls, yells]
[BROLY yelling]
[groaning]
[GOGETA yells]
How truly magnificent!
I think this battle is about
to come to a rousing finale.
[GOGETA]
Ka...
...me...
...ha...
[BROLY groaning]
[GOGETA]
Ha!
[BROLY groaning]
[screams]
Save Broly!
And send him back to the planet
he grew up on! Please, Dragon!
Huh?
[BROLY grunting]
[SHENRON]
Your wish has been granted.
Farewell!
[GOGETA chuckles]
[CHEELAI, KIKONO gasping]
Quick! Get in, Cheelai!
[CHEELAI]
See ya!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOGETA]
Not so fast.
[GOGETA chuckles]
[FRIEZA grunts]
I will be back for
this planet one day.
[GOGETA]
Hmph.
[coos]
[BEERUS] Mm... Looks like
everything turned out all right.
[CHEELAI]
Sorry for what happened.
I didn’t mean for you
to get mixed up in things.
Don’t worry about it.
Y’know, these have been
the most exciting few days
I’ve had since I joined
the Frieza Force.
[CHEELAI]
Think they’ll come after us?
It’s hard to say.
So, where are you planning
to go now, Cheelai?
Back to Broly’s world.
Vampa, really?
[CHEELAI] I can always drop you
off somewhere along the way.
Nah, I think I’ll tag along
with you for a while.
I’m a wanted man no matter where
I go after what we just pulled.
Having Broly to protect us
might actually put
my mind at ease a bit.
Whoa!
Well, if that’s the case,
we should stop and pick up
some food and supplies.
[KIKONO]
Sure enough, my lord.
It appears both the traitors
are with Broly.
[FRIEZA] Then let us leave them
alone for the time being.
We’ll allow them to
domesticate the brute
and bring his mind
under control.
Once he can release that immense
power without losing his senses,
I’ll come back for him.
That’s when he’ll become
my mightiest warrior.
Do you think that will work,
Lord Frieza?
I certainly hope that it does,
for all of our sakes.
No matter how much I manage
to raise my battle power,
my most hated foes, Goku and
Vegeta, remain triumphant.
I would like to have
someone at my disposal...
...to massacre them.
[laughs]
You’re kidding, aren’t you?
This is what you’ve
been surviving on?
Bleurgh.
Well, it’s sour,
but I guess it’s better
than starving to death.
You tried it yet?
[LEMO]
Mm? Hmm...
[LEMO gags]
[LEMO]
Nope. Count me out.
[CHEELAI] You won’t be
saying that for long.
We can’t even last 50 days
on the food we brought.
[BROLY grunts]
Somebody else just got here.
Huh?
[GOKU]
Hey! Can I come in?
[LEMO grunting]
What the‐‐?
Wait, hold on. Who are you guys?
You’re that Saiyan!
The one he fought on Earth!
Oh, I remember!
You’re the ones who used the
Dragon Balls instead of Frieza.
What are you doing on Vampa?
Wha‐‐?
So, Broly, are these guys
your friends now?
[LEMO]
Don’t ignore me!
I asked you a question!
Hey, come on, no need
to lose your temper.
I’m not here to
fight today. I swear.
Then start talking.
From what I heard,
this world is "repugnant."
So, I brought him some
good stuff from Earth.
Who asked you to do that?!
Get outta here.
I’m not gonna let you trick him!
[laughs]
I asked my friend Bulma
to make you these capsules.
She’s real smart.
You, uh, might wanna stand back.
[LEMO, CHEELAI gasp]
[GOKU] There’s food, water, and
a bunch of other stuff inside.
Go on, have a look
for yourselves.
[BOTH gasping]
[GOKU] Oh, yeah, and these
are called senzu beans.
I’m giving you two of them.
Eat one if you ever think,
"Yikes, I’m gonna die!" Okay?
They don’t work
against illnesses,
but they’ll completely heal
any of your battle injuries
and restore you to full power.
Bet the house’ll
shrink down and kill us.
It’s not like that, trust me.
I just want you guys
to be safe and healthy.
[BOTH]
Why?
I was so sure my strength
was getting close to its peak,
but then this guy showed up and
was so much stronger than me.
And he’s a Saiyan,
just like I am.
He’s probably even
stronger than Beerus.
Oh, Beerus is a God of
Destruction, by the way.
[WHIS]
Classy...
It’d be a shame to see
someone so incredible
die on this planet.
Then who would I train against?
[GOKU]
Well, anyway.
Make sure you take
care of yourselves.
Later.
[LEMO]
Uhh...? I don’t see a ship.
How’d you even get all
the way to this planet?
I tracked Broly’s energy here.
I used my Instant
Transmission technique.
I basically don’t understand
a single thing you’ve
said this whole time.
Is it okay if I come back again?
Just so you know,
we still view you as
an enemy, you got that?
We may have quit
the Frieza Force,
but we’re not gonna befriend
every Saiyan we meet
on some remote planet.
That’s fine, doesn’t
matter to me either way.
[CHEELAI]
It doesn’t?
[GOKU] As long as you
let me come and fight Broly
every once in a while, I’m good.
Huh...?
There’s plenty of stuff
I want to teach him, too‐‐
if he’s interested.
I think you’ve been hit in
the head one too many times.
Really? Why’s that?
Eh. Never mind, I guess
I should be grateful.
So, yeah. Thanks?
Oh, sure.
Bye, then, I’ll see
you all later.
You realize we might not even
be here when you return, right?
That’s not a problem at all.
As long as you’re not too
far away, I can find you.
[gasps] Hey, wait.
What’s your name?
It’s Goku.
But Broly...
...call me Kakarot.
♪ Monochromatic
Mother Earth ♪
♪ Too dark to see the morning ♪
♪ A tension in the atmosphere ♪
♪ It’s cold and never thawing ♪
♪ Follow common sense ♪
♪ In the way
That I’ve been told ♪
♪ But will it really
Make me happy? ♪
♪ Now I realize my breath
Has started to freeze ♪
♪ I’m in the middle
Of the blizzard
I can feel the pressure ♪
♪ Got ice encased
Around my heart
The beats the only measure ♪
♪ Of even knowing I’m alive
Come turn this pain
To pleasure ♪
♪ Before I shut right down
And shut the door for good ♪
♪ There’s a world
That’s towering over me ♪
♪ If I try to climb it
Will I succeed? ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I’ll find the truth
Deep inside ♪
♪ Life is in my hands
So no need to pray ♪
♪ ’Cause I’m ready now
For the judgment day ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ It’s gonna be mine to claim ♪
♪ No one else gets to decide ♪
♪ ’Cause the future’s only made
For you and I ♪
♪ Yeah, such an narrow world
Full of empty dreams ♪
♪ Poison ivy twists
Like my haunted screams ♪
♪ Staring through the fog
I can finally see ♪
♪ I will blow it all away
Like a blizzard ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Break the ice
Break the ice
Break the ice now ♪
♪ Break the ice
Break the ice
Break the ice now ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Break the ice
Break the ice
Break the ice now ♪
♪ Break the ice
Break the ice
Break the ice now ♪
♪ There’s a world
That’s towering over me ♪
♪ If I try to climb it
Will I succeed? ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I’ll find the truth
Deep inside ♪
♪ Life is in my hands
So no need to pray ♪
♪ ’Cause I’m ready now
For the judgment day ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I’ll be the one to decide ♪
♪ It is my right to be free ♪
♪ ’Cause the future’s only made
For you and I ♪
♪ And the story will ♪
♪ Last forever more ♪