[AKO]
I'll ask again.
Would you please
marry me, Rusian?
I fear I must decline.
[AKO]
Oh no...
May I ask why?
I swore to myself I would
never fall in love again.
I'm sorry, but that's
just the way it is.
I understand.
Then we should consider
getting married.
Ah!
Did you bother listening
to a single word I said?
I heard you, and
yet I dare to dream!
That's pretty tame,
as far as dares go.
If we get married,
we'll have even more fun!
'Cause It's dangerous
to go alone!
[RUSIAN]
Look. I'm glad you've found
this sudden surge of confidence,
but my answer is still no!
[AKO]
Why won't you say yes?!
[RUSIAN]
Here they come!
[OGRES roaring]
Now, Schwein!
[SCHWEIN]
I'm on it!
[chuckles]
Lightweight chumps.
[AKO]
Rusian!
I won't let you die
like this! I cast Cure 3!
Hey, dummy!
That spell pulls aggro!
Ako!
[AKO yelping]
[RUSIAN yelling]
Thanks, Rusian!
You stay back and
worry about healing.
Oh, poopie.
Hey, Master, what's the hold up?
[APRICOT]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Behold! Ha!
Witness the magnified firepower
of my extra buffed up staff!
[AKO] Amazing, Master!
Way to take out the mob trash!
You One Hit KO'ed
the whole area?
How much did you drop on
that fancy staff of yours?
Actually, I think it was from
this little magic booster.
When you buy ten,
they throw in the 11th free.
Don't use it on mobs.
It's a waste.
Then again, perhaps if
I had been quicker,
we wouldn't have had any
unnecessary casualties.
I'm so sorry, Rusian!
I'll bring you back right away!
Revive!
Please forgive me, Rusian!
Hey, it's fine.
What's done is done.
Thank you for not holding
your death against me!
I love you!
Uh...
Sweet, thanks.
[HIDEKI]
Breaking news!
At long last, I have
found myself a wife!
You say the exact same crap
every three months, Romeo.
Oh yeah? Isn't your body
pillow gonna be jealous?
That's different
and you know it.
Hey, Nishimura, got any anime
recommendations this season?
You bet I do!
This season's gonna be extra hot
with The Dogra Magra Chronicles.
You're pretty hardcore
into this geek stuff, aren't ya?
There's no use
tryin' to hide it.
Hide it?
Hideki's an open otaku, man.
So? What's the big deal?
I'm still into anime and
video games. Get over it.
Tch. Gross.
The whole "Otaku appeal"
thing is absolutely revolting.
[HIDEKI]
How mean!
Easy now, Akane.
Wait, just think about it.
There are wine otakus, and
flower otakus, you name it!
Someone somewhere
is nerding out over it.
And still, you remain
disgusting, Nishimura.
Hey, take it easy!
He doesn't need to hear that!
We're all thinking
the same, but still!
You guys just made it,
like, 20 times worse!
How could you say that about me?
And you couldn't even
try to sugar coat it?
Geez, Akane.
[HIDEKI]
What would you know, Four-Eyes?!
I'm done listening to this.
Okay, listen up! There's an
all-school assembly today!
It's time for everyone
to head to the gym!
Have you guys heard? Maeda in
Class 3 told her he loved her.
That dude's brave.
And?
He crashed and burned.
Yeah, well, that's what happens.
Seriously?
I thought she'd be
just your type!
She's all cute and petite,
and rockin' the twin tails.
If she were the shy
standoff-ish type,
but that chick's just
straight up mean. Uh!
Keep talkin' like that, and I'll
punch your lips out your butt.
I don't think she's bluffing.
[BOTH grunt]
Sorry! Are you all right?
I'm-- Oh no.
She didn't have to do that.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm student council
president Goshoin.
I'd like to extend
my gratitude to you all
for attending this assembly.
[HIDEKI]
Hi, I'm home!
[HIDEKI] The game that
we play is an MMORPG
called Legendary Age .
It gets reduced to LA in most
chat channels and game forums.
It's a way to have
some fun online.
Parts of it cost actual money,
but the core game is free.
With multiple people
accessing it at the same time,
we can share in adventures
in this virtual world.
Do it now!
So anyway, I declared
my love on a pier
looking over a romantic
sparkling lake.
You mean he made the
girl come out and say it?
Wuss doesn't even
begin to describe him.
--[APRICOT chuckles]
--[RUSIAN whimpers]
I can't believe he
made you ask him.
Ha! But he made up for it
by giving me this gold ring
that increases my resistance
to all types of damage!
[RUSIAN] Hey, guys! I pulled
those mobs! A little help?
I can't tank if you're chatting!
[AKO]
Are you okay, Rusian?
[RUSIAN]
Am I okay?
Not really. Mostly because
of your fumbling, Ako.
You miss your targets
and heal mobs.
You get lost because you were
too caught up in chatting.
Do you have any idea what my
armor repair costs have been
because of you?
Look, I'm really sorry.
Well, my experience points
were barely on the plus side,
so it's no big deal.
[AKO]
Rusian, you're so kind!
I, uh--
[SCHWEIN]
You're an armored knight.
Tanking is your responsibility.
Though, even when you die,
it doesn't affect this bad
mamma-jamma in the slightest.
If only our attacker
knew what they were doing,
then this wouldn't be a problem.
You sucking's my fault?
[APRICOT chuckles]
Just feel free to leave the mob
annihilation to yours truly.
I can do it.
As long as I have my stash
of pricy, real money buffing
items and artifacts,
it won't be a problem!
[BOTH] Lousy stinking
premium player scum.
[RUSIAN]
It's been nearly a year
since the four of us
formed this guild.
We've done a lot of
questing together.
We get along pretty well,
which makes playing
together more fun.
And Ako here is, for lack
of a better term, my waifu.
Although, our marriage
is only in the game.
I just couldn't bring myself
to turn her down again
after the last time
she proposed to me.
So, in this fantasy world,
I have a beautiful wife.
Which does not match my luck
with women in real life.
[HIDEKI] "I am now speaking
directly into your mind
so that we can have
a little privacy."
This is no time to be chatting
with the other guild members.
Instead, you should be paying
attention to your loving wife.
Your loving wife...
[RUSIAN]
Ako? Hello?
Man, she's always
doing things her way.
Seems like the two of you
are stuck together
like glue today, huh?
That's just 'cause Ako
won't leave me alone.
[SCHWEIN]
Heh. Like a couple of normies.
It's not in real life, okay?
It's just in the game,
you get me?
Hmm... Sure, I guess.
Now that I think of it,
I might be the biggest
normie in the whole group.
The other day, someone declared
their love for me in IRL.
For real?
[APRICOT chuckles]
[RUSIAN] Schew must be a real
looker. I always had a hunch.
I know I shouldn't be,
but I'm getting jealous!
[AKO
Wow, really, Schew?
[RUSIAN] Good-looking
guys can all piss off!
Why don't you shove off and die?
[SCHWEIN]
Huh?
Ako?
[AKO] Freaking normies
are the absolute worst.
And anybody who
gets confessed to
ought to just get
out of the game.
Just being close to one of them
makes me sick to my stomach.
And those are the people
who can die off.
They're nothing more than
a plague on the rest of us.
[chuckles]
I said no, you psycho!
This bad mamma-jamma ain't
got time for that stuff!
You're creepin' us
all out, calm down!
[chuckling]
[RUSIAN]
Hey, Ako, come back to us!
I freaking hate
normie losers too,
but you shouldn't take
it out on your guildmates.
Please forgive me, you guys.
Sure, but I get what you
were saying about normies.
I feel the same way as you.
By and large, I concur.
[GUYS sigh]
This guild is too
bent out of shape.
[APRICOT]
Mm-hmm.
[SCHWEIN] I don't know we've
enjoyed some peace and quiet
for a couple minutes now.
All right, fine!
I'll just say it!
Time after time, Rusian rejected
my love-filled proposals
to join together in the bliss
of digital matrimony!
The stress of it all
was shortening my life
like a D.O.T. bomb!
In the end, it all worked
out okay, didn't--?
[AKO]
But it's all about the journey!
I made ten proposals, and you
turned me down each time!
Ten times! Don't you have
any common decency?
[RUSIAN]
Hmm... Right, I get it.
What say we just
do a hard reset?
Start over from our
first conversation?
[thud]
I was only kidding,
my darling! I'm sorry!
Please don't divorce me,
I'm begging you! Have mercy...
Hey, why didn't you say yes
the first time she asked?
In-game marriages are dumb.
It's a role-playing mechanic
I could do without.
It's an online game!
Not the real,
flesh and blood world!
It's not like you have a shot
at getting married
in real life anyway.
Might as well go through
with it in-game.
So where do we draw
the line? With AI babes?
[AKO]
I know the real reason.
Rusian once asked another player
to get married here
in the game world.
[screams]
He did?
Oh?
Ako, how could you say that?
I was trying to
keep that a secret!
[APRICOT] You have to
tell us now, obviously.
[RUSIAN]
I'm begging you, my lady.
Marry me. Give me thine hand.
I'm afraid you'll
have to count meow-t.
I swear, I am in love with you!
[NEKOHIME sighs]
[NEKOHIME] Sorry, but I'm
actually a guy in real life.
I'm a middle-aged dude.
At first I wanted to
ogle a sexy avatar,
but then I got caught up
in cross-playing.
[RUSIAN]
Huh?
I mean, what chick would say
"meow" puns in real life?
Not the kinda girl
you'd wanna date.
[RUSIAN, HIDEKI scream]
[HIDEKI]
Damn it! Damn it!
I swear, I will never
trust another girl
I meet on the net again!
For as long as I live!
[APRICOT, SCHWEIN laughing]
[RUSIAN] You guys don't
have to laugh that hard!
[SCHWEIN] That chapter of
your life is beyond dark.
Ah, the majesty of young love.
Fart-knockers.
[RUSIAN]
The thing is, Nekohime,
the girl I first declared my
love to, was super cute,
had good taste
in equipment,
was nice to everyone she
played with and played well.
She was the ideal girl--
I mean, girl character.
The sheer shock of her
revelation was devastating.
To the point that I left
the guild I was with,
and for nearly a year after,
I stuck with solo
play exclusively.
Then, in my solitude,
I arrived at a certain truth.
Who cares as long
as they're cute!
Even if they are dudes in
real life, I don't care!
As long as they're cute in game.
Ultimately, it was the
cuteness in the game
I was enamored with.
Yes, I discovered the horrible
truth lurking on the web.
Rusian, are you mad at me?
For telling everyone
what happened
with you and the cat girl?
That kinda stuff happens
all the time, so don't worry.
Thank you so much, Rusian!
I love you.
[gasps]
Huh. Just calm down.
You gotta cool it, Hideki.
You know from experience that
if you take it too seriously,
you'll only regret it.
[APRICOT]
It makes sense.
Now I see why you were
so hesitant to agree.
All this spouse stuff has
nothing to do with me
in real life,
but in the world of
the game, Ako is Ako.
Just so you know,
I actually am female.
Yeah, fine. If you
say so, then you are.
At least to you, that is.
No, no.
In real life, I'm a nerdy,
nose-in-her-book kind of girl.
[SCHWEIN]
Whoa, hold on.
You shouldn't admit something
like that in open chat, Ako.
It's the greatest
net taboo of all.
I had no idea.
Taboos are ludicrous.
I, for example, am a high
school girl in real life.
You, Master?
A high school girl?
With that premium gear?
Not a chance.
Impossible.
Seriously, no way.
I'm pouring my heart
out to my friends,
and this is how you treat me?
Actually admitting it
feels kind of nice,
but what if we did this?
"Guild Alley Cats..."
"...First Offline Get Together"?
To be held in real life?
[RUSIAN, AKO, SCHWEIN]
Wha--?!
Guess they aren't here yet.
And what are the odds that
we're all pretty local?
We've been a guild for almost
a year now, and never knew?
"I'm by the big tree
in front of the station.
In a white T-shirt."
[GIRL]
Excuse me? Rusian?
[HIDEKI] Um, yeah.
That's me. I'm Rusian.
[GIRL] I-I knew it was you,
and I'm A-Ako.
From the game?
Hi, nice to meet you.
[HIDEKI]
Wow, Ako? The real Ako.
[AKO]
Yes.
You're a girl... in real life.
You aren't just pretending.
Um... Rusian? Ah!
Wow! Rusian! It's really you!
My husband Rusian,
live in the flesh!
Cool it! Stop calling
me by my username!
What if someone I know sees us?
[AKANE]
You're Rusian?
Nishimura? You're him?
[HIDEKI]
Wait, Segawa? Huh... Umm...
You already know each other?
Um, kinda. I mean,
I've seen him before.
Well, I'm glad to see
everyone got here safely.
It's you.
Madam President?
[KYOH]
Not today.
I'm not here as the student
council president,
but as the Alley Cats'
Guildmaster, the wizard Apricot!
[HIDEKI, AKANE gasp]
[KYOH]
You must be Rusian,
and the one clinging to you,
I assume, is Ako.
Yeah, that's right.
Wait, you said everyone.
[AKANE gasps]
[HIDEKI]
You? You're Schwein?
Oh. Hi, Schew.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Ah! No! Don't call
me that in public!
No way.
That's exactly what
I was going to say!
[chuckles]
All right,
it's time for Guild Alley Cats'
First Offline Get-Together!
Let's have fun!
[AKO squeals]
[AKO] Rusian, it's you!
I can barely believe it!
You're warm and everything!
You're makin' it sound
like I'm a mannequin
that came to life or somethin'.
Rusian. Rusian.
Mighty, noble Rusian.
Please cut it out.
He's Rusian, all right.
How can you
still be that happy
after he just treated
you so rudely?
Now then, let's start off
with proper introductions.
My name is Kyoh Goshoeen.
I'm a second year
at Maegasaki High
and the student
council president.
I came by on my way
home from school,
so excuse me for not
dressing to the occasion.
We're already good friends,
but we're also meeting
for the first time.
Thus, as questing has forged
our bonds of friendship.
May socializing take it
to the next level!
Now It's your turn.
[AKANE]
Wait, me?
I'm Akane Segawa.
I'm a first year at
Maegasaki and--
And well... here I am.
[KYOH]
I understand, Schwein.
It must be embarrassing
to go by a name like that
in such a public place.
Your name, "Schwein,"
is actually the German
word for "pig."
I doubt there are many
young ladies out there
who would wanna say,
"Hello, my name is Pig.
It's a pleasure to meet you."
[AKANE]
No way...
A pig? Schwein?
I take it you've been using
the name without knowing.
[AKANE whines]
Of course I didn't know!
Who in their right mind would
ever choose "Pig" for a name?
I just picked "Schwein"
because it sounded cool!
[AKO]
Poor, Schew.
My sympathies.
We've been playing
together forever,
how come you never
said anything?
I thought you chose a
joke name on purpose.
[AKANE]
That's right.
I'm the one you call Schwein.
And anyone who starts
calling me pig...
...gets stuck like a pig.
That's all.
All right, then. Rusian?
[HIDEKI]
Okay.
So. Hi there. I'm... I'm Rusian.
It's totally embarrassing
to introduce myself
as my character!
Don't worry, Nishimura,
your existence is
an embarrassment.
[HIDEKI]
That's mean!
Where was I?
My name's Hideki Nishimura.
I'm also a first
year at Maegasaki,
but I'm not in any clubs.
No special talents. My hobbies
are, uh, online gaming.
And that's it.
[AKO]
Hi. My name is Ako.
I always end up as a burden
on you in Legendary Age .
I'm sorry.
Oh, and I'm also a
first year student
at the same high school
as the rest of you.
So then we're classmates?
That's right, I was pleasantly
surprised as well.
My full name is Ako Tamaki,
so you can just keep calling me
"Ako" like you always have.
They're the same?
[AKO]
Yes. Why? Is that unusual?
Well, it's kind of
a net safety issue.
Don't worry about it.
[KYOH chuckles]
How totally Ako.
[AKO]
I'm not involved in any clubs.
And I don't really
have friends at school.
[BOTH gasp]
I tend to sit alone,
which gets the attention
of the other students.
It-It's all right, Ako.
I'm student council president,
and I don't have
any friends either.
Hey, think about this:
The four of us are friends!
Yeah, he's right!
I really appreciate it,
you guys.
I'm so happy to have
friends that I can talk to.
Friends that I can
have fun with.
I can't wait to see how
far our guild can go!
[clapping]
[HIDEKI]
Oh, yeah. Segawa?
What now?
When we were chatting in
the guild hall the other day,
you were telling us that some
guy declared his love for you
in real life, right?
Yeah, that's right.
So what about it?
[HIDEKI] Ha. I just
think it's kinda funny.
Little Miss Popularity.
Not really.
[AKO]
Schew is a total normie.
Schew is a total normie...
Hey! Ako?
Interesting.
Let the record show
that Schwein,
unlike the rest of us,
is a verified normie.
You should pick us up
in your minivan next time.
[HIDEKI]
Master, you too?
[AKANE] Like I already said,
I told the guy no.
I'm not interested in
going out with anyone.
I've been told that
Maeda from Class 3
is pretty popular
with the ladies.
Is he just not your type?
[AKANE]
I-It's not that.
If I had a dumb boyfriend,
it would cut into my time
playing video games.
[HIDEKI]
That's why you turned him down?
You wouldn't seriously want
something like that, would you?
Definitely not for me.
I'd turn him down.
You genuinely would
rather play video games?
[AKANE] Damn straight.
You got a problem with that?
Nope.
I definitely prefer this
to who you are at school.
I don't think I should take
that statement as a compliment.
[AKO] I may have an idea
to turn that around!
So, Schew, have you ever
considered getting married
in the game?
Rusian and I did, and we've
been having fun ever since!
You wouldn't lose any
gaming time that way.
Plus, you'd be spending time
with the one you love.
It's a total twofer!
I think I'll pass, thanks.
It sounds gross.
[HIDEKI]
That's mean!
I think it's a great idea!
Right, Rusian?
Yeah, but I can still
hardly believe it myself.
[AKO]
Huh?
[HIDEKI]
Ako, you're so...
I have a living, breathing
girl as my 2D wife.
Oh, Rusian!
[AKO] Are you trying
to humiliate me?
Lately, it's been frowned
on for the heroine
to be too forward
in Episode One,
but you're taking it too far
the other way, Rusian!
[HIDEKI]
I'm not the heroine here!