[KYOH] Remember, you guys,
this battle is our final chance.
Our objective is to
capture the fort
and hold it until the
siege timer runs out.
It's still under the control
of Guild Wallenstein.
We're going to take
it back from them.
Aren't we setting the
hurdle kinda high?
[HIDEKI] Actually, I don't think
it'll be that big of a problem.
They probably won't
even be in the fort.
What makes you think that?
He said as much in front
of us, that Bats guy.
Playing defensively
isn't any fun.
Conquering a player who's
desperately defending something
is much more entertaining.
[HIDEKI]
Those are his words.
I can't believe you would
even talk to that jerk
after he and his cronies
stabbed our guild in the back!
I can.
It's just like you two to endear
yourselves to that Alpha Geek.
[HIDEKI]
"You two" my pixelated butt!
It was Ako that was endearing.
[gasps]
But talking to him
was your idea!
So does that mean it should
be easy to take the fort?
Not necessarily.
I highly doubt
we're the only guild
planning to lay siege to it.
Capturing it is easy.
Defending it until the timer
runs out is the difficult part.
Which we had to learn
the hard way last time, huh?
Attacking and defending?
Bring it on!
I'll show off the results
of my practice!
Our real problem
is the end game.
If we're successful...
...they'll come again.
[KYOH] Mm. Which means PvP
versus the masters, Wallenstein.
And I, for one, am looking
forward to some payback.
That's strange.
I thought Phine would've
shown up for this.
He had to attend his
kid's field day.
Huh? Does that mean I'm the
only tank in the entire group?
[KYOH]
Welcome to all.
I'm beyond grateful that so many
of you have come together
to aid us in our time of need.
Now with our forces combined,
we in Guild Alley Cats,
with our comrades in
Nekohime's Elite Guard,
for this battle
shall be known as:
Alley Cat-Princess Elite Guard!
[groans]
Seriously?
We stand with Nekohime!
I see what they did.
"Nekohime" translates
to "Cat-Princess."
You just put that together?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Attention!
The siege warfare event
is now under way!
Sweet! I'm fired up!
Yeah!
Let's go do our best, Mu-tan!
[KYOH] May the victory we claim
here echo throughout eternity!
Alley Cat-Princess
Elite Guard! Move out!
[ELITE GUARD cheers]
[YUYUN]
The enemy got here first!
There're over 30 of them!
Emperor Sword, huh?
That's the same guild
that we took the fort from
the first time.
When did Yuyun get here?
[YUYUN]
I've been here!
They got in before we could.
[KYOH] Switch from defensive
posture to attack formation!
Let's take that fort!
Guess I'll go get the
siege weapons ready!
Good. Go.
Blast 'em!
Into the breach!
[ELITE GAURD yelling]
For the glory of our Mistress!
Drive the enemy out of here!
Kill! Kill!
Bring me their leader and we'll
stick his ugly head on a pike!
Damn... Can't break through!
We seem to be short
on teammates!
Gi! Move out!
Melee Gi, move out!
Decoy Gi, move out!
Transport Gi, move out!
That's a whole buncha robots!
None of which we need right now!
We're out of material!
We're gonna need more people
on the resource gathering team!
Too many gis and
not enough fighters!
Sette's overachieving is
starting to work against us!
[HIDEKI] Damn it!
They're not breaking rank!
We don't have enough tanks!
If we could just get an
opening for a half a second!
So you need an opening?
Okay then.
Hey, guys! Hang in there
a little bit longer!
The Black Magician is on
his way here now to help us!
[SETTE]
Oops! Wrong crowd.
So that was open chat.
Well come on, guys, why
don't you say something too?
[RUSIAN]
Not true. You're mistaken.
TMW's definitely not coming!
That's more fighting for us!
Okay! That's your opening!
Uh? It is?
Hurry up!
[ALL laughing]
[EMPEROR SWORD A]
Yeah, as if!
[EMPEROR SWORD B]
That's not even plausible!
[EMPEROR SWORD C] You guys
trying to bluff is too cute!
[AKANE]
You're mine! Take this!
Hog-wild attack!
It's almost like I died
and went to hog heaven!
If I strike twice,
I'm one shot ahead!
That's how you rock bad
mamma-jamma style!
See? You got through just fine!
How did you know they'd be
distracted while replying?
What if she turns that
sorcery against us?
Exploit the opening!
Push forward!
[KYOH] Come back for the
stronger opponents later!
For now, make sure to pick
off the weaker ones!
That's brutal.
[AKANE]
Slice and dice!
I'm putting it in.
[ANNOUNCER] Fort Cantor has
now come under the control
of Guild Alley Cats.
--All right!
--We did it!
This is way more satisfying
than the last time!
Sure is!
Keep an eye out.
We'll be defending right away.
[HIDEKI]
Twenty minutes left.
If we can defend
against this--
All forces charge forth!
We're charging?
Ako! Keep your eyes on me!
Um.
You're our mage!
What're you doing out front?
Remember, Ako!
Just keep your eyes on me!
What am I supposed
to be looking for?
[KYOH]
For me to do this!
[EMPEROR SWORD D]
Stop 'em, fellas!
Her stamina's way
higher than normal!
What's going on?
Ako!
Right!
Extra Damage Buff!
[KYOH]
Behold.
This is what happens when
I max out my attack power!
[laughing]
What do you know?!
Nicely done!
Uh! Thanks!
The timing was spot on.
I think I got my extra
damage buff in there too.
Come on.
This was Ako's moment.
[HIDEKI]
Only ten minutes remaining.
Just about time.
[AKANE]
And here comes the real fight.
Incoming!
What's the enemy breakdown?
[YUYUN]
Five players approaching.
It's Wallenstein.
They're here.
I knew you'd be coming,
Bats. Tough news.
We'll defend to the last man.
Now's the time!
What say we show these
turncoats what we're made of?
[ELITE GUARD]
Oh, yeah!
Rusian's squad, maintain
the second defensive line!
You got it!
Schwein's squad is on
standby in the inner courtyard.
If they get past Rusian's squad,
you come to greet them!
Gladly!
Here they come! Fire!
[yells]
Now, Schwein!
All right, guys! It's go time!
They know what you're doing!
Doesn't matter now!
[yells]
Damn! This battle's hopeless!
[AKANE]
It's not hopeless. Not yet!
Whoa, don't those white elixirs
go for like 500
freakin' K per potion?
How many did you take?
Enough to teach them a lesson!
I'm gonna show these jerks
I'm done messing around!
[AKANE]
Blade dance!
[growls]
I gave it everything
I had there.
I guess I'm not as useful
as I thought I was.
That's ridiculous!
You're our MVP!
Two minutes left?
We've got time to spare.
You dirty bastard.
Well then, do your worst!
Oh, hey there, Mr. Bats!
Oh, crap. We wasted
our cooldown skills!
Niaow! Crush these clowns!
[SETTE] Hey, Bats, you ever
hear of "bait and switch"?
'Cause you just fell for it!
Shut up, you scrub!
[RUSIAN]
He's stunned!
That's two of 'em down!
Only three more to go, guys!
Another one bites the dust!
I regret nyao-thing!
[BOTH gasp]
You bastard!!
Time to die!
Hiya.
Tank-on-tank action?
No one has the advantage!
Oh yeah.
My stun is about the only thing
with a chance of stopping Bats!
Outta my way!
You've gotta hurry up!
You're the only one who
can keep our crystal safe!
I know, but I can't
get past this guy!
Never fear...
for Apricot is here.
[BATS] One minute left,
and one person in my way.
Ha! This is gonna be too easy!
That chat left you
with 55 seconds.
Looks like somebody needs
to work on his typing speed!
Master!
Huh?
[KYOH chuckles]
Hang on. How are you
even still alive?
I can't believe it's working!
Whatever happens,
keep spamming that hotkey!
I need some help!
Come here! This one's trouble!
I need you to throw
a stun, Koro!
Ain't gonna happen!
Damn it!
Watch out, Master!
A stun's coming!
You gotta move!
I will not run!
If they get through,
then it's all over!
[RUSIAN]
But you'll die!
Not on my watch!
[AKO]
Peep-peep.
[BATS]
Out of my way!
Perfect timing, Ako!
Great job! Ako, you rock!
[HIDEKI, SAITO chuckle]
Why're you all so happy?
That guy just killed me!
[RUSIAN]
Let's dance!
[RUSIAN] Master, come on!
It's now or never!
[laughing]
Is that all you've got, Bats?
How very disappointing.
[BATS] Come on!
Just die already, dammit!
[RUSIAN, AKO, AKANE]
Three. Two. One.
Time's up!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Today's siege warfare event
has now come to an end.
[BATS]
You've gotta be kidding.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
The victors of the siege event
are as follows:
TMW have now been instated
as the lords of Lodestone.
The Aristocrats have
now been instated
as the lords of the
great citadel of Gramberg.
The Cleaning Crew
have now been instated
as the lords of the mighty
Templar Fortress of Ray Sword.
The Alley Cats have
now been instated
as the lords of Fort Cantor.
[cheers]
We won!
I'm so happy!
Well done!
In your face, Wallenstein!
Right in your dumb faces!
Lady Nekohime is victorious!
All glory unto our cat goddess!
Great work! I really
admire myew fellas!
[RUSIAN]
We made it!
[AKANE]
Well done, soldiers!
Gi! Powered by Mu-tan!
He'd just pull bigger mobs.
[KYOH] We fought for it,
and now the fort is all ours!
[ELITE GUARD cheering]
Are you crazy? You have
any idea what you've done?
What's the matter,
you a sore loser?
I didn't lose.
Every time I hit you, you used
a Drop of Ygg, didn't you?
Wait, what're you saying?
You mean a Drop of Yggdrasil?
Those are ten mil a piece!
[BATS]
How many of 'em did you use?
Let's see.
I started the battle with
500 hundred of them
and now I have 13 left.
I guess we won by a
really narrow margin.
You really drank
that many potions?
Taking over this castle doesn't
even net you five million.
What are you,
some kind of idiot?
He's got a point. How'd you
even end up with so much money?
It would take years to earn that
much just by killing monsters.
It's quite simple, actually.
I sold off the items
in my inventory
that I didn't need anymore.
Stuff you didn't need?
There's no way that would've
even come close to enough.
All I had to do was sell
the rest of my mystery boxes
and the premium items
that came with them.
In other words... real money.
That's a full-blown RMT,
you raging weirdo!
I never violated the
terms of use. How rude.
How many tens of
thousands did you spend?
[KYOH chuckles]
I got everything
for a single coin.
[BATS]
Like hell you did.
It's all true, Bats,
whether you believe it or not.
It wouldn't matter if
I had to spend millions.
If it helped out my friends,
it was but one coin to me.
[laughing]
That's a terrible
waste of money.
You're wrong.
This was easily the second most
beneficial financial transaction
I've ever been involved in.
This one really is crazy!
But I like that! Respect!
[HIDEKI] I guess Master endears
herself to weirdos too.
That's not exactly a compliment.
So it was real money after all.
I suppose a leopard can't change
its spots, can it, Master?
One thing I don't get.
What's that?
About what you told him,
how this was the second
most beneficial use
of your money so far.
So what was the first?
[chuckles]
I'm surprised you have to ask.
The best use of my money so far
was when I bought
my partner here.
[HIDEKI]
Whaddaya say?
You charged in head first
and got hacked to pieces.
Any regrets?
No way! I don't regret a thing!
I'm happy I actually tried!
[HIDEKI]
That's great!
Now it's time for the
culture festival itself!
You got this!
[yelps]
[STUDENT A]
Uhh... what's with this?
Hey, it's looking
pretty busy, isn't it?
Compared to some of the
school's other clubs,
I don't think our turnout is
anything to really brag about.
Yeah, well.
But still,
this screengrab will always be
something for us to be proud of.
Yo!
Well, at least our club had
a better time prepping
for the culture festival
than the other kids did.
Try not to get too chummy with
me when we're at school, 'kay?
Yeah, yeah.
[AKANE sighs]
[AKANE] I never would've thought
from the first day of school
you and I would ever end up
talking like this, you know?
You're saying this now?
We chat normally in the club
or in the game all the time.
It's like you said: The game
and reality are different.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
You did well today,
so consider this an award
for fighting spirit.
You're eating grilled
pork like a cannibal.
[AKANE]
Hardee-har, wise guy!
You gonna see the
other club displays?
No, I think I'll skip 'em.
Besides, you're going to check
out Ako's room, right?
[HIDEKI]
Uh-huh.
Throw it away when you're done.
Thank you!
I guess I'll see you around.
Partner.
[TAKASAKI]
Yo, Nishimura!
You sure took your time.
It's maid-o-clock, bro!
[AKO screams]
I just can't take it anymore!
Hey, Ako!
Hi, Rusian.
I don't think you're
supposed to run away.
I know, but--
Come on, get back in there.
Welcome to our maid café,
my darling!
I don't think that's the kinda
thing a maid usually says.
Aw, who am I kidding?.
Ako's not just some maid.
She's my wife.
This isn't fair. Why aren't
Master and the others
helping us clean
all of this junk up?
It's all right.
I think it's kinda fun!
Yeah.
So hey, this whole regular
school life thing
isn't so bad, is it?
No. It's okay I guess.
But that's only because
I get to be here with you,
and Schwein, and Master.
The whole Net Game Club
makes it all worthwhile.
[HIDEKI]
Still, I'm proud of you
for hanging in there during
the culture festival.
[AKO] Thanks!
I'm kinda proud of me too!
[HIDEKI] You were even
the café's head maid.
[AKO]
Please don't remind me.
[laughs]
Well I think you did
a pretty good job, Ako.
[AKO] Good enough to give me
some kind of reward?
[HIDEKI]
Sure. Anything you want.
[gasps]
You just said I could have
anything I wanted!
Hold on!
By reward, I meant some epic
item acquired in the game!
Big news, you guys!
This next update's gonna
feature player housing!
We're not interrupting
anything, are we?
Uh-huh.
[AKANE groans]
War Machine doesn't need to see
whatever you guys are doing.
No, no, it wasn't like that!
Uh! But you said you'd give me
whatever I wanted for a reward!
Hey, hang on!
No indecent behavior on
school grounds, you guys!
It's not!
I told you, your reward
has to be something
from in the game, okay?
It's the same thing either way
as far as I'm concerned.
[HIDEKI] It's not
the same thing at all!
The game and reality
are completely separate!
[AKO] But it doesn't
have to be that way!