[RUSIAN]
I remember.
This was right after my proposal
to Nekohime was rejected.
My friend Yuyun
and I were talking.
[YUYUN]
Sarasara, my wife,
one of her alt toons just got
married to some other man!
It's okay if it's a
different character, right?
No, it isn't!
She's cheating on me!
She probably just
married her alt off
for the spousal stat bonus.
Some players take the
in-game marriage mechanics
more casually than others.
But not me!
I actually fell in
love with her, man!
I guess Sarasara and I are over.
[RUSIAN]
Maybe.
This isn't fair.
Huh?
[YUYUN] I refuse to be
alone in my suffering!
So I begged your sweet Nekohime
to tell me the reason
she rejected your
marriage proposal.
Whoa! Hang on!
You did what?
The first!
"I am not the slightest
bit interested
in getting married in the game."
[yelps]
The second:
"Rusian is not the only suitor
vying for my affection
in the game."
[screams]
And lastly:
"I am a man, and have no desire
to meow-rry another man."
Soul-crushing. Why did
I ask her to marry me?
Word! Getting married
is lame-sauce!
I'm never doing that crap again!
Yeah! Same goes for me!
[BOTH] We don't need
no stinking marriages!
[RUSIAN] Since then,
Yuyun has married and divorced
two other cross-playing
characters.
This makes wedding number three.
And that's how it went down.
I'm not gonna divorce you.
[RUSIAN]
That was quick.
What I was getting
at was some people
have different stances
on marriage.
[AKO]
Of course,
but that doesn't change how
much I love you Rusian!
Right, well,
that goes for me too.
Look. I mean, not just
in the game world...
Rusian?
[RUSIAN grumbles]
[RUSIAN screams]
Off to bed. Night, Ako!
Oh. Yeah. Good night.
[sighs]
[screams]
[TAKASAKI] "A great sneeze
issued from the man.
With great effort,
the man rose to his feet."
Good. Now, you're next, Rusian.
[HIDEKI yelps, coughs]
I'm sorry. Nishimura.
[STUDENTS laughing]
[STUDENT A]
Check it out!
This one looks nice, doesn't it?
I think this look
is more your style.
Either way you go, they're
both really cute options!
Rusian!
Are you listening to this,
Rusian? It's awful! So awful!
[HIDEKI] It's all right. You can
tell me all about it later.
[AKO]
Just look at this!
It's like a whirlwind
of smug faces
all selling makeup
and clothing that says
"I am the model
that reigns supreme
at the top of the high
school caste system.
Kneel before me and despair!"
Do other girls actually enjoy
reading this garbage?
Yes I do.
If you're going to be
rough with my magazine,
then you can't
borrow it anymore.
[HIDEKI]
Wait. This is yours?
Yeah, it's mine. Got a problem?
[HIDEKI]
No.
All right, Ako.
Listen carefully.
You're looking at
it the wrong way.
Try to think of magazines
like this as a kind of
"Real-life Offline
High-School Girl" strategy wiki.
Wiki?
Right.
Just crack this sucker open
and it gives you a complete
walkthrough on proper skin care
and ideal makeup application.
That's not all!
It covers the minimum
as far as brand names
and celebs you should know.
Everything you need to be a
high school girl in real life!
Guess you're right.
That sounds important.
Wait, you bought that?
Reading a strategy
guide ahead of time
helps you have a better
understanding of the game,
wouldn't you agree?
[AKO] But I always liked the joy
of discovery from playing blind.
You should've gotten over the
LA blind play "honeymoon phase"
a year ago!
Right now, in the offline world,
the only ones looking for
group are high level elites.
And they only recruit players
with a comprehensive
knowledge of the endgame.
No! I can't handle
end-stage games!
Why resist it?
Real-life Offline
runs 24 hours a day,
so we better get good
at it while we can.
I've sunk countless
hours into it,
and if you don't start trying,
you'll never catch up!
Stop it! Please stop it.
Sorry I'm late, guys. Oh...
Is something wrong?
[ALL]
Not really.
[laughing
I understand, Ako.
I know just how you feel.
You too, Master?
I'll go talk to Nanako, and ask
her to tone it down next time.
[KYOH] Moving right along,
what are we doing today?
Uhh...
Hey, I've got an idea
for what we should do!
Why don't we join up with Sette
and get that quest
outta the way?
Ah, good idea!
Ugh.
I've gotta be around Miss Cotton
Candy Head in the game now too?
Try to see things from a
different point of view.
In Legendary Age , you're
a higher level than her.
Yeah, that's true, but still.
[howling]
All too easy.
This was a beginner's
quest for job advancement.
A mere walk in the park for us.
All right. There ya go.
The glowing thing.
I just have to touch it?
[RUSIAN] Yup. After that,
just click "yes."
[SETTE]
Got it!
[GAME VOICE] Sette has received
the divine beast power.
[laughing]
You're a summoner now.
'Grats.
[SETTE]
So can I conjure up my own pet?
Open up your skill panel,
and "summoning" should
be a new addition.
Next, you should consider
your play style,
--and choose a pet accordingly.
--[SETTE] I'll take this one!
It's the perfect pet!
Summoning!
At least she's not indecisive.
[barks]
How adorable!
Aw. I think I'm gonna
name you Mu-Tan.
You can't be serious.
That's the same name
as your dog at home.
Have you researched summoning?
Because generally, it's a job
chosen by veteran players.
I love animals,
so I thought, "Bingo!"
Using your pet to draw
the enemy's focus
while you attack it
from the rear?
This bad mamma-jamma's
more direct.
[giggles] Mamma-jamma.
[AKANE]
Would you drop it already?
Hey, I'm sorry! You just never
talk like that in real life.
You've been playing the game
a couple weeks now, right?
Time to let it go.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[groans] So let me ask you this.
Have you even bothered to look
at the strategy page I sent you?
I read it, but
didn't understand.
Whenever I don't understand
something, Nishimura...
...I mean, Rusian, is the
one I go to for advice.
Yeah, and take a long
look at the results!
You hit the wrong button
to disarm the trap,
and blew us all up!
You attacked that boss monster
when our healer was out of mana,
and caused a party wipe!
My bad.
[AKANE] You paying attention,
Ako? It's just like real life!
This is the result of ignorance!
[AKO]
I understand, Schew!
I'll do anything in my power
to not end up like that!
That isn't the nicest way
to talk to our new friend.
[KYOH chuckles]
I can't believe you
guys seem so relaxed.
About what?
[SETTE] You know. Final exams.
They're coming up soon.
[gasps]
[yelps]
I guess it is about
that time of year.
Uh-huh.
For the time being, our club
is on temporary hiatus.
The club room is off-limits
until testing is over.
That should give us all
a chance to study up.
How can you be so calm, Master?
I'm a good student,
and I excel at test-taking.
The worst part is that
it's totally true!
After we've finished
final exams,
it's off to summer vacation!
[giggles]
You planning something?
What, like an event?
[KYOH] Yes. Something
for us to look forward to!
Umm?
I know it's exam week,
but we're still free to log in
from home, aren't we?
I'll leave that entirely
to your discretion.
Besides, everybody needs the
occasional break from studying!
[AKO] If we're not having
any club meetings,
then I've lost one of my main
reasons for going to school.
Maybe I could just study
at home until the test?
No, you've gotta go!
If you miss any more days,
it might hurt your grade!
[AKO]
I guess you're right,
but I was only coming to school
for club meetings anyway.
There goes my motivation.
You won't be able to participate
in club activities if you flunk.
Push through to the other side.
This sucks.
I only go to school
to do club stuff,
and now I can't do club stuff
because of school?
How odd.
You can pass the
test if you try.
And I'll push you the whole way.
Yeah! Go team!
[AKO] You can push me like
this all the way home.
Stop leaning back,
your Royal Dorkness.
Still. It's almost
summer vacation time!
Summer vacation.
I've got a lot
to do before then.
Oh, no. What? We've got
tests to pass before then!
Tests. What? You are
ready for them, right?
[AKO humming]
Ako?
Personally? I dream of
being a homemaker.
So how did you do
on your midterms?
Like B's or C's? Or maybe D's?
They can't have all been F's.
[AKO whistles]
Seriously?
What to do?
If she gets stuck
doing summer school,
how am I supposed to
declare my love for her?
[MIZUKI]
What are you mumbling about?
[yelps]
[HIDEKI]
Oh, heya, Mizuki.
Hey yourself.
Are you doing anything?
I could use a
little help studying.
Studying?
She needs help with studying.
That's it!
[MIZUKI]
Hold on! Is that a no?
Ugh...
[KYOH]
Excellent idea.
Glad to hear you agree.
[AKANE] That seems like it would
be the most effective option.
Come on, you guys, no way!
Why are you all
conspiring against me?
Rusian!
[RUSIAN]
Next question.
What is the name of the law
where the government allotted
farmland and levied taxes on it?
[AKO]
The Handen Shuju Law.
That's correct.
Make sure that you know
how to write that in kanji.
I've had enough of
Japanese history!
I've got kanji ricocheting
inside my head!
All right then,
we can move on to math,
and this bad mamma-jamma's
gonna tutor you.
But I hate math even more!
My Icicle Wall will make sure
you can't worm your way
out of this study session.
[AKO] This is cruel and unusual!
I wanted to play the game,
but here we are, wasting
our time with studying!
It's the only way we
could get you to do it.
What're you complaining for?
You've got all of your friends
here to help you with this.
We don't wanna lose you,
so we're going to make sure
you get passing grades.
Who really cares about
the first term anyway?
I'll just take a couple make-up
courses over the summer break.
[NEKOHIME]
No, you won't!
The teachers have their hands
full with entrance examinees.
They don't have time to give
make-up classes for freshmen.
If you don't like math,
work on Japanese.
Just a second, please.
You're a teacher in real life.
Doesn't that make this
a make-up class?
I'm not a teacher in the game.
I'm just Nekohime!
Hey, Nishimura.
What is my name?
Sorry, Rusian.
What's all this about Nekohime
actually being a teacher?
That answer's not on
the test, so hey,
let's listen to what
she has to say.
[SETTE]
Okay!
When I look at all those
long, difficult sentences,
it makes my brain start to ache.
But essay writing is essential!
[AKO screams]
[RUSIAN]
Hang in there, Ako.
[SAITO]
All right. Begin.
Our test days are finally over.
Come on, Ako!
Pull yourself together!
I had Ako's answer
sheets graded first,
and it looks like she
passed every one of them!
No make-up classes or
anything? That's awesome!
[NEKOHIME] I'd say all our
effort has finally paid off!
[RUSIAN]
Isn't that great, Ako?
Sure is! Now let's
go do some grinding.
Hey, hold on! You still
seem a little woozy.
You need to catch
up on your sleep.
Aww.
I'm fine.
[KYOH]
And just because tests are over,
it doesn't mean you're allowed
to skip school again.
I understand.
I'll log off now.
Goodnight everyone. Sleep tight.
[RUSIAN]
Yeah, you too.
--Night!
--Goodnight!
[NEKOHIME] I have a stack
of papers to grade.
I'm out too.
--Bye!
--Night!
I can hear my bed
calling my name.
[AKANE]
Yeah, ditto.
Uh, could both of
you hang on a sec?
I, uh... need to ask your
advice about something.
[RUSIAN]
Yeah, so, uh...
I've decided to tell
Ako I love her,
so how should I do it?
Huh? Laggy?
I want to declare my love for
Ako. How do you think I should?
Don't ask us twice.
We heard you.
Then what was that ridiculously
long pause all about?
It's just so beyond too late,
we didn't know how to respond.
You moron!
You're too slow on the draw.
Your timing's all mixed up.
Uh, well, it's almost
summer vacation, you know.
We won't see each other
as much outside the game.
I see.
You want to create
lifelong memories
of youthful summer passion.
Yeah, I guess.
Sure thing, buddy.
You go right ahead and
try that out. Good luck.
Well said. This whole matter
is between you and Ako.
There's nothing we can say
that you don't already know.
How can you both be
so cold-hearted?
Like, what if she turns me down?
[AKANE]
So don't tell her you love her.
No, I have to.
You're being a total pain!
Indeed.
However, given
the circumstances,
I don't see her rejecting
your confession.
She's probably right,
and the sooner you do it,
the better your odds
are gonna be.
Ako's not the type to
shoot her husband down.
You mean it? You're not
just messing with me?
Yes, I mean it.
Yeah, all right,
but I shouldn't do something
this important over the phone.
This is new territory.
I've never really declared
my love to anybody before.
You're both real life girls,
what should I do?
Yes, that's a good question.
[RUSIAN] Surely, you've been
popular with the boys.
Quite the opposite.
I've actually never had
a boyfriend before.
So thanks for bringing that up.
Yikes. And you Schew?
Guys have declared their
love for you, right?
And I've turned them all down.
So talk to me if you need
advice on getting rejected.
I'm good, but thanks.
[KYOH]
Let's be honest.
We're all still too young
to have any real history
or experience with romance.
But we can still help.
We'll think of ways
to declare your love
that would leave any
girl speechless.
Yes! That's perfect!
And throughout your summer,
I hope you will all
remember to uphold
the proud standards
of Maegasaki Academy.
Ladies and gentlemen!
I hope you have a safe
and productive summer!
Bow!
[STUDENT C]
See you!
[STUDENT D]
Let's stop for some snacks!
[STUDENT A]
Whoa! Don't mind if I do!
[AKO]
Rusian!
It's time for our
last club meeting!
Oh. Yeah.
See ya later, Ako.
With a beautiful
face like yours,
I might actually miss
comin' to school.
We should hang.
Sorry, who are you?
[TAKASAKI screams]
Mega-burn!
May his soul find peace.
The final club meeting for
the first term begins.
We won't be doing
anything special.
Guild Alleycats will
continue operating,
but there will be no club
meetings during our vacation.
This summer, let's be sure
to enjoy our net games
in moderation!
--Yeah!
--Fine, fine.
One more thing.
[chuckles]
This weekend, the Net Game Club
will be holding a club camp!
Wow, that's so soon.
I can hardly wait!
A freaking Net Game Club Camp?
One thing is needed to excel.
Well, two.
Cash for premium items.
But the player's physical
fitness is most important!
Thus, life at this camp will be
primarily spent outdoors.
Brace yourselves for training!
[SAITO]
Mh-hm.
That's just what
kids your age need!
Naturally, I will be
accompanying you.
Looks like some beach time
is on the schedule too!
Ah! I guess we're
gonna need our swimsuits!
Yeah. I guess so.
If you follow this advice,
then it's bound to
go smooth as satin.
I wish you good fortune.
Rusian, what kind of
swimsuits do you like?
I assume you're into
the school one pieces.
What do you mean you assume?
I don't think I've ever
said anything like that.
I know, but as long as I have
my trusty ol' school swimsuit,
I'll make all the boys turn
into mindless animals!
[HIDEKI]
You seem real sure of yourself.
My mistake, then.
School swimsuits have no effect.
I don't really know.
I think the regular
ones are just fine.
Um, so hey.
You mind if we stop in
this park for a minute?
Sure, that sounds nice.
So, what's up?
[KYOH]
"Go for broke!"
Dammit, Master! You're
always screwing around!
[AKO]
Uhh...
[HIDEKI]
Don't let me down, Segawa!
[AKANE] "Create a nice mood.
Confess. Jackpot! Cha-ching!"
I'll "cha-ching" your head!
Useless morons.
Question: If you were trying
to set a nice mood,
what would you do?
Huh?
Uh.
The best way for me
to be in a nice mood
is spending time
with you, Rusian.
I mean, we are a
couple, after all.
[HIDEKI]
Uh.
Ako.
[AKO]
Hm?
Uh. Would you...?
[HIDEKI]
Would you...?
Would you be my girlfriend?
No thanks.
[HIDEKI]
But what?
[crying]
[AKANE, KYOH] ♪ Goodness
gracious, and so on. ♪
♪ It seems you
waited too long. ♪
♪ And that's the
end of our song! ♪
It's just all too much!
Ako destroyed me, and I
loved her like crazy, too!
Strange. It seems our
song had no effect.
I dunno. I think he's all right.
No I'm not. I just wanna die.
Now's my chance.
Goodbye, cruel world.
Hey, Ako. It's Schew.
Nishimura said something
to you, didn't he?
[HIDEKI]
Hey! Come on!
What do ya think you're doing?
Corpse-kicking?
What's next, teabagging?
So what did Ako have to say?
[AKO]
Well, um...
He asked me if I wanted
to be his girlfriend.
So what did you say to him?
[AKO] I said no. Of course!
What else would I say?
[screams]
[AKO]
I mean.
I would consider going from
wife to girlfriend a demotion,
wouldn't you?
Either that, or it means
we're getting a divorce.
And definitely don't want that.
Well, there you have it.
Put simply, your declaration
fell through. Tough luck.
[chuckles]
[HIDEKI screams]
[NANAKO]
Hold on a second.
When it comes to relationships,
I'm obviously the most
qualified consultant!
Why didn't you come ask me?
[HIDEKI]
Oh no, I couldn't do that.
[NANAKO]
Why not?