[RUSIAN] A long time ago,
I was playing in a pickup party.
[LEADER] Is one healer gonna
be enough for this instance?
We'll be fine!
[RUSIAN] I, personally, didn't
think we were gonna be fine.
[RUSIAN] Sure enough, her
healing rate couldn't keep up
and we were party wiped.
Isana kept apologizing to us,
but it wasn't really
her fault at all.
I should have said something
from the beginning,
before the disaster.
I started worrying that
she would eventually
get fed up with the game,
and quit outright.
Then, a few months later,
she was there in
another pickup party.
Same as ever.
You think one healer's
gonna be enough?
I'll be just fine.
[RUSIAN]
But after what happened before,
I couldn't just sit back
and say nothing.
This will be tough
with just one healer.
So let's make sure
to take our time.
[RUSIAN] And then Isana sent me
a message in private chat.
It was quick and to the point.
Thanks a lot.
So are you just trying to
brag about your ex-girlfriend?
She wasn't my girlfriend!
Did I get it wrong?
The point of the story
is that certain people
don't really know
how to ask for help
and that can lead to problems.
You understand that, right?
[AKO]
Yes. I understand.
I think sometimes people
fell overburdened.
And with a little
bit of empathy,
you can help them get past
whatever's slowing them down.
[AKO]
Yes, I see.
That's great!
Did any of that
help you understand
how I've been feeling?
What's that?
Summer vacation
will be over soon
and we'll all have
to go back to school.
I was just hoping that I could
get you to tell everyone
that you and I aren't
actually married.
We're just in a relationship.
There you go again,
you silly man.
Oh, Rusian, that was rich!
But all that build up...
That was an actual request,
not some joke.
[HIDEKI] Man, I wish I could buy
a heat resistance potion
right about now.
It's hotter than
an oven's armpit.
Yeah, it is. That's quite
the tan you've got there.
Thanks. But it's nice to see
you as pasty white as ever.
Gee, thanks.
[AKANE]
Nishimura.
[HIDEKI]
Huh?
I need a moment of your time.
[HIDEKI]
Um, Segawa?
Would you just come
with me already?
[HIDEKI]
Ow! My neck!
Now Segawa's dragging
Nishimura out of class.
I think it's safe to say that
summer break is officially over.
[BOTH]
Oh yeah.
[HIDEKI] Just because we haven't
seen each other in a while,
doesn't mean you can do that!
We hung out yesterday
afternoon in the game.
Yeah. Guess you're right.
It seems like something's
bothering you.
Ugh! Forced conversation
with classmates
to ask what they did over
the summer's so cliché.
In some ways, it's worse
than coming back to school.
Plus it all sounds
like suck-ware
with un-skippable cut scenes!
Oh really?
Well that's unfortunate.
I spent so much of last term
trying to come across as
a regular high school girl.
To be honest, I'm not even
sure I still know how.
[HIDEKI] I thought it was
your character class.
[NANAKO]
Akane! Good morning!
What are you two up to,
alone on the stairs? An affair?
Please don't say that.
If Ako heard, her brain
might explode.
We were just having
a little chat!
You could try to be
friendly in class.
You wouldn't have to slink
away to have a conversation.
[AKANE]
Butt out, would you?
It's not a team-killing
summoner's business anyhow.
You can talk to me
after you've abandoned
your precious Mu-Tan
in the mountains.
My puppy in the game?!
That's horrible!
Mu-tan's a good boy!
What'd he ever do wrong?
[ALL chuckling]
[AKANE]
He runs around out of control.
[HIDEKI]
Mm-hm.
[SETTE]
Mu-tan, bad boy!
[AKANE] Then the little
mongrel pulls enemies.
[HIDEKI]
That's true.
"Mu-tan, bad boy!"
That doesn't cut it!
Wow! You guys are such meanies!
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen Ako yet.
Same here.
I'd like to go and mess with her
a bit to make me feel better.
[HIDEKI] Speak of the devil.
Ako's calling.
[AKO] Hello, Rusian!
Good morning, dear!
Why haven't you or Schew
or Master logged in yet?
--[HIDEKI gasps]
--[AKANE groans]
Come on. Seriously?
What's wrong?
[KYOH]
Good morning! Welcome.
I hope everyone
had a great break.
And though it may have flown by,
I'm sure you all found
your time away
as productive and
memorable as I did.
It is also my hope
that during this new...
I'll try to just sneak in late.
[AKO]
Rusian...
Hey, I'm proud.
You resisted the urge to stay
at home and skip school today.
Well you did say how much
you were looking forward
to seeing my beautiful
face at school again.
Oh great. I just threw up
in my mouth a little.
[SAITO]
All right, everyone!
Today we embark
upon the adventure
that is the longest term
of the school year!
Now who's ready to learn?
Ahh... So nice and cool.
Oh yeah.
Did you miss me as much
as I missed you, War Machine?
So hey, how much of your stolen
gear did you manage to recover?
[HIDEKI] Uhh... Dunno.
Twenty percent-ish?
You've still got
a long way to go.
I know my Rusian.
Simply reassembling his old
set won't be good enough.
I bet you're going to try
to get better gear
than you had before!
Huh?! Is that really your plan?!
Curse you, and your
stinkin' female intuition.
[AKANE] Who the hell
do you think you are?!
Hear me out before you freak!
Y'know how sometimes
after you make your setup,
you have buyer's remorse?
Like wishing you'd chosen
different enchantments
or realizing that set
bonus wasn't worth it?
I'm talking 'bout
min max city, baby!
What you had was fine,
so just buy it again so you
can finally be useful!
Uh! Right! Yes, ma'am!
Eyes front!
Tell me. What do you think of
when you hear "second term"?
Well, there's rewards from
the summer events to distribute.
Collecting pumpkins for the
Halloween special event?
The bevy of new items coming
out with the fall update.
Quantities are limited.
And then the Christmas
event with Rusian!
I didn't mean that!
I meant the second term at
school, not in the game!
I feel like we're
forgetting something big.
When you think September,
you think Maegasaki's culture
festival, Sakikosai!
[AKANE, HIDEKI, AKO]
Oh.
C'mon, guys. It's a big deal.
Can't you at least pretend
to be more fired up?
Are you positive you're
high school students?
[KYOH]
All right.
While the whole thing
may be a nuisance,
it's a nuisance we
simply can't ignore.
It's supposed to be fun.
Since our club has
actual activities,
we have to take part.
Yeah, I get it. But what
are we supposed to do?
The easy answer is to show off
the results achieved
by our club.
What results? What've we
done besides game?
We got Ako to come to school.
[AKO]
Ta-da!
[AKANE]
That's it?
Ako's gonna be our
main attraction?
You mean like some sort
of science experiment?
I couldn't take such
an unorthodox display!
Any net gamer worth his salt
knows you can't spell
"exposed" without "dox".
So really, all joking aside,
we just need to come up with
some result and present it.
Yeah, but what?
If you have no ideas...
then I have a prime proposal!
Siege warfare?
Wait. You mean like
the recent PvP update?
Yes, siege warfare,
the long awaited expansion
content recently released.
It's perfect!
What if we make the winner
of that our exhibition?
Yeah, maybe, but
siege warfare is, y'know--
the large-scale, guild-on-guild,
PvP battle they
hold once a week.
That's your suggestion?
Yes. All club members will
compete for shared glory.
An elegant solution.
Yeah, I guess so.
Let's say we're able
to pull it off.
How do we present it for
the school festival?
Whoever wins siege warfare
becomes lords of the
castle for a week.
The guild's emblem is then
hoisted proudly over the castle.
So do we even have
an emblem to raise?
[KYOH chuckles]
Okay.
So we take the school crest
as our emblem, and raise that.
Is that what you were going for?
Indeed!
And we all take a commemorative
screen cap in front of it!
Then we can use that picture
as our display panel.
[chuckles nervously]
[AKO] Siege warfare, huh?
I don't know.
I'm not too wild about
the whole idea.
What, you don't
like PvP fighting?
I just know I'm not gonna win.
You seem pretty
cheerful, considering.
[AKO] I'll admit, I'm not
excited about this term
or going to school every day,
but at least at the end I get
to walk home with you,
my darling Rusian.
Yeah. It is nice.
I was wondering.
What's your class doing for the
festival, Ako? Do you know?
Oh, well, um...
We're doing a presentation
on the shops near school
that sell delicious food.
Wow, that actually
sounds pretty fun.
Yeah, I guess so.
Don't just stand there
looking tensely at each other!
Start fighting, already!
But I-- I don't have it in me
to attack poor Rusian
for no reason.
You have a reason.
It's called PvP practice!
Staring into each other's eyes
like a love-struck
couple isn't training.
We weren't, Master!
It's just that my current setup
doesn't have enough power
to take Ako in one shot,
so I was planning to
whittle her down first
with a taste of reflect damage.
Yeah, yeah. Go on.
Get to work, Ako!
Um, okay. Fine.
Ah! Oh no!
Ako!
Are you all right?
My attack bounced back
and hit me instead!
Go ahead and heal
yourself, okay?
Of course! Thanks again
for helping me out!
[RUSIAN]
Don't mention it.
[AKO]
My hero!
[RUSIAN]
Just doin' my thing.
That's it! Here I come, chump!
Extra Damage Buff!
Ho-ho! Not too shabby,
you guys.
One hit knocked her
into the red.
What was that? It was like
being hit by a train.
My bad. Force of habit.
The first attack he used
causes a stun effect.
He likes it when I cast
Extra Damage after that.
I never realized your
shield stun was so effective!
Well, stun moves in general
are pretty versatile.
But the down side
to that ability
is a long cool down time.
Whatever it was,
it's got me fired up!
Wonderful. Now it's my turn
to go head-to-head with you.
[AKANE]
You ready?
Let's roll, Master!
[KYOH] Abandon hope...
as I unleash my grand spell!
But that's Master's
finishing move!
That's how she's
starting the fight?
Meteor!
Did you really think I
would sit around and wait
for such an obvious
AoE attack?
You weren't in range of my
flaming maelstrom of carnage?
But how? Mobs always are!
This bad mamma-jamma
ain't no mob!
[growls]
How did you do that?
[KYOH]
Impossible. How could I lose?
[AKO]
I'll resurrect you. Hold on.
[KYOH]
You're next, Rusian! Let's go!
Wait! I can't move!
Impossible.
[AKO]
I'll resurrect you.
All right, Ako!
Let's see how you fare
against... my meteor spell!
I'm as good as dead for sure!
You're fine. Just chill
and blast an SS.
[AKO]
O-Okay. Skill Sealing Spell!
Master!
Brace yourself!
[KYOH whines]
[AKO]
I'll just, uh, resurrect you.
[KYOH]
But how?
My attack power and defense
rating are way higher
than any of the other members
of Guild Alley Cats.
Well, Schew knows her
melee fighter role well,
she's our PvP ace.
Magic users who go toe-to-toe
with her typically lose.
[chuckles]
As a tank, I have specialized
stun lock attacks
that stop spell casting.
And Ako.
She actually distributed
her stats pretty evenly.
She's ready for PvP play.
Whatever I did
was unintentional!
Frankly, Master,
a magic user like you
shouldn't be trying to
duel in the first place.
No, you're wrong.
I've seen videos where
magic users like me
singlehandedly wiped the
floor with their opponents!
But PvP play requires
its own kind of equipment
and a new approach to fighting.
Go ahead, Rusian! Say it.
Say that we're just a rag-tag
group of broken down characters
with a snowball's chance
in hell of ever taking out
enough players to win
the siege warfare event!
Pretty much.
[gasps]
[KYOH]
I never expected this.
I conducted a little research,
and I realized that Apricot
is not suited to PvP.
It would be quicker to
build a new character
from the ground up.
I tried sparring with
some of my friends
who've been playing
PvP for a while.
They wiped the floor with me.
I've played my fair
share of PvP matches,
but my current equipment
isn't top-tier.
A quick question.
How many siege battles are there
before the culture festival?
[HIDEKI]
They're held every Sunday,
so we've got three more.
Is it even possible?
[HIDEKI]
Well, worst case scenario,
we change our
festival presentation.
We could always do something
like a net game
discussion panel.
There's no way you're going to
get me in that discussion panel!
Speaking as the student
council president,
I can't do it either.
I'm okay with just staying here
and playing games with Rusian
for the entire afternoon.
Yeah, we should at least
get out and look around.
Right, we might as well
give it our best shot.
Everyone, get your gear ready.
We shall take part in
the next siege battle!
This will be the Alley
Cat's first campaign.
Let's stick together.
Of course we start off with the
Templar Fortress of Ray Sword.
The group that currently
holds the castle
are a guild known as
the Cleaning Crew.
[AKANE]
They can't be serious.
How cute! A guild of maids!
No.
If they're holding the fort,
they've gotta be tough.
Rusian's right.
We must be careful.
Otherwise, they'll end up
mopping the floor with us.
[ANNOUNCER]
Siege warfare will now commence.
[KYOH] Is everyone ready?
Be not too eager, nor too timid.
Onward!
All right!
Let's do this!
Looks like another guild
is gonna try first.
Yes. Let's watch them,
and analyze how they fight.
[AKANE]
That entire raiding party...
...wiped out in less
than ten seconds!
Brutal.
Let's go back!
No. We won't know how bad
it is unless we do it.
Onward!
But I don't wanna!
There are no death
penalties in siege warfare.
Let's give that
attack another shot!
I don't wanna go
there anymore!
I'm sorry about that!
Excuse me, sir!
What's the big idea?
Hey, that's my wife, you jerk!
You want a fight?
Well you got one!
Hold on!
We're badly outnumbered!
So that's it.
There's a single enemy,
but the forces arrayed against
them aren't a solid front.
Everyone laying
siege is a rival.
This sounds impossible.
[KYOH] Apparently, to break up a
deadlock like we've been facing,
we can gather together materials
and build our own siege weapons.
What?
We can bust down the walls
and charge in the breach?
[KYOH] Yes. For example,
a giant catapult,
a.k.a. "Gi," can be controlled
by five players.
Not enough.
Hang on, don't give up
on me just yet.
[AKANE] Oh, what? You know
the victory conditions?
Master?
I'm breaking out
the premium items
that you guys forbid
me from using!
Under these circumstances,
it's our only real option!
No! Come back!
The siege warfare event
temporarily locks access
to premium items!
[KYOH]
You've got to be kidding me!
[KYOH] A Drop of Yggdrasil is
about the only non-premium means
of total recovery
I have in my pack.
I've never even owned
such a precious item,
much less used it.
One of those is worth
about ten megas.
Selling it at the bazaar
and upgrading your gear
would be more practical.
[KYOH]
I can't accept this.
This could possibly be
the perfect opportunity
to wean Master off premium
items once and for all.
Good idea.
Wait, is that?
[CLOUD] Proud and noble warriors
of our lady's Elite Guard!
Hear me!
We have one goal! And that goal
is to take this fortress!
In the name of
our goddess, Nekohime!
[ELITE GAURD yelling]
Stop, you guys! Wait!
I never asked you
to do this for me!
Ms. Saito's guild is
pretty powerful, isn't it?
Nekohime's Elite Guard.
These dudes seem to be
experts at the game.
Hey. They occupied the fortress.
They sure did.
Huh.
We might as well go.
[RUSIAN]
Sometime after,
though Nekohime's guard
put up a good fight,
they were beaten
by a larger guild,
and chased off
the lord's throne.
"Death or glory in
Nekohime's name."
"For our lady's honor!"
"The holy cat-girl angel!"
"We devote our very
beings to her!"
[NEKOHIME crying]
[NEKOHIME]
It's not like that!
I was just chit-chatting
about the siege event,
and before I mew it,
all hell broke loose!
[NANAKO]
Listen up, everyone.
We can't just have wholesale
copying of the sources.
Rework the sentences to make
them sound like your own.
[ALL]
Roger that!
But tracing the school
map is still acceptable.
All of our sources come from
books in the library or the web.
Are you sure we've
got enough research?
I don't think the
bibliography is as important
as our level of presentation.
Which is exactly why I'm
questioning this method.
Being a teacher
isn't easy, meow.
Neither is finding a good excuse
to make cat noises apparently.
[AKO] No way on earth
I'm letting that happen.
Ako?
[AKO] It's our dumb
class presentation.
[HIDEKI] An exhibit of the tasty
foods around Maegasaki, right?
Originally, but
now it's changed.
Someone suggested that since
we were already doing
a presentation on food,
why not have something
the attendees could
actually snack on?
Sounds like an improvement.
Then they started suggesting
that we could raise a little
money by selling the food,
and even more money if
we have the girls in class
wait on the guests
who want a bite to eat.
Starting to come off the rails.
[AKO]
Right?!
Then they said,
if we're going to do a café,
why not make it a maid café?
That's veering way off course!
But you haven't even
heard the worst part!
They started saying,
"Tamaki knows all about
maids, doesn't she?
Let's make her
the head maid!"
Then they put me in charge
of the whole thing!
Well, I get why
they chose you.
[AKANE]
There's a common misconception
normies have that
otaku equals maid.
But every single one
of them is wrong.
I'm a devoted housewife,
not some stupid old maid!
You're not actually a housewife.
[AKO]
And that's not all!
They asked me to get the
uniforms, draw up shifts,
come up with a serving manual.
I don't know anything
about that stuff!
Yeah, picking you probably
wasn't the best choice.
Well, as far as
the uniforms go,
I'm sure Master could probably
track some down for you.
Oh yeah. I guess you're right.
Cool. Best of luck with that.
We'll help out however
we possibly can.
Okay.
Top ten reasons
you're glad I'm here!
Lame!
But number seven
will shock you.
Wait. What are you
doing here, Nanako?
Yeah, what's a total newb
scrub doing in our club?
I asked her to join us.
We need as many allies
as we can get, don't we?
That said, I ordered
a couple extra computers
for Sette and Ms. Saito.
Listen, Nanako, you don't have
to go through the trouble
of trying to help us out.
Whatever, it sounds like fun!
I just hope I can help!
Are you willing to come up
here on Sundays to work?
I wish you all shared
the same enthusiasm
for the class presentation.
[SETTE]
Awww. I'm sorry, Mu-tan.
But you have to stay
behind this time.
You cause too much
trouble for us
nipping at everyone and
their brother's heels.
Now, time for strategy.
Today, we're going
after Fort Cantor,
the smallest castle
in the siege event.
The occupying guild
is small like us.
Emperor Sword.
They're made up of
about 20 players.
Uh. But we've only got six
people fighting for us.
That's a pretty
steep disadvantage.
We'll all get killed off again!
Don't worry. I've come up
with a plan this time.
So you've got a trick
up your sleeve?
Yes.
I've lined up some
reinforcements
from the server's top class
powerhouse mercenary outfit.
Wallenstein's agreed to help.
Did mew say Wallenstein?
I knew she'd solve
the problem with money.
You've heard of these guys?
Yeah.
[AKANE]
Please, don't die, Master.
If you kick the bucket here,
what're we gonna do
about the festival?
We'll be totally lost
without you!
[HIDEKI] Next time:
"The Death of Apricot."
[AKANE]
Netoge Standby!