[SAITO] Looks like someone
didn't get enough sleep!
Did you stay up all night
grinding faction reputation?
Yeah, well...
It's just past the
butt crack of dawn,
but you look wide awake
and ready to go.
Back in college, I was
on the wrestling team.
We had practice every morning!
There they are.
Morning.
Good morning, Rusian.
Whoa.
[growls]
I didn't touch her!
Just the arms!
I don't care about that.
I'm just sleepy.
Oh. Cool.
Well, that's everyone!
Then let us begin.
The first annual Modern
Communications
Electronic Game Club
summer camp starts now!
This camp will build
our physical endurance,
leading to longer, more
efficient raid sessions.
As such, during camp...
...net connection is
henceforth prohibited!
It's called: The 24 Hour
No-Net-Connectivity-Camp
Excursion!
[AKO screams]
[AKANE yawns]
[HIDEKI] The net's totally
off-limits during the camp?
That's right.
[AKANE] Is this whole
"no internet" thing
a plan to force Ako to stop
associating her in-game persona
with real life?
Not quite. It goes deeper.
Ako's totally absorbed in gaming
because it's the one part of
her life that she can control.
You agree? Rusian?
Uh. Yeah.
But if we can
turn things around,
she won't want to escape a
world where things go her way.
[AKANE]
Hmm...
You might actually be
onto something there.
[KYOH] Which means we
need to stick with her
throughout the break.
Teach her to enjoy her youth,
to spend the summer like
a normal high school girl.
Toss in a proper love confession
under the right circumstances,
and things are bound to go well.
But wait a minute.
What constitutes a
proper confession
under the right circumstances?
Like sitting on the beach
watching the sun set?
Or maybe gazing up into a
star filled sky together?
[KYOH] Either of those
options and many more
would work where we're going.
But the rest of it's up to you.
[sighs]
Right. No pressure.
Sure. I can totally do this.
Just declare my love,
and hope Ako will accept
me on real life terms.
[gasps]
[SAITO]
GTFO.
This "cottage" makes my
apartment look like a closet!
How much was this place? Huh?
[HIDEKI] Um, you probably
shouldn't grill your student
on income-related stuff.
Right, of course. Never mind me.
It's like some fancy hotel.
So we drop off
our bags and then?
Dusting? Futon drying?
The caretakers knew
we were coming.
The staff would've already
taken care of all that.
Well, that was easy.
[SAITO gasps]
No!
This isn't what a club camp is
supposed to be like you guys!
Cleaning and bed-making
are all part of the deal!
Those are the camp experiences
that build character!
Indentured servitude
is part of what
makes the process legit, right?
[HIDEKI]
Our own private beach? Unreal.
[AKO]
Rusian!
[giggling]
[AKO]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
What? What's wrong?
You keep staring at my top.
Is there a stain?
Uh! No!
So, uh... Where's everyone else?
[AKO] They were all
taking way too long,
so I decided to come
out and join you.
I didn't want you to
get lonely waiting.
Cool, that's nice.
No need to be bashful.
You look great!
[AKO] When I first picked
out this swimsuit,
I was really excited about it.
Now, when the time comes
to actually put it on,
out of nowhere,
I feel so self-conscious.
[HIDEKI]
Don't worry.
It's cute. Really.
You look lovely.
Thank you very much.
[AKANE sighs]
[AKANE] Big surprise,
you came out here first, Ako.
[KYOH]
Ugh.
You've ruined my plan;
I'll have you know.
To all show up in
swimsuits together.
And send Rusian running
off, nose bleeding!
No, no nosebleeds.
Thanks anyway.
[AKANE]
By the way, Ako,
did you already put
on some sunblock?
If you spend all day in the sun
with skin as freakishly
pale as yours,
you'll be miserable
for a week straight!
You'll have a sunburn so
bad that it hurts to even move!
[whimpering]
[AKO laughing]
Just try to hold
still, would ya?
[AKO]
Hey, that tickles!
[AKANE]
Though I have to say,
you're soft and squishy
in all the right places.
[AKO]
Yeah, I just kinda...
My goodness! It looks like
you don't have any either.
Wha--? No. I don't really--
We're all friends.
I'll rub some on for you.
No thanks.
I'd be glad to lend you
a hand with that as well.
Whoa!
I wanna rub some
of this on you too!
Hold on!
[HIDEKI screams]
[HIDEKI] Slow down! No! Not
there! That's nice! Too much!
Ah!
I can't take anymore!
I'm spent. Defiled
and tossed aside.
It was just sunscreen, Rusian.
You should be thanking
us, quite frankly.
[SAITO] Looks like everyone
is ready to me!
[SAITO]
Okay, let's get to it!
[AKO, AKANE, KYOH]
Yeah!
[HIDEKI]
Yeah...
[BOTH sigh]
[laughing]
Aww... Great swimming!
And great diving!
A great day for floating.
Perfect day for floating!
How strange.
You all look like you've had
your fill, but it's midday!
And another thing, why
didn't you all play together
like a real club would?
Well, Miss,
the thing is... Hmm...
It's kinda like this!
Imagine there's an expansion
pack, with an entirely new map.
[SAITO]
Okay.
[HIDEKI] All right, so we all
head to the new map together.
But then, once there,
we immediately split up.
[SAITO]
But why?
[HIDEKI] To learn important
things about the new zone.
Like how good the XP is
for solo grinding.
Or if the enemies
drop any rares.
And, more often than not,
learning where the graveyard is.
Huh... And then?
[HIDEKI] After we've made our
rounds, we join up again.
We compare notes, and
gauge zone productivity.
We each do what we want,
then come back when we're done.
That's our pattern.
So is that the new normal
for today's teenagers?
I can't speak for every
other high schooler,
but it's normal for us.
Now that you got me
talking about it,
I really wanna play some LA .
he internet is off-limits
while we're at camp.
Yeah, I know, but--
I'm over playing
around in the water.
I might go inside
and take a nap.
I don't believe you kids.
You're at an awesome summer
camp with a private beach!
How can you guys not
wanna run around free,
untamed and glistening
with youthful perspiration?
[AKANE] Did you just say
"youthful perspiration"?
None of us are big on sweating.
Look, life is tough, and like
it or not, quitters never win!
Just give it all your heart!
You can do it if you try!
Why won't you give it
everything you've got?
Because we usually just
decide to move on
if we try out a new game--
There's no "moving on"
from real life, clowns!
Back to work!
Get your butts in gear!
That is an order
from your advisor!
Nope!
[BOTH laughing]
[AKO]
Okay! Ready?
Go up, up; down, down!
[KYOH] Then you need to go
left right, left right.
And finish it up
with some B A!
How's the Konami Code
supposed to help?
Our work here is done.
Oh, come on!
Not funny, you guys!
[ALL laughing]
[sighs]
[HIDEKI] That whole
"youthful perspiration" thing
was pretty fun.
Now then,
I suppose I should tell Ako how
I feel while we're still young.
Rusian!
You don't mind if
I come in, do you?
[gasps]
[AKANE] What the heck do
you think you're doing?!
[AKO] A little bit longer!
Just give me a little longer!
--[AKO] It was getting good!
--[AKANE] Absolutely not!
She saw...
BBQ is on!
[AKANE]
You mean barbecue?
BBQ! Let's go!
[HIDEKI]
Ohh... She's in denial.
[AKO]
Um...
So why haven't you prepped any
of the ingredients for the meal?
[KYOH]
Prepping... is what?
Don't worry about it.
I'll see what I can do.
I wanna give it a shot, too!
We don't really have the time.
[AKANE] I can't believe
Ako wouldn't let me help.
Like I'd just end up
getting in her way.
[HIDEKI]
Oh man! I call that one!
Whew. Now that was good eatin'.
[AKO]
It was pretty yummy, wasn't it?
[HIDEKI]
Still, I can't believe
you're the only one
of us who could cook.
We'd be in real trouble
if you hadn't come along.
[AKO chuckles]
[AKANE] Behold this bad
mamma-jamma's Burning Edge!
[HIDEKI] Is she acting out
a broadsword skill?
[AKO]
She is flailing around a lot.
[HIDEKI]
That's kinda dangerous though.
[SAITO]
Oh no you don't!
[HIDEKI]
Around and around she goes.
[SAITO]
Coaching complete!
[BOTH laughing]
[KYOH] Looks like the timing
is just about perfect.
[HIDEKI]
What's the matter, Ako?
Oh, uh...
It's nothing.
I tried to keep from crying,
and it just made it harder.
I couldn't help it.
I'm just so happy.
This whole day has been perfect.
I never dreamed my life
could be like this.
I just-- I feel lucky
for the first time.
And still, can't help
feeling a little sad.
Ako.
[AKO]
Um...
I really wanna thank you.
Thank for what?
Because if I'd never met you,
I never would've come here
and had such a wonderful day!
Guess what? If it
weren't for you, Ako,
I wouldn't be
here today, either.
Then it works out.
Good thing we're
together, isn't it?
[HIDEKI]
Yeah.
Listen...
Uh, Ako?
I love you.
[gasps]
You love me?
I love you too, Rusian.
So very much!
We're a great married couple.
Anyone would agree!
[HIDEKI] Despite everything,
it didn't work.
[BOTH sigh]
I would've sworn a
no net, normie summer
would've done the job,
but I guess I was mistaken.
Yeah, she definitely
still thinks
you're a married
couple in real life.
[HIDEKI]
And the worst part?
After all the struggling,
I had a revelation!
This: A husband totally
outranks a boyfriend.
It doesn't matter what I do.
Ako refuses to change her mind!
[HIDEKI crying]
I'm afraid this quest...
...has ended in failure.
[SAITO]
Come on, you guys!
It's time for lights out!
We got a busy day tomorrow.
[KYOH]
Okay! Ready?
Master. Why'd we pack up?
Where are we going now?
[chuckles] Someplace good.
[KYOH]
The Hotel Flores!
As of right now,
the Modern Communications
Electronic Gaming Club's
true camp begins!
[AKO gasps]
[HIDEKI]
What the--?
[KYOH]
We're in luck.
This hotel is part of a
Legendary Age collaboration.
[AKANE]
What kinda hotel would do that?
Sounds like a last attempt
to keep from going bankrupt.
They have a Powaring
King plushie!
He's so soft!
Segawa, you sure you
don't wanna go to?
Shut up! Of course I don't!
[SAITO]
Okay, we're all checked in!
Your keys. Here.
[HIDEKI]
What's this thing?
[KYOH]
Your token to use for the event.
And it's adorable!
One more thing.
As a result of abstaining
from the net for a day,
our training regimen has
given a permanent boost
to our gaming ability!
By using these token passes...
...you'll log in over there,
and the much-anticipated
event will begin!
[HIDEKI] I get it. So that's
what these tokens are for.
[HIDEKI] After entering in
that token's key code,
we just input our ID
and password as usual.
Hey, no peeking. It's just rude.
Uh! But what's wrong with it?
Couples share everything,
including passwords!
No, they don't.
[HIDEKI]
Huh?
What's wrong?
Well, uh, it didn't
take my password, I guess.
Must've typed it wrong.
[HIDEKI] That's because Ako
was butting in on me.
[AKO chuckles]
All right, I'm in.
Wow. Check it out!
The floor plan's just like
the real-life hotel!
[AKANE]
It's a special map
that only event
participants can enter.
"Hello, and welcome to
the Legendary Age Select
Collaborative Event.
There are several exciting
and rare bonuses
set aside for all
of our participants.
Begin by going to the restaurant
on the first floor
of Hotel Flores."
Huh.
[AKO squeals]
[AKO] There are special items
listed off to the side
of the dishes!
Does that mean
whatever you order
you unlock the matching
item in the game?
[KYOH]
That's right.
That's evil! It's immoral!
But I can't keep myself from
ordering strength-buffing items!
Okay, so you take
the code on the card
that came with the check,
and enter it into the game
to unlock your new rewards.
There's something
written on the back.
"Brave adventurers young and old
can find similar
bonuses awaiting them
in the first floor
gift shop." Huh.
[HIDEKI] So what's up with
the couple dozen boxes
of gingerbread cookies
you got there?
What am I supposed to do?!
These happen to come with
the items I wanted most!
A special item
matching sales event
might not be the smartest way
to teach the students
about budgeting.
Since we ended up
with more stuff,
I say it's time to split up.
Let's take a break
and head to our rooms.
She's right.
We checked in a while ago
and we haven't even been up
to see our rooms yet.
Our room blocks are tied into
this cross-promotional event.
They come fully-equipped
with computers
and internet connections.
That means we can unlock
the items we just got!
[chuckles]
Yes, we can!
Where're Schew and Master?
Where else?
They both went to try out
their brand new items!
No surprise.
I guess we should too.
Sure, we could do that, or...
If you'd like... to maybe...
come to my room?
Uh?
Duh, of course.
When you said come to
your room, you meant in LA .
[AKO]
Rusian.
We're in this fancy hotel,
sitting alone, together,
here in my room.
I-- I've been waiting for this
for a really long time.
Rusian?
So, uh, what were you saying?
It's finally our chance!
Alone together at last!
Well I was thinking,
maybe we could engage
in some couples chat?
[FAKE RUSIAN]
Couples, eh?
[AKANE] What's the big idea
with the swimsuits?
Just because it's summer,
we don't have to stroll around
wearing next to nothing!
[RUSIAN] It's okay,
your swimsuit was modest!
And you don't have a
lot to show off anyway.
[AKANE]
You want an ass whooping?