Long time nyao see!
Get it?
Yeah, long time no see.
[NEKOHIME] It's nice to know
you're still enjoying the game.
Of course! It's awesome.
That's excellent!
I worried you might've quit
playing after we talked.
But myew're still here!
[RUSIAN] You really are girlish
and adorable, Nekohime...
...considering you're
an older dude.
[RUSIAN] Oh, no.
What happened back then
was actually a good
experience for me.
In fact, I took what
I learned from that
and made it my personal mantra.
Mantra?
That's right.
"Role-Playing has nothing
to do with real life.
The game is not reality."
[laughing]
[RUSIAN]
So how about yourself, Nekohime?
Looks like you haven't
logged in in a while!
[NEKOHIME] My work schedule's
been extra hectic lately.
I heard someone mention
the game IRL,
and I thought it was the
purr-fect time to log back in!
And here you are!
I'm glad we bumped into
each other, Rusian!
[groans]
Why are you here? What's wrong?
Nothing!
I just came to pay my morning
respects to my master!
Uh, look, this is awkward.
That's only in the game, okay?
It doesn't transfer over
to the real world.
So could you, maybe,
cut that crap out?
Aww...
"Aww." Back 'atcha.
And another thing,
calling me master
makes you sound less like my
wife, and more like my maid.
I guess so. Well then...
How're you this morning?
Well? Husband? Dear?
You're ignoring that?
[HIDEKI]
Hmm...
I'm sorry, Ako, but that
quest line is closed
until further
requirements are met.
[AKO]
Huh? So if I level up,
will it raise our
affection rating too?
[NANAKO]
What's going on?
Did they get to know each
other in some game?
[AKANE]
Beats me.
Good morning!
[STUDENTS]
Good morning, miss!
See you later!
Cool.
Nishimura. A moment
of your time?
Mister Nishimura,
have you and Miss Tamaki
started seeing each other?
Ah! No! Ma'am,
it's not like that!
[SAITO]
But you do get along?
Yeah, I guess so.
Thanks for helping her
feel like she belongs.
From what I've seen, Miss Tamaki
doesn't have too many friends.
She's also been missing
a lot of school lately.
Well, that's no good.
Miss Goshoin.
Oh, Mast-- Uh! Madam President.
Hey, nice to see you, Hideki.
Hi, Ms. Saito. Regarding
what we spoke about--
Oh yes. Please
accept my apologies,
but I'm needed in the
literary club right now.
Of course,
but if you could at least
give me a name to jot down.
[HIDEKI]
Huh?
"H-e-l-l-o, Rusian."
And enter!
You do realize you don't
have to type to chat.
That's right! I forgot.
[AKANE] Ha! Sword upgrade!
It's so light!
Aww yeah!
Let's go to the Bluemke
Mega-volcano today, you guys!
Good idea.
Okay! Time for everyone
to gear up!
[HIDEKI, AKO, AKANE]
Yeah!
Hey, Ako. Mind if I take
a look at your gear?
[AKO]
Okay, go ahead.
Wow, that is completely nutso.
What is?
If we're going to fight
in a mega-volcano,
why are you wearing robes
with water resistance?
Oh, my robe?
You gave it to me, Rusian,
so of course I'm wearing it!
[HIDEKI] But you need one
with fire resistance!
[AKO] But my water resistance
robe is a lot cuter.
You're too focused
on your appearance.
And what's so great about
this pink star glitter wand
you've been waving around?
When you hit an enemy with it,
it sparkles and
shoots out stars!
It's like, mega-adorable!
[AKANE] Those stupid stars
were coming from you?
[AKO giggling]
[HIDEKI grumbles]
[AKO gasps]
[AKO] Are you implying
all my gear is useless?
That's an understatement.
Your build is a joke.
[HIDEKI] I've got a wand of
benevolence in my inventory
that you can borrow.
[AKO]
Oh, I've got that.
[HIDEKI]
Then freakin' use it!
[laughing]
That's great. Now the Master's
cackling like a lunatic.
[AKO] Ugh. This ugly flame robe
doesn't complement my style
in the slightest.
It's on!
[KYOH] All right. Time for
a taste of my umaibo staff!
Come and get it!
Uh.
What're you doing, Schwein?
Why are you holding my arm?
I thought we'd agreed that
premium items are off limits.
Oh, in that case,
I don't have any
equipment I can use.
Wait a second.
Is your inventory full
of premium items?
Master, you promised.
No premium item use
while we quest together.
Don't boss me!
Did you forget I'm club
president and Guild Master?
Oh, shut up!
Ha! Behold the
deadliness of my blade!
[RUSIAN] Your sword looks the
same to us as it always has.
Seems like Schew is having fun.
Uh! I deserve to have a
"woot" moment as well!
Sure thing! Just no premiums.
[KYOH groans]
[RUSIAN]
Here come two more!
This is foolish, but fine.
No premium weapons.
Let them come!
They can chew on the power
of this regular staff
that I've upgraded with
premium buffing items!
Now, Perfect Blizzard!
Well that got their attention.
Master just got pwned.
Don't open with your best move!
Maybe tone down
the "woot" factor!
[KYOH]
If I'd had my premium staves,
I would have overkilled
the lot of them.
[RUSIAN]
Ako! Cast Resurrect!
[AKO]
Okay.
I forgot to customize my
skill settings on this rig.
Do any of you guys know what
the "Resurrect" icon looks like?
It's this one here,
then you gotta click "Heal."
Ah! Wow, you really know
your stuff, Rusian!
[AKANE sighs]
[AKANE]
That seemed a lot more stressful
than our usual
grinding sessions.
[KYOH] But we learned
from our mistakes
and our efficiency went up!
That only happened
because Nishimura
was working half
of Ako's controls.
Thanks for sharing your
strength and skill.
[HIDEKI gasps]
I feel like I was more
useful to everyone today
because of you.
Yeah, no sweat. Glad to help.
[AKO sighs]
I haven't missed a day of school
since we started
the Net Game Club,
but I'm feeling
stretched too thin,
and could probably
use a bit of a break.
You've gotta show up.
You can't graduate otherwise.
That won't be a problem
because you're going
to support me, Rusian.
So really, whatever happens
along the way doesn't matter.
Whoa. I think I'd remember
agreeing to something like that.
[AKO gasps]
Don't tell me you want us to
become a dual-income couple!
If I had to actually choose,
two incomes sounds safest.
Uh. What did you say?
Two incomes sounds safer.
Uh. Could you repeat that again?
Not funny.
[AKO giggles]
Is something wrong, Rusian?
No.
I just realized I'm
starting to get used to
being called by my
name from the game.
[AKO]
Oh, sorry. Nishimura. I forgot.
[HIDEKI]
Let's make a pit-stop.
What was that?
I was thinking it's kinda
like we're in LA right now.
Nope, this is the real
world, without a doubt.
[AKO] Ya think people walking by
have any idea we're married?
[HIDEKI]
Doesn't sound very likely.
For one thing, I'm nowhere
close to marrying age yet.
I might look like
your boyfr-- Ah.
So, it's starting to
get late. Is that okay?
[AKO] Yeah. My parents
are barely ever home.
[HIDEKI]
Oh, really?
If they weren't
gone all the time,
I couldn't be up
gaming every night!
It's just that,
from what I've seen,
Miss Tamaki doesn't
have too many friends.
[AKO]
The sunset is so beautiful.
[HIDEKI]
Ready to go?
[AKO]
Sure!
[HIDEKI groans]
[HIDEKI] How 'bout we
all take a little break?
Ako's healing abilities have
been noticeably improving.
Which means less dying.
Amazing what you can do
with the right gear.
I'm going to step out
for a few moments.
[HIDEKI] Do you need
to go to the restroom?
You shouldn't ask a lady that!
Right! Let's do this!
Hey! What's going on here?
Too cute! You look great, Schew!
Hey, Schew! A little help?!
What's with this super-leek?
It's ridiculous!
[KYOH laughs]
That's because it's
been fully maxed out!
You love spending money
on the weirdest nonsense!
[KYOH]
I think we should call it a day.
[AKO] We accomplished
quite a lot, didn't we?
I've gotta say. You handled
yourself pretty well this time.
Rusian just complimented me!
Please! Hasn't this club
thing been kinda pointless?
[HIDEKI]
How so?
The entire reason
we started this
was to help Ako re-integrate
into the real world.
Yeah. So what?
[AKANE]
Because instead of doing that,
it seems like we're
making the boundary
between the game and
reality even blurrier.
We're all having fun,
why does it matter?
[KYOH]
No, it is a bit of a problem.
[HIDEKI]
Master?
It's simple.
There's the problem
of a time limit
closing in on the Net Game Club.
We don't have an advisor.
Without an advisor,
we don't have the formal
presence to maintain a club.
We'll probably be
disbanded soon.
Before that, we're gonna
try to achieve our goal.
[RUSIAN]
Yo, Nekohime!
[NEKOHIME]
Hm? Rusian!
I, uh...
I hoped you could
give me some advice.
[NEKOHIME]
Hmm... That is a pickle.
[RUSIAN] It doesn't seem
like she can distinguish
between real life
and the game.
[NEKOHIME]
I get it.
I just heard a similar
tale quite recently.
I don't know how else to
say it, but she's at risk.
One false step and your friend
is going to have
a really hard fall.
But you won't let
that happen, will you?
No. I hope not.
Believe in yourself!
[RUSIAN] Just keep doing
what I've been doing?
It can't be that easy.
So, uh, could I ask for your
advice again sometime?
Abso-mew-tly.
[HIDEKI]
Ako. I mean, Tamaki.
Come take a seat for a minute.
Uh. Yes, Rusian? What's wrong?
[HIDEKI]
I'm not Rusian. I'm Nishimura.
Huh? Oh, right. Yes, Nishimura?
This club is going to
come to an end soon,
so I'm going to say
this one more time.
The game and
reality are separate.
Like how your
character is married
to my character in the game,
but here at school,
we're ordinary classmates.
So let's try treating each
other like regular friends.
[gasps]
Also, if you haven't met IRL,
you should never let
your guard down.
Even if you know
them from the game.
Rusian, who's been planting
these ideas in your ear?
You met someone else,
didn't you?
And they said something
to change your mind.
Was it a woman?
No, why would you
even think that?
[I see. Another woman.
No, you're wrong.
Rusian, a wife can
tell with a glance
if her husband has been
unfaithful to her.
Look, I'm no cheater!
[AKO]
Could I ask for her name?
What for?
[AKO]
I wanna pay my respects.
No, please don't!
Why not, silly?
I just want to meet the
woman giving my husband
a helping hand and
thank her in person!
Of all the crazy
things you've said,
that was the scariest.
Oh, you have no idea.
'Cause you're already beaten!
I'm so angry it's almost flipped
back around to euphoric!
[HIDEKI] Wow, would you
look at the time?
[RUSIAN] It got ugly. She saw
through me in a second.
[laughs]
That story is
absolutely purr-fect!
Hi, Rusian.
So who's your friend?
Ah! Ako!
Do you like it when that woman
makes all of those cat noises?
Is that what mew're looking for
in the girl of your
dreams, Rusian?
[RUSIAN]
Don't you start doing it.
That was just an old
acquaintance of mine.
Remember that story
about the cross-player
I declared my love to?
[gasps]
That's who you confessed your
love to, Rusian? That one?
I'm so jealous. How outrageous.
Agh! What an awful
person she is!
Tell us what you really think.
She threw my darling Rusian's
heart through the meat grinder!
I'll teach her!
I'll make her pay!
Stop it, dummy!
Stalking me is one thing,
but I'm not gonna let you go off
and bother poor
Nekohime as well.
But Rusian...
[RUSIAN] You got that?
I mean it this time!
I understand.
Well, I have business
to attend to. Pardon me.
[RUSIAN]
Hey! Hold on!
Mister Nishimura?
Have you seen Miss
Tamaki around today?
[HIDEKI]
Huh?
[KYOH] She was playing in
the game last night, right?
Same as always.
Huh?
Ako!
[AKANE]
What is that girl up to now?
[RUSIAN]
Why aren't you in school?
[AKO] I have some important
business to attend to,
so I took the day off.
What's so important?
Offline meeting.
Offline?
I guess. I didn't know about it.
With who?
A person to person meet-up
with a player I know.
[AKANE]
Someone you know? In LA ?
Yes.
Is this someone that we
would be acquainted with?
No, I don't think so.
Really?
I thought you didn't know
anyone else on here,
other than the three of us.
One of your girlfriends,
I assume?
[AKO] Actually, this person
told me he was a male.
But I still haven't met
him face-to-face yet.
[HIDEKI]
Uh?!
An offline meeting
with an unknown man?
[KYOH]
Hmm...
Wait! Don't do this!
It's dangerous!
He's right!
And besides, you've still got
Rusian here to keep you company.
That's true.
I have a dashing husband
named Rusian.
Well, there you go.
But like you told me, that's
only in the game, isn't it?
You said the game and
reality were separate.
[grunts]
Can you explain?
The game and reality,
what's the big difference?
Hold on a second.
You don't sound like your
usual self today, Ako.
[AKO]
I'm going to head out now.
Unless you object, I'll leave.
Yeah.
Suit yourself.
Come on!
Do you really mean that?
Are you sure?
What's the big deal?
We finally got Ako
to acknowledge
that there's a separation
between the game and reality.
We've achieved what
we set out to do
when we created this club.
Guess everything's worked out!
[AKO]
Can you explain?
The game and reality,
what's the big difference?
Damn!
[AKANE]
What're you standing around for?
What do you mean?
[KYOH]
Ako's offline meeting is set
for six o'clock this evening.
Schew managed to
get that out of her.
Six o'clock tonight?
It's happening in front
of Maegasaki Station,
just like when we met up.
You've got to hurry
and stop her!
But I-- I don't have that right.
[AKANE] Are you still pulling
that melancholy nonsense?
We don't have time for this!
She is still your
wife, isn't she?
She isn't my wife! Well,
she is, but only in the game.
In real life,
she's just a friend.
She said so herself.
[AKANE] What is your problem,
moron? You are so lame!
I've known you were
a dork for a long time,
but I never thought you
had donkey-brains!
Shut up.
[AKANE sighs]
[AKANE] I get it.
You like Ako, don't you?
Then that's enough, isn't it?
Now go and stop her!
You aren't really gonna
let the girl you like
walk into danger?
He won't. Will you?
Because you're better than that.
In fact, the way I see it,
Ako may be guilty
of blurring the lines
between the game and reality,
whereas you are
the complete opposite,
assuming little connection
between the two.
Yeah, but...
[KYOH]
The real you is much different
from your character in the game.
The same can be said
of the two Akos,
but she sees the Rusian in you.
It's natural to feel affection
for such a regular
part of your life.
It's not that.
You're missing the point.
[AKANE]
What do you mean?
It's something more than that!
After meeting the real deal Ako,
talking to her, touching her,
I've realized I really like
the non-game Ako too.
And it isn't even
my digital wife
I'm worried about right now.
I'm worried about the real Ako!
I hope she's all right.
The last thing I want
is for her to get hurt!
Really?
That's right!
It's true. The game and
reality are different!
Good enough.
I guess you just answered
your own question.
So hurry up and
get outta here!
Yeah!
What absolute basket
cases. Both of 'em.
Oh, definitely.
[HIDEKI]
Ako!
Rusian?
As your husband,
I disapprove of any offline
meetings with strange men!
Things may be different
in the real world,
but in the game, you and I
are still husband and wife!
Oh, Rusian.
Rusian... is Nishimura?
[HIDEKI]
Huh?
Hang on. Miss Saito?
This is the real Nekohime!
[HIDEKI]
Huh?!
Whoa! Wait a sec!
No way. You're wrong.
Nekohime told me she was
actually an older man.
Not true!
As I see with my own two eyes.
Ever since I saw the cat girl,
I knew she was really female!
And when I invited her
to meet in person,
Miss Saito showed up.
[HIDEKI]
It could just be coincidence.
No, she's right.
I am Nekohime.
[HIDEKI gasping]
[AKO] Busted!
[SAITO]
Yesterday, I chatted with Ako.
I mean, Miss Tamaki, in LA .
Nekohime is actually Saito?
Then... Nekohime was a
woman the whole time?
Which means... I proposed
to my homeroom teacher?
I am so sorry.
As you can see,
it causes a lot of trouble,
so I pose as a
cross-player in game.
No. Just... wait...
I need time to process.
[AKO] How dare you toy
with a heart as pure
as my beloved Rusian's!
You wicked crone!
I don't care if
you are a teacher.
As his wife, I will
have my vengeance!
En garde!
[screams]
Whoa! What d'you
think you're doing?
Out of my way, Rusian!
I can't kill her with
you standing there!
[AKO screams]
[KYOH]
Ladies and Gentleman,
I present to you the new faculty
advisor for our Net Game Club.
Welcome, Ms. Saito!
[SAITO] After Miss Goshoin's
threat, I mean, invitation,
I had no choice, but
now I've come on board
as your new club's
faculty sponsor.
Don't you mean our "myew"
club's faculty sponsor?
Yes, of course. Oh, the fun.
Brutal.
Well, we couldn't let
our nice, new club
have such an inglorious ending.
[AKO grumbles]
She'd better keep
away from my Rusian.
Yeah, I mean you, meow-face!
You need to stop and think
about what you've done.
You're lucky this didn't blow up
into something more serious.
At least Nekohime
wasn't an old man.
All right, you guys!
Since it's come to this,
I will work hard as your
club's faculty advisor!
However, I do have one request.
Which is?
Every single member of the club
must attend school as often
as their health allows.
Right, Tamaki?
[AKO groans]
[HIDEKI growls]
Yes, ma'am. I understand.
Very well.
That's done.
Now we can all start playing
the game together again!
[AKO gasps]
Yeah! I can't wait!
Oh yeah, that reminds me!
You need to come by the house
and meet my parents
sometime soon!
I am not doing that!
[gasps]
So then, you want me
to come to your house
to meet your parents first?
No, I told you.
The game and reality are
two different things!
[SAITO]
Now it's time for your lecture.
If it had been anyone but me,
this could've ended terribly.
I mean, attacking someone
you've never met?
[AKO]
It was a myewstake!
[SAITO]
How dare myew mock me!