[HIDEKI]
Gimme a break.
This is her idea of
alone time in a hotel?
No way. It dropped me?
I guess these things
happen sometimes.
Well, at least it wasn't right
in the middle of combat.
Oh, man!
[HIDEKI]
Towel, towel.
I must've typed it in wrong.
[KYOH] Lately, some
net games, LA included,
have been rife with
account hacking.
Make sure to log off your
account before leaving.
[HIDEKI]
Don't tell me. I've been hacked?
Then that means...
the hacker must've logged in...
...and is playing Rusian!
[HIDEKI] Ako! That's an
impostor! He's not me!
C'mon! C'mon! Ako!
Rusian.
Rusian!
I'm sorry.
That must've been awful.
It's all okay now.
I'm gonna take a look
at your chat log, okay?
[gasps]
Rusian?
So, uh, what were you saying?
It's finally our chance. The two
of us alone together at last.
Well I was thinking
maybe we could
engage in a little
couple's chat?
[FAKE RUSIAN]
Hmm...
Couple? Huh.
'Course.
Because we're married.
Duh. I swear, you can
be so silly sometimes.
I remember everything,
the ceremony,
and the stained-glass
windows of the church
glimmering in the sunlight.
Whenever I think of
that day, even now,
my heart swells to bursting
with absolute rapture!
[FAKE RUSIAN] Oh man, you're
already good to go, aren'tcha?
Why don't we get
this party started?
Huh? Like how do you mean?
Like in that whole
"couple's chat" thing
you were just blabbing
to me about.
Oh, that.
Wow, you're being unusually
assertive, aren't you?
But you like it, don't you?
And you like me, right?
[AKO]
Uh. Umm... Well, I--
Stop it. You aren't Rusian.
[FAKE RUSIAN] 'Course I am.
Do I look any different?
No, but... you're not.
Hey, what's the big deal, baby?
Now how 'bout you send me a
nice pic before we get started?
Something real sexy
to help me out on my end.
And don't worry. It's not
a problem if you're kinda dumpy.
I know chicks who play
MMO's are all nerdy losers,
but that won't slow me down.
Please stop it!
Don't say things like
that using Rusian's face!
You've gotta be kiddin' me.
I am Rusian, babe.
The man I married would
never talk like that!
I know that you're
not really my man!
[AKO]
Rusian? I'm sorry.
What do you mean you're sorry?
There isn't anything that you
need to apologize for, Ako.
Sadly, this stuff happens
from time to time.
Especially in
browser-based games.
Getting pressured
into nasty chat
by some stupid hook-up troll?
You're the victim here.
You haven't done anything wrong.
In fact, if anyone's
to blame, it's me.
I was careless enough
to let it happen.
But still. Sorry.
It's fine. No need to apologize.
But I--
I made a mistake, and called
a complete stranger "Rusian."
And there, for the
briefest moment...
...I thought he was you.
[KYOH]
I tried to be careful.
I can't believe we actually
had an account hacked.
You can't just shrug it off
when it happens to
someone close to you.
We logged into a secure site
on a PC anyone could use.
We should've been more cautious
when using a public computer.
I'm sorry. It's my
fault we're even here.
What're you talking about?
You're not to blame, Master.
First things first.
I'll contact the management
and tell them what happened.
[HIDEKI]
Yeah, good call.
Okay, so what do we do next?
Well, I've already
had my password reset
and regained account access.
[KYOH] You think your
information was stolen
from the lobby PC?
It's the only option that
really makes any sense.
I see.
So the first time it didn't
take your password,
it wasn't because
you mistyped it.
[HIDEKI]
Right.
Huh? What's that mean?
The tab was already open
on the lobby computer,
but it was a fake login page
that looked just
like the real one.
And when I tried to sign on,
it captured both
my ID and password.
Then it forwarded me on to the
Legendary Age official website.
That's a classic phishing scam.
So, how bad's the damage?
[HIDEKI]
Take a look for yourself.
Rusian's been totally erased.
Rusian...
[HIDEKI]
Hey now, take it easy.
It's not like I really
disappeared, you know.
But he took my Rusian away.
My Rusian is gone forever.
Actually, he's mine. My Rusian.
There isn't much more
that we can do,
so I'll make a new character.
But more importantly,
I have to start looking for the
things I can't ever get back.
Like the items
Rusian was carrying.
He clued in on what was coming.
'Cause when I tried to recover
my items right away,
a bunch of 'em
were already gone.
This guy really works fast.
Which makes this a contest
of speed for me too.
I'm guessing he probably sold
everything of value off.
I'll have to buy back
whatever I can.
[AKANE] You're actually gonna
pay the guy who conned you?
I don't much like it, but some
items had sentimental value.
I want them back.
Understood.
I'll go scout out the shops
and auction houses.
Don't you worry.
I'll drum up some help.
I know some people
who can lend us a hand.
Time to get started.
Everyone use the
PCs in their rooms,
and let's find the stolen items.
So what are you going to do now?
Consult with an old friend.
He's got a ton of contacts
in the game community.
[BLACK MAGICIAN]
What dire news indeed.
Having your gear stolen
and your character
erased is most dreadful.
So now, I've been forced
to use this alt toon
that I made a long time ago.
That's why I'm showing up
in chat as Piroshiki.
But please just call me Rusian.
I've kinda gotten
used to that name.
[BLACK MAGICIAN] I'll be frank.
You were careless.
Try to be more
vigilant in the future.
The net can be quite a
dangerous place, after all.
I found that out the hard way.
And... this might
seem a bit forward.
I was hoping that maybe you'd
help me find my stolen stuff.
[BLACK MAGICIAN]
Sure, no problem.
[PIROSHIKI] Of course,
sorry to have bothered--
Uh? You're seriously
gonna help me?
[BLACK MAGICIAN]
Didn't I tell you before?
We're all fellow
gamers here, comrade.
[chuckles]
When a fellow player is
in trouble, you help them.
Only then can our society
be free from douches.
[CLOUD]
As you wish, dearest Nekohime.
All right then.
You heard her, boys!
In the name of
Nekohime's Elite Guard,
we will track down
the stolen items!
[ELITE GUARD]
Yeah!
[CLOUD]
Long live Nekohime!
[ELITE GUARD]
Wow, I really
appreciate you guys
volunteering
to help meow-ut,
but I feel like all the shouting
is kinda unnecessary.
[KYOH] Well? Are any of
these items familiar?
[PIROSHIKI] Yes.
Now that you mention it,
I had one of each of these
items in my inventory.
[KYOH]
I see.
Let's take note of the
seller's name. Rontan.
So is this the jerk
that hacked me?
[KYOH]
It's a strong possibility.
I'll send a screencap of this
to the admins for evidence.
[PIROSHIKI]
I already did.
I can't believe how much
he's charging for these.
Don't worry about that.
I'd be glad to buy
them back for you.
[PIROSHIKI]
No, you don't have to do that.
Yes I do.
I still feel partially
responsible
for what happened to you.
Master.
[beeping]
[AKO]
You've got mail!
It's from Cloud, one of
Nekohime's Elite Guards.
Oh wow! Look!
That's the wedding ring
I gave you, Rusian!
[HIDEKI] Apparently, he got
it as a drop from a monster.
It must've been thrown away
since he couldn't sell it.
The monster just picked it up.
[AKO] Thrown away?
That's just plain rude!
To say the very least!
But still, despite
him being a jerk,
our wedding ring
came back to us.
I'd call it a minor miracle.
Yeah, you're right.
This is the power of true
love at work online!
We were lucky.
[HIDEKI]
Maybe you're right.
[KYOH]
Okay then. Please excuse us.
Nishimura.
I know what happened must be
quite a shock to the system,
but try not to let it get
you down too much.
[KYOH]
The school is such a quiet place
during summer
vacation, isn't it?
[HIDEKI] Thanks for
coming up here with me
to explain what happened
to the administration.
[KYOH]
Not a problem.
It happened during
club camp, after all.
Stuff like this is part of
my job as club president.
[HIDEKI] I'm so outraged
by what happened.
Still, I can barely believe it.
That makes sense.
You had your items stolen,
and the character you'd spent
so much time on was erased.
[HIDEKI]
Yeah, of course.
But what's worse,
I can't stand the way
that he used Rusian
as a way to treat Ako like
she was a worthless nobody!
He took Rusian away from me.
And then, in the
blink of an eye,
he tried to steal
Ako's innocence!
That's one of
the problems online.
There are far too few
legitimate Nigerian princes.
And if you hijack an account,
it becomes all too easy to
pose as a different person.
The gaming world
is no exception.
It's sad to think the ties
we have to each other
are so fragile.
So easily corrupted.
[KYOH]
You think so?
Ako figured out
he wasn't really you
solely from the tone
of the chat dialogue.
If she knows it's an
impostor from just that,
it reinforces how deep your
relationship with Ako truly is.
That's why.
It's safe to say your ties
to her have stayed strong.
Looks like someone is
starting to cheer up a bit.
[HIDEKI]
Yeah.
You gave me a new perspective,
and now I wanna get this
bastard more than ever!
Oh yeah?
Because I was out for
blood from the get go.
Huh?
What do you mean, "The admins
aren't doing anything"?
And we've already found the guy
who's selling the
missing items as a set!
No ifs, ands or buts.
This Rontan guy's the culprit!
Whoever hacked me had
a different IP address
than the character we found
selling off my gear.
IP?
Yeah, that's right.
It's kinda like a personal
identification number
everyone who goes online
has assigned to them.
So if you do anything bad,
it can be used to track you
down, and bring you to justice.
And until we can identify
them as the same person,
we can't accuse them
of wrong-doing.
[PIROSHIKI]
I'm betting our perp
normally plays the
game from home,
but when he's account hacking,
or other illegal stuff,
he uses a different IP.
So what? We're just
supposed to take it?
[BLACK MAGICIAN] That option
isn't acceptable either.
Sorry to intrude.
[PIROSHIKI]
The Black Magician!
[BLACK MAGICIAN]
I came across something
I found rather disturbing.
You should take a
look at this URL.
"LON's Scam Blog-stravaganza?"
What is this crap?
[BLACK MAGICIAN] It's the
blog of a famous swindler
known for running scams
across multiple games.
In fact, his most recent post
jokes about how he
hacked your account.
Damn it!
We've gotta do what it takes
to make that A$$ face pay!
If I get the chance, I'll smash
the SH@# out of that guy!
Whoa, the chat window
isn't displaying those words.
If you ask me,
this guy's a real
F@#K-WIT A$$-GOBBLER.
[PIROSHIKI gasps]
He's a moronic miscreant
with a desire to show off.
He can't keep from
bragging about it.
The internet is full
of dorks like him.
And that's not all.
He also dabbles in
RMT's from time to time.
Though he must cover
his tracks well,
since he hasn't been
caught in the act yet.
What's a RMT?
[AKANE] You don't know
what that is either?
[KYOH]
Real money trades.
People sell off rare,
in-game items,
but for real life currencies,
instead of gil.
It's against the terms
of service in LA .
That's it!
It sounds like someone
just had an epiphany.
There's no guarantee
that it's gonna work,
but at least it will give us
a chance to take down
that swindling butt-munch!
[AKANE] Nishimura's plan has
us going through the night.
If this doesn't work, that
idiot better say his prayers.
[HIDEKI] So freaking tired.
Three days with no sleep.
Not to mention, I think my
stomach's eating itself.
[doorbell rings]
Doorbell, or am I hallucinating?
[doorbell ringing]
[HIDEKI]
Yeah, yeah. I'm coming!
[giggles]
I just dropped by--
Rusian, it's me,
your doting wife!
Geez, what was with
the harsh treatment?
I'm sorry. It was just a reflex.
I expected a significantly
warmer welcome.
It is the first time your wife
has visited your family home.
Well, technically speaking,
you're not my wife anymore.
Think about it. From the
moment Rusian was deleted,
it officially annulled
our marriage.
[gasps]
So we're divorced?!
Are you really just
now realizing that?
Rusian's disappearance
was such a shock.
I can't believe
he's really gone.
How could that phony Rusian
do something like this
to such a sweet, tender heart?!
What kind of maniac are
we dealing with here?
Glad you're all caught up.
Then that means...
If our marriage got annulled,
what does that make us?
Uh. Friends, I guess?
That can't be.
Um... if you and I aren't
a couple anymore...
...does that mean
you don't want this?
[HIDEKI]
Whoa!
[AKO] I don't really understand
what you've been up to
the last couple of days,
but I know that you've
been working extra hard.
I wanted to make
something for you.
I was wondering what I'd do for
lunch, and then you showed up!
Thanks, Ako!
Yeah, after I eat this, I'll be
ready for the home stretch!
Rusian, I'm proud of you
for working so hard,
but try not to overdo it.
Because the most
important thing to me
is making you happy.
Ako, of all the random,
sometimes inappropriate
things you've said to me,
that was the most wife-like.
[LON] "The Wannabe
Famous Swindler's Blog."
Get an email from someone
claiming to have found a blog
that's even better than mine,
so I take a peek to see
what all the fuss is about,
and this cheap
knock-off's all I find?
"From scamming Nekohime's Elite
Guard for fake membership dues
to conning the
Black Magician out of
a bundle of top-tier
purple items."
Pretty impressive, kid.
There's even a trading board.
"Seeking RMTs in LA ," huh?
[LON]
These rates aren't half bad.
It's almost that time.
Is everything ready?
Affirmative.
[KYOH]
All right.
Let's get it on!
Roger!
Target is confirmed.
[AKANE]
The character's name is Shoko.
Shoko! That's even more
ridiculous than Lon!
Mission proceeding to
Phase Two. Commence Plan N!
Roger that!
He's in. How are we?
Waiting for the admins to
respond. Another 30 seconds.
Master, how long?
Just 15 seconds.
[HIDEKI]
He's getting impatient.
Hold on. A little longer.
Almost there.
Okay, here they come!
[NYACK] Greetings,
I am Game Master Nyack.
Tell me, do you know
why the two of you
were teleported to
this location?
The admins received a tip.
We were told you were engaging
in Real Money Transactions.
Is there any truth to this?
What do you mean?
Yes, that is accurate.
This person contacted
me on a trading board
and negotiated
an RMT with me.
Bastard! You set me up,
didn't you?
Haven't you ever heard that
turnabout is fair play?
So what?
Have we met before or somethin'?
None of this matters
because an RMT where no
money even exchanged hands
doesn't prove anything.
At most, we're looking at a
one week lockout, aren't we?
Not quite. One more thing.
You have been accused
of account hacking
via the character
known as Rontan.
Rontan? Who cares about him?
[NYACK] Based on the IP
information submitted to us
by the trading board,
we have proof.
You have committed several
access violations.
We are considering
filing charges.
You can't intimidate
me, Blondie!
There's no way a site that dirty
would ever hand any
IPs over to an admin!
Exactly what we wanted
you to think.
[SHOKO]
Huh?
[RUSIAN]
It was my website.
I put the whole thing
up three days ago.
Dude, are you kidding me?
That site has posts that go
back for a couple years!
[RUSIAN]
Oh man, you're tellin' me!
Fabricating a few years' worth
of authentic-sounding posts
really takes it outta ya!
No way. You're bluffing.
You faked multiple years
worth of blog material
just to set me up?
[RUSIAN]
Heh.
Are you some kinda idiot?
You wasted that much of your
time to trick one person?
Damn straight.
Besides... you made my wife cry.
You better believe I was
going to make you pay!
[AKO]
You guys made a fake blog?
Is that why you've
all been staying up
to work the last few nights?
Yeah. And watching the hacker.
We logged him replying to
the trade request from home,
unaware of our trap.
[AKANE] Then, he showed up for
the deal as the character Shoko.
[HIDEKI] Whenever he got up to
anything not entirely legal,
he was careful to use
a separate IP.
Including, of course,
when he hacked my account.
The admins have been proactive.
Rusian-- No, Piroshki's account
has been locked out
for three days,
suspended for an attempted RMT.
Yeah, but I was prepared for
a much stricter punishment.
[AKANE] You guys failed to
mention the very best part!
The admins also restored
Rusian's character!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
[sighs] Nyack is
a total dreamboat.
So does that mean I
finally get to have
my dear Rusian back with me?
All's well that ends
well, right guys?
No. I'm afraid we still have
some unfinished business.
Ako, it's a bit late
to bring this up,
but when my account was hacked,
I was honestly shocked.
Having someone else logged in as
Rusian, I just felt so helpless,
so scared I would lose you too.
I don't ever wanna go through
something like that again.
I want-- I want to be closer
to you than I was before.
So, uh...
Would you like Rusian
a little less,
and try to like the real life
Hideki a little bit more?
I can't.
Sorry, I can't like you anymore.
Because I already love you
with all of my heart!
[KYOH] I came up with a
fool-proof anti-hacking measure.
[HIDEKI]
What is it?
[KYOH] We just buy
out the entire hotel!
[HIDEKI]
You can't!
[KYOH]
Fine, we'll buy the servers.
[HIDEKI]
As if!
[KYOH]
Even better, the admin team!
[HIDEKI]
Get serious!