Well, she's friendly.
Do you know her?
No, Sette here's a total
newb as far as I've seen.
So I offered to give her a few
pointers on how to get started.
[RUSIAN laughs nervously]
All right!
If you really wanna
learn the game,
then I, the Great Schwein,
would gladly mentor you.
You're named... Schwein?
I'll pass... but thank you.
Rusian... has been really nice!
[KYOH] Seriously? You wanna
play a different game today?
[AKO]
That's right.
As long as everyone else
is okay with that.
Sure, why not?
We're the Net Game Club,
so LA isn't the only option.
Right on.
So any special request for what
game we should play instead?
I was hoping for something
a bit more exhilarating.
Roger.
Then how about...
Let's give this a shot.
[AKANE]
Ultra Force ?
[HIDEKI]
It's an FPS.
This'll be my first First-Person
Shooter experience.
Do you think I'll be okay?
I've got an idea
that might help you.
Listen closely. All the enemies
in the game... are normies!
They're all normies?
I understand.
Let's go!
[ANNOUNCER]
Team Deathmatch!
You don't have to repeat
the game mode announcement.
[KYOH laughing]
[KYOH] Behold the might of
the self-destructing Bazooka!
One shot, five kills!
[AKANE] But you caught me in the
blast radius too, you dingbat!
Damn it!
They're out-flanking us!
[HIDEKI]
I'm toast.
No way. Was that Ako?
Beautiful.
Did you see that?
At last, I think I've finally
found the perfect game for me!
Yeah, sure.
[groans]
I fell deep in the
Ultra Force rabbit hole,
and the next thing
I know, it's morning.
And I never would've
thought that Ako
would take to an FPS
like a fish to water.
Hey.
So what exactly were
you doing out there?
I thought I had inbound
hostiles on my position.
That's all.
You're way too caught up in it.
[HIDEKI]
Huh? What's wrong?
Over here. Normie scum.
[HIDEKI]
Yeah. I guess so.
If only this were a
level in Ultra Force .
Huh? Hey, don't even
joke about that!
Don't joke about what?
Akiyama?
[NANAKO] Didn't your
club meet up yesterday?
Yeah, that's right.
That's weird.
'Cause I looked for you,
but couldn't find you
in your usual place.
[HIDEKI]
Hm?
[HIDEKI screams]
I was hoping you might show me
some more stuff in the game,
but you were nowhere
to be found.
What? You mean--?
Then you're... Sette, right?
--[AKANE screams]
--Yup!
But-But why?
How did you even...?
You guys seem to
have so much fun.
And Akane in particular
seems to be really into it!
[AKANE] It's over. My reputation
at this school is over.
And you're so nice, Nishimura.
I can't thank you enough
for helping me learn
how to play the game!
Totally not the impression
I got from you in class!
Right, well. Thank you.
So, Tamaki, when you said you
and Nishimura were a couple,
you only meant a couple
in the game, right?
[HIDEKI]
Hey, listen. Not here.
What's wrong? I'm just curious.
I wanted to find out
if you and Tamaki
were an item outside the game.
Ako!
Easy now. No need to freak out.
[AKANE]
It's all over and done.
I-- But why, Rusian?
That's mean!
[BOTH gasp]
[AKO crying]
[AKANE]
It's over. My life is done.
[SAITO]
That poor, confused girl.
I swear, I didn't mean
to make her so angry.
I think her reaction
was one of shock,
rather than some
outburst of anger.
[AKANE] I bet Ako freaked out
because she thought Nanako
was gonna take
Nishimura away from her.
As if! I'm not interested
in Nishimura like that.
Ugh! That's gross.
Brutal.
If it had been anyone
other than Ako,
we could've all had a laugh and
moved on with our lives by now.
After everything that happened,
I doubt she'd appreciate all of
us showing up at her house.
Ako... I'm sorry.
Going there now would only
make her more stubborn.
Yeah, it would.
I concur.
Well, for now,
let's just give her a little
bit of breathing room.
She needs some time to
process all these feelings,
and then I'm sure
she'll calm down.
We can figure out
what to do after that.
[SAITO] Basically, this is just
a big misunderstanding,
isn't that right?
Yeah.
If we can tell her
what happened,
it should clear everything up.
Fine, but how do we talk to her?
I've been trying to call her for
a while, but she won't answer.
What next? Any plan?
Yeah. We'll talk.
Great, but how?
She won't answer her phone!
[RUSIAN]
Ako!
So this is where you've been.
Perfect timing.
You arrived just as I
was about to level up.
Would you care to join me?
Listen up:
Akiyama isn't the slightest
bit interested in me.
I'm not her type.
It meant nothing--
Doesn't matter now.
I've given up on everything.
I forsake any life where
we're not together, Rusian.
What's all this
"forsaking life" stuff?
You don't mean?
I've decided to reincarnate.
Huh?
I'm maxing out my
character level,
and taking my chances
with the next life!
[groans]
So, uh, what're you saying?
Silly boy. Do you need
it spelled out for you?
I'm reincarnating within LA .
Ready to become a new character.
May I be reborn as someone
more cheerful and popular.
I'll settle for nothing less
than the total package.
You talked about forsaking life.
You're planning to do it
for real, aren't you?
That's correct. I've
decided to quit school.
But...
I'm living in Legendary
Age from now on.
I have no need for real life.
Ako... you can't.
[AKO] As long as
I have LA , I can go on.
This is a mistake!
[AKO] Inside this world, you're
still my faithful husband.
Okay. I'm gonna work
real hard to reincarnate.
[RUSIAN]
Wait, don't go!
[HIDEKI]
Damn it!
It looks like Ako's blocked
any incoming chat.
She's through talking.
I can't believe she's
completely closed herself off
inside the game.
I guess this means the club's
purpose has backfired.
That might not be true.
Unlike last time, when she tried
to assault me with a cudgel,
she's only closing herself off
from the world this time.
Sounds like she's improving
in her own special way.
Yes, I hadn't considered
things from that perspective.
She needs her own way
to blow off some steam.
And something tells me that
Ako doesn't really believe
that Nanako's trying
to take you from her.
Guess you're right.
She totally made a big show out
of sulking over what happened;
which snowballed into a bigger
deal than it should've.
Once she calmed down, she
probably felt a bit embarrassed.
That's precisely what I thought.
What's more, she has a
kind-hearted young man
who cares for her,
and has what it takes
to set her back on
the right path.
Or so it would seem.
Do you really think
it's a good idea
to put such complete
confidence in a minor?
Sometimes, part of
being a good teacher
is having faith
in your students.
[HIDEKI]
You make it sound so heroic.
All right, I'll try.
I'll see her.
On one condition:
I handle things my own way.
[AKANE] A word of
advice before you start.
Ako knows perfectly well how
ditzy she can be sometimes.
It takes her forever to learn
enemy attack patterns.
And I'd say half of
those, she forgets.
I mean, imagine the first poor
bastards she played with in LA .
They all gradually disappeared.
[HIDEKI]
That sounds about right.
But you... you weren't
like the others.
If things ever went belly up,
you'd say "We'll get
'em next time,"
promising there would
be a next time.
When you stuck with her
hopelessly inept character
in the game, it was like you
accepted the real life Ako.
She said that you were
the kind of person
she could stay with forever.
And she had such a
stupid grin on her face
you'd swear her brain was gonna
melt and pour out of her ears.
Did she? I never knew.
Funny thing is,
I feel the same.
[HIDEKI]
Uh.
[AKANE] And like Ako,
I get the feeling
you're someone I could hang
out with forever, too.
[gasps]
When I say hang out,
I mean playing games
together in a club setting,
or online from our own homes.
You get what I'm
trying to say, right?
Yeah, I think so.
What I mean is,
it could've been worse,
but I ended up getting
stuck with you.
And you got stuck with me.
As well as that reclusive psycho
and Little Miss Money Bags.
Look. Just make sure
you bring Ako back to us.
Deal! I'm on the case.
Great! Now, I'd say my
work here is done. Heh.
[door opens]
[AKO'S MOTHER]
Excuse me, young man?
[HIDEKI]
Huh?
How can I help you?
[HIDEKI yelps]
Uh, hello! I'm Mister Hideki
Nishimura, Esquire, or Sir.
In game.
[AKO'S MOTHER]
Uh...
You're the online husband
I've heard so much about!
[HIDEKI]
Uh?
She told you?
Yeah. My folks and I
don't talk that much,
especially not about my games.
[AKO'S MOTHER]
Oh, I see.
So what brings my virtual
son-in-law over?
I take it you've come to visit
my problem daughter.
Yes, that's right.
I just--
I came to visit Ako
to see how she was.
I'm cutting school right now.
Are you really? All for her?
Yes, ma'am.
I see.
Even though she says that
she's through with school?
I guess. Whatever that's worth.
[AKO'S MOTHER]
Hmm...
[giggles]
Huh? You giggled. What is it?
[AKO'S MOTHER giggles]
[gasps] Oh!
Look at me, I'm sitting
here chatting with you,
when I should be
heading off to work!
Please check on her,
if you don't mind.
What, you mean it?
Of course!
Besides, one day it won't
be me taking care of her.
Something tells me that job will
fall to you one way or another.
[HIDEKI]
Oh, wow, uh...
I'm not ready for that kind
of responsibility yet.
[AKO'S MOTHER] Oh, nice
and honest. I like that.
This is yours.
What's that?
[AKO'S MOTHER]
It's the key to Ako's room.
[HIDEKI]
Ako, it's me!
[AKO]
Huh? Rusian?
Sorry to drop by without
warning. Can I come in?
[AKO]
Uhh... What are you doing here?
You should be at school!
Where's my mom?
She asked me to
look out for you.
She even left me
a key to your room.
[AKO]
Mom! That is way uncool!
[HIDEKI] She also entrusted
me with your future.
[AKO] You've done
a bang-up job so far!
[HIDEKI] Which means I won't
take "no" for an answer!
I'm letting myself in.
[AKO] Whoa, wait a second!
No! Don't do that!
[HIDEKI] You can't hide
from reality anymore!
I'm coming in!
[whimpering]
[HIDEKI]
What the heck was that?!
Why are you in your
freakin' underwear?!
[AKO] I just like to feel
free and uninhibited
when I'm in the privacy
of my own room!
You know how it goes!
So just hold on.
I need to get ready.
Yeah.
[AKO]
Okay, come in.
Please be gentle.
What's wrong?
Aren't you coming in?
What the hell's wrong with you?!
You said you needed to get
ready, but you just got naked!
[AKO]
I was preparing myself mentally!
[HIDEKI] That's not the kind
of preparation I intended!
Could you please
put some clothes on?
[AKO]
Go ahead.
[HIDEKI]
Cool, thank you.
Dude, you have a fridge
in your room?
[AKO] I try to be prepared
to go a week straight
without leaving my room,
so I need some provisions.
Surely you have to
go to the restroom
at some point during
a seven day stretch.
[AKO]
There's no need to go anywhere.
I use plastic bottles.
[gasps]
[HIDEKI]
No way. Did she really?
I'm gonna... I'm gonna hurl.
I'm just messing with you.
I personally brewed
the tea this morning.
Couldn't you tell
from the taste?
How am I supposed to
know what it tastes like?
I've never drunk any!
C'mon, Rusian, the plastic
bottle thing was just a joke.
I use the restroom like
a regular person.
Between the nudity and the pee,
my heart can't take much more.
[AKO]
So... I was wondering.
What brings you here, Rusian?
I know what it is.
You came to try to get me
to go back to school.
Not today.
[gasps]
Today we're gonna
have some fun.
Huh?
[HIDEKI] Remember,
the highest-ranked clerics
manage the cooldown times
of each of their healing skills.
Using the right skill at the
right time will chain combos,
which boosts their power.
And don't forget to buff your
allies and debuff the enemy.
Also, having a couple
elixirs in your hotbar
will help you hedge your bets
if things start going south.
Those are the basics
rules for ideal play.
You got it?
I don't "got it"!
And I don't really understand
what's happening right now!
[HIDEKI chuckles]
Well, you said you're
trying to cap your level
and reincarnate, right?
Then you ought to
learn this stuff now,
or you'll never get anywhere.
Yeah, I guess you make
a pretty good point.
Of course! That's why
I'm tutoring you.
Ugh! You might be asking
too much from me!
No time to whine!
I'll stick with you until
you've got it locked!
[AKO]
Okay.
[HIDEKI]
Let's roll!
Watch out, that
werewolf's squaring off!
He's winding up.
Get ready to start healing!
[AKO]
O-Okay. Like this?
[HIDEKI] Your tempo's way too
fast for your cooldown times.
You're breaking all your combos.
But it's hard. How was that?
If you can chain the
timing just right,
you should be able
to secure the combo.
Then your cooldown time fits
within your response time.
[AKO]
I see. Is that better?
[HIDEKI] You're mixing up
your skills. It's this one.
This is impossible!
No it isn't.
If you want to reincarnate,
push it to the limit!
[AKO]
Okay.
[HIDEKI] Pay attention.
Your timing is still too fast.
[AKO sighs]
There we go. Was that right?
[beeping]
Oh. Looks like Schew
and Master have come online.
[AKO gasps]
[AKO]
Is it club meeting time already?
[HIDEKI] Ako, mind if
I borrow this cable?
[AKO]
Huh? Sure.
[HIDEKI]
Thank you.
I'll log in on this laptop
I borrowed from Master.
Signing on. Good.
All right, you knuckleheads,
what's so important that
you had to miss school?
We played together.
[AKO, AKANE gasp]
[AKANE] I oughta drop
kick the both of you!
What in the world were
the two of you thinking?
Me-yeah!
If they find out you cut
school to goof around,
they'll drop the hammer!
Sorry, Teach.
I'm nyat your teacher.
I'm Nekohime!
Hey, Nekohime, I needed
to have a chat with you.
You mind?
[NEKOHIME]
Hm?
What's the matter, Rusian?
No biggie.
I quit school.
Huh?!
You can't be serious about that.
[RUSIAN] But if Ako's quitting
school, why can't I?
To be honest, dealing with all
the "nerd-taku weeb" cracks
gets old.
My time would be better
spent playing LA .
That sounds stressful.
I wish you the best
of luck, Rusian.
Please don't, Rusian.
On one condition:
I handle things my own way.
My paws are tied. Very well.
No! You can't, Rusian!
[HIDEKI]
Why not?
If it's okay for you,
why not for me too?
You can't! Because if you
really drop out of school...
The others. Master and Schew
will miss you. That's sad.
[HIDEKI]
True.
But if you quit, Ako,
won't that be the same thing?
[AKO]
I guess.
Neither of them are
chatting back anymore.
[KYOH]
But it doesn't look like
they've disabled
their chat windows.
Sounds to me like
they must be busy.
But busy with what?
I'm gonna go ahead
and log out for now.
I'd say Rusian's done
an excellent job
bringing Ako this far.
For now, let's just wait
for Mister Nishimura
to convince Miss Tamaki
to come back to us.
What do you say?
Ako, I get it.
You aren't the only one
who dislikes school.
You have a hard time
making friends,
and you feel out
of place in class.
This whole situation you're
facing is a tough one,
and you're unsure of what to do.
You don't have any fun
outside the club,
so you don't wanna go.
That's the truth, isn't it?
Then Akiyama coming in
brought things to a boil,
and you felt like
you lost control.
At least, that's how
it seems to me.
[AKO] But how did you
know all of that--
everything I was
feeling, Rusian?
Because I'm your husband, dork.
[HIDEKI]
Did you have fun today?
I did! Tons of it!
[HIDEKI]
Awesome, me too.
So should we both drop out?
We could do this every day.
I used to think that as
long as there's the game,
it would be enough.
And in this world, I thought
I'd found the real me,
but I was wrong.
Totally.
Now, thanks to the club,
and most especially
because of you,
I've realized that life
doesn't always suck.
Schew feels the same,
wishing she could be
stuck with us forever.
With you, and me, and Master.
I'd like that. It would be
great if that were possible.
But real life?
Real life is way too hard.
Yeah, I know.
But hey...
It'll be all right!
Put a little time into real
life, then have fun!
We can play for hours, Ako!
Whatever game you want!
And when you feel like
you can handle it,
you can give the real
world another shot.
And if we can't play
hooky together again,
I'll be waiting for you
up at school, all right?
[AKO]
Rusian.
Ako.
[AKO] If I try, and I mean
really try, but then get tired,
will you stay home
with me again?
Of course I will.
For the sake of
my loving wife.
All right. Then I think
I can do it.
[GIRL A]
Hey Tamaki!
Uh. Hello.
[GIRL B] You were gone again
yesterday. What happened?
Well, I--
Sorry, is something wrong?
[GIRL B] You're not still
contagious, are you?
Good morning!
Can you believe it?
Ako's so lucky.
Her boyfriend's in my class, and
you'll never guess what he did!
When he heard that
she'd stayed home,
he actually left school
to go over to her house
and check in on her!
Yeah? The rumors were true!
Tamaki, you have, like,
the best boyfriend!
I want a man who'll skip school
to come check in on me!
But I'm alone.
Girl, you are fierce!
She, like, hit the jackpot!
Yeah!
[giggles]
You're right!
My boyfriend's the best!
[AKO] When the door
to my room was closed,
did you think I was
fully dressed?
[HIDEKI] Of course I did!
What else would I expect?
[AKO]
Guess what! I was buck naked!
[HIDEKI] Would you put some
clothes on? I can't take it!