It's freakin' huge!
I thought we were going
to your house.
This place looks like a museum.
Okay, I'm definitely out
of my element here.
Why'd you girls bring me
to this shiny palace?
Because you haven't touched any
of your vacation homework yet,
and now our summer
break is almost over!
In that case,
let's call Rusian too!
Things're better when
you work as a team!
I don't think our
parents would like it
if we invited a boy
to our sleepover.
Ugh. If Rusian can't be here,
why'd she have to come?
You called.
No I didn't! It wasn't me!
This is an opportunity for
you to learn to socialize
without using
Rusian as a safety net.
You can't do any better than
Nanako to practice with.
You're trying to
get me to practice
by squaring off
against the final boss?
[AKANE] Try getting good, scrub.
Time to learn by dying.
I'm standing right
here, you know.
I know.
[NANAKO chuckles]
Ready to work on
becoming friends, Ako?
[AKO]
Save me, Rusian!
[ALL] It's good to have you
back home, your ladyship.
Yes.
Now say hello to my
friends from school!
Take good care of them.
At long last, it's done.
Our beloved mistress has
finally made real friends.
We've dreamed of this
moment for so long,
and now it's actually
coming true!
Would you cut it out
with the water works?
No need to be
embarrassed, Master.
I'm proud of how
much you've grown.
I don't need your support pity!
Come on, let's go!
[AKO] I've never seen
a real maid before.
I thought they only
existed in stories.
Technically,
she's not a real maid.
Huh?
[MAID A chuckles]
When we learned the
mistress' friends
were coming for a visit,
we rush ordered the costumes.
[AKANE] What, so this
is just lousy cosplay?
What a terribly
rude thing to say!
That is a real-deal
maid's outfit,
totally accurate in material,
design, and practicality.
If you're interested,
I could have one made for each
of you ladies anytime you like.
Wow, you mean it?
Don't take the bait, you idiot.
[KYOH]
This is my room.
It's ten times bigger than mine.
It's almost as big as my house.
It's even got a side room!
What is that?
That is my personal
computer space.
[AKANE] You realize
you're not a day trader,
don't you, Cypher?
Just watch. I'll earn a
hundred million in seconds!
I wanna be you when I grow up!
I don't think you could even
a handle a dual-screen setup.
It's simple. I have a strategy
site open on this window.
Which means I can
quick reference...
Ah! I can't hear you! Stop it!
Well then. Should we
start our homework?
[groans]
I can't take it anymore!
How did you forget everything
we worked on last term?
Our vacation wasn't that long.
I left the flower of knowledge
untended for too long,
and now the poor thing
has withered away, Kupo!
Withered?
Master? Could you please
point me towards the restroom?
Go out, take a left.
It's the fifth door.
If you'll excuse me.
[NANAKO]
I'm coming too!
That won't be necessary.
What won't be necessary?
I need to use the restroom.
Good idea. Go with her, Nanako.
If we leave her alone,
she might try to run home.
Who, me? I would never
try something like that!
No, I'm afraid you
can't be trusted.
[AKANE]
Mh-hm. Mh-hm.
There you have it! Shall we?
[AKO grumbles]
Time to head back.
Go on without me!
I'll reconnoiter the perimeter!
I don't think we should be
walking around on our own.
It's fine. My gamer sense is
trying to tell me something.
It's saying I need to
reveal the local map.
Then my hands are tied!
If I leave you alone,
you'll run away.
Guess I'll have
to stick with you.
No. I wouldn't run away.
Uh? What's that?
I'm starting to think
I shouldn't have let
the two of them go.
Schwein is just a pig
and doesn't comprehend
difficult social nuances.
Don't be so immature.
Besides, they're
polar opposites.
[AKANE]
Hmm...
You might be surprised
by how well those differences
can compliment each other.
Well, I guess it's worth a shot.
This looks like
the kind of place
that would be chock
full of hidden items!
If someone hid them,
they probably don't
want us to find them.
[gasps]
[AKO]
Hey, check it out!
That book looks like it's
rigged up to something.
This isn't a game, Ako.
Nothing's going to happen.
I told you there'd
be hidden loot!
[NANAKO screams]
Let's see what kind
of treasure you hold!
[NANAKO]
An album?
[AKO]
I guess so.
[MAID A]
I see you found it.
[AKO, NANAKO gasp]
[BOTH scream]
This is a true Goshoin
family treasure.
This album chronicles the growth
of young Mistress Kyoh.
We're so proud.
Wait, why did you have it
hidden away in a secret room?
Some of the photos might
be embarrassing for Kyoh.
[AKO, NANAKO]
Oh.
But now you've seen it,
and that's that.
There's no other choice left but
for you to both become members
of the secret society
of mistress admirers!
[BOTH gasp]
[AKO, NANAKO screaming]
[AKO]
We're already in a guild!
[NANAKO]
One is enough for us, thanks!
[MAID A chuckles]
[AKO, NANAKO screaming]
[AKO]
We won't join your freaky cult!
If they try to give you fruit
punch, dump it, Nanako!
Is that Ako and
Nanako screaming?
Those idiots are probably
up to something.
[sighs]
If Nishimura were here,
he'd know exactly what to do.
So when the chips are down,
you like having
Rusian on your side.
Is that so strange?
No, it's understandable.
But you usually treat Rusian
like he's some kind of insect.
I'm sure he'd be surprised
if he heard you.
Wait, really? Is that how
I come across to you?
Huh?
During class, I may be
a little hard on him,
but I'm not like that
in the club, am I?
You don't honestly
think I'm some sort of
Nishimura-hating
monster, do you, Master?
Because that's not the
way I mean it at all.
No, it looks like
I had the wrong idea.
You're a good kid, Schwein.
[chuckles]
Why are talking
to me like that?!
And who're you calling a kid?!
Don't you worry. Rusian
understands you perfectly.
[AKO] Somebody, please!
You've gotta help us!
[BOTH sigh]
[MAID A laughing]
[MAID A] Just a few moments
of your time, ladies!
Sign our mailing list now
for a free bulletin!
That was too close for comfort.
What's the deal? Do you
really dislike me that much?
No. It's just...
Instinctively, you sorta
make my skin crawl.
Uh?! I make your skin crawl?
No one's ever told
me that before.
It's not so bad.
I've been told that a
few times up at school.
But hey, it's like water
off a duck's back!
[NANAKO]
It happens to you a lot, huh?
But still, when I said
I was interested
in becoming better friends
with you, I wasn't lying.
Oh. Okay.
All right. I'm lost.
Where are we?
[AKO]
Master! Master!
[gasps]
[AKO]
Master! We got lost!
And there's no way either of us
is going to find your room!
Without Nishimura around today,
I guess the whole "rescuing Ako"
thing falls to the two of us.
It's not a problem.
As the Master,
it's my responsibility.
What?
That "meow" lady from the
game is actually Ms. Saito?
Hey. It is fantasy.
That lying maniac actually
tricked my darling Rusian!
Oh man, if I'd met him first,
it wouldn't have gone that way!
You're sounding delusional, Ako.
What makes you think
you'd beat out Nekohime,
even if you met him first?
I'd make Rusian love me
even if I had to push that
cat-girl in front of a train!
Nothing says "true love"
like spastic aggression.
She must be stopped.
We don't need another
glitter wand incident.
Huh? What kind of
incident is that?
Ah... That was all part of
my dark, mysterious past.
And Ako's got more "dark past"
than any other girl her age.
You hear that? I'm number one!
Why don't we mix in some good
memories with that dark past.
Yes. Please.
Summer vacation is
winding down, after all,
so we should do
something unforgettable.
Unless of course, you still have
to finish all of your homework.
Any progress?
Tee-hee.
Don't you dare say
"Tee-hee" to me!
Starting now, we're all gonna
watch you do your homework!
How 'bout not? Why ruin
a lovely afternoon?
You can't keep slacking off!
But I--
Rusian!
This looks really delicious.
But is it okay for us to start
without your parents?
Of course.
Our family chef has been looking
forward to treating our guests.
What kind of regular household
has a private chef?
Stop frowning and
dig in, Akane.
Also, you're holding
your fork wrong.
I'm sorry.
I've never had a fancy formal
meal like this before.
[chuckles]
Hey, Schew. That little
bowl full of water is there
if you wanna make a toast.
Of course! As if I didn't
know that already!
We raise the bowls
in each other's honor.
[KYOH chuckles]
To our merry band!
Though the day of our account
creations may differ,
may we all retire from
Legendary Age together!
Yes. So we hope.
You guys are so funny
using finger bowls
like they're glasses of wine.
What? Finger bowls?
These are here as an easy
way to clean your hands,
and not ruin napkins.
[AKANE]
You tricked me, didn't you?
Yes, but I never assumed
you'd actually fall for it.
How does a crackpot like you
know about formal dining?
I wanted to be ready for when
Rusian decides to take me out,
so I studied up on it.
You can study this, but you
can't get your homework done?
[KYOH]
Mmm. Dinner was delightful.
Now it's time to soak
in a nice, hot bath
and get ready for
our pajama party.
[AKANE] That's something
Nishimura couldn't take part in
even if he were here.
There'd be more soapy
hands to go around.
Soap?
It's better to just ignore her.
[AKANE]
It's massive.
Does a private residence
even need all this?
How many people are you planning
to bathe at the same time?
[KYOH] It may seem
like overkill to you,
but after much debate,
we decided having a small
bath in a house so big
would be poorly balanced.
Poorly balanced?
How does the size
of a bathroom
affect the balance of the house?
Move it! Let's go!
[AKO]
I'll head in later.
[AKANE] What are you
so embarrassed about?
It takes self-confidence to
strut into a place like this.
I just need to track
mine down real quick.
I understand how you feel.
Sharing a bath with other people
could certainly
make one nervous.
It can almost feel like your
heart's going to burst out!
If that's the case,
then why was this part of
your evening schedule?
Come on! Let's go already!
[AKO]
No! I can't!
I don't want to right now.
No means no.
I made a promise to myself
to make sure that Rusian
is my first time!
What first time do you
think is gonna happen?
Well duh. The first time
I share a bath with someone.
That's too bad.
'Cause I already
claimed your first time
when we were at summer
camp, remember?
I-I guess you're right.
My first time is
now gone forever.
That's more Rusian's
fault than anyone else's.
He's lucky to have
friends like you.
Don't try to wash
anybody's hair with soap
like you did back at camp, okay?
Huh?
Sounds like you guys
had fun at camp.
I wish I could've gone!
But, Nanako,
you're not in the club.
Well I'm kind of in the club!
There's an unscalable wall.
And everyone outside
of it is not in the club!
I don't believe in
unscalable walls.
[AKO gasps]
Why do normies always say such
predictably uplifting nonsense?
Her soul wasn't beaten down.
What the hell?
This guild is really unfair.
[AKO]
What are you talking about?
[AKANE]
Look! Look! Look!
So what are we looking for?
We're all about the same age,
so why is there so much
difference between us?
It's totally messed up.
I mean what food
haven't I been eating?
I assumed that you customized
your character appearance
to be petite.
You don't get to choose
your character in real life!
[KYOH] That's not
entirely true, Schwein.
With exercise, a healthy,
well-rounded diet,
not to mention adequate sleep,
you too can have a
modicum of control
over your developing
young figure!
Yes. Your cuteness
is in your hands!
You heard the lady!
You failed to create any
cuteness, Shew. That's sad.
I don't have quite
enough materials
to make those items, Master.
There. All done.
[AKANE] How does a girl who
takes such terrible care
of herself have such
a perfect figure?
I tend to lead an
undeniably squishy lifestyle
in my free time.
My body got squishy too!
You're soft, but still
have good definition.
Do you have any diet tips?
Rusian likes me for who I am,
and he thinks I'm cute.
So I just eat what I want.
Every man prefers a certain
type. So what's his?
I've never even
bothered to ask.
But it might surprise you.
I think he's more
into slender ladies.
No. That's not true!
That's impossible!
I-- I'll ask him!
[NANAKO] Where'd that
cell phone come from?
It doesn't matter.
Just let her make her
stupid phone call.
All right then, I'll ask
him over video chat!
[AKANE]
Sure, sure.
Huh?! You're going to send
a video from the bath?!
I have to let Rusian look.
How else are we supposed
to know what he prefers?
You aren't seriously going to
broadcast from inside our bath?
I forbid it, as Guild
Master and host!
Please don't try to stop me!
Learning what kind
of girl Rusian prefers
could be the most important
quest I've ever undertaken!
That quest line...
...is totally forbidden!
Hey, back off!
[KYOH]
This will do irreparable damage
to our guild's efficiency!
Don't do it, Ako!
I don't care!
[AKO screams]
Over here, Ako! I'm wide open!
Thanks, Sette!
There, now it's turned off.
How could you?! You traitor!
What? I'm not sure
what you're upset about.
He didn't answer. It might've
gone to his voicemail.
It would've been a
disaster if he'd answered.
I'm amazed he was able
to read the situation.
It's easy to see just how
much he does for Ako.
Without him around,
she's out of control.
I was only going to show
myself in the video.
That's not the point,
you weirdo.
[AKANE] Seriously,
one bed fits four people?
This thing's ridiculous.
Today was one culture
shock after another.
Yeah, anybody would
think this is weird.
You may be right,
but no one's ever had the
chance to tell me before.
You're the first guests
I've ever invited
to a sleepover at my house.
Ako. Schwein. Sette.
I am beyond grateful
that you came.
What are you talking about?
We're all friends, right?
This is the first time
that I've ever been
invited to a sleepover,
so I'm feeling pretty
excited too, Master.
[NANAKO]
Oh, yeah?
If you're so excited,
let me feel your heart.
Watch out, Sette!
That's not my heart!
Okay, so what's with that?
You all call me by my game name.
Better get used to it.
That's how this club operates.
You know, doing stuff like
this with "just us girls"
can be pretty nice.
If I have to share a bed,
no offense, but I'd prefer
it was with Rusian.
And you can do that every night
when you're a married couple.
But we already are!
So I don't get how this works.
How exactly do you define your
relationship with him, Ako?
You're only married
to Rusian in the game,
but you behave like you
and Nishimura are a couple.
I was just wondering how your
thought process worked.
About Rusian and me?
Yeah, that's right.
Level with me.
You don't consider yourselves
married in real life, do you?
Uh.
I'm not really sure
how to put it.
That's a dangerous
question you're asking her.
Wait, is it? Haven't any
of you ever asked her?
The very prospect is terrifying.
Remember, if you gaze
into the abyss,
then the abyss eventually
gazes back into you.
What abyss?
Right! Picture, if you will,
a grand cathedral.
Let's say Sette, and, uh,
Schew were to get married.
[NANAKO]
Uh-huh.
[AKANE]
Why us?
[AKO] Solely for the
purpose of illustration.
Then, as a married couple,
you start playing
Legendary Age together.
It might go a little
something like this.
There's apparently a bonus
if our characters get married,
so why don't we have
an in-game wedding?
No way. Real life and
net games are different.
So we can't act
like we're married.
And what did our little
playlet reveal to you?
That your entire train of
thought is completely bonkers,
if I had to sum it up.
They're already married
in real life.
There's no reason not
to do it in the game.
You wouldn't want them marrying
someone else in the game.
That would be cheating.
How heart-breaking.
Right?
Now what do I do?
Heaven help me, I'm starting to
understand how her minds works!
It's not something I should get,
but I'm totally
picking up on it!
Oh, no! Our brains have
become tainted by Ako's mind.
Try to stay calm!
I thought my example was
pretty good. You guys are rude.
You're the one who's
being inconsiderate!
No one else is trying
to brainwash us!
How the hell does Nishimura
always handle Ako
like it's no big deal?
I've got it!
We should call Rusian!
He might be able to think
of something to do here!
Yeah, she's right!
We might actually
need that clown
if we're gonna fix this mess!
Please save us,
Nishimura the Brave!
Rusian! Everyone's
being mean to me!
Am I ever glad to see you!
Please help us, her crazy
is seeping into our brains!
I'm begging! It's horrifying.
We need you!
Help! You have to rescue us!
[RUSIAN]
Huh?
[AKO] I didn't get to
see him at all today.
I'm going through withdrawals.
Oh, Rusian, I need my husband!
[NANAKO]
Now, now. Rusian isn't around,
but I'm here for you, buddy!
[AKO]
I don't want you!