[panting]
Oh, Robby.
[PEOPLE cheering]
[groans]
-Mr. Yang fails at nothing!
-We did it!
Teamwork really does make
the dream work!
Yeah, but...
if dreams are working,
then where's Robby?
[ALLO] What?
Robby didn't contribute to this!
[GRAS]
Plus we're on Planet Tottska,
where racing is everything!
[groans]
Does that mean
we have
to run everywhere?
Because I refuse to sweat.
♪ Isekan's a perfect place ♪
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
Oh, barf.
Another visual assault
by Isekandar rodents.
You're watching Galaxy
Business Satellite.
Here's what's new in Odwarla.
The planet's elusive oarfish
is no longer a mystery
after it was caught by some
foreigners passing through.
Hark! The hunted!
Look, Mr. Yang!
Yeah, I can see the screen.
Oh, I've found you at last.
And you've caught yourself
something nice out there.
[chuckles] I wonder
what bait I'll be needing
to reel you back
into my manicured clutches.
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪
I think I can see it!
Uh, yeah,
it's kinda hard to miss.
[IKKU] The first
Galaxy Highway checkpoint,
Haccone Gateway.
Wow! It's all so exciting!
It definitely looks like
this is the place to be.
Let's head that way.
[ROBBY]
Uh, there's a hyper-road toll?
Wait, you mean
we have to pay that
on top of the transit fees?
Sounds reasonable to me.
Their expressway will shave
weeks off our travel time.
It takes way too long
to warp there.
Yeah. And I guess we're going
to keep using the money
we made on Odwarla even though
there's hardly any left?
Don't we have other options?
No, we don't.
This is literally
the only hyper-road
that connects this galaxy
to the rest of the universe.
Let's just pay a road toll
in every world we go to.
That'll be fun.
All we need now
are your travel permits.
I don't know if we have those.
Yeah, what does that mean?
We have passports,
will that work?
I'm sorry, no.
We've been having
a lot of trouble
with our denizens
leaving the galaxy illegally,
so travel permits
are mandatory now.
Happened in April. Surprised
you haven't heard about it.
[BOTH]
Huh?
That makes two of us.
Thanks a lot.
You can't brag about
all the research
you do before traveling
and then totally
not research this.
You know, you could look
into things
every once in a while, too.
You can't expect me
to do everything!
-Oh, please. Really?
-[IKKU yawns]
All you research is food,
and I was never into that.
You're a girlie traveler, man.
You can't assign a gender
to travelling!
Ladies, please.
Let's stop travel-shaming
for a sec
so we can get to Haccone
and figure this out.
♪
Yes!
They've got hot springs
out here!
Haccone is hands down
the best world in the galaxy!
Hot, fresh aliens!
Ooh, that one's got
her clavicle hangin' out!
Hurry! Let's go!
Hot springs! I scream,
you scream...
See that?
That's why we have to get
out of here
as soon as possible,
or he'll meet a woman
and ruin our lives.
♪
Which one should we do?
None of 'em!
We gotta go!
♪
It looks just like
the ones on Earth.
Well, in Japan on Earth. I don't
know about other countries.
Trip Sunvisor said
this is probably
the most popular hot spring here
and gave it a five
out of five stars.
It couldn't hurt
to check it out.
All right!
I guess you don't suck
all the time, Hatchi.
Let's invade this hot spring
laced with wet chicks
sippin' on drinks!
-Okay, I guess.
-Uh? Where are you going?
Since when do you follow
in Robby's pathetic
creeper footsteps?
[HATCHI]
We came all this way.
Might as well
enjoy ourselves, right?
Uh?
Besides, I just looked it up.
You can only get a travel permit
issued from your home planet.
Wha...
So, we have to go
all the way back to Earth
for that crap?
I can't go home.
I'd rather figure out
another way.
But not now!
I gotta get my swim on!
Springin' into hot springs!
Ehh! Hold on!
-Hatchi!
-[HATCHI chuckles]
[ROBBY]
For real?
There's a boys' bath
and a girls' bath?
Exactly what century
do they think
they're living in out here?
[screaming]
Wow, this is literally
a melting pot of aliens.
[MALE ALIEN 1] And you thought
he wouldn't give us
our travel permits!
You were totally wrong.
[MALE ALIEN 2] Shh!
There's no need to broadcast it!
Sorry. But, man,
that guy was creepy!
Thank you! Now I know
why everyone says
it's so hard
to get those things.
Way too dangerous.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help overhearing.
Can you please elaborate?
[humming]
That's Robophobic!
Excuse you?
You're just jealous
that my robot voice
is better than yours!
Quit being so bossy
and unbearable!
I can't help it! I'm a product
of my living conditions!
We might have our permits.
Why are we all pointing?
[ROBBY]
So, wait.
You know Haccone's
underworld boss?
[HATCHI] Shh.
No reason to broadcast it.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[HATCHI] He's been called
"The Kingpin of Haccone."
Others call him
"The Godfather of Haccone."
I've even heard "The Al Capone"
and "Don Juan of Haccone."
He's giving himself a lot
to live up to there.
Why can't he come up with his
own original supervillain name?
Who cares? Let him be
the God-King of Haccone.
If he can get us our permits
without making us
go back to Earth,
I'll call him
whatever he wants.
Hold on. It's not a done deal.
We still have to ask him, and
they say he's pretty dangerous.
-[IKKU] Uh?
-[ROBBY] Huh?
[HATCHI]
No one will give me details.
Just that there are those
who lose all sense
and never recover
from meeting him.
Seems pretty dramatic.
[HATCHI] It's like
something worse will happen
if they share specifics.
They're making it dangerous
by not giving us a heads-up.
Makes it easier to hide if he's
selling fake travel permits.
Are we sure this guy's legit?
[ROBBY]
No, Ikku, we're not.
That's what I was thinking!
Those are bootleg
travel permits!
They're not.
I already looked into that.
[ROBBY/IKKU]
Huh?
[HATCHI]
The ones this boss is giving out
are said to carry
even more weight
than the permits you can get
from your homeland.
You're instantly perceived
as having a higher status,
and everyone treats you
like you're elite.
So instant sports-star status.
Or like... flashing a black card
at a nightclub.
Ikku, hush.
They probably react that way
because they're afraid
of that dude.
They can look at you
and know you made a deal
with the dark emperor!
Hey! Can I get
a refill on this sake?
Sure thing, kappa.
So, if it's that dangerous,
why do we want to get
our travel permits from him?
Because it's the only option
we have right now.
[IKKU/ROBBY]
In here?
He's got giant black egg
gatekeepers?
I don't think I've ever seen
anything so round
and terrifying
in my entire life.
[screaming]
Help! Help us!
Whoa! Take a breath!
What exactly
do you need help with?
It's like we just escaped
a bad horror movie!
What? How?
I was about to become
a shell of myself!
Stay far, far away from him
if you value your life!
One sec.
Are you talking about the boss?
Well, the truth is...
[screaming]
I hope those guys at least got
their travel permits.
Hey, Hatchi, you sure
you want to see this guy?
Maybe we should all sit down
and weigh our options first!
-Excuse me!
-[BOTH] Aah!
Pardon me,
could you introduce us
to the person in charge, please?
[grumbles]
What is wrong with you?
Is there a reason
you're holding me so close?
Sorry, we don't let him out
in public very often,
it's our fault!
We'll get him back
to his safe space right away!
You've got issues, bro.
That wasn't funny!
It was!
We were stopped by eggs!
They were giving us dirty looks,
and you guys
were terrified of them!
Of eggs!
Of giant angry eggs!
Oh ha-ha-ha!
Well, if we hadn't been
sane enough
to drag you out of there,
they would've sucked our souls,
so you're welcome!
"Help! I'm being sucked
by an egg!"
[IKKU]
This guy's seriously twisted.
[BARTENDER]
Here you go. Enjoy.
Uh, smells like fruity coffee.
It's peach hot spring coffee.
Haccone's local delicacy.
I'm no expert, but I'm
pretty sure that's hot pink.
Oh, look at that,
four-point-seven stars
on Trip Sunvisor.
And someone posted that
it tastes amazing
with peach
hot spring sticky buns!
Let's get some!
I'm gonna kill you.
You won't look up
something as crucial
as whether or not
we need transit permits.
But show you
a neon cup of coffee
and you'll make damn sure
we know what to eat with it.
Wow! It tastes just like
regular coffee!
-Wow!
-[ROBBY grumbles]
By all means, take your time.
Have one for me, too.
Not like we've got
somewhere to be.
We don't need that sticky bun
money for important things
like checkpoint fees
and hyper-road tolls!
You're right, Ikku, you should
probably head back to Earth
and get those transit passes
handled for us
so we can all save
some time and money.
We'll make sure to keep
the hot springs hot for you
-until you come back.
-Huh?
Oh. Never mind.
Robots can't go
swimming anyway.
How dare.
Whoa! I spy
with my hungry eye
three alien hotties
ready for a hot bath!
And being the gentleman
that I am
I'm not gonna make them take
that dip alone, you know?
Counting on you, Ikku!
Hello there, ladies!
You must be tired
from runnin' around...
He's got rabies!
Damn it, Robby, you idiot!
How can you sip tea
at a time like this?
It's coffee.
Watch the bartender.
I don't trust him.
Huh?
Quiet.
He's pretending to do
the dishes, but...
he's actually trying
to eavesdrop.
Oh!
I bet he knows
the underworld boss.
Hmm.
Does he think he can just
walk up to anyone here
and demand information,
and with that haircut?
Thanks, you've been
a great help!
No problem!
Did you get all the answers?
I did.
Come on, let's go.
[camera shutter clicks]
[ROBBY]
Man, my feet are dying
from all that walking,
how about you?
A hot spring sounds pretty dope
right now, doesn't it?
-Huh?
-Uh, what do you guys wanna do?
We should try that
hot spring shaved ice!
I heard it's completely organic,
made with local ice!
Sounds good!
I wanna try vortex blue!
We can all go do
the pirate ship ride after that!
[overlapping conversation}
[sighs]
I mean, if it's right there.
I guess we can check out
the pirate ship.
Seems I was right.
The bartender back there
really does know
the underworld boss.
What?
His daughter was
one of the victims.
Apparently, she works
the ticket counter out here now.
What the crap, man?
Why would anyone just hand you
that information?
[humming]
La la la la la.
I've known Robby long enough
to tell the difference
between carefree
and whatever this is.
Hello. Excuse me.
I have a few questions
if you don't mind?
[ROBBY] Well! Look what
the cat threw up!
-[HATCHI] Uh?
-Robby!
Oh, hey, is that boy over there
one of your friends?
I think he falls more under
the category of fan than friend,
but his name's Hatchi.
You have really cute
fan-friends!
Hatchi is so hot!
Hey there, Hatchi!
Wanna take a photo with me?
-Uh... I guess.
-[camera shutter clicking]
Sure?
Look how adorable we are!
Come on, Hot-chi!
Let's go ride the pirate ship!
[HATCHI]
I really don't have time!
[GIRLS talking
over each other]
Do you think it's because they
see themselves in him, or...
Hey, wait! I wanna go!
Backstabbing, chili-bowl
hair-having bastard!
I saw them first!
What is he doing?
What are they doing?
Who picks princess Hatchi
over this?
I guess tourist girls who aren't
interested in older men?
Kid just looks better
in pictures.
[ROBBY]
They're too young and dumb
to appreciate a real man.
I mean, look at this jawline.
You know, younger women
typically date
older men for money, right?
So in that regard,
you have zero appeal.
In fact, you're in the negative.
[grunts]
It's like I came all this way
from Earth for nothing!
I hate it here!
-[KAPAKO] Excuse me, sir?
-Hmm?
I thought I heard you say
you came here from Earth?
Uh, yes. Tourist here.
What's up? You want
some of this, don't you?
I just think it's funny
that all Earth men
seem to love the hot springs.
Oh!
So you've dated
an Earthling before?
Is that why you find us
so funny and charming?
[KAPAKO]
Not exactly.
Well, you are charming,
but someone I work with
loves visiting Earth
and said hot springs
are pretty popular out there.
Yeah, we've got
some pretty good ones!
Why don't I tell you
more about them
in one of those
open-air baths?
[gasps]
I was thinking
of stopping by there
on my way home from work!
-I'm in!
-All right!
I'm gonna show you
what this older man can do!
Robby! Get back here!
[screams]
Why is everyone leaving me
for girls and pirate ships?
Jerks! This sucks!
Come on.
All these hot springs
and no mixed bathing?
[KAPAKO]
Doesn't the water feel great?
Heck, yeah, it does!
And the view of the lake's
pretty baller too!
[KAPAKO] My benefactor's the one
who built this place,
so I'll let him know
you like it!
[groans]
Maybe you should let
the idiot know
lots of virile adults
prefer mixed bathing.
Have you checked out
the Kappappa springs yet?
Those are nice, too.
[ROBBY]
Yeah, been there, done that!
My sweet benefactor is the one
who built that facility also.
He's actually the only reason
we have hot springs
in our world.
-He brought them here.
-[ROBBY] Oh, neat!
Thanks, dude.
Way to screw over
the rest of your bros
with these lady-free hot tubs.
♪
[sighs]
I'm exhausted.
Welcome back.
I guess.
Hope you had "fun."
I didn't. Where's Robby?
Oh.
He's off gallivanting
with some harlot
from the ticket booth,
'cause all we've got is time.
We've been looking
for you everywhere!
Come to the hot springs with us!
I can't.
I feel sick.
-You'll get over it!
-Let's go!
-[GIRLS giggling]
-[HATCHI whimpering]
[HATCHI]
Ikku! Grab my leg!
Sit in your mess!
Don't you dare cry to me!
You and Robby made my life hell
for these hot springs!
[KAPAKO]
I think I'm spent.
I'm gonna head out, Robby.
I hear ya.
I should probably
get going too, then.
No way.
What are you doing here?
Uh... Well...
[GIRL]
Wow, these baths are perfection!
[GIRLS giggling]
It's those hotties from earlier!
On second thought, I think
I may need to relax a bit more.
[grumbles]
Do you have any idea
how creepy you look right now?
Don't you dare judge me, prude.
There's a giant fence
between them and my ear,
so back off.
I can go anywhere I want to
within the boundaries
of my imagination!
[sighs]
[HATCHI] Whatever blows
your lecherous hair back.
By the way,
Ikku said you came here
with that ticket girl?
I sure did and what a waste.
None of the hot springs here
support mixed bathing.
Turns out her sugar daddy built
and owns this place
along with every other
boring hot springs facility
in this world.
Then I need to talk to her!
Where is she right now?
She was chillin'
in the women's bath
a little while ago
but had to leave.
-[HATCHI screams]
-[GIRLS scream]
What the hell is wrong with you?
I know something about
the underworld boss!
Forget that!
Way to knock down the wall!
Well, unfortunately,
I didn't see Kapako over there!
That is unfortunate.
Hey! Jerks!
Don't leave me here!
[HATCHI]
Kapako, wait!
Thank you.
You're the bartender's daughter,
right?
The one from the teahouse?
Yes.
Why do you ask?
Your father told me
what happened to you.
Involving you-know-who.
[gasps]
He said he hurt you
pretty badly
and that he left you broken
and literally empty.
"Hurt" is quite
the understatement.
I hate to ask anyone
to dig into their past,
but I need information
about him.
My friends and I are stuck.
We have to get past
the checkpoint,
but we need his help
getting our transit permits.
We're willing to do
whatever it takes.
Tell me.
Is there any way
to make him cooperate?
Any pointers?
Thanks, kid.
[KAPAKO]
Here's the thing.
He'll probably give you guys
your permits willingly.
It's just...
I've never met anyone
who's walked away
exactly as they walked in.
Is he really that dangerous?
Well, yes.
He's the most loving man
in the entire universe.
And the power
of a love so strong
can be extremely painful.
[ALL]
Huh?
If your only option
is going to meet him,
you mustn't look him
in the eye.
That's the only thing
I can think of
to help you avoid the worst.
Understood.
Just don't look at him?
♪
We want you to take us
to your boss.
Are you sure you know
what you're asking?
Absolutely! Right?
Why're you asking me?
Not like I have a choice!
Well, I'm ready and I don't have
a soul or bones to worry about,
so bring it on!
[GUARDS]
All right. Go in.
♪
Looks like he's not here.
Whew!
Over there!
I think that's him!
♪
Don't you dare get excited
and start looking into his eyes.
I know how you guys are!
Yeah, we get it, Ikku.
Obviously.
[BOSS] Is there something
I can do for you?
Uh, maybe?
I hope you're having
a good day today.
Are you? I am.
Get it together!
It's not a first date!
We need your help, sir.
We're stranded.
The only way we can get
out of here
is if you'll issue us
travel permits.
[BOSS]
Well, why didn't you say so?
All right, guys, remember not
to look him in the eye!
I'm not.
♪
Are you insane?
Cover your eyes!
♪
What the crap?
Close your eyes, Hatchi!
Great, now your eyes
are open, genius!
♪
[BOTH]
He's so cute!
He's a wombat?
That's no problem!
I'd be happy to help you
and your friends!
I hope you'll enjoy your travels
through this universe
filled with beauty and love!
Love is power!
♪
[shouting, laughing]
[ROBBY]
That guy really was dangerous!
Once you're caught in his warm
wombat web of love,
the last thing you want
is to be set free.
That soft, pink fluff
is dangerous.
I can't live without running
my fingers through it!
This is why they say
he leaves you hollow,
because he melts you
from the inside!
But, lucky for me,
you can't melt a steel heart.
But check it out!
We got these now,
so everything's gonna be gravy!
I need to see
your travel permits, please.
[ALL]
Ta-da!
[gasps] Wow!
I know that mark!
Let me see.
Special complimentary gift.
It's called
the "Anytime, Anywhere,
Fluffy Cellphone Strap of Love!"
Oh. Thanks, I think.
[excited shouting]
We're on our way to Isekandar!
See you there!
And they just walk right in?
No one's gonna stop them and ask
for their travel permits?
No, not in their case.
Did you not read about
the new permit clause?
The Space Tourism Administration
issued a notice
stating that travel permits
would no longer be required
for those heading to Isekandar.
[ALL]
Wha...
♪
[CONTROLLER over radio]
Nagaya Voyager,
you are clear to proceed.
♪
Finally!
Isekandar or bust!
Warp Speed, Mr. Ikku!
Okay.
I think that's enough for now.
♪
[ALLO]
Next time, "Qu-eel-le Surprise."