[COMMERCIAL NARRATOR 1A]
There is a world
where any dream you
dream can come true.
[COMMERCIAL NARRATOR 1A]
It's called... Isekandar.
Let's go.
[ROBBY] "If you could do
anything in the world
you wanted to do,
what would that be?"
I've given that a lot of
thought and my answer is,
"Not a damn thing."
'Scuse me!
[ROBBY]
Because whenever I do anything,
it turns out like this.
Gimmie back my bag,
you filthy bastard!
[ROBBY grunts, gasps]
[ROBBY gasping]
[ROBBY]
Damn it!
[BOTH panting]
[THIEF 1A gasps]
[ROBBY]
Move!
[THIEF 1A gasps]
[FEMALE PEDESTRIAN 1A gasps]
Yeah! Eat that cement! [gasps]
Look to your right and
you'll see some stuff!
[gasps] Hey! Don't
look in there!
[ALIEN TOURISTS chattering]
[ROBBY groans, gasps]
[ROBBY groans] Why can't my
life stop sucking so much?
Hm?
[HATCHI]
Hello, sir. Is this yours?
Gimmie that!
Oh, who's a sweet baggie-bag?
--'Kay...
--Wait a minute,
are you the one who stole
my bag in the first place
just so that you could bring
it back and freak me out?
No, I did not.
Your culprit's over there.
[ROBBY]
Oh.
[HATCHI]
Don't mention it.
Hey, hold on!
[RABBITS]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar!
Let's all go to Isenakdar! ♪
[chattering]
Heyya, Pops! My usual, for two!
For who? A girl?
Sex bots don't
gotta eat, y'know.
Oh, come on, man!
[ROBBY grunts]
Yep! Sweet!
You here to make me nuts?
What's with the change?
Sorry, this guy's
not havin' it today.
Again?
Throw it out and get
yourself a new one!
Ha! You read my mind.
That's how I feel
about my entire life!
Huh?
About to make my dreams of
doing nothin' all day come true!
Okay then, buddy,
good luck with that.
You gotta work if you
wanna eat in this world
and there's no way
to get around it.
Your order will be up soon!
[sighs]
[ROBBY] The twisted joke
here is that my family is
actually pretty wealthy.
I didn't get along with my
parents at all in my teens.
One day I was just so over it,
I ran away from home.
That's when the
job-hopping began,
and as of right now,
I guess you could say
I'm a freelance reporter.
Once, this girl I
was dating hired me
to be a beef rancher.
But then my cows got sick and
some A-hole slaughtered them.
I figured investing in
a nata de coco plant
would turn things around.
But I ended up drowning in debt
and boxes of unsold
fermented merch.
Turns out that stuff's
pretty high in fiber
and exactly what I needed to end
my struggle with constipation.
--[thud]
--[ROBBY groans]
[ROBBY] That's when I tripped
and fell down the stairs
and died.
[ROBBY]
I'm kidding!
It was an accident,
but my stupid insurance
thought I faked it
and wouldn't cover
my hospital bills!
My nurse was hot, though.
We kinda dated...
...till I found out she
was the girlfriend
of some baller gangster!
[ROBBY]
I broke up with her already!
[ROBBY] My life's like
this moody, bi-polar,
rollercoaster of misfortunes.
I've got no money,
no job, and no girl.
I swear, I'm cursed.
[ringing]
Hope you're ready to
read the best draft ever!
Unfortunately, no one is.
We've just heard our webzine
won't be published after all.
[ROBBY gasps]
[ROBBY] So when this
new thing rolled around,
I figured, what the
heck is left to lose?
This could be the key to
a life of doing nothing--
the ultimate success.
[POPS]
Order's up, Robby!
Uh--
--[ROBBY] Thank you!
--[POPS] See ya next time.
[ROBBY]
Thanks for waiting.
Pucker up.
You're about to make out with
the best fries in the world.
If Pops wasn't such a corn-hole,
I'd eat here every day.
Yeah, that's the stuff. [gasps]
Don't judge me.
You gonna eat or just sit
there being ungrateful?
Um... do you know how many
calories a fry has?
Uh--
Something else to think about.
When starchy foods are cooked
at high temperatures,
it creates a dangerous
toxin called acrylamide.
Small amounts are fine--
Blah, blah, blah.
Shut up and eat the
food I bought for you!
I'll eat what's safe.
You want safe, huh?
[HATCHI]
Pardon me?
[ROBBY laughs]
Just how many salads do you
think a place like this sells?
[chuckles] I've never been asked
anything so cryptic in my life.
You certainly have
an interesting way
of seeing things, sir.
Thank you.
Hold on! Who are you?
Um, I'm the one who
helped you, mister.
Uh--yeah, that's right.
You are. [chuckles]
But you really gotta stop
callin' me "sir" and "mister."
Then what should I call you?
Try my name, Robby Yarge.
Who are you?
No one important
enough to mention.
[ROBBY gasps]
Don't you dare try to bait me
with that hipster-emo
"I'm no one important" crap
just so I can give you some
motivational mom speech
about how you're special and
beg you to tell me your name
because of how
important you are to me
while holding you way
too close for comfort!
Sorry, I'm not fallin' for it
and I'm not gonna ask you again.
--Kita Hatchi.
--Huh?
That's my name.
Whoa! Don't turn this around!
So, there's money in
that bag, isn't there?
[ROBBY gasps]
At your age?
You still believe money has
the power to buy success?
I thought only
children were clueless
as to how the world works.
--[ROBBY] Excuse you?
--Oh, mister.
Hey! What did I just tell you
about calling me "mister,"
you stuck-up little brat?
I'm sorry, Robby Yarge,
but you've got a tiny
bit of something here.
[ROBBY gasps, groans]
[ROBBY] Don't distract me!
I'm done with this planet--
with its money and people,
and gravity is overrated!
I should've been out
a long time ago!
Oh, really?
Well, yeah. You remember
when that whatchamacallit
went to the moon 50 years ago
and made contact
for the first time?
I was gonna move up there
and help build kingdoms
and be super rich and fancy
living that sweet,
sweet moon life.
Uh, what was that thing called?
Uh... Doesn't matter.
The point is, you should
lead an honest life.
Heh. What makes you
think I don't?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You don't know about the new
enterprise I'm building.
Is it a respectable enterprise?
Yeah, in shrimp.
Shrimp?
Did I say shrimp?
I meant, "I like shrimp!"
Ugh, where's this going?
But you know what tastes even
better? Mount Fuji Burgers!
Anyway, you were being nosey
about the money
in my bag, right?
I'm gonna use it
to build my empire
so that I never
have to work again
and you're jealous, aren'tcha?
Not at all.
Come on. You gotta
live an honest life, kid.
I really couldn't care
less about being rich.
And I'm not a kid.
I'm just tired of being bored.
Uh--
All I want is to finally find
something that interests me.
You can't find anything
that interests you?
I'd like to direct your
attention toward these clouds.
"The little one just changed
shape! Oh, how interesting!"
"I wonder what's
down on the ground.
Looks like an army of ants.
Oh, my! How interesting!"
I mean, I'm not seein'
the struggle here.
It's bigger than that.
The world is so predictable
and created with this
preestablished harmony.
We know everything that's
going to happen, so...
...we're always five steps
ahead, no matter what.
Even into the future.
There's no mystery to unravel
here. Nothing to explore.
You don't have to predict
the weather, we know.
It should take about a
year to analyze a genome,
but every bit of information
we could possibly want
can be instantly accessed
with a quantum computer.
It's a privilege to wonder,
but there are no
surprises anymore.
[ROBBY]
What world are you livin' in?
Because nothing but the
unpredictable has happened to me
in this one so far.
[HATCHI]
Huh?
Should you, like,
get a job or something?
Or finish college?
I have many jobs.
And I skipped some grades
and graduated from college
a long time ago.
Bet you've been dyin'
to bring that up.
But I was bored in college, too.
They didn't teach me anything
I didn't already know.
Hey, you gotta admit,
it was pretty stupid of
you to think that college
was about anything
other than partying.
[ROBBY]
Hm?
What's with the death stare?
Nothing.
I just have a pet peeve
about unnecessary chaos.
So Mr. Brainy Pants
is also a snob.
Oh--you know, if I
were a snooty prudey
and constantly living my life
on the straight-and-narrow,
I'd probably find it
uninteresting, too.
What?
[ROBBY] If you don't get off the
beaten path and run into stuff,
then, yeah, you're always gonna
know what's coming next.
Oh, space balls!
It's almost time for me
to claim my success!
[HATCHI]
Huh?
[ROBBY] You can have the rest
of those fries, and good luck!
Hell yeah!
Now all I have to do is sit back
and watch the money pour in!
My life of blissful ease
is about to begin!
Woo-hoo!
--[applause]
--[ROBBY] Thank you!
[PATRON 1A]
Amazing!
Yeah, like, so amazing!
[ROBBY sighs]
Tell daddy what you girls want.
I'm about to be the
richest guy you know!
Then I would love to
go to that place on TV!
Huh? Isekandar?
They've been advertising
it like crazy.
It supposedly has the power to
make your dreams come true.
Oh, yeah, like miracles.
Is that so?
[COMMERCIAL NARRATOR 1A]
It's called... Isekandar.
[PATRON 1A]
There's nothing I want more
than to visit Isekandar
and find happiness.
Yeah, what she said.
[ROBBY gasps]
I almost forgot
I don't believe in
spiritual miracles
or wishing on
stars and whatnots.
Y'see, I already have everything
I need to make happiness happen
without flying off to
some random dreamland.
[ROBBY laughs]
[ringing]
Yes, hello?
I see, tomorrow? That works.
Please send me the
name and address.
[gasps]
Welcome to your dreams, ladies.
--[PATRONS giggling]
--AKA, my penthouse!
[PATRON 1A, 1B]
No way!
[ROBBY]
Oh, yes, way!
[PATRON 1A] Um, this is the
"high rise with the best view"?
[PATRON 1B]
Looks a little sketchy.
Wait! Hold your stones.
You gotta see it first.
[PATRON 1A] It's not
what you described at all.
[PATRON 1B]
Like, at all, at all.
I'm out.
Like, so out.
Hey! Wait! I've
got fruit snacks!
The hell?
[ROBBY]
Who turns down fruit snacks?
[ROBBY groans]
[IKKU]
Oh, there she is! Finally.
--[ROBBY snoring]
--Dude, your breath reeks.
--Like booze and beef. Gross.
Why would I expect
anything else?
--[doorbell ringing]
--[ROBBY snoring]
[groans] We don't want any!
Robby's asleep,
so leave a message.
Uh--it's you.
That kid from yesterday.
So we meet again.
We sure do, but why?
[HATCHI]
It's my job.
Your job?
Aw, sweet, are you delivering
the liquor I ordered earlier?
You can just set it
down by the door.
Give it back.
What's "it"?
That money.
You have to pay back
money you borrow.
What?
My boss says he insists.
What? Are you saying
you got a gig
as Yang's new personal
debt collector?
I've never met anyone in my life
who has actual debt and
probably never will again.
So I thought this
might be interesting.
What?
Honestly, I never anticipated
running into you like this.
[ROBBY gasps]
You were right. The world is
full of interesting things.
[gasps]
[RABBITS]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Isekan's a perfect place! ♪
♪ Let's all go! ♪
What the hell is going on?
My arm skin!
That doesn't hurt.
Do you remember how
I caught the criminal
who stole your bag yesterday?
Turns out my special training
actually came in handy for once.
Neat.
But you know, even though
I studied for so long,
I never learned anything new.
What are you? [groans]
So, the truth is you
borrowed all that money
from my place of employment?
That's right, I did.
Which makes me a customer,
and this is the worst
costumer service ever!
Maybe you should start
paying your interest.
[ROBBY]
Look, the investment I made
is about to start paying
off any minute now!
I've got a shrimp farm in
southeast Asia, all right?
I'll be able to pay it back
and then some if you can...
--Keep it down!
--[ringing]
See? They're calling
me already! [grunts]
Talk to me.
What the hell did you
just say? Are you serious?
I'm pretty sure I know
what that's about.
But for the record,
what did they tell you?
Some stupid tanker ship smashed
into the shrimp hatchery
I invested in and wiped
the poor little guys out.
Stupid freakin' jerks!
[HATCHI chuckles]
Oh, you think that's funny?
Well, obviously you've been had.
[IKKU] Oh, great! Is this
because of some girl again?
How many times is this now?
First the wagyu beef,
then nata de coco ,
then gambling,
then click-bait malware.
[ROBBY groans]
Come on. You're a really smart
guy until a woman shows up
and then you turn into
some arrogant douchebag
beefcake with no beef.
Look, my entire future's
been taken from me.
[HATCHI]
You can't plan a future
until you pay off
your present debt.
Told you.
I can't handle
unnecessary chaos.
--[IKKU yells]
--[ROBBY gasps]
What's your damage, bro?
Are you trying to take me
back to them or what?
That is my job.
And what are they gonna
do to me when I get there?
No idea.
All they said was that
you were gonna work it off.
So I'd say they'll either
put you on a tuna boat
or sell your kidneys.
[gasps] Please! Let me off
the hook just this once
and I'll buy you all
the fries you want--
--Poison.
--Salad, then.
--No thanks.
--Whatever you want!
A nice steak dinner, maybe?
Unless you're vegan! Sorry! Gah!
Um, uh--hey! Over there!
No one falls for that.
[ROBBY gasps]
For real! Look down!
--[IKKU] 'Sup.
--[HATCHI gasps]
Hey! Don't you dare!
[IKKU sighs]
Honestly. Uh--
Where's Hatchi?
How long does this take?
Yeah, Mr. Yang, we're gonna
go see what the hold up is.
[YANG]
I'll join you.
Let's go.
[ROBBY yelling]
[HATCHI]
Pay back your loan!
[ROBBY] I couldn't even
if I wanted to! Back off!
[HATCHI]
Give me the money!
[ROBBY]
Can't bleed a stone, man!
[HATCHI gasps]
[gasps] You did not!
[ROBBY chuckles]
[groans] Damn it!
[sighs]
--[doorbell rings]
--[gasps]
Yikes! Yang and his
whole crew are here!
What's the matter now?
Oh, nothing, Ikku!
They're just gonna
take my kidneys!
--[doorbell rings]
--[ROBBY whimpers]
Only thing I can do is
go for broke. [grunts]
Uh--huh? Robby, wait!
[doorbell rings]
He isn't answering.
What do we do now, Mr. Yang?
I guess... we'll have
to burn down the door.
[ROBBY pants, grunts]
Robby, what are you doing?
Putting the Nagaya
Voyager to use!
It's been sitting
here for decades.
You think it's gonna
start up that easily? Huh--
Ha, ha! Yeah, I do!
I'll be damned.
Nagaya Voyager, engage!
[engine revving]
[engine dies]
Or not.
Hey, I tried to warn ya.
[ALLO grunts] If I fire this,
it'll blow the whole thing down.
Hmm. That's fine. Do it.
[groaning]
Stop smacking it around
like it's prom night.
Ikku! You want them to
take my kidneys, don't you?
Please start. Please, damn it!
Uh?
--[YANG] What the--
--[ALLO, GRAS gasp]
Is that a flying penthouse?
And it's about to take off!
No! Why?
[ALL gasping]
Go!
[ALL gasp]
Damn you, Robby!
Hell yeah! I wasted those
psycho punk bastards!
I think this calls for a
celebratory toast, don't you?
Why don't you enter
a destination
before you drunkenly
get us lost, idiot?
When you're right, you're right.
I want to get as far
away from those jerks
as we possibly can first.
[sighs] You think
Galactic Immigration's
gonna let you through?
What are you gonna tell them
when they ask you why you
left the Earth's system?
I haven't thought
about that yet.
[IKKU] Well you better
not tell them you're runnin'
from a debt collector,
'cause hoo!
Go to Isekandar! Duh!
Ise-what now?
You know, those ads they
keep playing everywhere
about how we should all
see it once in our lives.
They promised that
if we go there,
evil will be destroyed and
happiness will prevail!
D'you hear yourself?
Travel companies only pay
for that kind of airplay
when their place sucks so bad
they're desperate to have
any kind of customers.
I'm not asking you
to move there,
but they do have Akafucrysals,
which are supposed to
have some cool powers.
You butt-munch! They're
just tryna make money!
[HATCHI] I'd love to buy an
Akafucrystal from Isekandar!
That's right! No way.
Good to see you again,
Robby Yarge.
[ROBBY] What the crap
are you doin' here, kid?
You're asking me that
after you shoved me in
your airlock, mister?
It wasn't an easy escape.
[groans] Yeah, and neither
are you, turns out.
Good news!
I've decided want
to go to Isekandar!
It's like you said before.
I have to stop driving
straight and hit some curves!
I said that?
Pardon me.
Will this ship make
it to Isekandar?
I mean, there's no reason
why it couldn't.
The best part is I have no idea
what's going to happen next!
It's all so unpredictable!
And I'm sharing my
first time with you!
You gotta go before I
throw up on my floor.
I guess I'll just have to
tell Yang how to find you.
You know what, kid?
I'm not fallin' for
your weak-ass threats,
so why don't you show yourself
out through the hatch, Hatchi.
Ikku, go open the hatch.
Actually, it may still be open.
That's the way I came in.
Ha?
--[explosion]
--[BOTH gasp]
Whoa.
[ROBBY] That's gotta be the
tackiest, trashiest looking ship
I've ever seen!
--Mr. Yang.
--[ROBBY gasps]
He's very insistent on
getting what he wants.
He followed me all the
way out into space?
Hey! Second wave comin' in!
[ALL gasp]
[YANG]
Why are we going so slow?
Don't worry about
speed! Catch Robby!
[ALLO, GRAS]
Yes, Mr. Yang!
They're catching up!
Do something, Ikku!
--Will you shut up?
--[HATCHI, ROBBY gasp]
[BOTH yell, groan]
That hurt!
[HATCHI laughs]
Hey! What are you laughing at?
Why don't you tell us
what to do next,
Mr. "I'm so bored with
knowing everything."
There's nothing predictable
happening at all right now.
I don't know what's coming
next, and it's awesome!
[laughs]
Glad you find it hysterical,
but if they catch us,
we can't go to Isekandar.
Excuse me? We can't have that!
I regret nothing!
Blessed be our tractor beam!
That's what I'm screamin'
about. Let's reel 'em in!
How sweet it is to
call you mine, Robby.
Welcome.
[BOTH gasping]
[HATCHI]
Weightless?
What is goin' on in here?
[HATCHI]
Are those space fighters?
[ROBBY]
Looks like it.
You know you could've mentioned
that you had these earlier.
Like I'm hiding them from you!
I didn't know they
were down here!
Guess we both have
to deal with it now.
What do you mean by that?
[ROBBY] We're gonna break off
the tractor beam with these!
But that would be...
...unforeseen and quite
interesting. [grunts]
[ROBBY] Tell me you can
pilot these things.
Sure. I've got a hobby
fighter's license.
Well I can fly a commuter,
so it shouldn't be too hard.
Maybe.
Almost there. Won't be long now.
What? No!
Aw, yeah!
Hatchi, swing around from
the right, would ya?
Would you mind not giving
me orders ever, please?
I do what I want.
How'd they even
get those things?
Go after them!
Roger that.
Whoa! They're
shooting at us now?
Uh, are there any
weapons in here?
I dunno, but my
console's lighting up!
Huh? What's this?
Yeah, at this point,
we just gotta do it.
Right!
[ROBBY grunts]
[music playing]
The hell? Where's that
music coming from?
[music continues]
I hear it, too.
There appear to be
speakers in here.
I think mine's flying
on its own now!
It's completely automatic?
What in the world?
Are they out of their minds?
Hey.
Okay...?
Hizakuriger!
They just merged with
each other! But why?
Did we... ya know?
Guess so.
But why did it
make me the bottom?!
[ROBBY] Next time,
"Truth Found From an Octopus."