[KANGAROOS]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar ♪
♪ Let's all go
to Isekandar ♪
[IKKU] We are now entering
the thirty-sixth planet
on the Galaxy Highway,
Akka Sakka!
-That's it's actual name?
-Don't be so rude.
It's a world filled
with dreams and adventure,
love and hope,
joy and more joy.
What the hell? Sounds like
we're going to Candy Mountain.
Let's see.
Regular Day Pass,
Reserved Tickets, Annual Pass,
Premium Tickets.
All this to visit a planet?
Guess no one
actually lives here.
Or they can't afford
to leave and come back.
Whoa! There's a five-hour wait
for a day pass?
Yeah, that's not
what I wanna do.
I've only got one attention
span, and it'll go on strike.
I don't do lines.
It's fine.
I know another way.
[BOTH]
Another way?
Right over here.
[IKKU/ROBBY]
Through the back door?
[trills]
[beeps]
[COMPUTER]
You are confirmed.
Please enter.
We're in. Great. Let's go.
[clears throat] Who'd you bribe?
Aren't we out of money?
The listing said that
as long as you have
over ten thousand
social media followers,
you can use the rear entry
whenever you want
for any occasion.
Oh. That many people wanna look
at your lunch pics?
I set up the account
a long time ago.
I guess it's picked up
some followers.
Ten thousand people think
you're that interesting?
I'm here, so I guess they must.
Yeah, right. Someone's been
shopping for likes.
-Kid's delusional.
-What are you saying?
Just that we better get going,
Mr. Bot Farm Influencer!
[HATCHI]
Bot Farm?
No, I said
Hot Charm Influencer!
♪
Oh, I hate this.
Uh...
[ALL]
Huh... Huh?
Good afternoon,
gentlemen callers!
And welcome to Akka Sakka,
the land of love,
dreams, and adventure!
Your amusement is our passion!
[BOTH] We hope
to help your day bloom
with pure joy and entertainment!
-Welcome!
-[BOTH] What is happening.
[TROUPE] ♪ Welcome, my friends,
welcome, my friends ♪
♪ To dreams, adventure,
hope, and romance ♪
♪ To entertainment of the... ♪
[ROBBY] Am I dehydrated or did
they all just burst into song?
[IKKU] Those are definitely
high-kicks.
Oh, that's right!
It says that this is
the "Love and Hope
Fantasy Musical Area."
-I absolutely love it here!
-No accounting for taste.
[grumbling]
[chuckles awkwardly]
What the hell?
♪ Hush, don't be shy,
you've just gotten here ♪
♪ Let us be your helpful guide
to this magical world of ours ♪
♪ Dreaming is the greatest thing
that you can do for yourself ♪
♪
Screw all of this.
I don't have time
for their jazz hands.
[GIRL 1]
♪ Now, you join in, too! ♪
Look, it's the door
of hopes and dreams!
♪ Let's see what's inside ♪
♪ Your fantasy's waiting
for you ♪
♪ Your wishes are sure
to come true ♪
Hey! Watch your feet!
Hatchi, help me!
♪ To dreams,
adventure, to love...♪
Kill me.
♪ There's so much here
so come on ♪
♪ It's nothing but fun ♪
They got him.
[HATCHI] ♪ Why aren't you
dancing with us? ♪
♪ Can't you see
we've just begun? ♪
♪ It's an amusing show ♪
[TROUPE]
♪ Amusing show ♪
[HATCHI]
[TROUPE]
♪ Amusing show ♪
Damn it. They're just going
to keep repeating
that same line
until we sing with them.
Absolutely not! I'm outta here!
[grunts]
[HATCHI]
♪ Amusing show ♪
-[TROUPE] ♪ Amusing show ♪
-[HATCHI] ♪ Amusing show ♪
-[ROBBY/IKKU screaming]
-[singing continues]
-[ROBBY] Damn it!
-[BOTH groan]
[ALL]
♪ Amusing show ♪
[BOTH]
[ALL TOGETHER]
♪ Amusing show ♪
Okay, where to next?
There are so many places
to explore!
[ROBBY whispering]
Shh. Quiet time.
[IKKU]
We're gonna need a minute.
Hmm?
♪
Is this entire freakin' planet
one nauseating amusement park?
I think that's what
they're going for.
Each area has its own theme.
Right now, we're in the "Fairy
Tale Flower Lovely Play Area."
Fairy what?
Can we leave?
They're obviously trying
to weed out anyone
who doesn't want to wear
a dance belt
with all this
"lovely flower fairy-song" crap.
[IKKU] They can have as much
flower fluff as they want
as long as I don't have
to sing about it!
I hate singing!
♪
[IKKU]
Hmm?
Oh. That's right!
It's opposite day!
Fooled you, didn't I?
[BOTH laughing awkwardly]
This is the stuff
nightmares are made of.
Yeah, it is. It's getting weird.
Oh, complaining
is forbidden here.
As in any kind of abusive
language or negativity,
so you might want
to lock that up.
Me? Abusive?
I mean, yeah, kinda.
You know how you are.
The constant insults
and disrespecting
my masculinity
are against the law.
Huh? Are they gonna kill me
for hurting your feelings?
Actually, it doesn't say
what the punishment would be.
But I did notice,
the garbage tends to disappear.
Hmm. Oh, yeah.
Fun facts from Hatchi.
[GIRL]
Maybe it's over this way.
[BOY]
Yeah, I think you're right.
-[IKKU] So fast!
-I think I get it now.
Get what?
How big a tool you are?
They dispose of garbage
right away.
Things and people.
Don't make me
spell it out for you.
-[laughing]
-[ROBBY] Uh...
Oh, now this looks fun.
Doesn't look too far.
Yeah, it's right over here!
Come on!
-[laughing]
-What the...
Can't stand these mood swings.
[sighs] This is exactly
how I imagine Hell to be.
Singing flowers,
no negative comments,
and forced fun.
I don't deserve this.
Uh?
[GIRLS grumbling]
[IKKU whimpers]
No! What do you want? Stay away!
♪ Welcome, my friends,
welcome, my friends ♪
♪ To dreams, adventure,
hope, and romance ♪
Stop singing at me!
I can't take it anymore!
♪ The purest, righteousness... ♪
I'm not joking! I'm allergic
to joy and harmonizing!
♪ Amusing show ♪
♪ Amusing
show ♪
[IKKU screams, groans]
[singing continues]
Fine! You win! I'll have
frikkin' fun, all right?
Please stop singing!
♪
We're grown-ass adults
on a flower ride.
[HATCHI]
Remember your tone, Robby.
I'm sitting in a giant flower
like some broken down honeybee
in the same spot
where teenagers come to get
all handsy with each other,
and you want me
to giggle about it?
-Robby. Stop.
-What? What'd I do?
I'm just sayin'
I get motion sick easily.
[IKKU] If you value your life,
you will start expressing
your love for this
horribly tender moment.
[gasps] Oh, duh. Of course.
I love sitting here.
Takin' in all this nature
in the land of fairy tales
and flower dreams, you know?
[TROUPE] All right!
Hope you enjoy the ride!
-[buzzer sounding]
-Have fun!
-[ROBBY/IKKU] Whoa!
-[HATCHI laughing]
-[IKKU] Damn it, Robby!
-[HATCHI] This is so much fun!
[ROBBY] My stomach
just jumped into my throat!
I hope your idea of fun includes
getting splashed in the face
with some pizza
and beer chunks!
[screaming
and laughing continue]
[BOTH gasp]
[ANNOUNCER] Welcome aboard
the Lovely Flower Treasure Box!
Never forget the real treasure
is in your heart!
It's time for you to find...
[ROBBY]
Why are we so high up here?
Ikku, do something!
[IKKU] This is not my fault!
Put us down!
As you wish.
[BOTH screaming]
[HATCHI laughing]
-[ROBBY] What the crap?
-[IKKU whimpering]
-[ROBBY/IKKU screaming]
-[HATCHI laughing] We're flying!
[ROBBY/IKKU]
We're barfing!
[HATCHI]
Best day ever!
Come on, guys!
Let's see that lovely smile!
[ROBBY/IKKU groan]
[shutter clicks]
So cute! I can't handle it!
Come on!
Let's see what's over there!
I need to sit very still
and let my brain
settle back into place.
But if we don't go now,
we'll miss the start
of the Akka Sakka
Lovely Fantastic
Fairy Tale Dream Parade!
I doubt it's the last chance
we'll ever have
to see a parade here.
You go ahead.
-I'm there in spirit.
-Don't be silly.
We'll claim spots early
so we'll have the best seats.
But let's finish riding
the rest of the rides first.
[BOTH]
We're already finished!
[ROBBY] Wait, claim a spot
and stay there?
Mm-hmm. I've just never been
to any place like this before.
I don't want to miss a minute!
Come on, boys! Let's go!
[IKKU] I swear he only skips
with his arms flailing like that
to piss me off.
Can't believe this is
his first time
to an amusement park.
It suits him well.
Because he wasted
half of his life in school.
Come on, guys! We gotta hurry!
It's like he's a giant toddler.
[laughing]
[ROBBY] Get up, Ikku.
You're suffering with me.
We're coming, quit waving.
[sighs]
This is the worst...
-[GIRLS grumbling]
-...time to be upset!
-I love a parade!
-[GIRLS gasp]
[ALLO]
It's bad news, Mr. Yang.
[GRAS] There's a 500 minute wait
for a day pass!
[YANG]
How many hours is that?
Let's see, one hour
is 60 minutes,
so two hours would be 120
add another 60 to that
then it would be--
Shut up! It's eight hours
and twenty minutes, you idiots!
[ALLO/GRAS] No one does
math faster than Mr. Yang!
I've got money!
Waiting is for the poor!
-Let's go!
-Hear, hear!
-Mr. Yang for life!
-[GRAS] He's the man!
♪
There's still, like, two hours
before this parade thing
begins, right?
Why's it so crowded already?
They wanted to get
the best seats possible,
obviously.
Hey, Ikku, what's wrong?
You okay?
You're too quiet.
It's weird.
I can't say anything
right now, Robby.
Any attempt I make
to be tactful
will be overridden
by my roast program
thanks to that gaudy
flower-shaped man-purse
slung across Hatchi's shoulder.
[muffled grunting]
[HATCHI]
You mean this?
This is called the Lovely Flower
Dream Treasure Caramel Box.
It's actually filled with
strawberry caramel popcorn.
And when it's gone,
I can fill up the same box
with any flavor.
-Wow. That sounds neat.
-Huh?
-Must be swell being you.
-Hmm.
[HATCHI]
Guess I ate it all.
-I'm going to get more.
-Great!
We'll be waiting
right here for you, lovely.
[chuckles] Thanks for saving
my place in line, lovely!
Did you know that
"Lovely Star Night"
only happens once a year
at this time?
I'm so excited
to see them crown
the Lovely King
and Queen tonight.
Yes, me too. And guess who
the Lovely King and Queen
are gonna be this year?
You and I will be ringing
that lovely bell!
Wow! That'll be
fantastically lovely!
[IKKU]
What's Lovely Star Night?
I am annoyed.
There's nothing but couples
floating around here.
Of course! That's because
it's Lovely Star Night tonight,
and it only happens once a year!
[YANG]
What does that mean?
[GRAS] I'm surprised
you've never heard of it!
It's a beautiful
and miraculous phenomenon!
The planetoids near Akka Sakka
will overlap
and their light will shine
through in the shape of a heart!
[ALLO] Legend says that
when the Lovely King
and Queen are chosen
on this night,
they will ring
the Lovely Bell together
in the Fairy Tale
Lovely Fantasy Castle
and be bound together forever!
What an excellent solution.
[chuckles] Robby, sounds like
tonight's the night.
We've got some
big bells to ring.
I thought I'd try a chocolate
caramel flavor this time!
What the...
Guys?
Ikku, can you hear me?
Robby, where are you?
[panting]
[HATCHI] Not funny, guys.
Where'd you go?
♪
[ALL laughing]
[HATCHI]
I love this planet!
♪
[GIRL] Hello, Lovely!
Are you all right?
♪
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention, ladies and gentlemen,
will Robby Yarge please report
to the missing
children's department?
You hear that.
You're being paged.
Huh? Why?
[ANNOUNCER]
He has a rounded haircut
and is wearing a rose-shaped
popcorn box across his body.
He says the new flavor
is chocolate.
-He's not my son!
-[IKKU] He's not your son!
Mr. Yang!
I think I just heard
Robby being paged!
You absolutely did,
'cause I heard it, too!
And, since I'm standing
right next to you,
guess what that means?
Find out where the missing
children's center is now!
So, uh, are you runnin' away?
Why can't you tell them
what your name is
-or where you came from?
-Just can't.
Fine, loser, don't tell me.
If being lost
makes someone a loser,
then I guess
that makes two of us.
I'm not lost.
I wanna be here.
That's why I'm not giving
my info out.
Exactly where I'm sitting
is my new address!
I'm pretty sure my BGs
are panicking right about now.
-BGs?
-That's right.
My mom and dad
are always busy working,
so they hired some bodyguards
to hang out with me
and make sure I'm safe.
So, as you've probably guessed,
my family's pretty rich,
and I'm sick and tired
of adults creeping around
trying to tell me what to do.
Can you blame me for needing
a breather once in a while?
♪
Which one did you get
separated from?
Was it your mom? Or dad?
Neither. I was never close
to my parents.
They didn't like
spending time with me,
so I never got to do much.
But then, I went exploring
all on my own
and discovered more than
they could ever show me.
Uh...
[ROBBY] Hey, Hatchi-Hot-Pants,
you in here?
Dude, Why're you paging me?
And telling everyone
I'm your frikkin' dad?
Not cool, okay?
Quit makin' my life hell.
Hella, awesome!
You little poodle!
What took you so long
to get here?
[ROBBY]
Huh?
Quit trying to do
all this by yourself.
Go outside
and make some friends.
You'll see.
Life will become more enjoyable.
♪
Damn. Least you could do
is say thank you
after I came all the way here
to bust you out of baby jail.
Find friends.
[grunts]
Hey, Hatchi.
You had us worried sick,
li'l guy. Try not to wander off.
[groans]
I wasn't wandering off anywhere.
I was tired and needed
to rest for a bit.
That place just happened
to be there.
-Punkin needed a nap? Huh?
-[CROWD cheering]
It's about lovely damn time!
He means we've had a lovely time
just dreaming about this moment!
Well done. Seems you two
are finding it easier
to fit in here.
Not really.
But seeing how much fun
you were having here
did something to me.
I guess it's okay
to still play like a kid
every once in a while.
And maybe,
maybe being forced to say
all those froofy things
and avoid calling you a wuss
with twiggy biceps
changed my brain shape?
Yeah! Me too.
Except for the part
about having a brain.
You ready to watch
this epic parade?
-I sure am!
-Mm-hmm.
[YANG] Greetings!
I am here to collect Robby!
He was paged just a moment ago.
He would have been searching
for a tall, lanky teenage boy
with an unfortunate
monochromatic aesthetic.
-Seen him?
-Well, yeah,
but they already left.
What?
Lovely as hell!
Fantastic as hell!
-Fairy frikkin' tale all day!
-Aw, yeah.
-[YANG] Lovely!
-[TROUPE] Lovely!
-[YANG] Fantastic!
-[TROUPE] Fantastic!
-[YANG] Dreaming!
-[TROUPE] Dreaming!
-YANG] Fairy tale!
-[ALL] Fairy tale!
-[YANG] Dreaming!
-[TROUPE] Dreaming!
-[YANG] Fairy tale!
-[ALL] Fairy tale!
-Lovely! Lovely!
-[GRAS] Lovely!
-Fantastic!
-[ALL] Fantastic?
Holy crap, it's Yang!
Let's go! We gotta hurry!
Can we make it to the spaceship?
-[IKKU] Uh...
-Wait,
we're running straight
in Yang's direction!
I'll go get the Nagaya Voyager
ready to launch!
You go find a place
where I can pick you up!
Right! Thank you, Ikku!
Let's go! Don't get lost!
[ROBBY] You talking to me,
Baby Jail?
[ALLO]
There they go, Mr. Yang!
-[GRAS] It's Robby!
-[YANG] After him!
[TROUPE cheering]
-[YANG] Lovely! Fantastic!
-[TROUPE] Lovely! Fantastic!
-[YANG] Dreaming! Fairy tale!
-[TROUPE] Dreaming! Fairy tale!
-[YANG] Dreaming!
-[TROUPE] Dreaming!
[ROBBY] We gotta get to
the highest floor in the castle!
[HATCHI]
Got it!
[ALLO] Mr. Yang!
They're running up the stairs!
[GRAS]
Our float's kind of in the way.
[YANG] Which is why we get
off of it, you fool!
-Mr. Yang!
-[GRAS gasps]
Robby's running straight
to the Lovely Bell,
-right where you want him!
-I know that!
It's perfect!
[panting]
I'll catch Robby, and then
we'll ring the bell together!
Two birds, one stone,
two wins for one.
Something. Victory!
Get him, Mr. Yang!
Give that bell a good tug!
It's the moment we've
all been looking forward to!
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
look up into the night sky,
if you will!
The miraculous phenomenon
that we only get to experience
once a year
is about to begin.
[cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] And now for
our most anticipated tradition,
the Akka Sakka Lovely King and
Lovely Queen have been chosen!
[cheering]
Only one can ring
that bell with Robby.
-And that's me!
-[BOTH panting]
[ANNOUNCER]
Are you ready to find out...
-Wait for me, Robby!
-[ROBBY grunts]
[ANNOUNCER]
This year's couple
-who will ring the Lovely Bell.
-Gotcha!
-Are you okay?
-I am now.
[ANNOUNCER]
The Lovely King
and the Lovely Queen are...
Never mind! Not okay!
[HATCHI screams]
[bell tolling]
[cheering]
What?
This was my moment,
and you stole it!
He was supposed to ring
that bell with me!
You'll pay!
♪
[GIRL 1]
♪ The both of you are bound ♪
♪ By red strings of fate ♪
[GIRL 2]
♪ The both of you are bound ♪
♪ And now have obtained ♪
[BOTH]
♪ An everlasting love ♪
[TROUPE]
[fireworks exploding]
[IKKU] When you're done
yankin' that ding-dong,
I'll be ready to go!
Ikku!
Robby! Wait for me!
♪
[BOY] Um, hi.
You dropped this.
♪
Thank you so much.
It's so awesome
that you like Isakangaroos!
So do I!
[BOTH laugh]
Why?
Please tell me why!
[crying]
-[BOTH] Mr. Yang?
-[YANG continues crying]
♪ Don't worry, it's okay ♪
♪ If you believe in fairytales ♪
[GIRL 2] ♪ As long as you keep
following your heart ♪
[BOTH] ♪ May all your dreams
come true ♪
[TROUPE] ♪ May all your dreams
My dream will come true...
someday.
I just have to believe
and never give up!
[ROBBY] That planet sucked!
What was that?
Not sure,
but it felt like a beating.
I mean...
Wait! I can say that now!
That planet was a candy-coated,
caramel popcorn-crusted
nightmare.
Robby smells like old cheese!
Freedom of offensive speech!
I actually liked being
in that world, a lot.
Hey, do you know
what all that drama with Yang
-in the castle was about?
-Tell us, Hatchi.
You looked it up
on Trip Sunvisor, didn't you?
What happens in Akka Sakka
if you ring
the Lovely Bell together
on the annual Lovely Star Night?
Um. It's been a while
since I've read that.
Did it get weird?
[IKKU] Next time, "Heads,
I'm Tin, Tails, You Lose."