[ROBBY]
It was the year 1969,
and mankind was about
to take one giant leap.
[CAPTAIN]
Houston this is Apollo 11.
We are entering our lunar orbit.
[CONTROLLER over radio]
Houston to 11.
Roger that.
Whoa! Did you see that?
It's official now.
I am the first man
to land on the moon!
[ROBBY]
It was July eighteenth,
and a lone Japanese astronaut
with wild hair
and a fist full of dreams
made it all happen.
He became the first man to walk
on the surface of the moon
and plant their flag.
However,
that wasn't the only "first"
he had that day.
[ALIEN groaning]
Are you okay?
What's the matter?
Chronic cramps are killing me.
[groans]
Those suck.
[ROBBY] In that moment,
an alien felt the touch of a man
for the very first time.
Galaxy Century triple zero one.
A new era had begun.
Consensual contact between
two intergalactic beings
changed both their worlds
for good.
[KANGAROOS]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go
to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
[ROBBY]
There it is,
the industrial planet
of Yokkamarche.
How weird. It's not known
for anything.
Great! Then we won't miss
anything by not stopping here!
'Scuse you?
We just got our butts beat
in battle!
We're gonna need to stop
for repairs.
Both Hizakuriger and this ship
were built on that planet
and we might need parts.
You makin' stuff up?
How can you be certain
about that?
Because I was made
by the same manufacturer!
And I can read!
Right there!
"Made in Yokkamarche!"
[HATCHI] That's an awful lot
of cargo ships!
[ROBBY] They bring in the bits
and pieces to be processed,
then when it's all done,
the ships carry away
-the finished product.
-[IKKU] Cool.
Looks like Armeni's
over this way.
[ROBBY]
What's an Armeni?
[IKKU] It's the name
that's on the plates
of both our spacecrafts
because he made them!
[ROBBY/HATCHI]
Oh!
Don't cry for me, Yokkamarche!
The truth is I never left thee!
[laughs]
Uh...
How cute!
I never knew
how homesick you were!
I won't judge you if you cry!
Shut it!
Just trying to lure him out
with a little hype.
It doesn't look like
there's anyone's here to excite.
[HATCHI]
Hello?
Anyone alive in here?
-[horn honking]
-[ALL] Hmm?
Hey! Didn't mean to keep
you guys waiting!
This place is completely
automated
so we don't get a whole lot
of humans out here!
Luci!
No way, is that you?
And the Nagaya Voyager!
Those were the days!
Oh, sorry!
You look like a friend of mine.
Luci was my dad's name
if that helps?
Right! Of course,
you would be Luci's son!
I'm Armeni, nice to meet you.
And you're the one who built
the Hizakuriger
and this little
red rocket ship?
Impressive, huh?
Big genius in a tiny body.
Yeah, wow, you're really
something else.
There's just one thing.
[ARMENI screams]
What did you do?
[ROBBY]
Kicked some ass.
This is just a full-sized model
in the shape of Hizakuriger!
I didn't build it for fighting!
It's for
decorative purposes only!
Oh, we, uh, figured that out.
Come on.
Yeah, that's pretty bad.
But if I just replace some of
the parts, it should be fine.
So, What did you bring me?
Hmm? Dude,
I don't have any money.
Well, good for you!
Didn't Luci tell you
how this works?
My family likes to pretend
I don't exist,
so he didn't tell me jack.
What I want more than anything
is to collect memorabilia
from classic Earth anime!
Scene sketches,
actor's scripts, whatever!
And anything from Hizakuriger
is a major bonus!
Why would aliens want
to watch any shows
that were produced on Earth?
Especially those old ones.
They're called classics and
they're the best ones ever made!
We didn't have access
to these treasures
when they were airing
exclusively on Earth.
It was only when they started
broadcasting shows
throughout the galaxy
that our eyes were opened
and our lives
changed forever.
Or rather, the collecting
started taking over our lives.
Basically, we just
found out my dad
was enabling a bunch of weebs.
He's a good man.
Especially
considering Hizakuriger
was perceived
as cursed on Earth.
What's that mean?
I'm not exactly fluent in "nerd"
but something about curses
and old anime.
This is no exaggeration.
Anything that could possibly
go wrong
during the production
of a show,
went above and beyond wrong
during Hizakuriger's run.
And once the show aired
for the first time,
that bad luck continued
to follow them.
No one can find
the completed series
because the episode
has been completely lost.
So all we can do now
is dispute its content!
I have absolutely no idea
what this nerd is saying.
-Me neither.
-Screw that!
They think it's okay
to keep feeding us the reruns?
We have been working tirelessly
to fight back
and find that twelfth episode
to fill our collector shelves.
But that's impossible
because even the master film
has been destroyed!
That show was made
even before VHS was invented!
-What does "VHS" mean?
-Ah!
I once made a pilgrimage
to Earth,
known as Hizakuriger's
holy land,
and that's where I met
and got to know your father.
By the grace
of some unknown entity,
he had several rare
Hizakuriger items
and decided to donate them
to my archive.
The most coveted pieces I have
are several original cels
from the transforming
and combining scene!
Of course the only
logical thing to do
was give him all my money
and the Nagaya Voyager.
I even threw in an actual-size
Hizakuriger I had completed.
[ROBBY] Okay.
I always wondered
how my family
got so rich all of a sudden!
Wait a sec.
Where did your father get all
that stuff in the first place?
Don't I wish I knew!
I have an idea!
My parents used to use the
Nagaya V as their storage unit!
Bet I could find you
something in there!
Only thing I saw
that smelled nerdy.
Hot cakes! Tenka!
These are rare cels
of the main character!
You can even see the tracing
indentions right there!
Cool, so will you do
the repairs now?
Hell yeah!
Amazing find, man.
This was the director Yarge's
first show before Hizakuriger!
The director's name's Yarge?
What? You've never heard
of Yuma Yarge?
Best director ever?
I've heard of Yuma Yarge because
it's my grandfather's name,
but that's it.
Hold on.
Are you telling me
you're the director's grandson?
I didn't say that.
But it would explain
how my dad had
the keys to otaku land.
So my grandpa directed anime
back in his day.
He passed away when I was
five years old,
so I don't have
many memories of him, but...
I kinda remember him hugging me,
so I know he loved me, at least.
Your father never told you
stories about him growing up?
No! He completely concealed
his entire identity
and then sold his belongings
after he died!
What kinda dad does that?
Like father, like son,
am I right?
[HATCHI] The highly automated
factories all over Yokkamarche
have made its people
extremely wealthy.
And their advanced
healthcare services
ensure much longer lifespans.
[ROBBY] Meaning they've got
way too much time and money
living in this world
so they spend their entire lives
dickin' around
and sport hobby-ing.
[HATCHI]
They've got anime shops
in a few different languages
out here!
[ROBBY] Oh, look,
they’re showing
"Samurai Giant: The Movie"
and that Adventurer one
with what's-his-name.
All this anime that was made
before I was born
is being pumped out
like it's the latest donut
Yeah, can't say I relate
to any of this.
Okay, that's enough.
A Hizakuriger specialty shop?
[HATCHI] Figurines, cups,
stickers, and t-shirts.
Oh! They even have
Hizakuriger-shaped food!
No wonder it says this planet
has no specializations.
Hey, welcome back!
Did you kids have fun?
Those cels you found
are fantastic!
I can't get over it!
[chuckles]
In fact, that was worth
way more than just repairs.
I'm also going to upgrade
your Super Hizakuri Beam.
How long will that take?
We gotta jet.
Places to go, huh?
Not to worry, my machine skills
aren't famous for nothing!
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
The Hizakuriger repair sequence
is about to begin.
Wow! That's so neat!
-Can I watch?
-Be my guest!
[HATCHI laughing]
It really is hollow inside!
Gonna be a minute
before this thing is ready.
Would you mind
coming somewhere with me?
Don't touch me.
I want to show you
the Hizakuriger Archive.
And there are some people
I want you to meet.
Wow!
So amazing!
[ALLO] Yokkamarche is
definitely serving
some "industrial planet
realness."
I'm coming to get you,
Robby boy.
[ALLO]
"Demon Haircut Afropunch."
[GRAS] "Mini Magical
Simian Monkeys"
[ALLO] Something about
a Guardian of Space.
[GRAS]
"Annie Get Your Sho-Gun"
[ALLO]
"Show Joe Who's the Boss."
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
The shops of Yokkamarche--
What fresh hell is this?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
...produced on Earth.
No item will be refused!
You got it, we want it!
The Yokkamarchese
are crushing hard
on their vintage anime,
am I right?
I need you, Gras.
Help me understand
these strange surroundings.
I haven't watched anime
since I was a kid.
I've moved on to shows
about real people.
Plus all this stuff is old,
even kid-me wouldn't get it.
[ALLO]
Isn't that Robby's robot-thing?
[GRAS]
It was in an anime? Weird!
Look! A description
that might answer our questions!
Interesting. So there's
a screening taking place
at the Hizakuriger Archive?
It says there will be
a special guest.
[YANG]
Of course there will be!
Our little Robby's a celebrity.
♪
Hizakuriger!
[applause]
And that's the reason why early
Earth anime is so amazing.
It was produced with a passion
that completely ignored
profit margins.
[clears throat]
Galaxy Traveler Hizakuriger!
You will face great dangers
on your journey!
[ALL ] "We depart
knowing full well the danger!"
[laughter]
I hope you'll join me
in welcoming
a very special guest today.
This is director Yuma Yarge's
grandson, Robby Yarge!
[applause]
Uh, thanks.
But my grandfather passed away
when I was only
five years old, so...
I don't remember much
about the guy.
Can you imagine having such
bad luck on your productions
and then not really getting
to know your grandkids?
You must have some memories
of him from your childhood?
Sure, go ahead, ask me whatever.
Pick me!
What was your favorite episode?
Oh, um, what's yours?
Episode three
from the early series.
That's respectable.
Mid-series is seven.
Mid-series was a little messy.
Late series was genius.
Even though there were
only 13 episodes,
they were all important parts
of the story.
Beginning, middle, and end.
[GIRL 2] You call
the early series respectable?
The first two OPs
weren't even completed on time,
they had to reuse shots
from the main ep
that were thrown together
by another director.
And that didn't even solve it!
There were more dummy cuts
swapped in later,
They didn't even fix it
until the last episode!
-You're so right!
-[ALL laughing]
Trying to collect
the full seasons was a pain.
Most of the reruns
eventually had
the completed openings plugged
in to each episode!
So, it was really hard to tell
how each one
was originally broadcast!
I mean the only way
we even learned about it
in the first place
is because of reruns!
-Sounds confusing.
-[laughter]
Speaking of unfortunate cuts,
their entire production schedule
was botched!
It was supposed to be
two seasons of 26 episodes,
but there are only 13.
Every time they dropped an ep,
they showed a rerun.
And towards the end,
the reruns were played
right after the recaps!
Um, actually, 52 eps
in four seasons
but got cut down to two
in the end.
[MAN 1] What messed
everything up was Earthlings
making first contact mid-season.
Learning about
real aliens seemed
to ruin the illusion
of the show.
Of course,
it seems ridiculous now,
since everyone's accepted it
as a work of fiction.
But that was actually the reason
for the cult following
the show's gained since then.
[grunts]
The toy quality at that time
was terrible.
The advanced
action figure technology
we have now didn't exist,
so they couldn't reproduce
the complex movements needed
to create a believable
transforming robot.
Don't even get me started
on the proportions.
[MAN 2] Oh, come on, the poor
quality is part of their charm!
It's also why no one
on Earth buys them,
but that's beside the point!
[laughter]
The studio decided to do
whatever they wanted
with the new episodes.
And they were amazing!
Yeah, but Earthlings
have horrible taste
and never understood
how good they were!
Nah, the studio
was already flirting
with failure regardless.
Gotta admit that last episode
was such a mind-swirl!
I felt lost the majority
of the time anyway,
but then they installed
the Super Hizakuri Beam
and we never even got to see
how it was used!
-That reminds me! I gotta--
-Yeah, screw that!
As one of the many fans
who has only seen
the rebroadcast of the show,
what we want more than anything
is to see the unseen,
legendary episode twelve!
But it doesn't exist!
I want it! Bad!
There are storyboards
and a script created by Yuma.
And Kinomata had signed on
to do character design.
We're talking high quality
for days!
How could this be the episode
that was lost?
It wasn't lost, it was removed
from all broadcast networks,
and then the master film
was destroyed!
Such soulless demons!
We tried it all.
We tried capturing the signal
from the original broadcast
several times,
but all the attenuation
and noise
made it impossible to reproduce.
We didn't care what it cost,
we wanted to see it.
And even after
all our hard work,
we still have nothing
to show for it!
Robby, you may be our last hope.
Did your grandfather
tell you anything
about the
legendary episode 12?
Well...
What you all keep forgetting
is that after 12 aired,
its content became an issue
and it was erased
from existence.
Some say that the creators were
being pressured to destroy it.
-That's the--
-[GIRL 1] That's when the film,
the script, and any
and all production materials
were disposed of.
I heard that Yuma left
the anime industry
and lived his life
completely heartbroken!
One tiny piece
of episode 12 still exists.
A few lines in the script
for episode 11
previewing the plot for 12.
"A terrible plot
has been hatched
"by the Saturnians!
"Hizakuriger faces
its greatest challenge yet!
"Next time,
'The Saturnian Gakudojin.'
We'll see ya then!"
We have a timeline.
The episodes before and after
mention things that happened
or will happen.
For example, in episode 13,
someone says,
"The Hizakuri Beam failed
to work earlier."
But there were no scenes
before or after showing that.
So, the enemy that
they were trying to beam
had to have been introduced
in episode 12.
And even though it was
the last episode,
13 tells us
basically nothing about 12.
The most popular theory on what
the plot for 12 could be is,
Saturnians were developing
a new kind of nuclear weapon,
and Hizakuriger sets off
to put a stop to it.
But the Saturnians are protected
by a powerful shield.
So, the plot becomes
about looking
for a new way to stop them.
At least that's what they're all
touting now on the interwebs.
What do you think, Robby?
Pretty sure you're all wrong.
[ALL gasp]
W-w-wait! What makes you
so sure about that?
-Uh, because I've seen it?
-How is that possible?
You weren't even alive
when it first aired!
Listening to you guys geek out
about the show
made me remember something.
It's the same Hizakuriger
I used to watch.
Twelve opens with
the robot's chest glowing
and then all of a sudden
we're in a flashback.
Then the entire episode
becomes about everyone as kids
which is why
I didn't realize at first
that it was the same show.
There's no opening attached
to that one either.
But how did you see it?
My grandpa would always play
these old movies for me
when I would go
visit him as a kid.
He'd put them on this
old-timey projector thing.
That was the master film!
So then, your grandfather
owns the original!
I hadn't thought about that
in a long time. I miss my--
Who cares? You have
to tell me where that film is!
[overlapping shouting]
We placed it in Grandpa's casket
when he passed.
[ALL gasp]
He's showing it to all
his friends in Heaven!
[ALL groan, cry]
Hold on! That means
you saw episode 12
several times
as a kid, right?
Yeah, but I was five,
and I've drank
a little since then.
I hardly remember any of it.
Aww, memories are important.
Especially from childhood.
So...
[ROBBY whimpers]
I want to help you remember.
What do you say?
Please?
-[electricity crackles]
-[ROBBY screams]
Huh? Huh?
So, uh, what the hell?
[ARMENI] Earthlings are born
with such a magnificent gift,
but most are completely unaware
of it and its powers.
[MAN 2] It's a gift
we would love to have
more than anything.
What do you mean?
[MAN 1] The device
you're currently sitting in
can directly access
a person's brain
and extract its memories.
[GIRL 2] There are so many
lost videos of Earth's anime
searching for a home,
and not just Hizakuriger.
[ARMENI] This is how we will
finally add those lost videos
to our collection.
Cool, so, does it hurt, or...
[MAN 1]
The pain is not that bad,
but it will leave you
with memory loss.
How bad are we talkin' here?
[MAN 1] You'll forget
who you are
as well as what you are.
[GIRL 2] You won't remember
anything about Earth.
Whoa. I call veto!
No just get away!
You are such
a strong person, Robby.
I expect great things from you!
[ROBBY]
Stop!
-[machine powering on]
-[ROBBY cries]
Take me to the memories
at age five.
Twenty-six years ago,
Earth time.
[ROBBY]
Somebody help me!
[crying]
Hatchi! Ikku!
-[YUMA] Robby?
-[ARMENI] It's Mr. Yuma!
-[GIRL 2] Is that really him?
-[YUMA] Robby.
All right.
Do you want to see
something special
-that Grandpa made?
-[ROBBY] Mm.
Here it goes!
This is it, guys!
Make sure you're recording
this for later!
Get it off! I'm gonna die!
You ready?
This is one of Grandpa's
special keepsakes.
♪
So surreal!
Stop picking my brain, creeps!
Private party, go away!
Hell no!
Who do you think you are
strapping down my Robby?
[BOTH]
Stay out of it!
[ALL shouting, grunting]
-[YANG growling]
-[ARMENI] Violence scares me!
[whimpering, screaming]
[machine powers down]
[YANG]
Wake up, precious sleepy head.
No way?
Mr. Yang?
-You saved my life.
-Yeah.
I'll be adding this to your tab.
[grunting]
Step away, right now!
Oh, really?
[YANG screaming]
Hey, cut it out!
[BOTH screaming]
[GIRL 2] Never underestimate
the passion of a collector!
[YANG]
On one condition!
You recognize the power...
of lust!
Please don't.
I'm a collector!
Make it stop!
No touch!
Oh, sweet mercy!
Is that "Binan Shonen
Love-Love" on your breast?
It's my favorite anime.
-Explain yourself!
-Like it?
Hizakuriger's animation
director, Kinomata,
did the character designs
for that show.
I love his work.
-Do you have it on video?
-Huh?
I know you heard me, kid,
don't play dumb.
Oh, well, look who showed up!
Guess what?
The repairs are done!
[tires screeching]
That's great!
We gotta go!
Wait! What's going on?
[ROBBY]
We've landed on planet evil!
I'll explain later, hurry up!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[groans, sighs]
Was I really rescued by Yang
or am I hallucinating?
Uh, Ikku? Woulda been cool
if you had told us
your homeland
was basically Hiza-Crazy-Con!
Oh, yeah. Well, apparently,
someone reset me
when we were on back on Earth
so I don't have
any data stored
from before
you turned me back on.
So, sorry 'bout that.
Please let me go!
"Binan Shonen Love-Love"
was my favorite anime
when I was in grade school,
but one day the PTA decided
it was inappropriate for
children and it was canceled.
-[ALLO] Is it really that bad?
-[GRAS] Is it that hot?
[ARMENI screaming, crying]
It's a story about love!
I'll show you episode four.
It's quite the eye-opener!
Let's see, is this it?
Come on!
[screaming]
♪
Grandpa's anime.
Who would have thought.
[ROCK]
Hey, Yuma, do you know
what you wanna be
when you grow up?
I think it'd be cool
to make movies
out of the manga we read.
What about you?
I think I'm gonna be
an astronaut!
I know!
We should make a cool outer
space adventure movie someday!
Oh, yeah!
Bet that would be really great!
Then both our dreams could
come true at the same time!
It's settled! We're making
this journey together!
[HATCHI]
Next time,
"Never Get Involved
in a Buddies' Quarrel"
♪