[RABBITS]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go
to Isekandar! ♪
[IKKU] We're about to enter
planet number 29
on the Galaxy Highway.
Welcome to Hamama II!
Looks like Hamama II's
actually a kingdom.
This says it's famous
for its "delicious" eel.
Are you supposed to eat eel?
[sighs] You proud of how you're
representing your generation?
Just curious.
Ever since commerce treaties
with aliens fell through
and the Totchinans went
overboard with their fishing,
our eel game has been
pretty sad back on Earth.
Little brain wrinkle for ya.
Oh, thank you. Happy to learn
from your experience.
I know that tone.
You're calling me old
without saying I'm old.
Not at all.
I'm saying people my age
are more familiar
with faux-eel sauce or flakes.
Most of us
have never had real eel.
Not gonna lie, eel sauce
is pretty damn tasty.
But oh, man, sorry 'bout ya.
I can't imagine
going my whole life
without an eel
or two in my mouth.
Mmm. Mmm!
[grumbling]
Don't you worry,
once we get to Hamama,
I'll show you exactly
how to get down on some.
As long as you respect
my boundaries.
Oh. Perfect timing!
Hamama II's
Great Eel Festival starts today!
Yeah!
Now that's what
I'm talkin' about!
I'm gonna show you
how my generation does it!
[cattle lowing]
Mm-hmm?
No one I know
would ever call these eels.
Under any circumstances.
Yeah, pretty sure
I'm staring at a giant ox.
[mooing]
There's nothing great
or festive about this!
Are we in the right place?
[ROBBY]
Excuse me, buff dude!
Wow, even your face is jacked.
[IKKU] Can you quit flirting?
We gotta go!
Hold your bolts!
We're looking for
the Great Eel Festival.
-Eel!
-[ALL] Huh?
-Eel! Eel! Eel!
-Yes. Correct. Eels.
[ALL]
Eel! Eel! Eel!
The festival is about to begin!
[ALL chanting]
Eel! Eel! Eel!
[chanting continues]
Maybe it's actually
a cattle drive festival?
Yeah, maybe their name
for ox is actually eel
and this is like a
bovine festival
of steaks and shakes?
I'm cool with that!
[HATCHI] Maybe their secret
ingredient is eel marinade?
I've never had that before.
Looks like we found
another new experience
for you
to be obnoxious about!
-Have a bite for me, huh?
-Where are you gonna go?
-[HAMAMANS cheering]
-What is that thing?
[roaring]
-It's a sea monster!
-Sea dinosaur!
Guys! It's a giant eel!
♪
No way that's a frickin' eel!
I never knew they got that big!
That is not a normal size!
It's eating cows,
for crap's sake!
[screaming]
[ALL screaming]
[HATCHI laughing]
I bet you've never been chased
by an eel before!
-This is kinda fun!
-[ROBBY] No, it's not!
What the hell sort
of festival is this?
[IKKU] It's the Hamama II
Great Eel Festival!
[ROBBY] It was a rhetorical
question, you jack-ass!
[HAMAMANS]
Eel!
[CROWD cheering]
♪
This seems like
it's gonna be pretty cool.
Never seen a live
tuna fileting show.
What's a tuna?
Oh, come on,
you've gotta be kidding?
No, never mind. We all learn
at our own pace, don't we?
Meaning what?
And was all that running
really necessary?
Couldn't they have used
a spaceship or something?
[ROBBY] You know, no matter
how far civilization advances,
we still hold on
to our traditions from the past.
And our superstitions,
inhibitions, blood feuds,
claims to the throne,
you get it.
-Hello there, misters!
-Uh?
I wanted to meet
the brave humans
who're taking part
in the Great Eel Festival
as first-time visitors here!
This is not an act of bravery!
This is a very unfortunate
coincidence! I'm leaving!
I just realized that the word
"great" in that title refers
to the actual eel
and not the festival itself.
[HATCHI] Oh really? I thought it
referred to the "festival," too.
That can be confusing!
Hey, I know!
You should hire me
as your tour guide?
A tour guide? It's not like
we're on vacation here.
Plus you look a little young
to have a job.
Where are your parents, kiddo?
Please don't make me talk
about it, Mister!
My daddy was swallowed by an eel
in last year's festival,
so I was just trying
to protect you.
I'm sorry.
And you're all alone?
Guess so.
So then...
you really offered to be
our guide because you're broke?
As a stale cookie.
-Right. Count us in!
-Aah!
Hooray! My name's Unami.
All right, Misters,
first thing you'll need to do
is change into
your Eel Fest garb!
[ROBBY]
One condition.
Don't call us "Misters."
Okay! Come on, fellas. Let's go!
Now that's some
good customer service!
♪
[ALLO] Almost there, Mr. Yang.
Hamama II awaits!
[YANG] And you're positive
we'll find him there?
You wouldn't lie to me?
[ALLO] No!
I want you to find him!
Hey! Mr. Yang, check it out!
They're about to have
the Great Eel Festival!
I've heard that festival
is one giant
all-you-can-eat eel buffet.
[YANG] Who doesn't love
a good festival?
Well, you know what
they say about eel.
I could use
a little fortification
before my date with Robby.
[chattering]
♪
[UNAMI]
Grilled Hamama eel is my fave!
[ROBBY]
Wow, it's so huge!
I'm gonna eat
the heck outta this.
No, you're not!
It's a waste of money!
Those things are
two thousand mons each!
These things are worth
two thousand mons, easy.
[IKKU] Those are four thousand
apiece, you idiot!
It's so good!
Has eel always tasted like this?
Yeah, but the eel you get here
are cruelty free.
And none of that
farm-raised crap.
Hamama II's known
for cooking with a conscience!
Are you sure you're not
overhunting these guys?
I'm positive!
Our king is abiding
by the generational tradition.
-Oh, I believe it.
-Okay, it's almost time
for our "Touch the Eel" event
to begin in the west arena!
-I'm not touching those things!
-[UNAMI] Why not?
They're long,
slimy, sticky good fun!
Even I'm gonna turn
that down, believe it or not.
How about
the eel-catching event?
It's in the east arena!
Still requires touching! Nope!
[UNAMI]
They're cute little babies!
And it's easy prize money!
-I heard prize money!
-Yeah!
The king always awards prizes
depending on how well you do!
Don't just stand there
holding your eel!
Move those barely covered butts
and go get that cash!
How hard can it be
to catch slimy babies?
Just check out
how big my hands are.
[boy screaming]
[UNAMI laughs]
Looks like that didn't go
so well for him.
Yeah, don't ever
sign me up for that.
[YANG] This is quite
a colorful festival, isn't it?
Mr. Yang!
I know how much
you love a good bone,
so I brought you this!
[ALLO]
That thing is huge!
[crunching]
-[hissing]
-Mmm!
Whoa! That's the spot!
Whoa!
Aah!
That's what gets
the banana swingin'!
Mr. Yang, can you believe
they're selling eel liver
over there?
You don't say?
There's no greater fuel
for the man brain.
[HAMAMANS chanting]
Seiya! Seiya! Seiya! Seiya!
[chanting]
[chanting continues]
Well, this is exciting,
isn't it?
[GRAS] Here's some eel liver
on a stick!
[YANG]
Glorious.
[chanting continues]
I love a good loin lifter!
I have no idea
what we're chanting about,
but it's giving me life
right now!
Same. Just gotta roll with it
like I been tellin' ya.
Aah!
Oh, Robby! Come out
wherever you are, Robby!
I'm ready for ya!
-[YANG giggling]
-[chanting continues]
[UNAMI]
This is the Hotel Unazuki.
Many of our tourists stay here.
It's very highly rated.
[ROBBY]
If it's got good reviews,
we'll take it, right, Hatch?
[UNAMI]
Hooray!
Make sure you come
to the eel rodeo tomorrow!
How could anyone ride
something so obscenely large?
[UNAMI] They strap on a saddle,
of course!
-Is that ethical?
-[BOTH] Eh.
Just remember to tip
your favorite guide
if you win something.
This has prize money too?
Whatever you were thinking
of doing, cancel that.
You're riding that wet snake
and you're gonna win!
-You got it?
-Okay, bye! See you tomorrow!
[ROBBY] No reservation, just
whatever rooms you've got left.
[RECEPTIONIST]
Are they for all three of you?
Negative. I am not a "you,"
I am a metal mascot,
designed to help the numbskulls.
Beep boop beep.
It's just me
and my partner here.
Would you like our regular,
deluxe, or supreme suites?
All come highly recommended.
Supreme, obviously!
Regular!
Regular! Regular!
Will two singles be all right?
As opposed to what?
Hmm, I'm not sure if this comes
with a "Mascot bedroom."
[IKKU]
Don't even go there!
I'm the one who kept us from
being overcharged, remember!
Speaking of which,
this impulsive splurge of yours
has cost us
every last mon we have,
so you better rest up because...
Wow, they've got
a wall-to-wall dinner buffet,
with all the eel you can eat!
Now we're talkin'!
Let's relax for a bit,
then I'll go down with you.
Stop ignoring me!
I have opinions, damn it!
[HATCHI]
You can share my room.
[IKKU sighs]
I guess. Since you asked.
All right, see ya later.
[YANG growling, hissing]
Where did he go?
Make sure you look both ways!
Left. Right. Everywhere!
[growling]
Don't mess with me!
I just ate a fried eel fin!
Be careful.
We don't want you
over-stimulating yourself.
I want him to receive me at
my maximum strength and power.
He deserves the best, after all.
-Uh...
-Uh. Wait. But why?
No idea.
This place had the best reviews
on the tourist apps, Mr. Yang.
Do you have any guests here
who are registered from Earth?
Of course, we have several
Earthlings every year.
They come in
for the eel festival.
[YANG] Any with this
classic bone structure?
Uh, sure.
All those Earthlings
look the same to me,
if you know what I mean.
[YANG]
You're useless!
[clears throat]
I need a room!
[RECEPTIONIST]
Supreme, delu--
[YANG]
Supreme, obviously!
And send some eel liver soup!
[HATCHI]
They grilled the whole eel!
Let's check it out.
Holy crap! That's good!
[HATCHI]
Broiled eel, eel liver soup,
eel gratin, eel steak,
eel curry, even eel pie!
Can't believe
you've never had eel.
It was like
all I ever ate as a kid!
They even have eel jelly
with rainbow balls!
Is that even possible?
♪
I know why I've never had this.
It's disgusting.
It is not! It's amazing!
Much better.
No balls. Just meat.
And side note,
have you noticed
there aren't
a whole lot of hot lady
Hamamans around?
Kinda weird.
Yeah, it does look like
a "beefy man only zone."
[HAMAMAN ANNOUNCER]
Attention, guests.
The Eel Festival Dance
is about to begin.
Did he say dancers?
I know that code!
This is what
I've been waiting for!
Oh, yeah!
Come on out, girls,
I'm ready for ya!
[IKKU] Don't you dare
get us kicked out!
[growling]
Robby.
Mr. Yang, you have to calm down.
We'll find him, all right,
keep your tighties on!
Robby. Oh!
[ALLO]
There he goes.
Over-fortifying himself
yet again.
-[music playing]
-[HAMAMANS cheering]
[ROBBY] It's just a bunch
of dudes in butt-floss.
-[IKKU] You know you like it.
-Whatever, Ikku.
I'm going to bed.
I think I'm going
to go look around
a little more.
Kinda curious about those
electric-eel baths!
[ROBBY]
Good luck not getting eaten.
[IKKU]
Rest up for tomorrow, champ!
You're so beautiful and soft/.
Will you hold me
till the morning?
[HAMAMANS cheering]
-[YANG] Robby!
-[gasps]
What the heck are you?
Robby!
[growls]
That's not him, Mr. Yang!
Don't forget
you haven't had your shots!
[grunting]
-[GRAS screaming]
-[ALLO] Ow!
[giggling]
Every inch of my body
feels so tingly.
It hurts, but in a good way!
It's fantastic!
You do realize this qualifies
you as a masochist, right?
Are you?
[screaming, giggling]
I don't know, maybe?
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Isekan's a perfect place! ♪
♪ Let's all go! ♪
[snoring]
Yeah, I'm single.
You're so hot.
You should really try
to get some rest, Hatchi.
You need your strength
to win that prize money.
Yeah, you're right.
[growling in distance]
Hear that?
Sounds like he ate
too much eel soup.
[groaning]
Poor man.
[pained groaning]
[thumping footsteps]
[groaning]
[mumbling]
I’m so full,
but it's so good
I can't stop eating it.
Robby! Robby!
-Robby!
-It's close.
It's coming.
Sounds like
it's right outside!
[chuckling]
Robby!
[screaming]
What the hell am I doing here?
I really should be going to bed.
So sleepy.
[door creaks open]
It's leaving. I hope.
[IKKU]
Huh? Is that...
-Blood.
-Something happened here.
Was that what I think?
-What?
-It's a ghost!
A ghost?
[sobbing]
It's gonna get me!
The ghost of a Hamaman
that was eaten by an eel
is going to sacrifice me!
And to think I considered you
the logical one.
Now you're hiding
from spirits in bed.
Incidents like this that
can't be explained by science
are much more terrifying,
don't you think?
Oh. So you're one
of those, huh?
It's okay, big guy.
There, there.
♪
[UNAMI]
Good morning, friends!
-[ROBBY] Hey there!
-[HATCHI] Morning.
Are we all ready to win
some prize money today?
I'll pass.
I didn't get much sleep.
I'm gonna dominate that race!
[UNAMI] Well, the race
is being held in the stadium,
so we should head that way!
Let's go!
[CROWD chattering]
♪
[EELS growling]
They said I could pick
whichever one I wanted,
but they all seem
kinda the same to me?
Oh. Hey, little guy,
you look tasty.
[IKKU] Pick the one
that's lightest on its feet!
Eels don't have feet, Ikku.
If you win today,
you'll receive a commendation
from the king himself
-and be our hero!
-[HATCHI yawns]
Heroes are pretty sweet.
Chicks'll be all over me!
[ALL laughing]
[IKKU] Would you stop
drooling on me?
Prizes are given for first
through third place!
[yawns]
They said this was gonna be the
biggest event of the festival.
So if Robby's here,
this is where he'll be.
I don't think we'd ever
find him in this mess.
He will be mine!
There he goes, trying to hulk
out on eel flesh again.
[ROBBY]
Yahoo!
Leave it to me
to choose the party animal!
You look so cool up there!
Remember, you're not
supposed to fall off!
-At last, I've found you!
-Aah!
I see you on that eel!
Ahh! Is that you, Yang?
What are you doing here?
But I thought he only chased us
while we were in space!
-And he brought us with him!
-No one wrongs Mr. Yang!
-Give me that!
-[MAN screams]
It's time to pay, Robby boy!
Right now!
[ROBBY] I'll get it to you when
we're back on Earth!
I don't even have any pockets
right now, bro.
Don't you realize
your account is in arrears?
-And I mean serious arrears!
-A what?
I need you to pay me
what you owe me plus interest!
You're not getting out of
a late fee so don't even try!
I hear ya.
Loud and clear.
I just don't have
anything on me right now.
Then figure it out!
I will be paid!
[ANNOUNCER] Let the main race
of the Great Eel Festival,
the Nurumite Cup, begin!
[ROBBY]
Run! I mean slither!
Or whatever it is you do! Go!
I'm coming for you, Robby!
You need to pay your interest
if nothing else!
How can I pay you anything
when I'm literally broke?
Why aren't you taking this
more seriously.
-You're in arrears!
-My rear?
Arrears! Pay me now!"
Sorry, but I can't hear you
over these eel.
If you don't give back
what you borrowed,
-you're boned!
-I'm boned?
Figure of speech.
I'm not so sure it is!
Your ass is mine!
[grunts]
[ROBBIE gasps]
What are you doing?
-Let go of me!
-Ass!
-[BOTH] Get him, Mr. Yang!
-Go, Robby!
[ANNOUNCER] Two of the racers
have pulled away from the pack
and have now taken the lead!
Ooh. They're picking up speed
leaving...
You get your big eel back here,
you darling debtor!
Phrasing, damn it!
[ANNOUNCER]
As we move into the final lap...
I won't ever let you go!
[ROBBY screaming]
[ANNOUNCER]
Who is it going to be?
And there you have it!
Our champion has reached
the finish line!
Number five
with a three-point-four!
My Rob--
Oh! Careful,
I bruise easily! Oh!
Eel!
-[YANG] What did you call me?
-Eel! Eel!
-Eel, Eel?
-[KING NURUMITE] Eel!
Why do you keep saying that?
-I am Yang!
-[HAMAMANS] Yang?
-Yang!
Eel!
-[ALLO] Stop!
You can't come in here
and change their culture.
[GRAS]
Their language is eel!
[growling]
Eel!
Yes! I heard you!
It's getting old!
-Yang, Yang, Yang!
-Eel, eel, eel!
Yang!
-[]CROWD jeering]
-[HAMAMAN] You stink.
Look who just won second place
in the eel race!
Here you go, Unami.
This is for you.
Oh, my eel, that's a lot!
Thank you, Robby,
my daddy will be so happy.
-Uh!
-Hmm?
Didn't you say your old man
was swallowed by an eel?
-So he's okay?
-Mm-hmm.
He was swallowed,
but he busted through its gut.
Ended up killing
the eel instead.
-Eel!
-[ROBBY/HATCHI] What the hell?
The money is great and all,
but I was hoping
the ladies would think I'm hot.
But I guess
they must be hibernating.
I haven't seen any other females
here besides you, Unami.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
What are you talking about?
-I'm not a female.
-[ALL gasp]
We Hamamans are
all born male. Duh.
[ALL gasp]
♪
I was wondering why Mr. Yang
would go all the way out there
to collect a debt.
Seems pretty inconvenient.
Well, Robby owes him something
like twenty million mons.
I'd chase the bastard, too.
Did he actually say
anything to you?
Uh...
[groans]
Well... not a whole lot.
Your ass is mine, Robby!
[shudders]
Anyway, where's
the next stage station?
I need to pee!
Space +runaway!
[YANG sighs]
[ALLO] Robby slipped through
the cracks again, huh?
[YANG]
He did.
[GRAS] We can probably
still catch him
if you want to try?
[YANG]
I don't have the strength.
-My feelings, you see.
-[ALLO] What feelings?
[GRAS] Is that something new
you're trying?
I've lost sight of what I'll do
with Robby when I catch him.
[ALLO] You're gonna make him
pay back every mon
you so generously loaned him!
[GRAS] Or you're gonna make him
pay with his hide!
Right, Mr. Yang?
[YANG] That's not exactly
the phrase I'd use,
but close.
[ALLO] You're gonna
make him work it off
on a tuna boat!
[GRAS]
You're gonna sell his kidneys!
[YANG]
No, I'm over that.
[ALLO] Then how are we gonna
make him pay?
Well, you see, I, uh...
-[GRAS] Huh?
-[ALLO] Yes, Mr. Yang?
-[GRAS[ Uh...
-[YANG] Oh.
[GRAS] Next time,
"Land of Dreams Just Ahead."
♪
[inaudible dialogue]