[KANGAROOS]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go
to Isekandar! ♪
[ROBBY] Well, kids,
it looks like our journey
across 53 Galaxy Highway planets
is coming to an end.
That's right, we're at
the last checkpoint
before Isekandar.
Hinaga Junction!
We're one straight warp away
from fortune,
happiness, and more fortune!
[IKKU over radio]
Our next warp will be
to Isekandar Checkpoint!
Get ready, ladies!
Or just sit around
and ignore me, what do I care?
That's all we can do
after that Haccone BS, Ikku.
I'm actually impressed I haven't
blocked that whole thing out.
I'm done singing with plants
and hunting down
creepy pink wombats
only to find out
that we could've
entered hassle free
the whole time.
Fortunately, I've done
some research on this.
If Isekandar is our destination,
no official documents
are required.
See, now that's a plan
that makes sense.
I hope there's hot chicks there.
My. I see a little treasure
inside that cave!
-Coochie-coochie-coo.
-[ROBBY whimpering]
Let me get real deep
and clean those ears for you!
It's the land
where dreams come true
and hotties live
for cleaning out your orifices!
[groans]
Wake me up when we get there!
Oh, is that how it is?
You might be building this
planet up a little too much.
[IKKU on radio]
Since we're all so sure
the entry is gonna be
a moonwalk,
then everyone's
on their own!
-[HATCHI gasps]
-[ROBBY screaming]
[groaning]
Hatchi! Did a clam bite
your nads off?
[HATCHI]
This isn't good.
What is it now?
I double checked,
and this is what I found.
-Read it.
-Huh?
Yeah? Customs. So?
No, look under there.
[ROBBY]
Under where?
Oh, you did that on purpose!
Okay, "Attention,
criminals, debtors,
"blacklisted yadda,
yadda, yaddas.
"You won't be granted
entry to Isekandar
by notice
of the Galaxy Police."
Ohh! Damn,
sucks to be them, right?
-[HATCHI] Are you that dense?
-Huh?
That list of losers
includes you!
-[ROBBY] Huh?
-Don't you get it?
We've made it all this way
and now,
because of your irresponsible
credit history,
we won't be able
to clear customs!
I was chased by eels
for nothing!
This entire voyage
was a waste of time!
Maybe you're not exactly
the expert travel researcher
you want us all
to think you are!
Maybe you shouldn't be
taking out loans
you have no ability
to pay back!
Scale it back, guys.
You're both idiots, all right?
[ROBBY] I told you I was going
to pay everything back
-once we got to Isekandar!
-[HATCHI] Great!
And how do you suggest
we convince them
you're not a
professional fraud?
I don't know because
someone was too busy
eating octopus on Mars
to do any research!
You don't need research to know
how to pay your bills on time!
What part of "I'm gonna pay you
back on Isekandar" was unclear?
We're not going to Isekandar,
so what's your contingency plan?
Don't you dare try to
business-word me into forgetting
that you fail at being
the Research General!
[HATCHI]
You fail at being an adult
and shouldn't take out loans
ever again!
Is this some kind of prank?
Guys!
[ROBBY] You'll get your money
when we get to Isekandar!
[HATCHI]
And now we're screwed
because we can't get
to Isekandar!
Do you know
how insane you sound?
You're just repeating the same
lines over and over again!
-[BOTH] Shut it!
-[IKKU groans]
[ROBBY]
Quit copying me!
[HATCHI] You're the one
who's copying me!
[ROBBY] So you wanna make this
into a whole thing?
You want to make this
-[HATCHI] No, I don't!
-Backing down now, eh?
Why do you always have
to be so barbaric?
I'm not barbaric, you wimp!
All right, I've had
enough of this!
Hey, you look at me
when I'm yelling at you!
Why should I?
-[IKKU] This is going nowhere.
-[shouting continues]
They're just going to scream
until someone's voice goes out
or one of them has
an emotional breakdown.
My money's on Hatchi there.
Robby's busted credit
is what kept us
from getting through customs.
But that's just the spark
that finally ignited
these flames.
And honestly,
it's not surprising.
This has been the longest trip.
Even with all
the planet pit stops,
when three beings
are all riding around
in tight, close quarters,
eventually you're gonna ride
each other's nerves.
Fine! Let's talk about this!
That's what we call
a shower, Hatchi.
Water is still dripping
and no one is in it!
Why can't you turn it
all the way off
when you're done in there
and conserve the heat?
Just be considerate for once!
Plus, I keep finding
mystery droplets
scattered randomly
all over the place!
Well, let me solve this
troubling mystery for you.
They're my droplets!
I did it!
Obviously!
I'm disturbed by the fact
that I have no way of knowing
what part of your body
they fell from!
[ROBBY] I don't even know
how to respond to that.
It's not like I'm enjoying
these images,
I'm being accosted by them!
It's starting
to make sense to me
why you take so long
in the bathroom.
I figured you weren't shampooing
all three of your
chest hairs individually.
[HATCHI]
Stop picturing me topless!
[ROBBY] I'm not "picturing" it,
my brain is under attack!
[sighs]
[ROBBY] You opened the can,
so here we go.
How much toilet paper does it
take to wipe your swamp ass?
Huh?
[ROBBY]
Do we need to change
your diet or something?
I mean, these little dots
are here for a reason.
They're telling you,
"this is all you need
for perfect hygiene,
unless you're gross."
Quit being gross!
Oh, excuse me,
Mr "I need to turn
the bidet on full blast
to handle my level
of filth" Yarge!
And you accuse me
of being unclean.
Don't you be jealous
of my premium engine flush,
Mr. Dingleberry.
Some of us just don't have
to work that hard.
Speaking of work, how tough
is it to put the seat down?
I was in a hurry
and didn't notice it was up
until I practically fell in
and drowned!
[chuckles] Dropping the kids off
at the pool?
Shut up! I wasn't doing that!
I was going number one.
[ROBBY] Stop the spacecar.
You're making it worse.
-You pee sitting down?
-[HATCHI] Yes.
Because I'm not
some savage animal
who sprays all over the seat
and then leaves it
for someone else
to clean up like you do!
[ROBBY] Don't even.
I have excellent aim,
thank you very much!
[sighs]
Oh, and how do you explain this?
Oh! I've been looking
everywhere for that!
-Thanks! Where did you find it?
-It was under my bed.
That's not all.
I found this.
And this.
And a full-on library!
Any idea how these things
ended up in my room?
I missed you so much!
You smell so good!
Promise you'll never
leave me again!
This is no time
for a pervy reunion!
This is about how every time
I roll over in bed,
another questionable item
is staring me in the face!
You know, once upon a time,
that room was my much-needed
and utilized storage closet
where I kept
many choice treasures.
But because of some
unexpected force,
I made it into a bedroom.
So maybe you should try
a little gratitude!
Seriously?
Who can sleep in there?
I don't know if these walls
are paper thin
or if you're part buffalo,
but your snoring could pull
a sloth out of a coma.
Might wanna go get
that checked out.
[ROBBY] I can't help
what I do in my sleep!
And that's not all you do!
[loud snoring]
[grumbling]
-[snoring stops]
-Huh?
[snoring resumes]
[grumbles]
I keep thinking you're dying!
It sounds like
you're struggling to breathe!
Yeah, well, you sneeze
like a sick cat!
Ah. Ah.
Hmm?
Ah. Ah!
[softly]
Choo.
Does it really have to be
a production every time?
Just sneeze like
a normal person.
Who has time for that?
[HATCHI]
You know, we can leave
our bodily differences
out of this.
[ROBBY] Says the kid
who insulted my snoring.
[IKKU groans]
You can read, right?
That's my name.
Right there.
So why is it missing water?
This line shows the amount that
was in there when I put it away.
And look how much
is in there now!
[ROBBY]
I have an idea!
Quit drinking half the bottle
and stuffing it in the fridge!
Are you gonna burst
if you drink the whole thing?
I was trying to be economical!
[ROBBY] And what are you gonna
do with that extra water money?
-Can you maybe do anything else?
-[yelling continues]
I'm bored and you're both
really annoying.
Are these seriously
the only pajamas you own?
Well, now we know
what you can do
with those extra water funds,
don't we?
Can you not wash your crusty,
smelling socks with my clothes?
Uh, can you not wash my clothes
with the essence
of everyone's ex-mother-in-law?
Would you rather smell
like a thrice-worn sock?
How and where did you even buy
this flowery crap?
Space mail order.
C-O-D!
[ROBBY] You gotta be
frikkin' kidding me!
Did you order one of everything
in their inventory?
I ordered what I need.
I came here with just
the clothes on my back,
so I'm starting fresh.
Usually starting fresh means
starting from zero.
Pastel candles
rarely make the cut,
unless you're moving
into a temple or something.
Are you one of those dance-
in-the-smoke-and-chant types?
I just like candles, all right?
They're very soothing
to have around
when you've had a rough day.
[sighs]
So relaxing.
Man, the jets
in that bath are... Uh!
Hey, don't be sacrificing Ikku!
You're interrupting my bedtime
self-love and healing process!
You can love yourself in private
just like everyone else does!
It's not good to absorb
this much light
before going to sleep!
It inhibits melatonin!
That's the sleep hormone
you're supposed to stimulate
if you want to
wake up refreshed!
La la la la!
I don't want to hear
about you stimulating anything!
I sleep just fine with
or without light rituals!
[HATCHI] Guess what?
Not everything's about you!
-Uh!
-It is if it's my house!
-[alarm blaring]
-Huh?
[screaming]
-[HATCHI] It's burning!
-[ROBBY] Put it out! Put it out!
[BOTH shouting, gasping]
[ROBBY screams]
Listen.
Just stay out of my face
from now on.
Best idea you've ever had,
so why don't you do
the same for me?
Like I want to see your face!
Good! Then I don't have to worry
about hearing your voice!
[BOTH grunt]
Uh... uh?
[doors sliding open]
Uh? Great. What now?
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH]
Don't step over that red line!
Don't you dare tell me
what to do!
Fine. As long as I'm
behind the line,
I can go wherever I want!
-And so can I!
-[BOTH huff]
[ROBBY] Remember when
you said you didn't...
Guys, this is dumb!
[groans]
[HATCHI] Remember when you said
you wouldn't talk to me.
As if it wasn't difficult enough
to get things done
with those two.
What the hell is going on?
[ALLO]
What are we gonna do, Mr. Yang?
[GRAS] Yeah, what are we
gonna do, Mr. Yang?
Was repeating necessary?
Wait, do about what now?
About Robby and friends?
Not that we don't appreciate
the food! It's wonderful!
Just wondering if
we're giving him the chance
to escape
while we're here eating?
[YANG grunting]
No need to rush.
Trust me, they can't wait to get
their hands on him down there.
[BOTH]
What? Down there?
[YANG]
I mean, he'll be stopped
because his name is
on the blacklist.
As long as he's in debt,
they won't let him through.
But I'm sure
they'll be sweet to him
over at the
Space Immigration Bureau.
Maybe give him a lolly.
[ALLO/ GRAS]
So that's how we'll get him!
All we have to do is
head over there later!
It's like
they're catching him for us!
I'm so proud of you.
Now let's destroy this meat!
[ALLO/ GRAS]
Yeah! Die, meat, die!
-[YANG] It's already dead!
-[GRAS] Waiter!
[ALLO]
Can you bring us the whole cow
and some wet wipes?
♪
-Huh!
-[door slides open]
Uh!
[whistling]
Wha...
[giggles]
Thank you, come again!
[HATCHI] Is that how
you wanna play, Robby?
It's on.
[whistling]
Ah!
Whatever, white line.
[alarm blaring]
So busted!
[grunts]
You're setting booby traps now?
What are you, nine?
[IKKU sighs]
Just what do you think
you're doing here?
Showering. Not that
it's any of your business!
[BOTH scoff]
Quit spitting your soup
all over my side!
[BOTH slurping]
[ROBBY]
Try your little games now.
You built a wall?
How far are you gonna take this?
As far as I need to
to keep him away!
[HATCHI]
Good!
Now I don't have to see
his stupid face
or hear his dumb voice anymore!
[ROBBY]
That little A-hole!
He literally did that
just to piss me off!
Hey, Hatch-scotch!
Get your butt in here!
Um, you said you're not talking
to Hatchi anymore, remember?
Uh...
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I'm not speaking to him.
He doesn't deserve
that privilege.
Ha!
[sighs]
♪
What? Why are you still wearing
Robby's pajamas?
-Thought you hated him?
-Uh?
I didn't have any other options!
This is what was there!
But you're right.
They're his.
-[grunting]
-Oh.
-[HATCHI] Ew!
-Such drama.
[scoffs]
For the love of Martians.
[YANG] Nothin' better
than a belly of beef!
And speaking of yummy meat.
How you doin' tonight?
Oh, I'm just grand, Mr. Yang!
-Thanks for asking!
-That was some good food!
Right. Well, Robby might not
be captured yet.
So, is there anything touristy
we can do on this planet
to kill some time?
Just a second, I'll look.
"Pinopendio," "sightseeing,"
"for grownups".
Here ya go!
Don't feel like reading.
Just lead the way.
[ALLO/ GRAS]
All righty!
[HATCHI]
Hey, Robby,
does this place have
a bathroom somewhere, or...
Of course!
I'm not an animal!
May I use it?
Yeah, fine. Here.
Doubt you brought your own.
You're gonna have to wash
your clothes, though.
I'm not your mom.
♪
[HATCHI]
Tacky.
-[gasps] Wasn't me!
-Hey!
How many walls do I have to
build for you to take a hint?
-Ooh, you looked at my face!
-Ooh, you looked... [babbling]
[BOTH scoff]
[sighs]
[IKKU]
I'm over it.
We gotta get to Isekandar.
I can't keep waiting on these
toddlers to figure it out.
[ROBBY]
It looks great on you!
Are you joking?
I've never seen pajamas
like this in my life!
Who would even wear these?
It was just an offer,
not a demand.
Sleep in the nude,
what do I care?
Absolutely not!
These are just fine, thanks.
I'm sure I can buy
my own along the way.
♪
[ROBBY]
Kinda weird, I guess.
With all the
online shopping he did,
he never did get his own PJs.
He always wore those old ones.
♪
[ROBBY]
Why's it all emo in here?
Can I turn on some
of these lights for you?
Please leave me alone.
[ROBBY]
Oh, excuse me.
Here, have another candle.
Huh?
[ROBBY] I got it from that
travel bureau dude
on Mars when we left.
I never touch the stuff myself,
so enjoy it.
Just don't burn
the place down.
Huh?
♪
[ALLO] Sightseeing on Pinopendio
was so much fun!
The Ossu is
the best museum ever!
Like, in the entire galaxy!
[GRAS] I'm so glad we decided
to take this photo!
[YANG] It's the memory itself
I shall cherish the most.
[GRAS/ ALLO] You say
all the right things, Mr. Yang!
I think my favorite part
of the evening was
the epic Cotton-Weaving Center!
Mr. Yang, you did so great
at the
loom-your-own-fabric exhibit!
Everyone in the gallery
was so impressed
with your high-speed
weaving technique!
Oh. Anyone could do that.
[GRAS/ ALLO]
Mr. Yang is so humble!
Now we just relax and wait
for that barbecued Roblet
to be escorted
from the checkpoint.
Come home, Robby!
Finally! We're at
the warp point. Here we go!
♪
-Ah, ah, ah, ah!
-[rattling]
[yells]
♪
Must've been turbulence.
[screams]
[yells]
[ROBBY] What the hell
did you do?
Yo. I got us back
on the hyper...
[ROBBY] Are you nuts?
This is arson!
Are you trying to blow
this spaceship up?
I'm not the one to blame!
Shouldn't the sprinklers
be turning on?
What's wrong with the sensors?
[chuckles awkwardly]
Oh, yeah, I forgot
I closed the main valve
cause I didn't want us
to get soaked again!
[IKKU/ HATCHI]
You idiot!
Damn it.
I'll take care of this!
-No, wait!
-Why?
Just use something else!
Those are my favorite pajamas!
Engage.
Ikku, Fireman Mode!
[BOTH blubbering]
♪
Objective completed.
[sighs]
[ROBBY]
Here.
After that stunt, you can wear
these tacky pajamas
for the rest of your life.
♪
[chuckles]
I'm gonna consider that
a promise.
Thank you very much.
That was quite a falling-out,
wasn't it?
-You almost lost me.
-What?
You were freaking me out
with all your nagging!
Was I?
Fine, I won't nag you
if put the toilet seat down
when you're done.
[ROBBY] As long as you quit
wasting so much toilet paper!
Reconciliation always makes me
think of poetry.
"Burning down the walls.
"Deepening the bonds
of our friendship
along this journey."
By Ikku the Great.
[ROBBY]
Where we goin' now, Ikku?
Once we warp out,
we'll be at the final checkpoint
before Isekandar.
-Baller.
-No, it's not "baller!"
You can't get in!
We're gonna be kicked off
Isekandar's doorstep!
I don't know what you expect me
to do about that, Ikku.
My name's not gonna take itself
off the blacklist, you know?
We're gonna have to think
of something!
Hey, Hatchi,
if they won't let me in,
just go without me, okay? Uh?
Did he have to pee, or...
[beeps]
[dings]
So, uh, let's just blow
through the checkpoint?
Without stopping.
I'm sure they've got
better things
to do than chase us down.
Yeah, no.
That wouldn't work!
[HATCHI] It might.
Maybe we should try.
[ROBBY] What were you doing
in there all this time?
I was thinking.
I've never had
so many unexpected events
happen one right after
the other like this.
So what makes us think
the shenanigans have to end now?
Maybe this'll work out.
Uh...
I mean,
we've already come this far.
We have nothing to lose.
I say we push forward
and go for broke.
You okay?
You seem like
a different person.
Yeah, I'm fine.
But if I've changed,
it's your fault.
[chuckles] Probably best
not to spread that around.
Back to the point!
Let's go for it!
-Exiting warp!
-[HATCHI] Great!
[ROBBY]
Look at that!
We made it to
the last checkpoint!
[HATCHI] Keep moving forward
as if we made all the rules.
[bell ringing]
[WOMAN over radio] Please
transmit your passport code.
Right. Remember, guys,
if this gets rejected,
we're just gonna blast through
and try to leave 'em
in the stardust.
I couldn't be more ready for it.
[beeps]
[WOMAN]
Entry approved.
Please proceed.
Eh? I didn't expect that!
How surprising!
Why would they let us through
with Robby's passport?
Guess it was easier
not to deal with it.
[HATCHI] Now we'll live
happily ever after!
[ROBBY]
Yeah, we will!
This is happening!
We're almost to Isekandar!
It's about to pay off, Hatchi!
Sure is.
Aw, yeah!
Akafucrystals,
I'm comin' for ya!
Daddy's home!
[siren wailing]
[OFFICER] Bringing in
some illegal spaceships
for impoundment.
Let's go!
Pick up the pace!
[GRAS/ ALLO]
Whoa.
[ALLO] I never realized
how many names
were actually on that blacklist.
[GRAS]
They look so embarrassed.
-I feel bad for them.
-[YANG] Hmm.
Keep your eyes open.
Robby should be prancing by
at any moment now.
♪
[MAN] We've managed
to track his location.
According to his
smart bracelet's credit history,
he appears to be heading
toward Isekandar.
Very well, then the Luna Guard
will also make
its way to Isekandar.
Full speed ahead, crew!
[whooshing]
Guys, look!
There it is!
That's Isekandar!
-Whoa!
-Oh!
[ROBBY] It's amazing!
And blinding!
[HATCHI] It's a little
over-the-top for my taste.
Ah! Are you seriously judging
the miracle world
that is Isekandar right now?
Maybe.
[ROBBY]
Attagirl!
On to the world of happiness!
[ROBBY] Next time, "Common Fame
Is a Common Isekandar."
♪