[RABBITS]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar!
Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
Hizakuriger!
They merged with
each other. But why?
Guess this doesn't
come with instructions.
Any idea what we
do next, Bottom Boy?
Please don't call me
that, Mr. Top Heavy.
Hey, you mean
Mr. Top of the World
who's ruling you from above!
You don't have the authority,
much less the audacity,
to tell me what to do, mister!
Well, she is fired up tonight!
I'd be bitter down there, too.
You're making it
worse for yourself.
If I leave, you would
be completely lost!
Dude, you wouldn't even
exist if it wasn't for me.
See, as the top half, I'm the
one who's got the brain.
Good luck getting around if
no one's controlling the legs!
You're right,
that is very important.
I do like to pee while
standing up! [laughs]
Shut up! The bottom
is super important!
[ROBBY] Oh! You just called
yourself the bottom! I heard it!
[HATCHI]
No I didn't, dammit!
[ROBBY] Move it! We don't have
time for your bottom-tantrums!
[HATCHI] Quit tellin' me
what to do, Tank-Face!
It doesn't matter if
you're top or bottom.
You have the same job!
Quit screaming and shut
down the tractor beam!
Yeah, that's what we were doing
before you so rudely
interrupted us!
I think this might be it.
Huh?
Aw yeah! Nicely
done, Bottom Boy!
I told you not to call me that!
[ALLO]
Uh, sir.
That robot's about to fire
a crazy-looking weapon!
It doesn't look good, Mr. Yang.
Emergency retreat, now!
[IKKU screams]
Are you kidding? What are
we supposed to do here?
What a cruel world!
[gasps]
Here we go!
Uh?
Uh? So it just lights up?
That was anticlimactic.
What are you waiting
for? Let's go!
Working on it!
[IKKU] Get back to the
ship! We're gonna warp!
[ROBBY]
A little easier said than done.
Just reach up and
grab hold of it!
It's a lot more
complicated than that!
I'm trying to save us
and the top half is the only
one that has fingers, so hurry!
I'm not used to getting
so much sass from my ass,
so shut up and
lemme do my thing!
What exactly is your thing--
Both of you shut up
and grab my rear!
They're getting away!
[GRAS]
What do we do now, sir?
What do you think? Fire!
Whoa! Why're they
gettin' violent?
[IKKU]
Prepare for warp speed!
[gasps]
This is exciting!
Now what do we do?
The robot disappeared
with their spaceship!
Quit narrating and
start chasing them!
Um, but we don't know
where they're going!
[chuckles]
Do you have any idea how many
humans and aliens I've chased
after in my lifetime,
or shall I give you a hint?
Enough to have a good idea
what they're cooking up
in their debt-evading
minds right now!
[BOTH gasp]
In olden days of Japan,
criminals who ran from the law
always headed to the north.
[BOTH]
Mm-hmm.
That's because they
knew Hokkaido was
the furthest distance
they could reach,
but we know that ain't the
truth, anymore, eh, boys?
Y'see, times they
have a-changed.
With their stamina, they'll book
it to the end of the universe!
[BOTH]
Do we even know where that is?
I do.
Exit off the Milky Way
and make a sharp turn.
Keep heading straight
on the Galaxy Highway
until you reach the first
checkpoint, Haccone.
[ALLO, GRAS]
Mr. Yang knows everything!
[ROBBY gasping]
No matter what happens,
you have to focus
and never let go!
[ROBBY groans] I got it,
they'll have to pry this ship
from my cold dead hands.
Now, now, don't shuffle
the mortal coil
until we're outta warp speed.
What does that word
salad even mean?
You guys! I'm still not bored!
I'm still processing the
fact that you made it back.
Please. Like you would've
done it any better.
What a strange spaceship.
Do you remember
where you got it?
It, uh, was my old man's.
I took it from our shed
when I ran away from home.
Looked like that
building would be
under construction for a while,
so I parked on the
roof and moved in.
[HATCHI]
Interesting.
So, what's the deal with
the Hizakuriger robot?
Yeah, no freakin' clue.
[groans] You fly like crap!
'Cause we're out of fuel!
Looks like we're warping out.
How is that possible?
You were supposed to go straight
to the first checkpoint.
Whad'ja do, the scenic route?
Are you still talking?
[YANG]
Full speed to Haccone!
[ALLO, GRAS]
Sir, yes, sir!
How far'd we get?
All the way to the fourth
planet of the solar system.
You mean Mars?
That's like Earth's
next-door neighbor!
[IKKU]
What part of "out-of-fuel"
don't you understand?
Oh, wow! Look at that!
I never thought I'd
get to see Mars!
Yeah? Well I hope you enjoy it,
'cause this is gonna be
your final stop, buddy!
Huh?
I'll think of you every time
I look down at my crotch.
Nice try. I'm not
going anywhere.
[ROBBY gasps]
You still have a debt to
pay, or did you forget?
Look, I'm going to Isekandar
to become a millionaire,
and when I do,
I'll pay things back.
Great! I'll be right
here to collect it!
I didn't borrow
the money from you,
so go tell your boss that I'll
be paying him back directly.
Hey, we're gonna keep going
when Hatchi jumps out!
Wow, that's incredible. Where'd
you get the fuel for that?
You should have this thing
serviced while you're here.
If you haven't flown it in over
12 years, it's probably due.
Oh, so now you're a mechanic?
Where do you even think I can
take it to get tuned up on Mars?
Doesn't matter.
It's a horrible idea.
I don't want some
Martian octopus
trying to work on my ship
with a bunch of floppy arms.
Huh?
[laughs]
How gullible are you, exactly?
You know those Martians
are fictional characters
created by H.G. Wells
a long time ago, right?
No they're not!
Look it up on the internet
if you don't believe me!
"Martian octopus."
--They're not real.
--Yes, they are.
--No, they're not!
--Yes, they are!
[BOTH yelling]
You're both wrong and ugly!
[MARTIAN GAS JOCKEY 2A]
Hello and welcome!
[IKKU]
Fill it up with regular, please.
Right. How about the windshield?
Or a deluxe wash?
[IKKU] Windshield would
be good. No wash, thank you.
You got it, friend!
Yeah, I'm gonna need that
written apology in triplicate.
[HATCHI gasps]
Watch your step!
Will you be needing
any services today?
You offer services here?
Of course! I'll have to
take a look at it first
before I can give you
an estimate on cost!
Whatever it is, let this
one know. He's payin'.
Huh?
Sounds like a plan!
Why do I have to pay
for your spaceship?
Because I gave you lift from
Earth to Mars against my will,
so we'll just
consider it your fare.
So you're charging your debt
collector. How does that work?
I've had just about enough of
your attitude, Miss Pissy Pants.
Why don't you give us
the ole' tuck-n-roll
and find your way back
to Earth or wherever?
And if I do, who's gonna
pay for the services
you just ordered?
Oh, you have an answer
for everything!
[MARTIAN CABBIE 2A]
Pardon me, sirs. We're here.
That's gonna be 720 mons please.
[chattering]
Wow! Everywhere you look
we're surrounded by Martians!
Quit havin' so much fun
just looking at them.
--It's rude and offensive.
--[HATCHI gasps]
Look! Let's try that!
Uh-- takoyaki ?
What are they, cannibals?
I've never had takoyaki
made by Martians before!
Come on, it'll be my treat!
Now you wanna play sugar daddy?!
[MARTIAN COOK 2A]
Here you go. Enjoy.
Smells delish!
Tear it up, bud.
Thanks, I will.
Hold on just a second.
What's with the smiling-fun act?
I'm paying, aren't I?
So I can have fun if I want to.
[HATCHI gasps, pants]
Seriously? Man, you're a wiener!
It's not even spicy!
Did we have the same dish?
[sighs] Wow, that
burned my insides.
But it's good.
Heh.
By the way, you do
know these things are
coated in flour, right?
You strike me as one of those
"a hundred percent organic
gluten-free" freaks.
It's like you don't even get it.
[ROBBY gasps]
This isn't just any takoyaki .
This is takoyaki
made by Martians.
Plus it had 4.8 stars online.
Sometimes I don't know
what you're saying.
[gasps] Just forget it.
You're wrong, though.
This is regular takoyaki .
What if it's just part of their
culture to fry up their neighbor
whenever they get
pissed at 'em?
Huh?
I remember seeing
a Martian prison
out in the desert
where we were earlier.
I bet we're chowin' down on
the legs of a Martian felon!
So we... could be eating
someone's... friend?
I've never done that before!
I wonder what other
flavors they have!
Something's wrong with that kid.
Don't you worry.
We'll be hitting Planet Haccone
very shortly, Mr. Yang!
[GRAS gasps]
Oh, look!
Haccone is supposed to be
famous for its hot springs!
Is that so?
Well, then, as long
as we're here,
we may as well step
out for a quick dip.
[ALLO, GRAS]
It's pool time!
[YANG]
Hmm.
Besides, I can't have my Robby
without making sure I'm
fresh and clean, now can I?
These crackers are so good!
They really taste like
regular octopuses!
Look who's catchin' up.
Bite?
Oh, no thanks.
We need to find a ship
to take you back to Earth
after you're finished
chewing on that.
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2A] Hey
there, handsome, how's it goin'?
You don't look like
you're from around here.
Are you Earthlings?
When you said "handsome,"
you were talkin' to me...
I sure was!
I'm startin' to see the
appeal of multiple arms now!
And yeah, I'm from Earth.
Are you from my sea of dreams?
Why don't you come on up to
my bar and see me sometime?
You know what they say,
--no time like the present!
--Hey! What about me?
Pull your diaper up!
You can come, too,
as a final send-off
and sit down at the
grown-up table!
For the love of Ursa Major.
[BAR PATRONS chattering]
Drink up, my sweet
Martian beauties!
--Bottoms up!
--Down the hatch.
Ha! Or should I say
down the Hatchi?
You sure can down a
drink, can't you, sailor?
He's only a sailor in the
sense he's 'swimming in debt.'
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2B]
I've heard about you.
You're the one
going to Isekandar
with that sweet sailor,
is that right?
Um, I guess I am.
[ROBBY]
Nope! No, he is not!
Our time together
is just about over.
You know, I've always wanted
to go to Isekandar, too!
So they're playing those
commercials on Mars, as well?
They can't get enough.
I swear, everywhere you look,
it starts playing somewhere!
Can I get you a drink?
Uh, I'm still underage,
but thanks!
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
the moment, moment
you've been waiting, waiting,
waiting for is here, here.
That soft-body, body,
body octo show,
featuring Martians, Martians,
is starting now, now, now!
Yeah, let's get
the party started!
[HATCHI sighs]
I gotta pee.
Yeah! Get outta here, Pee Pants!
[laughing, gasping]
[toilet flushes]
[HATCHI sighs]
[HATCHI] Idiot.
He's making my brain hurt.
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2C sighs]
I am spent!
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2D]
Sing it!
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2C]
Seriously about to melt!
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2D]
Girl, preach.
I am not gonna survive in
this suit for another hour.
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2C
groans, gasps]
[HATCHI gasps]
But they're--
No way! [gasps]
[HATCHI gasping]
What do you think, Hatchi?
Are we sending you
off, right, or what?
Hold up. Still peein'?
Hey, Hatch, you in here?
Huh. Guess that's a no.
That little punk, tryna
stick me with the tab.
There you are, Handsome!
It wasn't very nice
of you to run away
and leave me all alone!
I didn't mean to.
I just thought my buddy might
be drownin' in the toilet.
Don't be silly!
I'm willing to bet he's
off having a good time
with a new girl!
What do you say we get out of
here and go somewhere else?
You and me, alone?
Just me and eight tentacles?
Hell yeah! Lead the way!
Hey! This isn't funny anymore!
Let me out!
[gasps]
No signal. [sighs]
[chuckles] I don't know what's
going to happen to me...
...and I'm loving
every minute! [laughs]
[MARTIAN POLICEMAN 2A]
Hey! What's so funny in here?
What isn't funny in here?
You guys had me convinced
that octopus-Martians
were real and that I was
eating them fried on a stick!
Come to find out you're just
regular people in octopus suits
who have locked me in some
random jail in the desert
because my life is
so unpredictable!
And I love it! [laughs]
Huh?
Hey, aren't you
hot in that suit?
Well... kinda.
Is it hard to move in?
Nunya.
Ya know, it's the Earthlings'
fault we have to wear these
suits in the first place,
so what do you care?
What do you mean?
[MARTIAN POLICEMAN 2A sighs]
Mars looks the way
it does to you now
because it's been terraformed
by advanced technology.
But originally, it was known as
an inhospitable world full of
endless deserts and temperatures
averaging negative 65 degrees.
And so, it was necessary for
us to wear protective suits
in order to survive.
But then, one day, some humans
arrived here from planet Earth.
[EARTHLINGS] Martians!
Martians! Martians! Martians!
They went back to Earth
and spread what they
thought they saw as
if it were gospel.
I think I get it.
So with the recent
boom in space travel...
...you've turned this
into a tourist planet
geared towards Earthlings.
[ROBBY]
Woop! There it is!
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2A]
You're my hero!
--Here. Just for you.
--Ahh! Thanks!
I think he might need a
little brother, though.
[ROBBY]
Hmm. You got it. Here we go.
This is gonna be easy.
So tell me somethin', beautiful.
Ever danced with an Earthling
in the pale moonlight?
What do you say we try a little
interplanetary
exchange after this?
Look at that! A baby
on the first date!
Where'd you go?
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2A pants]
[ROBBY]
Hello? Where'd you g--
So you like to be chased?
[gasps] Y-You look like a human!
[ROBBY gasps]
Shh! If they know you know,
they'll send you to jail
for the rest of your life!
[ROBBY mumbling]
[HATCHI]
So you're not cannibals.
It's all making sense now.
I'm not sure what
you mean by that,
but I've already said too much.
[ringing]
Yes?
Very well, then.
Out. There's something
we need you to do.
We've got orders from the head
of the Mars Tourism Bureau.
[ROBBY]
Slow down.
So your dad is the head
of the Mars Tourism Bureau?
That's what I said.
And he's the one responsible
for this tourist cesspool
that used to be Mars?
Yeah. He also created a major
advertising company here.
Anyway, the problem
is that Earthlings
seem to be getting
bored with visiting.
Sounds about right.
It's a tough job
keeping Earthlings entertained.
Oh, no! It's about to begin!
Hey, not the face!
[TAKOKAWAINA] We want to know
what brings you to Mars?
This is Chu-Chu Takokawaina
of the Mars Tourism Bureau.
We're coming to you live from
the fantastical planet of Mars!
Not everyone lives here,
but boy do they want to!
Papa's doing one
of his broadcasts.
Huh? That's him?
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2A]
The live element of it
makes the whole thing
feel more urgent.
Papa and the bureau are trying
desperately to make it look like
Mars is still a
popular place to visit.
You gotta be kidding.
Ah! What have we here?
Yet another tourist enjoying
some of the local takoyaki !
Excuse me! I'd love to
know where you're from!
Oh, I'm here from Earth.
[TAKOKAWAINA]
Another one from Earth!
No way.
[TAKOKAWAINA]
Mars seems to be very popular
with the people on your planet!
We're dying to know,
what's your favorite
place to visit on Mars?
I have to say the wildly popular
Takotubo Land is indeed
the happiest place.
I am enjoying myself a lot.
That's what we like to hear!
Takotubo Land is a
brand-new attraction
and a real hit with you
youngsters, isn't it?
Would you mind if
we join you today?
[HATCHI]
Please! I would be so delighted!
Come on.
Aren't cue cards supposed to
make it seem more natural?
Doesn't matter to Papa
as long as it's said.
Takotubo Land is the most
unpopular theme park
that was ever built
by the tourism bureau.
He's turned our
entire planet into
one giant sham for visitors.
It's been going on so long
that there's no turning back.
Now every Martian will
have to live this lie
for the rest of their lives.
Not if you all decide to
ditch the octopus costumes.
What? [gasps]
You heard me. This is
a lie you can control!
[HATCHI]
Wow! It's amazing!
I've never seen so
many octopus pots!
What a marvelous sight!
I'm glad I came here today!
[ROBBY] Cut! Hope you're
not paying this dude! He sucks!
[HATCHI]
Hizakuriger?
Why is there a robot here?
I don't remember that
being in the script.
[ROBBY] Hatchi, have you
lost your damn mind?
No way. Did you--
How in the world did you
pilot Hizakuriger without me?
[ROBBY] I'm not doing
that with you right now!
What the hell is goin' on here?
You're staring at a
sea of giant pots!
You look psychotic!
This is your idea of fun?
Not exactly, but that's
what they told me to say.
He's corrupting the talent!
Arrest him immediately!
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2A]
No, Papa! Leave him alone!
Huh?
[MARTIAN GLAMOUR GIRL 2A]
Stop forcing all Martians
to deny who we are!
We are not octopuses--
we live in a desert!
[screams] Please stop!
That's what makes
the octopus Martians
so unique and exciting to see!
No one wants to buy a magnet
with a human on it
from a gift shop!
Papa.
Don't you want the universe to
know the true beauty of Mars?
That's ridiculous!
If this gets out,
it will be the end of us!
Is that what you want?
[HATCHI]
It's already out.
[gasps]
Guess that's the
magic of live TV.
[TAKOKAWAINA screams]
Turn it off!
Why are you still shooting this?
[sighs] It's already done.
My life is over.
Uh?
[ROBBY]
What have we learned?
Covering up the truth by
pretending to be someone
you're not is what awkward
losers and criminals do,
and uses a whole lot of
brain cells that you need.
This is freakin' Mars!
There's enough here
to brag about
without making it some
tentacle paradise.
Like your daughter,
for instance.
You should never ever cover up
a sweet, sweet snack like that
with some creepy octopus suit.
[gasps]
[TAKOKAWAINA]
No! We can't!
No one will know we're Martians
if we're not octopuses!
The real Martian...
was always inside.
The real Martian is just me?
That's who people want
to see, not some mask.
I should show the
people who I really am.
Just being yourself
is more than enough.
Just being myself
There's nothing to be afraid of.
[TAKOKAWAINA]
I've never felt more beautiful.
And it was all because
of my pep talk!
I was like, "Dude,
they can't love you
until you love yourself,"
like a freakin' yogi!
Glad you're amused
with yourself.
But do you think
they're gonna be okay now
without the octo-stuff?
[ROBBY] Hell yeah!
They've got a bunch of hotties
and regular Martians
running around
instead of octo-whatevers now.
Wait! Why the hell are
you still standing here?
What do you mean, "why"?
Because I haven't left yet.
Huh?
Heh. Robby knew he was
aboard with us the whole time
when we blasted off.
He's just tryin' to look cool.
Don't you remember
how we got here?
I paid for your ship
to be serviced.
[ROBBY groans] Fine. I guess
I owe you one more trip.
Sounds great.
I can't wait to see Isekandar!
Mr. Yang, look!
We made it to Haccone!
It's time to get
our hot spring on!
--[ALLO yells]
--What just died?
Some major news just
hit the internet!
Well put it on the big screen!
[ALLO] They discovered
Martians aren't octopuses?!
[YANG]
Huh?
Are you serious? That is
not 'big screen' news!
Yes it is!
It means they've been lying
to us this whole time!
[YANG]
Oh, this is a tremendous gift!
Take a closer look
at that photograph.
[ALLO, GRAS gasp]
You can run, but you can't hide.
Buckle up, boys!
We're makin' a U-turn!
[ALLO, GRAS whine]
[GRAS]
But what about the hot springs?
Mr. Yang, you promised!
[YANG]
I take it back!
Robby! There's something
huge we have to discuss!
[ROBBY] I know, I know,
it's impressive, right?
[HATCHI]
That's not what I meant!
[ROBBY]
This better come with a massage.
Shut up and take a look at this.
Ooh, a robot anime.
Dude, you pulled me out of
the shower for this crap?
Look again. It's not
just any robot.
It's ours, but in a TV show
made half a century ago
with cel animation.
Galaxy Traveler Hizakuriger.