[MAN 1]
Hizakuriger!
[KANGAROOS]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go
to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪
Uh...
Some kind of space fleet?
Where's it coming from?
The moon.
Definitely a lunar fleet.
Why would they come out here?
[HATCHI]
They're searching for something.
Their prince.
I'm the prince of the moon.
[BOTH]
Uh...
-[BOTH laughing]
-Okay, sure.
I hope my hearing's as bad
as I think it is.
Me too. So, could you repeat
that just in case?
All right.
I'm the prince of the moon,
and that space fleet is here
to take me back with them.
[IKKU]
Huh?
Uh, damn, my hearing's great.
Neat. Just me, a fraud,
and the moon prince.
Huh?
Look! Mr. Yang!
That's Robby's ship below us!
Hurry up and put it
on the big screen!
Peek-a-boo.
I see you.
Good talk. Now what?
Do you still want to go to the
priestess cafe before it closes?
Nah, we gotta get outta here
before Yang catches up.
Plus, Your Moon Highness
has places to be!
I'd prefer if you didn't
call me that.
Fine, Hatchi.
Aren't you going with them?
You don't have to.
I'm just asking what you want.
Not that.
I mean,
I started this journey
and I want to finish it.
And if we're being honest here,
we both want to do it
with each other!
And with Ikku, of course.
Oh, boy.
[chuckles]
Well, this adventure-party
doesn't stop
until someone goes home!
Let's jet!
You're stuck with us now
until the bitter end!
-Hmm.
-[ALL] Huh?
Hurry! Almost forgot
Yang still hasn't let up!
The Prince has been spotted!
He is currently boarding
the red spaceship ahead!
We will bring him
back home with us!
I swear by the name
of the Luna Guard.
-Time for an emergency blastoff!
-Yeah!
[whooshing]
Mr. Yang!
Robby's getting away!
As if I can't see that
for myself!
-Mr. Yang!
-Stop screaming at me!
♪
Gras. You didn't tell me
there was a fleet.
For real?
They're killin' us!
The Luna Guard won't be easy
to escape.
Prepare to engage
the tractor beam!
[MAN 2] Another craft is
approaching us at high speed!
From where?
Don't you dare attack
my Rob-asaurus-rex!
What is that?
They were pretty easy
to escape.
[YANG] Where are you going?
Robby is that way!
[ALLO/GRAS]
Sorry, Mr. Yang!
Ships two through five
are out of commission, sir!
Fine. But we must protect
the prince,
even if we do it alone!
♪
Are you boys stalling
on purpose?
They're getting away!
♪
Hey, Ikku, are you applying
as a tour guide
for Isekandar or something?
Get us out of here. Geez!
-Where do you suggest we go?
-[ALL gasp]
Back to Earth, obviously!
Not sure why you think
that objective suddenly changed?
As if it's so easy!
Wanna take a moment to remember
how long it took us
to get here from Earth?
Oh? What's that?
♪
-[ALLO] Uh?
-This is strange.
We've lost Robby's spaceship.
Well, find it!
Otherwise, what is
the point of you?
[ALL sigh in relief]
Looks like we gave 'em the slip.
I need a drink after that.
We have to figure out
what to do from here.
It's only a matter of time
before they catch up to us.
Oh. That's right,
you're the one
who's got
the real drama here, aren't you?
Sorry, man.
Things started blowing up
all over the place,
and I almost forgot to ask you.
Why would a moon prince
be running away?
Actually, that's
a great question!
Why? Because you made
the whole thing up
just to mess with me?
You better not be
some criminal on the lam
-making me your accomplice!
-What?
I promise, I'm the prince
of the moon, okay?
Look it up!
[ROBBY]
Hey! It's you!
"Nationality: Moon.
Profession: prince."
Uh! You're paid
to be a prince?
Damn. Glad we're friends.
[chuckles]
All right, spill it.
-Exactly how loaded are you?
-Huh?
Yeah, how often are you paid?
Is it called "prince allowance?"
Were you raised
by a flock of nannies?
Dude, let me see your
bank statements! Are they sick?
Are you next in line
for the throne?
Are you betrothed to a princess?
Is she all hot, rich, and fancy?
Does she have any single AI
or robot friends?
Shut up!
You have no idea
what it's like to be me!
Also, I don't have any money
left that I can freely withdraw!
Because I used it all
to get you out of debt, Robby!
Whoa!
What did you just say?
Seriously just thought I heard
you say you paid off my debt.
He did.
Now this makes sense.
I could not stop thinking
about how we were able
to make it past the checkpoint
when Robby's name was smeared
all over the blacklist.
Turns out, Hatchi was doing
a little princely philanthropy
to bring your credit score
back from the brink.
Which means Hatchi used
his smart bracelet
to make a payment,
and that's probably
how the moon folks
were able to track us down.
You really did that?
-Mm-hmm.
-What the hell, Hatchi?
It's just...
I thought that I...
Huh?
-I said, I... I wanted.
-Heh?
I wanted to go
to Isekandar with you!
Don't make it weird!
Hatchi, are you...
I was born as a prince.
It was a very strict upbringing.
Every breath I took
was spent training
to become the next king.
I learned kingcraft,
every subject in school,
-and mastered self-defense.
-Uh.
Explains all that ninja stuff.
Yeah. Kings have to know
how to protect themselves
and be able to answer
any question knowledgeably.
Sounds rough.
Still, why would any prince
take off and work for Yang?
Because I ran away
from the Luna Land embassy.
I fled when I came to Earth
for some kind of ceremony.
[panting]
♪
I bumped into Yang, who offered
me a job at his finance company.
-I started immediately.
-Wow.
So there's a moon kingdom
embassy next door
in little ole Tokyo?
Of course.
We're not originally
from the moon.
People of Japan
discovered Luna Land.
It was fifty years ago.
My grandfather was
the first human
to successfully land
on the moon
and the first
to make contact with aliens.
♪
[ALIEN groaning]
Are you okay?
What's the matter?
Chronic cramps are killing me.
[HATCHI] When my grandfather
helped that alien
who had chronic cramps,
the ET signed over
the alien base
located on the other side
of the moon to him.
This was the first of many
trades he would make with aliens
to build his fortune
and buy a kingdom.
So yeah,
there are several things
I find disturbing
about that story.
Like what?
Like who was this alien he met
and started bartering with, huh?
And how did he know
the cramps weren't contagious?
All I heard is that
they were painful
and the massage helped.
Robby, catch up.
This story's old.
Haven't you ever seen
those movies
where some girl is slumped over
on the side
of the road
having some personal drama?
That's when the man-piece
strolls by and notices her.
"What seems to be troubling you,
miss?" he asks.
And the girl gets all flustered
and says, "Oh, ya know, cramps!"
[ROBBY] Right, you'd think
they'd quit falling for it.
Ninety percent of the time when
someone says they have cramps,
they're actually
battling diarrhea.
That makes a lot
of sense to me.
I mean, think about how bad
suppressing the runs feels.
And if I were a hot chick,
I'd probably say
it was gas or cramps, too,
just so I could still get
a free meal later.
Although, if I were this dude,
I wouldn't care if she had
the pukes or the shoots as long
as she was hot and needing me.
-So charming.
-[HATCHI] May I continue?
My future was decided for me
the moment I was born.
I would become king someday.
That was my only purpose.
I knew I wanted more,
but I didn't know what that was.
As I was searching for myself,
I found you.
If you don't get off
the beaten path
and run into stuff,
then yeah,
you're always gonna know
what's coming next.
I knew you were right.
I was just so shocked
to hear someone else speaking
the secrets of my soul,
and I almost ignored it.
[YANG/GRAS/ALLO screaming]
There you are, Prince Hatchi!
Really, Unks?
What are you doing here?
I've kept my eyes on you
this entire time!
This running away stunt
of your is over!
You've been following me?
And it's not a stunt
Come home, the moon needs you.
No, it doesn't!
Please leave!
I want off the beaten path!
[UNKS]
But, Prince!
There's only one reason
I'm here,
because I didn't want to leave.
I never wanted the adventure
to end.
I love feeling that pounding
in my heart.
Wow, Hatchi.
You put that pounding
inside of me.
For the first time.
It's just,
I never thought I'd get
to experience all the thrills
I used to read about.
And now that you and I have done
so much together,
I can't just walk away from you.
Thank you, Robby, for letting
me share this journey with you.
I'm sorry!
You were just trying
to have some fun
with someone cool
and experienced,
and now you're in trouble
because of me!
Bro, I swear, I never intended
for you to pay my Yang debts.
That was pretty crazy,
if we're being honest.
But I appreciate it
and I promise
I'll pay you back someday!
I'm so sorry! You're the
only dude I've ever dropped
to my knees for like this!
Robby?
-[loud thud]
-What was that?
It was a tractor beam!
I'm surprised
you don't recognize it!
Yes! Just try
to wiggle away now, Robby!
Damn it, Yang,
get your stuff off my stuff!
But your debt's
been paid in full.
There's no reason
for him to be on you.
Uh...
Your ass is mine, Robby!
[chuckles nervously]
Dude's got issues, I guess.
At last.
Nothing will ever
keep us apart again, Robby!
[ALL screaming]
That was grossly uncalled for!
Leave me alone!
-Let's go! Now's our chance!
-I'm going!
-What's that up ahead?
-[IKKU/ROBBY] Huh?
Is this a hyper road?
Guess so.
But why's it here?
-Those are Dontsu ships.
-I see.
So they've been taking
their own secret routes!
Awesome.
Latch onto that ship, Ikku!
Roger that!
♪
Do you think this will work?
I mean, we made it all the way
to Isekandar, didn't we?
At this point,
we've got nothing to lose.
Let's give this journey
the ending it deserves!
Yeah!
♪
[scoffs] You should know by now
that any attempt to rip my love
from my clutches
will be met with pain!
What the hell did you do
with Robby?
Nothing!
We sorta lost track of him.
Then I suggest you find him!
Does anyone remember reading
about a hyper road here?
I think we're just a bunch
of lucky sons of bastards!
Things have been going
pretty well for us!
Yeah, for now.
-Whoa! What's going on?
-[BOTH] Hmm?
Why are we going
so freakishly fast right now?
I just caught a micro-glimpse
of every single stage
station planet we visited!
That's crazy!
Just let it happen.
Did you see that thing
we just passed?
I saw it said Dontsu on it.
Is this like
their private hyper road
that bolts between Earth
and Isekandar?
Mr. Yang? There's some kind
of hole up ahead.
A hole?
It's an entrance
to a hyper road,
not a floating orifice!
I'll bet every golden comet
that Robby entered that hole!
Which means we'll thrust
ourselves in there too!
[GRAS/ALLO]
It's on, Mr. Yang!
♪
Whoa!
How are we already at Haccone?
Figures Dontsu's been traveling
this way the whole time!
It certainly keeps
the roads clear
when everyone else
is wasting their money
taking the long way around.
One of the many benefits
they get
for being shady PR agents.
Must be nice to choose
what you want to be in life.
At least being a robot keeps you
immune from things like envy.
It feels like we've discovered
some sort
of secret express train
back to Earth, doesn't it?
Which means Dontsu actually
kinda did us a favor.
Thanks, losers!
[ALL laughing]
Do you happen to know
what kind of road
this is, Mr. Yang?
Yeah, it feels like
we're traveling
much faster
than we usually do.
As if any
of that trivia matters.
Robby is waiting
on the other side of this road.
So you're not going fast enough!
[GRAS/ALLO]
We're sorry, Mr. Yang!
We've already made it back
to the solar system!
We'll be back on Earth
in exactly one minute!
It all happened so fast,
I barely even noticed
we were moving.
After all the anticipation,
I thought
it'd be a bigger climax.
You have to admit
it's a great creation.
Do you think we should try
to become allies with Dontsu?
Wow. You need a nap.
[IKKU] Hey!
Something's coming up behind us!
I finally found you,
sweet Robby!
Come on! That dude needs
a frikkin' hobby, I swear!
Blast it!
Who put that thing there?
He's getting close,
I can smell his musk!
Oh, I'm getting so close!
♪
We're almost to Earth!
I'm thrusting all
of our energy in now!
♪
Quit diddling down there
and give it to me faster!
-We can't go any faster, sir!
-Our engine, sir!
I said slam it!
[GRAS/ALLO]
Okay, Mr. Yang!
♪
Aw, crap!
He's on our ass!
Robby!
[screams]
[ROBBY whimpering]
Prince Hatchi!
[ALL gasp]
Oh, my! Rammed from behind!
Oh, crap! We just got knocked
off the hyper road!
So what happens now?
We warp out wherever
this thing wants to go!
That's not gonna work, Ikku!
Hatchi and I need to get
to Earth one way or another,
and until we do,
this journey isn't over!
Awesome.
[spaceship pulsing]
♪
Right now,
a giant spaceship is hovering
right over Neo Tokyo.
You see it in the background.
Experts say their signals mean
they're about to attack.
These creatures were
not recognizable
as part of the Galactic Union.
When questioned,
they said their purpose
is to assimilate the Earth.
What does that mean
for Earthlings?
Could this be the end
of the world as we know it?
Ah! The answer
appears to be yes.
We can see
the blast port opening
and Earth's final moments
are here.
[ALL gasp]
[trilling]
Hmm.
-Hold on!
-Too fast! We're out!
-[ROBBY] Pull up, Ikku!
-[IKKU] I am!
[ALL]
What the...
-Are we stuck on something?
-Ikku, explain.
Looks like we got sucked
into the very tip
-of a huge craft of some sort.
-[alarm blaring]
There's a massive heat source
straight ahead!
Are we gonna die in here?
It's at least
gonna feel like it!
[ALL screaming]
[PEOPLE gasping, murmuring
Wow! I'm not sure
what just happened.
But it looks like the ship
just blew itself up!
Wait. What's that?
Whatever it is,
it's heading straight for us!
It looks like a golden person
jumping into a crowd of--
-Hey!
-Don't you know what that is?
"He who is clothed
in golden robes will descend
"from the magnificent
burning flames in the sky
and save all
who praise his name."
Yeah, sure!
Of course it's him!
He's come to rescue the Earth!
Whew! That was a close one,
wasn't it, guys?
Hey, what's up
with this lighting?
It's way too bright
for this moment.
Oh, that's one
of the new functions
that was installed
on Yokkamarche.
Looks like whatever it is acted
as a barrier and saved us.
Cool.
♪
Is that him?
Is it Hizakuriger?
What's a Hizakuriger?
He...
He was my hero
when I was a little boy.
I watched him on TV.
♪
Guys, wait.
It looks like something's
-going on down there.
-Like what?
♪
[PEOPLE chanting] Hizakuriger!
Hizakuriger! Hizakuriger!
Hizakuriger!
-We crash a show?
-Don't know.
Look! The mecha-man's pilots
have emerged to talk to us!
We are so grateful to these
brave heroes for saving Tokyo!
Not just Tokyo!
The entire Earth!
Uh, did he just say
we saved Earth?
Think so.
-We're space heroes?
-We're space heroes!
No, you're not.
♪
This was not part
of the agenda!
I'm sorry, sir, it looks like
we crashed into a building.
Don't worry, everyone thinks
we're a fancy gargoyle.
I don't care about that, Gras!
I just want Robby!
[shutters clicking]
♪
[MAN 1] Over here!
Can you look this way, please?
-You got it!
-[MAN 2] One for me, please!
-We love you!
-Hey, you wanna back shot?
I got what you're lookin' for
right here!
It's safe to say
we're pretty famous now,
-don't you think?
-Yeah.
By the way, since this happened,
I've had tons
of Grandpa's Hizakuriger
licensing fees drop
in my account.
It's almost too much to handle!
If this keeps up, I'll be able
to pay you back in no time,
no payment plan needed!
[laughing]
Really?
Good for you! Hmm?
[shutters clicking]
♪
-[MAN] Thanks, guys!
-You good, bro?
I'm great!
I mean, look where we are!
Guess going to Isekandar
did change our luck.
You know it!
Oh, cool!
It's the stone I picked up
when we were there!
-Oh!
-Wow!
That looks like an Akafucrystal
in the rough!
-No way?
-Awesome!
So that's what happened?
This thing's been bailin' us
out all along!
Mm-hmm. And you still got
to accomplish your main goal!
Yeah.
Here, you can have it.
Huh?
For reals.
It's a souvenir. Kinda.
Or just something to prove
it really happened.
Take it! Or is it not a good
enough gift for Your Highness?
Here!
A gift, huh?
[HATCHI chuckles]
♪
[sighs deeply]
This is not what I meant
when I started this adventure
saying let's "go for broke."
[groans]
How the hell did I end up
back here so quickly?
Uh?
Thought you'd be here.
You really are worthless
without me, aren't you?
Hatchi? Ikku?
What do you say, Robby Yarge?
Let's find happiness again.
Ready for a new journey?
[chuckles]
Yeah!
[KANGAROOS]
♪ Let's all go to Izumondar! ♪
♪ Let's all go
to Izumondar! ♪
♪ Izumon's a perfect place! ♪
♪ Let's all go to Izumondar! ♪
♪ Let's all go! ♪