[KANGAROOS]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar!
Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
[humming]
Let's all go to Isekandar.
Let's all go to Isekan--
Oh! Arrgh!
Ahhhhh!
Oh, man, I crushed my cockpit.
[groaning]
Iiiiiikku!
Do you really have to warp like
a drunken octopus on ice skates?
That hurt!
That's impossible, Ikku.
Robots don't have nerves.
-Oh, busted!
-I'm busted?
You're the one wearing
the towel skirt!
So is Hatchi.
What a strange coincidence!
I'm tired of you talking back
to me like that, Ikku!
-You're my robot!
-That's right,
and robots were
created to enhance the lives
of their human masters.
-You sick, twisted jerks.
-[ROBBY] Oh look!
I think that's Mulberry-Seven,
the forty-second stage
station world!
Well, I hope you're hungry
for some clams.
That's all they serve.
[chanting] I love clams!
They're my jam!
-Everybody dance!
-[BOTH] Grilled clams.
I hate to bust up
the tiny-towel festival,
but we're almost out of fuel
and have to land now!
[IKKU yelling]
Is this like the world
of the future?
There's nothing but robots here!
[MOTHER ROBOT]
Oh, please darling, don't cry!
[MALE ROBOT]
Yahoo!
Move your mini brass nuts
out of the way!
Watch where you're goin' there,
Buns of Steel!
[HATCHI]
Be careful!
[MALE ROBOT]
You living scum!
[MALE ROBOT] What the hell
are you doing here?
[ROBBY] What do you mean
by living scum, tin man?
Quit talking, idiot!
I'm sorry!
One has a learning disability,
and the other's dumb.
[MALE ROBOT]
Get control of your slaves.
[ROBBY/HATCHI]
Ow!
[RIGHT GUARD]
Let's get moving, Prince.
[LEFT GUARD] They're nobody
you need to even think about.
[PRINCE]
Yes, you're right.
[PRINCE laughing]
Did they just
call him a prince?
No wonder he's so frikkin'
full of himself!
I bet he has a number
after his name--
those kind are the worst!
Why're you generalizing?
What do you say we find
ourselves a nice clam dinner
and get out of here
as soon as possible?
That's a little easier
said than done at this point.
Why?
It's just clams.
It would be clams if we were on
Mulberry Seven,
but we made a little boo-boo
and landed on Mulberry Eight.
[BOTH] Whose fault is that?
Whose fault is that?
Doesn't really matter,
because here on Mulberry Eight,
robots and mech people
are in charge.
Their motto is "If you're not
a mecha, you're not a man."
And you're not a mecha,
so things are gonna be
a bit different
from what you're used to.
[ROBBY] I don't even know
what a mech person is.
Do they grow organically here,
like, not in a lab?
How am I supposed to know?
I'm sure we could
buy you a mech body
if you're feeling intimidated.
Don't be ridiculous!
So they're not gonna treat us
like men if we're not mechas?
Well what a coincidence,
I wonder how we're
-gonna fix that, Ikku?
-We're leaving anyway, right?
Hizakuri Formation!
Hizakuriger!
Uh...
Who's the mech man now?
Grilled clams and fried clams!
[IKKU]
Huh?
♪
And you're positive
that he's here?
Yes!
I'm sure I saw
them land here, sir.
Then begin our descent!
BOTH]
Yes, Mr. Yang!
What the hell is going on?
It's nothing but mechas
and robots everywhere!
[ALL gasping]
[BULL ROBOT] You're in my way
you bag of meat and bones.
You want to try that again?
-[GRAS] No he doesn't, Mr. Yang!
-[ALLO] Let's just go!
[GRAS/ALLO]
Ahh!
No touching, yes?
Ah!
[BULL ROBOT] You don't seem
to understand
the rules of our world.
I don't need your rules,
you troll!
[BULL ROBOT] Here on Mulberry
Eight our universal law is
"If you're not a mecha,
-you're not a man."
-I get it. No problem, alright?
[BULL ROBOT] I'd hate to have
to wipe you off my foot.
-Are you alright, Mr. Yang?
-Damn it.
You have to remember
that the mechas
are in charge in this world,
and we humans have to do
what they tell us to.
I can't keep up with all
this mecha verses human crap.
I'll just become a mecha
and call it a day.
♪
[YANG]
What do you think?
You like my manly mecha swagger?
I sure do, Mr. Yang!
You are swaggering hard!
Excellent.
Out of my way, Taurus mech!
[BULL ROBOT]
What did you say?
Wait, I've seen you before,
haven't I?
You want a piece of this
to take home?
[YANG] Oh honey, I want
the whole damn thing!
[BULL ROBOT grunting]
[ROBOT GUARDS] Oh no, sir!
Are you alright?
[YANG] Oh, looks like
you're gonna be
-the one who's stepping aside.
-[LEFT GUARD] How dare you!
[RIGHT GUARD]
You're gonna pay for that!
[MALE ROBOT]
Bling!
Shiny-shine-shine.
I was about to hire that twerp
to be my bodyguard.
But that would be foolish
wouldn't it?
Are you looking for a job?
Would you like to work
as my personal security?
[YANG scoffs]
And you are?
[MALE ROBOT]
Bling!
I am very impressive
and important in this world.
I am the Mecha-Count
of Gear Nation.
Tell me of your needs,
and I will do everything
in my power to help you.
Well.
We're trying to find a punk.
-[GRAS/ALLO scream]
-What are you doing?
[COUNT] Bling!
Showing them what's what!
Slaves should not be speaking
for themselves like that!
Our bad. Our master is looking
for this chump,
and I don't know why anymore.
[COUNT] You're searching for
a living creature? How strange.
[YANG]
Your face is strange.
[COUNT] Issue a proclamation
throughout the land!
[ROBOT GUARDS]
Yes, sir!
[COUNT]
Bling!
You are free to stay in the
castle until we receive news.
Fine!
Huh?
This is where all the clam
magic happens?
Not looking so great out here.
Of course not!
What do you expect?
This is a mecha planet!
No one's getting wined and dined
and sucking on clams! Ah!
Who brought us to this planet
in the first place?
Looks like they have
a grilled clam shop, though.
[ROBBY] Yo! Can we get
two orders of grilled clams?
Would you like me
to wrap them up for you?
[HATCHI] No thanks, we'll eat
them before we take off.
What?
You're humans?
When on Mulberry Eight,
do as the mecha do.
You know what I'm saying, kid?
[gasping]
[BOTH]
These clams are the jam!
Glad you like them.
Hey Ikku,
make yourself useful.
Open up some of these clam
shells for us!
Where do you get off
treating me like a can-opener?
He said clam-opener,
and we're worse off than you!
[SLAVE]
Robots here don't work.
Then, what's the point of
even having those jerks around?
They're fighters.
You'll find mecha-feudal
lords here who pit their armies
against each other
on battlefields repeatedly.
The thing is,
since none of them can die,
fighting is like
their recreational sport.
But even in sport fighting,
if their central processors
are hit, they're done.
There are certain rules
they all abide by.
Keeps them from being destroyed.
They call it the Tao of Mecha,
which teaches them to fight
without modern weapons.
Keepin' it real.
Grindin' gears, bolts, and nuts.
So as long
as their data's unharmed,
they can switch bodies
as much as they want.
You're exactly right.
That's why we work hard to pay
for the bodies they destroy
whenever they play war.
It's like the longer
I chew them,
the saltier they get.
Maybe your chewing's
hurting them,
and you're tasting their tears?
[SLAVE]
On the house, by the way.
They were going
to the mechas anyway.
-So, what's your name?
-Hoshiro.
Thanks for the grub, kid.
Allow us to scratch you back
for the hook-up.
-[SLAVES gasping]
-Thank you! That helps a lot!
[ROBBY] That's good, I didn't
really know what I was doing.
Huh?
[HERALD BOT] Presenting the king
of the mechanical world!
All hail
the exalted Chamechamecha!
[ROBOT GUARDS]
Chamechamecha!
[HERALD ROBOT]
Our mechanical king!
Chamechamecha,
his name is enchanting!
the lord of all mech!
I guess we should assume
this dude's pretty important.
-Yeah, probably.
-[GUARD] Hey Mech-truder!
Who gave you permission
to harvest our clams?
[GUARD #2] Any intent to steal
will be punished!
[GUARDS grunting]
[ROBBY] Oh yeah?
Well, guess what?
[ROBBY/HATCHI]
Hizakuri Javelin!
What do we do now?
Fight them, obviously!
We don't stand a chance
in this tin can.
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Isekan's a perfect place! ♪
♪ Let's all go! ♪
[ROBBY]
Nothing to see here.
Just a dude helping some other
dude with their clam digging.
[ROBBY] Heh. You keep stomping
toward me
like that and this javelin
will shoot fire.
[ROBBY] Don't test me!
I'll do it!
[KING]
Stop that at once!
[ROBBY]
Huh?
[KING] No need to show
off your talent.
I can see that it's quite large.
And I know something about size.
-I'm the King, after all.
-Great.
Doesn't make sense,
but it sounds like we're safe.
His eyesight sucks,
thank goodness.
[KING]
I'm wondering if you would mind
doing a bit of a job
for your king?
[ROBBY] What kind of job
are you wanting?
[KING] There's a battle
with the Mecha-Count coming up
in our neighboring land.
I will need an assistant
to fight valiantly at my side.
And I am willing to pay you
one million mons!
[ROBBY]
A whole million?
[KING]
And if you win, I'll double it!
-Boom!
-[ROBBY] Hell yeah, boom!
That's two million!
What do you think we should do?
-Do you really have to ask?
-Meh.
He's not worth fighting for
in my opinion.
Besides, this mech is
a look-don't-touch kind of bot.
Weren't you listening
to that kid earlier?
They're all snorting
the Tao of Mecha!
No modern weapons!
No one's gonna die!
All we gotta do is
start the fight,
collect the millions,
and then bolt!
[HATCHI groans]
[KING]
Now, what say you?
[ROBBY] Right, sorry!
I'm in!
[KING]
Excellent!
Come with me to the palace!
[ROBOT GUARDS]
Whrr, whrr, whrr!
Even on boats,
we whrr, whrr, whrr!
♪
[KING] Ta-da!
Welcome!
Available weapons are
drills, tomahawks,
yo-yos, and so much more!
Feel free to choose
whichever speaks to you!
[ROBBY] Oh, that's okay.
I brought my own.
[HATCHI] Wait, you have
modern weapons, too?
[KING] Oh, those are for
defending our world.
We would never use them
in our wars.
[ROBBY]
Huh?
[PRINCE]
Chame! Chame! Chame!
That's my pride and joy.
My son, Prince Chamemechamecha.
Wait, what determines
royalty among mechs?
Blood line, I guess?
Same core data!
There's no blood!
[KING] I've prepared a room
for you during your stay.
Feel free to make yourself
at home.
Incidentally, I don't think
I ever caught your name.
What shall I call you?
[ROBBY] All my friends call me
Hizakuriger Sanjuro.
He said he had a room
ready for us, but...
[HATCHI] Well, he meant that he
had an empty hangar
-where we could park.
-This place have a bathroom?
Where're we supposed
to take a leak?
-No toilet! Ha!
-Improvise?
Are they at least gonna
make us some food?
Why would they?
Mech's don't eat.
We could pretend to be AIs
or something?
Be all smart 'n' stuff?
That might work for me,
but there's no way you could
drum up the stamina.
[ROBBY]
You don't know me!
And now that I know
there's no toilet,
I have to pee
like a sloshed horse!
I mean there's really nothing
stopping you.
Damn it! Wait.
There are other humans out here!
[ROBBY]
Yeah, down there!
[SLAVES gasping]
[IKKU] Feel free to bow down
to your robot lord.
You're taking this thing way
too far.
My human slaves are hungry.
I need you to throw them
a carrot
or whatever your pets
aren't eating.
What are you guys doing here?
-Need toilet now!
-Koshiro, nice to see you!
Is this where you live?
Quit making small talk, Hatchi!
Just ask him
where the damn toilet is!
♪
[YANG]
Gross!
Shouldn't there be a banquet?
Why would they
feed me this crap?
Have they no manners at all?
It's because mechas
don't eat food.
This is the only
human food they have.
[YANG]
Ugh! Damn it!
What are you looking at?
-[GRAS/ALLO] Uhh...
-[YANG screaming]
[ROBBY]
Clam broth adds a nice flavor,
but I don't know about
these soggy silkworm cocoons.
[HOSHIRO] Everything harvested
by the estate is exported,
so unfortunately, this is all
we have left for ourselves.
Yeesh!
Sounds like you guys
need a revolution.
-What does that mean?
-What? You know!
When people fight the man.
-You know?
-[HOSHIRO] Never heard of it.
Of course, being from here
you probably wouldn't.
You're right, nothing here
ever changes.
[HATCHI] I used to feel
the exact same way you do now.
Then someone said
that if I wanted change,
I have to stop following
the straight path.
Hit some curves once in a while.
Hit curves?
Yeah, bump into things and
let yourself fall off the rails.
Then enjoy discovering
where you end up!
I don't know who that guy was,
but that's some
pretty good advice.
But how? I want change,
but I don't know where to start!
[COUNT]
Bling!
The battle will begin
at the break of dawn!
[YANG]
One moment, please.
You promised you'd
help me find Robby!
[COUNT]
I haven't found him yet.
[YANG]
Loser!
We'll just find him ourselves!
[COUNT]
Ka-bling!
Don't forget you signed up
to be my defender!
[YANG groans]
What the hell am I defending?
Do you even know
what you're fighting for?
[COUNT] The fight displays our
impressive level of performance!
It is our most noble sport!
[YANG]
Like a little game?
[COUNT] You don't have to say
it like that.
Our lives are at stake.
These battles provide
the natural selection
we need to evolve.
♪
[siren wailing]
[PRINCE] Yahoo!
Here's to war!
We're off to Se-Mecha-Hara!
[ROBOT GUARDS]
Chamechamecha!
[ROBBY] Man, these mecha
dudes love to fight.
They sent us our payment.
So what now?
Guess we follow them
and pretend
we know what we're doing?
[ROBBY] Look around for some
easy ass to beat,
and then get the heck
out of there.
[KING] We'll be the victors
of Se-Mecha-Hara!
♪
[PRINCE]
Huh? What the hell is happening?
[KING]
Oh, damn that Count!
He's dispersed
Minovsky particles!
All of our camera eyes
are jammed,
and we have no way
of seeing where we're going!
-[PRINCE] I can't see anything!
-[KING] Wait a minute!
That means the Count's vision
is hindered as well!
Prepare to move forward, men!
[ROBOT GUARDS]
Chamechamecha!
[horn blowing]
[COUNT]
Bling!
All right men, move out!
[ROBOT REBELS shouting]
[ALLO]
We're never gonna make it!
[GRAS] We're too young
and pretty to die here!
[YANG] Shut up!
There's no time for dramatics!
[ROBOT GUARDS shouting]
I can't see anything
with all this static!
Then quit looking through that
thing and use your own eyes!
Now, isn't that better?
No!
I still can't see!
[HATCHI] Because your robot eyes
are still jammed.
I swear, they rely too much
on technology out here.
[ROBBY laughs]
Which puts us in the perfect
position to mess with them!
Hizakuri Javelin!
[ROBBY]
Hizakuri-kuri-kuri Javelin!
Hiza-Hiza-Hizakuri Javelin!
Hiza. Hi-Hi-Hi-Hi-Hizakuri
Javelin!
Hiza, Hiza, Hiza,kuri-kuri-kuri
Ja-Javelin!
[KING]
King's Drill!
[ROBOT GUARD] Master Hizakuriger
has made himself known!
[KING]
I should have known.
Seize this momentum
and defeat the Count!
-[ROBOT GUARD] Right!
-[ROBOT REBEL] Chimu!
-[ROBOT GUARD] Zat!
-Chimu!
-Zat!
-Chim!
-Zat-zat-zat-zats!
-Chi-Chi-Chim!
-Zats!
-Chimu-Chimu-Chimu!
-Zat-Zat!
-Chim! Chim!
-Ha-Zat. Ha-Zat.
-Chim chim!
Zats, fool!
Say Zats!
Chimu! Chimu!
Say Chimu!
-Zats, boi!
-Chi-chi-chi-chi Chimu!
-Zat!
-Chimu chimu!
Chame!
[COUNT] They're taking this
skirmish far too seriously!
Bling! Ugh...
[COUNT]
Why, you!
You're going to die for that!
[HATCHI] What does it mean
to be human, anyway?
Huh?
We're battling that little guy?
That's almost insulting.
[YANG] Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Whoo! Whoo-ha!
-He flew right under!
-Step on him!
[YANG]
Whoa-ho-ho!
Whaaaa!
[ROBBY groaning]
[YANG] If this battlefield
were a runway,
the category would be "tragic."
You tell him, Mr.
Yang!
[ROBBY] Yang is in there?
How?
[YANG] Why must you play so hard
to get, Robby?
Remember when I tried
to get us to leave earlier?
What?
Wait no!
[YANG] Know what I love
about this planet?
The humans are the slaves!
Ahhhhh!
[YANG]
Oh, c'mon!
What the hell's going on now?
♪
-[KING] What was that?
-[COUNT] Bling!
No idea!
[PRINCE screaming]
[KING]
My son!
Oh, this is your fault!
You violated the rules!
[COUNT]
Look who's talking!
[BOTH]
Arghhhhh!
[SLAVES shouting]
This is a revolution!
[KING]
What did he just say?
[COUNT]
Who cares!
Ahhh!
Can you hear me?
Are you okay?
[ROBBY]
We are now.
Thanks for the save.
Hoshiro!
How're your rails?
Did you bend them, yet?
Yeah!
You guys should get out of here.
Not everyone is gonna know that
robot is just a big metal suit.
[ROBBY] Yeah, you're right.
We're out!
[ROBBY]
Later, tater!
[HATCHI]
Be safe!
[HOSHIRO chuckles]
I can't believe they actually
started a revolution.
And it's all thanks
to you, right?
Huh?
What'd ya mean?
Finally.
The jamming's gone
and I can see again.
What a nightma--
Argh!
I dare you to try a stunt
like that again!
I swear I'll unplug every cord
in your body!
Oh, come on.
Robots were first created
for humans to help them
with their daily life.
Like partners, actually.
[IKKU] Then treat me like
a partner and stop ignoring me!
[HATCHI] Right! On to the next
stage station world!
[ROBBY] Good call. We gotta lose
Yang or he's gonna...
Wait, is he even behind us?
Hey!
Why are you fighting
on our side, mister?
[YANG] 'Cause I hate
those mech bastards.
[YANG]
Viva Revolution!
[ROBBY] Next time,
"The Family That
Sticks Together, Hizakuriger."