[HATCHI] "Galaxy
Traveler Hizakuriger."
It's a fifty-year-old anime
about a shape-shifting,
combining robot
and its adventures
traveling through the universe.
It was a big hit until mankind
discovered actual aliens.
They weren't anything like
their written personas,
which made the show
feel contrived.
People were over it,
and it was canceled
after only a single season.
So you're saying there are
some serious weebs out there,
and this robot was created
by a fan of that anime.
Cool. What's it doing
on my spaceship?
I bet you could easily
find that out.
This ship used to be
your father's, right?
Yeah, and I remember
he did say something
about making a trade
with some aliens.
It's bugging me
that I can't figure out
where I've seen that anime
before, though.
Well, it's at least
half a century old.
[ROBBY]
Which means?
[IKKU on speakers]
Warp time, ladies!
Everyone back to the cockpit!
[RABBITS singing]
♪ Let's all go to Isekandar! ♪
♪ Let's all go
to Isekandar! ♪
Yeah! We're about to exit
the solar system, hold on!
[ALL grunt]
-What was that?
-[MAN on radio] Hey!
You in the red spaceship!
Yeah, you!
Gonna need you to warp out!
-[IKKU] Another debt collector?
-Please!
There's not enough discount
store bling for it to be his.
How many loans
did you take out?
[metal banging]
It's not like that, all right?
I had all my debts
consolidated with Yang
by some crooked-ass attorney!
The payments are low and easy
with no consultation necessary!
I only deal with honest,
clean debt, so quit judging.
I wish you could hear
how you sound to normal people!
[MAN]
I said, warp out!
[ALL yelling]
[ROBBY groans]
-[IKKU moans]
-[ROBBY grunts]
[ROBBY]
Great. Where are we now?
[IKKU] Looks like Pluto
to me, geniuses.
How did we get here?
I wish you could hear
what you sound like
to people
who were paying attention.
Do you realize what
a great opportunity this is?
Most people never get
to see Pluto up close!
And that's okay. I mean,
it's not even
a potty-break planet
on the Galaxy Highway.
Ain't nobody sitting around
dreaming of visiting Pluto.
-Trust--
-[MAN] There you are.
Follow me and land that ship.
What? Screw you, man!
Ikku, make this thing
warp again!
I can't! Everything got
all scrambled around!
That jerk!
I need time to fix it, idiot.
Now land this ship.
[growls softly]
[wind whistling]
[BOTH shuddering]
[ROBBY] I'm freezing
my frickin' nads off!
[HATCHI] This planet was
supposed to have been
terraformed, too!
Kinda reminds you
of being at the North Pole,
doesn't it?
[laughing] Being cold like this
is adding to the adventure!
Hey, Robby.
Look at my teeth!
[teeth chattering]
[BOTH] Huh?
♪
[BOTH]
Uh...
[MAN]
Welcome!
[HATCHI gasps]
W-W-W-W-Welcome to Pluto!
Mr. Pluto?
[HATCHI]
You know him?
[ROBBY]
Yes, we had lunch last week.
No! He's one of those little
mascot characters
they used in grade school
to make teaching kids
about planets "fun" or whatever.
[HATCHI]
Yeah, he looks real fun.
Those stupid characters
each had a trading card, too.
I tried to collect them all once
because I was told
they'd make me
a lot of money someday.
-How'd that turn out?
-None of your damn business.
[DENSHI]
Denshi is important!
-No way. Miss Denshi?
-What's that?
[ROBBY]
I used to love Miss Denshi!
[HATCHI] Until she left you
like all the rest, huh?
[ROBBY]
Have you guys been living it up
on Pluto this whole time?
[MR. PLUTO]
Not the whole time!
[MISS DENSHI]
Yeah, not the whole time!
[BOTH]
Number Nine is oh so fine!
You're looking at the new
and improved Pluto mascots!
I had no idea.
[MR. PLUTO] Pluto is the planet
of dreams and romance!
[MISS DENSHI]
Why not take a lovely vacation
on the farthest planet
from the sun?
[ROBBY]
Except it's not a planet.
[BOTH gasp]
But that's totally okay!
It's still a lovely
little planetoid.
-Yeah, sure.
-[BOTH grunting]
[BOTH]
We're not a 'toid!
Huh?
[MR. PLUTO] We were stripped
of our identity,
abused, and relabeled
a planetoid!
[MISS DENSHI]
I feel so violated!
[MR. PLUTO] We are the victims
of a cruel solar system!
[MISS DENSHI]
Denshi is important!
[ROBBY]
Just so we're clear,
neither of you
is making any sense!
[HATCHI] It's hard
to understand you from in there!
Can you take the costume off
and come talk to us?
Sorry about that.
You want us to take it again
from the top?
[WOMAN]
Let's all go inside.
♪
I'm the chief of the
Travel Bureau here on Pluto.
Good to meet ya.
And I am his daughter.
So this is really
what we're doing, huh?
It's called,
"establishing a theme."
I'm sure you've heard tell
of the terrible, humiliating day
our beloved Pluto
was unjustly demoted
from planet to planetoid.
And no one even asked us
for our input.
Talk about rude.
It's not like it was done
to be mean.
Pluto's just smaller
than Earth's moon.
It doesn't match
the definition of plan--
Do not come into my home
and say the word "moon" to me!
You wanna call us a planetoid,
then that's fine!
But you better tell me why
a common satellite
deserves to have a day
of the week named after it
when the rest of the days
are named after gods!
Why should the moon get Monday?
You think that's the best way
to kick off the week?
How is Zeus supposed
to feel about this?
He feels mocked and
disrespected, as well he should!
Some idiot thought it was okay
to list a moon before the gods!
And do you understand
how insulting that is for us?
A planetoid?
[BOTH]
No, please tell us.
[CHIEF]
In order to keep injustices
like these from happening,
we demand that
Pluto be restored
as an official planet.
[ROBBY]
Yeah, that makes sense.
The gods should be led
by a planet, not a moon.
We motion that Monday
be renamed Plutoday!
[HATCHI]
The moon will never go for that.
[BOTH]
Make Monday done-day.
Start the week with Plutoday!
You're listening to the chanting
and singing
of Plutonian citizens
marching down Main Street.
[CITIZENS]
Tyurya, tyurya, tyurya!
And leave Tuesday as Tuesday,
that's A-okay...
Whoa!
Look how they're banding
together on this!
We've got your back!
The only ones involved
in this campaign are Plutonians,
but don't other planets
need to vote?
You're right.
You're exactly right!
[sighs]
Where the hell
did those jerks go now?
[CHIEF]
We know it won't be easy
to have our status
legally restored.
That's why we're working
with a major ad agency
to help create
an effective campaign
and provide valuable advice.
That's who suggested
the mascots.
They said the
small-but-mighty attitude
of these ones
would be perfect for us.
So we immediately purchased
the rights for Mr. Pluto
and stepped
onto the battlefield.
Thankfully, he was on sale.
I'm guessing
you're talking about
a liquidation sale?
I'm glad Pluto encourages
repurposing.
Even that one?
They said if we
purchased immediately,
we could have Denshi
at no extra charge.
[ROBBY]
Ooh, what a bargain!
The agency said Pluto needed
to have its own
unique flair and cuisine
to attract tourists
and advised us to create
a signature shaved-ice dessert
using genuine Plutonian ice
that can't be found
on other planets.
[ROBBY] Shaved ice?
But it's freezing here!
Does anyone buy it?
-They don't.
-Cool, good talk.
[HATCHI] Hmm.
Do you remember
what flavor the green one is?
Whoa! Oh, hey, it's nitrogen!
You might want to add some fruit
or something to this.
-It's for more mature palettes.
-You're right.
We just wanted
to do exactly
what the PR department
instructed
to produce
the best possible results.
But so far, nothing has changed.
[ROBBY]
No? You're kidding?
Letting an ad agency tell you
how to run your planetoid
by purchasing expired merch
wasn't the answer after all?
Can't believe they sold you
tired-ass Mr. Pluto!
How was that gonna work?
His trading card
isn't even rare!
-I told you.
-Papa.
So, did you guys capture us
because you wanted us
to see how badly you failed?
I saw how successful
you were with Mars.
[BOTH]
Huh?
And the truth is...
The real Martian was inside.
Oh, yeah, they filmed it.
After watching that broadcast,
it finally clicked.
-[HATCHI] Hmm?
-[ROBBY] Uh...
We had to make Pluto
a planet again.
We had to take Monday away
from that moon.
We need a new campaign,
and we want you two
to take over!
[ROBBY]
Whoa! Time out!
We aren't PR dudes or event guys
or anything that's gonna make
anyone's lives better!
He can't even improve
his own life, much less yours.
He's going all the way
to Isekandar
to try to change
his crap luck.
Then why did you agree
to do the Martian TV show
as if you were available?
I didn't agree!
Excuse me?
Will you please do it for us?
-[deep voice] Of course I will!
-I'm sorry, what?
I know what you're thinking
and you're wrong.
I'm not wussing out
because she's crying
on her love mountains, okay?
[ROBBY]
Lies.
[GIRL]
I'm begging you!
That's it!
I'm tired of nice people
getting taken advantage of!
You don't know how not to let
people take advantage of you.
Let's go.
I've got a few words
to say to
a certain ad agency.
Aah! All right!
[BOTH]
Thank you from the Plutonians!
[ROBBY] What you gotta do is
look at what makes Pluto Pluto
and then crank
it up to like a seven.
So, like, what would you say
Pluto's best qualities are?
-There's none.
-I'd say dreams and romance.
Pluto is a planet that inspires
dreams and romance
for all who come to visit.
[ROBBY]
How's that?
According to what
our ad agency told us,
ex-planet Pluto
is known for being
the most remote
planet-ish outpost.
And I mean
in the entire solar system.
This is where battleships and
railway trains take a break.
Screw that.
We should be targeting visitors
with a [bleep] Memorial Hall.
That was a good idea.
Whatever happened to it?
Nothing! They always say
the plans are almost ready
and we should be patient.
You gotta forget everything
this ad agency
is telling you.
The key to strong
tourist attractions
is whether or not
they appeal to the ladies.
Mostly the twenty
to thirty-four demo.
And that schmemorial
or whatever it is
is not gonna make the list.
-He's right.
-[CHIEF gasping]
Aren't there like some
fluffy Plutonian creatures
that can be grouped together
for public snuggles?
-That's good!
-Like Plutonian pandas
or even the black
and white pandas that are lost?
Why just pandas?
Doesn't really matter what it is
as long as it's
cute enough to capture
-the heart of a woman.
-[GIRL gasps]
We have Plutonian penguins,
they're adorable!
Look! Have you ever seen
a sweeter face?
-[HATCHI] Hmm?
-[ROBBY] Huh? Uh...
[HATCHI laughs]
[cawing]
[GIRL]
Aww. [giggles]
That's so amazing!
Is anyone's heart captured?
'Cause that's not cute.
[GIRL giggles]
Speaking of hearts,
that reminds me.
When we were landing, we saw
a heart-shaped something.
I wanted to ask you about it.
Uh, yes, you saw
the Tombaugh Regio.
[ROBBY]
Wow!
Yep, that's a heart!
That's totally something
that girls would flip out about.
Especially if you tell them
it's some kind
of matchmaking power spot
where they'll meet
their soulmate.
"And that's why Pluto's
the planet of love."
Unfortunately, it's just
an ice field
that happens
to be shaped like that.
I guess it depends
on where you're positioned.
I don't see a heart
I'm afraid it doesn't have
any love powers.
Oh, my gosh, you two
have got to catch up.
Guys, you've got
a giant ice whatever
in the shape of a heart.
Slap a sign on it
and call it a love-shrine
or field of romance
and start pumping out
snow-globes and t-shirts
at triple your cost!
Like a Mr. Pluto Shrine?
How about Miss Denshi charms?
[ROBBY]
No one give a crap about those!
What are you talking about?
We've spent almost our
entire budget on Mr. Pluto!
-And Miss Denshi!
-[ROBBY] No one cares!
[BOTH]
Okay.
[HATCHI] Has your relationship
grown cold?
[GIRL] Does it feel like
the gap between you
will never close?
[BOTH] Maybe you should take
a trip to Pluto!
-Hey, wait for me!
-[GIRL laughing]
[GIRL]
You're gonna have to catch up!
[HATCHI] The home
of Pluto's Heartful Icefield
can become
your sweet salvation.
[GIRL] Love and affection
will be yours forever!
[MISS DENSHI]
Down with Monday!
[MR. PLUTO]
Make it Plutoday!
[ROBBY] Okay, what the hell
just happened?
Just cut before Denshi
and Mr. Pluto show up.
You don't need it.
But we already paid
for both characters!
No one likes them!
All right, you just hang out
and I'll make the cuts
and get this sent
to the galactic network
-and upload it on U-Chube.
-[CHIEF grumbles]
[IKKU]
We're just about repaired,
but we still can't warp
for some reason.
-We have something to do!
-And we're doin' it now!
Off to the
heart-shaped icefield!
[IKKU] You know, labor laws
apply to me, too!
[ALLO] Mr. Yang!
We're approaching Mars!
[GRAS] We'll catch those two
this time, I can feel it!
Just you wait, Robby.
There's nothing out here.
No, no, I was wrong,
here comes a tumbleweed.
Where are all
the takoyaki stands?
I was looking forward
to Takotubo Land.
[TAKOKAWAINA]
Hello and welcome!
Welcome to the Planet of Mars!
Would you like
a complimentary ride
aboard the Mars Adventure
Experience Tour?
On this tour,
you'll get to experience
an Extreme Martian
climate change!
Have you ever wondered
what it might feel like
to open your eyes
in the center of a dust devil?
Climb to an elevation
of over 25,000 meters
on the Olympus Mons Tour.
There are many great ways
to explore Mars!
Wait! Where are all
the octopuses?
-We've moved on.
-What does that mean?
You can't move on
from the citizens!
Octopuses live on Mars,
you can't kick them out!
The only thing I ever wanted
was to meet an octopus.
Just because the tourism
has changed here,
doesn't mean you have
to let it change your heart.
What about the Martian Cabaret?
It's still there, but with
a brand-new aesthetic.
But why?
Why destroy a man's dreams?
[sobbing]
These are some extreme changes
you've made here.
Well, we valued the advice
of a certain individual.
Oh, yeah?
Is this he?
It is!
Robby's a friend
of yours too, huh?
Yes, and I need to find him!
Unfortunately,
he and his partner
left Mars quite a while ago.
But I believe they said they
were going to Isekandar next.
Isekandar?
In the Andromeda galaxy?
Let's go!
If they're heading to Isekandar,
then that's where
we'll meet them!
[ALLO groans]
But it's like forever away!
[GRAS] Why are we going
all the way out there for Robby?
[YANG] Will you shut up?
We're not going that far.
We'll catch him
before he gets there.
-[ALLO] Huh?
-[GRAS] Huh?
[ROBBY] You gotta put
a gigantic cupid statue here.
And then like a shrine
of passion over here.
Oh! And this is
the perfect spot
to build your
big-ass souvenir shop!
I'd suggest coming up
with some new PR characters.
[GIRL]
Okay.
All that's left
is new local cuisine.
What do you think it should be?
Here's what it shouldn't be.
Frozen battery-flavored
shaved ice!
I'm thinking warm.
Like heart-shaped pizza
with love sauce.
How would you make that
appeal to women?
Uh, women eat food too,
precious.
-[spaceship approaching]
-[BOTH] Huh?
[MAN]
We've finally found you, Chief.
Who's that?
Those are the people
from that advertising agency.
[HATCHI]
Dontsu Incorporated?
My name's Kodai.
Rhymes with Toad Eye.
How're you?
And I'm Morisugi,
you're not dreaming.
Hey! We've got big news
to celebrate with you, Chief!
-It's finally completed!
-What do you mean?
The full-size
Mr. Pluto you ordered.
[CHIEF gasping]
Are you freaking out yet?
The real Mr. Pluto
is 20 meters tall,
and so is this robot!
Your guests will feel like
they're really meeting him!
I don't remember ordering this.
Maybe not by itself,
but he does come
with the Pluto PR package
we discussed.
I thought I was getting
the [bleep]-something-or-other
Memorial Hall?
Oh, you're still getting it.
We didn't spend much
of our budget building that guy.
I was afraid
you were gonna say that.
Relax!
All you have to do now
is sit back
and let Mr. Pluto
make you popular!
Act now, and we'll throw in
a set of spare parts!
[ROBBY]
Guys.
Quit trying to make
"Mr. Pluto" happen.
It's not gonna happen!
[HATCHI]
Neither is Miss Denshi.
[KODAI grunts]
Who are these jerks,
and what do they want?
Well, this is awkward,
but they're two new people
I've asked to help
with Pluto's PR.
Can't say that was
a good call.
Why would you trust amateurs to
handle something so important?
[ROBBY]
Look at this card!
Mr. Frickin' Pluto!
It's just a normal card.
There's nothing
rare about it.
Everyone has one
cause they were told
it would become
more valuable.
But it's been 20 years
since it came out
and no one cares!
If convincing your client
to spend money
on this kind of trash
is the work of a pro, then
I'm thrilled to be an amateur.
-[growls] Listen, Chief.
-Hmm.
I am more than happy
to rework our angle,
but don't forget we are the ones
you hired to do Pluto's PR.
I never officially hired you
because no one from your firm
ever gave me a contract!
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha.
-Is that true?
-Technically, yeah.
Then we gotta find a way
to at least sell him
on that stupid robot.
How do we do that?
I'll let you know
as soon as I get an idea.
[KODAI panting]
♪
All right, Chief!
Maybe the trading card
isn't rare,
but the performance level
of this robot sure is!
Launch!
[BOTH]
Whoa!
[ROBBY] Uh...
[BOTH screaming]
What the...
Hey! Watch where
you're goin' with that!
[KODAI] A good agency
always has a contingency plan!
-[ROBBY screams]
-Go back to where you came from
and try to steal
someone else's job.
Yeah, what he said!
Powerful machine.
Kinda wish I didn't have
to hate them.
Come on, Hatchi, let's go!
[HATCHI]
Right behind you.
♪
Hizakuriger!
Kodai, look!
I think theirs
might be bigger than ours!
Are we sure they're amateurs?
'Kay, now that we've whipped out
our giant Hizakuriger,
I'm not exactly sure
what to do with it.
We should wait for them
to make the first move
because this thing
doesn't have a lot of stamina.
Is a big stamina bar
the only thing you care about?
No, I just want to be careful.
I'm worried about not having
the proper equipment
to handle this.
-We're unarmed.
-It'll be fine, just breathe.
I read the instructions
on how to do this right.
Can you jerks hear me in that
two-for-one bargain tin?
This is a warning!
Take your junk
and get out of here
unless you're ready for a taste
of my Plutonium Buster!
What the hell is
a Plutonium Buster?
It's his finishing move. Crap.
[HATCHI]
Already? That's rude!
I can do that, too.
[ROBBY]
No, you leave!
Unless you want to taste
the explosion
of my Shining Hizakuri Attack!
What does that mean?
The ultimate way
to finish them off!
I just came up with it!
-Looks like they're ready to go!
-Damn it.
[KODAI]
Do what you want!
Nothing's getting past
the Pluto Shield I'm using!
[ROBBY] Well you're not getting
through this Hizakuri Barrier!
Come at me!
[KODAI]
Pluto Saber!
[ROBBY]
Hizakuri Ultimate Buster!
What are they doing
up there, Papa?
I have absolutely no idea.
What's with him?
He hasn't made any actual moves.
If you wanna do this,
then bring it!
If he brings it,
we'll get screwed.
-[KODAI] You don't think...
-[ROBBY] Could it be...
[BOTH]
He's... scared?
Oh, my gosh. Kodai, look!
It's an x-ray of the robot.
There's, like, nothing there.
It's completely hollow!
Seriously? I get it now!
They randomly combine so that
the arms and legs are hollow
which means they'll crumple
like a tin can!
But why would they
make it so big
if it can't even do anything?
[KODAI] Whoever designed it
enjoys having
to combine for power, I guess?
[MORISUGI] Why would anyone
agree to merge with it?
[KODAI]
Maybe theirs doesn't work either
and they find it comforting.
We're lying, too.
We may have
a better machine,
but we don't know
how to use it.
It's whatever.
We've got this!
-[HATCHI] He's coming!
-[ROBBY] Well, grab a weapon!
That's very vague!
♪
[HATCHI]
Uh, see if this works!
♪
[BOTH]
Hizakuri Javelin!
Wow, that looked so cool!
That'll only get us so far!
[KODAI]
I'm calling your bluff!
-Pluto Punch!
-[ROBBY] Dodge him! Dodge him!
[HATCHI]
I don't know how!
[BOTH]
Uh...
[BOTH] Uh...
[KODAI]
Uh. Uh. Uh...
-[HATCHI] Hey.
-[ROBBY] I know.
[BOTH]
Javelin Galactic Thrust!
[KODAI]
We never completed the delivery!
[BOTH screaming]
[ROBBY]
We won!
[HATCHI]
That guy was such a loser.
All right!
She's fixed and ready to go!
Okay, let's do this!
♪
[gasps] Where are you off to?
I wouldn't hold my breath
for Monday
to become Plutoday
if I were you.
But I do think your tourism's
about to get better,
so hang in there.
See you later!
[GIRL]
Please wait!
I didn't have a chance
to write them a check
for their consulting fee.
Eh, doesn't really matter.
♪
[chuckles] Man, I really can be
a heartless bastard.
Oh, well, they'll get over it.
Hey, guys, now that
the repairs are done,
what do you say
we flip a switch
and blast out
of this solar system?
Yeah! Good morning, Universe!
Feed me my future!
You're way too loud
when you get excited.
[MAN 1] What? They left
the Earth's system?
[MAN 2] Judging by the
smart-bracelet's credit history,
they're already gone.
[MAN 1]
This is bad.
Call the Luna Guard immediately!
[MAN 2]
Yes, sir!
[IKKU]
Next time,
"Merfolk on the End
of the Pole."
♪
[inaudible dialogue]