Ugh. Good grief.
[HERMES]
So... what do we do?
[KINO]
That's a good question.
For now?
[HERMES]
Yeah? Go on.
[KINO] Just till I come up
with a better idea...
[HERMES]
You'll do what?
[KINO sighs]
I'm goin' to sleep.
[HERMES]
What?
[KINO] Wake me up
if something happens.
[HERMES] You're kidding.
I thought you had some plan.
[KINO snores softly]
[HERMES]
Kino.
[grunts]
What's up?
[HERMES]
The ground started shaking.
You don't say.
[KINO]
Is it an earthquake?
[HERMES]
Doubt it.
The shaking's light,
but getting steadily stronger.
So then...
[HERMES]
It's simple.
Something's slowly
coming our way.
[KINO]
You think? What's that big?
[HERMES]
Look there!
[rumbling]
[birds squawking]
[KINO gasps]
Well. That answers that.
[HERMES] It's big enough
to be a country.
[KINO] Amazing. I've never
seen anything like this.
[HERMES] Neither have I.
So, what now?
You gonna stick out
your thumb or...?
Yeah, maybe I will.
Might as well see
what happens, right?
[HERMES] Aren't you a little
worried they'll just shoot'cha?
[KINO]
Well, yeah.
It's a gamble... but they
haven't shot us yet.
And I can't think of
a better idea, so...
[INTERCOM VOICE]
Greetings traveler.
Are you seeking entry
into our country?
I am!
[INTERCOM VOICE]
Wait just a moment, please.
[gasps]
[MALE OFFICER A]
Good afternoon, traveler.
I serve as the head
immigration officer here.
I'm also the guide,
the sole policeman, diplomat,
and a few other things.
Our country's unique
in a few ways.
Officials take on
a variety of duties here.
It's nice to meet you.
So, uh, this place is
a country? A real one?
Like, with citizens
and everything?
[MALE OFFICER A] Of course
it is! Albeit a smaller one.
[KINO]
Where is it heading right now?
We're making for the
plains past this valley.
[MALE OFFICER A]
So, what brings you here?
Just looking to sightsee?
Or are you a hopeful immigrant?
Uh. Sightseeing
and recreation is all.
Travelers are always
welcome in this country.
How long do you anticipate
your visit with us to last?
[KINO]
Hmm...
[HERMES]
Hmph.
About five to ten days,
if that's all right with you.
Long as we're here,
would you like to see
how the place works?
I'd appreciate that.
My apologies, Hermes.
We're not use to
motorrads visiting.
Hope you're not uncomfortable.
[HERMES]
No worries, I'm fine.
[MALE OFFICER A]
This is our main reactor.
It creates a vast
amount of steam,
which is then piped
to various generators.
Some electricity goes
to the general populace.
But most is used
to keep us moving.
The process is automated,
we just oversee it.
The difficult part
is maintaining
and sometimes replacing
the drive motors
and caterpillar tracks.
This is our
residential district.
We've prepared a room for you.
I'll take you there now.
[HERMES] So is this country
always moving, then?
Do you settle down
when you find good land?
There are two reasons why our
country is always on the move.
First off, there's the
size of our reactor.
It produces a vast
amount of heat and energy.
Far more than we could expect
our populace to easily consume.
We keep the treads
moving to expend
that energy, and prevent
the country from overheating.
That makes sense.
--[HERMES] I guess.
--[horn honks]
[KINO]
Huh...?
[MALE OFFICER A]
The other reason...
...is one I expect
you'll relate to.
We like this nomadic life.
We enjoy watching beautiful
landscapes come and go.
Why would we stop in one place?
We can see the world
and bring our home with us.
I do relate. Quite a bit.
[KINO]
Gotta say.
I've never seen a country with
this much hot water to spare.
[HERMES]
They recycle that water.
You'll probably be drinking
it at lunch tomorrow.
[KINO] I've had to drink
muddy river water filtered
through rags before,
so why would I get
squeamish about that?
[HERMES]
Good point. Say...
Where'd ya get those pajamas?
[KINO] The sign said
they were for guests.
[HERMES]
Oh.
[KINO]
Mm?
[HERMES] Are we going
over rocks or something?
[HERMES] Huh. I guess
it... ground them down.
[KINO] To think that something
this big can move.
It's amazing.
[sighs]
[HERMES]
Ya think this'll work?
No idea.
Guess we'll find out
in five days.
For now? We sleep.
[HERMES]
Oh, Kino--
We can talk tomorrow, 'kay?
I'm tired. Good night.
Oh, uh. Lights out, please.
[KINO]
A bed with clean sheets.
This is too nice.
[KINO sighs]
[HERMES]
'Morning, Kino.
[KINO]
You woke up before me?
That's weird.
[HERMES] So, what I was
gonna tell you last night...
[KINO]
Wh--?!
[HERMES] ...is if ya go to
sleep with your hair wet,
it'll get kinda crazy.
[MALE OFFICER A]
This is the highest level.
Which makes it the only part
of the country where
you can take in direct sunlight.
[KINO]
Hmm. I see.
[HERMES] Hope no one who
lives here is afraid of heights.
[KINO gasps]
[KINO]
A bird?
No, it isn't.
[HERMES]
Looks like a machine.
That's one of our
country's cameras.
We like to keep a video feed of
our surroundings on display.
Wow.
[MALE OFFICER A]
Hmm?
[HERMES]
Goodness.
[MALE OFFICER A] That's the
price of this lifestyle.
It pains us to leave such a
huge blemish on mother nature,
and I'm sure it's a bother to
others, but it can't be helped.
All who travel leave
their mark behind.
[MALE OFFICER A] We've made
peace with that inevitability,
and we pray that someday,
healthy greenery will grow anew
on all of the lands
we've traversed.
What's that?
[MALE OFFICER A]
Oh, those are cranes.
We use them when
we paint the murals.
Our oldest grade
schoolers paint them
to commemorate their graduation.
Would you mind
if we watched for a bit?
[FEMALE TEACHER A]
No, go right ahead.
[FEMALE TEACHER A] The students
have many discussions
in which they choose
one special sight from
their school years to
capture in a mural.
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Hey, traveler!
[GROUP gasps]
Nice to meet ya!
Hope you like our picture!
Settle down, kids.
The traveler will be
watching us, so focus!
Let's do our best
to make this a fine mural!
And to be safe.
We ready to impress our visitor?
[STUDENTS]
Yes! 'Kay!
[HERMES]
Hmm. I can't really tell
what they're painting
from up here.
Here's the camera's view.
This scene is from a land
that we passed through
more than 1,200 days ago.
It was a truly beautiful place.
I don't suppose you plan
to leave the mural up forever.
No, but we'll take a picture,
and give it a
protective coating.
After that, it'll
decorate the wall
until the next group
of students graduates.
That'll be in 500 days.
A nice tradition.
[MALE OFFICER A] Today, I'll
take you to see our farmlands.
[alarm blares]
[KINO]
Hmm? What's the commotion?
--[HERMES] A fire?
--[MALE OFFICER A] No.
That alarm indicates we've found
another country in our path.
As our sole diplomat, I'll have
to head to the command post.
Would you like to
come and watch?
[KINO]
Mm.
[OPERATORS gasping, murmuring]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Don't be. I'm glad you're here.
Hello there, traveler.
Nice to meet you.
I serve as the president
of this fine country.
Please relax, and enjoy
the proceedings.
[MALE OFFICER A]
This is just-- Wow.
[FEMALE PRESIDENT A]
Rather troubling. Isn't it?
[MALE OFFICER A]
And, they don't seem friendly.
Oh, well.
Good afternoon. I am
this country's diplomat.
We would like to open
discussions with you.
Could you bring
your representative
to the radio please?
[MALE OPERATOR A]
Connected.
Rogue entity, I am
this country's general.
Tell us who you are
and what you want,
and we may yet
avoid hostilities.
[MALE OFFICER A] Ours is
a nation constantly moving.
We ask you to help us pass
through your country.
[gasps, growls]
We would never comply
with such an absurd request.
[HERMES]
Saw that comin'.
[MALE OFFICER A]
Forgive me,
but your country's
border wall stretches
completely across these plains.
There's simply no way for our
country to go around yours.
[MALE GENERAL A]
Yes. Our walls stretch far.
We fought long and hard
to expand our borders.
Now, I'm warning you--
Draw no closer,
or we will be forced to preempt
your aggression with our own.
[MALE OFFICER A sighs]
Deploy the dome.
[MALE OPERATOR B]
Sir.
[MOTHER B, DAUGHTER A gasp]
You ignore me? So be it!
As you are attempting
to invade our country,
we will defend ourselves.
Fire!
--[gasping]
--Direct hit.
[gasps]
[MALE GENERAL A whimpers]
[microphone feedback screeches]
[sighs]
People are so
bothersome sometimes.
Hmm?
Madam President,
I think I see some fields
behind that part of the wall.
We'll crush fewer houses
if we take that route.
I'm relieved to
hear that. Carry on.
As we pass through
your country,
we'll attempt to stay within
the agricultural region.
Please evacuate any
people in our path.
Rest assured,
we will increase our speed
in order to pass through
in less than half a day.
We will never allow
that to happen!
Even if our cannons
can't breach your armor,
you'll never be able to break
through our great wall!
[gasping]
How the hell...
did they do that...?
[gasps]
[HERMES] The Woodsman
has a laser, right?
This one seems
a little stronger.
[MALE OFFICER A]
We have a path now.
That sounds lovely.
Why don't we proceed?
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[gasps]
[growls]
[MALE OFFICER A]
I beg your pardon, General,
but we would like to avoid
endangering any citizens.
Please instruct them
to evacuate.
[MALE GENERAL A]
You selfish bastards!
You're abusing the environment
we were blessed with,
you know that?!
[MALE OFFICER A] Greetings.
We'd rather not run you over.
Please move.
We will not change our path.
[MALE GENERAL A] Just how
ruthless are you people?!
Have you no thought for
the countries you trample?
The pain you cause?
The lives you destroy?!
Damn you! Do you really lack
that bare minimum
of human decency?!
[HERMES]
The man has a point. What now?
Think we should
pretend we didn't hear it.
[HERMES]
Same.
[music plays over speakers]
[music continues]
[MALE OPERATOR B] They've
started shooting missiles
at our outer walls again.
We can take it.
Just keep pressing forward.
[MALE OPERATOR B] Well, they
seem to be aiming for the mural,
so the education board is
asking us to deal with it.
What? They're actually
aiming for it?
What a spiteful thing to do.
Why, the children'll
be devastated.
Should we employ
the laser, Madame?
What's... that?
[MALE OFFICER A] The tool they
use to guide their missiles.
[FEMALE PRESIDENT A] What if
we just destroyed those?
I fear that's impossible.
Given the laser's strength, it
would hit the soldiers as well.
I don't want to cause any more
casualties than necessary.
Continue as planned,
and I'll explain things
to the children later.
[MALE OFFICER A]
Mm-hmm.
[KINO]
A sniper could take them out.
What?
Perhaps, but no one in this
country is that good of a shot.
I'm a decent shot.
Would ya like me
to take care of it?
Open it, please.
Careful out there.
[inhales slowly]
[MALE SOLDIER C yelps]
[MALE SOLDIER D grunts]
[KINO gasps]
[MALE OFFICER A gasps]
[CITIZENS cheering]
[OPERATORS cheering]
[FEMALE PRESIDENT A]
Hmm.
[MALE OFFICER A] We do
apologize for any inconvenience.
Stop right there!
We demand full and complete
restitution! Damn it!
You've infringed on our rights
as a sovereign nation!
Halt, so we can
discuss terms of peace!
[MALE OFFICER A]
I'm afraid we can't do that.
Have a nice day though!
[KINO] With this much power, you
could extort, raid, or conquer
other countries pretty easily
if you wanted to.
Well, yes, I suppose
you're right,
but I really don't feel like
we have any reason to.
This country's doing
just fine as things are,
so why would we risk turning the
rest of the world against us?
Incidents like
yesterday's are tough.
We try to avoid them.
[HERMES] And yet,
you keep on travelling.
[MALE OFFICER A sighs]
Yes.
Every country,
just like every man,
causes some degree of bother
to others merely by existing.
Yet we all must carry on.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[MALE STUDENT A]
Thanks a million!
[FEMALE STUDENT C]
Come back soon, okay?
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Take care!
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Bye-bye!
[HERMES]
I'd say that went pretty well.
[KINO]
Yeah.
[HERMES]
That country was interesting.
And bothersome, too.
[KINO]
Which one?
[HERMES]
Uh. Both, actually.
I thought as much.
[HERMES] I mean,
the country that got bulldozed
only walled off those
plains so they could extort
whoever needed to get through.
They kinda deserved
what they got.
Yeah, it was just too high.
[HERMES]
The border wall? Or their toll?
Actually, I guess both.
If they'd asked me
for something other
than the Woodsman,
maybe offered to let me
work to pass through,
I probably would've
gone with it.
[KINO] Anyway, I wonder where
that country'll end up next.
[HERMES]
Who knows?
I'll tell ya one thing
for sure though.
What's that?
[HERMES] A few hundred
days from now?
They'll have a mural of you
and your rifle on their wall.
That's, uh,
weird to think about.
Kinda embarrassing.
[HERMES]
Does it bother you?
[KINO]
I mean...
No, I guess it's fine.
[KINO]
"Ship Country."