[KINO sighs]
The sun's so warm on my back.
It's starting to make me
feel a little sleepy.
[HERMES]
Don't give in to it.
We'll fall.
And I wouldn't
want that to happen.
It takes way too much effort
to stand you back up after.
[HERMES] So that's why it
always takes you so long.
Here I thought you just
enjoyed watching me suffer.
Hey, it isn't my fault
you weigh so much.
Maybe you should
try going on a diet.
[KINO]
What're those?
[HERMES]
Hmm. Oh, it's a flock of sheep.
You think so?
[KINO]
Yeah, you're right.
[HERMES]
I think they're wild.
[KINO] And it looks
like they're resting.
Not a bad way to live.
Let's try not to bother 'em.
[bleats]
[SHEEP bleating]
[HERMES]
So much for not bothering them.
Yeah.
[HERMES]
Sheesh, talk about cranky!
Are they tryin'
to eat you or what?!
Well, I doubt
they wanna eat you.
[HERMES]
I'm almost offended by that.
C'mon, Kino.
Gun it! Let's move!
Think we're far enough ahead?
[HERMES]
Uh. Kino...?
I've got bad news.
Huh?
[SHEEP bleating]
[gasps]
Gonna have to take
you off-road, okay?
[HERMES]
Keep an eye out for rocks.
[KINO]
What's going on here?
I've had more than my fair
share of scary encounters
with wild animals, but...
Why are these sheep so evil?
[HERMES] You've hunted sheep
for your dinner before,
so technically,
this is just payback.
D'ya think they'll let us go
if I say I'm really sorry?
[HERMES]
I'm goin' with a "no."
We'll just have to keep goin'
til they wear themselves out.
Persistent, aren't they?
[HERMES]
So shoot 'em.
We can have ram steak tonight.
I don't have nearly
enough bullets.
And besides that, I'd rather
not kill unnecessarily.
Let's just run.
[HERMES]
Wait, no. Hit the brakes!
Whew! That was a close one.
[KINO]
What the...?
[HERMES]
It's called a ravine.
They're like canyons
but narrower.
We'd be in real trouble
if we'd fallen down there.
Nice save. Thank you.
[HERMES]
Sure, glad I could help.
But I think we're
in trouble anyway.
[KINO]
Hmm?
--[SHEEP bleating]
--[KINO] I almost forgot.
[HERMES] No point in
trying to put up a fight.
You should just
escape on your own.
Where to?
[HERMES] Down the ravine.
You should be able to climb it.
But it's definitely too
steep for the sheep.
[KINO groans]
[KINO]
And what about you?
I mean, I could
slide you down, but--
[HERMES]
I'm pretty sure I would break.
Just lay me down right here.
They won't hurt me.
[KINO] Hmm... What if
we tried to jump it?
There's still time to go back
and build up some speed.
[HERMES]
There's no way!
I mean if we had a stunt ramp,
maybe, but we don't.
[gasps]
[HERMES]
Hurry up! Start climbing.
And take your bag with you.
[KINO sighs]
[KINO] I promise
I'll come back for you.
[SHEEP bleating]
[KINO grunts]
[KINO growls]
Damn you!
[HERMES]
Don't do it!
These guys
aren't bothering me,
so I guess they target humans.
I think your best bet
it to leave the area
so they lose interest.
Try and climb up
on the other side.
Doesn't look
like that's an option.
[HERMES]
All right.
Then you'll have to walk
upstream till you can
find another way outta there.
Yeah, I'll give that a try.
I'll come back for you
as soon as I'm able.
Hang tight till then.
[HERMES]
Sounds good.
I mean, hey, it's not like I'm
not gonna starve or anything.
So, take your time.
Who knows? Maybe I can talk
some sense into these guys
while I'm waiting for you.
Didn't know you spoke sheep.
Somethin' all motorrads
can do, or just you?
[HERMES]
I don't yet. They'll teach me.
Right. See ya soon.
[KINO] I only have a
few days' worth of food.
Wasn't looking
for trouble with you guys.
But if you're still stalking
me when I get hungry.
[SHEEP bleating]
Man, you're persistent.
And annoying, too.
What's your deal?
Don't you have
a home to go back to?
[KINO]
Goodnight.
[KINO groans softy]
[KINO]
Hmm?
[KINO gasps]
[KINO] Whoa. I guess
he couldn't escape.
[KINO]
It's just one man.
He wasn't able to
see the ravine in time.
Drove his car right into it.
After crashing,
he prob'ly climbed out
of it to try and escape.
But the sheep were closing in.
[KINO]
He had a broken shin.
He must've realized he had
no chance of outrunning them.
[KINO]
Oh.
Come on...
[engine chugs weakly, starts]
[KINO]
It worked...
I'm glad you taught me
how to use these, Master.
Thanks.
[KINO] I'll be making
use of your pistol.
And your vehicle.
I owe you my gratitude.
[SHEEP bleating]
[HERMES]
Huh...?
Ohhh...!
Kino!
[SHEEP bleating]
Don't worry!
I'm getting you out of here!
[HERMES]
Thanks!
Where did you get that thing?!
[FEMALE SHEEP B bleats]
[KINO]
I found it by the ravine.
[HERMES]
All right, well, good work!
Why don't you drive that
thing to the next country
and call for backup?
I don't think so.
[SHEEP bleating]
[KINO]
Think about it.
There's no guarantee
they'd be willing to come
this far out just to help us.
[HERMES] That's true,
but what chance do we have
of escaping like this?!
[KINO]
We won't know unless we try.
Hey, Hermes. You're not
leaking fuel, are you?
Those sheep didn't
damage you at all?
[HERMES]
Nope, we just cuddled.
[KINO]
All right...
All right!
[HERMES]
Goodness, Kino.
You sure know how
to put on a show.
Here goes.
[SHEEP bleat loudly]
I didn't start this fight.
[bleats]
[gunshots, various bleating]
[HERMES]
Whew. No mercy at all.
[SHEEP bleating]
[KINO]
Hermes!
[HERMES]
Welcome back.
[KINO]
Good to be back.
[HERMES]
Pretty clever plan.
So... What now?
--[SHEEP bleating]
--[KINO] Hold on for a sec.
[HERMES]
Huh...?
Huh?
[KINO grunts]
[HERMES]
Huh?!
[KINO grunts]
[HERMES]
Huh?!
[KINO grunts]
[HERMES]
Kino, you're... not serious?
Are you?
You're the one who said
we could jump it with a ramp.
[HERMES]
I said maybe.
And I was obviously joking!
[KINO]
Too late to turn back now.
Ready?
[HERMES]
Kino, this is cruel!
You know, if I didn't need you
to get outta this predicament,
I would hand you division notes.
[KINO]
Divorce papers?
[HERMES]
Yeah, those!
--Okay, fine. Let's go.
--[KINO] Roger.
[HERMES] Accelerate gently, lean
forward, and keep me straight!
That's a lot to ask.
[HERMES]
That is a crazy brave sheep.
Y'know if you're gonna eat one,
it should be one like that.
You'll absorb its strength.
[BRAVE SHEEP bleating]
This one's for...
this gun's owner!
[KINO]
Hermes. Let's go!
[HERMES]
Jeez. Screw it! I don't care!
Here we go!
[HERMES]
Oh, no, no, no, no-no--
Oh, yeah!
[SHEEP bleating]
[KINO chuckles]
[HERMES grunts]
[HERMES, KINO scream]
[HERMES]
Kino... You alive?
I'm fine, not even injured.
Didn't mean to fall, though.
Sorry.
I did everything you said
except keeping you straight.
[HERMES]
Hey. All's well that te--
Ends well.
--Heh. I'm glad ya screwed up.
--And why's that?
[HERMES]
Because thanks to that fall,
I took the brunt of
the impact on my side.
If not for that, I think
I'd've taken some damage.
A blown-out tire at least.
There's a chance that
my frame would've busted.
[HERMES]
Hey. Come back!
Stand me up!
[KINO]
Why'd you fight so hard?
Normal predators
would've given up.
Do you hate humans that much?
[KINO]
We made it.
[HERMES]
Somehow.
[INSPECTOR A] Whoa, I haven't
seen a traveler in ages.
Like, literally.
No one's entered the country
through this gate in years.
My job was gettin' kinda lonely.
[KINO]
You don't say.
[HERMES] What do you think
this country'll be like?
[KINO] As long as they
have beds, I don't care.
[HERMES]
Yeah. You do look tired.
[KINO]
The second I get in there,
I'm jumping into the first bed
I see, and passing out.
[INSPECTOR A]
Oh, yeah. Traveler.
Since you came through
the eastern plains, tell me.
Did you run into any sheep?
[KINO]
I sure did. Quite a few of them.
[INSPECTOR A]
Truly? That's wonderful news!
See, they were originally
bred in our country.
We'd have them fight
for entertainment.
You bred those
sheep for pit fights?
Yeah, same as
you'd do with dogs.
We would pit a pair of sheep
against each other in the ring.
Then, as they fought by butting
heads, we'd watch and take bets.
It used to be a very
popular past time
for the citizens
of this country.
We used selective
breeding to create strong,
courageous sheep with extremely
aggressive dispositions.
From what I've heard, they
were borderline bloodthirsty!
[INSPECTOR A]
But...
But what?
Proponents of animal rights
put a stop to all that.
So we took those sheep out
to the eastern plains
and released them.
I'm excited to hear
they're doing so well.
Once I'm off work, I'll have
to let the other citizens
know the good news.
If you two would
please follow me.
I'll show you inside.
[KINO sighs]
[HERMES]
What'll you do?
Tell them?
[KINO] I know
that nothing's certain,
but I'm pretty sure
this is the nicest spot
for a hammock in the world.
Wow. This is perfect.
[HERMES]
You know, I'm a motorrad.
Not a tea table.
By the way, you're gonna
regret not taking advantage
of this perfect riding weather.
You're being wasteful.
[KINO]
I disagree.
There's only one way to
truly take advantage of
weather like this.
And that's with a nap.
[HERMES sighs] I hope you melt
right into that hammock.
[KINO giggles]
That doesn't sound so bad.
My journey's at an end now.
I'm goin' to sleep.
Right here.
[HERMES]
Yup! Roger that!
Kino's journey ends right here!
Wait, if your journey's over,
then what'll I do?
[KINO]
Whatever you want.
I, for one,
will be taking a nap.
[HERMES]
'Kay.
And what about once you wake up?
[KINO]
When I wake?
I'll start my journey.
[HERMES]
"Start" it? You lost me.
[KINO]
It's how you think of it.
Know what I mean?
If I decide this is the end of
my journey, that'll be that.
The journey ends with
me taking a nice nap.
And once I wake up
from that nap,
if I should happen to decide
to set out on a journey...
Well, that will be the start
of a brand-new journey.
[HERMES]
I still don't get it.
[KINO]
It's like this.
You can change your situation.
just by changing the way
you think about it.
[HERMES]
So?
[KINO]
So, that's it.
[HERMES]
What?
[KINO]
Forget it.
Thinking about
complex stuff like that
makes me feel exhausted.
[HERMES] Okay,
all I'm hearing is that you
really wanna take this nap.
[KINO] Mm-hm.
And so, my journey ends.
If this were
a serial radio drama,
then this would be
the last episode.
The grand finale.
[HERMES]
Gotcha.
[KINO] We'll start the
sequel when I wake up.
So hang tight until then.
[HERMES]
No problem.
Can do. In fact,
it's all I can do.
Can't move on my own, after all.
[KINO chuckles]
Don't worry.
I can't move
without you, either.
Not with all the luggage
I've got you carrying.
[HERMES]
Well, be sure you wake up.
Wake up, and start
your new journey.
Or else.
[KINO]
Sure thing.
Well. Goodnight, Hermes.
[HERMES]
Sleep tight, Kino.
[HERMES] You know,
the journey we just finished?
It was lots of fun.
[KINO groans softly]
[HERMES]
Kino. You awake?
[KINO grunts]
Yeah. I'm up.
[KINO]
Ah! There.
Now then.
Let's get this journey started.