[HERMES] Shouldn't you be
chopping wood right now?
[KINO]
Shh!
Better luck next time.
[gunshot]
[HERMES]
Something the matter?
[HERMES] You look like you're
about to eat a bag of sand.
Oh, no.
I mean the sausage
is definitely a little cold,
but that doesn't hurt
the flavor too much.
I was just...
[HERMES]
Just what?
[KINO] Thinkin' about
our time with Master.
[HERMES] Hmm...
That's unusual. Which time?
[KINO] One of the times she got
the jump on me during training.
[HERMES]
Why that?
[KINO]
Good question.
Oh. Right, it's 'cause
of the sausage.
After that, we ate
some exactly like this
and she told me a travel story.
[HERMES] Like from back
when she was young?
[KINO]
Yeah.
I think I remember it
being about a country
with a tall clock tower.
It actually might be
pretty close by.
[PARTNER]
Master?
[MASTER]
What is it?
Well, we'll reach
the next country pretty soon.
Once we do, I think we should
sell the rest of the gems there.
[MASTER]
Hmm.
Look, we're running
dangerously low
on food and fuel.
So we're gonna need some cash.
That, or something
we can trade more easily.
You know, like liquor.
Yeah, you're right. That said...
Make sure to sell high, right?
Don't worry. I'm aware.
[PARTNER]
Hey, this country seems nice.
Looks like their technology's
fairly advanced, too.
In a place like this?
Gems are worth a fortune.
[MASTER] I see an awful
lot of police officers.
[PARTNER]
Yeah, same.
This could be
one of those countries
with a military police force
that doubles as an army.
What I've seen
of these countries,
it's important not to
let your guard down.
Bad public order?
Actually, the crime rate
is quite low here.
I'd bet.
As long as you
don't count the crimes
of the people in power, that is.
Roger that.
Why don't you take it
easy at the hotel,
n' let me handle this?
I'll be back by lunchtime.
[MASTER sighs]
[POLICEMAN C]
So there you have it.
Your lover was found in
possession of illegal drugs
and promptly arrested.
[MASTER]
I understand.
Though, I should make
one small correction.
The man is not my lover.
We simply met on the road.
Forgive me for assuming.
[MASTER]
Where is he right now?
He's in an underground
detention cell, sweetheart.
You have an underground
level, too?
This police force seems
very well-funded.
[POLICEMAN C] Oh, yeah, this
building used to be the palace,
back when our
country had a king.
There's so much history here
that we decided to preserve
the clock tower,
as a cultural monument.
It's currently
a shared headquarters
for multiple branches
of government.
But, everyone knows that
we're the ones in charge here.
So this is really
just the police HQ.
[laughs]
That's good to know.
Things are just
as I expected, then.
[POLICEMAN C]
Come again?
I do understand the situation,
but as you can clearly see,
I'm a traveler.
I wonder if you'd
be willing to show mercy,
and use your authority to issue
exile as his punishment.
[POLICEMAN C]
Hmm... 'N what'll you give me?
I can go this high.
No. That pittance is
out of the question.
You should get out of this
country while ya can, though.
I'll do you a favor and keep
quiet about your attempt
to bribe a police officer.
In that case,
I will gladly do just that.
This man is little more
than a stranger to me,
so it's not like I
owe him any loyalty.
If he committed a crime
and got arrested,
there's nothing I can do.
I'll leave him behind.
[POLICEMAN C]
Wise decision.
I don't suppose you'd permit me
to give him a final farewell?
[POLICEMAN C]
'Fraid not.
Possession of drugs
is a serious crime.
Please, sir.
I would appreciate any
assistance you could offer.
[POLICEMAN C]
Ah-- Hmm...
Sis, you came!
I knew that you would rescue me!
How many times have I told you
not to do something illegal?
[PARTNER] Wait, what?
I was falsely accused!
Perhaps you can prove that
when you face your trial here.
I'm overdue in another
country right now,
so... I can't really
wait for you.
[PARTNER]
Oh, come on!
I've never so much
as touched an illegal drug,
let alone tried to bring
'em into another country.
[POLICEMAN D laughs]
Tough break, punk.
Maybe this'll teach ya to keep
a closer eye on your pockets.
After all, you never know
what might slip into 'em.
[laughs]
One last thing.
You know that super-secret
case I have that I've never
revealed the contents of?
It's yours now.
Use it to fund
your travels, okay?
And don't let it
go for cheap, either!
When I bought the thing, it cost
me 434 silver coins, no less!
[MASTER] Hmph. I'll do as
you say. Thanks for the gift.
[PARTNER]
Hmph.
[POLICEMAN C]
Visit's over.
[MASTER]
Right.
[PARTNER sobs]
[POLICEMAN E]
These are the man's belongings.
What about the gems he had?
Or the money he was going
to exchange them for?
Ah.
Well, we assumed it was the
capital he used to purchase
those illegal substances,
so we went ahead
and confiscated
all that as evidence.
Of course you did.
[MASTER]
A silencer. Plastic knife.
Thin wire cord.
And poison capsules?
Just about every tool
an assassin might need.
Good grief. What was this
kid doing before I found him?
[tower bell rings]
About that woman
you had us tail.
I'm told that she left
the country peacefully.
That so?
See to it that she
never gets in again.
That woman was trouble,
I could tell.
Right.
By the way, sir, our director
is currently dining with
a few statesmen,
but... he gave me a message.
He says you did an excellent
job, and your cut's been sent.
[POLICEMAN C] Good. You all
did a fine job as well.
Thank you, very much, sir.
What should we do
with that man now?
[POLICEMAN C] We could just
exile him and be done with it,
but if we put him to trial,
the state could get 20 years
of hard labor out of him.
It's a tough call,
so I might have to
roll some dice.
[MASTER]
All right.
Ahh, not bad.
Night vision.
Now this is a handy toy.
[yawns] Maybe I'll have
time for a quick nap.
[MASTER]
Now then.
--[MAN A] What?
--[bang]
[MAN A]
Ah, this is nice...
--[MAN A] So warm!
--[bang]
[MAN A]
Huh...?
[police sirens blaring]
Stay in your homes!
[yawns]
[POLICEMAN H]
Run! You see those fires?!
Someone planted bombs
around the building!
It's gonna collapse,
let's get out of here!
[POLICEMAN I]
Should we release the prisoner?!
[POLICEMAN H]
Hell no! Forget about him!
--You wanna die in here?
--Like I said,
I knew you'd save me.
Thanks, Master.
Yeah. You know you're
a crap apprentice, right?
Guess that's fair.
Sorry I let my guard down.
Say, what'd ya think of my toys?
Were they helpful?
[MASTER]
Yeah, to some extent.
Once you finish changing,
we're getting out of here.
What's the plan after?
[MASTER]
Whole country's on alert,
so we can't escape it yet.
[PARTNER]
I hear ya. So what can we do?
What would we do
if it were up to you?
If it were up to me?
I'd probably look for
somewhere obscure to hide.
You know, like a random attic
or a sewer pipe
we could hole up in.
Then, after three days or so,
once they've worn
themselves out lookin' for us,
we could either try
and sneak out of here,
or launch a quick,
surprise offensive.
And hopefully shoot our way out.
You're on the
right track at least,
but not quite there.
Oh, yeah?
[MASTER] Three days is about the
right length of time to wait.
But instead of hiding...
We'll what?
[MASTER]
We'll make a scene.
Every now and then
it's important to test
your abilities to the fullest.
We wouldn't want to get rusty.
I bet the view from the top
of this tower is lovely.
Yeah.
[HERMES] Whoa. So what
happened after that?
Well, as she predicted,
the police armory
was in that same building.
Thanks to the
commotion that she caused,
all the police who would've
guarded it were gone.
So, the two of them
leisurely loaded up a cart
with weapons and ammunition.
[HERMES]
That is terrifying!
Talk about adding
fools to the fire!
[KINO]
You know what?
That kinda works.
[HERMES]
So, uh...
You gonna finish
the story, or what?
[KINO]
Yeah.
Then they found
a provisions storeroom,
and loaded the cart with as much
food and water as they could.
[HERMES]
And then? And then?
[KINO] They took it up
to the highest floor.
[HERMES]
The highest floor?
But they'd be trapped, right?
[KINO]
Escaping wasn't quite the goal.
Instead, Master and her
apprentice climbed
to the clock tower roof.
The highest point
in the country,
and prepared to
make their stand.
They used explosives
to cut the cable on
the only elevator, which
made it to drop to the basement.
[HERMES micmics explosion]
So later,
when the police finally finished
restoring order to the city
and tried to go
back to their HQ.
[HERMES]
Ka-bang?
[KINO]
Yup.
[HERMES]
So they killed them one by one?
[KINO] No. That's what
was amazing about Master.
She didn't kill any of 'em.
[HERMES]
No? What do you mean?
[KINO]
She was an incredible marksman.
So, she aimed to
incapacitate without killing.
Shot their knees
and shins, mostly.
[HERMES]
Ah!
So when more police came
to help the wounded ones,
she could shoot them, too.
Classic sniper tactic.
--Nope, she let them be.
--[HERMES] Huh?
When people came to
help the wounded,
she just let them go.
She also didn't shoot
anyone who ran away.
[HERMES]
Why not? What for?
[KINO] I asked her
the exact same question,
and she tried to have
me answer it myself,
but I couldn't figure it
out till she got further
into the story.
[HERMES]
I give up, too, then.
For now, at least.
Go ahead.
She knew full well
that the two of them
wouldn't stand a chance
of breaking through
that gate on their own.
So instead of trying to escape,
she sat tight where she was
and waited for the country
to open the gate 'n
bring her a car.
Which they later did.
[HERMES]
Oh, I get it now.
[KINO] By holing up
in that clock tower,
they made it impossible for
half of the government
to get to their jobs.
And that put a lot of
pressure on the police
to do something about it.
But--
[HERMES]
They'd be shot.
[KINO] Yup. I don't think
she aimed for the legs
out of any compassion, either.
It was devious.
Since none of the police
were actually killed,
they didn't feel the need to
avenge their fellow officers.
[HERMES]
That does make sense.
Oh, and the apprentice
they imprisoned
on false charges?
He got really into it.
Every single officer he shot
went straight to the hospital.
[HERMES]
Ah...
Then they wrote
the police a letter.
Put it in a nice envelope
and dropped it down.
They used all of the police's
own equipment, of course.
[MASTER]
"To whom it may concern.
Hello down there!
How goes it?
The winds are getting
somewhat chilly up here,
but we'll manage.
We hope that you and
all the other officers
are enjoying
good health."
[PARTNER]
"To the point:.
This pair of scoundrels
have accepted your tower
as our grave. We shall
defend this position to the end.
We'll fight till
our bows are broken,
and our arrows spent.
Wreaking all the havoc
we can in the meantime!
These are two alleged
drug traffickers
you'll never take alive!"
[FEMALE REPORTER] "Because
we're just a pair of determined
amateurs, we humbly
ask for your leadership
and encouragement
through the trying days
that are surely ahead of us.
Thanks so much."
And that concludes
the clock tower
occupier's letter.
The various directors
have demanded
that the police
respond in force.
For his part,
the director of police
has promised to launch an
assault on the tower
this evening.
I guess we can
take it easy till nightfall.
[HERMES]
Kinda dumb he told the news.
Yeah. Master said
the same thing to me.
The broadcasts were
a big help, apparently.
They always knew what
the police had planned.
[HERMES] So, how many days
did they hole up there?
Three days and three nights.
[POLICEMAN C clears throat]
Can you idiots hear me?
We have the tower surrounded.
There's nowhere to run.
You'll die up there
as you wished.
Or, if you don't die
up there, we're gonna
hang you after dragging
you through the streets.
[PARTNER]
Hmph.
[POLICEMAN C]
So preparse yourselv--
[POLICE gasping]
[POLICEMAN C]
Bandits!
Your position up
there is untenable.
But if you come down
quietly, and surrender.
We are now willing
to spare your lives!
[POLICEMAN C]
Heh.
[POLICEMEN whimpering]
[POLICEMAN C] Do you people have
anything you'd like to say?
If so, we'll graciously
hear you out.
--[gunshots]
--[POLICEMEN gasping]
[POLICEMAN C] Good morning,
esteemed travelers.
I come bearing a message.
If you two wish to leave
this country, we will gladly
permit you to do so,
and have thus,
for your convenience,
provided you with this truck.
[POLICEMEN scream]
Huh?
[POLICEMAN C]
From the bottom of our hearts.
We earnestly request that you
stop holding our tower hostage
and leave this country.
--[rapid gunfire]
--[POLICEMEN screaming]
Make it stop... Please...
We give up...
If you feel that
strongly about it.
I suppose you could persuade us
to leave your country
instead of dying in this tower.
[gasps]
D'you really mean it?
[MASTER]
Depends. What'll you give me?
Uh...
I said, "What will you give me?"
[POLICEMAN C]
Ah...
Let's see...
How about the
amount I've written here?
[POLICEMAN C]
We can go higher!
So yeah.
Apparently, that's
how it all ended.
[HERMES]
She's a demon.
[KINO] And thus, Master extorted
cash from their government,
and they departed
the country safely.
[HERMES] And they
lived happily ever after.
I enjoyed that story.
[gasps]
[HERMES]
Look, there it is.
[KINO]
Perfect timing.
[tower bell chimes]
[HERMES]
It's octagonal.
This must be the spot.
[KINO]
And there's the old clock tower.
[BOY A]
Mama, look!
[laughter]
[HERMES]
Kino. Over here.
[KINO]
Hmm?
[HERMES]
There's a plaque.
What does it say?
Uh, something about
the government being corrupted.
[OLD MAN A]
I can fill you in.
[KINO]
Hmm?
That plaque was erected
in honor of a pair of
brave heroes who
saved our country
and gave the people liberty.
[HERMES]
Brave heroes, huh?
I'm a traveler,
but I'm curious about
your country's history.
Would you mind
telling me more about it?
Sure, I'd be happy to.
A couple decades ago,
when I was still a young man,
the government of this country
was rife with corruption.
[HERMES]
Oh? Go on, please.
[OLD MAN A] Our standing
police force was guilty of
the lion's share of wrongdoing.
And no one had the courage to
stand up to them on behalf
of the people's
right to liberty.
Not till those travelers came.
[HERMES]
What did they do?
[OLD MAN A]
They rallied the will
of all of us citizens
behind them.
And then they petitioned
the government to reform.
Did it in this very building.
[HERMES]
Incredible.
[OLD MAN A]
After that,
our politicians and policeman,
deeply moved by
the passion of
those brave souls...
Why, they grew ashamed
of their wicked deeds.
And they vowed to do better
from that moment forward.
[OLD MAN A]
Thanks to those travelers,
our country is now both
pleasant and prosperous.
We're living happily ever after.
[GIRL A] Hey, Grandpa,
why do your stories always end
with "happily ever after"?
I see.
So that's what this
plaque commemorates?
Yes, that's correct.
The event is now recorded in
our country's history textbooks
as the "tale of the two
travelers of justice."
I'm sorry to change the subject,
but what happened
to your left leg?
I noticed that a lot
of the elderly in this country,
the men in particular,
seem to be using canes.
Well, men can be
rather reckless,
and accidents happen.
[GIRL gasps]
[HERMES]
So what do you think?
Did he lie to us?
You already know that, right?
It's obvious.
[HERMES] Heh. But what
an optimistic country.
It's good to think positively.
Sure, within reason.
[HERMES] But what do
you think would happen
if Master visited again?
--Huh?!
--[tires squeal]
[HERMES]
Don't worry. She's not here now.
[KINO]
Right. 'Course not.
[HERMES]
So, face forward and drive.
[KINO]
Yeah. Will do.
"Country of Radio Waves."