[KINO] This might
not make sense, but...
[HERMES]
Don't worry about it. Go ahead.
[KINO] Sometimes I...
wonder if I'm a hopeless fool.
Underhanded, petty...
All the things I don't wanna be.
I'm not sure why, but...
Sometimes, that's how I see it.
Sometimes, that's the
only way I see it.
But in times like those,
I just have to look
around at the world.
The life flourishing around me.
Just by seeing these wonders,
I become wholly beautiful.
These things are precious to me.
I want to learn about them,
as much as I can.
That's probably why
I keep traveling.
[KINO]
I know this life won't be easy.
There's sadness and pain
on the road ahead.
But I don't think that
means I should quit.
[HERMES]
Hmm?
[KINO]
I like traveling. It's fun.
Even if people try to kill me.
Even if I have to
kill them to stay alive.
That doesn't change
my mind about this.
Besides...
[HERMES]
Besides?
[KINO]
I can stop anytime I want.
So, I might as well keep going.
That make sense?
[HERMES]
Frankly? Not so much.
[KINO]
It doesn't have to.
[HERMES]
No?
[KINO]
To be honest...
...maybe I just think
I know why I do this.
Maybe I'm just another lost kid.
Maybe I'm travelling,
so I can figure all that out.
[HERMES]
Hmm...
[KINO]
Well... I'm going to sleep now.
We've got a long way
to go tomorrow.
[yawns]
Goodnight, Hermes...
[HERMES]
Goodnight, Kino.
[HERMES] So, are we
in the next country yet?
Don't worry,
we're almost there now.
[HERMES] The last time you said
that, we were two days out.
[KINO] That's what "almost
there" meant in that country.
[HERMES]
Uh-huh.
Oh?
[HERMES]
Hey, it's a horse.
[KINO]
Looks like someone's there.
Let's stop. Say hi.
[MAN A]
Hmm?
Hey there.
--Good afternoon.
--[HERMES] Hello.
Are you two from
the country up ahead?
No, but I'm on my way
there right now.
Hey, so am I!
Isn't that a nice coincidence?
Say... how 'bout you
carry half my stuff?
--'Fraid I can't do that.
--[HERMES] Same.
Aw, man, and here
I thought you were friendly.
[KINO] I could've said yes
and then made off with it.
[MAN A]
Hmph.
I'd get there first, with plenty
of time to sell it all, too.
Pfft. I guess.
But, hey, forget that.
What've you heard
about this country?
I don't know too much about it,
but someone told me
that people are
very polite there.
[laughs]
What kind of idiot
told you that?!
They couldn'ta been
further off the mark.
Hmph.
I'll tell ya what I know.
In that country,
you can kill people.
[HERMES]
Wait. What do you mean?
They don't have any laws against
murder--it's legal there.
Though, for some reason,
it's still a crime to steal.
So is that the reason why
you're wanting to go there?
[MAN A]
Yeah! I'm startin' a life there.
In the country
where I was born,
law and order
were stupidly high,
and everyone got
along out of fear.
Couldn't even try
startin' a damn fight
without getting locked up.
That's why I up and left.
[HERMES] So, what about
once you've moved?
[MAN A]
Hmm? Who knows?
Maybe I'll try and
find work there.
Ooh!
Or maybe I'll find someone
I don't like 'n kill 'em.
I can be myself in this place--
that's what matters.
[HERMES]
Oh.
[MAN A sighs]
Anyway.
That's not all I heard
about this place.
They say Regel
himself lives there.
--Who's that?
--[HERMES] Don't know him.
You guys must be from
deep in the sticks.
Regel is a mass murderer.
'N he's just about world famous.
He headed up a cell of
bandits in the big country
south of here. Some folks
called him a terrorist.
Regel got caught once.
But naturally,
he broke out of his cell
before they could hang him.
That went down
a few decades ago.
And nobody's
heard about him since.
Which tells me that he must've
made off to this country.
I bet he's been living out
his days killing freely there.
Surely, he's carved out
his own little empire.
A guy like me
could learn from him.
Thanks for sharing.
We'll be heading out now.
[MAN A]
What?! C'mon!
Aw, fine. You're no fun
at all, ya know that?
[engine revvs]
Hey. You really won't
help me carry anything?
Nah, it is your stuff after all.
I'm sure you can manage it.
[MAN A]
Hmph.
[gasps]
[HERMES]
Think that's it?
[KINO]
Hmm. Probably.
[HERMES] Might be
dangerous if he was right.
Possibly.
[HERMES]
Got Cannon ready?
[KINO]
Of course.
[HERMES]
And the Woodsman?
[KINO]
Always.
[HERMES]
In a good headspace?
For now, at least, yeah.
Well, let's go.
[INSPECTOR A]
Just a three day stay, is it?
And that motorrad you're on,
you're bringing it, too?
Yes, if that's all right.
I should tell you--
Murder isn't prohibited
by law in this country.
Killing is legal. Be you
a citizen, or just a visitor.
Everyone within our borders is
free to kill anyone they please
regardless of
circumstance or motive.
Do you understand that?
[KINO]
Yes.
[INSPECTOR A]
And despite that,
you genuinely still
wish to enter?
[INSPECTOR A]
Very well. Go ahead.
[TOWNSFOLK chatting]
[HERMES]
Hmm...
[KINO]
What a strange country.
[HERMES]
Hmm? Seems pretty normal to me.
[KINO]
Yeah. It does seem normal.
The streets are clean and
full of friendly people.
I hardly see any police.
The stores don't have
especially heavy shutters.
They're even nice to travelers
here, and the food's good, too.
[HERMES]
So what?
[KINO] By all appearances,
this is an orderly society.
Doesn't that seem odd?
[HERMES]
Oh, I get it.
You were hoping to see gangs
of ruffians strutting around.
Guys knifing each other over
women in the bars maybe.
Or like a mean stray dog with
a human hand in its mouth.
Yeah, that would've been great.
Too bad.
Come on. I didn't want that.
I just thought it
seemed likely is all.
[KINO sighs]
[HERMES]
Goodnight, Kino.
All right, Hermes.
Do you feel like wakin' up yet?
[KINO] I'll come and get you
once I finish up breakfast.
Sound good? Then we can
check out the country.
[MALE CLERK A]
There's a little extra for ya.
Everyone oughta give travelers
a bit on the house.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Anything else I can do for ya?
[KINO]
Think I'm all set.
Pardon, but do you keep
that to deter thieves?
[laughs] No, I've never
had a robber in my store.
That there...
...is what I use to kill people.
[HERMES]
Does it get used often?
That is the question, isn't it?
You never know when
until it's time.
That's why I keep it near.
[WAITRESS A] You won't find
this anywhere but here.
Please enjoy.
[HERMES]
Kino?
[KINO] Life certainly
is full of challenges.
[giggles]
Well. We'd best be off.
--[HERMES] How was it?
--[WOMAN C] Glad we came.
[KINO]
No regrets.
[GRANDMA A]
Pardon, but are you a traveler?
I suppose you must be.
[laughs]
[KINO]
Hello there.
We come here after
a callisthenic dance group
we're part of that
meets twice a week.
If you want to keep yourself
going strong at our age,
you have to make exercise
just another part
of the routine, you see.
--That makes sense.
--[WAITRESS] What can I get you?
[GRANDMA A]
I'll have the usual, dear.
[GRANDMA B] Yes,
I'll take the usual as well.
The tea here is always
so good, isn't it?
[REGEL]
Traveler.
Can I tempt you to try some of
this country's special dessert?
It would be a tale to
add to your collection.
And for our part, we'd
love to hear stories
from beyond the wall.
I wish I could.
[HERMES]
But it's too late--
just finished
polishing one off.
Ah, that's too bad.
Tell you what. How 'bout
tomorrow, during morning tea?
[HERMES] Hey, Kino.
You gonna eat another one?
Won't be hard with two of us.
Planning to stay in
our country for a while,
or just passing through?
That. I'll be setting
out after this.
Ah, fair enough.
From the sound of things, you've
been through a great number
of countries already. How far
will this journey take you?
[KINO]
I'm not sure.
Ahh. Then perhaps your
motorrad might know?
[HERMES chuckles]
No way.
[REGEL]
Hmm... Well, then, hey--
If you've no clear destination,
why not settle in this country?
If I may say so,
I think a person like you
would fit in well.
[HERMES]
A person like what?
A person who is able
and willing to kill.
Ah, well. Seems I
misjudged, forgive me.
Thanks for the company,
and for the treat.
I was happy to hear all
your stories from the road.
So, no, thank you.
--[HERMES] You're too kind.
--It was good to meet you.
[MAN A]
Ha! I found you.
Yeah, that's right! You!
Stupid brat with the motorrad!
[KINO]
What do you want?
[MAN A] I want you to grab your
stuff and put it on the ground.
[KINO]
Why would I do that?
[MAN A] Your travel gear
must be pretty heavy, right?
I'm "offering"
to relieve you of it.
I'll make use of what I can, the
rest I plan to sell for cash.
That'll help fund
my new lifestyle.
No, thank you.
You don't get it?
If you turn me down...
I'll fill you with holes...
...and take it after.
So you've joined
this country, then?
As of this morning,
I'm now a bonified citizen.
May be, but you
don't act like one.
Huh?! And why
should I give a damn?
You givin' up or not?
I decline your offer.
Well, that's all
there is to say, then.
[KINO]
Hermes.
Sorry, but I might
need your help here.
[HERMES] It's fine.
Just patch the holes up later.
What're you yappin' about?!
[gasps]
Get up, ya damn coward!
You're not even gonna draw?!
What, are those pistols
on your hips just a bluff?!
[HERMES]
Fair question.
Fine, if you're not gonna
fight then stay still.
And I'll make your death clean!
[MAN A grunts]
[gasps]
[screams]
Guh! Shit!
God damn it all!
[grunts, screamas]
Shit! Oh, shit!
Who shot me?!
Huh?!
[gasps]
[footsteps]
What is this...?
What's wrong with you people?!
Huh?!
--[gunshot]
--[gasps]
[GRANDMA A] A fine shot,
but you need to be careful
since we're all in a circle.
Imagine if you missed and hit
one of us. Why, that would be
--just awful, wouldn't it?
--What the hell? Give me my--
[screams]
[wailing, grunting]
You shot me again...
Shit, why? Why'd you do that?!
Hey! Why in the hell'd
you get in my way?!
[REGEL]
I think you know.
[gasps]
What you were doing was wrong.
Why's that?!
What's so wrong with it?!
I don't know where you
come from, but in this land,
the country I call my home,
murder is not permitted,
nor is its attempt allowed
to go without punishment.
Shut your lying mouth!
The whole reason I came
to this piece of shit place
is 'cause I heard
that murder's legal here!
You're right about that much.
It's no crime.
And that is why all of us
are gathered here today.
--Hear, hear!
--Exactly right!
Couldn't have said it better.
[gasps]
What the hell are
you people talking about?!
You see, in this country,
those who have killed another,
those who have tried
to kill another,
and those who are trying to kill
another,
are instead killed themselves,
by the people united.
You've gotta be kidding me!
That doesn't make sense!
[REGEL]
Murder's legal here.
That's the reason
you came, is it not?
This little tradition of ours
falls well within the rules.
[MAN A pants]
[growls]
Screw you!
Who do you think you are?!
[REGEL]
Who am I?
Oh, no one special,
that's for sure.
Just an average citizen.
A nice old man who goes
by the name of Regel.
[gasps]
Sorry to do this, but you see...
...you're dangerous.
[MAN A]
Wait... Regel?
[grunts, rasps]
[MAN D] It's never easy...
killing another.
Safe travels to you.
Thanks. Uh...
[gasps]
[HERMES]
Hey, it's a horse.
Yeah. Looks like
someone's there.
Let's stop. Say hi.
Hey.
Afternoon.
[HERMES]
Hello.
Tell me. Are you from
the country up ahead?
Nah. I'm travelling right now.
Although, my friend
and I did spend
the last few days
visiting there.
I see.
Could I... ask you something?
What is it?
Thing is... I rode a
very long way to try to
get to that country,
because I heard it was safe.
Do you know? Is it true?
Yeah, no doubt about that.
[MAN E sighs]
Though to what extent,
might depend on
your perception of things.
My home country...
It was not a good place.
I had to fight
just to stay alive,
and I killed a lot
of people there.
Decent men that just wanted
to live normal lives.
I never want to kill again.
I want to live somewhere safe.
In that case...
you'll like it there.
Even if it seems a bit wrong
at first, stick it out.
Really? Thank you.
[KINO]
Well... We'll be on our way.
Oh. I wanted to know
one last thing.
Uh... Well... Forget it.
That's a weird thing
to ask about.
I'm heading there now--
I'll find out soon.
Farewell, then.
[MAN E]
Yeah.
I wonder if it's true
what they say...
...that in that country,
they serve mountains
of crepes for dessert.
[HERMES]
Hey, Kino.
What's up?
[HERMES] I've been meaning
to ask this for a while now.
Why only spend three days
in each country?
There was a traveler
I met a long time ago.
[KINO] ...who said that was
about the perfect length.
[HERMES]
Huh. Good to know.
Kino. You asleep yet?
[KINO]
Yes. Wide asleep.
[HERMES] Motorrads are
happiest when they're running.
And going on a journey
means running every day.
Therefore, we love to travel.
[KINO]
Okay? Where is this coming from?
[HERMES] Sheesh. Don't you
know what a soliloquy is?
[KINO]
You mean a syllogism.
--[HERMES] That's what I said.
--[KINO] What about it?
[HERMES] Well. Mostly,
I just like similes,
but then I got to wondering why
you decide to keep travelling.
I mean, I know you don't
have a place to call home,
but you've been in so many
rough situations on the road.
Nearly been killed even.
Don't you ever think about
finding a place to settle down?
As good of a shot as you are,
I bet you could find
a job anywhere.
Or you could've made a living
back at master's place.
[KINO]
You're right.
A reasonable person
would've stopped by now.
[HERMES] Yeah? And why
are you so unreasonable?
[KINO sighs]
Well...
[KINO] This might not
make sense, but...
[KINO]
"Colosseum."