[SHIZU] So that's
the Ship Country, is it?
[RIKU] It's more like a
man-made island if you ask me.
[RIKU]
Hmm, they've set up a market.
[SHIZU] Guess that's how
they make their living.
Trading as they
travel across the coast.
Hey, you know what?
I think we should travel
with them, if they'll have us.
Does that sound good, Riku?
There's no need for
you to ask my permission.
I'm a dog.
[alarm sounds]
[MALE LEADER A]
Traveler.
So glad you could join us.
We are the governing
body of this country,
known as the Tower Clan.
[MALE LEADER B]
How long will you be with us?
[SHIZU] Till you reach the
western continent, please.
[MALE LEADER B]
That should do nicely, I think.
We have a few more
stops on the coast,
so it'll be ten days
before we start west.
It's only a five-day
voyage after that.
[FEMALE LEADER A]
If you work for us,
we'll provide you
food and a room
with the same lovely
view that we have.
[SHIZU]
What kind of work?
[FEMALE LEADER A]
Overseeing the lower class.
[MALE LEADER A]
The people have been getting
rather bold as of late.
Making various demands
in the guise of petitions.
Feel free to use
violence as you see fit.
[MALE LEADER A] Alternatively,
you could join them,
and spend your days
doing manual labor.
What's your preference?
I think...
...I'd rather take the lifestyle
and work of the commoners.
[LEADERS gasping, murmuring]
I simply believe
that will be the best fit
for a humble man such as myself.
[CITIZENS murmuring]
[CITIZENS whispering]
[MALE ELDER A]
Please, eat. I hope you like it.
[SHIZU]
Hmm.
It's an honor to have
a traveler among us.
It's very tasty, thank you.
I'm quite glad to hear that.
My face may not show it,
but I've lived a long life.
I'll be turning 55 soon.
And in all those years, you are
the kindest stranger I've met.
When we meet travelers
in this country,
typically, they wear
the garb of the tower clan,
and give us orders while
brandishing their weapons.
[MALE ELDER A] Allow me to
introduce you to your guide
sent from the tower.
This is Tifana.
Most know her as Ti.
[door creaks]
Will I have this room to myself?
Great. Thank you, Ti.
[SHIZU]
See ya. Have a good night.
Hey, it's a decent
room, and quiet.
That their way
of telling us to sleep?
Guess we should obey.
Sleep soundly, Riku.
I intend to. You as well.
[SHIZU]
Hmph. Travel is exhausting.
Hopefully, we can settle down
in the next continent.
[SHIZU]
All right, then.
Now that we've had breakfast,
I guess it's time to work.
I doubt I can do
much skilled labor,
but I am fairly strong.
Do you have anything for me?
Or, if not, could you
show me around the place?
Where are you taking us?
Strange that they chose someone
who doesn't talk for our guide.
I suppose.
[CHILDREN gasping]
[FEMALE CHILD A]
It's so cute!
Hey, look, he's smiling!
No, you're just
forcing my mouth open.
I've done that loads of times.
Enjoying your stay, Traveler?
[SHIZU]
Yes, thank you.
[MALE CITIZEN D]
Traveler. Welcome!
[SHIZU grunts]
[door creaks]
[SHIZU]
Good morning, Ti.
[RIKU]
I hope you slept well.
So what's new?
Find any work for me?
Not today, huh?
Well then, what about tomorrow?
So it goes.
This trip might be more
boring than expected.
[RIKU sighs, chuckles]
[SHIZU groans]
Only five days, huh?
[MALE CITIZEN F]
Elder.
[MALE CITIZEN E]
Another traveler's come aboard.
[MALE CITIZEN F] But we hear
this one went to the tower.
[MALE ELDER A]
Ah. Tsk. That's too bad.
[plates clattering]
We're shaking?
[metal scraping]
What's causing this?
[SHIZU]
That sound...
Ti. Have you heard anything
about the ship taking damage?
Or needing repairs maybe?
[SHIZU] Could you show me
the parts of the ship
that people don't go to anymore?
[SHIZU]
So it's partially flooded.
Doubt it's just here,
but how bad is it?
The blueprints.
Hey, Ti.
Would you mind pointing out
some places for me?
I need to know what spots are
flooded like that one room
we saw, or wrecked beyond use.
Could you do that?
Worse than I thought.
Unless I made a mistake
with my counting,
that's 143 sites.
Any thoughts, Riku?
This strange country,
or rather this massive ship,
has lost much of the
functionality it once posessed.
Rather than repairing
or replacing worn-out parts
of the ship,
they're just letting it rot.
At this rate...
[SHIZU]
If nothing changes...
...it'll sink.
[RIKU]
One can assume as much.
It's pouring.
You like that sound, don't you?
Well then. Guess I'll
listen to it with ya.
[SHIZU]
Forgive me.
But I have to tell you
the danger of letting
this ship fall into disrepair.
There is nothing
to worry about, Shizu.
The Tower Clan is aware of all
that happens in this country.
As you say, sir.
But, tell me, do the people
have enough food here?
I've noticed that it's
rather difficult for you
to obtain anything
aside from fish.
I know you're
speaking sincerely,
out of kindness and concern.
But your worries are misplaced
here, for we are a happy people,
living happy lives.
As we always have.
And just as we always will.
[SHIZU sighs]
Hold on, are we on top--
It's beautiful.
It is indeed.
Feels like we're
flying above the sea.
Thank you for
showing it to us, Ti.
I needed this.
I haven't had a chance
to relax in days.
[SHIZU] There's something
I have to do today.
It's dangerous,
so please wait here.
[SHIZU sighs]
Here it goes.
[MALE LEADER A]
Traveler. Stop where you stand.
[rumbling, metal scraping]
You and I need to talk.
About the ship's shaking.
You've allowed your
country to rust and flood
and neglected its
maintenance for years.
I would like to hear
the thinking behind this choice.
Many lives are at stake.
Why haven't you acted?
[MALE LEADER A] I have
no thoughts on this matter.
This country is
under our command.
Therefore, the land
and people belong to us.
Yes, this country
will someday sink.
We've chosen to accept our fate.
I understand.
Thank you for explaining.
[SHIZU]
Hello there, traveler.
Rest assured,
I won't take your life.
You must be skilled.
Come, then.
[SHIZU grunts]
[SHIZU gasps]
That's surprising.
[KINO]
Pretty surprised myself.
[SHIZU]
Kino? You're here?
[KINO] Would you go back
with the others, please?
Sorry, but no.
--[KINO sighs]
--[MALE LEADER A] Kino.
Why have you stopped
fighting this man?
Is he a friend of yours?
Were the two of you plotting
against us from the start?
Well. I do know him, but--
[rumbling, metal scraping]
[MALE LEADER A]
I've changed our course.
We're no longer bound
for the continent.
Huh? Why, because
I stopped fighting him?
[MALE LEADER A] You may
live out the rest of your days
with the people.
--[gunshot]
--[MALE LEADER D grunts]
Don't kill them.
Stay back if you must.
That's no problem.
I never planned to kill anybody
while working for these guys.
--[gunshots]
--[LEADERS grunting]
[KINO]
So I'm using rubber shot.
Tell me, Kino.
When did you come aboard?
It was about five days ago.
What about you?
Uh... Say...
What was your name again?
[SHIZU]
It's Shizu.
[KINO]
Right, that was it.
And your name
was Riku, wasn't it?
--[gunshot]
--[MALE LEADER F groans]
[gasps]
A back way through?
[KINO]
Let's go around.
[SHIZU]
Please surrender.
[MALE LEADER A]
What do you plan to do
once you've taken this
country ashore?
If nothing else.
I'll be able to give the people
a chance at survival.
They'll all die
if they stay here.
[MALE LEADER A] Are you planning
to become this country's king?
If I have to.
[MALE LEADER A]
Very well.
Then you shall be next.
Perhaps fate
will be kinder to you.
[gasps]
Wait, what?
[SHIZU] You don't have
to follow me anymore.
But thank you. For everything.
[MALE ELDER A]
Shizu?
[SHIZU]
Huh...?
Tell me--why have we stopped
here? What's going on?
The Tower Clan
was neglecting the country
they claimed to govern.
So I spoke with them.
And afterwards, fought them.
[CITIZENS gasping]
Their rule is finished.
They all boarded a ship
and fled from this country.
I suggest you leave it, too.
[CITIZENS gasping]
It'll take adjusting.
But you now have
the chance to start
a new country, in this land.
Let's go back.
It doesn't even shake
a little bit here.
It feels weird.
No, the ship's fate is sealed!
You have no future there.
Your country is going to sink.
[CITIZENS gasping]
It might not happen today,
but in a few years--
[MALE ELDER A] You can't
fool us with such lies!
Our country has floated for as
long as anyone can remember
and it's not gonna stop now!
[MALE CITIZEN G] Yeah, what're
you tryin' to scare people for?
[MALE ELDER A] A traveler like
you could never understand
the love we feel
for our country!
In that case...
...it seems there's
nothing more I can say.
[SHIZU]
I couldn't convince them.
Look, you should
go with your people.
What's wrong?
Go back to your country,
before they leave--
--[knife slicing]
--[SHIZU grunts]
But I don't have
anywhere to go back to.
[RIKU]
Shizu, no!
Don't interfere!
[RIKU gasps]
[HERMES] Oh, I get it now.
That girl must be Tifana.
[gasps]
What do you mean,
you get it now?
[HERMES] Well, I was talkin' to
a black robe in the warehouse,
and as a favor to
a fellow non-human,
he told me all about
who they really are,
and about that kid as well.
Once upon a time,
there was a ship called Tifana.
About 600 years ago,
it drifted right into
this old, deserted,
man-made island of a ship.
Now, Tifana's
only passengers were
a few hundred young children.
Apparently, the adults had all
been killed by a strange plague.
So those people were
descendants of those kids?
[HERMES]
Yeah.
The AI that had been
in control of Tifana,
those machines themselves
transferred to the ship country
and became the Tower Clan.
Because they knew
those kids needed
someone to guide them.
[HERMES]
Spoken like a former prince.
So they became the elite.
Organized everyone and
tried to keep 'em alive.
Why didn't they just
take the country to shore
and beach it?
[HERMES] Well, they
considered it a few times.
But neither they,
nor the people,
knew how to live on land.
Plus, as machines,
they couldn't protect
the people from other countries.
[SHIZU] Then when
he said I'd be next,
did he hope I'd do
what they couldn't?
And what about Ti?
[HERMES] She isn't actually a
part of the original population.
A traveling couple gave
birth while visiting,
and then... abandoned her.
[SHIZU gasps]
[HERMES] The black robes
gave her the name
of their drifting ship,
and raised her with care.
But since she wasn't related
to any of the country's
human citizens...
...the people rejected her.
[gasps]
[SHIZU]
Ti...
I didn't understand...
But even without knowing that,
what I said to you was cruel.
[SHIZU]
Sorry... Listen...
If you...
...want to, then, please...
[SHIZU] ...come with me.
I won't abandon you.
I...
[TIFANA]
I could do that...
No need to thank me.
But... you are welcome...
Now say goodbye,
'cause we'll never
see that country again.
[SHIZU]
From now on.
You and I are...
[SHIZU rasps]
[TIFANA]
No... No...
You can't leave. Not like this.
Not... without me...
[HERMES] She's planning
to kill herself and him.
Don't do it!
[SHIZU]
Kino.
Ah.
Thank you for everything.
[KINO]
What?
I just... realized I hadn't
had a chance to thank you yet.
So there it is.
It was no trouble.
[HERMES]
"All's well that tends well."
--"Ends."
--[HERMES] Ends well.
Well, uh...
Hope we meet again.
Yeah, same here.
As long as me and
Hermes keep travelling,
I'm bound to find where
you eventually settle.
Really just a matter of time.
When that time comes...
...I'll be happy to welcome you.
[HERMES]
By the way, Kino.
[KINO]
Hmm?
[HERMES] If we were
to see that man again,
I feel like...
Yeah, I agree with you.
If it did happen...
the shock might kill him.
[KINO]
"Country of Liars."