[gasps] Hey! Check it
out, a car's comin'.
[BANDIT B]
Mm-hm.
Take a good look again
and tell me what you see.
Sure! All over it, sir.
Well, uh.
It's a weird car.
The driver's got a sword.
And there's a little girl with
a dog in the passenger seat.
All right.
You've got all
the basic details,
now tell me if this group would
be a good target for us.
Yeah. They look like easy
pickings, if you ask me.
And what makes you say that?
Well...
I'm pretty sure that
car's custom-made.
Bet we could sell
it for a fortune.
The man looks like
he's fairly skilled,
but what use will a
sword be against a bullet?
And we might as well ignore
the little girl and the dog.
That'd be a mistake.
Uh! What do you mean?
I was wrong?
Take a better look
at that little girl.
[BANDIT A]
Um. I see somethin' in her hand.
It's dark and roundish.
Head of a doll maybe?
Think again.
That's a hand grenade.
[gasps]
Whoa, you're right.
You'd be surprised what
a skilled swordsman can do.
And dogs have keen noses.
If we set up an ambush,
it would sniff us out easy.
That's a target we'd be
much better off avoiding.
[BANDIT A]
Look sir!
There's a motorrad comin'.
Well done.
I've got eyes on it, too.
Observe and make a report.
[BANDIT A] Right.
The driver is a young boy--
Or wait.
Actually, I think it's a girl.
What's more, she's sorta cute.
Really cute.
[BANDIT B]
What you should concentrate on
is whether or not she's
suitable to become our prey.
Well, that's easy!
We could definitely take her on!
I mean what's a lone
girl gonna do, ri--
Couldn't be more
wrong if you tried.
Uh?
She may not look like
much of a threat,
but that girl
is almost certainly
a highly-skilled warrior
whose seen and won
a number of hard fights.
Don't be fooled.
If she's traveling alone,
it's because she's
capable of traveling alone.
[BANDIT B] Our ideal
target is the kind of person
who carelessly picks
a fight with someone
stronger than themselves.
In short, someone like you.
[BANDIT A]
Hey...
Don't be discouraged, now.
I'd wager you're less
than half my age.
That gives you plenty
of time to learn better.
[BANDIT A]
Sure...
By the way, I heard that you
were the one who suggested
this lookout point to be posted
here in the first place.
Well, you heard right.
But I'll tell you that was
a good number of years ago--
[BANDIT B] It was just a
regular day for me and the gang.
We'd stopped a worn down, yellow
car with two travelers in it.
Driver was a goofy
looking young man.
Passenger was
a black-haired beauty.
[BANDIT B] We thought
we had 'em at our mercy.
But they were devils!
Bloodthirsty devils
straight from hell!
[BANDIT B]
Run away! Run!
Hey, uh...
You all right, sir?
Sir?
[MAN B] I'm curious, traveler.
Have you already heard?
About our country's
unique system
of accruable virtue points?
[HERMES]
Ooh, what's that about?
This is the first time
we've heard of it.
Here in this country,
whenever someone is witnessed
performing a good deed,
they're rewarded with
what we call virtue points.
Huh.
So how do you measure what
makes a deed worth rewarding?
[HERMES]
Yeah, how?
[MAN B]
Various ways.
I understand that this café
supports an orphanage.
Please, put this
towards your efforts.
Thank you!
So, there's an example.
Donations earn virtue points
based on their proportion
to your income,
not just the raw amount.
[HERMES]
Oh, yeah?
[MAN B] This measure was
introduced so that people
couldn't obtain virtue points
simply by being rich.
Makes sense to me.
[MAN B] The single best way
to obtain virtue points
is by making great
contributions to society.
Think of prodigy singers.
Or doctors who
cure the incurable.
You also get points
for little things,
like giving up your seat on
the bus for an elderly person.
When someone observes
your good deed,
they apply for you
to get points.
Making such an application
earns virtue points as well.
Your virtue point total
is part of your resident
registration data,
and is displayed on
every citizen's ID card.
Gotcha.
So anyone can easily
tell how much a citizen
has contributed to your society.
[HERMES]
All right.
Now what if you're rude
and bother a lot of people.
Or straight up commit
some kinda crime?
You lose points?
That's correct.
Small crimes don't hurt much.
But felonies cost
a great deal of points.
And when someone goes negative,
they're made to
serve time in prison.
So if I'm hearing right,
then if someone built up
enough good deeds in their life
before they committed a crime.
They could basically
get off without punishment.
Or am I mistaken?
Well. Yes, the points
would offset each other.
As long as their
total's positive,
they'd avoid jail time.
--[KINO] Figures.
--[HERMES] Figures.
[MAN B]
I think it's a fair system.
Tell me if you've
heard stories like this.
Someone who's lived
virtuously all their life
randomly slips up and
does something wrong.
Suddenly, they're
condemned by all.
[KINO]
Yeah.
[MAN B]
On the other hand,
someone can spend their entire
life being selfish and cruel,
but then, thanks to
a single good deed,
be viewed as an angel.
[HERMES]
It happens.
[MAN B] It's irrational, judging
someone off of one or two
short moments of their lives.
Our system is different.
It views us fully.
That said,
losing points does hurt.
In terms of reputation and more.
It's very rare for someone
to think it's all right
to indulge in a bit of crime
simply because they've
built up a few points.
[HERMES]
Well, that's good to hear.
[MAN B] That said...
I've been debating it.
What?
[MAN B]
You see, up until now,
I have devoted my life to
the people of this nation.
First as an inventor,
then as a business man.
And up until last month,
I served as this
country's president.
Quite successfully, too.
I helped a great many
people to prosper.
[CITIZENS cheering]
[HERMES]
Wow, that's incredible!
You must have a whole lotta
points built up, huh?
Yes. You're right about that.
I have many points.
[HERMES]
How many?
Enough for me to commit
the crime of murder.
Once.
[HERMES]
Whoa!
That's impressive.
At any moment.
I could slay someone
without cause.
And face no penalty aside
from a reduction in points.
No one's ever had
this many points before.
So you're debating if you
should use them, is that right?
[MAN B]
Yes, that's right. I am.
[KINO grunts]
[MAN B] I've managed to accrue
all of these points, and yet,
I can't think of
a single person to kill.
I've earned the right,
but no matter how hard I try,
I can't think of who.
What's more,
I'm running out of time.
My heart's giving out on me.
If I don't act quickly,
I'll die before I can decide.
[HERMES] Hey, there's no need to
force yourself to kill someone.
[MAN B]
It's not like that.
Don't you get it?
This is why I've saved points.
In the hopes that this
moment would come.
I've worked my
whole life for this!
And I made it. I can't just
throw all that away.
I want to kill.
Killing's always been my dream.
Ever since I was a child.
From the moment I learned
how the virtue point
system worked,
I have been obsessed.
Obsessed with the idea that
I could save up enough points...
...to erase a life.
Yes. To kill.
To end someone.
It's all I want.
I understand.
Thanks for the explanation.
When I first approached
you, I had planned to--
You know, most would-be
murderers don't give
their victims this much warning.
[MAN B] No. But it didn't
make a difference with you.
You noticed that I was
hiding a knife in my jacket
from the moment I sat down
here, did you not?
[KINO]
True.
And that's why your right
hand hasn't strayed once
from the revolver
you keep on your hip.
True.
[MAN B whimpers]
[MAN B whimpers and chuckles]
[bell rings]
[MAN B]
Fool.
[MOTHER A]
Mister President!
[MAN B gasps]
It's an honor, sir!
Forgive me,
but might you be willing
to give my child your blessing?
I'd love for him to grow up to
be a great man like you, sir.
Could you touch his forehead?
Yes. Perhaps a child, would--
Certainly, ma'am.
You've got a fine boy.
Wow! Thank you so much, sir!
[BABY BOY coos]
Oh, child who knows
yet nothing of life.
I bid you grow up
to live happily.
Take care not to end up like me.
[MAN B] Don't become a man
who failed at his only dream.
[MALE OWNER D]
Now then.
Let the annual meeting of
restaurant owners commence.
[MALE OWNER E]
We've all heard, right?
The rumors of
this wandering chef?
Yeah, they say
that guy can make
an exquisite meal out
of any ingredients!
And if he feels that
it's up to his standards,
he'll leave you the recipe!
Also, he keeps
his identity secret,
so people won't bother him.
[MALE OWNER A]
Listen and be shocked.
That very man is
coming to our country!
[ALL gasp]
Let's ask him to make
a new signature meal
--for our country! Oh!
--Yeah!
Every restaurant in
our country'll prosper!
Yeah!
But as much as he
values his secrecy,
do you think he'll
be willing to help?
He will if we make him!
Do we have any idea what
this chef looks like?
No.
Never fear, my friends,
for I have picked up
a reliable tip.
What is it?
[MALE OWNER A] Ha, ha, ha.
The wandering chef is--
[FEMALE OWNER B]
A traveler whose coat is
the color of fallen leaves?
Hello, traveler!
Please agree to cook
something for us!
[KINO]
Um...
[HERMES]
What?
We would be honored to try out
a sample of your cooking.
Our kitchen is yours,
come in, please!
--[BOTH laugh]
--[KINO] Uhh. If you're sure.
[HERMES]
Wait.
[FEMALE OWNER A] Come along now,
right this way, we insist.
[HERMES] Those poor fools.
They're all doomed.
[ALL gasping]
Okay.
Kino's fried chicken! Coming up!
[DINER A gasps]
Wow, it's...
[WAITRESS B]
Colorful, isn't it?
It seems to have a lot
of chili peppers in it.
That's right!
The recipe calls for them
in equal proportion
to the chicken itself
and a cup of vinegar.
Whole bunch'a
sansho peppers, too.
Do you love it?
[DINER A whimpers, grunts]
Oh, yeah!
Makes an impact, right?
That's the signature dish
of our nation!
Yeah, this is somethin'.
[MALE OWNER A] We got the recipe
from the wandering chef himself!
--[WAITRESS B giggles]
--[MALE OWNER A laughs]
[HERMES]
Hey, Kino.
[KINO]
What's up, Hermes?
[HERMES]
How do you think the people
of that country are holdin' up?
[KINO]
Which country?
[HERMES] The creepy,
masochistic one with the people
that liked your cooking.
Oh. They weren't creepy.
[HERMES]
Honestly, Kino.
I don't even eat food and
I know your cooking is foul.
All I know is that those
people said they enjoyed it,
and they ate it all.
[HERMES] Sure, but did you see
the look on their faces?
Yeah. That's fair.
It might've been
a bit too spicy.
[HERMES]
A bit?
Well, I've never had that
many peppers to work with,
so I guess I got carried away.
But it didn't seem inedible
when I tried it out.
[HERMES]
Right.
Maybe those were actually looks
of really intense enjoyment.
Yeah. Y'know sometimes it can
look like you're in pain,
when in reality--
[HERMES] Gonna have
to stop you right there.
[KINO] Either way,
that country was fun.
[HERMES] Either way,
that country was weird.
I've gathered all of you here
to discuss Kino's fried chicken.
The dish gifted to us by
the wandering chef himself.
It has become our
country's specialty.
It takes a refined,
yet durable palate to
truly appreciate.
Yet, the dish is wildly popular.
However!
Another itinerant chef of great
skill has put a marvelous twist
on the already incredible
dish and left us the recipe!
I've reproduced it. Behold!
[ALL gasp]
[MALE OWNER D] At first, I
didn't want to have a knock off
of our own specialty,
but taste it.
Let's see.
Wow, this really isn't bad.
Although it doesn't have as much
impact as the original dish.
Amazing, the chicken
is wrapped in
a paste of mashed
fruits and vegetables.
It really tones
down the spiciness!
Y'know what?
This would be a lot easier for
children and the elderly to eat.
Which is why
I propose we do this!
[SHIZU]
Huh.
Good afternoon.
I take it you're a traveler?
Yep.
In that case,
you'll have to try
one of our country's
signature dishes.
Sure, and what
kind of dishes are they?
Well! Here we have
Kino's original fried chicken.
And here we have
Kino's mild fried chicken!
Huh?
--Kino?
[SHIZU]
"May I get a raise at work."
"May my love become mutual."
That's interesting.
It looks like those statues
are covered head to toe
in people's wishes.
[WOMAN A]
Oh, are you two travelers?
Here, for you.
They say that if you write
your wish down and give it to
one of those three, they'll
make it come true for you.
Hey, you should
give it a shot, Ti.
I'll go find out what
I can about immigration.
Wait, Shizu, why don't
we simply write,
"may we find a country
that accepts immigrants
and isn't populated by
the violently delusional"?
I would rather act than wish.
[TIFANA]
Hmm...
Hey, kid. Have a wish
you'd like me to post?
Give it here and
I'll put it up for ya.
Wow. That's the most
generous wish I've seen.
Yeah.
"May the wishes of everyone else
who came here come true."
Well, you are just
the sweetest little girl!
[MAN D]
What a pure-hearted kid.
[MAN C] Ugh. Wish I
had a daughter like that.
[RIKU]
That's very kind of you, Ti.
A truly wonderful wish.
Was there nothing
you wanted for yourself?
You know that the wishes
don't really come true, right?
Hey, you two.
Sorry about the wait.
We're glad to have you
back, Shizu, how'd it go?
Not so well.
They aren't taking
in immigrants.
[KINO]
Heh.
[HERMES]
You're in a good mood.
[KINO]
Yeah.
I remember the country
up ahead especially well
from Master's travel stories.
I'm pretty sure it was
a favorite of hers.
I may want to stay here awhile.
[HERMES] Oh? It's a bit
unusual to hear that from you.
[KINO]
You think?
[HERMES]
Eh. So what's this country like?
She would never tell
me anything about it.
[HERMES]
What?
[KINO] Really, she wouldn't
give me a single detail.
All she would say
about it was that
of all the countries
she'd travelled through,
it was the only one she knew
she would never forget.
--[HERMES yelps]
--[KINO] Sorry.
So yeah, I'm excited
to see what it's like.
[HERMES] Just don't forget to
clean me up once we're in.
[KINO] Of course.
I'll even change your tires.
[KINO gasps]
--[tires screech]
--[HERMES grunts]
Huh...?
[KINO]
Hey. Hermes.
[HERMES]
Yeah? What's up?
[KINO] I thought we were just
about to go into that country.
Is that wrong?
[HERMES]
Um. Not "wrong."
[KINO] Then why are we
on the other side now?
[HERMES] Take it easy.
I'll explain everything.
Maybe get off for a sec.
[KINO]
Yeah, all right.
[HERMES] 'Kay, so I'm
just gonna say it flat out.
We entered the country,
enjoyed it, and left. The end.
What?
[HERMES]
It's just like I said.
Two days ago,
in the early afternoon,
we went in through
their east gate.
We stayed for three days,
just how you like it.
Then we said our goodbyes
this afternoon and left.
Which brings us here.
[KINO] But... there's no way.
I don't have any memory of that.
[HERMES]
Of course you don't.
[KINO]
Huh?
[HERMES] Oh, yeah,
there oughtta be an envelope
in the box on my left side.
Check it out.
[KINO] Why don't I
remember putting it there?
"Dear me.
"Or 'From Kino, to Kino.'"
What the heck is this?
[KINO] "This country
has a single condition
for would-be visitors.
A pretty unique one.
It's that I agree to have
my memories of it erased
with a drug, once this visit
comes to an end.
[KINO] They don't want word
of what this country is like
to reach any outsiders.
However, they still
want travelers to enjoy
a pleasant stay.
So they decided to do
this as a compromise.
They say that they've been doing
it for a few centuries now.
I consented to the treatment
and entered the country
for a three-day stay.
Sincerely, you."
[KINO] This is crazy.
I don't remember at all!
[HERMES] Well, yeah.
That was kinda the point.
[KINO]
Wait. What about you?
I don't even remember
rolling up to the gate,
so how do you
know what's going on?
[HERMES]
Huh? Oh, that's easy!
Motorrads aren't human.
So you can't drug us.
[KINO]
So you're telling me that--
[HERMES]
Yeah?
You remember everything
that happened in there?
--[HERMES] Sure do.
--Spill!
[HERMES]
I can't tell.
I made that country a promise.
Aw, come on, Hermes.
[HERMES]
I won't talk.
Not even if you disassemble me.
A motorrad's word is his bond.
[KINO sighs]
[HERMES]
But don't worry.
You were still your usual self.
In fact, I'd say you had a
better time in that country
than you've had in
any other we've been to.
If you want proof,
then remove the envelope
from the box on my right side.
[KINO gasps]
[KINO]
Uh! Wait a second!
That's me.
[HERMES] They said
a picture would be fine.
Everyone there was so nice.
Man, that country was awesome.
[KINO]
Great, but...
I don't remember.
It's like it never happened!
[HERMES]
Oh, it happened.
[KINO] But what's the point
if I can't remember?!
[KINO] So, I guess Master
didn't tell me about it
because she couldn't.
[HERMES]
Yup.
By the way, that's the second
time you've realized that.
You said the exact same thing,
syllable for syllable,
when we first went inside.
[KINO]
How are you on fuel, Hermes?
[HERMES]
Full tank.
We're stocked up
on food and water, too.
You even got me new tires.
All right, then.
[engine revs]
You ready? Let's go.
[HERMES]
Sounds good to me.
Hey, Kino.
Is there even
a country out here?
[KINO]
Who knows?
[HERMES]
I was hoping you did.
Sorry to disappoint,
but to be honest,
I don't know why we're driving
through here either.
We just are.
[HERMES]
Figures.
Hey, Kino.
Where are we heading?
Straight.
[KINO]
"Kind Country."