[KINO]
To be honest with you.
The country we're
heading to next is--
Well, it has a bad
reputation with travelers.
[HERMES]
How so?
[KINO]
I've heard a few things.
Like "they're cold
towards outsiders."
Or they're "disagreeable"
and "rude."
"When travelers come,
they close their shops,
or claim to be sold out
when they're not".
"They'll only give you food
that's gone half bad.
And be careful that they
don't overcharge you.
No one who'd been
there wanted to go back.
One guy said he
hoped it would burn.
[HERMES] Doesn't this
seem like the kind of country
we could skip?
Nah, I'm too curious.
I wanna know what kind
of country would make
people say all that.
[HERMES]
Has some beautiful scenery.
[KINO] Yeah. Too bad
it doesn't tell us
what the people who
live there'll be like.
[HERMES]
True. Let's go, then.
And may this country leave us
with such strong memories
that we never forget it.
Fingers crossed.
[MALE CAPTAIN A] How many days
are you planning to stay here?
Just three.
So I'd leave the day after
tomorrow, in the early evening.
[SOLDIERS sigh]
[laughter]
Huh?
Most excellent.
We're honored to
bid you welcome.
We're grateful. Thank you
for coming all this way.
Open the gate!
You don't need to
inspect my belongings?
Or ask me any more questions?
'Course not.
Why would we search someone when
they've committed no crimes?
That would just be rude.
[HERMES] So did we take
a wrong turn, or what?
No. This is the place, I'm sure.
[CITIZENS cheering]
--Hello, traveler!
--Be welcome!
Glad you're here.
Thank you so much for coming.
[MAN B]
Go let everyone else know.
[MAN C]
Mm-hmm!
[HERMES]
There's no way.
This has to be
a different country.
It's not what
I expected. For sure.
[KINO]
Thank you very much.
Gotta admit, I didn't
anticipate such a grand welcome.
So I'm not sure what to say.
But, uh, if I could
ask something.
Could someone point me
to a hotel that's
not too expensive?
Preferably one with a shower?
[HERMES] It would be nice
if it had enough space
to park a motorrad in.
[MAN B] There's a
cheap inn near my place.
They serve pretty
good food there, too.
If good food's
what they're after,
then I know the place.
Say, honey.
What was the name of that
inn we stayed at last spring?
I think there's one
just around the corner.
The traveler is
looking for a cheap hotel
with a shower!
[SAKURA]
We've got a hotel!
Hi! Welcome, traveler!
My name is Sakura.
It's nice to meet you.
And you as well.
My name is Kino.
This is my partner, Hermes.
[HERMES]
Hello.
My parents run one of the
nicest hotels in the country.
It's around the corner.
Oh, and it isn't
too pricey, honest.
I'm sure you'll like it!
[KINO] Well. Guess
we'd better go for it.
[HERMES]
Lead the way! Please.
[giggles] Sure!
[MAN H]
Welcome to our country!
[BOY A] Hey, traveler.
Come play sometime!
Hey, Kino?
I like your name.
It's unique, but it still
has a nice ring to it.
Plus, it's short.
Thank you.
I used to feel the
same way about it.
"Used to." Did that change?
I still feel the same way.
That's why I kept it.
But. Sakura's a nice name,
too, if you ask me.
What's it mean?
Well, it's the name of a flower.
A pretty pink one that blooms
for one week every spring.
[KINO]
Oh?
I like it, but all my
friends tease me about it.
They call me Ok-u-ra,
or Sock-wear-uh.
They're really dumb.
[HERMES]
What's wrong, Kino?
Oh, it's nothing.
Nothing I can put
into words anyway.
I brought us a guest!
Hello there.
Welcome to our hotel.
[SAKURA] Kino, Hermes,
these are my parents.
They're the joint
proprietors of this hotel.
And they also work as
tour guides for this area.
I'm still learning, but...
I do plan to follow
in their footsteps.
[BOTH chuckle]
[SAKURA'S MOTHER]
So, what room do you think
would suit them best?
Is the first-floor room
with the wide door still open?
[SAKURA'S MOTHER]
Mm-hmm.
[SAKURA]
Then I'll show them to it!
[HERMES] This place
is nothing like the rumors
said it would be.
I'm just as
surprised as you are.
[KINO gasps]
[SAKURA]
Is the room to your liking?
[KINO]
I'm quite happy with it.
So, hey, Kino.
I'm still training,
but do you think I could be
your tour guide?
You know what?
I'd appreciate that.
[gasps] Where would
you like me to take you first?
Uh? Hm...
[KINO]
It's straight down this road?
Yep! Just about everybody in
town agrees that the gunsmith
on South Street
is the best at it.
Show me.
[PERSUADERSMITH]
I know the make.
It's pretty well-worn, so
I'll take a look at the frame.
If needed, I'll change
out some parts.
It should take me about a day.
[KINO]
Then I'll come back tomorrow.
[PERSUADERSMITH]
Well I'll be damned--
Now this truly is
a bit shocking.
[chuckles]
Who'd've thought
I'd see you again?
[SAKURA] Here in this park,
we like to put on plays
for the children,
so they can learn
about our country's history.
[NARRATOR A]
Long, long ago,
a downtrodden clan was driven
by force from a distant country.
[MALE ACTOR B] No country is
kind enough to take us in!
[MALE ACTOR A] And we ran out
of food a few days ago!
[FEMALE ACTOR B]
If nothing changes,
our children will perish!
It already started,
but wanna watch the rest?
Oh, traveler. Won't you join us?
Please, take a seat.
Hey, wait a sec. Pardon, but...
Am I mistaken?
Or is that the traveler
who just joined us?
Yup, that's right!
And I'm her tour guide.
[CITIZENS cheeer, applaud]
I have a proposal, everyone.
It hasn't been
long since we started.
So why don't we just start
this show from the top?
Wait. You don't have to--
Great idea!
--That works for me!
--[MAN K] Sure! Why not?
[BOY B]
Start it over!
--[KINO gasps]
--[BOY C] From the top!
Thank you all very much.
[NARRATOR A]
All right. That settles it.
Long, long ago.
A downtrodden clan was driven
by force from a distant country.
No country is kind
enough to take us in!
And we ran out
of food a few days ago!
If nothing changes,
our children will perish!
[NARRATOR A]
They continued their long,
aimless journey. Until one day,
they found themselves
deep in a forest,
the likes of which
they'd never seen.
[MALE ACTOR C]
Hmm? [chuckles]
[CHILD ACTOR gasps]
I'm scared, mommy!
Let's get out of here!
You have to be brave for me.
No...
We have no food left
to give to the children.
[gasps] Wait.
There's fruit falling
from the trees!
Whoa, you're right.
And there are animals here, too!
[NARRATOR A]
The forest may have seemed
frightening at first,
but its bounty was rich.
And it saved the lives
of the starving exiles.
What a wonderful
forest we've found!
Here's a place where
no one will persecute us!
[MALE ACTOR B] No one to throw
stones at us, or chase us away?
[ACTOR A]
Mm-hmm!
[CHILD ACTOR A]
Let's stay forever!
[ACTOR A]
Yes!
Let's build a
new country right here!
[SAKURA] After deciding
to make this forest
their permanent home,
the people built a beautiful,
prosperous country.
Countless time has passed
since those trying days.
[applause]
[SAKURA] And now, thanks
to the resolve of my forbears,
I get to live here.
And carry their legacy.
Nice work.
You're a really good cook, Kino.
You sure know how to grill.
It looks delicious.
[HERMES]
Just grill it, okay, Kino?
No seasoning.
I know, I know.
[FEMALE ACTOR B]
Here, put this on.
We wouldn't want you to get
your clothes all greasy,
now, would we?
[KINO chuckles]
I appreciate it.
It looks good on you, Kino.
Very cute!
[HERMES]
Someone's having fun.
[KINO]
Hey, Hermes. You up?
Once I finish breakfast,
let's go shopping.
All right? And after that,
we can go pick up Cannon.
I'm honestly shocked.
It feels better than when I
picked it up for the first time.
'Course it does.
[KINO]
How much do I owe you?
None.
[gasps]
[PERSUADERSMITH]
Though I would like to ask.
Yeah?
[PERSUADERSMITH]
A while back, there was
an expert marksman who
made all of her students
call her "Master."
She was a traveler.
The type to poke her nose
into all sorts of trouble,
earning spite and gratitude
wherever she went.
That was a long time ago.
Have you heard of her?
Or met her, perhaps?
Afraid not. Don't know her.
[PERSUADERSMITH chuckles]
Fair enough. Anyway...
The Woodsman is a very dear,
old friend of mine, but
I've decided to pass it on
to you, traveler.
[gasps]
Years ago, back when
I was a traveler,
this gun saved my life
countless times.
It's been quite a while
since I've used it, though.
I settled down and got old.
Too old to start again.
This guy's still usable.
I'd hate to see him
waste away with me.
I wanna let him travel.
Like we did in the old days.
[PERSUADERSMITH]
Won't you take him?
That's a kind offer.
I'd be glad to take it.
[chuckles] All right!
That's the spirit, kid!
Come on 'round back 'n
we can fire some test shots!
I'll show you all its quirks.
We'll have to adjust the holster
and grip for ya, as well.
Ready?
Hey. You finished?
[HERMES] I've been dying
of boredom out here.
Sorry for keeping
you two waiting.
Wanna head back now?
[SAKURA] Wait a sec, Kino.
And Hermes, too.
Before we call it a day,
there's one more place
that I wanted to show you.
[gasps]
This view is amazing!
[HERMES]
Pretty.
[SAKURA]
I come to this spot a lot.
It's my favorite place
in the whole town.
So yeah.
I always told myself
that if a traveler came,
I'd show it to them.
And you two happen to be
the first ones who did!
It's an honor.
When I grow up,
I'm going to inherit the hotel
from my mother and father.
I'm training hard, 'cause
when that day comes,
I wanna be a great
innkeeper and tour guide.
Think I could be?
[KINO]
Of course.
Heck. You're already
a great tour guide.
I've enjoyed these past
two days a whole lot.
[HERMES]
Same here.
This kind country
was perfectly matched by
the kindness of our guide.
[giggles]
Well, thank you for saying so.
[SAKURA] I wanna learn more and
more about all kinds of things.
That way, I'll never stop
becoming a better tour guide.
You're the first I've met,
but I hope that lots and
lots of travelers end up
visiting this country.
And I hope, before they leave,
that they'll have made lots and
lots of wonderful memories.
The kind so good
they'll never forget 'em!
It's nice, that I'm able
to help make that happen,
don't you think so?
Yeah. It's a
lovely job you have.
[SAKURA]
Hey. Kino?
Do you ever run into
hardship in your travels?
Or have to do stuff you hate?
I do. Now and then.
But you keep going?
[KINO]
Yeah.
It doesn't make me wanna stop.
Why not?
Is it because traveling is
something you feel like
you're supposed to do?
[KINO]
It's more like
I just keep traveling
cause I want to.
[SAKURA'S MOTHER]
Hey, Sakura.
If you really wanted to, you
could start a journey as well.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
[SAKURA'S MOTHER]
You could go and see the world,
just like Kino does.
And then you could come back
and be a guide afterwards.
[SAKURA'S FATHER]
Hmm.
Oh. You think so?
[SAKURA] Mm-mm. I wanna be
the best tour guide I can.
That means studying here,
at the place I'll be
showing people around.
After all, it is my dream.
[BOTH gasp]
Well, that's lovely, too.
[SAKURA'S FATHER]
Looks like we'll find ourselves
with some free time
not too long from now.
Exactly!
[laughing]
[SAKURA]
Well, Kino, this is the spot.
[HERMES] They seem a bit
young to be getting married.
Normally, people
don't get married here
until they're after 20.
This is unusual.
[HERMES]
What are they doing?
The bride and the groom
are gonna throw
a bunch of little bags
out to the crowd.
Most of the bags'll be empty,
but there'll be a few bags
with a seed in it for every
kid they wanna have.
And they say if you get
one of the seeds they throw,
and you sleep next to it,
then you'll become
a happy bride
yourself before long!
Want me to help
try and grab some?
It should improve your odds.
You'd do that?
Sure. Let's go.
[BRIDE A]
We'd like to have...
[GROOM A] ...a grand
total of five children.
[BOTH chuckle]
[cheering, laughing]
Aww...
Here. Take it.
[gasps]
[KINO] Luck is one thing
I've always had.
[SAKURA] I've never even managed
to get an empty one before.
Let alone one that
has a seed in it!
So, Kino, thank you.
I was happy I could help.
Traveler. Good evening.
Could you please start
preparing to leave now?
Well, actually, I was
really hoping I could stay
for another day or two.
[gasps]
[HERMES] Whoa! What's
gotten into you, Kino?
Nothing. I just feel like it.
Is this really that shocking?
My apologies,
but when you entered,
you told us you would
only stay for three days.
I must insist that
you hold to that.
These are the rules.
Since your
next stop is out west.
You should camp up on the ridge.
Stop any closer than that,
and you'll risk rocks
falling on you.
He's quite right.
Be sure to reach the top of the
ridge, before you stop to rest.
[SAKURA'S MOTHER]
Here. Take these.
The small one is a snack for
tonight, and you can have
the larger one for
breakfast in the morning.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
I'm grateful to all of you.
In all my travels, I've yet to
experience such a pleasant
and welcoming country.
[CITIZENS gasping, laughing]
It was a pleasure to have you.
Thank you very much for coming
all this way to see our country.
No, thank you.
I made a lot of wonderful
memories here.
[SAKURA]
You're welcome.
Goodbye. See ya next time.
[CITIZENS]
Come back and see us!
[HERMES]
That really was strange, Kino.
You almost never ask to
stay more than three days.
[KINO] Yeah. I'm surprised
at myself, too.
[HERMES]
That was a nice country.
[KINO]
It was lots of fun.
[HERMES] Just about the
opposite of those rumors.
Yeah.
[HERMES]
Makes me wonder.
Me, too.
Then again, rumors
can just be rumors.
But at the end of the day,
it doesn't really matter.
[KINO grunts]
[HERMES]
What's up?
Don't know.
I just have a bad feeling.
Something's wrong.
My mouth is all dry
for some strange reason.
[HERMES]
That's weird.
Everything seems fine.
Didja have a bad dream?
--[explosion]
--[KINO gasps]
What the...?
What is that?
[HERMES] If memory serves,
that's a pyroclastic flow.
A burst of super-hot ash
and pumice that flows down
a mountainside at high speeds.
It's one of the ways
a volcano can erupt.
It's a volcanic eruption?!
[HERMES]
Yeah, that.
[KINO]
If we went back right now...
...could I do anything...?
[HERMES]
Nope.
[KINO sighs]
[HERMES] Pyroclastic flows can
get to almost 2,000 degrees so,
they prob'ly died instantly.
[HERMES] There's nothing
you can do for them.
You'd just die, too.
[sighs]
Feels weird,
but I shouldn't waste it.
Hey, there's a letter.
It's written by Sakura's mother.
[HERMES]
Read it.
"To Kino.
And to Hermes, too.
By the time you read this,
my country will be
completely gone.
You already know that much,
but I would like to tell you
the rest of the story.
About a month ago, we
learned that a large-scale
pyroclastic flow would
destroy our country."
[gasps]
"Faced with this awful news..."
[SAKURA'S MOTHER]
"...we had two options:
To abandon our country,
or to die in it.
We made our choice.
We decided to stay.
Such a choice may seem foolish,
especially to a traveler
such as yourself.
But this country is where
every one of us was
born and raised.
This is the only land we know.
The only way of life we know.
So rather than lament
our fate, or curse it...
...or fight it...
...we simply chose to live our
final days to the fullest.
Now, this may come
as a surprise, Kino.
But up until recently,
our country has been
rather disrespectful toward
travelers like you.
In learning our fate,
we also realized that
the only thing our people
would be remembered for
was our rudeness.
So we resolved to do better.
To ensure that the only memories
people kept of our country
would be wonderful,
and full of joy.
However, it began
to seem our rudeness
had caught up with us.
Not a single traveler
came our way.
Until, with only three days
left, you arrived.
So when we welcomed you,
it truly was from the
bottom of our hearts.
I'll say it one last time:
Thank you for coming.
P.S. Only the adults
knew about this.
We didn't tell Sakura.
Honestly, my husband and
I were hoping to talk you
into taking her
with you, but...
Then, last night,
she told us she wanted
to inherit the inn.
That it was her dream
That told us she belongs here.
So we'll be taking her with us."
[HERMES]
Well. That solves the mystery.
Hey, Hermes.
[HERMES]
Hmm?
[KINO] Care to guess
what my first thought was
when I read this?
[HERMES]
Go ahead.
[KINO]
I thought... I was lucky.
That they didn't talk me
into taking Sakura.
I felt relieved.
[HERMES]
That's understandable.
It's just selfish.
I'm so damn selfish.
[HERMES]
I dunno about that.
But I do know there's
nothing to be done now.
And it's not like I could
have carried both of you.
[gasps]
"Hey there, Kino.
I just realized that"...
[HERMES]
Read it.
"That there's no point..."
[SAKURA] "There's no point
in me hanging onto this.
I think you'd better
keep it instead.
Take care.
And don't forget about us.
Your friend, Sakura."
[wheezes]
[HERMES]
You're all set.
[KINO]
Hmm.
[HERMES]
What a nice country.
Yeah. We had fun there, right?
No complaints about that one.
[KINO]
Let's go.
[HERMES]
Yeah.
[KINO]
"Country of Adults."