[HERMES]
You're going too fast!
[KINO grunts]
[HERMES groans]
Sorry, Hermes.
Are you all right?
[HERMES] Thought my
frame was gonna break.
There's no way. You're sturdy.
[HERMES] I just don't get
why we're rushing.
Well, every now and then,
I think it's important
that you test your
abilities to the fullest.
Because otherwise,
you could really start
getting rusty before ya know it.
[HERMES]
Huh, is that so?
[KINO]
Sure is.
By the way, we're almost
to the next country.
[HERMES] Yeah, I still
don't trust your "almost."
[KINO]
Over there. See?
I've been wanting to visit
this one for a while now.
[HERMES]
Once we get in...
I wanna rest in
a cool, dark place
with the right humidity, okay?
What did you call me?
[GUARD C]
Number 24.
By entering our country, you've
automatically been granted
the privilege of
participating in the fights.
Exciting, right?
And if you came here
without knowin' that rule,
then tough break. 'Kay, boy?
I would rather you
didn't call me "boy."
My name is Kino.
I was... told that this country
was verdant and prosperous,
and it was known for
its beautiful countryside
and great, bountiful forests.
I also heard that its
citizens were a wonderful,
yet modest people.
Living simple but happy lives.
Oh, yeah, this country's
a damn paradise.
And if ya get lucky,
ya might even live to see it.
[GUARDS laugh]
I see. Now, could you
tell me about these fights?
We hold the fights
once every three months.
Over as many days,
you vagrants'll compete
for the honor of
becoming a citizen here.
One-on-one matches,
elimination style.
Whoever wins the whole thing
is granted citizenship.
Also, they get a shiny
new medal from the king.
Oh, and they get to add any new
rule to this country's laws.
Weapons're allowed,
and you can yield,
but your opponent
doesn't have to spare ya.
If they do,
you'll be free to go.
Refuse to fight at all,
and you're enslaved,
but don't run away.
Running is an automatic
death penalty here.
[KINO]
Okay. Can I ask you something?
--Huh?
--Am I the first?
Or have you had other travelers
come through this country
without knowing this fact?
[GUARDS laugh]
Yeah, it happens sometimes.
We could warn them before
they come in but why would we?
Their expressions when they
find out are priceless.
You guys remember
that one couple?
They came through recently,
in a carriage.
[GUARD A] They drew each other
in the very first round, right?
[GUARD D]
Lucky break.
The wife yielded,
husband spared her.
[GUARD C] Oh, yeah, and then
he got killed in the next round!
Talk about a dramatic show!
That stuff's the
whole reason I watch!
I'd like to participate.
[HERMES]
'Course you would.
Huh?
[KINO]
I said I wanna fight.
Please take me to wherever
you hold the combatants
before the contest begins.
Are you serious, boy?
D'you even have a weapon?
Or do you just plan
to charm your opponents?
Try n' win 'em over with
that cute face of yours--
[gasps]
This should work.
Don't you think?
--[metal clangs]
--[glass shatters]
[WOMAN screams in distance]
[GUARD A] Your turn to fight
should come up pretty quick.
Best of luck in your matches.
How long has your country
been holding this kind of event?
'Bout seven years now.
It's one of the first big things
the current king changed.
[CROWD cheering]
Well, hey, it's cold and dark.
And it seems like it's just
the right humidity, too.
[HERMES]
You always come through.
So you're serious, Kino?
About what?
[HERMES] You don't have
to go along with this.
We could fight our way
out of here if you wanted.
Yeah. I know.
[HERMES]
But you still plan to compete?
[KINO]
I'll go as far as I can.
[HERMES]
Good grief.
Every now and then,
I need to test my
abilities to the fullest.
Because otherwise...
...I could start to get rusty
without even realizing it.
--[HERMES] Yeah, yeah.
--[footsteps, keys jingle]
[knocking]
Hey, 24. You're up now.
[CROWD cheering]
[KINO] What if someone's
hit by a stray bullet?
[GUARD A] Spectators come to see
these fights at their own risk.
That's true even
if someone dies.
[KINO]
Huh. So that's the king.
[FIGHTER A]
Come on. The hell is this?!
How am I s'posed to look good
beatin' up a kid?
Well. You could
always just yield.
What, are you stupid?!
--[grunts]
--[trumpets blare]
[cheering]
--[FIGHTER A growls, grunts]
--[gunshot]
Uh... Nice shot.
Thanks, I practice.
[FIGHTER A sighs] If it's still
an option, I'd like to yield.
[CROWD jeering, yelling]
[cheering]
[KINO] Hey, there,
would you like to yield?
This is a surprise.
How'd such a puny brat
make it to the second round?
[trumpet blares]
[grunts]
[yelps]
I yield...
[KINO]
Good.
[HERMES yawns]
Hey, Kino. When'd'ja get back?
A second ago.
By the way, we're gonna have to
stay in this place overnight.
[HERMES]
Yeah, that figures.
[CROWD cheering]
There's nothing for it, then.
I give up, you're the winner.
Thanks, I'd hate to kill you.
Feel free to look me up
when you get older.
[CROWD cheering]
If you were wanting to yield,
then feel free to.
I will definitely accept it.
[trumpet blares]
Figured that was more
than a trombone.
[grunts]
You can't use your
flamethrower anymore, old man.
This fight's over,
will you yield to me?
[OLD MAN]
No, finish it.
You want to die?
If you win, you live on.
Lose and you die.
I've lived my entire
life in this way.
Left countless corpses
in my wake.
Well, in that case,
I suppose I have to.
[CROWD whooping]
[KINO]
Hmph.
[OLD MAN grunts]
Awesome work, Number 24!
You made it to the finals!
[HERMES]
Hey, Kino. What'cha got there?
[KINO] Liquid gunpowder.
I'm brewing it.
[HERMES] That sounds safe.
Run out of bullets?
No, not yet, but I'm
making a very special one
with this denser propellant.
It oughta pack
more of a punch.
[HERMES]
Hmm... Oh, right.
I heard more about this country
from some old man today.
An old man?
[HERMES] Yeah.
The one who calls you 24.
[KINO]
Oh.
[HERMES] So, seven years
ago, the previous king
was assassinated by his son,
which is how he
became the current king.
[KINO]
Yeah?
[HERMES] The previous king was
a good and diligent one,
but he was very
strict with his son.
Too strict, I guess.
The son bottled up his
rage for many years.
Eventually though,
it all came out.
He slaughtered his father,
did the same to anyone else
that opposed him,
and seized the throne.
But his wife couldn't cope
with what he'd done.
She killed herself,
and their two children
were run out of the country.
No one knows where they are now.
So, the murderous king
was left alone.
He made selfish rules--
even legalized slavery.
The country attracted
a lot of rough types,
so the king decided to make them
fight to become citizens.
The people questioned
all this at first,
but eventually,
they just went with it.
Slavery made life easier.
The killing was fun to watch.
For them, at least.
All finished.
[HERMES]
Were you listening?
Yeah, sort of. I think I got
the gist of it at least.
Thank you.
[HERMES]
Uh-huh. You're welcome.
It's time I turned in.
[HERMES]
Hey, Kino.
I'm here. What's on your mind?
[HERMES]
Nevermind.
During my fight tomorrow,
I'd like for you to come and
watch from somewhere nearby.
[HERMES]
How come?
'Cause as soon as I'm finished,
I wanna ride straight
outta this filthy country.
[CROWD cheering]
[BOTH]
Yeah!
[HERMES] That young man
is Kino's last opponent?
[GUARD A]
Yeah, that's him, all right.
He's an incredible fighter.
Your partner's no pushover, but
I think he might be in trouble
against this one.
[HERMES]
Hmm... Nah, I'm not worried.
Well actually, I think that
Kino's planning to do
something drastic once
this match is over,
so... I am worried about that.
Uh.
Hi there, my name is Shizu.
And mine is Kino.
[SHIZU]
Kino, huh?
I'd like to ask you a favor.
[KINO]
What is it?
[SHIZU] Yield to me now,
before blood is shed.
I swear I'll accept it.
[KINO] Are you hoping to become
a citizen of this place?
[SHIZU]
No. That's not my goal.
But I won't be able
to do what I have to
until I've won this tournament.
That'll be easier if you yield.
I have no idea what
you're trying to get at,
but I'm not yielding.
And why not?
Think that should be
pretty obvious.
I'm not yielding because
I wanna fight you.
Here and now.
[SHIZU sighs]
[trumpet sounds]
[KINO grunts]
[CROWD gasping]
[sighs]
[gasps]
[CROWD gasping]
Incredible.
[gasping]
[GUARD A]
Whatcha think?
[HERMES]
He's amazing.
I'm not sure if this world is
beautiful, but it sure is big.
Listen, Kino.
You can still surrender.
Thanks, but I'm gonna pass.
[SHIZU grunts]
[KINO grunts]
[CROWD gasping]
What the...?
[KINO grunts]
I'll admit,
you fought quite well.
An impressive display.
But it really is
time you yielded.
My refusal stands.
If this goes any
further, you'll die.
To tell you the truth,
I haven't killed anyone
in this country yet.
I asked 'em to yield, like you.
[SHIZU]
Oh? Your point?
I'm leaving soon.
But before I say
bye to this place,
I wanna make sure I get to
take out at least one person.
[SHIZU growls]
[whispering]
[SHIZU grunts]
[KINO grunts]
[whispering]
[GUARD A whimpers]
[SHIZU sighs]
[KINO]
You lost focus.
Whatever it is that's
driving you to fight,
it's distracting you.
[SHIZU sighs]
Guess that's it.
The match is yours, Kino.
So what now?
Let's say I surrender to you.
Will you spare me? Or will
you shoot me where I stand?
Technically, I'll do neither.
--[CROWD yelling]
--Just kill him!
[CROWD] Kill him! Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Do you know what's behind you?
The one I want to
take out is there.
What...?
Wait, are you serious?!
Just duck!
[grunts]
[GIRL A whimpers]
[GIRL B whimpers]
[GIRL A, B scream]
[CROWD yelling]
[SHIZU gasps]
[GUARD A gasps]
[CROWD yelling]
Everyone! Due to an
unfortunate accident,
your king was slain
by a stray bullet.
My condolences...
...but I still won this fight.
That makes me a citizen.
Since I won, that means
I have the right
to impose a new law
in this country.
Starting right now, every
free citizen of this country
will fight their friends
and neighbors.
The fighting will continue
until only one is left standing.
They will be the new king.
[KINO]
This is the law now. Follow it.
Why...? What the hell
did you just do...?
--[SPECTATOR E] Die!
--[yelling]
--[SPECTATOR A grunts]
[screaming, shrieking]
[HERMES]
Welcome back.
[KINO]
Thank you.
Uh... Hey, kid... Why did you--
[HERMES]
Oh, hey, old man?
You should probably get out of
this country as soon as you can.
If you don't wanna die.
[gasps]
[HERMES]
Best of luck!
[GUARD A gasps]
[yelling, grunting]
[sighs]
I told you I'd be back.
[HERMES]
It's pretty out here.
Um, Kino?
The lake... It's calm now.
[KINO] No matter how brutal the
shockwave, serenity returns.
[HERMES] You're thinking of that
couple with the carriage, right?
[KINO]
Yeah.
[HERMES]
If I'm remembering right,
they told us about
a wonderful country
out in the vast western forests.
They were planning to
start their lives there.
Yeah. They were.
[HERMES] But later on,
we met the wife by herself.
Do you think that they...?
Yeah.
[HERMES]
As I recall, at least.
She seemed just fine.
She smiled and said:
Visit that country as
soon as you can, Kino.
[KINO grunts]
[KINO]
All right. Let's go.
[SHIZU]
Kino.
My father was a vile man.
He needed to be slain.
So thanks.
[HERMES]
You're the exiled prince?
Used to be. If I had beaten you,
I would've waited for him to
present me with my medal,
and then cut him down,
consequences be damned.
Planned that for seven years.
[KINO]
You should know--
Revenge is stupid.
[SHIZU sighs]
I think so, too.
Well, Riku?
Where should we go from here?
Wherever you'd
like to go, Shizu.
[HERMES] No way!
A talking dog?! That's crazy!
[RIKU] Am I the first
talking dog you've met?
Nice to meet you.
Likewise. I am
Shizu's loyal servant.
My name is Riku.
It seems my master owes you.
You saved him from having
to kill the king himself.
That might not have ended well.
Therefore, you have my thanks.
I'm glad I was helpful.
He's very cute.
Does he mind being petted?
Go for it.
[chuckles]
[HERMES]
Hmph. Pervy mutt...
Uh...
[KINO]
Pardon, but...
[SHIZU]
Oh, that?
I'm keeping it as a
rememberance of my grandfather.
I realize that it isn't
exactly my place
to ask something
like this, but...
...do you not wanna
become the king?
No, I don't.
How come?
I just don't feel like someone
who planned to kill
his own father could
ever be fit to be a king.
That's interesting.
Wouldn't suit me anyway. Right?
Yeah, I'm not sure if it would.
[SHIZU]
Hey, Kino.
We could travel to the next town
over together if you'd like.
I can show ya the way.
I'll pass, but thanks
for the offer.
--Ah.
--[KINO] Nothing personal.
I was taught not to go wandering
off with strange men is all.
Huh...?
Hey, Shizu.
[whispers] You do
realize that Kino is...?
I understand.
Just be careful, okay?
But you are
stronger than me, so...
I'm pretty sure
you'll be just fine.
Thanks. You take care.
The both of you.
I'm glad to have met you.
[HERMES]
Catch ya later, pervy mutt.
Yes. Until then, rust bucket.
[HERMES]
Hmph!
[KINO]
That Riku was a real cutie.
[HERMES]
You mean the dog?
I kinda figured you two
would get along.
[HERMES] Why? What, do we
have something in common?
--Hey! Kino!
--[KINO chuckles]
[SHIZU sighs]
Really though...
What should I do now, Riku?
[RIKU] Are you sure you would
like to ask me for advice?
I lick my own butt sometimes.
Pretty often, in fact.
[SHIZU]
Fair point.
[KINO]
"Bothersome Country."