Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to build
between them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
Kagero... That's enough.
What now? Will you
still proceed to Sunpu?
In your condition?
Entering there without
sight may not be a wise move.
Wise or not, I have a mission.
I need to ask Lord Ieyasu
the meaning nehind this.
Until I discover
his true motive,
there is no turning
back for any of us.
We've known from the
beginning they would attack.
If we let this
sway us from our path,
then the Iga can
rightly claim victory.
And we will never make it
to Sunpu to learn the truth.
Forgive me. I allowed
my fears to speak for me.
Upon Saemon's return,
we will make our departure.
I expect you both to be ready.
Gennosuke-sama...
Fear is only the concern
for an unknown future...
and I sincerely hope
my fears are unfounded.
For there is a way before us
that has every possibility of
bringing about
the type of carnage
we have only
heard about in legend.
You actually did it?
You killed them all?
This should be a
time of celebration.
I killed Gennosuke.
And the rest of the Kouga
were even easier than him.
He died by your hand?
Seems his mysticism
couldn't help him very much.
What about Hyoma?
A blind ninja? He was
easier than any of them.
I've cut radishes that
put up more resistance.
And while she was distracted
by your butterflies,
I made very short work of the
female ninja they call Kagero.
Which leaves one...
Saemon... Does that
mean he still runs free?
He was the one
slippery fish that got away.
But, I will find him,
just like I found the others.
I expected much more
from you, Nenki-dono.
We all have weak moments.
I'll find you Saemon.
You will not live for long.
Oh, and I almost forgot.
With her dying breath,
the female ninja
told to me something.
The ninja who
killed Yashamaru...
was none other than Saemon.
Nenki-dono, how could you
do that?! You let him escape?!
You killed them all but him.
The man who
murdered Yashamaru-dono.
We'll find him.
And make him suffer.
He's the one...
You should have
found him, and cut him
in two before you bothered
with any of the others.
This must... be fate.
My fate... The heavens
charge me to this...
I will track him. And then
I will slay him like a dog.
You think you can, Hotarubi?
Saemon is a
man of disguise with
many faces you
would never question.
I will see through
any falsehoods that
scum puts in front me.
I'm going to kill him.
This I swear. If
it's the last thing I do.
So...
You'll see
through my falsehoods.
But you didn't... Did you?
You... Saemon...
You... killed...
Ya-sha...
Yashamaru... dono...
Let me... go...
Go with you... Yashamaru-dono...
Ya... sha... maru... dono...
Why the hell do we
have to get on a boat?!
Traveling over
seven leagues of ocean.
It's enough to make me want
to stay here. All by myself.
What's wrong with the ocean?
You act like it would
kill you if it had the chance.
Of course it would kill me!
Salt can liquefy my body
and there's gonna be a
whole sea of it under our boat!
Better believe I'm nervous.
I can't even stop shaking.
Calm down, Jingoro.
You'll be safe.
It's not as if you
have to do any swimming.
I know that. I'm not an idiot.
But it doesn't
make me any less scared.
In looking around...
I see no sign that the
Kouga boarded a boat here.
If they chose
to stick to the land
and travel the Tokaido Road
only, then we should be able to
get ahead of them and
overtake their
position by use of the sea.
But Tenzen-sama, Nenki-dono
and Hotarubi have
still not returned.
I don't consider it very
wise to move on without them.
If they haven't
shown up by this point,
then we must assume the worst.
We do not have the time to wait
for those who may be lost...
or dead... And so we move on.
My desire to fight is
absent, but I will in no way
alter my own path
to avoid an attack.
If you attack, you will leave
us with no choice but to resist.
And if before we
reach the gates of Sunpu,
we engage in a battle to the
death between the Kouga Five
and the Iga Seven,
then so be it.
I am one of the Iga Seven.
And to Gennosuk-sama, all he
sees are his remaining enemies.
It is a world of black
and white to him now.
The elders say the absent
get further off every day.
And to him this must be true.
I assume that in his
mind I am nothing more than
the Iga woman who knowingly
lured him into a trap.
If only he knew this was
not the truth, not even close.
My feelings are deeper.
My feelings are real.
Be careful, these
waves can be very harsh.
Koshiro... Thank you
for staying close to me.
Oboro-sama?
It's getting rough out
here. You should come in.
Here, let me help you.
I've prepared some tea.
I'd like to stay out here.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I have never been
on a boat before.
I want to take in as
much of this as I can.
The smell of the water is nice.
The splashing of the waves...
The crying of the gulls,
and the salt of the ocean
soaking into my skin.
This is all very new to me.
And I am wondering
why am I here.
Why am I a part in all of this?
Thank you and enjoy
the rest of your trip.
Thank you!
They were fantastic. I'd
love for them to play more.
Gennosuke-sama...
Akeginu?
Yes.
Take Jingoro and go
to the back of the boat.
Of course. Why?
Because I need to
speak with Oboro-sama alone.
I don't want any
disturbances, so have Koshiro
guard the main cabin. No one
is to enter while we are inside.
What's wrong? Just have
him sit there and stay still.
People won't approach
someone who looks like him.
I will tell him.
But what matter are you
going to discuss
with Oboro-sama?
Once we reach the port in Miya,
we may find the Kouga waiting.
Unfortunately, Oboro-sama's
thoughts seem to be elsewhere.
She still has doubts,
ever critical of
the dissolution of
the No-Hostilities Pact.
Her heart is not
with us, and each second
brings us closer to our destiny.
I must ensure that she
is completely prepared for
the fate that awaits us all.
No matter the cost, I need
to make sure she is strong.
Now do as I ask.
Tenzen-sama...
What is it?
What if... What if she
does not heed your advice?
What do you plan to do then?
She is headstrong.
More than anyone I know.
She knows reason. And she
will hear what I have to say.
I am sure of this.
I haven't heard a
flute that fine in ages.
You know, we should offer
him a drink of our wine later.
That's a great idea.
I don't know how much
longer I'll be able to last.
When do we get there?
Who is there?
Is that you, Tenzen?
Tenzen... Where
are all the others?
I asked them to wait
at the back of the boat.
Why would you do that?
Is there a problem?
Tenzen?
You and I have a very important
matter we need to discuss.
A lovers bond has been
shredded by words both
spoken and unspoken. While
old enemies rise up again like
the coming of a squall, a
grieving woman has set sail
across a sea of uncertainty.
One ninja is driven to
desperation from inside
his own locked cage,
as sacred rules governing
the master and servant are
scattered to the wind
like the ashes of the dead.
On the next Basilisk,
"Fallen Flower."