Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to build
between them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
She said you will
never die from any wounds
because you are
an immortal ninja.
What?!
Immortal?
There are only two
ways to keep you dead.
Burning, if your
corpse is reduced to ashes,
or slicing your
head from your body.
Tenzen cannot be
killed? But no one knew.
Why can you not be seen? Is
it that you have been killed?
Tenzen-sama is not dead. It's
impossible if you didn't know.
You have such vast knowledge.
Akeginu told you this?
Yes.
I find it hard to believe
that one of the Iga ten would
reveal such a valuable
secret to a stranger.
It cannot be.
He is still alive.
All wounds on
you heal completely.
When they do, you awaken
like a bear from the winter.
Such an art...
This is something I feel I must
witness to in order to believe.
Now show us.
Yakushiji... Ten... zen...
But wait...
I thought that was your name.
You were dead...
I saw... your body...
That was nothing... Those
wounds were mere insect bites
against my power.
What's that?
Long ago, during
the Tensho Era wars,
one of the Iga possessed
the same ability as you.
Being proficient enough
to deceive the Kouga,
he performed his part without
as much as a second glance
from your people,
assuming the identity of
a leader of Manjidani.
The Tensho...
You... lie...
Kisaragi Saemon...
This is the
fate you chose when
you decided to
steal my identity.
Yes, Kagero...
Gennosuke-sama.
Oboro of the Iga is no more.
I see... Very well done.
Have you been injured?
I'm fine.
As is Saemon. He fought
well. He has infiltrated the
Ofuku party using his technique.
Gennosuke-sama...
As this bloody feud
finally comes to its end...
my one desire is to stay by
your side if you will have me.
Keep your touch from me
forever, I would still be happy.
My only wish is to see to
your every need. That's all.
Please... Please tell me
my request is not impossible!
If that's your wish...
It is not.
I know that once
the Iga are destroyed
and we take dominion
over Tokugawa,
peace will blanket the land.
There will be
no need for ninja,
no need for me
to continue living.
My sole wish is to serve
you. To give my life over
to your daily satisfaction.
In this, my duty will
finally be complete.
Of the Iga Ten,
only one remains.
Death is coming to you Oboro.
My hands will see to it.
Well... I assume you have
already heard what happened.
Yes, I have. Did
you forget the ninja code
forbids revealing
one's art to strangers?
I must. How very foolish
of me to forget such a thing.
In truth, it has not
been terribly long since I
became a ninja
for the Iga people.
I stumbled upon their
village a mere one hundred
and eighty years ago. I'm
still a tenderfoot I suppose.
You shouldn't
sell yourself short.
Immortality has greatly
sharpened your wits.
My wits were not the
only sharp thing that
Kouga felt as he
coughed up his bowels.
Wonderful.
You should know that
my men have been talking.
They say that they saw the slash
to your cheek heal on the spot.
Most of your men
have never taken a life.
They were so shocked by
this new experience I feel they
may have jumped to conclusions.
In their turmoil, they must have
seen things that
weren't necessarily there.
Oh, yes...
Very soon... At
Hamamatsu or Maisaka...
A Kouga woman will come seeking
me and I ask of you one thing.
Instruct your men to show her no
hostility or hinder her arrival.
Allow her to pass.
It will be done.
He rubs me, the wrong way.
Akeginu...
Please come back
to me. I need you.
Saemon-dono...
You're inside.
We'll see how crafty you are
when I defile your womanhood.
Saemon-dono... Where is Oboro?
You must stay
close to me, Kagero.
Be careful.
They are watching us.
But why? They didn't
seem suspicious of me.
Do they think you're
not who you appear to be?
They believe their eyes.
It's not me these people
don't trust,
Kagero... It's you.
By these
people, you mean Oboro.
She has no concept
of mistrust for anyone.
Then who?
Lady Ofuku. She does not
believe that a Kouga could
show disloyalty to
her people so easily.
After I told her the story
of how I stole your virginity,
she said that you were
an extremely shrewd woman
and that it was me who was the
one taken being advantage of.
Her suspicious nature
runs deep in her veins.
But then why was I even
allowed entry to this place?
To keep an eye
on you... Kagero...
Wait... Saemon-dono...
We must do whatever it
takes to earn their trust.
What are you doing? Tell me.
I told them all, that
I made you into a woman who
begged for the
flesh of the Iga.
If we are to prove
ourselves what we claim to be,
then we must show
them that I am not a liar.
You must allow this!
Please, wait--
Kagero...
Saemon-dono... You
must stop... My breath...
Yes, your breath.
Use it. Breathe deeply.
Moan with passion
and cry out in ecstasy.
No...
This is not
Saemon-dono. It can't be.
I do not know
how it is possible,
but I know who this is.
Tenzen!
But how?! How
is this happening?!
He's supposed to be dead!
Saemon-dono...
Saemon-dono is dead.
Damn you... Damn you, Tenzen!
Kagero...
Gennosuke-sama...
Gennosuke-sama!
Sir! Tenzen-sama!
What is the problem?
Lady Ofuku! Something
awful has happened!
This Kouga wench we allowed
in has murdered Tenzen!
She did?
Did you find her
carrying a ninja scroll?
We found nothing.
Oboro... I want you to
cut this woman's throat!
You, are a cheat, Oboro! You
brought outsiders into this war
between the Iga
and Kouga peoples.
You've wrapped both
of our clans in shame!
And now you've
blinded yourself.
Don't you think
Tsubagakure deserves better?
You're no leader.
Oboro, listen to me.
I told Gennosuke-sama
that I killed you myself
and do you know
what his response was?
It surprised even me.
I doubted it would ever
come out of his mouth.
Any guess as to what
his words might have been?
He praised you. He
praised you for killing me.
Oboro, you foul-stinking
wench! I will kill you!
I'll strip your soul from your
body if I have to use my last
breath to do it! I will send
you to hell like I did Akeginu.
Why are you stalling?
Get over there and kill her!
These men cannot
hold me forever!
I can't stand to
listen to this any more!
I will not kill her.
Perhaps she is more useful
to us alive than dead.
How is that?
You see...
If we hold this woman hostage,
Gennosuke will certainly
come for her. This will bring
us our opportunity to kill him.
He must be dead
before we reach Sunpu.
Only then can we take
back the ninja scroll.
Without this in our possession,
the Iga will not claim victory.
I don't need that.
You have great potential.
Wait, mister...
Do you know how to play this?
What is your name young man?
Shinnosuke.
A good name. I am Gennosuke.
Well, it's nice to meet you.
Do you mind if I try it out?
Can you play
like my papa did?
Did this belong to him?
Gennosuke-sama...
I don't care if
my people hate me.
I only care that just once...
just one more time...
I want to see you.
I want to feel
you next to me.
I want to be in your
arms, one last time.
As an immortal takes away
life in an abandoned temple,
the one he seeks most,
journeys through darkness.
Iron needles pierce flesh,
carving dark letters onto
the snow-white canvas.
Cries of sheer mortal pain
shatter the silence of the
night, and a hero wanders.
His journey is long,
but his destination imminent.
On the next Basilisk,
"The Haunted."