Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to build
between them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
Gennosuke-sama's
in Tsubagakure?
The word came last
night. And apparently,
he'll be spending a few
days at Ogen-dono's Villa.
Can you pass the soup, please?
He's not alone, is he?
I believe Udono is with him.
I don't know if that
makes you feel any better...
I'm curious as
to how they met up.
Well, who knows with him?
He probably ran out of hot
air and fell out of the sky.
Mm, hmm... What?
I wanted to go! I've
never been to Tsubagakure!
Don't worry.
You'll get your chance.
There'll be plenty of
opportunities in the future.
That's the future!
What about the present?
What am I supposed to do?
What do you mean
"what are you supposed to do?"
I'm dying of boredom!
It's not fair, Saemon.
You men aren't allowed
to leave the compound.
You're like prisoners.
And it's all because of
that demonstration in Sunpu.
Even Jyubei got to go. I can't
even take a walk with him.
I beg your pardon...
When have you ever
taken a walk with Jyubei?
Please. Refresh my memory.
Well, what about Gyobu?!
He promised to
take me boar hunting!
Well, that's true. And I know
he was looking forward to it.
But duty first.
We must be vigilant
while Danjo-sama's gone.
You can wait longer.
You'll survive.
Hey! Why don't you
go boar hunting with
us when he gets back?!
Thanks. But I don't think
so. It sounds like fun.
But... I'd prefer
a nice relaxing day of
fishing to cleanse the soul.
Come on brother...
you could be our decoy!
You mean you would feed
me to a boar? Shame on you.
You should show your older
brother more respect than that.
Hmm!
Oh, by the way, Okoi. I have
a special request to ask of you.
I can't believe
this is happening.
How can he marry an Iga woman?
What a slap in
the face. It's not right.
Stop. That's enough, Kagero.
Put your personal
interests aside for once.
Gennosuke-sama has thought
this through carefully...
with all of us in mind.
You may not accept it,
but it's the best
thing for our future.
Is it, Hyoma? I'm not
sure. It's nice talk but
it sounds like
you're still trying to
convince yourself of that.
Maybe so... But perhaps that
stems from my own weakness.
It's easy to cling
to old ways but what
Gennosuke-sama is
doing takes true courage.
I still think that he's wrong.
No one wants this
peace with the Iga.
There's no need
for this marriage.
I'm not even sure Gennosuke-sama
is in love with Oboro.
If he truly respected her
he wouldn't be meeting her
before a ceremony is even held.
What kind of woman
would consent to that?
We should kill
that little tramp!
Kagero! That's enough! We'll
have no more talk like that!
We will all support
Gennosuke-sama's
decision and that's final.
But still... That doesn't mean
we should blindly trust the Iga.
Jyubei saw ominous
signs for Danjo-sama
and he still hasn't returned.
Gennosuke-sama's safety
is as vital as our own breath.
Do you wish for me to go
and check on him at Tsubagakure?
There's no need, to worry.
I've already sent Okoi.
She should be on
her way there now.
A wise choice Saemon...
She'll attract less attention.
The Iga won't
be as wary of a woman.
True... And
Gennosuke-sama won't be
nearly as angry if Okoi
comes for him. He'd kill me.
Yes, my thoughts exactly.
Then we'll
wait for her return.
Hmm?
Someone's approaching!
They're Ninja Footsteps!
Coming from the North!
Sunpu is North. Maybe
it's Danjo-sama returning.
No... The head count
is different... Let's see...
There are five
and one is a woman.
I sense aggression
in their stride...
They are definitely not Kouga!
Have either of you
seen Udono this morning?
No, not this morning.
But I did see him last night.
I wasn't going to say anything.
But he paid several
imprudent visits to
my room late in the night.
He didn't?
What happened?
Akeginu! What is it?
Don't tell me you--
Oh, no. I promise
you that he's just fine.
But I'm afraid that perhaps
my rejection may
have been too harsh.
Too harsh? What
did you say to him?
Well, I... I called him a fat
pig and said he was repulsive.
It was awful...
He suddenly grew silent.
And that look on his face...
Akeginu! That's terrible!
I thought you would be angry.
For what? We can't
blame Akeginu for
telling Udono that
she's not interested in him.
No, I guess not...
But she could have
told him in a nicer way.
Josuke's not one
to take subtle hints.
Trust me...
It was good for him.
Akeginu-dono, I am sorry that
he caused you so much trouble.
Please! Do not bow,
Gennosuke-sama!
Now that the mystery
is solved, I'd be honored if
you showed me
Ogen-dono's prized garden.
I'd love to.
Akeginu?
Yes!
Do you know if Tenzen and
the others have returned yet?
Uh, no. I don't
think so. Not yet.
That's strange.
Where could they have gone?
So many years have passed...
What a fine tree it has become.
Now!
Right!
Hmm!
One Kouga is dead...
He is but the first of many.
Move quickly.
It seems too quiet.
There's no need for concern...
We are merely
humble couriers sent to
deliver a message
from Gennosuke.
Yes I like it, excellent plan.
Since we know the
names of the Kouga Ten
it might be possible
to lure them out.
We can say that the
message we have is for them.
Hmm.
Let's go.
This fog will
work to our advantage.
Yes! It will provide
the perfect cover!
Let us slay the Kouga
Ten before it clears!
Let's not take
unnecessary chances...
Kazamachi was a
formidable opponent alone.
What is it, Koshiro?!
Someone's here.
Rousai! What the
hell is happening to you?
Damn!
Rousai! What are you doing?
That wall! It spoke to me!
It said there are no secrets
from the walls of Manjidani!
Alert! Intruders! Intruders
have entered Manjidani!
Damn it!
Please wait... You're
making a big mistake...
Our presence
here is peaceful...
We come from Tsubagakure bearing
a message from Gennosuke-sama.
Fool! Do you really think we're
going to fall for that trick?
Tell us friend. If you
were sent from Tsubagakure,
why did you come
in from the North?
And if you're
really messengers...
then why were you
masking your words?
Don't let them
get away! Attack!
Prepare yourselves!
Go! Show no mercy!
Hmm!
You've felt the wrath
of my Cyclone Death Song.
Now, which one of
you Kougas is next?
I never fall for
the same trick twice.
Huh?!
Tenzen-sama!
You must stand firm!
Those who dare to attack
Manjidani must pay the price!
Mark my words, Iga.
You won't leave here alive.
Is that so?
Hmm!
Let's get them!
Gyobu! That's enough!
You there, Iga! Tell me,
what sort of madness is this?
I can assure you, any
madness lies with you Kougas.
This is our first
time to Manjidani.
Is this how you
receive your visitors?
We detain only
those who act suspicious.
Surely, you
can understand that.
We've done nothing since we
arrived but defend ourselves!
You gave us no choice...
I believe this belongs to you.
Be gone! You have
no business in this place.
It's quite clear to us
now how you Kouga operate.
If you and your Kouga Ninjas
should ever pay a visit to
Tsubagakure you
will be embraced with
the same greeting
we've received here.
Only you won't walk
away to tell about it!
Damn you!
Gyobu!
Arise, arise,
my sleeping flies.
Flit and flutter,
before their eyes.
Blind our foe,
I know they doubt.
You are our shield,
now spread throughout.
Conceal us with
your florid light.
Now swarm, you must,
disguise our flight.
Gennosuke-sama...
Who's there?!
He must be an Iga...
What are you doing here?!
Stop!
He's good!
Damn! I missed him!
Oboro-dono?
What is it?
I need a favor...
Would you send a messenger
to Manjidani for me please?
It's not like Josuke
to leave suddenly...
I'm worried about him.
I just want to be certain
that he returned safely.
I pray that my
fears are unfounded.
Of course...
Consider, it done.
Thank you.
The darkness pervading the
sky seeps into the souls of men.
As pounding rain falls,
fervent prayers rise...
Sinister hearts, plagued
with heinous desires long for
the pure and forbidden fruit.
The innocent shall be defiled,
and another life will be lost.
The truth struggles
to find illumination
but the sun
withholds its light.
On the next Basilisk,
"Longing in the Rain."