Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to build
between them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
Koshiro-dono...
That was Akeginu-dono's
voice. I know it.
Akeginu-dono,
what are you doing here?
Koshiro-dono, behind you!
The man who died
standing in the road,
is Muroga Hyoma of the Kouga.
He is?!
I understand. That is why
I did not sense him fall.
He stayed true to the end.
Muroga Hyoma,
this was all my pleasure.
Akeginu-dono, why are you here?
Has something
gone wrong at the Inn?
Is she... Is Oboro-sama
still hiding safely with you?
Now matter how bad
the truth, please tell me.
I must know of
Oboro-sama's fate!
Koshiro-dono...
It was the Kouga. Kisaragi
Saemon appeared at the Inn like
a flash of lightning.
In no time at all, he had...
He had viciously
slaughtered Oboro-sama.
There is nothing left
of her in this world.
Not my princess...
What now?!
What am I going to do now?!
I swore to protect her
with my life and I failed!
I failed in my sole obligation!
Dammit! Dammit!
I hate them!
I hate all of them!
Every single one
of those evil Kouga
will pay for
this with their lives!
Koshiro-dono...
You must tell me.
At the Inn... when
Oboro-sama was slain...
what were you doing?
Tell me.
I was bound hand and foot. Tied
up a like a boar for slaughter.
But I was able to free myself.
I was overcome with desperation
to find you and Tenzen-sama
and report what had happened.
I didn't think I could
evade them well enough to
make it here,
but somehow I did.
My princess is dead...
I can't bear to hear this!
Akeginu-dono,
I fear this is the end!
It is.
But now I have no regrets for I
can see the path I must follow.
Please, Koshiro-dono...
You must use your hands.
Akeginu-dono...
Use your hands and kill me.
Kill me. You must kill me.
I-I don't know if I can.
Please, Koshiro-dono. Kill me.
Koshiro-dono...
It's over. The Iga have lost.
And so, we must do
the honorable thing.
Let us die... together.
Koshiro!
It's tiring. The
seductive voice of a woman.
Chikuma Koshiro, all you
need to know in moving from
this world to the next is
that you died in Akeginu's arms.
Hyoma...
Oboro's hawk must
have made its way back
to the Inn where she stays.
We must find them.
Koshiro-dono?
Koshiro-dono? Koshiro-dono!
He's gone. Koshiro-dono.
They killed him. He's dead!
Akeginu.
Koshiro...
But... how?
They came here
just as we expected.
Saemon, if you hold
on to your current guise,
you can approach close
enough to kill them both.
Oboro...
Koshiro-dono...
They killed you, and
somehow they did not leave
a single mark on your body.
You bastard. You
killed Koshiro-dono!
Akeginu? Do you see someone?
I see a Kouga ninja who died
standing on his own two feet.
This sewer rat
and Koshiro must have
killed each other in battle.
I must take this opportunity
to use your body, Hyoma.
Please forgive me.
His face is shredded
like goose-meat,
but his hair hangs loose...
If memory serves, this is
a member of the Kouga clan
known as Muroga Hyoma.
Akeginu. What are you doing?
Akeginu! Stop now!
Akeginu, please.
You must stop!
Dishonoring the dead
goes against everything that
we as Iga believe.
You should know this.
Listen... When Tenzen
humiliated Kasumi Gyobu
by staking his body
in front of that bridge,
I was disgusted by it.
Hyoma may have been our enemy,
but his skill
was great enough to
take Koshiro
with him into death.
And to disrespect that struggle,
would disrespect everything
that Koshiro worked
toward in his final moments.
You can see. Hyoma
didn't fall even in death.
Which says his heart must
have ached deeply for someone.
Do you not
agree with me on this?
Where is Tenzen?
Could the same fate
have befallen him?
Tenzen-sama is not dead.
It's impossible
if you didn't know.
Saemon-dono, are you
confident in Tenzen's death?
Of course I am.
I have seen enough death
to know it when I see it.
That woman is mad with grief.
She's doesn't know
what she's saying.
We must destroy them,
and now is the time.
Oboro--
Something is wrong.
What is it, Saemon-dono?
What are you waiting for?
People are approaching
from the east.
It's rather late to
be traveling with so many.
Father...
I assume you have
heard that Lady Ofuku has
secretly taken
her leave for Ise.
Is that the reason
for your return?
I suspect that she will
try and force the results
between Kouga and Iga.
I can deploy my men.
Do not.
As, you wish...
Koshiro-dono.
Put down the weapon and
identify yourself immediately.
Something's wrong!
Stay on guard. We don't know
if they are friend or foe!
We are travelers on our way
to Sunpu under the orders of
retired Shogun Ieyasu, and
I demand to know who you are
as well. There are many
enemies on this road tonight.
Wait, what's that?
On their way to the Shogun?
You dare utter his name?!
Only an insolent person
would toss his name around!
That's enough!
Tell us who you are!
We are Iga, traveling
from Tsubagakure.
Iga?
What was that?!
What did she just say?
Did you just say that
you are Iga from Tsubagakure?
Lady Ofuku, please.
Enough, men.
You may stand down.
I hear the truce was
nullified by Hattori Hanzo
and your people now fight
with the Kouga. Is this true?
Are you and your traveling
companion part of this war?
Tell me who you are.
I am wetnurse and caregiver to
the Shogun's
heir, Lord Takechiyo.
My name is Ofuku.
I suspect I know who you are.
Are your names
Oboro and Akeginu?
What do you know of us?
I know much more
than you might think.
Ogen herself
made a list of the
ten best ninja
she had in her clan.
This register was passed on
to Retired Shogun Ieyasu who
in turn passed it on to me. The
Iga ten have been trusted with
an important duty.
You were chosen especially
to serve Lord Takechiyo.
I would like to know,
who is this dead
man lying in the road?
An enemy. He was
one of the Kouga ten
and he went by the
name of Muroga Hyoma.
Well done! You slaughtered
one of the Kouga!
Tell me, my Iga women,
what of your comrades in this?
Surely you do not travel
this late at night alone.
Where are the other
eight from Ogen's list?
They're dead.
We are all that remain.
How could that be?
The No-Hostilities Pact was
dissolved only a few days ago.
There is something
I do not understand.
A moment ago you said we were
chosen to serve Lord Takechiyo,
which is the first
I have heard of this.
Can you explain these
duties of which you speak?
How can you not know?
That's impossible.
You are saying that you
and the Kouga have been
killing each other
and no one has been
informed of a reason for this?
Very well.
I will explain to you. There
are extremely grave consequences
resting on the
shoulders of your war.
Are you certain
that leaving Lady Ofuku to
her own devices
is a wise move?
We let her run rampant and
unwanted conflict may surface.
It will be quite
the opposite, I believe.
In the interest of
preventing further strife,
I have decided to
leave Lady Ofuku alone.
Perhaps you did
not know that she was
the second wife of
Lord Inaba of Sado.
One day she discovered
that he had a concubine
who had borne him a child,
and he intended this
child to be his heir.
While Lord Inaba
was away from home,
Ofuku invited the concubine and
child to move into the estate.
Once there, she stabbed
them both to death,
calmly climbed into
her palanquin, and left.
The fact is that the more
you try to rein this woman in,
the angrier she becomes. And
at that point, she will cross
any bridge to spite you. It
is wiser to simply let her be.
This way there will be
less trouble for all of us.
Are you sure in this plan?
Kyohachiro, as the fourth
Hattori, I, Hanzo Masahiro
will guarantee it.
Regardless of what
conniving tricks Ofuku has
up her sleeve, there is no one
in the world who can
step in between two warring
ninja factions and wield
any kind of true influence.
Do you see now? Is it
not the most noble of causes?
Oboro... Akeginu...
I would be most honored
if you both joined
me on my trek to Sunpu.
In fact, given the
dangerous circumstances,
I must insist upon it.
These are the only two left.
For the sake of Lord Takechiyo,
I cannot let these two perish!
Ladies, what do you say?
I promise the journey will be
a worthy one for both of you.
The No-Hostilities Pact
that has bound our people for
so long has been nullified.
However, I do not intend to
resume this fight because
I see no purpose behind it.
Why should I
kill in the name of
something I do
not believe nor see?
Questions like these have
compelled me to travel to Sunpu
and ask retired Shogun Ieyasu
and Hattori-dono for
guidance in these matters.
We will go to Sunpu.
A wise decision!
Oboro-sama, we cannot run
with our tails between our legs
and let the Kouga win!
Of course not. I will
oversee their demise.
Also, I will ensure
the two of you stay alive.
The woman is right. Getting
Oboro-sama to Sunpu as quickly
and as safely as possible
should take priority.
As for myself,
I have other plans.
If we go to Sunpu, I can have an
audience with the Retired Shogun
and Hattori-sama.
Then, even if I must
sacrifice my own life,
I will make sure the
No-Hostilities Pact
is reinstated.
I would have never thought the
end of the No-Hostilities Pact
was an effort to
determine the next Shogun.
I don't know whether to
be intrigued or offended.
I see...
Finally, I understand.
With pain and darkness
closing in from all sides,
a woman waits patiently at
Imurebashi, on the Tokaido Road.
Stoking the raging
fire within her breast
are vengeful thoughts.
Compassion grows in the
faces of those we
see and those we do not.
But humanity is most potent
in the eyes of one's foe.
On the next Basilisk,
"River of Mercy."