Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to build
between them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
Oboro-sama.
Koshiro. What is it?
Tenzen-sama. He
wishes to speak with you.
I see.
Gennosuke-sama. I
must meet with my cousin.
Your carvings are well adorned.
What?!
Impressive craftsmanship.
I wanted to know
who among the Iga could
carve such charming owls.
So I asked Oboro-sama.
It's something that I
hope you may someday teach
to the children of Kouga.
Your name is Koshiro-sama, yes?
Oboro-sama and you grew up
together, if I'm not mistaken.
I have my share of siblings.
It's frustrating to
care for them sometimes.
I don't have time for this.
You filthy Kouga.
You will answer all of
my questions truthfully.
If you are dishonest,
you will not leave this
place alive or in one piece.
Now out of the Kouga Ten...
First, there's
this Muroga Hyoma.
I have heard
much about that one.
It is said that
he's a blind ninja.
What I want to know is,
what are his specialties?
There is the woman, Kagero.
What techniques
does she employ?
And let's not
forget Kisaragi Saemon.
Ah, nature is calling
is she? I will be happy to
provide assistance, as
soon as you provide answers.
Do you actually think
I'd tell you anything?
If you don't tell me,
you know what happens.
Tell me something
first, old man...
What is it?
The more I look at
you, the more I wonder.
What the Hell's crammed
into that head of yours
to make it look like that?
Why don't you tell me that while
I think up answers for you?
You should know this.
My head is packed tight.
Filled with
loathing for the Kouga,
it swells with
each breath you take.
For me, the memories echo
as if sent from yesterday.
You treacherous
Kouga took advantage of
the Oda's surprise attack
and you massacred the Iga with
no regard for what
the future would hold.
That's a filthy lie!
I think the liar here is Danjo.
He's kept so
much hidden from you.
He would never
lie to us! The Kouga...
We're more honorable than that!
We treat our
enemies with respect!
You don't know what
you're talking about!
I can't criticize you for
your loyalty. It's natural.
Quite honestly had the Iga
been in the place of the Kouga,
we would have
done the same as you.
Then how in the Hell can
you Iga call us underhanded?
Now then. It's
time for you to answer.
I don't think I need to ask
you about your skills, do I?
Cutting off your
ears will be first.
Then I wslice off your
right arm. Then your left arm.
Then on to those
voluptuous breasts.
Somehow, I doubt you're up
to such an unending torture.
Now...
It's time for you to speak.
My hand it's...
it's... stuck!
Let go of me you...
You really should
have asked my specialty.
You... bitch!
I hope your journey
to Hell is a swift one.
The Igas are up to something.
I must see if
Gennosuke-sama is safe.
Then back to Kouga. If
I can make it there alive.
Gennosuke has told me
many things about this place.
He was right about this
much. The layout is amazing.
They've been attacked
by the Oda in the past.
They've ensured they're very
well-protected at this point.
We must take care.
It's likely they have
scouts all over the area.
I'm going in through the
front. We should meet inside.
Unless you have an objection.
See you inside.
Saemon!
Remember that
Gennosuke-sama's safety
is at the center
of our concern.
You think for one
second that I've forgotten?
I am counting on you, Okoi.
I know.
Go on! Get out of here!
That girl is hopeless.
Goodbye, my brother.
I won't fail.
Yashamaru-dono...
Rousai. Are you in here?
Tell me something, wench...
Has my friend Rousai
been through here tonight?
You know, the old man
with the long white beard.
Kill me.
Well it looks like
you've already gone ahead
and told him
everything that you know.
No Kouga woman who
has been humiliated by
an Iga can
allow herself to live.
What?
That old dog.
I didn't think he
could get it up anymore.
But what do you know.
He's still got some life left.
I'm surprised.
And he was nice
enough to leave you behind
so I could take a turn myself.
Is it really you, my love?
Well. No use in hiding.
This is the same woman.
She was part of the Iga who
attacked Manjidani this morning.
What does she see?
What?!
It really is you. I knew it.
I knew you'd be alive.
I never gave up hope.
So these two were in love.
You came back
to me. You're alive.
Of course, I am. But just
who do you believe me to be?
If she's testing me,
there's only one other
course of action
I can to take.
Uh... Thank you.
Did I raise my
suspicions too early?
It... It must be the
shock. Or the snakebite.
But I just
wasn't completely sure
that you even recognized me.
I'm so sorry. It was just
because when you left for Sunpu,
you hair was so
different than it is now.
I was just confused, my love.
Really?
I tried to make sure
everything was the same.
It's Kouga Danjo.
And that beast Kazamachi Shogen
who are behind all of this.
The signs do point to that.
I do have some
good news though.
There is word circling
that Danjo is dead.
What?!
And as for Shogen, I
think you'll be proud of me.
I killed him myself.
No mercy spared.
I killed him...
for you, my love.
I see. You've
done... very well.
Now I see Jyubei's prophecy.
It seems his sight is pure.
You have to
tell me the truth.
Don't you prefer
me so much more than
that wrinkled old
bag of wind. Don't you?
No!
Are you still turned on?
Get off me!
You spell-binding leech!
You're right. You do have
more to offer than that old man.
I'm going to suck every ounce
of your blood right out of you.
I'm sorry to
have kept you waiting.
Tenzen. Is there something
you need to tell me?
Tenzen?
I've given this
matter much thought.
And I'll be as forward
with you as I can.
I hope you can
forgive my bluntness.
Oboro-sama. You must
listen very carefully.
The retired
Shogun Ieyasu has ordered
that the pact be dissolved.
It has come to an end and so
the hostilities between
Iga and Kouga will rise again.
We are at war.
A hapless beast coaxed
into rapturous encounter,
as a stranger goes unnoticed.
One mind ignores
what another fears.
Innocent eyes torment
the dark horse of deceit.
The pangs of Hell prick.
As death yearns to cut through,
a final flicker moves through
the fading light of life.
On the next Basilisk,
"Cage of Blood."