Through all these years,
you have never changed.
Hey... Wake up, Kouga.
We've arrived at
Hattori Hanzo-sama's estate.
Oboro of the Iga.
May I enter?
Yes.
I am Kyohachiro,
son of Masanari...
Hanzo the II... Adopted by
Masahiro... or Hanzo the IV.
It is an honor to
make your acquaintance.
You don't remember me.
I suppose you were quite young.
This horrible war...
It has sent your clans
spinning out of control.
And we are responsible.
You must hate us
for what we've done.
I wish that none of
this had ever happened.
Do you carry a sword with you?
No, I do not.
Very well.
You will use this.
Please take it.
It's a fine sword.
I am grateful. Thank you.
Use it well. Is there
anything you desire?
Where is Gennosuke
of the Kouga?
Not too far from here.
He is conscious.
But I don't
know for how long.
Bring him to me. The
only thing the man needs to
be able to do is stand.
Yes, my lady.
These events, have struck
across time like lightning.
Ten days and nights have
brought this wretched
concept to a brutal end.
The frost is finally melting.
This harsh winter
will soon be over.
I've longed for spring...
So many things that were
old become new once again.
Oboro-dono.
It's no matter. I'd wait
forever, Oboro-dono.
I was on my way to Ise.
That is when by coincidence,
I stumbled upon
this clan conflict.
But I assure you
I have not interfered.
I have not favored
one faction over the other,
and I ask you to be
my witness to this fact.
As this conflict's referee,
it is your duty to
report these dealings
to Retired Shogun Ieyasu.
My only wish is that you
represent my
position to him truthfully.
Is this something
you will be able to do?
As you say, it is my duty.
Good. Kouga Gennosuke
seems to have been blinded by
the Iga at some point. Possibly
when they beat him into the
condition in which we found
him. I don't believe this to be
a problem considering
this is a ninja duel.
Would that be correct?
Yes. However, you're continuing
insistence that you have
been uninvolved
in this ninja war
may cause suspicions in some.
Perhaps I should
tell him, you seem anything
but honest in
this matter, my lady.
Is there anything you desire?
There is little I can do now.
But I can at
least hear a request.
Thank you, but no.
There is nothing I desire.
Very well then.
Hattori-sama?
There is something...
If you would be so kind...
there is something I would
like for you to hold for me.
Yes...
This...
Please keep it safe.
Is this an
heirloom of your people?
Or is this special to you?
This is my people's. It
is our prayer for the future.
You'll have it
when this is over.
But if I fall...
If I fall... I do
not know to whom it goes.
With all certainty,
you will walk away today.
Kouga Gennosuke is
in no condition to fight.
The battle is half won.
Oboro...
It would be merciful of
you to strike him down quickly.
Send him into death with honor.
Yes...
Gennosuke-sama...
What is going on here?!
Oboro! Raise your sword
and strike down that Kouga!
I love you...
Gennosuke-sama.
Someone cut his
head off before she dies!
This cannot happen!
Fools...
Oboro...
Father?
Were those two... in love?
Kyohachiro.
Yes.
It reads, "The last on to
write on this scroll is I..."
"The Iga leader... Oboro."
Who would have imagined,
that in this final moment,
in this manner, the Takechiyo
faction would emerge victorious.
This is the end of me.
My glorious life is over.
That woman surely
has the devil's luck.
The Iga have won the war.
Now go inform Sunpu.
I see a time when you
and I could stand together
and feel the
breeze across our face.
A time when our
dreams were the same.
Of the same place.
Of the same feelings.
Sometimes this thought crosses
my mind, when I least expect it.
This thought is that you
and I were once a single soul.
One soul split
into two equal parts,
which now longs
to be together again.
I feel this as truly as I
feel the rain in the spring,
or the love for
all of my ancestors.
And that is why... That is why
I feel so strongly toward you.
If we are indeed one soul...
we will bond without fail.
Such a journey may
take a thousand lifetimes.
Across the vast
expanse of as many worlds.
But... it will happen.
It will happen.
Are you going to Aekuni Temple?
I am. I would like
to make an offering.
Perhaps you should consider
traveling with a companion.
I would rather not.
This is something
I feel I should do myself.
That is very admirable of you.
But, father... tell me...
The scroll that the
late Lord Ieyasu possessed,
the one from the ninja war.
Do you know what became of it?
I do not.
The time of peace
has finally arrived.
Iga Tsubagakure and
Kouga Manjidani fought
and died for the
sake of the Tokugawa.
Each told that glory and
prosperity awaited the victor.
These days, distance is
still kept between the clans,
but I do hear word of some
who associate with the other.
Oboro... Gennosuke... And
all of your fallen comrades who
have faded into the
darkness of history...
I will live each day the
rest of my life, remembering.
For the least I can do...
is to never forget.