Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to
build between
them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
This is the original
scroll granted to Danjo.
There's no doubt a
replica was given to
Kazamachi to
deliver to the Kouga.
We must intercept him...
To rid a web you
must eliminate the spider.
There is no room for chivalry in
a war between Ninjas, Koshiro.
If we fail our people
will die. Do you understand?
Yes.
Tenzen-sama...
Do you think Yashamaru-dono
has made it home, yet?
Hmm...
Yes, judging by the hawk's
return to the encampment...
He should arrive
at Iga Tsubagakure
late tonight or
early tomorrow morning.
Well, hopefully.
That's if he managed to
make it out of
Sunpu with his life.
Jingoro.
Hmm?
Oboro-sama may cause
trouble if she finds out...
It's best if we leave
her in the dark for now...
As long as the contents of
the scroll are kept hidden from
Gennosuke and Udono,
they pose no threat.
I understand. Treat
them as honored guests.
But, if I get the chance,
do I have permission
to kill Gennosuke?
Hmm. Don't fool yourself.
Gennosuke is not someone
who can be killed so easily.
Those eyes of his... there's
something unnerving about them.
He is a frightening adversary.
We can't afford
to make mistakes...
Don't do anything until
we get back. Understood?
Hmm... Don't worry.
Good... Now then...
Let us find Kazamachi...
Remember, no mercy will
be spared to our enemy...
What's wrong?
That carriage next to
us is transporting a Kouga!
Kill the carriage bearers only!
You are a Kouga I presume...
Step out of
the carriage... Now.
And what would
you do, if I told you no?
I recognize you... that face...
Are you not Jimushi Jyubei?
I didn't know I was
so well known out here...
I guess a beautiful face
like mine is hard to forget.
Where were you
heading in the carriage?
Heh... What carriage? The
one you so rudely destroyed?
Enough!
My apologies... We
were under the impression
you were someone else.
That's why we attacked...
I am Tenzen of the Iga clan.
Hmm.
We're all on edge. Ogen
hasn't returned from Sunpu...
We fear that something dreadful
may have happened to her.
Yes... I understand...
I saw misfortune in his stars
and I too fear
for Danjo-sama's life.
Astrology...
So that is your talent?
I can handle this alone.
I want the four of you to go...
Find Kazamachi
Shogen and kill him.
Now...
I know that you're one of
the Kouga Manjidani Ten.
You didn't become one of
the best Kouga Ninjas
with your Astrology...
No. You have
many special talents.
Tell me what techniques are
used by the Kouga Manjidani Ten!
Answer! Or I'll
chop off your head!
Why do you laugh?
Your stars show
misfortune as well!
If my enemies learned
of my secret technique...
I wouldn't last
more than a day.
So the Iga are annihilating
the Kouga Ninjas...
Why now? Something unexpected
must have happened at Sunpu.
And I'm going
to find out what.
I think marriage
between the Kouga
and the Iga is a
great idea! Don't you?
He's a mess... Sorry.
Hmm? Hmm.
Look, Akeginu-dono!
The ancient Ninja hand-holding
technique! Let's try it!
This is it! It's begun!
You're Igas... You would
defy the No-Hostilities Pact
and attack a helpless Kouga?
We know the pact has been
broken and you have the scroll.
Hand it over!
Scroll? Now how
did you know about that?
Do not underestimate
the Iga Clan.
We know all about the
scroll and its contents.
Well since you put it
that way, I guess I only have
one option don't I? To cross out
your names with your own blood!
Not a chance!
I thought I was going
to have to miss dinner...
What an unexpected treat...
I love eating brains...
and Iga brains all the more.
Now... who wants
to be the first course?
Look at the size of that head. I
must say, you are well endowed.
You must have a brain
the size of a watermelon.
I usually save the best for last
but this is too good to pass up.
Now how do you
want to be eaten?
Dead... or alive?
It is you who will be food!
Arise, arise,
my sleeping flies.
Latch onto his web and
light a path. Then eat away at
his silken thread. And finish
him off like a smothering wind.
You must not sway,
don't let him fight.
Devour this spider,
savor each bite!
Now! Quick!
Throw Koshiro's sickle!!
Did I not mention?!
My hair's more dangerous
than my hands and feet!
We all have our secrets!
Now you know mine!
No!
Damn!
Huh?
Jyubei!
Death awaits you Kouga!
Is Yashamaru-dono still alive?
Tell me!
Tell me! Tell me, damn you!
Yashamaru-dono.
Got you now!
Damn he's fast!
You seem to be in a dilemma.
You need to get by me,
but you can't do it
without dropping the scroll.
How else will you be
able to use the dagger that's
hidden in your throat?
That's it, right?
That's your secret.
What do the stars
say now, Jyubei?
That trick only works once.
Tenzen!
Jyubei won't be
troubling us anymore.
One copy should be enough.
We have no
need for two scrolls.
What became of Kazamachi?
He's dead... I made sure of it.
Seven still remain.
Indeed. We're well ahead.
It appears Fortune is on
our side... it's Destiny.
The Iga will conquer the Kouga.
You're excited.
Now who's walking fast?
Come in...
Welcome to Tsubagakure.
You beat us back.
Goodness. You came, too?
I left early to make
preparations for the feast.
Jingoro spares no expense
when he throws a party.
Especially for
such important guests.
We're honored to be here.
I wish Grandmother was back.
She'd be happy
to see you again.
I smell sake... Is
Iga sake sweet? Or sour?
Amid a maelstrom of hatred,
a piercing enemy takes flight.
Blinded by loyalty and trust,
forgiveness will be the
end of one ninja's life.
Brethren, ignoring true
love's unwavering path,
cloud the night
like a dark crimson mist
drenched with
treachery and deceit.
Weak and worn, a cunning
assassin laughs mockingly.
On the next Basilisk,
"The Horned Owl."