Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to build
between them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
Pardon me.
Tenzen-sama.
You summoned me, Ogen-sama.
Yes, Tenzen. I must ask you...
When the Oda made their
initial attack against us,
where in the battle were you?
I am ashamed to
say that I missed it.
The moment fighting commenced,
I received a single
gunshot wound and died.
I heard something Ogen-sama.
Apparrently, you missed
the perfect opportunity
to kill Kouga Danjo.
A pity. I assume that
taking such harsh
action proved too much.
You were deceived
by someone for whom
you held such strong feelings.
Even the boldest
of warriors could find
such a thing overwhelming.
But please do not consider this
a failure by any means.
Danjo being alive has
unified the Iga more than
his death ever could.
I take my leave of you.
Tenzen, please wait.
Forgive my weakness.
Ogen-sama. The
insults are over.
I will not allow the
past mistakes to be repeated.
Oboro-sama will be mine.
And Gennosuke...
I will bury him
with my own hands.
The sounds of
the wind are chilling.
Perhaps they bother
you because they are
actually curses
of the dead.
Tell me, Gennosuke-sama...
After the things
we heard tonight,
are you having
any second thoughts?
This cannot be stopped.
The bloodshed of both
Kouga and Iga will continue
until one is eradicated
from this world.
Only on that day
will this war end.
Where is Gennosuke-sama?
I asked him to get some rest and
stay out of sight for a while.
If the Iga are being
protected by the Tokugawa,
the tide will hasten
a turn in our direction.
But Gennosuke-sama
has made up his mind.
He said himself
that he is prepared to
kill Oboro and the Iga.
Even more reason to hide him.
We need our leader
to survive at all costs.
It is he who carries us.
We need him to follow through
with the goal that we
may be unable to complete.
Listen... Kagero.
The sun will always rise
and set. This is a constant.
But during the next few cycles,
how many more
lives will be lost?
I do not wish to appear
this way any more than
Gennosuke-sama wishes to hide.
But we do our part so those
in Kouga can live their lives.
Do you believe
we can win?
Be alert. We must
assure our guests' safety.
Oboro-sama!
No, you can't.
You must stay inside.
Akeginu, I am sorry,
but I wish to walk.
I want to feel the
earth beneath my feet.
I do not want to
forget this one thing.
That we are truly alive,
and part of the world.
Just what do you
think are you doing?!
Don't you realize the Kouga
could attack at any second.
You must exercise more caution.
We're moving right now!
To your positions men!
Yes, sir.
She refused breakfast
and has not touched
the dinner before her.
Let her do as she pleases.
She need only survive until
the successorship
has been made official.
Halt, right there!
This inn houses a
important person who
enjoys their privacy.
There are no vacancies.
Interesting... Now what
important person would that be?
A vagrant like you
doesn't need to know.
Now get out of here
before I remove you myself!
What are you doing?!
We need help!
There's an intruder, men!
Tenzen-sama!
You're mistaken.
He's our ally.
I am sorry for the
confusion, Tenzen-sama.
But... these men
are merely vassals.
They're with Lady Ofuku,
who is the wetnurse for
Lord Takechiyo, the
Shogun's firstborn.
Their party came upon Oboro
and I when we found Koshiro.
Then she is in
line with the Shogun?
Please, Tenzen-sama.
Listen. We must tell her.
Explain it. Why we are here.
There is no time. I
have other pressing issues.
I have located a Kouga.
The woman who is known
to her people as Kagero.
I saw her at Imurebashi,
waiting, or so it seemed.
It is likely that the
ones for whom she is waiting
are none other than Kouga
Gennosuke and Kisaragi Saemon.
If you're going on
a hunt for Kouga blood,
we would like
to lend our support.
You would be wise to
leave war to the soldiers.
The fight that
rages is not yours.
The Kouga are much
too formidable an opponent
for the likes of you.
Do not forget that
we are Iga by birth.
Our pride would
never allow us to
have anyone hurt
our enemies but us.
If you did not know, Kagero
is the one who killed Koshiro.
Koshiro-dono...
But I saw him there. He
died while fighting Hyoma.
So you were to understand.
But from what I know
this Kagero woman
is a stealthy type,
who will gladly
steal a kiss from a man
just before turning
her breath into poison.
You didn't find any wounds
on Koshiro's body, did you?
This treacherous art
takes no effect on women.
So I'm afraid I must ask you--
Tenzen-sama!
You must wait for a moment
while I retrieve something.
We can't.
Oh, Tenzen-sama!
Akeginu. Is that
what I think it is?
Please forgive me! I
know that he is our enemy,
but to Oboro-sama,
he is the man she loves!
I didn't think it right to
send her into the world with
nothing to remember him by.
Think nothing of it.
I will allow this, but
we will speak no more of it.
This woman you call Ofuku,
is she prepared to use
all her resources to
kill the Kouga herself?
Yes.
Then she is a fool. The
succession is not something that
any Kouga or Iga would consider.
What exists between our people
is hatred and vengeance,
a drive to bring
this age-old feud to a close.
If any of us were to use
outsiders to bring about
victory, we would disgrace all
of those who died before us.
Their souls could
never rest in peace
after such an indiscretion.
I agree... I've felt that
way about this conflict since
I was just a young girl.
I want to ensure no Kouga
ever see the sun rise again.
This war... It is my war and it
will only end when they all die.
I wish, though, that
through these dark days
Oboro-sama would
not be without sight.
I worry for her. Her eyes...
She must make it to Sunpu.
They are a serious
problem for all our interests.
I don't much want to be
in a war between two clans.
But Lady Ofuku has ordered this.
This flute of Kouga Gennosuke...
You have had it with you
since last being in Tsubagakure?
Yes.
From what I've come to
understand, it was given to
Oboro-sama as
a token of farewell
and remembrance from Gennosuke.
Then why do you keep it?
It is not your gift to
give and receive at will.
If it is Oboro-sama's,
then she should have it.
This flute might quell
the longing inside her.
It may do the opposite.
The human heart is
more difficult to understand
than anything. Especially
the heart of your enemy.
No matter how you may
meditate over the subject,
the answers simply do not come.
It is one of
the oldest mysteries.
Is something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's time. Are you ready?
Yes.
Where is Gennosuke?
He's not here to protect you?
I challenge you.
That's funny, because
I've been waiting for you...
Akeginu.
Die!
Ogen-sama, Rousai-dono,
Nenki-dono, Jingoro-dono,
Hotarubi, Yashamaru-dono!
This is for Koshiro!
You're dead!
Tenzen-sama!
Oboro will be
joining you very soon.
And I hope your blood
stains the road to hell,
leading her back to you.
The Kouga and the Iga...
We are all the same
in birth and in death.
All of us human, we need to
break these bindings of hatred
and revenge which hold us.
We need to open our eyes
to the other side. To the Iga.
Even if it is
only one of them,
then that one we will try
to know and better understand.
It is not possible. The time to
know the other side has passed.
It is time to finish...
this bloody war.
You did a very nice job gaining
her trust. I commend you.
Thank you.
Only one remains alive. Oboro.
If you don't mind, I would
like to be the one to kill her.
It would be my honor.
Perhaps you are unaware.
Oboro's eyes have been blinded.
Well, do you
think we should go?
Greetings men. Please forgive
me for my earlier rudeness.
I did not know you
were the Lady's vassals.
I was raised in a place
where niceties are seldom used,
so I ended up a bit
rough around the edges.
I hope you understand.
I do not see Akeginu.
Is she with you here?
No. She has gone.
Went Kouga hunting.
Specifically for
their leader Gennosuke.
She did? Where is he?
We know he was seriously
injured in a conflict.
All likelihood points to
him ending up dead on some road.
Akeginu went
searching just to be sure.
According to Akeginu-dono,
one Kouga woman also remained.
She said that this
woman is a crafty one
who goes by the name of Kagero.
I know this woman.
I have been holding
her captive for some time.
And what have
you done with her?
First I tied her up.
Then I went about
making her into a woman.
And the strangest
thing happened.
She now favors solely
the flesh of the Iga.
Interesting... Yes...
You are truly a warrior.
I should have known. Your
strength back at the Inn was
the first clue to your
greatness. We are all quite
fortunate to have such
staggering power on our side.
But there is something about you
that I am most overwhelmed by.
Akeginu-dono told us that
you have a great
ability, don't you?
She said no matter
how many wounds are
inflicted on your body,
you will never die.
She said that you
are an immortal ninja.
What?
Tears for those lost
fall like blood from a blade.
Aware of deception,
a warrior's baited breath
hangs heavy in the air.
The flesh of those loved
and lost can
tempt like moth to flame,
as the fires of
passion burn brighter than
even those of revenge.
All roads lead to death,
but passion may prove
an even quicker
path to the end.
On the next Basilisk,
"With All Her Heart."