Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to build
between them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
All this rain...
falling on Kouga and Iga...
Eventually it will cease.
For at some point, the clouds
must make room for the sun.
Tenzen, is there something
you need to tell me?
Tenzen?
I've given this
matter much thought...
And I'll be as
forward with you as I can.
I hope you can
forgive my bluntness.
Oboro-sama... You
must listen very carefully.
The retired Shogun
Ieyasu has ordered
that the pact be dissolved.
It has come to an end...
And so...
the hostilities between
Iga and Kouga will rise again.
We are at war.
You're not...
You're not serious...
The shackles that
suppressed the hatred between
the Kouga and the Iga for four
hundred years have been broken.
The retired Shogun
Lord Ieyasu has ordered
both clans to gather strength.
He said, "we
face each other..."
And to fight to the bitter end.
What?
If you doubt the
news that I bring,
read Lord Ieyasu's
scroll for yourself.
What scroll?
Oboro-sama the time has come
for you to harden your heart.
This is all a lie!
The Iga and the
Kouga are at war.
Even if the
truce is nullified...
we can't fight each other...
We can't allow this to happen!
Gennosuke-sama would agree.
I have to go tell him.
Wait!
You can tell him if you wish,
but your efforts to inform
the enemy will be in vain.
It has already begun.
You're right.
You do have more to
offer than that old man.
I'm going to suck every
ounce of blood out of you.
Stop whatever it
is you're doing, Rousai.
Tenzen needs the
ninja scroll immediately.
You, whore!
You're dead!
They've actually
locked away a Kouga woman?
Yes. A younger
woman named Okoi.
She was listed as one of
the Manjidani ten
on the ninja scroll.
Listed on the ninja scroll?
Yashamaru, you can't
tell me you know nothing of
the register or its purpose.
Of course, I know about it.
What are you going to do?
I'm... I'm going
to find that Kouga girl.
You certainly have some
fine skills, Kouga wench.
But you can take that as
the last compliment
you'll ever receive.
What's happening?
I need more of his skin.
I have to touch him.
What is that?!
I've had enough of
your trickery, you whore.
I was ordered not to kill you.
But you don't leave
me much of a choice.
After all, your name is
on Ieyasu's ninja scroll.
This body will be of no use
to you anymore, my young one.
Now that the truce is
broken, coming to this place
means certain death.
That's what is being said.
I can't believe
that Kouga girl.
Sneaking into Tsubagakure.
She's either brave or foolish.
Don't you think so, Yashamaru?
Okoi...
My brother...
Oh... Greetings Yashamaru...
Are you just now returning?
Nenki, what happened?
Keep your mouth shut about this.
You didn't answer me.
Did you just get back?
Yes.
This is the first I've seen.
Since I've
returned to this place.
What the hell are
you sitting down for?
I think some of
Hotarubi's snake venom
may still be coursing
through my veins.
Fooled around with
another woman, did ya now?
Come on. I'm
just playing with you.
Enough with the glaring? Look!
I said it was just a joke.
Hey! I'm just kidding
Hotarubi! Put that knife away!
Okoi... Okoi...
Okoi...
My... brother...
Please forgive me, Okoi.
I was too late.
Brother... I killed
one of them... he was old.
An old man.
You did? I'm proud of you.
You've always been strong.
Even stronger than me.
Between the bales...
there is a scroll...
Do you hear?
You have to find it.
I will.
Brother... My dear brother...
My brother...
My brother... My brother...
Woman, I've
had enough of you...
Yashamaru, what
happened in Sunpu?
I cannot speak a word of
it until I see Oboro-sama.
You've haven't
talked to her yet?
That should've been
the first thing you did.
Tenzen-sama sought
her for a private meeting
some time ago, and she's
still there, I think.
Yeah, he really has
his work cut out for him if
he's trying to
put the moves on her.
It's actually kind of
funny if you think about it.
Even though the
war between the Kouga
and the Iga has finally begun,
Oboro-sama still
spends her time trying to
convince herself she's
in love with Gennosuke!
From what I hear...
Gennosuke's being kept alive.
That's right.
Tenzen-sama's too afraid of him
to bother doing
anything about it.
That's probably because
we don't have a clue as to
what Gennosuke's
really capable of.
Doesn't look like much to me.
Let me go and get
some medicine for you.
I often question
Tenzen's motives,
but that ninja
scroll is evidence of
our battle superiority.
Following him, we've killed
Kazamachi, Jyubei and Udono.
And let's not forget my
excellent handling of Okoi.
But still...
I don't understand..
Why is he holding back
from defeating Gennosuke?
I forgot about the ninja scroll.
I need to go find out what
the hell Rousai did with it.
Jingoro? What happened?
How'd you get that way?
Water...
Please help, me... Water!
Out you go, drink up.
That should be
enough water for you.
Rousai!
Hotarubi, what is it?
Is that Rousai?
Oboro-sama, please wait!
No! I cannot allow this!
Keeping that woman from
Manjidani locked up in here!
This is not how we operate!
I will not be a party to this!
Who is that?
Oboro-sama, listen!
We must not turn back!
Oboro-sama!
Yashamaru?
What's wrong with him?
Yashamaru-dono?
He's a Kouga!
I'll kill the bastard!
Princess!
The scroll!
It's the register!
Jingoro-dono! Turn around!
What? Yes, I've got it!
What the hell's that!
Ha!
Impossible...
That looks like...
Kasumino... Gyobu.
Where is he?
The one who disguised
himself as Yashamaru?!
We must not let
the Kouga escape!
After him!
You won't get away from me!
Koshiro...
Yes?
Gather everyone.
Gyobu...
Saemon...
The time has come for
our return... to Manjidani.
A man stands in the rain,
shimmering through the drops.
His heart, all that he is,
sinks deeply into
anger and resentment.
Quiet in its remorse. Now,
this young leader will ignore
the powerful call of love to
make a choice, as he stands
balanced only
for the time being,
between life and extinction.
On the next Basilisk,
"Farewell."