Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to build
between them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
Men are such fools.
That's it. Your shift
is over. It's my turn.
What happened?!
He's... He's dead!
Kill or be killed...
to the very end.
Finally...
The Kouga are victorious.
And now, Oboro,
is your time to die.
What is this?
A proclamation?
What does it say?
Now let's see.
This thing says...
"To where has
Kouga Gennosuke escaped?"
"We have the only
other remaining Kouga,
Kagero, in our custody.
For the time being she will
be interrogated to
the breaking point,
and in two days
she will be executed."
Executed?
"If you are truly the
leader of the Kouga as
so many have claimed
you to be, then you will
emerge from your cowardly hiding
place to save this poor woman.
Do you have the skills
of a warrior and leader
as you have professed?
If so, then bring the
scroll and come to us."
"We will gladly bind you like
a hog the way we did Kagero
and drag you both to Sunpu."
"Signed, Oboro of the Iga."
What is this about anyway?
I don't know, but
I saw this same sign
posted in Kanaya
yesterday afternoon.
Who cares?
Sounds like
someone's pretty angry.
He's forsaken you, Kagero.
Don't you think?
You actually caught
me by surprise.
I would have
never thought that
your sickly sweet
breath was poison.
Oboro-dono!
Tenzen!
I cannot speak for Oboro,
but I am almost impressed at
how urgent and nasty
this war has become.
Were that not the case,
I would have gladly spent
a few more days sucking
at your venomous breath
and dying in your arms.
Why don't you finish
this? Just kill me.
Of course, that is the idea.
But why rush the fun part?
Give me a few more
hours of of enjoyment,
and then tomorrow morning, I
promise to grant you your wish.
Stop! Tenzen
you must stop this!
Tenzen...
Even blind, you managed to
climb all this way on your own.
A feat that proves your
worthiness of being a leader.
Tenzen you have to stop.
It has gone too far.
I can't take it. This
torture cannot continue.
Oboro-sama.
I must express my
renewed admiration for you.
After all, using
this Kouga woman to
lure Gennosuke from
the shadows was your idea.
I could not have forged
a better plan myself.
Lady Ofuku is just as
impressed with you as I am.
She says you are
a true ninja leader.
She is, however, surprised
that such an innocent face
could devise
such a devious plan.
Tenzen, regardless
of who she is,
allowing her a quick
death would be merciful.
Merciful?
We are trapped
in a living hell.
This woman may be our
enemy, but she's human.
You must show her compassion!
Compassion? And mercy?
I find it odd...
I hear those words dripping
from the mouths of warriors
so much these days.
But as for me, I have
no concept of such
useless things as these. I only
know what I've always known.
No... Tenzen...
What is this?!
What are you doing?!
Just altering the plan a bit.
Kagero is special.
She possesses the
ability of a toxic breath
during times of sexual arousal.
We'll let her watch as we
consummate our relationship.
Then, when she is aroused
and her breath turns lethal.
You will use your mystic eye
and strip her of her power.
Tenzen... Let me go, please!
When you're done, I will be
able to take Kagero in any way
I please and I won't have
to worry about dying again.
No!
I will never do
such a thing! My eyes--
Oboro-sama... Do you
know how many days it has been
since we left our village?
The Iga are the
victors in this war.
And tomorrow, you will walk
with me into Sunpu as my wife.
The way it was destined to be.
No! No!
Tenzen, stop! Please! No!
Yakushiji Tenzen.
He's here...
You're alive...
Why did this happen?
Why am I alive? You should
know the answer to that.
It's simple.
I am alive so I can
send you to hell myself!
Gennosuke-sama!
Oboro-sama, I am
quite proud of you.
This sad, blind
Kouga fell feet first
right into the
trap you set for him.
You have brought an end
to this war for our people.
This moment will be considered
a great turning
point in Iga history.
But... You must leave
this final kill to me.
It is my understanding that you
were trained by Muroga Hyoma.
However...
Without your Dojutso,
you would lose even a battle
with a falling
tree in the forest.
No, Gennosuke-sama...
You're not holding together
very well, Gennosuke.
If I were you, I would
try begging for my life.
Depending on how pathetic
you are, I might consider
dragging you only
half-dead to Sunpu. Once our
audience with Retired
Shogun Ieyasu is complete,
if you are still breathing, I
would even consider allowing you
to tag along with Oboro-sama
and me as our servant.
You can never have too many.
Oboro-sama...
Just a while ago
you said you felt as if
you were inside
of a living Hell.
If such a thing
as Hell truly exists,
my knowledge of
it surpasses yours.
Hell is enduring the pain
of death, only to be reborn.
This limbo I suffer has the
persistence of the rising sun.
Never a sign of salvation or
deliverence into the next world.
To me, that is Hell!
You Kouga bastard!
Gennosuke-sama?
This fight is over.
You should see that.
No, Tenzen.
The time for last
requests has passed.
Tell me. Why are you
filled with such loathing?
There was a time when
the Iga were focused.
They did nt question
their hated toward the Kouga.
However, over time
these feelings began
to fade like a bad dream.
The reason being, fewer
and fewer of our people had
personal experiences
of this hatred.
Then it was you. Was it not?
You were the one so long
ago who betrayed the Kouga.
It was near the
end of the Tensho wars,
and you had
formulated a plan.
It was the perfect opportunity
and I had to take advantage.
The Iga people were on
the edge of annihilation.
If the attack from
the Oda had never happened,
Tsubagakure would
have been shackled by the
relationship of
Kouga Danjo and Ogen-sama.
Then Hattori Hanzo
the first had to step in.
I must say that I
didn't see this move coming.
I had not one
notion he would
draw up the No-Hostilities
Pact between us.
It was a
simple miscalculation.
Ogen-sama... and Danjo-sama...
Tenzen... You
manipulated our families.
I would not say
that I "manipulated" them.
No. I simply made sure
that they would continue to
hate each other for
as long as they lived.
Gennosuke-sama...
The Iga and Kouga will
put an end to this rivalry.
Here and now!
In war, first blood
must always be drawn before
the final drop falls.
The time between is a world of
tears glimmering with
the hope for life itself.
Forbidden love binds both sides
lost in the madness of hate.
Yet this distant spark of light
in the darkness may well be
the ember of
hope still glowing.
On the next Basilisk,
"Emancipation."