Two tribes sworn to hate...
Their bloodstained bodies
left out in the open to rot.
Their souls longing for a
peace that they failed to find.
As they sought to break
the shackles of darkness
and heal the
wounds of the past,
Fate denied their quest
and thrust them into war.
The bridges of
hope some dared to build
between them were torn asunder.
Their dreams were ripped from
their hearts with a sword...
with their destiny
revealed at last.
Okoi is no more.
They killed her.
Gyobu...
Saemon...
It's time for our
return... to Manjidani.
How cruel!
Oboro-sama...
Akeginu, you've been
deceiving me this whole time.
Did you kill Udono-sama, too?!
Yes.
Oboro-sama!
Gennosuke-sama! I'll
die if they've hurt you!
Why is he hesitating?
We have the advantage!
Make haste! What
are you waiting for?!
Attack us or
move out of our way!
Oh, I see... Terror has frozen
you cowards in your tracks.
Igas! Attack!
No! Wait!
Tenzen!
Tenzen?
What's the matter?
What are we waiting for?
We must attack!
Don't be hasty! We must
wait for Kouga Gennosuke
to make the first move. His
intentions are still unclear.
Heh! Hanzo's
pact is finally broken
and they're too scared to fight.
They're not always fearful...
not when they
have the advantage.
Like when they killed my sister.
Did it please you to murder
an innocent woman,
you twisted bastard?
You killed Yashamaru-dono!
Yashamaru? That's right.
Damn you. Murderers!
Control yourself, Hotarubi.
Who are you to give me orders,
you disgusting filthy Kouga?!
You spoke to me earlier
of killing Kazamachi.
Tell me, does that not
make you a murderer as well?
Don't pity that whore
Okoi. She tried to kill me!
Jingoro! That's Enough!
Now control yourself!
Do not be provoked!
Atta-aa-ck! In the
name of Iga honor kill them!
All of them!
Nenki!
Gennosuke-sama!
I knew that he had hidden powers
but this! This is madness!
We cannot allow him to
make it off of Iga soil alive,
or defeat may be certain. But
who could withstand his Dojutso?
Koshiro!
No! Koshiro!
Oboro-sama. You must be strong.
This war...
It cannot be stopped.
Stop! That's far
enough, Gennosuke!
Turn and fight, you coward!
You're making a
mistake Koshiro-sama.
We'll see... won't we?!
Yes, we will.
Do you really think those
blades are going to save you?
Your tricks may work
on the weak-minded, Kouga.
But they won't work on me!
Well, he's got guts,
but he's obviously
lacking in brains.
Those burning eyes!
I have seen this sort of thing
before but this is unparalleled.
The terror on their faces.
What force could overcome
the mind that would make
another take their own life?
Koshiro can defeat Gennosuke...
But it's sure to take
more than sickles and knives.
Gennosuke-sama...
This next attack will decide
the outcome of the battle.
Yes, that's it. Use
your Cyclone Death Song!
No man can defend
himself against this attack.
Not even Gennosuke
has a chance of survival.
Its sheer force will rip
his head right from his body!
The vacuum will steal their
air in a matter of seconds.
And then comes
the finishing blow!
Stop, Koshiro! Please!
Oboro-sama!
Please! I beg you! No more!
Akeginu! Why didn't
you hold her back?!
I'm sorry. I-I wasn't thinking.
This isn't the time!
Move out of the way!
Please don't ask
me to move. I can't.
I don't want either
one of you to die.
Oboro-sama! You'll get
him killed! Look behind you!
He's the one! Gennosuke!
It's his lethal technique that
you need to stop! Not Koshiro's!
Why do you think he has his
eyes closed?! It's a defense!
He's protecting
himself against you!
He knows your gaze
will mean his death!
Oboro-sama! Stand behind
Koshiro as he attacks!
Look at Gennosuke and
we can end this war now!
Koshiro's Cyclone
Death Song pitted against
Gennosuke's
mind-stripping Dojutsu.
We'll see whose skill
will come out victorious!
Koshiro! No! Please stop this!
I don't want him to die!
Koshiro!
Damn! She'll be
the death of us all!
Gennosuke-sama!
No! Please! Don't go!
Love has turned a deaf ear...
Gennosuke-sama,
please, come back to me.
He lives. But he
has permanent damage.
He punished his eyes with
his unforgiving Death Song.
I see... Stay by
his side night and day.
As you wish, Tenzen-sama.
Oboro-sama... Your
behavior out there...
It was inexcusable. Damn
it! You should know better!
If you were not
Old Ogen's successor,
you would have no place here!
I'm sorry, Tenzen. Truly.
Don't apologize! Not to me!
Apologize to your Ancestors
and your Grandmother!
To the 400 year old
Iga Clan that you betrayed!
Three of the Iga
Ten have been slain...
Ogen-dono... Rousai...
and Yashamaru as well.
And now, Koshiro has
suffered serious injury.
To make matters worse, they made
off with Ogen-dono's scroll.
According to the terms of
the war we must have it to win.
Why must you
insist on complaining.
We've waited our
whole lives for this day,
we should be celebrating!
We'll slay every last one
of them! Death to the Kouga!
Years from now
the Kouga will be
nothing more
than a distant memory!
You're right, Nenki. But
in order to achieve victory
Oboro-sama must agree to take
her place and stand at our helm.
It's your birthright...
You're our chieftess...
We can not defeat
Gennosuke without you.
On the grave of
your Grandmother Ogen,
swear that you'll use your
power to help us slay him!
Oboro-sama!
I can not...
I can not use my power
to kill Gennosuke-sama.
You must! How can you think
of denying your own people?!
What about all of
our innocent children?!
Whether they live
or die depends on
you and the power
of your Mystic Eye!
I don't understand, Tenzen.
Why all this hatred?
Why are the Kouga
considered our mortal enemy?
I know why you have
asked this question.
Because of your Grandmother...
She raised you
as an innocent girl.
She chose not to
speak of bad things.
Such what the
Kouga did to us...
after the Oda army
attacked Tsubagakure.
What do you mean
after the Oda attacked?
What'd they do? Tell me.
Your Grandmother
insisted that we were
not to speak of such things.
She didn't want
you to be troubled.
That's why you
never heard the story.
Yes... None of us
knew why that was so.
The Oda destroyed our village.
The Kouga had
nothing to do with it.
That's true, Oboro-sama...
But the Kouga learned about
the Oda's surprise
attack before it occurred.
So they waited for
us in the forest.
They killed our
survivors as they fled.
Of course, they were too
cowardly to own up to it.
That's right.
The Kougas denied that they
were ever there that night.
But your Grandmother saw them
attack us with her own eyes.
If not for the Hattori's
No-Hostilities Pact,
we would have killed them
all long ago. Spineless scum.
But even so... Gennosuke-sama
and the others had
nothing to do with that!
Nor did we, for that matter!
We are the descendants!
We must avenge our ancestors!
And you're our leader!
What more needs be said?
Before the horrors
of that night took place,
your Grandmother
Ogen-dono was planning to
marry Danjo of the Kouga.
Ogen's situation was not unlike
the one you're facing now.
Danjo begged
her to continue their
love affair but
she wouldn't have it.
She forsook her
own heart's desire
for the good of her people.
She knew it was her duty
to lead the Iga and
she dedicated her life to it.
And Danjo, the same man
that begged her for her love,
is the one who
murdered her in Sunpu.
So bury your emotions
and become the leader that
you were born to be!
Your Grandmother
will be proud if you do.
I need a little time.
Please, excuse me.
I think that did it.
I wish I was like you,
Grandmother. So strong and wise.
Please, forgive me.
I don't see Udono.
Okoi isn't with them either.
Saemon-dono is
covered in blood!
What is your
decision, Oboro-sama?
Chieftess. Have you taken
ill? You don't look well.
Oboro-sama!
The secret chambers resonate
with tales of bloodshed,
while the architects
of war watch coldly from
their seats of power.
Innocents, ignorant of
the unseen river of blood
are unaware that
ambitious serpents
are waiting to strike
and shape their destiny.
Like ninja shadows,
skillful spies become
the eyes of a fading ruler.
On the next Basilisk:
"Divine Mandate."