Yay!
Wow!
Huh?
Hmm.
Wow!
Hmm?
Huh?
Onh.
Yes.
Hmm.
Ket.
Hmm?
Huh?
Bye!
Why?
Now.
Wow.
Hmm?
Huh?
Hey!
Hmm?
Wow!
Yes.
Yup.
Hey!
Fly.
Huh?
Yeah.
Okay.
Ciao!
Uh...
Hmph!
What?
Okay.
Uh...
Jiji.
Yeah.
Um...
Okay.
Jiji.
What?
Kiki?
Okay.
Jiji.
Um...
Okay.
What?
Jiji?
Kiki.
Sure.
Okay.
Kiki?
What?
Kiki.
Jiji.
Ta-da!
Hello?
Why...
Naked?
Osono?
Right.
Tombo!
Tombo.
Well...
I will.
It was.
Thanks.
I know.
Boring.
See ya.
Thanks.
Uh-huh.
But me?
Oh, my.
Uh-huh.
Thanks.
Oh, my.
Mmm-hmm.
Hold on!
Hold on.
A phone?
All day.
Mmm-hmm.
Bye-bye.
Why not?
Oh, boy!
Mmm-hmm.
Come on.
Like it?
Sure is.
Mmm-hmm.
Come on!
Hey, Mom.
Uh, Kiki?
Let's go.
Sure can.
I'm done.
Let's go.
Not that.
I'm okay.
Hurry up.
Go, Kiki.
Thank you.
Now, Kiki,
Bye, Kiki.
Oh, great.
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
Don't you?
Whoa, boy.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Please do.
Thank you.
Breakfast.
All right?
Dirigible?
Your face.
I'm sorry.
Over here.
Watch out!
There. Dad.
Sorry, Dad.
Here we go!
Be careful.
Fly safely.
Go get 'em!
How lovely.
No problem.
Hey, Tombo.
Here we go.
Oh! A nest!
Oh! Oh, no!
Okay, okay.
Jiji? Jiji?
Yes, but...
Mmm. Hmm...
What is it?
Watch this.
I was sick.
Oh, my God!
Hey, Tombo!
Kiki? Kiki?
Be careful.
Very pretty.
It's so big!
My pleasure.
That's okay.
Yeah. I can.
She sure is.
Almost done.
That's okay.
Here we are.
Well, maybe.
Now we wait.
There we go.
Here you go.
Okay. Ready?
Look at him.
I don't know.
Good morning.
Thief! Thief!
There you go.
Oh, be quiet.
This is dumb.
Anybody here?
Barsa. Barsa.
We're flying.
I have to go.
Come on, Jiji.
Yes, midnight.
Hey, you, kid.
Hey! Don't go.
Oh, poor baby.
There you are.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Can I breathe?
Uh, I'm sorry.
There you are.
No, I'm tired.
Come on, Jiji.
Stop worrying.
Fly carefully.
Wake up, Kiki.
Where are you?
Taking a walk?
Yeah. Are you?
Yeah, me, too.
Well, I'll be.
What happened?
Get him, Kiki.
Of course I am.
Uh! Kiki, wait.
You're no help.
Oh. Yeah, sure.
Look. Up ahead.
Ready, set, go!
Oh, never mind.
Let's go, Jiji.
This is quaint.
Can I help out?
Hey. Pull over.
Leave me alone.
That's my girl.
How's it going?
Ah, no problem.
You understand?
I don't get it.
It's a miracle.
Dad. Guess what?
Or maybe a town?
Kiki, it's time.
Fortune-telling?
What's my skill?
My name's Osono.
All right, then.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my gosh. No.
I could use help.
No, no breathing.
What do you want?
Certainly, madam.
Um... Never mind.
Should I get off?
Afternoon, ma'am.
Oh, dear. Oh! Oh!
You're going away?
Hey. Good evening.
He's getting away!
Thank you so much.
Morning, everyone.
You're a bit late.
That's no problem.
Are you all right?
I'm gonna be late.
Help. Barsa, come.
I have a delivery.
Kiki, there he is.
Gee, thanks a lot.
What do you think?
What's the matter?
Hey. Look at that.
That's why I came?
Kiki. How are you?
You've got a deal.
Aye, aye, Captain.
She can fly again.
Oh, Barsa. Oh, my.
then what'll we do?
Where are we going?
Wow! A clock tower.
No, sir, I'm alone.
Did you sleep well?
Huh? But that's me.
Please hurry, Kiki.
Hello. Anyone home?
Oh, no, I couldn't.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
There you go. Here.
We're quite a team.
You mean that's me?
You're very pretty.
Come on. Over here.
You can do it. Yes.
I'm glad about that.
You be strong. Okay?
Aim your broomstick.
You okay back there?
Thanks, mister. Bye.
Wait. Wait a minute.
And I'm Kiki, ma'am.
Well, look who's up.
Kiki, look. It's me.
We've gotta go back.
We have to. Hold on!
Yeah. Give it to me.
I've gotta run. Bye!
Thank you very much.
How are you? Hungry?
I do this every day.
Hey, what'd you get?
We're going on this?
Kick off. Now! Good!
That's all I can do.
Some friend you are.
Nice place you have.
It's beautiful here.
That sounds like me.
He's still up there.
Thank you very much.
Grab a hold of this.
And there may not be.
Now, come back again.
Any money left, Kiki?
What a charming girl.
But would you listen?
You gotta be kidding.
Ket. Did you hear me?
Ket, turn off the TV!
I mean, my customers.
Right this way, dear.
We're ready. Come on.
Have a good time now.
We've got a delivery.
Oh, you gotta see it.
My, my. How terrible.
Skies are clearing up,
They're looking at us.
Really? You'd do that?
Depends on the people.
You know how boys are.
My name's Kiki, ma'am.
Why don't you come up?
What took you so long?
Jeff helped me escape.
How much will that be?
There's the blue roof.
You are right on time.
Broom and a black cat.
Yes? What do you want?
But it is soaking wet.
The name is "Koppori"?
Oh, boy. Just hold on.
Go away? That's right.
Hey, look. Over there.
Huh? But, Kiki... Wait.
Your little baby is 13?
You're new, aren't you?
Not if nobody finds us.
Mmm. This smells great.
Somebody call the cops.
Hmm. What a cool witch.
Don't waste your money.
Yeah! We've got a deal.
His head's falling off.
Here's your invitation.
- Really? - How's work?
What a wonderful witch.
You have quite a fever.
Are you feeling better?
"Don't be such a clown.
Guess what's up, Tombo?
Hey, who's your friend?
Stay out of the street.
And come back a failure?
Won't we get in trouble?
Too many, if you ask me.
Well, of course, we are.
Hey, shut up, all right?
Well, I'll be on my way.
And the amazing thing is
Wow! This costs so much.
Yeah. I got to see this.
They seem awfully upset.
Hey. Stop that. Go away.
Leave us alone. Stop it.
Don't worry. Hold still.
Jeff's such a funny dog.
May I take that for you?
But I must admit defeat.
It should be about time.
Mmm, yummy. Herring pie.
A lot better. Thank you.
He's all yours. Bye-bye.
It's so pretty and warm.
Hey, look at that. Whoa.
Your bike's a real mess.
Uh-huh. What went wrong?
Well, that's no problem.
What? Kiki? She hung up.
Sometimes it's not easy.
Do not block the street.
After all, she is a baby.
And that's why it's good.
Will you tell my parents?
Now you stay right there.
It's right up here, Kiki.
Oh, Kiki, perfect timing.
Look at them. Up so high.
Come on, you stupid bird.
Yes. May I help you, sir?
Thank you very much. Bye.
But that's much too much.
Not for all of your help.
Maybe we still have time.
Great. You're doing fine.
What are you laughing at?
No thanks. See you later.
Hey, where are you going?
Oh, no. Talk to me, Jiji.
What's going on with him?
Hey, there. Unbelievable.
I loved to paint so much.
So I guess it's worth it.
Oh, no, no. It's useless.
Don't give up now, sonny.
Yeah. There's a full moon.
That's my town down there.
No, you can have it, Jiji.
Oh, dear. Oh, my goodness.
Hey, there! Your pacifier!
Yes. Oh, that smells good.
She's your first customer.
My, delivery time already?
Ma'am, it'll work, really.
Come on. We can catch him.
My head's hurting so much.
You're a very nice person.
Really? Wow! That's great.
Oh. Why not? It'll be fun.
What are you so mad about?
You better believe I will.
tonight might be the night.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
Can we look for a new town?
Pardon me, Miss Snooty Cat.
Osono, you're the greatest.
And they're coming with us.
Ket, dear. Turn off the TV.
But I haven't finished yet.
He sure will. He sure will.
Oh, well, this is exciting.
Not feeling very well, huh?
I think I pedaled too hard.
Forget her, Tombo. Come on.
Hello? Kiki? Are you there?
What's the matter with you?
I'm the adventuresome type.
It has broken loose from...
Come on, broom, fly for me.
Hang in there, my good lad.
Please excuse me, Miss Dora.
Oh, Mom. I look really dumb.
But, Mom, that one's so old.
Oh, yes. A lot can go wrong.
But a phone is so expensive.
She's the most amazing girl.
I think her plan is perfect.
Now, don't burn your tongue.
Hey. Hey, there, Miss Witch.
That's the dirigible, right?
Do I really look that funny?
I'll be back in a sec, okay?
Thanks, but I don't want to.
Boy, did I have a cool time.
Goodness. It's a strong one.
Congratulations, young lady.
Don't worry. He doesn't mind.
Go, Kiki. Go, Kiki. Go, Kiki.
I could reach her in no time.
Hmph! If you wake up tomorrow
It's me, you remember? Tombo.
Better luck next time, Tombo.
Great. How much will it cost?
I really need to finish this.
He'll do it. He's a good dog.
What? Pardon? Uh, yes, ma'am.
I'll take this, please. Okay?
Yes, the fire's almost ready.
Oh. How nice of you to offer.
Let me pay you for your time.
Not according to my whiskers.
I hate Grandma's stupid pies.
Only if you want to get well.
Uh-huh. Now, take this money.
Hey. Who's your friend there?
All right. We're doing great.
Huh? You just found that out?
I'm losing my witch's powers.
Please don't call me anymore.
You get along with the crows.
You think my problems will...
You've got such a great face.
Yes? Good Cooking Pan Bakery.
Barsa, bring the package now.
It's being lifted like a toy.
Don't give up. Don't give up.
I've decided to leave tonight.
All right. It's yours already.
You sound like my grandmother.
and find a white cat, it's me.
And the excitement is building
Yup. We're gonna need a phone.
Ooh, a delivery business, huh?
You mean it? Oh, that's great.
Aha! How about this much then?
Thank you. Enjoy your present.
Yeah, me, too. I'm very tired.
Is the pie baked? Is it ready?
Well, yes. Since I was a baby.
It's become very weak, so I...
It's gonna be fine. I promise.
Oh, goody! It's back on. Look.
Are you all right, young lady?
And what exactly is your skill?
Jiji, come on. I'm all through.
I'm getting sick to my stomach.
That was a long time ago, okay?
I got a brand-new home for you.
Trust me. He'll be good as new.
Could you take this in, please?
Hello. Good Cooking Pan Bakery.
I wrote the address on the box.
Oh! Oh, the box. Oh, I'm sorry.
Madam, here. Look what I found.
Stay there. I'll be right back.
Hey, that's my name. That's me.
Miss Witch, I got a great idea.
Why are you talking like a cat?
But I just can't figure it out.
I had to discover my own style.
Uh-huh. We fly with our spirit.
But it ended up being so great.
Could you turn it down, please?
Hey, there. Over here. Come on.
Yes. I tell fortunes about love.
Just go away and leave me alone!
Do you have some identification?
Is anybody here? Anybody? Hello.
You're just about through, okay?
I'll bet he thinks it's a puppy.
My name's Kiki, and I'm a witch.
Lily's her name. Be right there.
This is my first time on a bike.
So, please, just leave me alone.
It's my way of saying thank you.
Then I can bake her another one.
It'll pass quickly. Don't worry.
I don't believe what I'm seeing.
What matters is the heart inside.
Go, Kiki. Go, Kiki. Go, Kiki. Go!
Do any witches live in this town?
Hey, that was me yelling "thief."
And, this is for you, little guy.
I have a little saved up already.
I'm gonna work very hard for you.
We're gonna go shopping. Come on.
How come you're not flying today?
Are you sure it won't be too far?
Look who's behind us. Wild geese.
They say a gust of wind's coming.
Maybe we better rethink our plan.
It must be my present from aunty.
You're a good birdie, aren't you?
I cannot believe they're related.
You mean you can't speak anymore?
You know what the captain said...
Hurry. Hurry. The bus is leaving.
Hello, everybody. I'm home again.
and not very good copies, either.
She has another delivery for you.
Thank you so much for everything.
Gosh, I hope it hasn't taken off.
They'll be hitting us any minute.
My, oh, my. What's this all about?
Now, Kiki, do this for me, please.
I'm headed south to see the ocean.
Yes, to you I'm sure it looks big.
Look at how many people there are.
Now give me your name and address.
Why don't we go find another town?
I better go give it to her myself.
You'd really let me stay with you?
Look, Jiji. Aren't they beautiful?
Unless we buy ourselves some time.
Mom, can I put the canary in here?
About time we got a customer, huh?
Mmm-hmm. Yes, this is much better.
Then we gotta see it. Let's do it.
I'm not sure. Anything's possible.
Yeah, but still, if I can't fly...
But how can anyone rescue him now?
And she's trying to reach the boy!
Jiji, wake up. Tonight's the night.
Yeah, I'll expect you then. Thanks.
We better rest here until it's dry.
I have to do that with every minor.
Kiki, aren't you going to eat that?
Where are we going to stay tonight?
Ones that are friendlier than this.
Here you go. See you tomorrow. Bye.
"Thanks for returning the pacifier.
It's a birthday gift for my nephew.
I can fly there straight from here.
Kiki, how high do you intend to go?
They're calling you an egg stealer.
Jeff likes my present more than me.
He's getting to be such an old dog.
Yeah. All he does is sleep all day.
Would you get Kiki's money, please?
Osono, how could you do this to me?
What happened, Tombo? Are you okay?
Okay, now I'm officially exhausted.
Maybe you should just take a break.
So you really think I'll fly again?
He can't... Something just flew by.
I'm soaked through down to the bone.
I wonder if they have a witch there.
Smile, so we make a good impression.
And this is Jiji. He's my black cat.
Really. That's very nice, dear. Bye.
Hey, what can you tell me about her?
We won't be able to make it in time.
We're both gonna sleep well tonight.
I know that. That's not what I mean.
Thank you very much. Good afternoon.
Oh, my, what a pretty witch you are.
Maybe we should eat something, okay?
This oatmeal will pick you right up.
- Here it is. - Do I have to eat it?
Oh, no, ma'am. No money. It's on me.
You mean, she's working, at her age?
What if it means... Oh, my goodness.
How about it, kitty-cat? Wanna come?
Rather be with your girlfriend, huh?
Huh? You really thought I was a boy?
Freak winds blowing in from the sea.
Dad. Oh, can I please take the radio?
Jiji, climb up and turn on the radio.
Tell me we're not landing down there.
And Jiji here is my very best friend.
Jiji, we can see the ocean from here.
Customer? Oh, my! I'll be right back.
They say they're going to fly higher.
I am, but today this place is boring.
Osono! Osono! I've got a big problem.
Oh, madam, the delivery girl is here.
All of it. Pay her what we agreed on.
Do you think I'm going to die, Osono?
I know. I still feel that way though.
You know, my mom says the same thing.
And you can wash your plate yourself.
Yup. We've become real close friends.
You mean it? Then what? What happens?
I just felt like I'd lost my ability.
Sorry about taking your bed from you.
I said I wasn't sure you could do it.
Well, well, we've been expecting you.
Oh, there's been a terrible accident.
Sir, is there any word about the boy?
My delivery service is a big success.
and everything is falling into place.
You're gonna find a city by the ocean?
Uh-huh. That's what I'm hoping anyway.
If you mind the store once in a while,
Dear, this lady is a customer of ours,
I'm sure it'll be a great party, Kiki.
It seems fine. Now you'd better hurry.
and maybe you should have some potpie.
I thought I'd come here and visit you.
Good afternoon. I wanna say I'm sorry.
Sometimes I'm unable to paint a thing.
She actually caught the boy in midair.
but all in all, I sure love this city.
pushing the clouds out by this evening.
My goodness, but time flies so quickly.
Will you write us if you have the time?
But I'm not going just for a good time.
Yeah. Be sure to tell that to the boys.
I hope you don't have too tough a time.
What are we gonna do? We can't stay up!
Ma'am, you forgot your baby's pacifier.
Osono's told me great things about you.
I can get it there for you, guaranteed.
Check the potpie and see if it's ready.
Kiki, we were all so worried about you.
Don't tell me you didn't hear about it?
Was it your magic that made us stay up?
Will you keep an eye on my bike for me?
That's Kiki. I'll get her to come over.
Hey, come over and meet the gang, Kiki.
I was waving at you from the dirigible,
She was kind to me and a very big help.
and keep it from drifting into the air.
Are you sure it's your friend, my dear?
Huh? I'm not gonna give you my broom...
Listen, we just got a letter from Kiki.
But, first, here's the weather forecast.
Just follow your heart and keep smiling.
Wow! You're gonna have such a good time.
I'm so jealous. You'll have so much fun.
Honey, it's too small to be really safe.
Um. Hi. My name's Kiki, and I'm a witch.
zooming around on your broom back there.
Thank you for getting me out of trouble.
I'm sorry. We're still alive, aren't we?
Frankly, I think this is a major insult.
So, why was it alone in the forest, huh?
Better go get Jiji before it's too late.
But it always gets busy about this time.
And what am I supposed to do about that?
I think there's something wrong with it.
Please accept it. This was all my fault.
I used to help my mom bake all the time.
But it's such a big job to build a fire.
I can't take her money and not help out.
My propeller. I have to go get it, Kiki.
Jiji, I think something's wrong with me.
What did you say? I can barely hear you.
I'm still in training to become a witch.
Come on, girl. Why not? We'll leave now.
But I really haven't got the face right.
Maybe I have to find my own inspiration.
Great. Stop there on your way back. Bye.
Release the helium from the tail. Quick!
I prefer to fly without being distracted.
You're kind of old-fashioned, aren't you?
I'll let you have the room and the phone.
And I'll throw in a free breakfast, okay?
They tell me you have a delivery service.
It's old. Like me, it's seen better days.
Come on. I'll introduce you to everybody.
Well, since you didn't come and visit me,
Come on, Kiki. You have got a great face.
My legs are bothering me more than usual.
Would you do me a favor and open the box?
Come on. Be a good broom. Hold on, Tombo.
Lilac would look prettier on me, or white.
Big deal. It's just a big puddle of water.
And we'd be honored if we could live here.
Of course, I'm going to tell your parents.
I'll bet there are bigger and better ones.
Jiji, I've decided not to leave this town.
I hope it'll be enough. What do you think?
This much for me? That's great. Thank you.
Could I please have your signature, ma'am?
Hey! I know. How about we work out a deal?
How about we use that old oven over there?
You're never gonna make the party on time.
Oh, no. I told Grandma I didn't want that.
And that poor boy waited such a long time.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize I'd overslept.
Hmm. I kind of thought you looked unhappy.
Well, it's the way you're dressed and all.
Let's turn out the lights and go to sleep.
Well, you take plenty of time coming home.
Midsummer is always when these winds come.
The dirigible is being blown towards town.
You saw it all live as she saved his life.
Mom, didn't you say I could have the radio?
Miss. Wait up. I sure fooled that cop, huh?
I was planning on putting a phone upstairs.
Hey, there. Miss Witch, do you remember me?
I wasn't trying to steal your eggs. Really.
That gust of wind took them all the way up.
and, you see, it's mine and I need it back.
Jeff, shut the door when you're done. Okay?
And the address? Yes. The blue roof. Right.
We can't keep our next appointment waiting.
Well, if it burns firewood, I can help you.
You think so? All right then. Let's try it.
You think 40 minutes should be about right?
Um. It's very nice to see you again, ma'am.
Please. I promise I'll bring it right back.
Get outta the way. The blimp's gonna crash!
"Dear Mother and Father, How are you doing?
I've really started to gain some confidence
Mild winds will be blowing in from the west,
And I want to leave on the perfect midnight.
And I know having a good heart is important.
Um. Well, I haven't really decided that yet.
Jeez, what a snob. And did you see that cat?
Bless my hourglass. It's a real, live witch.
Your parents are here with you, aren't they?
who will like me and accept me for who I am.
What I think you should do is use our phone.
I'm getting to like this town more and more.
Kiki, we've got a problem. The toy fell out.
Your birthday guests are gonna be here soon.
It's at 6:00, but it's only 15 minutes away.
That's right. When I told him you were sick,
This is the engine of a man-propelled plane.
- That bad, huh? - I'm not working much now.
Don't give up. Don't give up. Don't give up.
Kiki was so brave. She really saved the day.
I don't think I can handle it. Can you do it?
Nobody's seen one around here in a long time.
- Here you go. - Okay, I'd like one of those.
So, tell me, whereabouts are you two staying?
Do you think you can deliver this by tonight?
Now, let's see. Yup. It's just past the cape.
Don't blame me if you're late for your party.
Would you like some hot tea? It's no trouble.
Uh, will you please sign this receipt for me?
Kiki, what's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
You must be tired. You try to get some sleep.
Uh-uh. I'm looking for someone named Koppori.
Hey! Why don't you come and stay at my cabin?
I'm going home soon to show off my new skills.
It's my specialty, herring and pumpkin potpie.
I'll have to phone her and tell her I'm sorry.
Now, put your weight into it again. That's it!
No tea, thanks, but some milk if you have any.
You're the spitting image of that stuffed cat.
I bet your name's Jiji, right? Coming through.
Now, don't you be nervous. Sit down over here.
And then, pretty soon, you'll be flying again.
And there it is, folks, the Spirit of Freedom.
Oh, look at that. It's completely upside down.
so if you have been planning something special,
That's the broom you're going to be leaving on?
Yup. I just made it this morning all by myself.
I'd rather you took my broom. I know it better.
Yup! How'd you guess? I just left home tonight.
Mmm-hmm. Would you mind turning off that radio?
You were almost responsible for a big accident,
Show me on the map where you want it delivered.
This is terrible. I can't deliver it like this.
No. But my problem is, what am I going to wear?
She made a delivery to my house on my birthday.
but then I start feeling like such an outsider.
I can't understand anything he's trying to say.
Hi, Kiki. It's me, Tombo. Did you see me today?
Hold on there, son. Just hold your grip steady.
Please, sir, may I use your broom for a minute?
Of course, they are. But Kiki will be just fine.
You'll be okay now. Worked out pretty good, huh?
told me she wants to do a drawing with me in it.
Will that be inside or outside city limits, sir?
Can you watch the store until I get back, Osono?
Well, it's just as my great-grandmother told me.
I'm sorry, but when we flew up, I was so scared.
Gosh. You're so lucky, Kiki. I wish I could fly.
Uh-huh. It's right over there across the street.
You'd make my life easier if you'd model for me.
Doze off at noon. Don't even think about flying.
There are less than five minutes to takeoff now.
You mean tonight? Next month is what you told me.
Your broom is nice, but let's take your mother's.
May our little baby be well and have a safe trip.
Stay here tonight? I'm afraid I don't understand.
And that'll be all for you? All right. Thank you.
I really must do something to show you my thanks.
Why didn't you tell me you have no place to stay?
I'll make you a deal. Since I'm expecting a baby,
Oh! Well, I haven't really thought about a price.
Stop shouting. I'm on the roof. What do you want?
Wake up. You're supposed to be minding the store.
Oh, come on. You're not still mad at me, are you?
Oh. Well, I'm sorry. It began to rain on the way.
But don't worry. The food came through all right.
I really don't know. Maybe if I make a new broom.
So, how's the delivery biz? You making any money?
I got so caught up in all the training and stuff.
Today when I saw you, I thought, "I wanna paint."
All citizens are kindly requested to remain calm.
It's snagged on the building across the street...
That brave young boy is hanging on for dear life.
Tomorrow also looks good with clear skies and sun.
Mom, it's a perfect midnight for me to leave home.
I know. She seems so young to be leaving home now.
You look just like your mother when she was young.
But I put so much work into this one. Right, Jiji?
But there may be some witches living here already.
Do you think maybe you can teach me how to fly it?
"Your new delivery girl is really quite special."”
Follow me. Bakery is downstairs. Upstairs is home.
Oh, my! It's a little bit dustier than I remember.
It's a great idea. Kiki's Flying Delivery Service.
Ket, dear, go open the door. Jeff wants to go out.
By the way, that painter who found the stuffed cat
Come in, dear. Please make yourself right at home.
It'll only take me 15 minutes if I fly there fast.
No, you're not. I'll bring some medicine right up,
Well, then, I'll just make something else for you.
About the other night. I'm sorry I didn't show up.
People like you can just fly away on a broomstick.
We're all gonna get to go for a ride in the blimp.
It's not really important what color your dress is.
If things don't work out, you can always come home.
The baby's mother told me to give you this message.
Well, I'm glad to see Jeff excited about something.
Well, I like pancakes, provided they're not burned.
I feel just awful having you come here for nothing.
Exactly right. So why don't we take a little break?
Because otherwise we're gonna have trouble turning.
I'm not mad at all, Tombo. I have a lot on my mind.
And don't forget that this summer, the hit music...
I didn't know things like that happened to witches.
Tell me. What kind of a boy has these legs, mister?
It's exactly the same, but then I found the answer.
But we each need to find our own inspiration, Kiki.
Oh, no, there's a young boy hanging onto the cable.
We are listening to the sound of a helium gas leak.
And be sure to write home as soon as you're settled.
This is just the kind of place I've always imagined.
Mmm. These are nice and fresh. Just out of the oven.
We have a spare room in the attic. You can use that.
Why, of course. But we haven't introduced ourselves.
and we were talking about your new delivery service.
If I were you, I wouldn't go back down there, again.
Uh-huh. But you be sure not to let it fly away, Ket.
Oh, well, you have a black cat in your cabin window,
So you're on your own at 13. That's pretty exciting.
Uh, oh. I'm sorry. Yes, of course, we can handle it.
Besides, it makes you look beautiful and mysterious.
We can beat the rain if we just fly a little faster.
Sorry. But at first I thought you were such a clown.
Why don't you go inside, and I'll go get some water?
Painting and magical powers seem very much the same.
You know, it could be you're working at it too hard.
That's Tombo. That's my friend hanging on that rope.
He's being lifted away together with the police car.
Hi, Miss Dora. Hey, Mom, it's gonna be clear tonight.
Dad, can you lift me up high, like when I was little?
I'm going to miss the wonderful sound of those bells.
Maybe you can sweep her off her feet with that broom.
There's a lady here who wants you to make a delivery.
To be completely independent and a witch. Impressive.
Just don't forget to send your aunt a thank-you note.
Quickly! We have to hurry. Kiki is running very late.
I tried and tried, but nothing I did seemed any good.
I'm glad you came. Please excuse me for not standing.
Would you please bring this to a young delivery girl?
Now, she's bringing him down to land, safe and sound.
There'll be a beautiful full moon lighting up the sky,
Ah. Well, I'm nearly finished with my training period.
Jiji, you've gotta come see the ocean. It's beautiful.
Sit down and relax. Would you like some hot chocolate?
If I weren't about to have a baby, I'd help you clean.
Well, I really only have one skill, and that's flying.
Crows used to serve witches and do what you told them.
I almost forgot about that. It's already 4:00. Oh, no.
Please don't talk. I'm trying to fly this broom, okay?
Could we get out of the rain, please? I'm begging you.
Oh. And he said he wanted to visit you a little later.
Hey, wait. You can't not enjoy flying. You're a witch.
You should have seen how Tombo's friends looked at me.
And guess what? The radio says there'll be a full moon.
she has to leave home for a year to begin her training.
A little girl flew down from the sky on her broomstick.
Yes, but I could fly. Kiki barely knows how to do that.
How come you never told me you were growing up so fast?
But I'm a new witch, sir. We're supposed to fly around.
Excuse me. But would you like me to deliver it for you?
for the moment when the big blimp appears in our skies.
So I thought a delivery service wouldn't be a bad idea.
Kiki, you haven't got a problem. You look fine in that.
A great idea, ma'am. I never liked that electric thing.
Then stop trying. Take long walks. Look at the scenery.
She was really very insistent. What do you think, Kiki?
Better call the hospital, honey. I think it's time now.
Did you borrow your father's radio again without asking?
Yeah. But the next full moon might be on a cloudy night.
Witches have worn this color for a very long time, Kiki.
How much do you think it would cost to get a phone here?
I can't wait to write Mom and Dad about my new business.
Don't worry. You've done enough. Now, go on and get him.
Her designs may be fabulous, but her cat's still a snob.
Dear! What did you say to me was the time of your party?
You should come and eat your meal while it's still warm.
Oh! You know that boy stopped by to see you again today.
That's okay. Come down later. I have a favor to ask you.
If you go around that way, I'll be right with you, okay?
The party was to celebrate the completion of this thing.
That's why it busted. You wait here. I'll be right back.
We're all going for a tour inside the Spirit of Freedom.
What do you mean? You haven't lost your magic, have you?
I'd paint all day until I fell asleep right at my easel.
They were copies of paintings I'd seen somewhere before,
Hey, well, it's better than you cleaning my floor again.
Ah, yes, and can you find out when her next birthday is?
It's a bird? No, it's not a bird. It's a young girl. No.
That's great. Our trip is over. We're staying right here.
It may need a little dusting, but I think you'll like it.
How about if we go in after dark? Go in. Get it. Get out.
And, you know, everybody'd be really excited if you came.
It's very urgent this package arrive as soon as possible.
Lean your body to the inside when we go around the curve.
"Quit looking up at the sky, and get back to your books."
Without even thinking about it, I used to be able to fly.
It's falling. Too much gas has escaped. It's coming down!
There are still some times when I feel a little homesick,
It's one of our oldest customs that when a witch turns 13,
Well, I'm gonna be the very best witch that I can be, Mom.
You can rely on it time after time in any kind of weather.
Your city is SO amazing. And what a beautiful clock tower.
You gotta be a real witch, the way you can fly that broom.
You know, it will take some time to get regular customers.
Kiki, in the city, you can't just run out into the street.
Hey, wait. Come back, please. I didn't mean to insult you.
That's where I dropped it. Um. May I have it back, please?
He'll be upset when Ket wants to take it and play with it.
Listen, we're gonna have a huge party at the club tonight.
Maybe I can help around the house while the pie is baking.
It doesn't matter anyway. I can't go in these wet clothes.
Of course, you were flying since you were very young, huh?
I'll bet your powers come back after you've had some rest.
I've been waiting for you to come back so I can try again.
When you fly, you rely on what's inside of you, don't you?
because she'll be able to give her a present to repay her.
That broom she used was mine. That was my broom, you know.
I'm gonna put my paws together
and pray you're not serious.
I've come to this town because
I'm a new witch in training.
Without this, the baby'll wake
up and cry all the way home.
Maybe I can stay and find some
other nice people like Osono
I wish I had something pretty
to wear. My dress is so ugly.
He simply adores that stuffed
cat. He won't leave it alone.
It's got a mind of its own,
and it doesn't want to heat up.
Ma'am, since I don't have any
other jobs, maybe I can help.
Something really great. You're
gonna love it. Come on over.
Oh, darn this old thing. And
just when it was getting good.
I remember very well the exact
day you arrived in this town.
Beautiful, isn't she? They
tell me she's a clothes designer.
I got an invitation to go to
a party at Tombo's flying club.
he asked me how a witch could
catch cold in the first place.
Huh? Mmm-mmm. I'm sorry you
had to end up so sick like that.
Flying used to be fun until 1
started doing it for a living.
What's the matter, dear? Is
there anything I can do for you?
Must've been blinded by two
beautiful girls in front of him.
I have to say I became inspired
after the first time we met.
Kiki, please, don't move. It's
hard to draw a moving target.
You see, I hadn't figured out
what or why I wanted to paint.
Well, it's been repaired, and
is now in final preparation...
We gotta get up higher or else
we'll hit the tower, Captain.
thanks to a high-pressure front
moving in from the mountains.
Aren't you worried about Kiki
living in a big city all alone?
But since my skill is
fortune-telling, I can handle anything.
Oops! Sorry. We didn't mean to
fall asleep in your breakfast.
Yes, sir. Oh, hi, there. Come
in and wait a minute, will you?
Well, don't look now, but
that's an airplane flying under us.
After my sister telephoned, we
were wondering where you were.
I know you fell close by, so
you've got to be here somewhere.
Well, I think I've got to take
a break from my delivery work.
Help yourself to some of these,
and I'll go make us some tea.
When I was your age, I'd already
decided to become an artist.
I guess I never gave much
thought to why I wanted to do this.
Oh, and by the way, that older
woman you made a delivery for?
There's not enough helium.
Jump onto the tower before we hit.
When I saw you fly off, I
thought for a second I was dreaming.
And so we're gonna go to Scott,
live, as he reports in from...
He's so cute. I hope he's still
invited to her birthday party.
Not much. Looks like all we
can afford to eat now is pancakes.
You can just pretend to be the
doll until 1 find the real one.
You're a very clever girl, my
dear. Your mother must be proud.
Well, you flew in that weather
and you never really dried off.
Come on in, 'cause I'm done
now, and I can take a break, okay?
Now I'm trying to look inside
myself to find out how I did it.
And I have had no time to teach
her how to mix potions like me.
Look at this city. A place like
this would be great to live in.
there's never been a dirigible
this large and this safe before.
He keeps me company. I've gotten
sort of fond of him, you know?
Hey, come over to my place.
There's something I wanna show you.
I have to practice all the time
anyway. Gotta build up my legs.
If I lose my magic, that means
I've lost absolutely everything.
But I'm not very beautiful.
What do you want me to do that for?
Not yet. Barsa is absolutely
mad about lighter-than-air travel.
The young boy has somehow managed
to keep his hold on the rope.
It's a young witch soaring
through the sky, and she's riding...
Well, now, you certainly look
very grown-up, my little princess.
Who do you think you are, jumping
out into the street like that?
You're supposed to obey the law.
I'm gonna have to write you up.
You can tell she's a witch "cause
she always wears a dark dress.
Oh, my goodness. I'm afraid my
clock runs about 10 minutes slow.
Now, I'll just open up the window
so you'll have some fresh air.
But am I ever going to find it?
And is it worth all the trouble?
"I'm happy to say that Jiji and
I are doing fine at the moment."
But I really shouldn't be talking
to you, and you wanna know why?
The woman with the baby carriage
who just went around the corner.
So tell me if I'm right. I'm
guessing you're a witch in training.
Now, take me, for instance. I
just met you and I know I like you.
Oh, Grandma sent me another one
of her crummy herring pies again.
Impossible. Work is work, and
make sure you deliver it in person.
And then one day, for some reason,
I just couldn't paint anymore.
You'll just have to wait for the
right inspiration to come along.
Kiki, if we ask him, I bet he'll
take the stuffed one back inside.
It used to bake beautiful bread,
but I haven't baked in it lately.
Brace the bike with your foot
until I get her revved up. Let's go.
Well, that's sort of a white lie.
I need to do some shopping, too.
Raise your chin up a little. Look
straight ahead. Now, don't move.
In order to be a good witch, I
have to train a year away from home.
That same spirit is what makes me
paint and makes your friend bake.
The condition of the boy is
unknown, but from where I'm standing...
Hurry up! We always said we'd
leave on the perfect night. Didn't we?
You know, miss, I love flying,
too. Can I see your broom? Hey, wait!
Yeah. I'm pretty sure I have it
all. And thank you very much, ma'am.
It's called the Aviation Club,
and we'd really like for you to come.
I'm planning on flying this thing
during most of my summer vacation.
Get on the sidewalks. You there.
Young lady. Don't block the street.
She got him. She saved the boy.
I've never seen anything so amazing.
can't you make yourself another
fine broom when you get settled down?
Water and bathroom are downstairs.
Give a shout if you need anything.
How about some nice hot oatmeal
with honey in it? You want some, too?
My mother used to take me with
her. She taught me never to be scared.
But it's extremely doubtful whether
or not this can actually be done.
And if we put it off for a month,
and I find some wonderful boyfriend,
And since you're staying right
here, I can be your very first account.
Well, why didn't you tell me sooner
why you needed it in such a hurry?
How great would it be to go around
the world in a dirigible like that?
Trusting your spirit. Yes, yes!
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
I'm sorry, folks. But could you
wait just a minute? I'll be right back.
Well, I thought you might feel that
way, so I turned him down politely.
I meet a lot of people, and at first
everything seems to be going okay,
But something came up at work, and
I can't make it to the party on time.
Yes, ma'am, 4:30 will be a perfect
time to pick it up. If you'll just...
It's a serious club for kids who
are into flying and aircraft and stuff.
Why don't we go down to the beach
where that dirigible landed yesterday?
We're going to assemble the wings
and the frame at somebody else's house.
Could you tell me? Is it really hard
to get settled into a brand new city?
I really love it here. But people
don't seem to like witches in this town.
This is my first job, and I do not
want to be stopped by that traffic cop.
Well, it's your fault. The geese were
kind enough to warn us of that wind.
'cause the captain let me come into
the control cabin during the test run.
It'll probably make you feel better.
Your boss would let you have a break.
All I know is that the radio said
that the police car dropped into a pool.
You know, ever since I turned 13,
I've been excited about making this trip.
If the wind doesn't shift, the Spirit
of Freedom will smash into the tower!
Hmm. Young people are all the same.
They all want to do something different.
Ooh, it must have been the crows. They
were making such a big fuss over him.
My name's Kiki, and someone telephoned
for a delivery service, so here I am.
We can't. That'll make us even later,
and the food will get cold if we stop.
And look! The young boy is safe, but
he's clutching that rope for dear life.
But I hope you at least get to teach
her the potion that cures my rheumatism.
Hi, Mom, it's me. I wanted to make sure
you knew that Kiki is leaving tonight.
Look, fur ball, when you get as fat
and round as a pancake, you see if I care.
You were so mad at that boy. I don't
understand why you're going to his party.
A desperate last-ditch effort is being
made to tie the dirigible to the ground
Why don't I bring you here whenever you
want and train myself at the same time?
But I'm very glad I came with you today.
I feel much better sitting by the beach.
I'm so sorry, but that special treat you
were supposed to deliver isn't ready yet.
I was hoping you'd be able to deliver a
dish to my granddaughter's birthday party.
Of course, I will. And maybe the young
girl will want to know the lady's birthday,
Sorry to surprise you, but the lady in
the bakery asked me to return this pacifier.
Jiji, if nobody comes in, I'm gonna have
to eat pancakes forever and be fat, fat, fat.
The tremendous lifting power of the helium
balloon is lifting the police patrol car...
Hey! You know, you can't be late for every
meal just because you have a new girlfriend.
Well, yeah, but what happened to the camping
trip we were supposed to take this weekend?
...and the ship making some kind of landing
just so that everyone can get a closer look.
Ladies and gentlemen, it appears that the
blimp is heading directly for the clock tower.
And I was certain she was much too young to
hold such an important job as resident witch.
Well, I hope you make up your mind by 6:00.
"Cause that's when I'll be by to pick you up.
It's very rude to talk to a girl before you've
been introduced and before you know her name.
Uh-uh. Our plan was that we would stick around
for another month and play it safe. I like that plan.
Recently downed in a spectacular forced landing
due to torrential rains just outside the city limits.
Well, for example, there were quite a few times
when I thought of painting something over that painting.
But I promise I'll be really good with my work in
the bakery, so please let me stay in the room upstairs.