(gentle music)
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
(horse neighs)
(water sloshes)
- Oh, Hans, isn't she beautiful?
- Huh, did you say
something to me, Margarita?
- I'm talking about that
swan with the crown.
- [Hans] Huh?
- Isn't she just magnificent?
- Don't you go away.
- What are you up to now, Hans?
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- Fit for a princess, my princess.
I've got a surprise for you.
- You have a what?
- But you have to close your
eyes, Princess Margarita.
- Sometimes, you're so silly.
Can I open my eyes now?
♪ Tah dah dah dah ♪
♪ Tah dah dah dah, dah dah dah ♪
(gasps) Oh, no!
- What is it, Hans?
What on earth is the matter?
- Uh, oh.
- Oh, what is this thing?
Ugh, you are such a jug, Hans.
(horse neighs)
(gasps) I'd know that horse anywhere.
It's Prince Siegfried
coming from the castle.
- Wait for me Margarita!
Wait, Margarita, wait!
- Boo, now we're even, Hans, hmm.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
Oh, prince, you're so wonderful,
not like that stupid Hans.
- Will you please stop
comparing me to him?
And, hey, by the way, when are
you going to marry me anyway?
- Oh, don't be silly, I'd never marry you.
Prince Siegfried.
I'm fainting, oh.
- Oh, watch out.
Oh.
(both groan)
- You saved my life, Hans.
(lips smack)
(both gasp)
Hans.
(Hans chuckles)
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- Swans.
Wow.
Oh, how strange.
(gasps)
Oh.
I feel like I'm being
watched by a beautiful lady.
- [Adolf] Prince Siegfried,
is something wrong your highness?
- Take a look over there.
- Ooh, would you look at that?
A swan with a crown on it's head.
- Well, blow me down.
(wings flap)
(Siegfried gasps)
- Look, the swan.
- Ah.
(bow creaks)
What are you doing?
- I'm going to bring that swan home,
so you can hang her up over the fireplace.
- [Prince Siegfried] No, don't shoot!
- [Adolf] Oh!
- Adolf!
Look, look, Adolf's been
turned into a statue.
- I knew there must be something strange
about this forest, your highness.
I bet it has something to do
with that mysterious swan.
- But she was so beautiful.
- We'd best get out of here
in a hurry, your highness,
before the sun goes down.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- [Prince Siegfried] I
just don't understand it.
- [Benno] Excuse me, your highness,
I don't think it's hard
to understand at all.
That swan with a crown must
be some kind of a witch.
When you come to think of it,
no one has ever been to the
other side of that lake, ever.
- No, no, I can't believe
anything as beautiful as that swan
could possibly be a witch.
- But, your highness, you
saw Adolf turn into a statue
when he tried to shoot that swan.
If you take my advice, your highness,
you won't ever go near
that enchanted lake again.
- [Woman] Prince Siegfried,
the queen wants to see you.
(regal music)
- [Prince Siegfried] Hello, Mother.
- Tomorrow is your birthday,
Siegfried, your 21st birthday.
You're all grown up now, my son.
- [Prince Siegfried] I hope so.
- Of course, since your poor
father's no longer with us,
you automatically become
lord of the kingdom.
You'll have to marry someone right away.
You can choose someone at the ball.
- Do I have to marry someone?
- Of course, how can a
king rule his kingdom
without a queen by his side?
- [Prince Siegfried] But--
- There's nothing to worry about,
I've already sent invitations to six
of the most beautiful
princesses in the land.
And they will all be here
at the ball tomorrow night, Siegfried.
It's up to you to decide
which one you want to marry.
I warn you, it won't be easy.
- Do I really have to?
What's the big hurry, Mother?
- My boy, that's the law, dear.
It's always been the law and
it wall always be the law,
unless you already have
someone you want to marry, Siegfried.
- How could I?
I never meet anyone around here.
- Always complaining.
Until tomorrow.
- [Prince Siegfried] Goodbye, Mother.
- Well, congratulations, your highness.
- You better stop it.
Just because I'm turning 21,
and taking over the kingdom,
and getting married to someone
I don't love all in one day,
doesn't mean you have the
right to make fun of me.
I wish there was some way out.
How can I marry a stranger?
I know what I'll do, give up.
I've never disobeyed my mother,
and I can't start doing it now.
- Why are you so surprised?
You were born a prince
and this is your fate,
so you have to accept it.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- Benno, Benno!
- What is it, your highness?
- I have to see that swan
with the crown again,
Benno, right now.
- [Benno] (gasps) You're crazy.
- So I am crazy.
- [Benno] If your highness
says so, who am I to disagree?
- If that swan is really a witch,
if it really has magical
powers like you say it does,
then I'm going back to that lake
and make it turn Adolf back into a person.
- Don't do it, your highness,
what if you got turned
into a frog or something?
- Well, then, I'll just have
to find a beautiful princess
to kiss me and turn me back into a prince.
Don't try and stop me.
- I won't.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- Now, how on earth did
that statue get here?
- [Margarita] Hans, Hans!
- Coming.
What's wrong, Margarita?
- The swan with the crown is leaving.
(swans squawk)
- Don't you worry about a thing, Adolf.
- Oh, why is the prince back so soon?
- Look over the there,
the swan with the crown
is leaving, let's go.
- [Benno] Where are we going?
- Why is Prince Siegfried
following that beautiful swan?
What are you waiting for?
- Huh, why do I have to come?
- [Prince Siegfried] Why does
this stupid road have to end?
- Because it's time to
give up and go back home.
- Hiyah, hiyah.
(horse neighs)
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- [Benno] You can't go
up there, your highness,
it's too steep.
- I love you, Prince
Siegfried, you're so brave.
- That other guy's never gonna make it.
- (grunts) Come on, come on.
(horse neighs)
- [Benno] Wait for me,
Prince Siegfried, wait.
- [Hans] Margarita.
- [Margarita] What is it now?
- [Hans] Where are we going?
- [Margarita] Honestly, Hans,
sometimes you ask the
most idiotic questions.
- So what's that Prince Siegfried got
that I haven't got, hmm?
- [Prince Siegfried] Yah!
(Margarita gasps)
- Let's go back, Margarita,
it's too dangerous for us here.
- You would say that.
- Yah (yelps).
- Margarita!
- (whimpers) I'm dying, I'm dying.
Farewell my prince,
you'll never know how much I loved you.
- Well, if you need some
help getting up from there,
you can just call your prince.
- Come on, boy, there's
nothing to be afraid of, hiyah.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
How far is that swan going to go?
(horse neighs)
Ah, stead boy, steady.
Come on, come on.
(bats squawk)
Whoa, what a terrible place.
(horse neighs)
(gasps) What's that?
The swan.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
Huh?
- Did you see what I saw,
or is all of this a bad dream?
- You shouldn't be afraid now,
nothing's gonna happen to us.
- Right, because the prince
is here to protect us.
(water splashes)
- [Odette] Oh, Prince Siegfried.
- Huh, how do you know what my name is?
What on earth made you turn
into a human being like that?
Can you tell me what's
going on around here?
- I can tell you that my name
is Odette, Prince Siegfried.
- Odette, are you a swan that
turned into a human being?
Or are you a human being
that turned into a swan?
- I'm really a human being,
but an evil sorcerer put
me under a magic spell,
and turned me into a swan.
- An evil sorcerer?
- Yes, I can only turn
back into a human girl
after the sun goes down
and the moon comes out.
- Then the spell that turned
my friend Adolf into a statue?
- [Odette] Yes, that was Rothbart's doing.
- Who's Rothbart?
- Did you see that strange
owl in the forest by the lake?
- [Siegfried] Yes, I did see an owl.
- That owl was Rothbart
in one of his more horrible disguises.
- That was him?
- You'd better go now, Prince Siegfried,
if I know Rothbart,
he's probably listening
to every word we say.
- (gasps) So you mean this
place is Rothbart's castle?
(uneasy music)
- That's the sorcerer's castle, Margarita.
- I hope nothing terrible
happens to Prince Siegfried.
- [Siegfried] I'll show that
Rothbart a thing or two.
- No, you mustn't go into the castle.
- Don't try and stop me,
I must save my friend
from that evil spell.
- Do you honestly think
you can hurt Rothbart
with that tiny little sword of yours?
- What makes you so
certain that I couldn't?
- We tried to fight against Rothbart,
he destroyed my entire country.
- (gasps) Rothbart destroyed it?
- [Odette] I was once the princess
of a beautiful land far across the sea.
Three years ago, Rothbart came
and asked for my hand
in marriage, I refused.
He kept asking and when I kept saying no,
he threatened to destroy my country
and everyone in it.
We tried to fight him, but it was useless.
He destroyed my land,
and then kidnapped me and brought me here.
- But why does this Rothbart
make you turn into a swan every morning?
- Because he never wants
me to meet another man
for the rest of my life.
- Why not?
- If a man comes along who truly loves me
with all his heart and soul,
then Rothbart will lose his power,
and all his spells will be broken forever.
That's why he turns me
into a swan everyday,
to make sure that I won't
ever meet such a man.
- No, is that really true?
- Yes, he has cast this spell upon me
to prove that I am under his power,
and that there is no way for me to escape.
- [Siegfried] Then my love for
you is going to destroy him.
- Don't say that, Rothbart
will kill you first.
He's stronger than you are.
- Nothing is stronger
than what I feel for you.
I felt it from the first
moment I saw you on the lake,
even though you were only a swan.
When you looked at me with those eyes,
I knew I'd never love anyone
else for as long as I lived.
Odette, I love you.
Tomorrow night at my castle
there's going to be a ball,
and I have to choose someone to marry.
Come to the ball,
come to the ball and I'll
choose to marry you, Odette.
- [Odette] No, don't, don't say that.
- Odette, I know we just met,
but I can't believe that anyone in world
could love someone as much as I love you.
Come to my castle tomorrow.
Marry me and you won't have
to live your whole life
in fear of Rothbart.
- Rothbart will never let me go.
Goodbye, go away before he kills you.
- Odette, wait, you have to
come to the ball tomorrow night,
you have to, Odette.
I'm never going to marry anyone else.
I'm in love with you, Odette.
- Siegfried, unless you must
leave this place at once,
he will kill you, I know it.
- All right, I'll go away,
but you have to promise me
that you'll come to the ball.
- [Odette] No, no.
- Then I'm going away, Odette.
I'd rather be killed by Rothbart tonight,
then think of you living your whole life
in this horrible castle.
Odette, please.
- [Odette] (sobs) No.
- Why do you want me to die
when we can both live
happily ever after together?
- [Odette] You fool.
- [Siegfried] I'll be waiting.
(tender music)
(Odette sighs)
(Rothbart snores)
- All he ever wants to do is sleep.
It's time to wake up now,
Daddy, it's dark outside.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- Huh, huh?
- [Odille] You look even
worse than usual, Daddy.
Is something wrong?
- Every single time I
turn someone into a statue
it really takes it out of me, you know?
Especially in broad daylight (grunts).
- You certainly are crazy
about the boring Odette,
aren't you Daddy?
- Crazy, why that's not the word for it.
She's the only thing in the world
worth getting out of bed for.
Mmm, I think I'll propose
again tonight (laughs).
Maybe she'll even say yes.
I feel lucky.
- Daddy, dear, if I were you,
I wouldn't get my engines
revved up quite so soon.
- No, and why shouldn't I
get my engines revved up?
- Your precious Odette's
been seeing a young man.
- Why didn't you say
so in the first place?
- Because you were too
busy picking up the flowers
you wanted for your wedding.
- [Rothbart] What's he like?
- Well, Daddy, I hate to say this,
but that Prince Siegfried
is a dreamboat on wheels.
- Prince Siegfried?
- And he'll be King Siegfried tomorrow.
- Are you telling me the truth?
- Would I lie?
He's invited her to a dance
at his castle tomorrow,
and you can bet your wolf's
bane he'll ask her to marry him.
- Why that lousy pipsqueak,
I'll turn him into a goose
and I'll have him for dinner (growls).
- Your blood pressure, Daddy.
- Where are you Siegfried?
Nobody does this to
Rothbart the magnificent.
I'll find you if it takes me all night.
- You can turn the
whole castle upside down
and you still wouldn't find him.
- [Rothbart] Are you telling
me the rat's out of the trap?
- And he almost brought the cheese.
- Where's Odette?
- Oh, I'm sure she's safe and sound
up there in her little birdcage,
dreaming of her sweetheart,
and crying into her pillow.
Maybe if you lost a few pounds
and shaved once in a while
she wouldn't fall for the
first guy that came along.
- [Rothbart] Shut up!
- Oh, oh.
- No more mister nice guy,
my little princess (screams).
That Siegfried lays one hand on my Odette,
I'll turn him into a hundred pigeons
and put him in a pie.
I'll pulverize him and
sprinkle it on my corn flakes.
(pants and coughs)
(grunts)
Odette, it's me.
(Odette gasps)
I hope you're decent
because I'm coming in.
Hello, there, how are
you this fine evening?
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
And who was that young man
you were chatting with today?
Prince Siegfried from that silly castle.
- But how, but how did you know?
- You can't hide anything
from Rothbart, princess.
I let you meet him because
thought it time you found out
how pathetic all the men in
the world are compared to me.
But forget all that,
are you ready to accept
my humble proposal,
settle down, and start raising a family?
I've been patient for
all these years, Odette.
Just say that one little word
and make me a very happy man.
I love you (whimpers).
(growls)
Oh, my precious Odette,
say that you'll marry me,
and I'll give you the most
beautiful things in the world.
Why if you marry me, I'll give
you more money for clothes
than you could spend in a lifetime.
Answer me Odette, don't you
like talking to me anymore?
Until you accept my offer,
I'll have to keep turning you
into a swan every morning of your life.
Doesn't that bother you?
- [Odette] I don't want your money.
I don't want to settle down
and raise a family in this castle.
There's only one thing I want.
- I'll give you anything you want, Odette.
- All I want is to live
with someone I love.
- Someone you love?
- [Odette] Mm hmm.
- (grunts) Please, tell me it
isn't true, Odette, please.
(bird tweets)
So it's that puny little
Prince Siegfried you're
in love with, isn't it?
I'm the only man for you, Odette.
Please, tell me, please, Odette.
Tell my why you haven't
fallen in love with me yet?
Why don't you make me
fall in love with you?
If you're the greatest
wizard in the world,
that shouldn't be a problem for you.
- Quiet, enough!
all the power of all
the wizards in the world
can't move a single human heart.
You think I would've
waited all these years
if hocus pocus could've helped me?
(footsteps thud)
Oh, please, Odette, take pity on me,
I'm a much better person than you think.
Or would you rather marry
that primping little prince
on his ridiculous prancing palomino?
- Yes.
- But why, how could you
be in love with someone
you never laid eyes on until today?
- [Odette] You're wrong about that.
I've been in love with Siegfried
from the first time I swam onto that lake.
- What, for three years?
- Every time he went out
hunting with his friends,
I'd go down to the lake
and watch him go by.
- So that's why you never
fell in love with me,
even a little bit.
Don't push your luck with me,
there's only so much
humiliation a sorcerer can take,
you know, even from the
only woman he'll ever love.
Why, if I felt like it,
I could turn you into
a slimy little snake.
If you don't do what I say,
I'll turn you into a caterpillar,
Odette, just watch me.
- (gasps) Oh, no!
- But I didn't do that to you, Odette,
I turned you into a beautiful swan.
Don't you see why?
It's only because I love you, Odette,
it's proof of how much I love.
- It's not, if you loved me
as much as you say you do,
you wouldn't have done
anything to make me so unhappy.
If you really want to
prove how much you love me,
if you really want to prove it,
then leave my room immediately,
because you're the last person
in the world I care to see.
- Huh?
How dare you, how dare you say that?
Odette, do you want to
go to this secret ball?
Hmm, and you think I'd let you go?
(laughs) You obviously don't know
very much about Rothbart
the magnificent (coughs).
- Oh, my poor little friend, forgive me.
- My poor little Odette,
like a bird in a gilded cage.
It looks like your gallant
Prince Siegfried will have
to choose some other princess to marry
at that ball my little sparrow (laughs).
- [Odette] Oh, Siegfried,
Prince Siegfried (sobs).
(tense music)
- So this is what I get
for loving a princess?
(growls)
- I'll bet I can guess what put you
in such a terrible mood (giggles).
- What's so funny about it?
- She turned you down again, didn't she?
- Shut up.
- It's hopeless, Daddy,
she'll never marry you,
no matter how long you keep on waiting.
- Enough is enough!
- Oh my, so now you hate her, do you?
- I certainly do, she
dares to break my heart.
- Why not kill her?
- What?
- That would solve all your problems.
You can't wait forever.
And she'll never say yes,
so you might as well get rid of her now.
- Hmm,
oh, oh.
- A good idea, don't you think?
- No, that's something I could never do,
never in a million years.
I could never do anything
to hurt my beautiful Odette.
- [Odille] Oh, how did you
get to be such a softie?
If you don't have the guts to do it,
I'll do it for you.
- No, please, put that horrible
thought out of your mind.
I love her too much, Odille, please.
(Odille laughs)
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- [Siegfried] Of course, she'll
come, I just know she will.
- [Benno] But, your highness,
if that sorcerer, Rothbart,
uses his evil powers--
- Don't say that, I'll
never marry anyone but her.
- [Benno] But what if she doesn't show up?
- She will show up.
If you'd looked in her
eyes the way I have Benno,
you'd know that she could never break
a promise to anyone, never.
She'll be here, Benno.
And the minute that I am
king, she'll be my queen.
You'll see.
- Wake up, Margarita, wake up, wake up.
- Now what do you want?
- Well, its just that.
- Out with it.
- Out with it, okay.
You see, I was just thinking
about Prince Siegfried and Odette,
and it made me think of, well (giggles),
did anyone ever tell you how
much you look like Odette, hm?
- You know, Hans, flattery
will get you everywhere.
And to tell you the truth,
I was just lying alone here
in the moonlight thinking
about Prince Siegfried and Odette myself.
I keep thinking about that ball (sighs).
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
♪ La la la la, mm hmm ♪
All right, Hans, you can stop that now.
I said you can stop singing.
- Huh, but the night is
still young, Margarita.
Bye-bye.
- Don't go, Hans.
I, uh, oh, you're so silly.
Mm, see you tomorrow, Hans.
- If you only knew the way I felt (sighs).
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
Ah!
(Hans thuds)
Sweet dreams, Margarita.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
Margarita, wake up, wake up,
wake up, Margarita.
What a sleepy head.
That's funny, where could she have gone?
Margarita, Margarita!
- Shh!
Look.
- [Hans] Oh.
- [Margarita] Wait.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
(both sigh)
(both applaud)
Have you ever seen anything so wonderful?
- No, huh?
(swans squawk)
- I wonder what's wrong.
- The swans are all
excited about something.
Something's up, that's for sure,
- We'd better go down and see.
- Okay.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
Princess Odette isn't here today.
- That must be why they're so excited.
- Must be sick.
- But for the last three years,
Odette hasn't missed one
single day, not one single day.
- Well, there's always
a first time, you know.
- Oh, she must have been
locked up in the castle
by that evil magician Rothbart.
- Oh, no, that means she won't be able
to go to the ball tonight, Margarita.
- That's right, Hans,
and that means Prince Siegfried
is going to have to pick
one of those other princesses to marry.
- Hmm, what do we do Margarita?
- There's nothing we can do now.
- There's gotta be something.
- Oh.
- Hmm.
- I know what,
I'll go to the castle
and tell Prince Siegfried all about it.
- Prince Siegfried?
- We're just a couple of squirrels.
We couldn't possibly help
Odette without Prince Siegfried.
- That's for sure.
- And now, Hans, you
go to Rothbart's castle
and find out what terrible
thing he's done to Odette.
- But, but, you've gotta be joking,
go to Rothbart's castle alone?
I, uh.
- If you're saying you're
afraid to go into the forest,
then you can forget all about marrying me,
because I'm not going
to marry a coward, hm.
- Oh, right, don't get
so upset, I'm going.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Will you be proud of me when I'm dead?
Oh.
(somber music)
- Oh, Prince Siegfried, I'm so sorry.
(menacing music)
- [Odille] Huh.
- Ah, I know how to solve my problem,
I'll murder Prince Siegfried.
- [Odille] Murder the prince?
- Yes, once the prince is
dead, she'll be so unhappy,
she'll have to fall in
love with me (laughs).
- Oh, that's brilliant, Daddy.
You have such a fabulous
understanding of human nature.
Don't you see, if the prince is dead,
she won't forget about him
for as long as she lives.
- You're right again, Odille.
What'll I do?
How can I make her love me?
- Well, I can think of
one way out of this.
- Oh, tell me quickly.
Make Odette fall in love with me
and I'll give you a whole planet to rule.
- We make Siegfried fall
in love with someone else.
- Mm, but suppose that idiotic prince
won't fall in love with
anyone else except Odette.
What do we do then?
- [Odille] I'll show you, Daddy.
- What are you, what are you doing?
(riveting music)
Oh, ah, Odette, my princess!
- Don't get all hot
under the collar, Daddy,
it's me Odille.
- [Rothbart] Well, you
certainly look like Odette.
I can't believe it (giggles).
- Believe it, Daddy.
I just know, the minute
I walk into that ball,
he'll fall in love with me.
- Only a daughter of
Rothbart the magnificent
could come up with such an idea.
If you show up at the ball like that,
you'll have the prince
crawling on his knees.
You are brilliant, my dear.
- You know, I don't think I'd mind
marrying that gorgeous Siegfried.
If that's all right with you, Daddy.
- Of course, you may
marry Prince Siegfried,
as long as you keep him out
of my hair and Odette's.
- Play your cards right,
and she might even marry you, hmm?
- (laughs) I'm so lucky.
- We've got lots of things to
do before the ball, you know,
so you'd better stop
laughing like an idiot
and get some rest.
- Yes, beautiful sleep, that's
what Rothbart needs (laughs).
Lucky, lucky!
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
(regal music)
- Huh, hmm.
- What's wrong?
- Either I saw a squirrel
riding on that coach,
or I'm crazy.
(Margarita chitters)
- Huh, well a squirrel.
You're pretty brave to come
all the way up here from the forest.
Did you come for the ball?
(Margarita chitters)
What's bothering you?
- [Margarita] Of course,
he doesn't understand
one single word I'm saying.
What'll I do?
- I wish you could take
a message to Odette
to remind her that she
promised to come to the ball.
She's got to come, or I'll
have to marry some stranger.
(Margarita chitters)
Goodbye, squirrel, this
castle's no place for you.
(Margarita chitters)
What's the matter?
- Oh, my gosh, what now?
How am I supposed to
get into Odette's room?
If only I could fly.
Hmm, all I have to do is move this chain.
(grunts) It won't budge an inch.
I'm no good at anything.
Oh!
(Odette gasps)
- (grunts) Who's making all that racket?
- Boy, that was scary.
But I guess it worked.
(Rothbart pants)
(tense music)
- Someone's been chewing.
Must be those rats again.
- Who's he calling a rat?
(drawbridge creaks)
- The sun is just about
to go down, Odette,
and the ball will begin.
I think I may just drop
in on that ball myself,
and see which of those princesses
young Siegfried decides to marry (laughs).
(Odette sobs)
- Oh, and after all I went through.
(gong chimes)
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- [Siegfried] Odette.
- [Odette] Siegfried.
- [Rothbart] Have a
pleasant evening, Odette,
curl up with a good book or
play a few hands of solitaire.
I want you rested for your
wedding tomorrow (laughs).
- [Odette] Oh, Siegfried,
Prince Siegfried (sobs).
- [Margarita] Hans, Hans!
- Margarita.
Margarita.
- [Both] Oh!
(Hans' lips smack)
- Odette's in there all alone.
- [Margarita] I know.
- [Hans] The problem is how're
we gonna get that door open?
- Not by standing here talking about it.
What are you doing, Hans,
hurry up and help me with this thing.
- [Hans] Okay.
(both groan and grunt)
Whoa!
(wood clatters)
- My goodness, are you all right?
(door creaks)
- Oh, somebody's coming.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- May I now present
the Princess Catherine.
- Happy birthday, Prince Siegfried.
(Siegfried sighs)
Well.
(scoffs)
- [Siegfried Voiceover]
Odette, please, hurry.
- May I now present, Princess Rosanna.
- [Rosanna] Many happy returns
of the day, your highness.
- Huh?
Please, Odette.
- My name's Francine.
I've never been so
insulted in my entire life.
Daddy's gonna hear about this.
- And now my son, the time has come
for you to tell all of us assembled here
which one of these lovely princesses
you have decided to marry.
- And now, Mother, the time
has come for me to tell you
that I'm not going to marry
any of these princesses.
- (gasps) Siegfried.
- Listen, everybody, I'm
sorry to have to say this,
but the ball is over.
I'm sorry it had to end like this,
and that you lovely princesses had to come
all this way for nothing.
(princesses gasp)
You can all go home now.
(gasps)
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
Odette, I knew you'd come!
I knew all along that
now matter what happened
you wouldn't break your promise, Odette.
- [Odille] Odette?
My name is Odille.
- Odille?
- That's right.
Oh, prince, how could you forget my name?
- But last night, you said your name was--
- I'm sure I said my name is Odille
because that's what it is.
The moonlight must have
affected your hearing.
I just love what moonlight does to men.
- That must be it, but who cares?
It doesn't matter to me what your name is.
I'm just incredibly happy that
you came to the ball, Odille.
(tense music)
- Who is that mysterious
lady there dressed in black?
- I have never seen her.
She's lovely.
- Whoever she is, I'm glad
my son has finally found
a young woman he's interested in.
Have them begin the music now.
- Music, maestro!
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
(Odette pants)
- Stop!
Where do you think you're going?
- [Hans] Oh, no.
- [Odette] Oh.
(tense music)
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- [Hans] Ya ha!
- [Guard] Oh, no, rats!
- [Guard] Rats, rats,
oh, look it on my neck.
(Odette screams)
- What brings you here?
- [Both] Whoa!
- Well, now, as long as you are here,
I might as well show you something.
I think you'll be amused (chuckles).
Take a look, take a look, princess.
(laughs)
- [Siegfried] And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
princes and princesses, I
have an announcement to make.
(Odette sobs)
Today, the day that I have come of age,
I would like you all to
meet the woman I have chosen
to be my queen, Princess Odille.
(guests applaud)
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- What?
- Oh, no, it can't be, it can't be.
- [Queen] Well, Siegfried, I
have no idea who this woman is,
but I will do nothing
to oppose this marriage
if you are sincerely in love with her.
Are you?
- Yes, of course, I am.
She's the only woman I have ever loved.
And I have vow to love Princess Odille
for the rest of my life.
(guests applaud)
(Rothbart laughs)
- [Odette] Oh.
- What?
Who are you, and how did
you get into my castle?
- (laughs) Just call me Dad,
now that you're planning to
marry my daughter, Odille.
- You mean, he's your father?
- I'm afraid, he is.
- You must be that evil
sorcerer, Rothbart.
- Very smart, now, Odette
belongs to me (laughs).
- But if that's Princess Odette,
who did I just propose to?
- Well, I told you my
name is Odille, didn't I?
(Siegfried gasps)
It's too late to be shocked, prince,
you've already given your
solemn oath to marry me
and to love me for the rest
of your ever-loving life.
- My princess!
- Oh.
- No, please forgive me, Odette.
- (laughs) Forget it, Siegfried,
she's my princess now.
Oh, oh, you're waking up at last, Odette.
- [Odette] Oh, farewell, Prince Siegfried.
- [Siegfried] Wait!
Come back, Odette!
- Get away, boy.
(guests gasp)
(Odette screams)
- Odette, come back!
- [Odille] You're all mine, my love.
- [Rothbart] Nice work, Odille.
- [Siegfried] Odette!
(Rothbart laughs)
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- [Queen] Siegfried, wait!
- [Siegfried] Mother!
- What chance can you possibly have
against that terrible sorcerer?
- Please, try to understand, Mother,
I have to go and rescue Odette.
It doesn't matter how
dangerous it might be.
- As of today, you're
the king of this country,
you can't just do anything as you please.
- Forgive me, goodbye.
- No, wait, you can't.
Siegfried, Siegfried!
(horse neighs)
- Yah!
- [Hans] Hurry!
(Odette sobs)
- Would you please stop
crying for one minute.
One of these days, you will
have to forget about Siegfried.
But I'm patient, I'm sure that
if I just wait long enough,
you'll finally give in and marry me.
(horse neighs)
- (gasps) Prince Siegfried.
- Who, who?
(grunts) That little runt.
I've had enough of him.
Where is he?
(tense music)
- Rothbart, fight like a man.
- Me, Prince Siegfried wants to fight me?
- I'll fight you to
the death if I have to.
- Poor boy, perhaps you don't realize
that standing in front of you
is Rothbart the magnificent.
(speaks gibberish)
(Siegfried grunts)
- Please don't let him
kill you, Siegfried.
- Odette!
- Run away, Siegfried.
If you try to fight
Rothbart, he will kill you.
- Don't worry, blondie,
Daddy won't kill him,
he'll just chase him away.
Isn't that right, Daddy?
- Mm hmm, that's right.
How can I kill any man who
promised to love my daughter?
And why would I want to
go and deprive myself
of such an outstanding son-in-law?
- You better watch out, Daddy,
your little lovebird's flown the coop.
- What?
Odette!
- [Hans] There goes the prince.
- [Margarita] Hurry.
- [Rothbart] Where is
she, which way id she go?
(growls)
If you take one more step, Odette,
you're going to be very sorry
you ever met that prince.
- You'd better get out of here, Siegfried.
- No, stand back.
It's time somebody got
rid of this Rothbart
once and for all, Odette.
- (laughs) Don't push
your luck, little prince.
I may lose my patience and kill you
even if you are engaged to my daughter.
(speaks gibberish)
- [Odette] Be careful!
- Nice try.
But let's be fair.
(both grunt and groan)
- Help him, Hans.
If you really want to marry me,
then do something to help the prince.
- Hmm, I will.
- But be careful, Hans.
- You'd better go back to
your castle now, prince,
while you still can.
(Hans grunts)
You miserable swill.
What are you doing here?
(Hans groans)
- Hans, Hans, Hans, my poor Hans.
- [Odille] Those two haven't
learned their lesson yet.
- They must think me pretty stupid.
- [Siegfried] Ah!
- Let's come to an
understanding, Siegfried.
I'm a reasonable man.
You agree to marry my daughter,
I won't squash you like a bug.
- I'll never marry your daughter.
Do you hear me, never!
- (gasps) Well, of all the nerve.
I don't want him anymore.
Go ahead and kill him, Daddy.
- [Rothbart] You don't have
to ask me twice, my sweet.
Now comes the fun part.
(speaks gibberish)
(Siegfried groans)
- [Odette] Oh, no, hold on.
(Siegfried screams)
(Rothbart laughs)
(Odette gasps)
- Watch me now, prince.
- [Odette] Stop, you can't kill him.
- So you want him to live?
- Please, don't kill him.
- Finish him off.
- Oh, I'll let him live, Odette,
if you'll accept my
humble offer of marriage.
Everything has it's price.
Now, have you fallen in love
with me all of a sudden?
Or do you want me to ask more nicely?
You always were the romantic, weren't you?
Oh, most beautiful of princesses,
from the bottom of my heart,
I humbly beg you to be mine.
- You can't say yes.
Forget about me, don't
give in to this monster.
I'm not worth it.
- It's up to you now.
Please, shall I put him out of his misery?
- [Odette] Wait!
- Don't try to stop him.
- Well, please give me
your answer, princess,
I haven't got all day.
Will you love me forever,
or will you let Siegfried die like a rat?
- Odette, let him kill me,
my life doesn't matter.
- [Rothbart] Give me your
answer, Odette, I'm waiting.
- I promise that I will
love you, Rothbart,
for the rest of my life.
- No, Odette, ah!
- No, no, you must--
- [Siegfried] Ah!
(Rothbart screams)
(Odille screams)
- [Rothbart] Ah, Odille, help me!
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
- [Adolf] Oh,
huh?
- Hip hip hooray!
- [Margarita] Yeah!
- [Hans] Ah.
- (groans) Siegfried.
(gasps)
(sighs)
- You're alive!
- [Odette] Siegfried.
- [Siegfried] Odette.
- Rothbart's magic was no match
for the love between Siegfried an Odette.
Listen, Hans, will you promise to love me
as much as the prince loves
Odette, forever and ever?
- [Hans] Mm hmm.
- [Margarita] Mwah.
(\"Swan Lake\" by Pyotr Tchaikovsky)
(singing in foreign language)