- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- LINNA!
HUH?
- WHAT THE--?
- Reporter:
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THOSE ARE THE TERRORISTS
WHO JUST DESTROYED
THIS BOOMER FACTORY.
AND AS WE SPEAK, UNITS OF THE
AD POLICE ARE SURROUNDING THEM.
- THIS WOULD BE HAPPENING ON
OUR ONE DAY OFF, WOULDN'T IT?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER,
LEON?
WERE YOU PLANNING ON
CAPTURING THE KNIGHT SABERS
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- KNIGHT SABERS,
GET OUT OF THERE.
THIS WHOLE INCIDENT HAS BEEN
SOME KIND OF GIANT TRAP.
THERE'S A NEWS CAMERA
UP IN THAT BLIMP,
AND THEY'RE BROADCASTING
EVERYTHING ON LIVE TELEVISION.
- Nene:
Sylia! Linna fell.
I think they've got her!
- WHAT?
- ( breathes deep )
( gasps )
- Nene:
Linna, are you okay?
- I'M ALL RIGHT,
BUT I'M ALMOST OUT OF POWER.
- Nene:  Hold on.
We'll think of something.
- THERE IT IS.
I'VE FOUND IT, SIR.
- ( screams )
( grunts )
I CAN BARELY MOVE IN THIS THING.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT WE'VE BEEN WORRIED
ABOUT SOMETHING THIS PATHETIC
FOR SO LONG.
- Back off, Kuyama.
You're supposed to hurt it,
not kill it.
- THE LIGHT'S NOT
VERY GOOD IN HERE, SIR.
I MIGHT MISS.
( grunts )
- Nene: PRISS!
THAT'S A K-SUIT,
NOT A BOOMER!
- WHO CARES?
AN ENEMY'S AN ENEMY.
- ( Linna sighs )
THANKS.
- COME ON, LINNA.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
( screams )
- ( Linna and Nene screaming )
- DAMN!
ALL RIGHT.
THE GLOVES COME OFF!
- IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
NOT TO KILL THEM.
FIRE!
- ( men shouting )
- ( grunts )
DIE!
NENE, LINNA?
( grunts )
( groans )
- PRISS!
- OH, CRAP.
I THINK THEY GOT ME.
( screams )
DAMN.
WHAT A WAY TO GO.
- ARE YOU CRAZY?
THEY'RE PEOPLE,
NOT BOOMERS.
ARE YOU TRYING
TO KILL THEM?
- YOU'RE OFF DUTY, LEON.
WE'VE GOT OUR ORDERS,
SO BACK THE HELL OFF.
- WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
I'M GONNA--
- HOLD IT, LEON.
THE ORDER FOR THIS CAME FROM
ABOVE THE COMMISSIONER.
- ( sighs )
- PRISS.
- IT'S OVER.
MY BATTERY'S GONE.
- WHAT NOW?
- I GUESS WE DIE.
- ( men shout )
- HUH?
- Nene: SYLIA!
- THERE'S ANOTHER ONE?
- NOW THAT'S INTERESTING.
I HAVEN'T SEEN THIS ONE
IN A LONG TIME.
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
( grunts )
( whimpers )
- SHOOT IT, SHOOT IT!
- HUH?
LEON, TIME TO RUN.
- DALEY!
- ( man screams )
- WHAT THE--?
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
- ( men shouting )
- FALL OUT, FALL OUT!
- Man: GO!
- Reporter: IN A SPECTACULAR
FAILURE FOR THE AD POLICE,
IT APPEARS THAT
THE TERRORIST GROUP--
- WE'VE JUST BEEN INFORMED THAT
THE RELAY FROM OUR REMOTE UNIT
IS NO LONGER FUNCTIONING.
THIS SPECIAL NEWS BREAK
WAS BROUGHT TO YOU
BY GENOM CORPORATION,
THE COMPANY OF
BOOMER TECHNOLOGY.
- Stewardess: WE'RE ABOUT TO
BEGIN OUR DESCENT TOWARD JAPAN
AND THE HANEDA AIR SPACE PORT.
PLEASE RETURN ALL
CHAIRS AND TABLES
TO THEIR UPRIGHT
STOWED POSITION.
- NICE.  LOOKS FAST.
WHEN YOU'RE FINISHED,
WOULD YOU LET ME
GIVE IT A TRY?
- I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
REPAIRS AGAIN?
- UH-HUH.
OH, NO.
NO, NOT THAT ONE.
- OKAY.
I'LL GO UP THERE LATER.
- NIGEL?
UM...
JUST HOW LONG
HAVE YOU KNOWN SYLIA?
- A LONG TIME.
- OH.
- ( engine starts )
- ( sighs )
I REALLY DO
HATE THIS JOB.
- MISS YAMAZAKI.
- UH?
- I CAN'T LET THIS GO ON.
A CHAIN IS JUST AS STRONG
AS ITS WEAKEST LINK.
AND ONE BAD ATTITUDE CAN
SOUR A WHOLE DEPARTMENT,
YOU KNOW.
YOU SEE,
PERFORMING IN ONE'S WORKPLACE
IS JUST LIKE ANY OTHER
FORM OF HUMAN RELATIONSHIP.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT
I'M SAYING, MISS YAMAZAKI?
IF YOU DON'T TREAT
YOUR WORK WITH RESPECT,
IT CAN MAKE LIFE
VERY DIFFICULT.
IT MAY BE TEDIOUS TO STARE
AT THESE NUMBERS ALL DAY,
BUT A JOB WELL DONE
CAN BE LIKE A GOOD BOYFRIEND.
EHH?
BUT OF COURSE
I DON'T HAVE TO
TELL YOU ABOUT THAT,
DO I?
( laughs )
I WANT THAT PROJECT FINISHED
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
- ( sighs )
- OH, MISS YAMAZAKI?
IT'S ALL VERY WELL
FOR YOU EXERCISE,
BUT PLEASE DON'T OVERDO IT.
YOUR CALVES ARE
MUCH TOO MUSCULAR.
( laughing )
- ( groans )
I'D LIKE TO
CRUSH HIS CORE.
- ( sighs )
IT'S REALLY SO DEPRESSING
WHEN YOU'RE NO LONGER ABLE
TO WEAR AN OUTFIT
THAT YOU REALLY LIKE.
- MISTRESS SYLIA,
YOU SEEM TO HAVE A GUEST
WAITING FOR YOU.
- NIGEL YOU MEAN?
WELL ACTUALLY,
I WAS EXPECTING HIM
TO COME BY A LITTLE LATER.
- UH, NO.
IT'S NOT HIM.
- HUH?
( gasps )
OH.
IS THAT...?
- THIS GENTLEMAN
KEEPS INSISTING
THAT HE'S YOUR BROTHER,
EVEN THOUGH I'VE
TOLD HIM REPEATEDLY
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY BROTHERS, MY LADY.
- MAKI?
- SYLIA.
- IT CAN'T BE.
BUT IT'S REALLY YOU.
- MISTRESS SYLIA?
- OH, IT'S FINE.
WHAT ON EARTH
GAVE YOU THE IDEA
THAT I DON'T HAVE
ANY BROTHERS, HENDERSON?
- ( gasps )
- YES, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE IS, HENDERSON.
HE'S THE ONLY FAMILY
I HAVE LEFT.
WELL, COME ON,
LITTLE BROTHER.
I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO GET
A ROOM READY FOR YOU, WON'T WE?
- ( elevator dings )
- NIGEL, GUESS WHAT?
I FINALLY GOT TO WEAR MY
HARDSUIT AGAIN YESTERDAY.
- YOU SHOULDN'T
PUSH YOURSELF SO HARD.
- OH, YOU REALLY DO
CARE ABOUT ME, DON'T YOU?
- WE CAN'T AFFORD
THAT KIND OF RISK.
- YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE SO CROSS.
I KNOW THAT I SHOULDN'T BE
WEARING THAT HARDSUIT ANYMORE.
SO HOW LONG DO YOU THINK
THE REPAIRS WILL TAKE?
- FOR ALL THREE SUITS?
PROBABLY A WEEK.
- THAT'S TOO LONG!
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO
IF ANOTHER BOOMER
GOES OUT OF CONTROL
BEFORE THEN?
I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I'VE BEEN JUST
A LITTLE ON EDGE LATELY.
OH, BY THE WAY,
MY BROTHER'S HERE.
DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
I DO HAVE ONE.
A YOUNGER BROTHER.
HIS NAME'S MAKI.
- Henderson:
THIS WILL BE YOUR ROOM FOR NOW.
PLEASE MAKE YOURSELF
AT HOME, MASTER MAKI.
- UM, EXCUSE ME?
- YES, MASTER MAKI?
- IS SYLIA STILL,
UM, YOU KNOW?
- YES?
- UM... NEVER MIND.
JUST FORGET IT.
- MASTER MAKI.
- HUH?
- WELCOME TO TOKYO, SIR.
I THINK WE'RE ALL
VERY GLAD
THAT YOU'RE FINALLY HERE.
- OKAY.
SYLIA.
- THE OFFICIALS IN CHARGE
OF THE AD POLICE
WILL TAKE FULL RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THEIR FAILURE
TO CAPTURE THE KNIGHT SABERS.
IN ADDITION,
I'VE ENSURED
THAT WE'LL CONTINUE
TO HAVE SOMEONE
WHO WILL BE WILLING TO GO ALONG
WITH ALL OF OUR
FUTURE SUGGESTIONS.
- THAT'S ALL VERY WELL, MASON.
BUT FINDING SCAPEGOATS
IS HARDLY THE MOST IMPORTANT
ITEM ON YOUR AGENDA.
- SIR?
- HAVE THERE BEEN
ANY FURTHER DELAYS
ON THE SHOWEN PROJECT?
- IF YOU'RE REFERRING
TO THE REPORT
THAT FOUR OF THE BOOMERS
ASSIGNED TO THE SPACE PLATFORM
HAVE ALREADY GONE ROGUE,
IT'S BEEN ADDRESSED.
OUR OPERATIVES WERE ABLE
TO DISPOSE OF THEM.
- VERY GOOD.
BOOMERS ARE LIKE HUMAN BEINGS.
IF HUMANS WERE KEPT IN SPACE
FOR THE SAME LENGTH OF TIME,
I'M SURE THEY WOULD HAVE
GONE MAD AS WELL.
- THAT MAY BE TRUE, SIR,
HOWEVER,
THE NUMBER OF MAD BOOMER
INCIDENTS IS INCREASING.
- BOOMERS ARE A MENACE
THAT SHOULD BE ERADICATED.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE THINKING,
ISN'T IT, MASON?
- NO.
- I'LL HAVE YOSHIKIRI
HANDLE THE BOOMER BUSINESS.
I WANT YOU TO CONCENTRATE
ON THE SHOWEN PROJECT.
- ERADICATE ALL OF
THE BOOMERS?
( chuckles )
( sighs )
LAUGH.
- LAUGH?
- LAUGH.
- ( laughing )
- Mason: IT'S ME.
YOU HAVEN'T FOUND WHAT WE'VE
BEEN LOOKING FOR YET, HAVE YOU?
- NOT YET.
BUT DON'T FORGET,
THE CENTER STRATUM
FROM THE EARTHQUAKE
WAS DISPERSED ALL OVER.
- YES. THERE WAS CERTAINLY
ENOUGH POWER AVAILABLE.
- SEARCHES MADE AT GROUND LEVEL
ARE EXTREMELY RISKY.
- I UNDERSTAND.
I'LL HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO WORK AROUND IT.
IS THERE SOMETHING FUNNY?
- NOTHING, SIR.
- THEN WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING,
YOU PATHETIC TOY?
- YES, THIS WOULD LOOK
ABSOLUTELY WONDERFUL ON YOU.
- REALLY?  CUT THAT LOW?
- OF COURSE.
YOU HAVE SUCH A LOVELY FIGURE.
IT WOULD BE A SHAME
NOT TO SHOW IT OFF
WITH SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
- HUH?
( gasps )
( sighs )
- ( elevator dings )
- OHH.
OH, YOU REALLY KNOW
HOW TO COMMUNICATE
WITH MACHINES, DON'T YOU?
- HMM?
- UM, YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEAN, DON'T YOU?
A MACHINE CAN UNDERSTAND WHETHER
IT'S BEEN PUT TOGETHER CORRECTLY
AND WHEN ITS POWER SUPPLY
HAS BEEN OPTIMIZED.
YOU'RE A REAL MASTER,
AREN'T YOU?
- MAKI, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- HUH?
- DID I SAY THAT
YOU COULD COME IN HERE?
WELL, HENDERSON HAS PREPARED
A LOVELY MEAL FOR US.
LET'S GO UPSTAIRS
AND EAT, SHALL WE?
I'M SO HAPPY THAT WE'RE FINALLY
TOGETHER AGAIN, MAKI.
I HADN'T FORGOTTEN ABOUT YOU,
YOU KNOW,
BUT THERE ARE THINGS
I HAVE TO DO HERE
THAT HAVE BEEN
OCCUPYING MY ATTENTION,
AND, WELL...
- UM, SYLIA,
IS THERE A REASON
THAT THE MAN DOWNSTAIRS
DIDN'T COME UP
TO EAT WITH US?
- UM, NIGEL...
DOESN'T DO THAT.
- Maki: HE REALLY IS
INCREDIBLE, ISN'T HE?
I UNDERSTAND THAT BECAUSE
I LOVE MACHINES THE WAY HE DOES.
A MACHINE CAN'T OPERATE
AT ITS FULL POTENTIAL
UNLESS THE PERSON WHO MAINTAINS
IT REALLY CARES FOR IT.
- ( groans )
- ( gasps )
- STOP TALKING ABOUT MACHINES
AS IF THEY WERE HUMAN BEINGS,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?!
- ( gasps )
- OH, I'M SORRY, MAKI.
IT'S JUST THAT...
WELL, SOMETIMES I LOSE
CONTROL OF MY TEMPER.
I DON'T KNOW WHY IT HAPPENS,
BUT IT DOES.
I GUESS MAYBE I HAVE MORE
OF MY MOTHER'S GENES IN ME
THAN I THOUGHT I DID.
( chuckles )
I CERTAINLY HOPE THAT YOU
HAVEN'T INHERITED ANY OF THAT,
HAVE YOU, MAKI, DEAR?
- OF COURSE NOT, SYLIA.
YOU KNOW I HAVEN'T.
- ( sighs )
THE ONLY THING
I HAVE TO KNOW
IS THAT YOU'RE MY REAL
YOUNGER BROTHER, MAKI.
AND FROM NOW ON,
THE TWO OF US ARE GOING
TO LIVE HERE TOGETHER
THE WAY A REAL
FAMILY SHOULD.
- ( rock music playing )
- Priss: ♪ IF YOU COULD
JUST FEEL THE WORDS ♪
♪ I'LL MELT INTO
YOUR EMBRACE ♪
♪ THERE'LL BE
NOTHING LEFT TO SAY ♪
♪ IT'S JUST
A PRETENSE OF LOVE ♪
♪ WITH WHICH
YOU DRAW MY HEART IN ♪
♪ IT'S THERE,
BOTH SIDES THAT YOU USE ♪
♪ ON MY SOUL ♪
♪ THAT LEADS ME TO HELL! ♪
- ( footsteps approach )
- ( sighs )
- ( gasps )
- ( phone ringing )
- Nene: HELLO?
ROMANOVA RESIDENCE.
- Linna:
Um, hi. It's me.
- Nene: LINNA,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- Linna:
Um, well, define "wrong."
- Nene:
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- Linna: Um, no.
- I SEE.
- IT'S JUST THAT
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU'D EVER DONE
ANY SPECIAL TRAINING
LIKE IN A GYM.
- UM, NOT REALLY.
I'M NOT VERY GOOD
AT THAT SORT OF THING.
- BUT YOU'RE STILL ABLE
TO MOVE AROUND IN YOUR HARDSUIT
PRETTY WELL, AREN'T YOU?
- YES.
BUT I'M SPECIAL THAT WAY.
NOT ONLY AM I A MASTER HACKER
AND A COMPUTER GENIUS,
BUT I'VE ALSO BEEN BLESSED
WITH NATURAL GRACE
AND AN AMAZING
ATHLETIC ABILITY.
AND DID I MENTION
DROP-DEAD GORGEOUS?
( laughing )
ACTUALLY, THAT WAS
JUST A JOKE, LINNA.
- Linna: I KNEW THAT.
- WELL, YOU COULD AT LEAST
HUMOR ME FOR A BIT.
- IT'S JUST THAT I'VE
BEEN GOING TO THE GYM
EVERY DAY, NENE.
AND NOW I FEEL LIKE
I'VE BEEN WASTING MY TIME.
- HMM.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S RIGHT.
- HMM?
- WELL, TO BE HONEST,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND EXACTLY
HOW THE HARDSUITS
ACTUALLY OPERATE.
SYLIA'S GOT A REAL HANG UP
WITH SECURITY, YOU KNOW.
BUT I THINK THEY'RE MUCH MORE
THAN JUST SUITS OF ARMOR.
FROM WHAT I'VE BEEN
ABLE TO DETERMINE,
THE ABILITIES OF
THE SUIT DEPEND UPON
THE STRENGTHS OF THE WEARER.
- OH, SO I AM ON
THE RIGHT TRACK.
- SURE.
BUT TAKE IT EASY, WILL YOU?
THE LAST THING WE NEED
IS FOR YOU TO WEAR YOURSELF OUT.
- THANKS, NENE.
NIGHTY NIGHT.
- DON'T LET
THE BED BUGS BITE.
- HUH?
- REGINA 45.
- DON'T MAKE ME
REPEAT MYSELF.
- YOU MEAN YOU WANT ME
TO HELP YOU?
- I ASKED FOR A REGINA 45.
- AHH!  YES, SIR.
HERE YOU GO.
- ( door chimes )
- HMM.
LOOKS LIKE THERE'S
A MISSING MODULATOR
COMPONENT TO THIS ONE.
COULD YOU GO FETCH
A NEW ONE FOR ME?
- UM, WHERE SHOULD I LOOK?
- ( sighs )
I'M NOT SURE, EXACTLY.
PROBABLY IN THE UPSTAIRS
STORAGE AREA.
- OKAY.
I'LL GO GET IT THEN.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
MAYBE I SHOULD
HAVE TOLD HIM
I DON'T KNOW MY WAY
AROUND HERE YET.
OH, WHAT'S THIS?
( yelps )
( stammering )
- I THINK I'M GOING TO
SCREAM MY HEAD OFF NOW.
- OH MY GOD.
- ( screams )
- AAH!  EXCUSE ME!
( panting )
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, NOTHING WRONG AT ALL.
REALLY, SIR.
( yelps )
( murmurs )
- ALL RIGHT,
JUST HOW DID YOU GET IN HERE,
YOU LITTLE PERVERT?
DON'T YOU KNOW THAT
THIS PLACE IS FOR GIRLS ONLY?
- ( stammers )
BUT I-- BUT HE--
- THAT MAN IS AN EXCEPTION.
WHO ARE YOU?
- OUR LITTLE FRIEND'S NAME
IS MAKI STINGRAY.
- SAY WHAT?!
- MAKI STINGRAY, HUH?
STRANGE.
I DIDN'T KNOW SYLIA
HAD A LITTLE BROTHER.
- ( murmurs )
- OKAY, HOW MUCH DID YOU SEE?
- OF WHAT?
- OF ME IN THE DRESSING ROOM,
YOU LITTLE SNEAK!
- OH, I DIDN'T HAVE TIME
TO SEE ANYTHING.
I WAS OUT OF THERE BEFORE I EVEN
HAD A CHANCE TO LOOK AROUND.
- OKAY THEN.
- YEAH.
SO I DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE
TO SEE YOUR PINK UNDERWEAR
OR ANYTHING.
( gasps )
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
( groans )
- ( murmurs )
- HEY, WAIT A SECOND!
COME BACK HERE, YOU!
- I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY,
I'M SO SORRY!
- Nene: NOT AS SORRY AS
YOU'RE GOING TO BE!
- Maki: PLEASE NO! I WAS JUST
GUESSING ABOUT THE PINK PART.
- Nene: WHICH OF YOUR BONES
AM I GOING TO BREAK FIRST?
COME BACK HERE!
- ( Maki screams )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS: TOKYO 2040,"
A SERIES OF
UNEXPLAINED OCCURRENCES,
AN UNDERSEA BOOMER
ON THE LOOSE IN TOKYO.
WHERE DID IT COME FROM
AND WHAT IS ITS PURPOSE?
WITH LINNA'S SUIT
DOWN FOR REPAIRS,
IT'S UP TO PRISS AND NENE
TO SOLVE THE MYSTERY
AND PREVENT A MURDER.
NEXT EPISODE...