- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( police sirens )
- OH, COME ON.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
Daley: IT'S NO JOKE, AND SINCE
IT ESCAPED FROM A CLASSIFIED
MILITARY HANGAR, YOU CAN BET
WE WON'T BE LAUGHING.
ALTHOUGH, IT MIGHT BE FUNNY
IF THEY DECIDED TO SEND YOU
TO JAIL FOR DESTROYING
GOVERNMENT PROPERTY.
- ( bangs fist ) SAY WHAT? ARE
THEY REALLY THREATENING THAT?
- ( sighs )
- DAMN, WHY DON'T THEY
JUST LET US SHOOT IT?
- IT'S UP TO YOU, PRISS.
NENE CAN'T GET AWAY
AND I JUST FOUND OUT
LINNA'S NOT EVEN IN THE CITY.
- I FORGOT TO TELL YOU, SHE
MIGHT NOT BE COMING BACK.
- WHAT?!
- ( sighs ) THERE'S NO WAY.
EVEN IF I HAD THE CASH FOR
THE METRO EXPRESS
THE STATION'S AN HOUR AWAY.
THERE'S NO WAY I COULD
POSSIBLY GET THERE IN TIME.
- I THINK WE'D BETTER
BE GETTING BACK, LINNA.
IT'S TIME FOR DINNER.
- OH, DINNER?
GREAT, JUST GREAT.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M READY
TO MAKE A DECISION LIKE THIS.
THIS IS REALLY GOING
TO SCREW THINGS UP.
- MAYBE WE CAN HAVE
A NICE, LONG TALK OVER DINNER.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
Man: ROGER, PLEASE KEEP THE
CIRCUIT IN S-MODE AS IT IS.
TARGET IS NOT
CURRENTLY IN MOTION.
- ROGER THAT, COMMANDER F.
ASSAULT GROUPS 3 AND 5 ARE
TAKING POSITION.
WE HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED
PERMISSION TO ATTACK BOOMER,
ALL UNITS STAND BY.
( groans ) WAIT A SECOND HERE--
THIS IS THE ADP
INFORMATION CENTER.
YES MA'AM, THE NORMAL
POLICE HAVE BEEN ASKED
TO ASSIST WITH THE
CIVILIAN EVACUATION.
HUH?  THERE ARE TWO MORE
GIANT BOOMERS?
- MORE OF THEM!
- I KNEW IT,
THE MOD ARE GOING TO TRY TO
TAKE IT OUT THEMSELVES.
I GUESS NOT EVEN THE ARMY
TRUSTS US THESE DAYS.
- ( rumbling )
- SYLIA!
- TAKE OVER, I'M DRIVING THE
MOBILE PIT OUT TO SUPPORT PRISS.
- I'M ON IT!
- IT'S LIKE A COMBAT ZONE
OUT THERE.
THEY MUST HAVE BEEN INSANE
TO BUILD A BOOMER THAT BIG.
OUR ONLY HOPE IS TO THROW
EVERYTHING WE'VE GOT AT IT
AND PRAY.
- AN EVACUATION ORDER FOR
ALL CIVILIANS
RESIDING IN AREA G3
IS NOW IN EFFECT.
THE DETAILS AND CAUSE OF THIS
INCIDENT ARE NOT YET CLEAR...
- ( melancholy piano )
- I'M SORRY, MASAKI,
BUT SOMETHING'S COME UP THAT
I HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF.
YOU'RE A REALLY NICE GUY,
AND I'M SORRY TO RUN OUT
ON YOU LIKE THIS, BUT--
BUT I'VE GOT RESPONSIBILITIES
I CAN'T IGNORE.
AND IF I WAIT ANY LONGER,
THE THING I WANT MIGHT
NOT BE THERE ANYMORE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
- THROWING MY OWN WORDS
BACK AT ME, HUH?
( sighs ) I REALLY DO UNDERSTAND
WHERE YOU'RE COMING FROM, LINNA.
BUT I GUESS THAT THE
TIME ALWAYS COMES
WHERE SOMEONE HAS
TO MAKE A CHOICE--
WHEN YOU HAVE TO DECIDE WHETHER
TO STICK WITH WHAT YOU HAVE,
OR BURN YOUR BRIDGES BEHIND YOU.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.  I GUESS YOU
DO UNDERSTAND.
WHICH IS GOOD,
BECAUSE I'M ABOUT TO ASK FOR A
REALLY BIG FAVOR FROM YOU.
- A FAVOR?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE I ASKED THAT.
OR THAT HE ACTUALLY
LOANED ME THE MONEY.
- ( sighs )
BUT I HAD TO,
FOR PRISS.
- THOSE IDIOTS!
- UH-HUH, ONE MORE HIGH-RISE
FOR URBAN RENEWAL.
BUT AT LEAST THE ARMY
WILL TAKE THE BLAME.
- LOOK!
- ( rumbling )
- TO HELL WITH THE FEDS,
THAT THING'LL DESTROY THE CITY.
IF WE DON'T STOP THAT BOOMER,
WHO WILL?
- ( screeches )
Roland: - ALRIGHT,
THAT'S ENOUGH.
TELL THE GENERAL
HIS TEAM BLEW IT.
WE'RE MOVING IN!
YOU HEARD ME, GET MOVING!
THAT THING'S A BOOMER,
AND WE'RE TAKING IT OUT.
Daley:
- IT'S ABOUT TIME.
Officer: - SIR, I JUST REALIZED
THAT THING WAS USING
SURFACE-TO-AIR MISSILES.
Roland:
- SWEET JESUS, YOU'RE RIGHT!
FIREBEES, GET THE HELL
OUT OF THERE!
NOW WHAT DO WE DO?
- IT'S THE KNIGHT SABERS.
( grunting )
- BYE-BYE.
HUH?
- NENE, SYLIA'S NOT GOING TO
BE ABLE TO MAKE IT IN TIME!
- ( gasps)
- IT'S NO GOOD, THOSE JERKS
AT GENOM ARE STILL REFUSING
TO DECLASSIFY THE SCHEMATICS
FOR THAT BOOMER.
- ALRIGHT, IF THEY
WON'T COOPERATE
MAYBE WE CAN GET THEM
FROM THE ARMY ITSELF.
- HEY, I CAN'T LET YOU HACK
INTO THE MINISTRY OF DEFENSE.
- THEN TURN YOUR BACK
AND CLAIM YOU DIDN'T SEE IT.
( thinking )
HOLD ON, PRISS.
- ( cars honking )
- GET OUT OF MY WAY!
MY HOUSE IS RIGHT THERE, I'VE
GOT TO GO SAVE MY FAMILY!
Police Officer: - I'M SORRY SIR,
WE CAN'T LET ANYONE THROUGH.
IF YOU DON'T RETURN TO
YOUR VEHICLE IMMEDIATELY,
WE'LL BE FORCED TO ARREST YOU!
- I CAN'T GET THROUGH.
- ( screaming )
- I DON'T GET IT, WHY
WON'T YOU DIE?!
- THIS ISN'T THE EASIEST HACK
I'VE EVER DONE,
BUT AT LEAST IT'S NOT AS BAD
AS CRACKING INTO GENOM.
- ( beeping )
- WHAT PROGRAM'S THAT?
- A PARASITE BOMB.
IT'S LIKE A VIRUS COMBINED WITH
A LOW-VOLTAGE ELECTRICAL PULSE.
THE SURGE SNAPS THE SYSTEM,
AND THE VIRUS UPLOADS ITSELF.
- AND YOU'RE SENDING IT
TO THE DEFENSE DEPARTMENT?!
- I'M GOING TO BLOW
THEIR FIREWALL AND GRAB THE DATA
BEFORE THEIR DEFENSE SYSTEM
KICKS IN.
OTHERWISE, THIS COULD TAKE
HOURS TO HACK.
- OKAY, I DIDN'T SEE
ANY OF THIS, IT NEVER HAPPENED.
- HERE WE GO!
- WHERE IS THE CORE?
- ( screams )
Priss: - MACKY, HOW DO
I KILL THIS THING?
- JUST WAIT, NENE'S
TRYING TO PULL IT OUT
OF THE DEFENSE
MINISTRY'S COMPUTER.
HOLD ON!
- ( panting ) THIS MIGHT BE
TOO MUCH FOR ME TO HANDLE.
MY POWER CELL IS
ALMOST EXHAUSTED.
HURRY UP AND DIE,
DAMN YOU!
- ( screaming )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M COVERING
FOR A KNIGHT SABER.
NOTHING WILL SURPRISE
ME ANYMORE.
- HOLD ON!
- ( panting )
- LINNA, YOU'RE BACK!
- MM-HMM.
- ( electric guitar )
- ( panting )
- I'VE GOT TEN SECONDS TO GO--
FIVE SECONDS--
GOT IT!
- HOLY COW!
NO WONDER WE CAN'T HIT THE CORE,
THAT THING'S NOT REALLY
A BOOMER AT ALL.
IT'S ACTUALLY A SUIT
WITH A NORMAL BOOMER INSIDE IT.
- I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WEREN'T SEEING ANY OF THIS.
Sylia: - PRISS, YOU'RE
ALMOST OUT OF POWER,
GET OUT OF THERE
WHILE YOU CAN.
- IT'S A BIT LATE
FOR THAT NOW.
- Nene: ATTENTION AD
POLICE COMMAND TEAM,
THE LOCATION OF THE
MILITARY BOOMER'S CORE
HAS BEEN IDENTIFIED.
TRANSMITTING DATA FILES NOW.
- ( shouting )
- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
Linna:
- PRISS!
- ALRIGHT!
- UM, WHAT'S ALRIGHT?
- UH... ( laughing )
- Linna:
LOOK OUT, PRISS!
JUMP!
TRUST ME!
- Linna:
ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
Priss: - YEAH, BUT YOU TOOK
YOUR SWEET TIME GETTING HERE.
Linna: - WHY PRISS,
WERE YOU WAITING FOR ME?
Priss:
- LET'S GO.
- I'LL DRAW ITS FIRE.
- TIME TO DIE!
- ( grunting )
- THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- THANK GOD NENE FIGURED IT OUT.
- YEAH, LET'S GO.
- SURE.
- WHAT IS GOING ON, MASON?
I THOUGHT WE HAD TOTAL
CONTROL OF THE MEDIA.
THIS IS
A PUBLIC RELATIONS DEBACLE.
- IT'S NOT OUR FAULT SIR.
I HAVE PROOF THE MILITARY MADE
UNLICENSED MODIFICATIONS
TO THAT BOOMER,
WHICH CAUSED IT TO GO ROGUE.
- HM, SEE THAT THE MEDIA
STARTS DISTRIBUTING THE
STORY IMMEDIATELY.
THIS IS WHY I WAS AGAINST
THE APPLICATION OF BOOMERS
FOR MILITARY PURPOSES.
- AN IMPRACTICAL VIEW SIR.
MILITARY CONTRACTS ARE WHAT KEEP
OUR LEDGERS IN THE BLACK.
AND THOSE PROFITS
FINANCE THE SHOWEN PROJECT.
- YOU KNOW HOW HARD I'VE WORKED
TO MAKE PEOPLE ACCEPT BOOMERS
AS THE FRIENDS OF HUMAN BEINGS.
I WILL NOT ACCEPT THIS TYPE
OF ERROR AGAIN!
- ( coughing violently )
NOW, GO.
- ( door opens and closes )
Kusui: - YOU KNOW, THIS IS
A REALLY NICE CHAIR YOU HAVE.
ACTUALLY, THE WHOLE ROOM
IS PRETTY DARN SNAZZY.
IT'S GOT THAT, "I'M THE SECOND
MOST POWERFUL MAN
IN THE WHOLE
WORLD" FEEL TO IT.
- MHM, HOPING TO MOVE IN?
- I DON'T THINK SO,
IT'S A BIT TOO EXPOSED FOR ME.
I PREFER ANONYMITY AND
A GENEROUS PAYCHECK.
WHICH REMINDS ME, I WANT A BONUS
FOR RIGGING THAT
MILITARY BOOMER.
- I'M CHANGING OUR PLANS. IT'S
CLEAR THAT THE KNIGHT SABERS
HAVE BOTH A TECHNOLOGICAL
AND STRATEGIC EDGE.
NOT ONLY IS THEIR COMBAT
EQUIPMENT SUPERIOR,
BUT THEY OBVIOUSLY HAVE
OTHER RESOURCES
THAT WE KNOW NOTHING ABOUT.
I HAVE NOW COME
TO THE CONCLUSION
THAT WE'VE BEEN GOING
ABOUT THIS THE WRONG WAY
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
RATHER THAN TRYING TO ELIMINATE
THE KNIGHT SABERS,
I SUGGEST THAT WE EMPLOY THEM.
- YOU WANT THE KNIGHT SABERS
TO SEARCH FOR YOU?
- STINGRAY LEFT ME
AN INHERITANCE.
I INTEND TO USE IT.
- ( chattering )
Sylia: - MACKY, TRY CHEWING
YOUR FOOD THIS TIME.
Linna:
- WOW THIS IS INCREDIBLE!
Nene:
- I'M SO HAPPY.
THIS IS WONDERFUL,
YOU'RE A GREAT COOK!
- I'M GLAD YOU ENJOY IT.
MORE WINE?
- HENDERSON IS A GREAT COOK.
BUT IF YOU EAT TOO MUCH
YOU MIGHT NOT BE ABLE TO FIT
BACK INTO YOUR HARDSUIT AGAIN.
- BY THE WAY NENE, JUST HOW DID
YOU GET PAST THE FIREWALL
ON THE DEFENSE MINISTRY'S
COMPUTER NET?
- THAT'S MS. NENE, REMEMBER?
BUT SINCE YOU ASKED,
I USED A VIRUS I'M DEVELOPING.
- WHAT?  WAS THAT A SAFE THING
TO DO, NENE?
- OF COURSE IT WASN'T,
THEY'RE PROBABLY STILL TRYING
TO RECOVER THEIR HARD DRIVES
OVER THERE.
- Priss: BUT THEY WON'T KNOW
THAT YOU DID IT, RIGHT?
- Sylia: OF COURSE NOT,
NENE KNOWS WHAT SHE'S DOING.
THE FIRST TIME I RAN INTO NENE,
I WAS TRYING TO HACK INTO GENOM
AND FOUND OUT THAT SHE HAD
ALREADY FOUND
THREE DIFFERENT BACK DOORS IN.
I ASSUME YOU USED A PULSE CODE
SCRAMBLER TO COVER YOUR TRACKS?
- Nene: (laughing)
ACTUALLY, I DIDN'T.
- HUH?
Nene: - DON'T WORRY, IF THEY
DO MANAGE TO TRACE IT BACK
THEY'LL FIGURE IT
WAS JUST SOME KIDS
USING A FAKE ADP LOG IN ID.
- YOU EITHER HAVE
NERVES OF STEEL,
OR NO COMMON SENSE AT ALL.
- ACTUALLY, I JUST DIDN'T
HAVE TIME TO WORRY
ABOUT THE CONSEQUENCES.
- ( all laughing )
Sylia: - SO, DID YOU HAVE A NICE
STAY AT YOUR PARENT'S HOUSE,
LINNA?
- I GUESS IT SET
MY PRIORITIES STRAIGHT.
- HM.
- HEY, NENE, CAN YOU HELP ME
LOAD THE NEW SYSTEM DOWNSTAIRS?
- IT'S MS. NENE TO YOU!
- BUT YOU'RE NOT
THAT MUCH OLDER THAN ME.
- I AM MENTALLY!
AND I WOULDN'T LET YOU
CALL ME JUST NENE
IF YOU WERE BORN A TRILLION,
JILLION YEARS BEFORE I WAS!
OH, NO YOU DON'T! YOU'RE NOT
GETTING AWAY THAT EASILY!
- HEY, PRISS--
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW...
- ( arguing continues
in background )
Henderson:
- MASTER MACKY...
Sylia:
- CHILDREN...
Nene:
- OKAY, I CREATED THIS SYSTEM
BUT IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I DEBUGGED IT.
HM, I'M AFRAID IT MAY BE
GETTING TOO LARGE
FOR THE SIZE OF THE BUS.
OF COURSE, IF I PUT A REPEATER
HERE AT THE BRIDGE
THE OVERALL RESPONSE RATIO OUGHT
TO BE IMPROVED A LITTLE BIT.
AT LEAST FOR THE MOMENT.
- OH, I SEE. THAT MAKES SENSE.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
WHEN THE CIRCUITS FOR SYLIA
AND PRISS GOT DOUBLED UP,
I SURE COULD HAVE USED YOU THEN.
- ( both shout )
- HEY, WAIT. I THINK
YOU SHOULD HAVE
TO FIGURE THESE THINGS
OUT FOR YOURSELF.
AND ANYWAY, I HAVE A LOT OF
MORE IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO
THAN BABYSITTING YOU.
- OKAY.
- BUT YOU CAN STILL
ASK ME QUESTIONS.
- THANK YOU, NENE.
- ( scowls )
- MA'AM!
- ( both laughing )
- THE GATE'S STILL OPEN.
WHOSE CAR IS THAT?
- ( gasps )
- ( heavy metal plays )
- I KNOW YOU,
YOU'RE DR. STINGRAY'S...
- I'M SORRY, BUT I THINK
THAT YOU'VE MADE A MISTAKE.
YOU HAVEN'T MET THIS BOY BEFORE,
HE'S JUST MY ASSISTANT.
- REALLY?
WHAT AN UNUSUAL COINCIDENCE.
WELL, TAKE SOME TIME AND
THINK ABOUT MY OFFER.
STRANGE, YOU NEVER SEEMED LIKE
THE KIND OF PERSON
WHO'D WANT TO GET
HIS HANDS DIRTY.
- HEY, DON'T STAND THERE.
GET INSIDE, QUICKLY.
- THAT WAS PROFESSOR MASON,
WHAT DID HE WANT?
- FORGET ABOUT IT.
- DID YOU TELL HIM ABOUT SYLIA?
- STUPID KID.
I WISH HE WASN'T
SO MUCH YOUNGER THAN ME.
- UGH, WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
AM I NUTS?
- I FINALLY FOUND OUT THAT
WHAT MASON'S BEEN LOOKING FOR
IS AN OLD UNDERGROUND RESEARCH
FACILITY CALLED THE WIZ LAB.
- WAIT A MINUTE, I THOUGHT
MY FATHER'S LAB WAS DESTROYED.
- THAT'S WHAT I BELIEVED,
BUT MASON APPARENTLY THINKS
THAT THE ENTIRE STRUCTURE
WAS SIMPLY DISPLACED
DURING THE EARTHQUAKE.
- AND HE'S TRYING TO FIND IT?
IS HE INSANE?
- HE'S BEEN BORROWING
ENGINEERS AND EQUIPMENT
FROM THE DRAGON PROJECT
IN ORDER TO CARRY
OUT HIS SEARCH.
ALL OF THIS WITHOUT CHAIRMAN
ROSENKREUTZ'S KNOWLEDGE,
I MIGHT ADD.
- NO, HE CAN'T BE
LOOKING FOR THAT,
IT MUST HAVE
BEEN DESTROYED!
- I'M AFRAID THAT'S ALL I KNOW
AT THE MOMENT, GOOD-BYE.
- ( monitor turns off )
- ( crying )
- GALATEA.
Kusui: - THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANTED, RIGHT?
- ABSOLUTELY PERFECT.
I'M VERY FORTUNATE TO HAVE
EMPLOYEES LIKE YOU.
Kusui: - FORTUNATE'S NOT
EXACTLY THE WORD THAT I'D USE.
I JUST SELL MY SERVICES TO
WHOEVER MAKES THE HIGHEST BID.
IT'S A MATTER
OF SIMPLE ECONOMIC PRINCIPLES.
Mason: - AND A NOT SO
SIMPLE CODE OF ETHICS.
COME IN.
- HM?
- MR. KUSUI DESERVES A BONUS FOR
HIS SERVICES. GIVE IT TO HIM.
- SO ARE YOU THE BONUS, OR IS
THERE CASH INVOLVED AS WELL?
- THANK YOU, MR. KUSUI.
- ( choking sounds )
- ( crashing )
- THIS IS BORDERING
ON OBSESSION NOW.
( typing ) HM, LET'S SEE--
STINGRAY FAMILY RECORDS.
FATHER,
MOTHER,
BROTHER.
- ( gasps )
HEY NOW, WAIT A SECOND.
WHEN IN THE HELL WAS
THIS PICTURE TAKEN?!
OH MY GOD,
THAT WAS TEN YEARS AGO.
Macky: - NIGEL, DID YOU TELL
PROFESSOR MASON ABOUT SYLIA?
Nigel:
- SHUT UP!
HURRY UP AND GO TO BED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
Woman: - IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040--"
SEEKING THE HELP
OF THE MYSTERIOUS DR. SHAN
SYLIA LEARNS THE TRUTH ABOUT
GENOM'S SECRET PLANS
FOR THE EXCAVATIONS
BENEATH THE CITY.
NOW SHE MUST FIND A WAY
TO STOP MASON FROM UNEARTHING
THE ULTIMATE NIGHTMARE.
BUT NEW FRICTIONS AMONG
THE KNIGHT SABERS
MAY PROVE TO BE HER UNDOING.
THE SECRETS TO HER BURIED PAST
ARE UNVEILED,
AND A NEW HORROR IS UNLEASHED.
NEXT EPISODE...