- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Man: ALL RIGHT, LEON.
I THINK THIS TAPE
SPEAKS FOR ITSELF.
IF YOU'VE GOT AN EXPLANATION,
I'D LOVE TO HEAR IT.
- ( groans )
McNichols here.
Those damn Knight Sabers
beat us to it again.
The situation is over.
- THE SITUATION IS OVER?
IT'S JUST BEGINNING.
YOU WERE SPEAKING ON AN OPEN
COMM FREQUENCY, YOU IDIOT!
WHAT THE HELL WERE
YOU THINKING?
- MAYBE IT'S TIME THAT WE ALL
STARTED THINKING, SIR.
SOMETHING HAS TO BE DONE
ABOUT THE KNIGHT SABERS.
- YES, BUT IT'S NOT OUR JOB.
THEY'RE UNDER THE JURISDICTION
OF THE REGULAR POLICE.
- SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS
THAT YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY SURE
THAT THEY'RE HUMAN BEINGS,
NOT SOME NEW KIND
OF BOOMER TECHNOLOGY.
NOT ONLY ARE THEY
INCREDIBLY MOBILE,
BUT THEY'RE A QUARTER
OF THE SIZE OF ANY COMBAT ARMOR
I'VE EVER HEARD OF,
WITH THREE TIMES THE WEAPONRY.
FRANKLY, THEY MAKE OUR
DIVISION'S MOST ADVANCED K-2s
LOOK LIKE REFUGEES
FROM THE 20TH CENTURY.
- ALL THAT MAY
OR MAY NOT BE TRUE,
BUT THE FACT REMAINS THAT THE AD
POLICE ISN'T RESPONSIBLE
FOR CONTROLLING THESE
VIGILANTES.
- AH, SOMEONE UPSTAIRS
HAS TOLD US TO BACK OFF.
- NO, I NEVER SAID THAT,
AND I DENY IT CATEGORICALLY.
NOW GET OUT OF HERE, YOU BUMS.
AND THE NEXT TIME
THE KNIGHT SABERS BEAT YOU,
I'LL TRADE THEM FOR YOU.
- IT SEEMS TO ME THAT THE
KNIGHT SABERS
ARE A LOT LIKE THE
GUARDIAN ANGELS.
- THE GUARDIAN WHAT?
- ANGELS.
THEY WERE A VOLUNTEER POLICE
FORCE THAT TRIED TO PROTECT
THE SUBWAYS IN LATE 20TH CENTURY
NEW YORK AGAINST MUGGERS.
- EXCEPT THAT THE KNIGHT SABERS
AREN'T INTERESTED
IN REGULAR CRIME.
THEY ONLY SHOW UP
FOR BOOMER INCIDENTS.
I DON'T THINK THEY'RE
INTERESTED IN JUSTICE,
JUST AN EXCUSE
TO KICK SOME ASS.  DAMN!
WHY DOES TOKYO ATTRACT
ALL THE NUTS?
- YOU KNOW--
- DID YOU JUST HAVE AN IDEA?
- MAYBE IT'S SOME KIND OF TEST.
- A TEST?
WHAT FOR?
- THEIR POWERED SUITS
ARE YEARS AHEAD
OF ANYTHING
I'VE EVER HEARD OF,
AND THAT INCLUDES
MILITARY MODELS.
THAT KIND OF EFFICIENCY MUST
HAVE COST A BUNDLE TO DEVELOP,
WHICH MEANS THEY MUST BE PART
OF SOME LARGER ORGANIZATION,
RIGHT?
- YOU MEAN LIKE MAYBE
A MILITARY STRIKE FORCE.
- YES, BUT IT'S ONLY A THEORY.
- THEORY OR NOT.
IT'S JUST ONE MORE GOOD REASON
TO GET RID OF 'EM.
- Nene:
GOOD MORNING, LEON-POO.
- NENE, WHY DO YOU HAVE TO
KEEP CALLING ME
BY THAT INFANTILE
NICKNAME?
- 'CAUSE I LIKE YOU, SILLY.
- HOW CAN YOU REFUTE SUCH
AN ELOQUENT ANSWER?
- DAMN IT, DALEY.  WHY DO YOU
HAVE TO KEEP ON ENCOURAGING HER?
- I WAS JUST PROVIDING...
- ( Nene laughing )
- ...A DIVERSION.
- HUH?
- ♪ LEON'S A GREAT BIG
POO HEAD ♪
- THIS ISN'T THE POLICE.
IT'S A KINDERGARTEN.
GOD HELP US.
- THIS DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
ALL THAT VIOLENCE,
ALL THAT DESTRUCTION,
AND THERE'S NOTHING ON THE NEWS
ABOUT IT AT ALL.
- Boomer Female Supervisor:
MISS YAMAZAKI,
MISS LINNA YAMAZAKI.
- PSST, LINNA.
SHE'S TALKING TO YOU.
- HELLO, CAN I HELP YOU?
- ACCESSING A NEWS SITE
USING YOUR WORKSTATION
IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED.  THIS
WILL BE NOTED ON YOUR RECORD.
- HEY, WHY DIDN'T YOU WARN ME
A LITTLE EARLIER?
- EXCUSE ME.  I WARNED YOU
FOUR TIMES, BRAIN DONOR.
- OH!  I'M STARTING TO HAVE
SERIOUS SECOND THOUGHTS
ABOUT WORKING HERE.
- HMM.
NOW THIS SHOULD SHOW OFF
THAT LOVELY FIGURE OF YOURS.
- YES, BUT DON'T YOU THINK
IT MIGHT BE SHOWING OFF
A LITTLE TOO MUCH?
- FOR SOME PEOPLE, BUT WHEN
A GIRL HAS A LOVELY BODY,
I CAN'T STAND TO SEE HER HIDING
IT UNDER A BUNCH OF FLOPPY RAGS.
PLEASE, TRY THIS ONE ON FOR ME.
- WELL, IF YOU INSIST.
- ( doorbell rings )
- WHY, IT'S PRISS THE SINGER.
WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
IF YOU'LL JUST WAIT
THERE A MOMENT,
I BELIEVE I'VE GOT EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
- ( scoffs )
- SO HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
HAVE YOU FINALLY TIRED
OF THAT WORN LEATHER LOOK?
HMM, AND JUST LOOK
AT ALL THOSE SPLIT ENDS.
YOU'LL NEED A NEW CONDITIONER.
- I WANT MY PAY.
- HUH?
OH, YES, OF COURSE.
I HAVEN'T PAID YOU
FOR THE LAST ONE, HAVE I?
YOU KNOW, IT WOULDN'T HURT YOU
TO WEAR THE CLOTHES I RECOMMEND
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
- I WEAR YOUR HARDSUITS.
ISN'T THAT ENOUGH?
SHE DOESN'T FIGHT VERY WELL AND
SHE'S ALWAYS GETTING IN MY WAY.
- YOU MEAN NENE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
SHE WANTS TO FIGHT AND SHE'S
THE ONLY BACKUP WE HAVE.
- I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF YOU WERE READY TO MAKE
ANOTHER HARDSUIT YET.
- ANOTHER HARDSUIT?
DO YOU HAVE SOMEBODY IN MIND?
- NOT REALLY.
- MISS, IT'S NICE,
BUT ARE YOU SURE THIS OUTFIT
REALLY COVERS ENOUGH OF ME?
- OH, NO, YOU LOOK FABULOUS.
HERE, LET'S TAKE A GOOD LOOK
IN THE MIRROR, OKAY?
- I WANT TO BE A KNIGHT SABER,
TOO, AND I'M NOT GIVING UP.
- So will I see you later?
- OF COURSE.
I'LL SHOW YOU THE ROPES.
( laughs )
- ( gulps )
- WHY, GOOD MORNING, KAIN.
DID I JUST HEAR YOU MAKING
A DATE OVER YOUR COMPUTER?
- NO, IT'S NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS ANYWAY.
- FORTUNATELY, THE REGULATIONS
DON'T SAY THAT I CAN'T USE
SOMEONE ELSE'S COMPUTER
TO ACCESS THE NET.
LET'S SEE WHAT THERE IS
ON THE KNIGHT SABERS.
- ( videogame beeping )
- ( alarm blaring )
- HUH?
THE AD POLICE COMPUTER
MUST HAVE SOME RECORD
OF WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
- TRYING TO CRACK INTO THE FILES
OF THE KNIGHT SABERS, ARE YOU?
YOU'RE BRAVE, BUT CLUMSY.  LET'S
SEE HOW BRAVE YOU REALLY ARE.
- ( maniacal laughter )
- WHAT?
- Nobody who has investigated
the Knight Sabers
has ever survived.
Turn back before it's too late.
- WHAT IN THE HELL'S
GOING ON HERE?
- HEY, WAIT, I KNOW HER.
- Man: MISTRESS SYLIA.
- HUH?
- ARE YOU INTENDING
TO ADD ANOTHER MEMBER
TO THE KNIGHT SABERS,
MILADY?
- NENE LACKS THE SKILLS TO BE
A SOLID PARTNER FOR PRISS,
AND SHE'S NOT GOING TO BE
READY ANYTIME SOON.
OF COURSE, I COULD GO BACK
TO ACTIVE DUTY MYSELF.
BUT SOME PEOPLE DON'T
LIKE THAT IDEA.
- ( sighs )
THE CURRENT MEMBERS WERE FOUND
THROUGH FORTUNATE ACCIDENTS.
SURELY YOU DON'T EXPECT
SERENDIPITY
TO PROVIDE YOU ANOTHER
VIABLE CANDIDATE.
- I'M GETTING SICK AND TIRED
OF YOUR WORRYING, HENDERSON.
THE TRUTH IS THAT
I HAVEN'T DECIDED
WHETHER TO INCREASE
THE NUMBER YET OR NOT.
- SORRY TO BOTHER YOU, MILADY.
- ( whirring )
- HMM.
- Woman: Greetings, Sylia.
You have an encoded
voice transmission.
- LET'S HEAR IT.
- Man: Things are really
beginning to heat up.
People in the tower are
beginning to become sensitive
to the fact that the ratio
of mad boomer occurrences
is slowly increasing.
There's a rumor going around
that the lab people suspected
it may be transmittable.
But the Tower is spreading
disinformation to the contrary,
claiming that the boomers
are completely safe.
We're headed for a crisis.
I'll call you again later
when it's safe.
- Woman: End of transmission.
No more voice mails.
- DAMN IT!
BOOMERS ARE SAFE!
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MINDS?
BOOMERS ARE A THREAT
TO EVERYONE ON THE PLANET.
THOSE FOOLS, DON'T THEY KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE PLAYING WITH?
( sobs )
THEY'RE INSANE.
THEY MUST ALL BE INSANE!
- I LIKE BOOMERS, MASON.
IN FACT, THE TRUTH IS
THAT I LOVE THEM.
THEY EXIST ONLY TO RELEASE
MANKIND FROM THE BURDENS
OF PHYSICAL PAIN
AND EXHAUSTION.
WHEREAS PREVIOUS SOCIETIES
HAVE BANISHED THOSE
WHO PERFORMED THE MOST BASIC
AND VISIBLE TASKS
TO THE LOWEST CASTES,
MY BOOMERS WILL CHANGE
THIS FOREVER.
WE WILL TAKE CARE OF THEM.
- BUT, SIR,
THE MARKET IS SHRINKING
AND DEMAND FOR OUR PRODUCT
IS DECREASING.
WE OVERPRODUCED
AFTER THE EARTHQUAKE
AND THE MARKET IS FLOODED.
- THAT'S WHY WE HAVE
ADVANCED THE SCHEDULE
FOR THIS SHOWHAM PROJECT,
ISN'T IT, MASON?
- TRUE AND WHEN THE PROJECT
SUCCEEDS, YOU AS THE MASTER
OF THE GENOM CORPORATION
WILL BE IN A PRIME POSITION
TO TAKE CONTROL
OF THE ENERGY INDUSTRIES
OF EVERY NATION
IN THE WORLD.
- ( sighs )
WE'RE NOT DOING THIS FOR PURELY
FINANCIAL GAINS, MASON.
- I KNOW THAT, SIR.
HOWEVER--
- ( laughs )
I CAN HEAR YOUR THOUGHTS
AS PLAINLY AS IF YOU'RE
SPEAKING OUT LOUD.
YOU'RE WONDERING
IF I'LL EVEN LIVE TO SEE
THIS PLAN THROUGH
TO COMPLETION, AREN'T YOU?
I MUST LOOK PATHETIC TO YOU
DESPERATELY CLINGING TO LIFE.
- NO, SIR.
- I WON'T BE LIKE THIS FOREVER,
MASON, AND IT'S THAT THOUGHT
THAT KEEPS ME ALIVE.
WHY DO YOU THINK
I INVESTED SO MUCH
INTO MAKING GENOM CONTROLLER
OF ALL BOOMER TECHNOLOGY?
- HMM.  HOW PATHETIC.
AS ANTICIPATED,
CHAIRMAN ROSENKREUTZ
HAS INSTRUCTED US TO ACCELERATE
THE TIMETABLE
FOR THE SHOWHAM PROJECT.
INCREASE OUR PRODUCTION
OF BOOMERS ACCORDINGLY.
- YES, MR. VICE PRESIDENT.
- ♪ WE TRAVELED TO THE EAST ♪
♪ WE TRAVELED TO THE WEST ♪
♪ AND THEN WE SLEEP
A LITTLE WHILE ♪
♪ WHY DO WE DO IT?
IT'S STUPID ♪
♪ WE'RE LIVING
A MADMAN'S FANTASY ♪
♪ STOP THE WORLD,
I'M GETTING OFF ♪
♪ I'VE HAD IT
WITH THIS CRAP
♪ CATASTROPHE ♪
♪ CONSUMES US ALL. ♪
- OKAY, KNOCK OFF
FOR FIVE MINUTES.
- I'D KILL FOR A SMOKE
RIGHT NOW.
- I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA QUIT.
- HUH?
- Man: DON'T YOU KNOW ALL
MUSICIANS ARE SELF-DESTRUCTIVE?
- YOU AGAIN.  BUT HOW?
- I JUST ASKED THE MANAGER
OF THE CLUB
YOU WERE PLAYING AT LAST NIGHT.
HE TOLD ME I COULD PROBABLY FIND
YOUR BAND REHEARSING HERE.
- OH, A GROUPIE!
- REALLY?  LET ME SEE.
MAN, WHY DOES OUR PRISS ALWAYS
ATTRACT THE MOUSY COUNTRY GIRLS?
- I DON'T KNOW, DUDE.
MAYBE WE'RE PLAYING
IN THE WRONG KIND OF CLUBS.
- I KNOW THAT'S RIGHT.
- OKAY, YOU FOUND ME.
NOW WHAT?
- I WANT TO JOIN UP.
- JOIN WHAT?
- YOU KNOW.
- THE BAND?
- OF COURSE NOT.
YOU KNOW WHAT.
- BIKER GANG.
- LOOK, I'M SERIOUS.
STOP PLAYING WITH ME.
- AM I?
- YOU KNOW THAT YOU ARE.
- TRUE.
BUT YOU'RE ASKING FOR IT.
- YOU GET OFF ON TAUNTING ME,
DON'T YOU?
JUST BECAUSE I'M A DUMB
COUNTRY HICK DOESN'T MEAN
THAT I HAVE TO TAKE YOUR CRAP.
NOW CUT IT OUT OR ELSE, DAMN IT!
- OR YOU'LL CRY AGAIN?
- LISTEN, IF YOU THINK YOU CAN
SCARE ME OFF, YOU'RE WRONG.
I KNOW YOU'RE ONE OF THE KNIGHT
SABERS AND I WANT TO SIGN UP
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
- IT TAKES MORE THAN WORDS.
HEY, GUYS, I GOTTA SPLIT.
- WHAT?
HEY, ONE "MOMENTITA",
SENORITA.
WE STILL HAVEN'T WORKED OUT
A BRIDGE FOR THAT NEW SONG YET.
COME ON, LITTLE SCOOTER.
YOU COST ME MY ENTIRE
FIRST PAYCHECK.
YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP UP
WITH HER.
COULD THIS BE SOME KIND
OF TEST?
( screams )
OH, NO!
YOU CAN'T BREAK DOWN.
I KNEW I SHOULDN'T HAVE
BOUGHT A USED ONE.
( panting )
- WOW.  SHE'S GORGEOUS.
- Linna:
BUT NOW WHAT?
WHY ARE THEY GOING IN THERE?
( grunting )
THAT WAS TOO EASY.
- UM, EXCUSE ME.  HELLO.
I'M NOT INTERRUPTING ANYTHING,
AM I?
HUH?  NO WAY.
HOW CAN IT BE A DEAD END?
( screams )
I SUPPOSE THAT IF THIS PLACE
IS REALLY THE HIDDEN BASE
OF THE KNIGHT SABERS, THEY'D
NEED THIS TO HANDLE INTRUDERS.
HUH?!
- Nene: HEY, PRISS,
LOOK AT THE NEW MODIFICATIONS
NIGEL MADE TO MY HARDSUIT.
- NENE, IT'S YOUR BODY
THAT NEEDS FINE TUNING,
NOT YOUR HARDSUIT.
- OH!
HUH?
- WELL, WELL.
- AT LONG LAST SHE ARRIVES.
- HEY, I DIDN'T ASK HER.
SHE JUST FOLLOWED ME HOME.
- EXCUSE ME.
- HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
I KNOW HER, TOO.
SHE'S THE ONE WHO HACKED
INTO THE AD SERVER
LOOKING FOR INFORMATION
ON THE KNIGHT SABERS.
AND SHE WAS THE ONE
WE RESCUED THE OTHER NIGHT.
- HMM.
- IF YOU WANT ME TO LEAVE...
- YOU'RE A PRETTY ONE,
AREN'T YOU?
NICE HIGH CHEEKBONES,
VERY NICE INDEED.
AT LEAST NOW I'M FINALLY
BEGINNING TO UNDERSTAND
WHY OUR LITTLE PRISS WANTS YOU
TO JOIN OUR LINEUP.
- THAT'S NOT EXACTLY
WHAT I SAID, YOU KNOW?
- PRISS WANTS ME TO JOIN?
- NOW WAIT A SECOND.
PRISS WANTS HER ON THE TEAM?
BEING A KNIGHT SABER
IS A BIG RESPONSIBILITY.
WE CAN'T JUST LET ANYONE
WALK IN OFF THE STREET.
- YES, THAT'S TRUE.  THAT'S
EXACTLY WHAT I TOLD SYLIA,
BUT SHE GAVE YOU
A HARDSUIT ANYWAY.
- STOP BEING MEAN TO ME!
- STOP IT!
- HMM?
- PLEASE, BEFORE YOU MAKE UP
YOUR MINDS ABOUT ME,
LET ME SPEAK FOR MYSELF.
I DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT YOU YET,
BUT I KNOW THAT I WANT
TO BE ONE OF YOU.
I DIDN'T MOVE TO TOKYO
JUST TO GET A STUPID JOB.
I'VE BEEN READING RUMORS ABOUT
A GROUP OF ARMORED VIGILANTES
ON THE INTERNET
FOR OVER A YEAR NOW.
AND THE MORE I HEARD,
THE MORE I FELT THAT WHAT
YOU WERE DOING WAS IMPORTANT
ENOUGH TO RISK EVERYTHING
TO JOIN THE KNIGHT SABERS,
IF YOU'LL HAVE ME.
- WELL, LET'S TRY YOU OUT.
THE HARDSUITS WE WEAR
HAVE TO BE CUSTOM FITTED.
THE PLUMBING AND MUSCLE
CONNECTIONS ALONE
ARE A NIGHTMARE
TO CONFIGURE.
WHAT THAT MEANS IS THAT
THERE'S NO WAY TO TEST YOU
IN REAL ARMOR, SO WE HAVE TO
USE THIS TORTURE DEVICE INSTEAD.
WELL, COME ON, GIRL.  THIS IS
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR,
ISN'T IT?  LET'S SEE IF YOU'VE
REALLY GOT WHAT IT TAKES
TO BE A KNIGHT SABER.
- TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
- Sylia: IT'S NOT EXACTLY
THE SAME, OF COURSE,
BUT THE SIMULATOR
SHOULD GIVE YOU AN IDEA
OF WHAT A REAL MISSION
IS LIKE.
NENE, PULL UP FILE 84.
ARE YOU STILL SURE YOU WANT
TO GO THROUGH WITH THIS?
- I'M SURE. ( gasps )
- TARGET CONFIRMED.
LET'S DO IT.
- EVERYBODY, STAND BACK.
THE K-2 WILL HANDLE THIS.
- Nene: OH, BOY,
IT'S THAT IDIOT DHARMA
AND HIS PIECE OF JUNK.
- WELL, LET'S SEE
IF HE'S LEARNED ANYTHING YET.
- HA!  GOTCHA!
- Priss: NOPE, PARTY OVER.
CLOSING TOO QUICKLY.
- WHAT?
- ( screaming )
- SHOULDN'T WE HELP HIM?
- Nene:
PRISS, WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
- Sylia: ALL RIGHT, PRISS,
YOU'VE HAD YOUR LITTLE FUN.
NOW GET IN THERE
AND TAKE THAT BOOMER OUT.
- OKAY, LET'S GO.
- DAMN IT.  HERE COME
THE KNIGHT SABERS.  STOP 'EM!
- ( panting, screaming )
- I'M GOING IN.
- ( screaming )
- Nene: WE'RE RUNNING OUT
OF TIME, PRISS.  HURRY!
- ( panting )
OH, MY GOD.
MY GOD.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040,"
LINNA'S TRIAL BY FIRE CONTINUES
AS HER KNIGHT SABERS' HARDSUIT
IS READY FOR ITS FIRST TEST.
MEANWHILE, CHAIRMAN ROSENKREUTZ
AND MASON UNVEIL THEIR PLANS
FOR THE DOMINATION OF TOKYO.
ANOTHER BOOMER GOES BERSERK AND
THE SABERS STREAK INTO ACTION.
BUT WILL THEY ARRIVE IN TIME?
NEXT EPISODE...