- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( sighs )
HAS THE ENTIRE STATION
BECOME GALATEA?
- Linna: NENE?
- MMM?  WHAT, LINNA?
- HOW MUCH LONGER WILL OUR SUITS
BE ABLE TO OPERATE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THE POWER RESERVES
ARE ALMOST DRAINED.
- IF WE BOTH
POOLED OUR POWER TOGETHER,
COULD WE GET BACK?
- NO.
IT MAY LOOK
LIKE WE'RE NOT MOVING,
BUT WE'RE ACTUALLY
FLYING TOWARD EARTH
AT THE SPEED OF THE EXPLOSION.
AND AS WE GET CLOSER TO EARTH,
ITS GRAVITY WILL PULL US IN.
- WHAT?!
ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT WE'RE
GOING TO CRASH INTO THE EARTH
OR BURN UP IN THE ATMOSPHERE?
I WON'T BELIEVE IT!
I WON'T!
- Nene: IT'S POSSIBLE.
- NO! I WON'T ACCEPT IT.
THINK, NENE.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT IT.
- IT'S ALL UP TO PRISS NOW.
- ( Priss panting )
( grunts )
GALATEA!
WHAT THE HELL?
- ( rumbling )
GODDAMN BOOMER!
- ( chattering )
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AH!  GOD DAMN IT.
GET THE HELL OUT!
AHH! GET OUT OF MY MIND!
OH!
( shouting )
( grunting )
( roaring )
- ( squeaking )
- HELLO.
- ARE YOU SYLIA?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
MY NAME IS SYLIA STINGRAY.
WHO ARE YOU
AND HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
- WHO AM I?
DON'T YOU KNOW?
DON'T YOU KNOW WHO I AM?
- MMM?
- UH, SORRY.
MY NAME IS PRISCILLA.
BUT YOU CAN CALL ME PRISS.
- OH, THAT'S PRETTY. YOU HAVE
A VERY NICE NAME, PRISS.
- WHERE ARE WE?
- THIS IS MY MOTHER'S HOUSE,
BUT SHE'S NOT HOME RIGHT NOW.
- Priss:
AM I SOME KIND OF MEMORY?
SOMETHING GALATEA COPIED
FROM INSIDE SYLIA'S BRAIN.
- Galatea: THE HUMAN BRAIN
IS MERELY A SYSTEM
FOR THE STORAGE
OF ELECTRICAL IMPULSES.
TRANSFERRING SUCH DATA INTO A
SIMPLE VESSEL SUCH AS YOURSELF
IS CHILD PLAY.
- WAIT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"TRANSFER INTO"?
- SYLIA'S NEURO PATTERNS
FORMED MY VOOMER CORE.
NOW THE OPPOSITE WILL OCCUR
AS YOU BECOME MY ANTI-SEED
AND ABSORB THE INFORMATION
WHICH I HAVE CHOSEN TO
DOWNLOAD INTO YOU.
YOU WILL BECOME A PART OF ME,
A HUMAN COMPONENT.
YOUR MIND AND BODY
ARE BECOMING ONE WITH ME.
YOUR ORGANICS WILL
BE SUPPLEMENTED
BY VOOMER COMPONENTS.
AND LIKE SYLIA,
YOU WILL SIMPLY BECOME
ANOTHER FACET OF MY MEMORY.
- NO!  STAY AWAY FROM ME!
- ( chattering )
- ( grunting )
OH!  OH!  AHHHH!
- ( airplane passing )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- WE HAVEN'T HEARD ANYTHING.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
WE CAN DO FROM HERE.
ALL OF OUR ARMIES
AND WEAPONS,
AND IN THE END,
THE FATE OF MANKIND
ENDS UP DEPENDING UPON
A HANDFUL OF YOUNG WOMEN.
IT'S SO IRONIC.
- LET'S GO.
SYLIA WANTS TO TAKE MACKY
BACK TO THEIR OLD HOME.
- ( door opens, closes )
- ( airplane passes )
- Linna: OKAY, NENE,
WE'RE IN SERIOUS TROUBLE HERE.
LET'S PUT THOSE BRAINS TO WORK.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A WAY
WE CAN GET TO EARTH SAFELY.
- Nene: HARDSUIT,
I'M RELEASING YOU
FROM THE RESTRAINTS
ON YOUR FORM AND FUNCTION.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- CAN YOU SEE
THE IMAGE IN MY MIND?
- ( gasps )
NENE, WHAT DID YOU DO?
- AN AIRFOIL--
TRANSFORM YOUR SUIT.
- TRANSFORM IT?  HOW?
- WITH YOUR MIND.
- HARDSUIT, MERGE YOUR MIND INTO
MINE AND BECOME ONE WITH ME.
LET NENE ALTER YOUR SHAPE.
PRISS?
- Priss:
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
HAVE I BECOME PART
OF GALATEA?
ARE THESE THINGS I'M SEEING
THROUGH HER EYES?
WHAT IS THAT?
NENE AND LINNA?
WE'RE STILL ALIVE.
IT'S NOT OVER.
NOT YET!
( grunting )
I AM NOT PART OF YOU!
I AM DIFFERENT.
( grunting )
- Galatea: FOREIGN SUBSTANCE
DETECTED IN THE BODY.
IMMUNE SYSTEM ACTIVATE.
- ( grunting )
GALATEA!
I'M COMING FOR YOU!
- ( alarm sounding )
- NO!  NO!
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
OXYGEN-- HOW LONG UNTIL THE AIR
IN MY SUIT RUNS OUT?
MAYBE A FEW MINUTES
IF I'M LUCKY.
I-- I DON'T WANT
TO DIE THIS WAY.
- ( grunting )
NENE?
- Nene:
JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
- ( heartbeat )
- Male voice: YOU NEED POWER.
- WHAT?
- RELEASE THE RESTRAINTS
THAT HOLD ME
AND I CAN HELP YOU.
- UH, I'D BE GLAD TO DO IT,
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- ( alarm sounding )
- THAT WAS SUFFICIENT.
- ( whirring )
- MY CREATOR BOUND ME
TO YOUR THOUGHTS.
YOU HAVE RELEASED ME.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- I WAS CREATED
TO SERVE YOU, PRISS.
- YOU'RE MY MOTOSLAVE.
- ( chanting ) AHHHHH.
- Priss: YOU REALLY ARE ALIVE,
AREN'T YOU?
- YES, I AM CAPABLE
OF INDEPENDENT ACTION.
HOWEVER, MY POWER RESERVES
ARE RUNNING LOW
AND I WAS DAMAGED
WHEN THE SKY HOOK CRASHED.
- Priss: ALL RIGHT,
LET'S FINISH HER OFF
BEFORE SHE REALIZES
WE'RE NOT DEAD.
MOTO, YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
BUT I'VE GOT
TO DESTROY GALATEA.
ARE YOU WITH ME?
- I WAS CREATED
TO AID AND PROTECT YOU, PRISS.
YOU ARE THE ONLY MASTER
I SERVE.
- DON'T CALL ME THAT.
INTELLIGENT BEINGS
CAN'T OWN EACH OTHER.
- ( Galatea
continues chanting )
- AHHHH!
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO LEARN
WHAT THE OTHER HALF
OF BEING ALIVE IS LIKE!
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO DIE,
GALATEA!
- Galatea: WHY?
WHY DO YOU PERSIST
LIKE THIS?
WHY DO YOU WISH TO REMAIN
AS A HUMAN BEING?
AS LONG AS YOU REMAIN HUMAN,
YOUR MIND AND BODY
CANNOT EVOLVE.
WHY DO YOU
RESIST YOUR DESTINY?
I DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
( chanting ) AHHHHH!
- Priss: WHAT'S GOING ON?
IS SHE FALLING APART?
- Moto: INCORRECT.
SHE IS SPEEDING UP
HER EVOLUTION.
- ( beeping )
- PRISS!
- ( grunting )
- ( Galatea chanting )
- Moto: PRISS,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YOU'VE GOT IT WORSE THAN ME.
- YOU MUST HURRY.
POWER SUPPLY DIMINISHING.
- AHHHH!
- ( sighs )
- MOTOSLAVE, YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M THINKING OF, DON'T YOU?
- AFFIRMATIVE.
- GOOD.  LET'S DO IT.
- AS YOU WISH.
- AHHHH!
AHHHHHH!
- GALATEA, I'M SORRY
IT HAD TO COME TO THIS.
MOTOSLAVE!
- ( Galatea chattering )
- Galatea:
TO DIE,
TO REPRODUCE,
TO BE REBORN.
THE ENDLESS CYCLE
OF DEATH AND RESURRECTION.
THAT IS THE EVIDENCE
OF GOD.
- ( booming )
- ( sighs )
- ( Galatea chattering )
- Galatea: AT LAST
I HAVE FOUND THE PATH.
AT LAST I UNDERSTAND.
WHEN PRISS ENTERED MY BODY,
WHEN MY THOUGHTS WERE PASSED
INTO PRISS'S BRAIN--
INFINITE WISDOM
REQUIRES INFINITE PERSPECTIVE.
ONLY BY EXPERIENCING
EACH ELEMENT,
EACH MOMENT SEPARATELY
AND IN THEIR OWN TIME,
DOES THE BEAUTY OF THE WHOLE
BECOME APPARENT.
IT IS THE CYCLE THAT IS THE
REAL NATURE OF THOUGHT.
- ( mutters )
- IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- MMM.
IT IS, LIKE A BIRTH.
- ( pinging )
- ( giggling )
- THIS IS CRAZY!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- AS TREMENDOUS AMOUNTS
OF NEUTRINO PARTICLES
CONTINUE TO BE OBSERVED,
THE GOVERNMENT IS URGENTLY
TRYING TO ORGANIZE A COMMITTEE
TO INVESTIGATE
THE CAUSING OF THIS PHENOMENON.
- Galatea: PRISS?
DON'T YOU WANT TO GO HOME?
- I WANT TO,
BUT IT'S TOO LATE.
- YOU GAVE ME A GIFT.
NOW PLEASE ACCEPT MINE.
- Sylia: MACKY?
ARE YOU--
MACKY!
( crying )
- SYLIA.
- Priss:
♪ THOUGH I CAN'T SEE YOU ♪
♪ I KNOW THAT YOU'RE HERE ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL IT
INSIDE MY HEART ♪
♪ YOUR PRESENCE
IS ALWAYS NEAR ♪
♪ YOU HIDE IN MY MIND ♪
♪ IN THE CORE OF MY SOUL ♪
♪ A MIRACULOUS PRESENCE
INSIDE ♪
♪ I'VE OPENED THE PATH ♪
♪ TO COME THROUGH ♪
♪ TOMORROW'S MY PROMISE
FOR YOU ♪
♪ SHA LA LA LA
LA LA ♪
♪ I GIVE ALL I HAVE FREELY ♪
♪ FOR YOU ♪
♪ I ASK FOR NOTHING MORE ♪
♪ THAN A PLACE TO LIE DOWN ♪
♪ NEXT TO YOU ♪
♪ AND IN TIME
OUR HISTORY ♪
♪ WILL KNOW US
AS SHOOTING STARS ♪
♪ WHOSE UNION GAVE BIRTH ♪
♪ TO THE WIND. ♪
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )