- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( Boomers
banging into glass )
( banging continues )
- PRISS, LINNA, NENE,
COME ON.
- Linna: RIGHT.
- ( banging )
- ( screeches )
- WHAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
IS WHY SHE'S SENDING THEM
TO ATTACK US NOW.
- BECAUSE WE'RE HERE.
NOBODY ELSE IS.
- THIS MIGHT BE THE LAST TIME
WE GET TO CHANGE IN THIS ROOM.
THE LAST COUPLE OF MONTHS HAVE
BEEN PRETTY CRAZY, HAVEN'T THEY?
- THEY SURE HAVE.
- ( banging on glass )
- ( both gasp )
- OH, I DON'T BELIEVE THIS!
GO AWAY!
- THEY'RE JUST BOOMERS.
WHO THE HELL CARES?
- ( banging )
- Linna: WE'RE NOT ALL
EXHIBITIONISTS, PRISS!
- HURRY UP! IF THEY BREAK THAT
WINDOW AND FLOOD THE ROOM,
YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO SUIT UP.
- RIGHT.
PRISS AND I WILL SUIT UP FIRST.
OKAY, GO AHEAD.
- YEAH.
- SO HERE WE GO
INTO BATTLE,
BUTT-FRIGGIN' NAKED.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THIS PICTURE?
- ( grunts )
- KEEP YOUR MIND OPEN.
I KNOW THAT YOUR CUTS
AREN'T HEALED YET,
BUT IF YOU'RE NOT RECEPTIVE
TO THE SUIT,
THE INNER METAL WON'T BE ABLE
TO SET PROPERLY.
- I UNDERSTAND.
( grunting )
- ( banging continues )
- ( cracking )
- OOH!
- ( rumbling stops )
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE THEY DOING OUT THERE?
- Sylia:
WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
- IT WON'T HOLD MUCH LONGER.
CAN EVERYONE HERE SWIM?
- AHEM.
- Nene: I CAN DOG PADDLE.
- Linna: LOOK AT THE GLASS.
- HUH?
- ( glass smashing )
- IT'S GOING TO GO!
- THAT ONE'S GOING TO GO TOO!
- Priss: WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?! COME ON!
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- COME ON, MACKY!
- Linna: SYLIA!
- LET'S GO.
- ( inhaling )
- GO AHEAD.
- Nene: YOU TOO, MACKY.
- ( grunting )
- OH, CRAP!
- NENE!
I THOUGHT
YOU COULD DOG PADDLE?
- NOT VERY WELL.
- HERE WE GO NOW.
READY? UP!
- ( panting )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- FOR MY AGE,
I'M DOING REMARKABLY WELL.
- LET'S GO.
- OH!
- HUH?
- Leon:
MY GOD, THEY'RE EVERYWHERE.
- ( fighting sounds continue )
- IS EVERYONE ALL RIGHT?
- Leon:
WELL, WE'RE ALL ALIVE.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO THIS PLACE?
- Nene: SOMETHING DISGUSTING!
- Sylia: IT'S NOT JUST THIS
BUILDING. LOOK DOWN THERE!
- ( gasps )
LOOK AT THE CITY.
IS THIS REALLY TOKYO?
- Linna: IT'S AS IF A
COMPLETELY NEW ECOSYSTEM
SPRUNG UP OVERNIGHT.
- Nigel: IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE GOT NOWHERE ELSE TO GO.
- GALATEA DIDN'T TARGET US.
SHE ABSORBED THE WHOLE CITY.
- ( rumbling )
- ( all screaming )
- NOW WHAT?
- Linna: ANOTHER EARTHQUAKE?
- NO, WORSE!
WE'VE GOT TO
GET OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW!
- YOU NEED A LIFT?
- HOLD ON.
- ( grunts )
- ( rumbling )
- Nene:
IT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS!
- Linna: JUST AS I THOUGHT.
- Nigel: GALATEA
MUST HAVE EXTENDED
A BRANCH OF A DRAGON LINE
BENEATH THE BUILDING.
- ( Brian shuddering )
OH, YES.
AT LAST.
SO LOVELY, SO EMPTY.
EVEN MORE BEAUTIFUL
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
AH, THIS IS WHAT I WANTED,
WHAT I'VE DREAMED OF
FOR SO LONG.
AH.
( laughing )
- ( beeping )
- ( children playing )
- Boy: GIVE ME THE BALL!
- HEY!
- GO, GO!
- ( whimpering )
- ( suit whirring )
- Sylia: PLEASE TELL ME
I DIDN'T SEE THAT.
- Priss: YOU DID.
- Leon: NO MATTER WHERE WE GO,
IT'S ALL THE SAME.
- Priss: SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
- Sylia: THERE'S ONE PLACE
THAT MIGHT STILL BE SAFE.
- HA!
MAN, I'M STIFF.
- MMM, AT LAST.
- LOOKS LIKE
IT HASN'T GOT THIS FAR YET.
- Sylia: THIS IS THE ONLY PLACE
I COULD THINK OF
THAT MIGHT NOT BE AFFECTED.
THE GROUND WATER LEVEL
IS SO HIGH
THAT THE DRAGON LINE
COULDN'T BE EXTENDED HERE.
AND YOU DON'T NEED BOOMERS
IN A PARK.
- HOLD ON.
SHOULDN'T THERE
AT LEAST HAVE BEEN
SOME CLEANING OR
MAINTENANCE BOOMERS?
- THEY WERE PROBABLY SET
TO RETURN TO A GARAGE AT NIGHT.
SO IF THERE WERE ANY HERE,
THEY'RE GONE NOW.
- IF YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT,
THEN WE OUGHT TO BE SAFE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- THAT'S GOOD.
AT LEAST
WE COULD GET SOME REST.
- ( both chuckle )
- ( twigs breaking )
- WHAT'S THAT?
- ( shuddering )
- MAN, YOU SCARED THE HECK
OUT OF US.
- Sylia: I CAN'T BELIEVE
THERE'S ANYONE
STILL IN THIS CITY
BESIDES US.
- ( shuddering )
BOOMERS!
- BOOMERS?
I THINK WE MAY
HAVE A PROBLEM HERE.
- LOOK.
- LET'S GET 'EM.
- WHEN THE EVACUATION ORDERS
CAME,
WE DIDN'T BELIEVE
THAT THEY WERE REAL.
AND WHEN WE SAW
WHAT WAS HAPPENING,
IT WAS TOO LATE TO GET OUT.
THE BOOMERS WERE EVERYWHERE.
- ( panting )
- WE TRIED WALKING,
BUT THE ROADS WERE ALL BLOCKED
OFF BY BOOMERS.
AND WHEN THE BUILDINGS
ALL STARTED TO TURN AS WELL,
WE DIDN'T HAVE ANY PLACE
LEFT TO HIDE.
- ( panting )
- AS NEAR AS WE CAN TELL,
THIS PARK IS THE ONLY PLACE LEFT
IN THE ENTIRE CITY
THAT IS FREE OF BOOMERS.
FAR TOO MANY OF US
DIDN'T MAKE IT HERE IN TIME.
HMM?
- TA-DA!
HOW DO I LOOK?
( laughs )
- JUST FINE.  HUH?
- ( both chuckling )
- Leon: I SEE.
SO EVERYONE WHO COULDN'T GET OUT
DURING THE EVACUATION
HEADED FOR THIS PARK?
- YES.
WE'RE PROBABLY
THE LAST 50 PEOPLE IN TOKYO.
- THAT MANY OF YOU?
- YES.
BUT IT'S NOT SO MANY
WHEN YOU CONSIDER
HOW MANY OF US DIDN'T MAKE IT.
MORE TEA?
- YOU'RE A STRONG MAN.
- ACTUALLY, I USED TO BE
A REAL JERK.
I REMEMBER MY MOTHER
ALWAYS USED TO SAY
THAT GOD HELPS THOSE
WHO HELP EACH OTHER.
AND HE DID LEAD US
TO THIS PARK.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT COMING HERE WAS MY IDEA,
YOU KNOW.
- BECAUSE YOU SLEPT HERE
WHEN YOUR WIFE KICKED YOU OUT.
- AH!
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO ADD THAT!
- ( men all laughing )
- I HOPE YOU LADIES
CAN FORGIVE US
AFTER MISTAKING YOU
FOR BOOMERS.
- WELL, I REALLY CAN'T BLAME YOU
UNDER THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
- YEAH, AND IT'S NOT AS IF WE'VE
KEPT A HIGH PROFILE, IS IT?
- BY THE WAY,
THANKS FOR THE FOOD AND COFFEE.
YOU'RE AWFULLY KIND TO BE
SHARING THEM WITH US LIKE THIS.
- DON'T WORRY.
YOU CAN GO HUNTING WITH US
TO PAY IT BACK.
- HUNTING?
- Man: YEAH, THAT'S
WHAT WE CALL IT.
- ( bottles rattling )
- THIS ISN'T HUNTING,
THIS IS LOOTING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE MAKING ME DO THIS.
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
A POLICE OFFICER, DAMN IT.
- SHH.  THE BOOMERIZATION LINE
IS RIGHT DOWN THE STREET.
YOU CAN COMPLAIN LATER.
- I KNOW,
IT JUST BURNS MY ASS.
- ( humming )
( gasps ) THE BOOMERS!
THE BOOMERS ARE COMING!
AAH!
- TIME TO GO.
- ( grunts )
- RUN!
- ( men laughing )
- HEY, THIS IS REALLY GOOD.
- YEAH, THAT'S MY SPECIAL BLEND
OF SIX DIFFERENT KINDS OF CURRY.
I ADDED A SQUIRREL
FOR SOME FLAVOR.
- YEAH, I'M IN
THE CLOTHING BUSINESS TOO.
- LIAR! I KNOW FOR A FACT
YOU WORK AT YOUR UNCLE'S RUBBER
GALOSHES FACTORY.
- ( Sylia chuckling )
- HERE YOU GO.
- THIS STUFF IS GREAT.
YOU REALLY KNOW YOUR BOOZE,
MISTER.
- OH, I'VE HAD A LOT
OF EXPERIENCE.
- ( men laughing )
- ( sighs )
- HMM!
- WELL, YOU'RE REALLY
PUTTING THAT STUFF AWAY.
BUT DON'T WORRY,
WE'VE GOT LOTS MORE.
SO YOU HELP YOURSELF
TO ALL YOU WANT.
- ( men chattering )
- YOU DON'T SEEM LIKE THE KIND
WHO GIVES UP EASILY.
WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS NOW?
- I'M NOT SURE YET.
I'M STILL TRYING TO COME UP
WITH A PLAN OF ACTION.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS?
- Nigel: TOKYO'S ALMOST
COMPLETELY TAKEN OVER NOW.
IT WON'T BE POSSIBLE
TO GO HUNTING ANYMORE.
YOU'D BETTER LEAVE
WHILE YOU CAN.
- IF WE CAN LEAVE.
- ( chattering )
- ( silent )
- ( men laughing )
- ( gulping )
( sighs )
AND THEN THAT-- THAT PERVERT
PUT HIS HAND ON MY THIGH.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?!
- SOUNDS LIKE A REAL JERK
TO ME.
- THAT'S RIGHT!
MEN ARE SUCH PIGS.
- UH-HUH, UH-HUH, UH-HUH, YEAH.
- ( moans, laughs ) PRESENT
COMPANY EXCEPTED, OF COURSE!
- JEEZ, HOW MANY OF THOSE THINGS
HAS SHE HAD ALREADY?
- ( chattering continues )
- ( laughing )
- ( beeping )
- SO THIS IS WHERE
YOU'VE BEEN HIDING.
I THOUGHT YOU FINISHED
YOUR BACKUPS.
- ( beeping )
- HMM?
- THAT'S SYLIA'S
CLASSIFIED FILE, RIGHT?
- ( laughing )
- WHAT'S WRONG, MACKY?
- ( evil chuckling continues )
- Nene: MACKY!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040,"
LIKE A MULTI-HEADED SERPENT,
THE BRANCHES OF THE DRAGON LINE
BECOME THE ARMS
WITH WHICH GALATEA SEEKS
TO CRUSH THE LAST
VESTIGES OF RESISTANCE
REMAINING IN THE CITY.
ONLY THE KNIGHT SABERS REMAIN,
MANKIND'S LAST DEFENSE
AGAINST THE NIGHTMARISH SPAWN
OF MAN AND MACHINE.
BUT CAN EVEN THE SABERS DEFEAT
A BEAST WITH A MILLION EYES
AND THE MIND
OF AN INSANE CHILD?
NEXT EPISODE...