- ( theme music playing )
- Daley: WHAT?  HOW CAN YOU
TALK ABOUT THE STRIKE
AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
THIS IS AN EMERGENCY.
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT LITTLE
PHRASE "TO SERVE AND PROTECT"?
WELL, LET'S SEE WHAT HAPPENS
IF YOU NEED TO BE RESCUED.
WHAT THE-- THEY HUNG UP!
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT THOSE
UNION JERKS, DALEY.
WE'VE GOT ENOUGH MEN
TO HANDLE THIS
ALL BY OURSELVES.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, MEN?
- All: YES, SIR!
- REMEMBER, IF ANY OF YOU
GET SEPARATED DOWN THERE,
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO MEET UP WITH
LEON AT THE MAIN LOADING DOCK.
- Daley: OKAY, SPARKS AND HIS
MEN ARE IN THE SEWERS NOW.
I'M GUESSING THAT IT WILL TAKE
TEN MINUTES FOR THEM
TO REACH THE BASE
OF THE TOTEM POLE.
- ROGER.  WE'LL MEET UP
WITH THEM INSIDE.
- FIRE!
- KEEP THE ENTRANCE CLEAR WHILE
WE SCOUT OUT THE FIRST LEVEL.
- RIGHT, SIR.
- HEY, GET BACK HERE!
HOLD UP.
YOU CAN'T GO IN THERE ALONE.
- WHICH WAY NOW?
- FORGET ABOUT UP.
IF ANYONE'S STILL IN HERE,
THEY'RE PROBABLY
ON THE LOWER LEVELS.  THAT'S
WHERE ALL OF THE OFFICES ARE.
UPSTAIRS, THERE'S NOTHING
BUT COMMUNICATIONS EQUIPMENT
AND COOLING SYSTEMS
FOR THE TOTEM POLE.
DO YOU REALLY WANNA TRY
TO FIND NENE ALL BY YOURSELF?
- GET OFF.
- ( pounding )
- ( gasps )
- THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
( screams )
- Man: HEY, ROMANOVA,
IS THAT YOU?
- Nene:
HUH?
OH, MY GOD, A K-SUIT!
MR. ROLAND, IS THAT YOU?
- I HAD THIS UP
IN THE MAINTENANCE CENTER.
UNFORTUNATELY, IT'S THE ONLY
ONE.  ARE YOU OKAY?
- YOU ALMOST MADE ME RUIN
MY UNDERWEAR
WITH THAT THING.
- DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
DUCK, ROMANOVA.
- UH-OH.
( screaming )
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
I'M IN THE FRAY,
HEADED INTO THE FIRE.
- HEY, ROLAND,
I'M GETTING LOW!
- RIGHT, PULL BACK.
- THIS IS AS LOW
AS THE FREIGHT ELEVATOR GOES.
- WHERE NOW?
- THEY'RE PROBABLY IN--
THIS IS NUTS.
THEY JUST KEEP COMING.
- UM, SIR.
- OH, MY GOD.
WE'VE BEEN FLANKED.
- IT'S ALL OVER.
- OH, MY GOD.  PRISS!
- LEON, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
- PRISS, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
CAME FOR ME.
- NICK, WE BLEW OUT THE DOOR
TO THE MAIN LOADING DOCK.
WE CAN EVACUATE EVERYONE
VIA THE FREIGHT ELEVATORS.
IS THIS ALL THERE IS?
- KID.
- PRISS, TAKE NENE
AND CLEAR A PATH FOR US.
- COME ON, MOVE YOUR ASS,
NENE.
- RIGHT.
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN DOING
OKAY FOR SOMEONE YOUR AGE, NICK.
- QUIT BROWN-NOSING, LEON.
- ARE THOSE STAIRS CLEAR?
- I'M CHECKING.
( screams )
- ENOUGH, SIR!
- ( snarls )
- WHAT'S THAT?
- Leon:
NICK, IT'S ON YOUR BACK.
- IT'S WHAT?
- YOU'LL HAVE TO
SHAKE IT OFF OF YOU SOMEHOW.
I'M TOO CLOSE TO SHOOT
THAT THING OFF SAFELY.
- ( laughing )
- HOLD ON.
- GET OUT OF THAT K-SUIT.
THAT BOOMER'S FUSING WITH IT.
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A REALLY GOOD IDEA.
DAMN IT, I CAN'T GET THE HATCH
ON THIS PIECE OF JUNK TO BLOW.
- ( laughing )
- STOP LAUGHING.
- GIVE IT ANOTHER TRY, ROLAND.
- RIGHT.
HERE IT COMES!  ( screams )
- WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF AMMO.
WILL YOU STOP PLAYING
AND GET WITH THE PROGRAM?
- ( grunts ) OH, SURE.
THIS'LL JUST BE A WALTZ
IN THE PARK.
WELL, COME ON, DAMN IT!
LET'S GET MOVING.
AND BY THE WAY, THANKS.
- ( engine revving )
- I HOPE YOU'VE GOT
A REAL GOOD GRIP ON ME.
'CAUSE I'M NOT STOPPING.
- ( shouting )
- ( growls )
- NENE.
- MOVE YOUR ASS!
- ( gasps )
- WELL, COME ON.
- THANKS, GUYS.
- LEON-POO CAN BE SO COOL.
- ( growling )
- LEAVE THE BIKE.
- ( grunting )
- DAMN IT.
- ( screaming )
- GET READY TO CLOSE IT.
SAFE.
OH!
UH...
- ( squealing )
- HARUMA.
- HUH?  OKAY.
IT'S NOT GOING THROUGH.
THEY'RE JUST ABSORBING
THE BULLETS.
- ( glass shatters )
- OH!
THERE'S NO WAY.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO GO BACK
AND FIND ANOTHER WAY OUT.
- Daley: WHAT?  WHAT DO YOU
MEAN NOBODY'S THERE?
- Man: THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY MUST HAVE BEEN CUT OFF.
BUT WE'VE GOT THE MASTER
POWER GRID SECURED.
- OKAY, TURN IT ON.
( sighs )
- ( electricity crackles )
- WELL, AT LEAST THE LIGHTS
ARE BACK ON.
- SPARKS GROUP MUST HAVE
RESTORED THE POWER.
- DOES ANYBODY ELSE THINK
GOING DOWN'S A BAD IDEA?
- YEAH, I DO.
I GUESS THE ONLY WAY
TO GO IS UP.
- IS ANYONE ELSE COLD?
- IT'S ALWAYS LIKE THIS UP HERE.
THAT'S THE LIQUID NITROGEN TANK
THAT COOLS
THE ADP COMMUNICATIONS TOWER.
- LIQUID NITROGEN.
NO WONDER I'VE GOT GOOSE BUMPS
ON MY GOOSE BUMPS.
I'D REALLY LIKE TO GET MY HANDS
ON THE IDIOT
WHO PUT A MINISKIRT
ON A COP'S UNIFORM.
- WOULD YOU REALLY WANNA DEPRIVE
US POOR OLD FOSSILS
OF ONE LAST CHANCE TO SEE A LEG
WITHOUT VARICOSE VEINS?
IF YOU WANNA BLAME SOMEONE,
BLAME THE IDIOTS WHO INSTALLED
A COMMUNICATIONS TOWER
THAT'S 100 TIMES MORE POWERFUL
THAN WE'LL EVER NEED.
- WHAT IN THE HELL?  WHY ARE
ALL THE BOOMERS GOING UP?
IT MAKES NO SENSE.
COMMANDER SPARKS, ARE YOU
SURE THIS DATA'S ACCURATE?
- IT'S ACCURATE.
- Leon: DALEY, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- HUH?
- LEON, WHERE ARE YOU NOW?
- WE'RE INSIDE
THE COMMUNICATIONS TOWER.
AND UNFORTUNATELY,
WE'RE NOT ALONE.
- WHAT?!
EVERY BOOMER IN THE PLACE
IS HEADING TOWARD YOU.
GET THE HELL OUT OF THERE
RIGHT NOW!
- WE'RE TRYING TO.
- NOT AGAIN.
- I GUESS THE LADDER'S
THE ONLY WAY.
- IT LOOKS LIKE THE ONLY WAY
LEFT TO GO IS UP.
DAMN IT, DALEY,
CAN'T YOU DO SOMETHING?
- DO SOMETHING?
ARE YOU NUTS?
I'M ALL ALONE, YOU BIG IDIOT.
- ( door opens )
- HUH?
- OH, NOT COMPLETELY ALONE.
WELL, IF YOUR FRIEND
AND THE OTHERS
HAVE DECIDED TO GO UP,
I SUPPOSE THE LEAST WE CAN DO
IS TO GO UP
AND MEET THEM.
- ARE YOU WHO I THINK YOU ARE?
- HEY, DON'T LOOK A GIFT HORSE
IN THE MOUTH.
- ( laughs nervously )
- HUH?
THEY'VE STOPPED FOLLOWING US.
- I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
- THEY WERE NEVER
FOLLOWING US.
THEIR REAL TARGET MUST BE THE
CENTRAL COMMUNICATIONS NEXUS.
FROM THERE, THEY CAN JACK
INTO EVERY COMPUTER NETWORK
IN THE CITY.
- YOU'VE GOT TO GET CLOSER.
- I KNOW THAT.
- ( groans )
HEY, WATCH IT!
WHERE IN THE HELL DID YOU
LEARN TO FLY THIS THING?
- THIS ISN'T A STUPID TAXI,
LADY.
- ( grunting )
OHH!
I'M SORRY, ROLAND.
- IF ROMANOVA'S RIGHT AND THOSE
BOOMERS ARE REALLY PLANNING
TO FUSE WITH
THE COMMUNICATIONS TOWER--
- THEN THIS WHOLE PLACE
HAS GOTTA BE FILLED WITH THEM.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, NO!
- HARUMA, HOW MANY BULLETS
DO YOU HAVE LEFT IN THAT THING?
- I HAVE 65 ROUNDS
OF BLASTERS LEFT.
- I THINK I'M ABOUT
TO BE BRILLIANT.
HEY, YANO, JUST HOW
MUCH LIQUID NITROGEN
IS THERE INSIDE THAT
COOLING SYSTEM?
- IT'S KIND OF HARD TO SAY.
IT USUALLY DEPENDS.
ASSUMING THAT THE CENTRAL TANK
IS FULL,
IT'S GOT A MAXIMUM CAPACITY
OF ABOUT 350 TONS.
YOU'RE NOT THINKING OF--
- THAT'S JUST WHAT
I'M THINKING.
AND YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S GOING TO HELP ME.
- ME?
- OKAY, EVERYBODY,
HERE'S WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME LEFT.
LET'S GET A MOVE ON.
- OH, MY GOD, LOOK.
- BOOMERS.
- YOU'RE IN TROUBLE, LEON.
THE WHOLE TOTEM POLE
IS BEING FUSED.
WHERE ARE YOU NOW?
- WE'RE ALMOST AT THE TOP
OF THE STAIRWAY.
- WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?
- RIGHT ABOVE YOU.
ARE YOU WITH ALL THE OTHERS?
- NOT QUITE. NICK AND DIRECTOR
YANO ARE STILL DOWN THERE.
- DOING WHAT?
HEY, I SEE THEM.
- CAN YOU SET THIS THING DOWN
ON THE ROOF?
- I CAN TRY.  LEON, I'M GONNA
TRY TO LAND THIS THING
ON THE COMMUNICATIONS PLATFORM.
- ROGER THAT.
- ALL RIGHT!
- WAIT A SECOND.
LEON, TELL THEM TO BACK OFF.
I KNEW IT!
- HURRY UP, YANO.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME LEFT.
- I'M HURRYING.
I'M HURRYING.
OH, NO, DAMN IT.
I CAN'T DO THIS, ROLAND.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- REMEMBER HOW I TOLD YOU
THAT THE MAIN COOLING TANK
HAD OVER 350 TONS
OF LIQUID HYDROGEN IN IT?
- SO WHAT?
- IN ORDER TO OPERATE
THIS CONTROL PANEL,
YOU NEED A CLASS 1 LICENSE,
AND I ONLY HAVE A CLASS 3.
- ( laughs, screaming )
YANO, IF YOU DON'T DO IT,
THERE WON'T BE ENOUGH OF YOU
LEFT TO HAVE YOUR LICENSE
REVOKED.
DO IT NOW!
- FINE.  YOU EXPLAIN IT
TO THE LICENSE BOARD.
- ( screaming )
- All:
OH, YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
- MOVE YOUR ASS, NICK.  WE CAN'T
HOLD 'EM OFF MUCH LONGER.
- WHAT ARE WE DOING
TO HOLD THEM OFF?
- DO IT NOW, LEON!
- PRISS, NENE,
ARE YOU OKAY?
- LINNA, MACKY.
- WELL, IT WORKED.
I'LL PROBABLY LOSE MY CLASS 3
FROZEN GASSES LICENSE
OVER THIS.
- I THINK THEY'LL UNDERSTAND,
YANO.
I GUESS THE A.D. POLICE
REALLY IS DEAD AND BURIED NOW.
- Rosenkreutz:
WELL, GENTLEMEN,
ARE WE IN AGREEMENT THEN?
- Man: WE'LL CALL
FOR A GENERAL MEETING
OF THE STOCKHOLDERS
IMMEDIATELY.
- AND NOW, MASON,
MY WOULD-BE KING,
YOU SHALL LEARN THAT
YOU ARE JUST A PAWN.
YOU!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE DESTROYED.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WHY DON'T YOU ANSWER ME?
NO BOOMER CAN IGNORE
MY ORDERS.
NO, YOU CAN'T DO THIS TO ME.
I CREATED YOU, BOOMER!
MASON!
- PLAY TIME NOW.
- ( theme music playing )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040,"
THE BATTLE FOR TOKYO MOVES
ONTO THE CITY STREETS
AS WAVE AFTER WAVE
OF ROGUE BOOMERS
ARE UNLEASHED AS GALATEA'S
POWERS BEGIN TO FULLY MANIFEST.
THE KNIGHT SABERS FIND
THEMSELVES COMPLETELY
OVERWHELMED.
THEIR ONLY CHANCE--
A DANGEROUS NEW TYPE
OF TECHNOLOGY.
BUT ARE THEY READY
FOR THE RISKS INVOLVED?
NEXT EPISODE...