- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( people chattering )
- HEY, MISTER.
WANT A DATE?
- SO I WAS
TELLING MY BOSS--
- ( screaming )
- All: HUH?
- ( screams )
- ( woman screams )
- ( crowd gasps )
- LOOK AT THAT!
- IT'S SOME KIND
OF A BOOMER!
- ( screaming )
- DAMN!  THAT RECREATIONAL
BOOMER'S GONE ROGUE.
- ( crowd screaming )
- DIE!  KILL IT!
( screams )
- OH, COME ON.
I'M NOT GOING TO
MAKE IT IN TIME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT THEY MADE ME
PULL DOUBLE OVERTIME
AT THE OFFICE AGAIN.
SYLIA, I'LL BE THERE
IN JUST A FEW MINUTES.
TWO MINUTES, I SWEAR!
- Sylia: I'm sorry, Linna.
I just sent Priss and Nene
out by themselves.
- OHH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY LEFT
WITHOUT ME AGAIN.
HUH?  OH, NO.
NOT NOW.  WHY ME?!
( groans )
IT'S JUST NOT FAIR.
WHY CAN'T I GET
JUST ONE BREAK?
HUH?
( sighs )
- ( groans )
- AND HOW WAS THAT?
- NOT TOO BAD.
- ( giggles )
- ALL RIGHT.  WHOO!
- ( cheering )
- HUH?
- ( applause )
- ALL RIGHT!
THANK YOU!
REALLY, YOU'RE TOO KIND.
BUT DON'T STOP.
- ( panting )
I'M FINALLY HERE.
( gasps )
- YOU SEE, PRISS?
I CAN DO THIS JOB JUST AS WELL
AS YOU AND LINNA CAN.
- ( sirens wailing )
- Priss: ARE YOU GONNA KEEP
PLAYING TO THE CROWD ALL NIGHT?
I'M LEAVING.
- WAIT FOR ME.
- WHOA!
- ( gasping )
- I GUESS I PUT
TOO MUCH STRESS ON IT.
HEY, WAIT.
THIS PART'S MANUFACTURED
BY GENOM.
- A PART IS A PART,
NO MATTER WHO
MANUFACTURES IT.
- YOU DON'T LIKE USING
A PART MADE BY GENOM, DO YOU?
- WELL, IT'S NO BIG DEAL,
I GUESS.
- ACTUALLY, GENOM PARTS
TEND TO BE
A LITTLE BETTER MADE
FOR THE MONEY.
- MACKY,
TORQUE WRENCH, PLEASE.
- OH, RIGHT, NIGEL.
HERE YOU GO.
- UH, HI THERE.
NENE'S BETTER THAN
SHE USED TO BE.
- Priss: IS SHE?
- YEAH.  A LOT BETTER.
AND THE TWO OF YOU HAVE
A LOT MORE EXPERIENCE
WORKING TOGETHER
AS A TEAM.
IT JUST FEELS LIKE
I'M BEING LEFT BEHIND.
- YOU NEED TO GIVE UP
THAT DEAD-END JOB.
- WOW.
- WHAT?
- THAT ALMOST SOUNDED
LIKE YOU LIKE ME.
- ( sighs )
- BUT SERIOUSLY,
I'VE GOT TO LEAVE
TOWN FOR A FEW DAYS.
- AND WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- MY PARENTS' PLACE.
MY MOM SAYS THERE'S
SOME BUSINESS
THAT SHE AND DAD HAVE TO
TALK ABOUT WITH ME.
COULD YOU TELL SYLIA I'LL BE
OUT OF TOUCH FOR A BIT?
- I SUPPOSE I COULD.
- Quincy:
WATCHING MY BOOMERS WORK
GIVES ME GREAT PLEASURE,
MASON.
- ON THE SUBJECT OF
THE SHOWEN PROJECT, SIR,
THE UMBRELLA WILL BE
COMPLETED ON SCHEDULE.
HOWEVER,
THERE IS A PROBLEM.
- A PROBLEM WITH
THE DRAGON?
- Mason: YES, SIR.
THE DRAGON IS NECESSARY
TO STORE THE ENERGY
SENT DOWN FROM
THE UMBRELLA.
BUT CONSTRUCTION OF
THE UNDERGROUND CHANNELS
AND RESERVOIRS IS
RUNNING BEHIND SCHEDULE.
- I THOUGHT WE HAD TAKEN
THE EARTHQUAKE INTO ACCOUNT.
- IT APPEARS THAT THE SHIFTAGE
WAS MORE THAN EXPECTED.
IN ADDITION, THE NUMBER OF
BOOMERS AVAILABLE
TO WORK ON THE PROJECT
HAS BEEN GREATLY REDUCED.
- I SEE.
DO YOU BELIEVE THIS PROJECT
IS IMPORTANT?
- IT'S OUR SOLUTION
TO THE PROBLEM OF EARTH'S
DWINDLING ENERGY RESOURCES.
BY CONTROLLING A SOURCE
OF CHEAP, UNLIMITED POWER,
GENOM WILL BE ABLE TO
MANIPULATE THE WORLD'S ECONOMY
THROUGH OUR ENERGY
MANAGEMENT.
- HMM.
DO YOU KNOW HOW I'VE
STAYED ALIVE LIKE THIS, MASON?
THE ANSWER IS MACHINES.
THERE IS NOTHING
THE BODY CAN DO
THAT A MACHINE
CANNOT DO BETTER,
PROVIDED THAT THE MACHINE
IS NOT RESTRICTED
BY A LACK OF ENERGY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THAT MEANS, MASON?
ONCE I BELIEVED THAT
BOOMERS WOULD FREE US
FROM THESE ORGANIC PRISONS
WE'RE BORN IN.
BUT AS IT TURNS OUT,
I WAS WRONG.
BOOMERS WILL SERVE MAN
MANY WAYS,
BUT NOT AS THE PATH
TO IMMORTALITY.
THE UMBRELLA MY BOOMERS
ARE BUILDING
IS ALMOST COMPLETE.
THE SHOWEN PROJECT
WILL GENERATE POWER
THE LIKE OF WHICH
HAS NEVER BEEN SEEN.
AND WITH THAT POWER,
I WILL CONTROL MORE THAN
JUST THE WORLD'S ECONOMY.
THE NATURAL ORDER ITSELF
WILL BE BENT
INTO SUBMISSION.
WITH MY BOOMERS
AND THE LIGHTNING OF HEAVEN,
I SHALL BRING ABOUT
A NEW ORDER
TO WHICH ALL LIVING THINGS
ON THIS PLANET WILL BE SUBJECT,
OR THEY SHALL
FEEL MY WRATH.
- MAMA?
MAMA?
- DREAM ON,
YOU SENILE OLD FOOL.
GET THE KNIGHT SABERS
FOR ME.
- ( chuckles )
WOULD YOU LIKE YOUR VIGILANTES
POACHED, FRIED,
OR SERVED ON A HALF-SHELL?
( clears throat )
UH, I'VE HEARD THAT
CHAIRMAN IS LOSING INTEREST
IN THE KNIGHT SABERS.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST LET
THE AD POLICE HANDLE IT?
- I DON'T THINK
I ASKED FOR YOUR OPINION.
- I DELAYED CONSTRUCTION
OF THE DRAGON LIKE YOU WANTED.
I'LL GET THEM FOR YOU.
( sighs )
- I DIDN'T THINK
THE EXPRESS WOULD
GET ME HERE SO FAST.
I'M TWO HOURS EARLY.
I SUPPOSE I COULD CALL.
BUT THEY'RE PROBABLY BUSY.
- A GEO-BATTERY?
SO ALL THIS DIGGING
HAS BEEN TO BUILD
A STORAGE VESSEL FOR THE POWER
THE UMBRELLA WILL GENERATE?
CHAIRMAN ROSENKREUTZ HAS
DELUSIONS OF GRANDEUR.
- Yes.  However,
they've recently begun
slowing down construction
on the dragon project.
I believe you're
already acquainted
with the person in charge
of the operation.
- BRIAN J. MASON.
- I'M SORRY,
BUT DR. STINGRAY
IS IN THE MIDDLE
OF AN EXPERIMENT.
YOU WANT TO BE A GOOD GIRL,
DON'T YOU?
AND A GOOD GIRL DOESN'T
BOTHER HER FATHER AT WORK,
DOES SHE?
GOOD GIRL.
- THERE MUST BE
SOMETHING MORE TO THIS
IF HE'S INVOLVED.
BUT WHAT?
- ( yawns )
- ( distant chattering )
- HUH?
- ( laughing )
- HELLO?
- ( laughing,
chatter continues )
- ( breathes deep )
I'M HOME.
- IS THAT HER?
- YEAH.
- AH, THE PRODIGAL RETURNS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE'S BACK, MAN.
- LINNA, WHY DIDN'T
YOU CALL SOMEONE
TO PICK YOU UP AT THE STATION?
- I'M SORRY, MOM.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO BE LATE.
- WELL DON'T JUST STAND THERE
LIKE A KNOT ON A LOG, GIRL.
MAKE A PROPER GREETING
TO OUR GUESTS.
- ( groans )
PLEASE ACCEPT MY APOLOGIES
FOR BEING LATE.
- I'VE HEARD YOU'RE
A CAREER WOMAN IN TOKYO NOW.
- SO, HAVE YOU FOUND
A BOYFRIEND YET?
- ( laughs ) GOD KNOWS
SHE DIDN'T HAVE ONE HERE.
- ( all laughing )
- I'LL TAKE BOOMERS
OVER MY RELATIVES ANY DAY.
- ( sighs )
- OH, I'M SORRY, MOM.
I WAS GOING TO HELP YOU
FINISH CLEANING UP, BUT--
- BUT YOU NEEDED A FEW
SECONDS TO YOURSELF.
I KNOW.
- I'VE JUST STARTED GETTING USED
TO BEING ON MY OWN IN TOKYO.
AND TO SUDDENLY COME BACK TO THE
MIDDLE OF ALL THIS IS WELL...
OVERWHELMING.
BUT I HAVE MISSED YOU
A LOT.
- AND HOW ARE THINGS
IN TOKYO?
ARE YOU EATING PROPERLY?
- I'M FINE.
- YOU KNOW YOUR FATHER
IS VERY HAPPY THAT YOU'RE BACK.
- AH?  HE DIDN'T SOUND
LIKE HE WAS GLAD TO SEE ME.
- WELL, HE'S NOT
THE KIND TO SHOW IT.
- NO KIDDING.
- ( chuckles )
THAT'S GOOD.
HOW LONG CAN YOU STAY?
- UNTIL TOMORROW.
NEW EMPLOYEES DON'T
GET VACATION TIME.
I HAVE TO BE AT WORK
MONDAY MORNING.
- I REALLY WISH YOU COULD
STAY ONE EXTRA DAY.
YOUR FATHER AND I ALREADY HAVE
SOMETHING PLANNED FOR TOMORROW.
- I KNEW IT.
THIS IS ANOTHER
OF DAD'S SCHEMES
TO FIX ME UP WITH
A NICE YOUNG MAN, RIGHT?
- WELL, ONE OF YOUR
FATHER'S CUSTOMERS
HAS THIS SON--
- BUT I'M...
- HMM.
IS THERE SOMEONE
SPECIAL IN TOKYO?
I KNOW YOU ALWAYS
USED TO SAY
THAT YOU DIDN'T KNOW WHAT IT WAS
THAT YOU WERE LOOKING FOR,
BUT THAT YOU WOULD KNOW WHAT IT
WAS WHEN YOU FINALLY FOUND IT.
- AND I DID.
- HUH?
- I FOUND SOMETHING.
BUT NOW THAT I'VE FOUND IT,
I THINK I'M AFRAID OF
MAKING THE COMMITMENT TO IT.
- COMMITMENT IS
A SCARY THING.
- YES, IT IS.
- Mason:
THE OLD FOOL WAS RIGHT.
THESE POWERED SUITS
ARE EXTRAORDINARY.
MAYBE I'VE BEEN
MISSING SOMETHING.
DISPLAY DR. STINGRAY'S STAFF.
ELIMINATE ALL
CONFIRMED DECEASED.
HMM.
NIGEL KIRKLAND.
BOOMER ENGINEERING SECTION.
DO YOU KNOW HOW AND WHY
YOUR PROTOTYPE
WAS ORIGINALLY CREATED?
- NO, SIR.
I DON'T KNOW.
- THE TRUTH IS,
STINGRAY DIDN'T INTEND
TO CREATE AN
ORDINARY ANDROID.
- "MET"?
IT MEANS "DEATH" IN HEBREW.
- CORRECT.
BUT WATCH WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN I CHANGE THE PATTERN
THE WAY STINGRAY DID.
- "EMET."
SO "DEATH" IS CHANGED
INTO "TRUTH"?
- THE CREATORS OF
THIS TOWER OF BABEL
HAVE LABORED ON,
BUT THEY ARE MISSING
ONE KEY BIT OF INFORMATION.
THEY BELIEVE THAT
THE WORSHIP OF SOULLESS GOLEMS
IS THEIR PATH TO BECOMING
A LIVING GOD.
BUT I WILL FIND
THAT MISSING KEY
AND WAKE IT.
FINDING THAT BOOMER
IS THE PURPOSE AND REASON
FOR WHICH I WAS BORN.
BUT YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- NO, I DON'T.
- HOW COULD YOU?
YOU'RE A GOLEM.
AN EMPTY SHELL.
FOR SO LONG I BELIEVED
THAT ROSENKREUTZ
WAS BOTH THE BIGGEST
OBSTACLE IN MY PATH
AND MY GREATEST
POTENTIAL ALLY.
BUT PERHAPS I WAS WRONG.
- WHY COULDN'T YOU WEAR
THAT NICE KIMONO WE BOUGHT YOU?
- BECAUSE MY HAIR'S
NOT RIGHT FOR IT.
- IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL, DEAR.
IT'S JUST A SIMPLE
INTRODUCTION.
- YOU'RE WRONG, MOM.
I WENT AHEAD AND CAME
TO SPARE YOU ANY EMBARRASSMENT,
BUT PLEASE DON'T PUSH ME
ANY FURTHER, OKAY?
MOVING TO TOKYO
WAS THE FIRST TIME
I EVER DID SOMETHING THAT
YOU AND DAD DIDN'T APPROVE OF.
I'VE GOT MORE THINGS
TO DO WITH MY LIFE
THAN MARRY SOME FARM BOY
AND START PUMPING OUT
GRANDCHILDREN ON COMMAND.
- NOW NOW, LINNA,
ALL YOUR FATHER AND I DID
WAS NOTICE A NICE YOUNG BOY--
- AND SET ME UP.
- EXCUSE ME.
YOUR GUESTS HAVE ARRIVED.
- I'M SORRY WE
KEPT YOU WAITING.
- NOT AT ALL.
- HMM.
- ( chuckles )
- OH?
( sighs )
SO YOUR NAME IS MASAKI?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- I'M SO SORRY ABOUT THIS.
I MEAN, BEING STUCK
WITH SOMEONE LIKE ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE OUR PARENTS
WOULD TRY TO SET US UP
LIKE THIS.
- ( chuckles ) I'M NOT VERY
HAPPY WITH MY PARENTS EITHER.
- I KNOW.  I MEAN,
WHAT DO THEY THINK WE ARE?
- SINGLE.
BUT I MUST SAY, YOU'RE A
LOT NICER THAN I IMAGINED.
MY MOTHER WAS SAYING THAT YOU
WORK FOR A COMPANY IN TOKYO.
- UM, YES.
I JUST STARTED.
- THAT'S GREAT.
I WENT TO COLLEGE THERE.
YOU'RE REALLY LUCKY.
- YEAH.  I GUESS I AM.
- I WAS THERE
RIGHT AFTER THE EARTHQUAKE.
THE PLACE WAS FULL OF BOOMERS
AND CONSTRUCTION EVERYWHERE.
BUT MY FATHER NEEDED HELP
MANAGING HIS BUSINESS,
SO I CAME BACK HOME AS SOON
AS I GRADUATED FROM COLLEGE.
ON THE OTHER HAND, I UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU WENT TO TOKYO
TO GET AWAY FROM YOUR FAMILY,
DIDN'T YOU?
- WELL, KINDA SORTA,
I GUESS.
- WAS IT REALLY
SO BAD HERE?
- BAD?
WELL, YEAH.
IT WAS LIKE TEENAGE HELL.
IN 20 YEARS I NEVER ONCE LIVED
UP TO ANYONE'S EXPECTATIONS.
THE ORIGINAL ROUND PEG
IN A SQUARE HOLE, THAT'S ME.
- I COULDN'T WAIT TO LEAVE.
BUT THE FUNNY THING IS,
NOW THAT I MAY HAVE FOUND
WHAT I WAS LOOKING FOR,
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO NOW.
TO BE HONEST, I'M KIND OF
ENVIOUS OF YOU, MASAKI.
BECAUSE YOU SEEM TO KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
I KEEP WONDERING IF I'M
GOING TO SCREW EVERYTHING UP.
- OR EVEN WORSE,
FIND OUT THAT THE THING
YOU WANTED ISN'T THERE ANYMORE.
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
I GUESS I GOT A LITTLE
TOO PERSONAL THERE.
- UM, YEAH.
CONSIDERING THAT
WE JUST MET.
- IT SEEMS LIKE WE HAVE
A LOT IN COMMON.
MAYBE OUR PARENTS
AREN'T SO DUMB.
- ( sighs )
- HA HA!
YEAH, I'M OUT OF HERE.
COME ON, WEASEL.
- MORNING, NENE.
- MORNING.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
( humming )
( grunts )
GET OUT OF MY WAY.
I'M GOING HOME.
- SORRY.
YOU'RE NOT FINISHED YET.
- YOU WANT TO BET?
- YOU'RE OUR TOP VIDEO EXPERT,
AREN'T YOU?
- YOU KNOW I AM.
- IN WHICH CASE,
WE HAVE A PIECE OF VIDEO
THAT WE'D LIKE YOU
TO TAKE A LOOK AT.
- WHAT'S SO IMPORTANT
THAT I HAVE TO WORK LATE?
- CLANDESTINE VIDEO
OF THE KNIGHT SABERS.
- SOMEBODY SENT IT
IN ANONYMOUSLY
AND WE'D LIKE TO
HAVE IT ANALYZED.
- ( sighs )
OF ALL THE PEOPLE HERE,
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO
KEEP PICKING ON ME?
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- NEVER MIND.
BUT I GUESS I'LL DO IT
BECAUSE I LIKE YOU, LEON PEON.
- HEY, WAIT. DID YOU JUST
CALL ME "LEON THE PEON"?
- I REALLY WANTED
TO GO HOME.
- FUNNY SOUNDS ARE ONE THING,
BUT I DON'T LIKE
THE IMPLICATIONS OF
LEON THE PEON.
- BUT I DON'T HAVE
A CHOICE, DO I?
- ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
- DOWN, BIG FELLA.
SHE'S DOING YOU A FAVOR.
JUST LET IT GO.
- I THOUGHT
"LEON NOODLE" WAS BAD,
BUT THIS IS JUST TOO MUCH.
- I'M LEAVING NOW.
- HEY, WAIT.
I NEED YOUR SUPPORT HERE.
- OH, WOW.
WHOEVER TOOK THIS
IS A GREAT PHOTOGRAPHER.
( chuckles )
OH, AWESOME.
I REALLY AM GETTING GOOD.
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
THIS TAPE IS
A LITTLE TOO GOOD
TO BE THE WORK
OF AN AMATEUR.
WHOEVER IT WAS
WHO TOOK IT
MUST HAVE BEEN
WAITING FOR US.
- ( siren blares )
- Man: MAY I HAVE YOUR
ATTENTION PLEASE.
WE HAVE A CLASS EIGHT SITUATION.
- HUH?
- ALL DISPATCHERS REPORT
TO THE COMMUNICATIONS CENTER.
- ( crowd screaming )
- I CAN'T LEAVE.
I'M ON DUTY.
- Priss:
WHAT'S THE TARGET?
- IT APPEARS TO BE
SOME KIND OF MILITARY BOOMER.
ALL WE KNOW RIGHT NOW
IS THAT IT'S DESTROYING
EVERYTHING IN ITS PATH.
- THEN I GUESS WE'LL BOTH
BE PUTTING IN SOME OVERTIME.
- ( chuckles )
OH, WOW.
IS IT REALLY
LIKE THAT IN TOKYO?
- SURE IT IS.
- AFTER HEARING
A STORY LIKE THAT,
I'M WONDERING IF
I SHOULD HAVE LEFT.
- ( giggles )
- ( phone beeping )
- OH, EXCUSE ME.
- Nene:
LINNA, WHERE ARE YOU?
- WHAT?
HASN'T PRISS TOLD YOU YET?
- Nene:
SHE DIDN'T TELL ME ANYTHING.
LOOK, I'M STUCK ON DUTY
AND WE'VE GOT BIG TROUBLE.
PRISS IS ON HER WAY,
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
SHE CAN HANDLE THIS
ONE BY HERSELF.
- BUT I CAN'T COME.
I...
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS: TOKYO 2040",
THE BOOMER CONTINUES
ITS RAMPAGE,
DESTROYING HUGE
SECTIONS OF THE CITY
AS THE ARMY AND AD POLICE
PROVE UNABLE TO STOP IT.
ALONE AND RUNNING
OUT OF POWER,
PRISS TRIES FRANTICALLY
TO DESTROY THE MONSTER.
NENE RACES AGAINST TIME,
TRYING TO UNLOCK THE SECRET
BEHIND THE BOOMER'S ARMOR,
BUT PRISS HAS ONLY
MINUTES LEFT TO LIVE.
NEXT EPISODE...