- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WELL, IF YOU REALLY
WANT MY OPINION, LEON,
I THINK YOU SHOULD START TAKING
THINGS A LITTLE MORE EASY.
- HEY, HOLD ON.
HEY, NENE.
SOMETHING WRONG, KIDDO?
- HUH?  OH, NO.
I'M JUST FINE, REALLY.
- ARE YOU SURE?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU HAD
A LOT ON YOUR MIND.
- NO, REALLY.  I'M FINE.
IT'S JUST THAT MY BLOOD SUGAR'S
A LITTLE LOW, OKAY?
- I SEE.
- WELL, WE'RE GOING TO LUNCH.
YOU WANT TO COME?
- YOU'LL PROBABLY
SPEND THE WHOLE TIME
ASKING ME ABOUT PRISS,
WON'T YOU?
- ( groans )
- BY THE WAY,
HAVE YOU SEEN HER LATELY?
- NOPE.  NOT THAT
MR. DATELESS HERE
HASN'T BEEN KEEPING
AN EYE OUT FOR HER.
OR LACK OF INTEREST HASN'T
SHOWN UP ON HIS RADAR YET.
( chuckles )
- HEY, WAIT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
SHE'S JUST--
UM, WELL... SHY.
- SHE AND LINNA MUST BE
GOING AT IT 24 HOURS.
- Both: HUH?
- UH...
( chuckles nervously )
NEVER MIND,
I'M JUST BABBLING.
- 24 HOURS A DAY?
WHO'S LINNA?
- READY, SYLIA?
- Sylia:
ROGER, PRISS.  GO AHEAD.
- FIRING PULSE.
- ( beeping )
- NO.  THAT'S NOT
THE ONE, PRISS.
- Priss:
NUTS.  NOT THIS ONE EITHER?
- I'M SORRY.  PLEASE PROCEED
TO THE NEXT POINT.
- Priss:
OKAY, WHATEVER.
- ( sighs )
- Linna:
SYLIA, I'M IN POSITION.
- OKAY, FIRE YOUR EMP PULSE.
- ( beeping )
- Linna:
I'M NOT GETTING ANY RESPONSE.
I'M GOING TO MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT SPOT, OKAY?
- Sylia: ROGER.
ONLY SIX POINTS LEFT.
WHERE ARE YOU?
I KNOW YOU'RE THERE.
- Linna:
SYLIA, ARE YOU THERE?
- I'M SORRY, LINNA.
ARE YOU ALREADY THERE?
- Linna: NO, THIS TUNNEL
COMES TO A DEAD END.
AM I CLOSE ENOUGH
TO TRY FROM HERE?
- IF THE DISTANCE IS
MORE THAN 300 METERS,
I'M AFRAID THE SONAR
CAN'T REACH THAT FAR.
- Linna: I SEE.
IS THERE ANY OTHER WAY IN?
- LET ME TAKE A LOOK.
THERE MIGHT BE ANOTHER
ACCESS TUNNEL NEARBY.
- Priss: I DON'T THINK
YOU'LL NEED TO DO THAT.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- Priss: I THINK WE HAVE
A WINNER HERE.
- Sylia:
THAT'S IT, PRISS.
NOW WITHDRAW AND
RETURN TO BASE.
- HOLD ON. LET ME SEE HOW CLEAR
THE PASSAGEWAY IS FIRST.
- Sylia: UM, OKAY.
- Priss: HMM. LOOKS LIKE THIS
USED TO BE SOME KIND OF ROADWAY.
CORRECTION, FREEWAY.
THERE'S A BUILDING COLLAPSED
ACROSS THE ROAD.
SYLIA, THERE'S A PATHWAY
BENEATH THE BUILDING.
HEADING DOWN.
- Sylia:
PRISS, STOP RIGHT THERE.
- IT LOOKS CLEAR.
- Sylia: NO, PRISS. STOP NOW.
COME BACK NOW, DAMN IT!
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
- ( sighs )
YOU COME HERE OFTEN?
- I WISH I COULD AFFORD
TO COME HERE OFTEN.
- IT'S WORTH IT.
- WELL, SINCE SYLIA'S PAYING.
I'M SURPRISED YOU ACTUALLY
LISTENED TO SYLIA
AND DIDN'T GO IN.
I THINK CURIOSITY WOULD HAVE
GOTTEN THE BETTER OF ME.
- WELL, IF MY BATTERY
HADN'T BEEN DEAD,
I PROBABLY WOULD HAVE.
- IT'S DRIVING YOU CRAZY TOO,
ISN'T IT?
- YEAH, AFTER FIVE DAYS,
TO GET PULLED BACK FROM THE
BRINK LIKE THAT?
- YEAH, BUT I WONDER
HOW DANGEROUS
THAT THING REALLY IS.
- PRETTY DANGEROUS FROM THE WAY
SYLIA REACTED, I'D SAY.
- SHE WAS DESPERATE,
ALL RIGHT,
TO STOP YOU FROM
GOING IN THERE.
- Priss:
BUT I'M ALMOST THERE ALREADY.
- Sylia:
GET BACK HERE NOW, DAMN IT!
- Priss: I JUST WANT
TO CHECK IT OUT.
- I SAID TO COME BACK NOW!
PRISS!
( gasps )
( breathing heavily )
- MY BATTERY'S OUT ANYWAY.
I'M COMING BACK.
- THANK GOD YOU FOUND IT.
AT LAST I'LL BE ABLE
TO DISPOSE OF IT PROPERLY.
- WHAT IS IT WITH THIS
"I" STUFF, SYLIA?
YOU WOULDN'T BE TRYING TO FINISH
THIS ALL BY YOURSELF, WOULD YOU?
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I'M DOING, PRISS.
I CAN HANDLE
THE REST FROM HERE.
- NO WAY.
LINNA AND I ONLY
AGREED TO HELP YOU
IF YOU KEPT US
IN THE LOOP.
- PRISS IS RIGHT, SYLIA.
KEEPING SECRETS
IS WHY WE LOST NENE.
- VERY WELL THEN.
I PROMISE WE'LL
DO THIS AS A TEAM
JUST AS SOON AS
EVERYTHING ELSE IS READY TO GO.
- Both:
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, LADIES.
PLEASE COME BACK
TO VISIT US AGAIN.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WANT TO SIGN UP?
- UM, SURE.
I'VE BEEN GOING TO A PLACE,
BUT THIS IS A LOT NICER.
I'M KIND OF SURPRISED
THAT YOU GOT SO INTO IT THOUGH.
- WHY'S THAT?
- NOW IF THIS HAD BEEN
THE Y.W.C.A.
- HMM.
- UM, PRISS?
HAVE YOU HEARD FROM NENE?
- WE'RE INTO
THE HOME STRETCH NOW.
THE QUESTION IS,
WHERE CAN I GET THE POWER FROM?
ARE THERE ANY
ACTIVE LINES LEFT DOWN THERE?
- ( beeping )
- HERE WE GO.
THIS OLD POWER CONDUIT
JUST MIGHT DO THE TRICK.
IF I CHANNEL THE CURRENT FLOW
THROUGH THIS FACTORY
INTO THE GRID,
IT'S POSSIBLE.
- SYLIA?
SYLIA?
ARE YOU HERE?
SYLIA...
- Henderson:
I'M SORRY, MASTER MACKY.
MISTRESS SYLIA
IS OUT NOW.
- SHE WENT OUT?
DO YOU KNOW WHEN
SHE'LL BE BACK?
- I'M AFRAID
SHE DIDN'T SAY.
LATE, I BELIEVE.
- OH, WHAT'S SHE UP TO?
- EXCUSE ME, SIR?
- SYLIA'S BEEN DISAPPEARING
A LOT RECENTLY.
I MEAN,
EVEN MORE THAN USUAL.
- PERHAPS SHE HAS PERSONAL
BUSINESS TO ATTEND TO.
- ( sighs )
I THINK SHE'S AVOIDING ME.
- THAT'S HER WAY.
- HUH?
- MISTRESS SYLIA
FINDS IT DIFFICULT
TO SHARE HER CONCERNS
WITH PEOPLE SHE CARES ABOUT.
- OH.
- IF SHE'S AVOIDING YOU,
IT'S BECAUSE SHE'S BUSY
WITH SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
THE BEST THING YOU CAN DO
IS ACCEPT HER FEELINGS
AND WAIT UNTIL SHE'S READY
TO EXPLAIN HERSELF TO YOU.
- ( sighs )
THIS CAN'T WAIT.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
I'M SENSING SOMETHING.
IT'S AS IF SOMEONE
IS CALLING ME.
- DR. SHAN TOLD ME
THAT YOU WOULD ALREADY KNOW
HOW TO OPERATE
ONE OF THESE.
- YES.  TELL HIM
I SAID THANK YOU.
- AND REMEMBER,
IF YOU CAN'T RETURN IT,
MAKE SURE IT'S DESTROYED.
- BELIEVE ME,
I SINCERELY HOPE
I'LL HAVE THE CHANCE
TO RETURN IT TO YOU.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- THERE'S SOMETHING HAPPENING.
I'LL SEND YOU
A VIDEO FEED.
- Mason: THAT'S IT.
GET READY TO MOVE.
- YES SIR.
- WHY IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE DAY?
CANCEL MY SCHEDULE
FOR THIS AFTERNOON.
- AS YOU WISH,
MR. MASON.
- I HAVE ONE MORE
LETTER FOR YOU.
( chuckles )
"E."
FOR END OF GAME.
- WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME.
SET UP A SKIRMISH LINE AND BLOCK
THE UNDERGROUND EXPRESS WAY.
I'LL STAY HERE
AND WAIT FOR MR. MASON.
- THIS IS MURAKAMI.
READY TO DETONATE
THE CHARGES, SIR.
- Mason: GO AHEAD.
- BLOW IT!
- ( Nene sighs )
I'M STARVING.
HEY, MEGU.
MEGU!
- HUH?
YOU WANT LUNCH ALREADY?
- WHAT DO YOU FEEL LIKE?
- IT'S NOT LUNCH YET,
YOU KNOW?
IT'S 30 MINUTES TILL
WE CAN TAKE A BREAK.
- BUT I'M HUNGRY NOW.
- ( beeping )
- YOU'LL LIVE.
YOU'VE GOT A CALL
COMING IN.
- THIS IS THE AD POLICE
HOTLINE.
HUH?  YOU'RE SAYING THERE'S
BEEN SOME KIND OF EXPLOSION
IN THE UNDERGROUND
EXPRESSWAY
IN THE OUTSIDE WARD?
- OUTSIDE WARD NEAR THE EXIT,
OF THE SHINO SOBE INBOUND.
IN ADDITION
TO THE EXPLOSION,
THERE'S SOME KIND OF
UNAUTHORIZED ROAD BLOCK.
- ( Dispatchers chattering )
- HEY, WAIT.
WHY ARE THERE ARMORED BOOMERS
GUARDING THOSE TRUCKS?
- ( siren wailing )
- THE SUBJECTS APPEAR TO BE
DIGGING BENEATH
THE FREEWAY.
- ( gasps )
- REPEAT, SUBJECTS ARE DIGGING
BENEATH THE FREEWAY.
- THE LAB WAS BURIED
BY THE EARTHQUAKE.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND IT.
- ( grunts )
- THIS IS CHIEF MYLES.
- HUH?
- ALL UNIT MOBILIZATION
ORDERS ARE CANCELED.
- THE CHIEF.
- NO INTERFERENCE
WILL BE PERMITTED.
WE HAVE RECEIVED WORD
THAT THE INCIDENT...
- ...NOW OCCURRING IN
THE UNDERGROUND EXPRESS WAY
HAS BEEN CLASSIFIED
ON A NEED-TO-KNOW BASIS.
THIS IS AN ORDER FROM
THE TOP BRASS.
- WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON HERE?
- I REPEAT,
ALL DISPATCHED VEHICLES
WILL RETURN TO
THE STATION IMMEDIATELY.
- ( phone beeping )
- HI, YAMAZAKI HERE.
- Nene: LINNA, I THINK SYLIA'S
GONE TO DESTROY THE LAB.
- SHE DID WHAT?!
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT SOMETHING'S GOING ON
AND GENOM'S SENDING TROOPS
DOWN INTO THE TUNNEL SYSTEM.
- HAVE YOU CALLED PRISS?
- SHE'S ON HER WAY.
GO TO THE FRONT DOOR
AND SHE'LL PICK YOU UP.
- ROGER.
I'M ON MY WAY.
- COME ON.
WHY DID YOU WASTE TIME CHANGING?
- BECAUSE WITH THAT
STUPID SKIRT ON,
I'D HAVE TO RIDE SIDE SADDLE,
AND I'VE SEEN YOU DRIVE.
- GOOD POINT.
HANG ON.
- WHERE'S ALL THAT
SMOKE COMING FROM?
YEAH, MAYBE I CAN TAP INTO
THE TRAFFIC CONTROL
CAMERAS FROM HERE.
THAT'S NOT IT.  NO.
AH-HA!  THERE IT IS.
SYLIA.
- SYLIA!
- DID YOU FIND HER?
- NO.
SHE'S DEFINITELY NOT HERE.
I CHECKED AND
THE MOBILE PIT'S MISSING
AS WELL AS HER HARDSUIT.
- SHE MUST HAVE BEEN
PLANNING THIS FROM
THE VERY BEGINNING.
NO WONDER SHE GAVE IN
SO QUICKLY.
- YEAH.  REMIND ME TO
BEAT THE CRAP OUT OF HER
ONCE WE'VE SAVED
HER SORRY ASS.
- I CLAIM SECONDS.
- COME ON, WE'VE GOT TO HURRY.
- THIS WAY, SIR.
- YOU DON'T DO THINGS
HALFWAY, DO YOU?
- NO, SIR.
- YES, THIS IS IT.
I FEEL HER PRESENCE.
SHE'S WAITING.
- AFTER ALL THESE YEARS.
GOD HELP ME.
OKAY, I HAVE POWER.
NOW ALL I NEED IS TIME.
AND A LITTLE LUCK
WOULDN'T HURT.
BUTCHERS.
- OH, MAN.
I DON'T KNOW IF I
SHOULD BE DOING THIS.
( grunts )
- ( panting )
I'M SORRY IT HAD TO
COME TO THIS.
BUT IT'S TIME
TO SAY GOOD-BYE FOREVER.
- Mason: I'M SORRY,
BUT THAT WON'T BE POSSIBLE.
- HUH?
- IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME, SYLIA.
- Sylia: MASON!
- PUT DOWN YOUR WEAPON
AND YOU WON'T BE HARMED.
- YOU KNOW I CAN'T
LET YOU HAVE IT, YOU BASTARD.
- A MICROWAVE CANNON.
YOU'RE GOING TO TRY TO
DESTROY THE CONTENTS
WITHOUT RELEASING
THE SEAL?
( chuckles )
I'M AFRAID THAT WON'T WORK.
GENOM TRIED THE SAME THING
SEVEN YEARS AGO
AND IT DIDN'T EVEN
SLOW HER DOWN.
- MAYBE SO,
BUT SEVEN YEARS AGO
GENOM DIDN'T HAVE
THE SKYHOOK.
- HMM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SHE'S USING THE SKYHOOK'S
ELECTRIC SURGE
AS A POWER SOURCE!
STOP HER!
- SYLIA?
- THE CONTENTS MUST BE
ON THE VERGE OF BECOMING LIQUID.
NOTHING COULD WITHSTAND
THAT KIND OF MICROWAVE BARRAGE.
- BUT YOU'RE TOO LATE.
- HUH?
MACKY!
- MACKY STINGRAY.
SO THE QUEEN HAS SUMMONED
HER DRONES, HAS SHE?
- OH, UH--
- MACKY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS,
SYLIA?
SHE'S AWAKE.
- NO, THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE!
- Nene: SYLIA!
- Linna: MY GOD.
- Priss: SYLIA.
- Nene:
MACKY? MACKY?
- MACKY, NO!
- HUH?
( screaming )
- Soldiers:
GET BACK! LOOK OUT!
( screaming )
- WHAT?  WHAT THE--
- ( gunfire )
- MACKY!  GET BACK.
( screams )
SOMETHING'S GOT ME!
- NENE!
- ( grunts )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MY HARDSUIT'S
NOT RESPONDING LIKE IT SHOULD.
- Sylia: MACKY,
GET AWAY FROM THERE!
COME BACK BEFORE
IT'S TOO LATE.
MACKY, PLEASE!
Sylia: MACKY, NO!
- ( groans )
- UH?
- Mason: NO. COME WITH ME.
- ( sighs )
- ( Nene grunts )
MACKY!
- Linna: I CAN'T MOVE.
- DAMN IT.
NEITHER CAN I.
- NO, NO!
IT'S STARTING.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS: TOKYO 2040,"
WITH MASON IN CONTROL
OF GALATEA,
THE KNIGHT SABERS ARE
FORCED TO ABANDON THEIR ARMOR
AND CLIMB TO THE SURFACE.
AN UNEXPECTED ALLIANCE,
AND A DANGEROUS SHIFT
IN THE BALANCE OF POWER.
ALL ENSUE IN
THE CHAOTIC AFTERMATH.
THE COUNTDOWN TO THE END
OF HUMAN CIVILIZATION
BEGINS AS THE TRUTH COMES OUT
IN A SERIES OF
HORRIFYING REVELATIONS.
NEXT EPISODE...