- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- SECURITY!
SECURITY,
CALL THE AD POLICE NOW.
IT'S A MAD BOOMER!
( gasps )
( screams )
( whimpers )
( screaming )
- ( rock music playing )
- ( elevator dings )
- Linna: THERE YOU ARE.
YOU'RE LATE, PRISS.
- WE SEEM TO HAVE
A FACTORY BOOMER
IN THE 11th DISTRICT THAT IS
IN THE PROCESS OF GOING ROGUE.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THE AD POLICE
HAVE ALREADY RECEIVED
ORDERS TO DISPATCH.
- AND THAT'S NOT
THE WORST OF IT.
APPARENTLY, THE BOOMER IS FUSING
WITH THE OTHER MACHINES
IN THE FACTORY.
- HMM.  LET'S GO.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON IN THERE,
BUT IT'S BAD.
GO AHEAD AND SEND
THE PROBOT IN.
- ROGER.
LAUNCHING PROBOT.
- UH-HUH.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S ALREADY
GETTING OUT OF CONTROL HERE.
- ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT THE BOOMER
OR OUR COLLEAGUES?
LET'S HANG BACK
FOR A MINUTE.
- ( car door opens )
- HMM?
MY MY MY.
SUCH DEDICATION.
- THE AD POLICE LOOK
LIKE THEY'RE GETTING READY
TO START A WAR.
- Linna: PRISS?
ABOUT THIS BOOMER.
HOW BAD IS IT?
- IF IT FUSES WITH ALL
THAT MACHINERY IN THERE,
REALLY BAD.
- COME ON, LINNA.
HURRY UP!
- MMM.
- KNIGHT SABERS,
PREPARE FOR ACTION.
- TELL ME, MASON,
WHY ARE YOU USING
THE AD POLICE FOR THIS?
- THERE ARE MANY OFFICERS
IN THE ADP
WHO HARBOR A CERTAIN
ANIMOSITY
TOWARDS THE KNIGHT SABERS.
THAT MAKES IT EASY FOR US
TO ACCOMPLISH OUR OBJECTIVES
WITHOUT TOO MANY
UNCOMFORTABLE QUESTIONS.
IT WAS A MATTER
OF CONVENIENCE.
- AND WHAT ABOUT THE BOOMER?
HAVE YOU DISCOVERED
HOW TO MAKE THE BOOMER'S CORE
GO ROGUE ON COMMAND?
- NO.
THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE,
SIR.
NOT WITH OUR
CURRENT TECHNOLOGY.
OUR PEOPLE ARE STILL TRYING
TO DECIPHER THE ALGORITHM.
- I SEE.
AND YET YOU ARE ABLE
TO MANUFACTURE
A ROGUE BOOMER INSTANT.
HOW IS THAT?
- IT'S QUITE SIMPLE.
WE REMOVED
THE SERVICE DRONE'S CORE
AND REPLACED IT WITH ONE
FROM A BOOMER
THAT WAS ALREADY
GOING ROGUE.
WITHIN A FEW HOURS,
WE HAD THE DESIRED RESULTS.
- HOW CLEVER.
I WONDER IF OUR
LOVELY IRON LADIES
WILL APPRECIATE YOUR EFFORTS
ON THEIR BEHALF.
- AND ONCE WE HAVE
OBTAINED THE KNIGHT SABERS,
WHAT DO YOU INTEND
TO DO WITH THEM, SIR?
- DINNER, PERHAPS.
I WOULD LIKE TO
HEAR THEIR STORY.
I'M SURE THEY COULD TELL US
MANY INTERESTING THINGS.
- SIR, I'VE LOCATED THE BOOMER.
- WOW, WHAT A MON--
( gasps )
DAMN.  IT JUST ABSORBED
OUR PROBE ROBOT.
YAMAGUCHI,
TAKE YOUR SQUAD IN
AND WASTE THAT THING.
AND DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ANY CIVILIANS
WHO MIGHT GET IN THE WAY.
- Understood.
Have the K-suits standing by.
- SQUAD THREE, MOVE OUT!
- OH, PLEASE. THOSE IDIOTS ARE
GOING TO TRY A FRONTAL ASSAULT.
- Priss: BAD MOVE.
THAT BOOMER'S GOT THE POWER
OF THIS WHOLE FACTORY BEHIND IT.
NENE, CAN YOU ACCESS
THE POWER GRID?
- OF COURSE I CAN.
BUT FIRST, I'VE GOTTA
TAKE CARE OF THOSE
ADP SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS.
TAKE CARE OF THE NEWBIE
FOR ME.
- THE WHAT?
( sighs )
SO SHOULD WE RUSH IT
FROM BEHIND?
- WHAT YOU'LL DO IS
STAY OUT OF MY WAY.
- EXCUSE ME?
I MAY BE THE NEW GIRL,
BUT I DON'T ROLL OVER
FOR ANYONE.
LET'S GO.
- THE KNIGHT SABERS
ARE HERE, SIR.
- IT'S ABOUT TIME.
HUH?
WHAT THE--?
- AH AH AH.
IT'S NOT POLITE
TO SPY ON PEOPLE.
- Mason: SWITCHING TO THE CAMERA
MOUNTED IN THE BOOMER.
- I JUST WANT TO ASK THEM
A QUESTION, MASON.
I WANT TO KNOW WHY THEY
HATE BOOMERS SO MUCH.
WHY CAN'T THEY
LOVE MY BOOMERS?
WE MUST TAKE THESE
KNIGHT SABERS APART
AND FIND OUT
WHAT DRIVES THEM.
I WANT TO SEE WHAT IS
IN THEIR BRAINS.
UNLESS WE CAN TEACH
WOMEN LIKE THESE KNIGHT SABERS
TO LOVE MY BOOMERS,
MY VISION OF
A BOOMER-SUPPORTED PARADISE
CAN NEVER COME TO PASS.
DON'T YOU THINK SO,
MASON?
- I REALLY CAN'T SAY,
SIR.
BOOMERS AND HUMANS
MAY BE INCOMPATIBLE.
- AH, I SEE.
YOU REALLY DON'T LIKE BOOMERS,
DO YOU, MASON?
- YOU MAY REST ASSURED
THAT WE SHARE THE SAME GOALS.
YOU'LL EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
- YES, LADIES.
YOU WILL COME TO LOVE
AND ACCEPT MY BOOMERS,
JUST AS THE MASTERS
OF THIS CITY DID.
YES.
WHEN THIS CITY COLLAPSED
INTO RUIN AND RUBBLE,
IT WAS MY BOOMERS WHO
BROUGHT IT BACK TO LIFE.
I GAVE THEM MY WORD,
AND MY BOOMERS
MADE IT SO.
FOR THIS THEY
DESERVE RESPECT.
- ( moans )
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THE CHAIRMAN ASKED ME?
HE ASKED IF
I HATED BOOMERS.
- BUT YOU DO, SIR.
YOU DO HATE BOOMERS.
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
- I DON'T HATE BOOMERS.
- ( sighs )
- NOT ALL OF THEM,
ANYWAY.
AS YOU KNOW.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
I CONTINUE TO CATER
TO THAT SENILE OLD ZOMBIE'S
EVERY WHIM.
AS YOU KNOW,
I HAVE VERY SPECIAL
REQUIREMENTS.
AND FOR THOSE NEEDS...
I NEED A VERY SPECIAL BOOMER.
- ( sighs )
- PATTERNS.
THERE MUST BE A PATTERN.
- Reporter: THE DAMAGE CAUSED BY
THE EARTHQUAKE IS INDESCRIBABLE.
TOKYO'S PRESTIGIOUS
BIOSCAPE LABORATORIES
IS IN UNRECOGNIZABLE RUIN.
- Henderson:
MISTRESS SYLIA?
I'VE JUST RECEIVED A CALL
FROM BIOSCAPE HEADQUARTERS.
YOUR FATHER HAS BEEN MISSING
SINCE THE EARTHQUAKE.
I'M AFRAID THAT
THE AUTHORITIES
BELIEVE THAT
HE MUST BE DEAD.
I'M SO SORRY.
- IS IT SO BAD
THAT HE'S DEAD?
- ( gasps )
MISTRESS SYLIA.
- I THINK MY MOTHER
MAY HAVE CALLED HIM.
- I DON'T CARE IF YOU HAVE TO
RUN A CABLE OUT TO THEM.
I WANT COMMUNICATIONS BETWEEN US
AND THE ASSAULT TEAM RESTORED.
SO DO IT!
I KNEW THIS PLAN
WAS DOOMED FROM THE GET-GO.
HUH?
OH, LEON.  I THOUGHT
YOU WERE OFF TODAY.
- GOING A LITTLE OVERBOARD,
AREN'T YOU?
- NOT AT ALL.
THE PUBLIC NEEDS TO TRUST
THE AD POLICE,
AND THIS BROADCAST
WILL PROVE THEY ARE PERFORMING
A NECESSARY FUNCTION.
WHERE'S THAT CAMERA,
DAMN IT?!
- It's almost ready, sir.
- WAIT A SECOND.
THIS IS ALL A PUBLICITY STUNT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT THE WHOLE THING
SMELLS REALLY FUNNY TO ME.
IT'S NOT LIKE OUR TOP BRASS.
WHY WOULD THEY WANT TO
STAGE A BIG SHOW LIKE THIS?
WE'RE TOO FAR AWAY
TO RISK EVERYTHING NOW.
- TOO FAR AWAY FROM WHAT,
DALEY?
- ( explosion )
- Both: HUH?
- AAH!
( screams )
( screaming )
- ( screams )
- SEND IN THE K-SUITS.
OUR FIREARMS AREN'T EVEN
SCRATCHING THE DARN THING.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY'RE
GONNA TRY
THOSE OUTDATED PIECES
OF JUNK AGAIN.
SOME PEOPLE JUST
WANT TO DIE.
- TO DIE?
NENE, HAVEN'T YOU
FINISHED YET?
- I'VE BEEN BUSY.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS SO SIMPLE THAT
EVEN YOU COULD HAVE DONE IT.
GIVE ME A SECOND.
I'LL HAVE IT DOWN
AS SOON AS I CAN.
- WELL, HURRY UP.
SYLIA, I'M GOING IN NOW.
Priss: Sylia?
- ( gasps )
PRISS,
STATUS REPORT.
- The ADP are pulling out
their assault team
and moving their K-suits in.
- OKAY.
LET'S HIT IT HARD AND FAST.
- ( roars )
- ( grunts )
- ( screaming )
- THIS IS A TOTAL FIASCO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THE KNIGHT
SABERS HAVEN'T SHOWN UP YET.
- ( screams, grunts )
( gasps )
- ( roars )
- THE K-SUITS.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
- GET OUT OF THE WAY, SIR.
LET US FINISH IT OFF.
- AND HERE COME THE CLOWNS.
OH, NENE?
HAVEN'T YOU FINISHED YET?
- OH, CHILL OUT.
I HAVEN'T DONE THIS
IN AWHILE, YOU KNOW.
- Priss: Yeah, whatever.
Just stop screwing around
and do it.
- I'M NOT SCREWING AROUND.
YOU'RE THE EXPERT ON THAT.
- YEAH, WE GOT IT!
- YOU IDIOT.
IT'S NOT DEAD YET.
- ( gasps )
- GET OUT OF THERE NOW!
THAT THING'S TRYING TO
ASSIMILATE YOUR K-SUIT.
- ( screaming )
- TA-DA!  I'M DONE.
ARE YOU READY, PRISS?
- Priss:
I've been ready, lard butt.
- ( sighs )
HERE WE GO.
BOMBS AWAY.
SWITCH ON.
- Priss:
HUH. IT WORKED.
- Linna:
WHAT DID SHE DO?
WHY DID IT SHRINK?
- LET'S GO.
- ( gasps )
- I KNEW THEY'D SHOW UP.
- YES.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR YOU LADIES.
- Priss: NENE REVERSED
THE PHASE OF THE CURRENT FLOW.
THAT'S WHY IT
STOPPED GROWING.
COME ON,
WE GOT A BOOMER TO KILL.
- ( gasps, screams )
- LINNA!  DAMN.
( grunts )
- PRISS, WE'VE GOT TO HURRY!
THAT THING WILL BLOW UP
ONCE ITS POWER CELLS ACTIVATE.
( grunts )
- Priss: NENE.
- NOT TOO SHABBY, HUH?
WHY SHOULD YOU HARD BODY
TYPES HAVE ALL THE FUN?
- NENE, STOP BRAGGING
AND SMASH ITS CORE.
- Nene:
I know the drill, Sylia.
- Sylia:
GOD, WHAT A MONSTER.
- MAMA, WHAT IS PAPA MAKING?
- IT'S...
A BIO-ORGANIC CONSTRUCT.
- WHAT'S BIO-ORGANIC?
- A MACHINE THAT'S ALIVE.
SOMETHING THAT CAN TAKE
THE PLACE OF HUMAN BEINGS.
- REALLY?  PAPA'S GREAT,
ISN'T HE, MAMA?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I WONDER...
WHAT HE'S DOING IS
AGAINST THE WILL OF GOD.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S YOUR FATHER,
EVEN THOUGH I LOVE HIM,
CAN I FORGIVE HIM FOR THAT?
AND WILL YOU BE ABLE
TO FORGIVE HIM, SYLIA?
- MAMA?
( giggles )
- PAPA.
- ( Nene screams )
- ( gasps )
- ( whimpers )
- LINNA.
- THOSE POWERED SUITS...
SUCH PERFECTION.
- ( roars )
- OKAY.
HERE GOES NOTHING.
( shouts )
- I'M SORRY, BUT YOU'LL
HAVE TO LEAVE IMMEDIATELY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ARE WE JUST SUPPOSED TO
LEAVE LIKE NOTHING'S HAPPENED?
WHY DOESN'T HE WANT TO
SEE HIS WIFE AND CHILD?
ARE HIS EXPERIMENTS MORE
IMPORTANT TO HIM
THAN HIS FAMILY?
WHAT KIND OF MAN
HAS HE BECOME?
- I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT YOU WOULD UNDERSTAND.
NO MATTER WHAT WE DO,
THE REJECTION SYMPTOMS
ALWAYS OCCUR.
EVERY SINGLE EXPERIMENT
HAS ENDED IN FAILURE.
- Sylia's Mother:
OF COURSE IT DOES!
IT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE
DOING SOMETHING
WHICH GOES AGAINST
THE WILL OF GOD!
COME HERE, SYLIA.
- Young Sylia: AAH!
- YOUR FATHER'S SAYING
HE DOESN'T NEED YOU ANYMORE.
- THE DOCTOR NEVER SAID
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
- Sylia's Mother:
LET'S GO, SYLIA!
- PAPA!
( crying )
- Sylia: PAPA...
WHY DID YOU
LEAVE IT TO ME?
- ( crying )
MAMA IS-- MAMA.
- YOUR MOTHER WAS SICK.
AND SHE HASN'T BEEN
THE PERSON SHE WAS
FOR A LONG TIME.
BUT THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE GOOD CARE OF YOU
FROM NOW ON.
- PAPA.
- DON'T WORRY.
HAVE FAITH IN ME.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
BUT FIRST,
I'M GOING TO NEED YOUR HELP.
- WHAT?
- I NEED YOU TO HELP ME
WITH MY RESEARCH.
- DOING WHAT?
- YOU DON'T NEED
TO DO ANYTHING.
YOU JUST NEED TO
GO TO SLEEP FOR
A LITTLE BIT,
THAT'S ALL.
YOU TRUST YOUR FATHER,
DON'T YOU, SYLIA?
AND YOU KNOW HOW IMPORTANT
MY RESEARCH IS TO ME, RIGHT?
SO YOU WILL HELP ME,
WON'T YOU?
- MM-HMM.
- THAT'S GOOD.
AT LAST I CAN GIVE
LIFE TO MY BOOMER.
- ( grunts )
( screams )
( grunts )
- CLOSE CALL.
- THANKS, NENE.
- WE DON'T HAVE
MUCH TIME LEFT.
CHECK YOUR BATTERY.
- HUH?  OH NO.
- LINNA!
NENE AND I WILL TRY
TO HOLD THE BOOMER.
YOU GO IN AND SMASH ITS CORE.
- OKAY, PRISS.
I'M ON IT.
- LET'S DO IT!
- ( gasps )
- SMASH THE CORE, LINNA!
MM.
( shouts )
( breathing heavily )
I DID IT.
- Nene: LINNA, COME ON!
- NO TIME TO GLOAT.
WE'VE GOT TO GO.
- WAIT!  WHAT THE HELL?
ARE YOU TRYING
TO KILL THEM?
ARE YOU INSANE?
- DON'T HIT THEM.
THIS IS JUST A THREAT.
BUT DON'T LET THEM
GET AWAY EITHER.
- NOW THIS ALL MAKES SENSE.
THIS WASN'T ABOUT
THE BOOMER AT ALL.
- YEAH, I GET IT NOW.
- WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
WHY ARE THEY
SHOOTING AT US?
( screams )
- SYLIA!
- ( screams )
- Nene: LINNA!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040,"
THE AD POLICE HAVE
THE KNIGHT SABERS CORNERED,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE PRISS,
LINNA, AND NENE MAY BE TRAPPED.
WITH THEIR BATTERIES DRAINED
AND THEIR WEAPONS EXHAUSTED,
THERE'S ONLY ONE HOPE LEFT.
BUT WILL IT
ARRIVE IN TIME?
WAR ERUPTS ACROSS TOKYO
AS THE ADP FINALLY DECIDE
TO ELIMINATE THE KNIGHT SABERS
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
NEXT EPISODE...