- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Leon:
PRISS, WHAT'S WRONG?
DO YOU NEED A DOCTOR?
- ( crying )
PRISS?
PRISS!
- PRISS!
DID YOU SEE IT TOO?
- YEAH, COME ON.
WE'VE GOT TO GO SEE SYLIA.
( sighs )
- HUH?
- SYLIA!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
- HENDERSON SAYS THAT SHE
JUST COLLAPSED.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
AND HER PULSE AND TEMPERATURE
ARE BOTH DROPPING RAPIDLY.
I'VE ALREADY SENT
FOR THE DOCTOR.
- PRISS, LOOK.
- HUH?
WHAT IN THE HELL?
- ( moaning )
- THE SOTAI.
- Man: THE LEVEL OF
THE SOTAI PHENOMENON
SUDDENLY STARTED TO INCREASE
A FEW MINUTES AGO, SIR.
THE WALLS OF THE ENCLOSURE
ARE 500 TIMES AS STRONG
AS THE ONES IN
THE OLD WIZ LAB STRUCTURE.
HOWEVER--
- JUST RAISE THE ELEVATOR.
- OUR LITTLE GALATEA
IS JUST GETTING LONELY.
- ALRIGHT SIR, THE ELEVATOR
IS CLEAR. YOU MAY PROCEED NOW.
-  ( door opens )
- Mason:
WHAT'S WRONG, GALATEA?
YOU'VE BEEN TRYING TO CALL
YOUR FRIENDS, HAVEN'T YOU?
I'M AFRAID THAT
IT'S MUCH TOO EARLY FOR THAT.
- IT IS, EARLY?
- MM, YOU'RE STILL TOO YOUNG.
YOU'RE A VERY CLEVER GIRL
MY DEAR, SWEET GALATEA.
MORE SO EACH DAY,
BUT I WON'T MAKE THE SAME
MISTAKE AS DR. STINGRAY
AND ALLOW YOU TO USE
YOUR POWERS PREMATURELY.
- I WANT TO PLAY.
- WELL, IF YOU WANT TO PLAY
THEN WE'LL JUST HAVE TO FIND YOU
SOMETHING TO PLAY WITH.
WON'T WE THEN?
- ( giggling )
- SYLIA?
- SHE'S CALMING DOWN NOW.
- JUST WHO DO YOU MEAN BY "SHE?"
- THE SOTAI.
THE OTHER PROTOTYPE THAT WAS
CREATED AT THE SAME TIME
AS I WAS.
- SHE'S CONFINED SOMEPLACE
AND LOOKING FOR A WAY OUT.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
HOW IS SHE CONNECTED TO SYLIA?
- IT'S AN ARTIFICIAL LIFE FORM.
SYLIA'S FATHER USED HER
LIKE A LABORATORY RAT
AND GREW IT INSIDE HER BRAIN.
- INSIDE HER BRAIN?
- MACKY:
YES.
AND THAT'S WHERE I
WAS GROWN AS WELL.
- IN ANY CASE,
THAT'S THE LINK.
- ( sighs )
- HEY, HER EYELIDS MOVED.
- ( groaning )
- WAIT SYLIA,
DON'T TRY TO MOVE.
MR. HENDERSON,
SHE'S AWAKE!
- Sylia:
THANK YOU, HENDERSON.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT
THE DOCTOR TO EXAMINE YOU,
MISTRESS SYLIA?
- NO, HOW COULD I EXPLAIN
THAT SOMEONE'S BEEN YELLING
INSIDE MY HEAD?
AND I DO FEEL BETTER.
- I'M SO GLAD,
WE ALL THOUGHT--
- I'M SORRY TO HAVE WORRIED
YOU ALL LIKE THAT, REALLY.
ESPECIALLY SINCE
YOU ALL SEEMED TO HAVE
EXPERIENCED MY MEMORIES.
- YES, WE ALL SAW IT
SO VIVIDLY.
HOW COULD THAT HAPPEN?
IT WAS--
- IT WAS LIKE WE WERE
DREAMING WIDE AWAKE,
BUT WITH YOUR DREAMS.
- YES.
- DO THOSE DREAMS MEAN
THAT WE'RE ALL CONNECTED
TOGETHER PSYCHICALLY SOMEHOW?
I MEAN, IT CAN'T BE
A COINCIDENCE,
SO IT MUST HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH BEING KNIGHT SABERS, RIGHT?
- NO, IT'S NOT A COINCIDENCE.
PERHAPS IT WAS INEVITABLE.
I KNOW THAT PRISS HAS
SUSPECTED THIS FOR SOME TIME.
BUT I THINK YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT YOU'RE NOT THE FIRST
KNIGHT SABERS.
I FORMED A TEAM
BEFORE YOU.
AT THE TIME, I WAS YOUNG
AND ALMOST AS
HOT-HEADED AS PRISS.
I LED THAT TEAM
INTO BATTLE PERSONALLY.
I HAD RECRUITED THAT TEAM
IN MUCH THE SAME WAY
AS I DID YOU.
THERE WAS A MARTIAL ARTIST.
BUT SHE WAS NEVER ABLE
TO COMPLETELY MASTER
HER HARDSUIT
LIKE YOU HAVE, LINNA.
ANOTHER RECRUIT
WAS AN AMERICAN,
A FORMER
SPECIAL FORCES OPERATIVE
WHO HAD BEEN ATTACHED
TO THE PENTAGON'S DELTA FORCE.
BUT ALL OF THEIR SKILLS
AND ABILITIES
MEANT NOTHING IN THE END.
EVEN WITH MY HARDSUITS,
THEY WERE JUST ORDINARY WOMEN
WITH FANCY COMBAT ARMOR.
THEY FOUGHT BRAVELY,
BUT IT WASN'T ENOUGH.
ONLY I WAS ACTUALLY
ABLE TO ACHIEVE A TRUE GESTALT.
WHAT I REALIZED TOO LATE
IS THAT A HARDSUIT REQUIRES MORE
THAN JUST A BODY TO FILL IT.
IT REQUIRES A COMPATIBLE MIND
AS WELL.
- THE SUITS ARE BOOMERS,
AREN'T THEY?
- SO THE SUITS ALLOW
A HUMAN'S BRAIN AND REFLEXES
TO CONTROL A BOOMER'S STRENGTH
AND AGILITY.
BUT THEN THAT MEANS
THAT WE...
- YES, AND I SHOULD
HAVE TOLD YOU ALL
WHAT YOU WERE GETTING INTO.
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
I'M TRULY SORRY ABOUT THAT.
BUT I TOOK CARE TO USE ONLY
CORES THAT I BELIEVED TO BE SAFE
FROM THE DANGER OF GOING ROGUE.
THAT'S ALSO THE REASON I LIMITED
THE HARDSUITS POWER SUPPLY.
- Linna:
ONE QUESTION,
IS THERE A REASON YOU
ONLY RECRUITED FEMALES?
- WELL, I'M A FEMALE.
SO I DESIGNED THE FIRST SUIT
TO FIT A FEMALE'S CENTER
OF BALANCE AND ANATOMY.
ONCE I'D SOLVED THOSE PROBLEMS,
IT WAS SIMPLY A MATTER
OF EXPEDIENCE
TO RECRUIT WOMEN WHO HAD
PHYSIQUES AND ABILITIES
THAT WERE SIMILAR TO MINE.
- HOLD ON, NEITHER NENE
NOR I ARE BUILT LIKE--
- THAT'S RIGHT.
ALTHOUGH THE DIFFERENCES ARE
REALLY VERY MINOR.
WHAT I LEARNED WAS THAT I
NEEDED MORE THAN JUST A BODY.
- UHH...
- WHAT I NEED, NENE DEAR,
IS SOMEONE WITH WHOM I SHARE
A VERY SPECIAL PHYSICAL
COMPATIBILITY.
- OH, WAIT NOW A SECOND!
JUST WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I MEAN, I LIKE-- I LIKE YOU
AND ALL THAT, BUT I'M--
I'M NOT CURIOUS THAT WAY.
AT LEAST NOT THE WAY
THAT I THINK YOU
AND MAYBE LINNA ARE,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- OH, THANKS A LOT.
- LET ME TRY TO EXPLAIN--
THE SUITS RESPOND
TO YOUR MOTOR REFLEXES,
BUT THEY ALSO TAP
INTO YOUR SYNAPSES
TO ANTICIPATE YOUR ACTIONS.
BUT FOR THAT PROCESS TO OCCUR,
YOUR BRAIN HAS TO
SUBCONSCIOUSLY ALLOW THE SUIT
TO ENTER YOUR MIND.
- Sylia: YES, THAT'S
WHAT I MEANT
BY BEING PHYSICALLY COMPATIBLE.
IN A VERY REAL SENSE, THE SUITS
ARE AN EXTENSION OF ME.
OR AT LEAST THE ME THAT WAS
WHEN THE SUITS WERE MADE.
- Nene: OH YEAH, I KNEW
THAT'S WHAT YOU MEANT.
- Priss: HOW CAN YOU SIT THERE
AND PRETEND THAT ANY OF US
MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU?
I USED TO THINK YOUR MONEY
WAS WORTH PUTTING UP
WITH YOUR GAMES,
BUT YOU KNEW HOW I FELT
ABOUT BOOMERS
AND YOU STILL LIED TO ME,
YOU BITCH.
- I KNOW YOU HAVE EXTREME
FEELINGS ABOUT BOOMERS, PRISS.
BUT I THOUGHT THAT ONCE YOU
UNDERSTOOD WHAT MY GOALS WERE--
- SPARE ME YOUR
GODDAMNED EXPLANATIONS!
- I'M OUT OF HERE.
BYE, LINNA.
- Linna:
DAMN IT, PRISS.  WAIT!
- MACKY, WILL YOU PLEASE CALL
NIGEL FOR ME?
TELL HIM THAT WE'RE GOING TO BE
NEEDING THREE NEW HARDSUITS.
- RIGHT.
- UM, BUT, ARE THEY BOOMERS?
- YES, AND IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT
YOU CAN QUIT!
I'LL DO IT ALL BY MYSELF
IF I HAVE TO.
I'LL DESTROY THAT DAMN THING
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO!
- ( both sigh )
- Daley: WELL HEY THERE, TIGER.
I'VE BEEN HEARING ALL ABOUT YOU.
- HUH?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- OH, I THINK YOU CAN SPARE ME
THE PROTESTS OF IGNORANCE,
LOVER BOY.
TRAFFIC'S ALREADY SPREADING
THE STORY ON YOU
AND THE LADY SINGER.
- THERE'S NOTHING
TO TELL, DALEY.
- I THINK YOU'RE FIBBING.
DON'T YOU KNOW
THAT THOSE FIREBEES
HAVE A CAMERA ON CONTINUOUS
RECORD, PINOCCHIO?
HEY WAIT,
WAIT JUST A SECOND,
YOU MUST BE REALLY SERIOUS
ABOUT THIS ONE
IF YOU HAVEN'T BRAGGED ABOUT IT
TO THE WHOLE DEPARTMENT YET.
- IS THIS THE ONLY THING
YOU WANTED TO TALK TO ME ABOUT?
- NO, I THOUGHT YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT THERE'S A MEETING
GOING ON RIGHT NOW.
ALL THE HEADS, ABOUT THE
CONTINUED FUTURE
OF THE A.D. POLICE.
- HUH?
- YEAH, THE RUMOR MILL HAS IT
THAT WE'RE GETTING READY
TO BE RIFFED BACK INTO
THE NORMAL POLICE DEPARTMENT
AT THE END OF THE MONTH.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
- UNFORTUNATELY OUR UNDERWRITER
SEEMS TO HAVE PULLED OUT ON US.
- BY THAT YOU MEAN GENOM?
- RIGHT.
APPARENTLY GENOM DOESN'T THINK
KEEPING ROGUE BOOMERS IN CHECK
IS A WORTHWHILE EXPENSE
ANYMORE.
- ARE THEY OUT OF THEIR MINDS?
THIS CITY NEEDS US.
- YOU AND I KNOW THAT,
BUT TO GENOM WE'RE JUST
A WASTE DISPOSAL SERVICE.
- ( shouting and gunshots )
- Leon:
GENOM!
- Dr. Rosenkreutz: MASON,
YOU'VE BEEN HIDING SOMETHING
FROM ME, HAVEN'T YOU?
- JUST WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT, SIR?
- UNDERESTIMATING ME
WOULD BE A FATAL ERROR.
I SUGGEST YOU TELL ME
THE TRUTH.
IT HAS COME TO MY ATTENTION THAT
YOU HAVE BROUGHT INTO MY TOWER
SOMETHING THAT MAY BE
DANGEROUS.
- I'M NOT SURE
AS TO WHAT YOU MAY MEAN
BY POTENTIALLY DANGEROUS,
MR. CHAIRMAN.
WHILE WE ARE CURRENTLY
DEVELOPING A SYSTEM
TO TRANSFER ENERGY
TO THE UMBRELLA,
I DON'T REALLY ANTICIPATE
ANY POTENTIAL PROBLEMS
WITH ENERGY OVERFLOW.
IS THAT ALL?
- HM... MASON?
YES, WAS THERE
SOMETHING ELSE, CHAIRMAN?
- Dr. Rosenkreutz:
YOU WON'T BETRAY ME.
- NO.
- ( electric guitar )
- ( yawns )
- ( beeping )
- Nene:
A MESSAGE.
OH, GREAT.  WELL, I GUESS I CAN
ANSWER HIM THIS TIME.
- Macky:
HI, HOW'S IT GOING, NENE?
- THAT'S MS. NENE.
- Macky: OH, WHATEVER.
LOOK, CAN YOU COME
TO THE SHOP AFTER WORK TODAY?
- HUH?
- Macky: SYLIA'S TALKED NIGEL
INTO MAKING HER A NEW SUIT.
THE THING IS, THE CORES
WERE DESIGNED AROUND
HER ADOLESCENT BRAIN SCAN.
HER BODY'S MATURED TOO MUCH.
BUT IF YOU COME IN,
I CAN CONVINCE THEM TO MAKE
THE NEW SUIT FOR YOU.
- WAS ALL OF THAT JUST A
ROUNDABOUT WAY
OF CALLING ME IMMATURE?
- Macky: NO, I KNOW HOW YOU
FEEL ABOUT THE SUITS NOW.
BUT I CAN'T LET SYLIA DO
THIS TO HERSELF.
I'D FEEL BETTER IF THERE
WAS SOMEONE TO WATCH HER BACK.
SHE'S MY SISTER NENE,
I CAN'T LET HER KILL HERSELF.
PLEASE, HELP ME.
- YOU REALLY ARE HER BROTHER.
- HEY NENE, WHAT ARE YOU
STILL DOING ON DUTY?
- I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T HAVE
A LIFE, I GUESS.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
DON'T YOU KNOW THAT EVERYBODY
ELSE IN THIS ENTIRE SECTION
IS TAKING SICK LEAVE
THIS AFTERNOON?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- IT'S A STRIKE.
WE'RE PROTESTING THE FACT
THAT THE A.D. POLICE
IS GOING TO BE MERGED
INTO THE NORMAL POLICE.
YOU ARE IN THE UNION,
AREN'T YOU?
- WELL, NO.  NEVER PAID
MUCH ATTENTION TO IT.
WELL, THE REGULAR POLICE
IS ALL UNION.
IF THE MERGER HAPPENS
YOU'LL HAVE NO CHOICE.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
THE REST OF THE AFTERNOON OFF?
GO SEE YOUR BOYFRIEND,
OR SOMETHING.
- AND WHAT IF I DON'T HAVE
A BOYFRIEND?
( groans )
WHAT SHOULD I DO NOW?
DO I REALLY WANT
A NEW HARDSUIT?
- I THOUGHT YOU
WERE IN THE UNION.
YOU KNOW THEY'RE FINING
MEMBERS WHO SHOW UP
FOR WORK THIS AFTERNOON.
- I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT,
I'VE GOT A JOB TO DO, NICK.
AND IF HALF OF WHAT
I'VE HEARD IS TRUE,
THE A.D.P. IS GOING TO BE
DISSOLVED ANYWAY.
- THAT'S JUST A RUMOR
THAT'S GOING AROUND.
- Leon:
IS IT JUST A RUMOR?
- WELL, SOME RUMORS DO HAVE
A GRAIN OF TRUTH AT THEIR CORE,
AND THIS MIGHT BE ONE OF THEM.
- HUH?
I SEE.
- BUT I DIDN'T TELL YOU THAT.
- YEAH, AND IF I GOT
THAT IMPRESSION,
IT WAS JUST IN MY MIND, RIGHT?
- Roland:
YOU'RE A GOOD COP, LEON.
YOU'VE GOT AN
OUTSTANDING TRACK RECORD.
THE NORMAL POLICE WOULD BE
GLAD TO HAVE YOU.
- I WAS IN
THE NORMAL POLICE, NICK.
I'M NOT GOING BACK THERE.
- SOME PEOPLE ARE BORN
TO BE COPS.
THEY WON'T EVER BE HAPPY
DOING ANYTHING ELSE.
- OH YEAH?
PROVE IT.
- ( laughs )
- YEAH, BUT YOU'RE OLD.
- I WAS YOUNG TOO, ONCE.
- Nene: "SO WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO, NENE?"
HM, WELL YOU'RE THE WEASEL--
WHAT WOULD YOU SUGGEST?
"I THINK YOU'RE SCREWED."
OH, THERE MUST BE
A WAY OUT OF THIS.
"SOMETIMES, YOU JUST HAVE
TO DECIDE WHAT'S IMPORTANT."
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND WE BOTH KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
( sighs ) I WONDER IF LINNA'S
GONE BACK TO SEE SYLIA.
I KNOW PRISS WOULDN'T,
BUT...
- ( alarm )
- WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
THE WHOLE SWITCHBOARD'S
BEEN CUT OFF!
- ( alarm )
- AHH!
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
- ( running )
- ( gasps )
NO WAY!
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
OW-WW!
OUCH-HH.
THIS ISN'T HAPPENING, AM I THE
ONLY ONE LEFT IN THE BUILDING?
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
- ( footsteps )
- AH-HH!
- HEY, KID!
- MR. ROLAND?
- YOU'RE AN OPERATOR IN THE
INFORMATION CENTER, AREN'T YOU?
WHAT'S GOING ON OUT THERE?!
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT CAUSED IT,
BUT ALL OF OUR DEFENSE SYSTEMS
CAME ONLINE,
AND THEN THE PHONE SYSTEMS
CUT OFF.
- IT JUST CUT OFF?
I KNEW THAT BACKUP SYSTEM WAS
A PIECE OF JUNK!
BACK OFF YANNO,
IT'S PROBABLY RESTORING
ITSELF EVEN AS WE SPEAK.
- WHETHER IT CAN FIX ITSELF OR
NOT IS BESIDE THE POINT, HARUMA.
WE STILL NEED TO CHECK IT OUT!
- ( rumbling )
- THAT WASN'T
A SOFTWARE FAILURE.
- HOLD ON A SECOND.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I CAN CHECK OUT EVERY
LEVEL THROUGH MY STATION!
OKAY, LET'S TRY...
THE BASEMENT FIRST.
HUH?
WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?!
( screaming )
OH MY GOD, BOOMERS!
- ( rock music playing )
- ( explosions )
- WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
- HOW IN THE HELL DID
ALL THESE BOOMERS GET DOWN HERE?
- STORAGE. THOSE ARE ALL
ROGUE BOOMERS
THAT WERE BEING KEPT IN
THE EVIDENCE ROOM.
- BUT WHAT DO YOU THINK
MADE THEM COME BACK TO LIFE?
- I DON'T KNOW,
I'M MORE INTERESTED IN
KILLING THEM AGAIN!
- Man:
IT'S AT JUNCTION K-24.
R-34.
Y-133 HAS BEEN SEALED.
THE CONTAMINATION IS TRAVELING
THROUGH THE DRAGON LINE
IN EXACTLY THE PATTERN
YOU PREDICTED, SIR.
- IT'S NOT CONTAMINATION,
THE SOTAI PHENOMENON
SIMPLY ALLOWS THE BOOMERS
TO PROGRESS TO THE NEXT STAGE
OF THEIR EVOLUTION.
- ( giggling )
I THINK SHE'S HAD
ENOUGH PLAY TIME NOW.
- Man: THE INNER WALLS
HAVE BEEN CONTAMINATED,
BUT THE EXTERIORS
REMAIN UNTOUCHED.
- Mason: WELL, WELL,
CHAIRMAN ROSENKREUTZ.
DID YOU EVER ENVISION THAT
YOUR PRECIOUS DRAGON LINE
COULD BE USED THIS WAY?
HAH, I THINK NOT.
SO, IS IT HAPPENING?
- Man: AS PREDICTED, THE
BOOMERS WHICH WERE STORED
IN THE UNDERGROUND WAREHOUSE
ARE REVIVING.
- ( laughing )
IT'S TOO BAD THERE'S NOBODY
LEFT IN THE TOTEM POLE
TO BEHOLD OUR HANDIWORK.
THE A.D.P. STRIKE
WAS CONVENIENT,
BUT I WOULD HAVE LOVED TO SEE
HOW PATHETIC THEIR EFFORTS
TO STOP THIS WOULD HAVE BEEN.
- ( falls down )
- Nigel:
WHAT'S WRONG, SYLIA?
- IT'S HER, AS IF SHE'S INSIDE
MY BRAIN, SCREAMING TO GET OUT.
- SYLIA...
- ( elevator opens )
- HUH?
LOOKS LIKE THE FREQUENCY
IS INCREASING.
- Macky: BOOMERS WERE NOT
TO BE SLAVES TO HUMANS.
- Nigel:
IT'S YOU!
- YES, I AM THE SOTAI.
I AM THE ONE
THAT STINGRAY NAMED GALATEA.
- DAMN IT, YOU'RE NOT
A BOOMER, MACKY!
YOU'VE GOT TO FIGHT HER!
- BUT I--
I AM NOT HUMAN, EITHER.
- YOU ARE TO NENE.
- NENE...
NENE'S IN DANGER!
- Yano: ROLAND, THESE GUNS
AREN'T EVEN SLOWING THEM DOWN!
- Roland: PULL BACK,
I'LL USE A DELAYED CHARGE.
RUN-NN!
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
ROMANOVA, ARE YOU THERE?
TRY THE EMERGENCY BEACON,
AND SEE IF YOU CAN GET
A MESSAGE TO THE NORMAL POLICE.
- I'M TRYING SIR,
BUT ALL OF THE OUTSIDE CIRCUITS
HAVE BEEN CUT OFF.
EVEN THE RADIO
AND SATELLITE LINKS ARE DEAD.
- SHE'S RIGHT, THE SECURITY
SYSTEM IS PROGRAMMED
TO DROP A COMPLETE FIREWALL
ON ALL COMMUNICATIONS
IN CASE THERE'S EVER A HOSTILE
TAKEOVER OF THE BUILDING.
- Yano:
LOOK OUT!
THEY'RE COMING IN
THE BACK WAY, TOO.
- THAT FIREWALL WON'T
HOLD UP MUCH LONGER.
THIS WAY, HURRY!
- SIR, THE ENTIRE
SUBBASEMENT LEVEL
IS CRAWLING WITH THOSE THINGS.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET UP HERE
BEFORE THEY CUT YOU OFF!
- OKAY, WE'LL TRY IT.
BUT FIRST, IS ANYBODY ELSE STILL
IN THE BUILDING?
- Nene: NO, I RAN AN ID SCAN
AND WE'RE THE ONLY ONES LEFT.
- AND MEANWHILE,
IN OTHER NEWS TODAY,
A.D. POLICE HEADQUARTERS
HAS BEEN SHUT DOWN BY A STRIKE
PROTESTING RUMORS OF A MERGER
BETWEEN THE A.D.
AND REGULAR POLICE.
ATTEMPTS TO GET A COMMENT FROM
AD OFFICIALS PROVED FUTILE...
- HEY, I LIKE THIS ONE.
WHAT-- WHAT IN THE HECK
WAS THAT?
DID I IMAGINE IT?
- ( phone rings )
HELLO?
LINNA YAMAZAKI SPEAKING.
- Macky: LINNA, IT'S NENE,
NENE'S IN DANGER.
SHE'S TRAPPED
IN THE A.D. POLICE BUILDING.
THE WHOLE PLACE IS FULL
OF ROGUE BOOMERS.
YOU'VE GOT TO SAVE HER, LINNA.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE!
- HOLD ON, I'M COMING.
DAMN IT, I'D KILL
FOR A HARDSUIT RIGHT NOW.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040"...
AS PREVIOUSLY DESTROYED BOOMERS
CONTINUE TO REVIVE,
THE REMAINING STAFF
OF THE A.D.P.
FIND THEMSELVES WAGING
A DESPERATE BATTLE FOR SURVIVAL.
WITH THE REST OF THE WORLD
UNAWARE OF THEIR FATE,
TIME IS RUNNING OUT.
ONLY NENE'S FELLOW SABERS
CAN SAVE THEM.
BUT TO DO THAT, THEY'LL NEED THE
AID OF THEIR FORMER ENEMIES--
THE A.D. POLICE.
NEXT EPISODE...