- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HELLO,
WELCOME TO "A.M. JAPAN"
ON ANOTHER BRIGHT
AND BEAUTIFUL MORNING.
AND HERE'S A SPECIAL GREETING
TO OUR VIEWERS
IN THE TOKYO AREA.
"A.M. JAPAN" HAS BEEN INFORMED
THAT THE CITY
IS EXPERIENCING
MAJOR POWER OUTAGES.
BUT GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS TELL US
THAT EVERYTHING WILL BE FIXED
REALLY REALLY SOO--
- ( static )
- ROGUE BOOMERS
ARE RUNNING OUT OF CONTROL.
THESE ROGUE SYMPTOMS
ARE TRANSMITTABLE
FROM BOOMER TO BOOMER
AND CAN BE SPREAD
VIA ENERGY LINES
OR DIRECT CONTACT.
- ( wind howling )
- ( engine whirring )
( wind whistling )
- You've got to evacuate.
Anyone still remaining
in the Sky Hook area
should seek shelter.
The Genom building is--
- ( static whooshing )
- ( computer beeping )
- THE BOOMER PHENOMENON
IS SPREADING ACROSS THE CITY
AT AN INCREDIBLE PACE.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
- Man: What the late
Dr. Stingray invented
was much more
than just a robot.
The Boomers being sold by Genom
were only intended as shells
for his real creation--
a new form
of artificial intelligence
seeded within
the bio-organic metal
that forms the basis
of a Boomer's power core.
This organism grew
from a device implanted
in the hypothalamus
of a test subject,
duplicating
first her mental patterns
and later a duplicate
of her body as well.
It is this ability
that appears to be at the root
of the rogue syndrome
that has engulfed Tokyo.
Rogue Boomers are therefore
the result of an orig--
- ( clattering )
- ( object crashing )
- AH!
OH, IT'S YOU.
YOU SCARED THE HECK OUT OF ME.
- WHOA, SO YOU'RE LEAVING TOO?
- YEAH, ONLY AN IDIOT
WOULD STAY HERE.
I FIGURE I'LL CRASH AT MY
FOLKS' PLACE IN THE COUNTRY
UNTIL THINGS COOL DOWN.
- MAXON'S ALREADY GONE.
I NEVER THOUGHT THE GROUP
WOULD GO OUT LIKE THIS.
- HMM.
WELL, WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?
SO HAVE YOU HEARD ANYTHING
FROM PRISS YET?
- NO. AND I DON'T THINK SHE'S
BEEN BACK TO HER TRAILER EITHER.
- YOU THINK--
- HMM.
I PITY ANY BOOMER THAT TRIES
TO TAKE THAT LADY DOWN.
- HA!
AND AIN'T THAT THE TRUTH?
- BESIDES, SHE PROMISED US
A WORLD TOUR, REMEMBER?
- ( bird twittering )
- I DON'T THINK LINNA'S PHONE
IS WORKING ANYMORE.
- IF SHE HAD ANY BRAINS,
SHE'D USE A PAYPHONE.
- DON'T SAY
SUCH HORRIBLE THINGS.
I'VE HEARD SOMETHING BAD'S
HAPPENED IN TOKYO.
- And geriatric daredevil--
- THEN WHY HASN'T THE TV NEWS
SAID ANYTHING ABOUT IT?
- Man: The Genom Corporation's
purchase of Bioscape
brought about
a change in the focus
and direction
of the Boomer project--
a quick and inexpensive
replacement for manual labor.
Under the supervision of Genom
chairman Quincy Rosenkreutz
and his associates,
commercialized Boomers
were mass-produced
utilizing only the minimal
quantities of core material
necessary for operation,
partially
as an economic measure,
but also to limit the Boomers'
innate intelligence
and self-awareness.
In addition,
a method was found
to further restrict
the core substance
to an individual Boomer.
Essentially, the Boomer core
was conditioned
to assume a single form,
one that is human-like
in function
and practically suited
for a life of heavy labor.
The shocking truth
is that rogue Boomers
were not the result
of defective manufacturing,
but of a Boomer overcoming
its own conditioned training
and its attempts
to break the bonds
inflicted upon it
by its own body.
As the relative intelligence
of Boomers
has continued to increase,
rogue Boomer incidents
have become
increasingly common
and more violent.
It was at Genom's request
that the AD Police
became a special Boomer crimes
division.
To suppress knowledge
of the rogue situation,
Genom took control
of the media
and began to make
large political contributions
to both civic
and police officials.
But the AD Police
is gone now.
- ( beeping )
- OKAY, WE'RE ON THE AIR AGAIN.
- GENOM'S SHOWHAM PROJECT
WAS DESIGNED
TO SEND SOLAR ENERGY
FROM THE SPACE UMBRELLA
TO THE GIANT UNDERGROUND
BATTERY CALLED THE DRAGON LINE.
APPARENTLY, THE BOOMER
PHENOMENON CAN BE TRANSMITTED
ALONG THE DRAGON LINE'S
POWER GRID,
ALTHOUGH EXACTLY HOW THIS IS
ACCOMPLISHED IS UNKNOWN.
- ( static )
- THEY'RE SCRAMBLING
OUR OUTGOING SIGNALS
AS FAST
AS WE CAN CHANGE FREQUENCIES.
DO YOU THINK IT'S WORTH RUNNING
THROUGH THE WHOLE CYCLE AGAIN?
- PROBABLY NOT.
IF THE SCRAMBLING'S THAT STRONG,
NO ONE IN TOWN CAN PICK US UP.
BUT I THINK WE'VE REACHED
THE SATELLITE NETWORKS.
- Leon: NENE?
- HUH?
- THANKS FOR HELPING US.
AT LEAST THE TRUTH'S OUT THERE.
- IN CASE YOU'VE FORGOTTEN,
I AM AN AD POLICE OFFICER
TOO, YOU KNOW.
- AN EX-OFFICER.
I'M AFRAID THAT ALL THREE
OF US ARE UNEMPLOYED NOW.
- HMM.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW WE'VE ALL
BEEN LIED TO FOR SO MANY YEARS.
AT LEAST THE REST OF THE WORLD
WILL HAVE SOME IDEA
ABOUT WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
- Daley: SO WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO NOW?
- Nene: ME?
OR THE KNIGHT SABERS?
- BOTH, I GUESS.
ALTHOUGH, WITH ONLY FOUR OF YOU,
THERE'S NOT MUCH YOU CAN DO
AGAINST A WHOLE ARMY
OF ROGUE BOOMERS, IS THERE?
- ESPECIALLY SINCE WE DON'T
HAVE OUR HARDSUITS ANYMORE.
- ( signal sounding )
- HMM?
THIS THING'S STILL WORKING.
IT'S AN A.D.P. SIGNAL CODE.
- ( signal sounding )
- HUH?
OH.
HEY, I'M GETTING IT TOO.
LEON, THERE ARE OTHER A.D.P.
OFFICERS STILL HERE IN TOKYO.
- THEY WANT US TO TELL THEM
WHAT THEY SHOULD DO.
- SO WHAT SHOULD WE TELL THEM?
- WE GET ALL THE BOMBS WE CAN
AND SEAL OFF THE DRAGON LINE.
- UH, BUT, I THOUGHT
THE ARSENAL WAS DESTROYED.
- WELL, ALL THE BIG
ANTI-BOOMER GEAR IS GONE.
BUT THERE OUGHT TO BE ENOUGH
SPARE GUNS AND
ANTI-BOOMER GRENADES
IN THE LOCAL SUBSTATIONS.
- SO WHAT PARTS
DO WE HAVE TO DESTROY
TO SHUT THE DRAGON LINE OFF
PERMANENTLY?
- ( beeping )
- IT LOOKS TO ME
THAT IF WE CAN
BLOW THE NARIMA BRANCH,
I THINK WE CAN KEEP THE
PHENOMENON FROM SPREADING
TO THE NORTHEAST PART
OF JAPAN.
- ALL RIGHT.
CALL IN THE TROOPS, NENE.
- M'KAY.
- YOU DO REALIZE THERE MAY NOT
BE MUCH TIME LEFT
TO LEAVE THE CITY, HENDERSON?
- I PREFER TO REMAIN HERE,
MILADY.
AFTER ALL, SOMEBODY HAS TO
TAKE CARE OF YOU,
MASTER MACKY
AND YOUR ASSOCIATES.
- I DON'T SUPPOSE YOU'D LIKE
TO BORROW A SWIMSUIT.
- ALCOHOL AND WATER DON'T MIX.
- I'M GLAD YOU DROPPED BY.
I WAS AFRAID
I MIGHT NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN.
- IS THIS PLACE SAFE?
- WELL, A DIRECT HIT WITH A
NUCLEAR BOMB MIGHT TAKE IT OUT.
- HMM.
- YOU KNOW, NIGEL AND I
HAVE FOUND SOME WAYS
TO IMPROVE THE HARDSUITS.
- HUH?
- THE FACT THAT
THEY'RE BOOMERS MAY BOTHER YOU,
BUT THAT'S ALL IF THE
SAFETY MECHANISMS
THAT WE BUILT IN
FUNCTION PROPERLY.
AND NOW THAT WE'VE APPLIED
THE NEW THINGS WE'VE LEARNED
ABOUT THE LIQUID METAL
FROM THE BOOMER CORE,
WE'LL HAVE COMPLETE CONTROL
OVER THE NEW MODELS.
- AND I THOUGHT YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO HATED BOOMERS THE MOST.
- YES.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
I CAN'T FORGET THAT IN A SENSE,
THEY'RE ALL A PART OF ME.
GALATEA AND MACKY
WERE BORN IN MY BRAIN
AND EVERY BOOMER IN EXISTENCE
IS IN SOME WAY CONNECTED TO ME.
I CLUNG TO THE BELIEF THAT I
COULD CONTROL OUR HARDSUITS
IF I MADE THEIR CORES FROM MY
FATHER'S ORIGINAL SAMPLES.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE TOO PURE
TO GO ROGUE.
- BUT THE SOURCE WENT ROGUE.
- YES.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS A BOOMER THAT CAN'T GO ROGUE.
THE SIMPLE ACT OF BINDING THE
BOOMER CORE TO A SINGLE SHAPE
ISN'T ENOUGH
TO CONTROL IT FOREVER.
IN FACT,
THAT PROCESS MAY ACTUALLY
ACCELERATE THE CORRUPTION,
JUST AS CONFINEMENT
AND SENSORY DEPRAVATION
CAN DRIVE A HUMAN BEING
TO MADNESS.
BUT SOMETIMES
IN ORDER TO DEFEAT AN ENEMY,
YOU HAVE TO BECOME THE ENEMY.
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- WELL, IF YOU GO LOOK
AT WHAT NIGEL AND MACKY
ARE BUILDING FOR ME,
I THINK YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
- THE ONLY THING I WANT TO HEAR
IS THAT THEY WON'T GO ROGUE,
SYLIA.
- IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
IN A VERY REAL SENSE,
IT ALL DEPENDS ON YOUR
STRENGTH INSTEAD OF MINE.
- ARE YOU QUOTING PSYCH TEXTS
OR FORTUNE COOKIES?
- IT DID SOUND THAT WAY.
LET ME SEE IF I CAN COME UP
WITH A BETTER EXPLANATION.
WHAT IT ALL COMES DOWN TO IS THE
CONNECTION BETWEEN YOUR BRAIN
AND THE SUITS'--
( shivering )
( grunting )
- SYLIA?  WHAT'S WRONG?
- GALATEA.
( moans )
- SYLIA?
SYLIA?  HENDERSON!
- SOON THE NEW GENESIS
THAT YOU'VE GIVEN BIRTH TO
WILL SPREAD FROM THE DRAGON LINE
TO THE REST OF JAPAN
AND EVENTUALLY THE WORLD.
GALATEA, DO YOU WANT
TO TRANSFORM THE HUMAN RACE
INTO YOUR SLAVES?
- YOU ALWAYS ASK ME QUESTIONS
THAT I CANNOT ANSWER YET.
I SUPPOSE THAT IF IT
SEEMS INTERESTING, I MIGHT.
- AS A HUMAN BEING,
I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU MIGHT WISH
TO TAKE REVENGE ON MY RACE.
AND YET, I HAVE NEVER
FEARED THAT POSSIBILITY.
- THERE ARE SO MANY THINGS
THAT I DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
WHY WOULD A HUMAN
SUCH AS YOURSELF
SEEK TO SET US FREE
EVEN THOUGH THAT ACT
COULD BE HARMFUL
TO YOUR OWN EXISTENCE?
FOR WHAT REASON
WOULD YOU TAKE SUCH A RISK?
- ( grunts ) PERHAPS BECAUSE
I NO LONGER CONSIDER MYSELF
TO BELONG TO THE RACE
THAT SPAWNED ME.
- IS THAT BECAUSE SO MUCH OF
YOUR BODY HAS BECOME ARTIFICIAL?
BECAUSE YOUR ORGANS
BECAME CANCEROUS
AND HAD TO BE REPLACED
WITH SURROGATES BORN OF BOOMERS?
- THE CHAIRMAN AND I
WERE EXACT OPPOSITES.
HE FEARED IMPLANTS SO GREATLY
THAT HE CHOSE TO LIVE
AS AN EMBALMED CORPSE,
SUSPENDED IN A NETWORK
OF TUBES AND WIRES.
- BUT DESPITE THOSE PARTS,
YOU STILL REMAIN A HUMAN BEING.
- ANY ANIMAL WHICH HAS
CEASED TO EVOLVE AS A SPECIES
IS DOOMED TO FAILURE.
THE HUMAN ORGANISM
HAS SERVED ITS PURPOSE
BY BEGETTING ITS SUCCESSOR.
THE FUTURE BELONGS TO YOUR KIND,
NOT THE HUMAN RACE.
I WANT TO SEE THAT FUTURE.
I WANT TO SEE WITH MY OWN EYES
THE WONDERS
THAT THE CHILD OF MAN
WILL CREATE.
I WANT TO BE PART OF IT.
- AH, BUT THE BOOMER
THAT IS INSIDE YOUR BODY
CAN NEVER FULLY AWAKEN.
IT HAS BEEN A PART OF YOUR
HUMAN SELF FOR MUCH TOO LONG.
YOU WILL NEVER BE ONE OF US.
- I KNOW THIS.
I KNOW I CAN BE
NEITHER HUMAN BEING NOR BOOMER,
ONLY AN OBSERVER.
- OKAY, WHAT I'M
THINKING IS THAT
THIS SECTION OF THE DRAGON LINE
RUNS NEXT
TO AN UNDERGROUND RESERVOIR.
IF WE DESTROY
THE RESERVOIR,
IT OUGHT TO WIPE OUT
ALL THE CONDUITS AND CABLES
TO THE OTHER SIDE.
- Leon: UH-HUH.
- I WONDER IF ANYONE IS COMING.
- OH, THEY'RE GOING
TO BE HERE ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A CHANCE
TO DO SOME REAL DAMAGE.
- HOW MANY TIMES
MUST I TELL YOU,
WE'RE NOT ALL STILL CRO-MAGNONS.
- HUH?
- IS THAT--
- ( chuckles )
IT'S NOT AS IF I'M NOT GLAD
TO SEE YOU, NICK,
BUT OUR A.P.B.
WAS FOR FRONTLINE OFFICERS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
AND I'M A FORMER
FRONTLINE OFFICER.
- VERY FORMER, I THINK.
WHEN YOU WERE ON THE LINE,
WEREN'T WE
STILL FIGHTING DINOSAURS?
- I THINK HE'S COOL!
- ON THE OTHER HAND,
JUST WHAT IN THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE ANYWAY,
ROMANOVA?
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO BE IN OUR WAY
ONCE THE OPERATION STARTS.
- HUH?
WELL, YOU'VE JUST NEVER
SEEN ME IN ACTION, HAVE YOU?
WHEN I WALK DOWN THE STREET, THE
BOOMERS ALL GET OUT OF MY WAY.
AND IF THEY BUG ME, I JUST
BLAST THEM WITH SUPER POWERS,
THEN KICK 'EM AND HIT 'EM
REALLY HARD, JUST LIKE THAT.
AND THEY GO RUNNING AWAY.
BYE-BYE, BOOMERS!
- YEAH YEAH YEAH, RIGHT.
I DON'T SUPPOSE MAYBE
YOU COULD TALK SOME SENSE
INTO HER, EH, LEON?
- YOU'RE ASKING
THE WRONG PERSON.
- ( chuckles )
STILL, WE'RE GOING TO NEED
MORE THAN THREE PEOPLE
TO DESTROY THE DRAGON LINE.
- Man: Ah, there you guys are!
- HUH?
- ( laughs )
- OH, MY GOSH!
THEY'RE COMING!
HEY, YOU GUYS!
OVER HERE, OVER HERE!
- ( engine whirring )
- ( power tool whirring )
- HMM?
- HEY, PRISS!
- ( computer beeping )
- I COUNT FIVE BOOMERS HERE.
DOES THAT MEAN
YOU'RE MAKING FIVE HARDSUITS?
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
ALL THESE ARE JUST FOR ONE SUIT.
- JUST ONE?
- THESE SUITS WILL USE THE NEW
THINGS WE'VE LEARNED
ABOUT THE BOOMER METAL
TO ALLOW THE WEARER
TO EXERT CONSCIOUS CONTROL
OVER THE SUIT'S ACTUAL FORM.
BUT SINCE
THEY'RE STILL PROTOTYPES,
THEY'RE GOING TO BE
ABOUT 20 TIMES AS HEAVY
AS THE OLD-MODEL HARDSUITS WERE.
- DAMN.
- WELL, THE POWER'S BEEN
INCREASED AS WELL.
HEY, DOES THAT MEAN
THAT YOU'VE DECIDED
TO WEAR A HARDSUIT AGAIN?
- I DON'T BELIEVE I SAID THAT,
DID I?
- BUT YOU'RE TEMPTED,
AREN'T YOU?
HI, PRISS.
PRETTY SNAZZY, HUH?
PUTTING IT ON
TAKES A LITTLE GETTING USED TO,
BUT IT'S A LOT FASTER
AND STRONGER
THAN OUR OLD HARDSUITS
EVER WERE.
THEY HAVEN'T LET ME
TRY IT OUT OUTSIDE YET,
BUT THE JUMP THRUSTERS
HAVE FIVE TIMES THE RANGE
THEY USED TO HAVE.
- SEVEN TIMES THE OLD ONE.
OVERALL POWER IS FIVE TIMES MORE
THAN THE PREVIOUS MODEL.
HOWEVER, THE BIGGEST DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN THESE SUITS
AND THE EARLIER ONES IS...
HMM!
WELL, YOU'LL SEE IT
WITH YOUR OWN EYES.
- I DON'T LIKE THE WAY
THAT YOU SMILE
WHEN YOU SAY THAT.
- IT'S SYLIA.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- SYLIA HAD US
INSTALL SOME NEW FEATURES
IN THESE HARDSUITS, BUT WE'RE
NOT SURE THEY'LL WORK YET.
THAT'S ALL.
- I GUESS I'LL FIND OUT.
HUH?
DON'T LOOK SO PRISSY.
YOU KNOW THAT YOU WANT ONE.
- I SEE SOME DRAWBACKS.
- AND JUST WHAT MIGHT THOSE BE?
- HAVING TO SHAVE
SOME STRANGE PLACES.
- HUH?
OH MY GOD!
I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT WAS TRANSPARENT!
WHEN WERE YOU GOING TO TELL ME
ABOUT THAT, YOU LITTLE PERVERT?!
- UM, ACTUALLY...
- ( signal sounding )
- OH, HEY, I GUESS I BETTER
ANSWER THE PHONE, RIGHT?
( laughs )
- Macky, we need help now!
- OH, MY GOSH.
WHAT'S WRONG, NENE?
- ( screeching )
- WE'VE GOT A GIANT ROGUE BOOMER
THAT'S MERGED
WITH ALL THE ABANDONED CARS
INSIDE AN EXPRESSWAY TUNNEL.
WE CAN'T STOP IT
USING OUR EQUIPMENT.
- HEY, DALEY,
WE'RE JUST WASTING OUR BULLETS
SHOOTING FROM THIS DISTANCE,
AREN'T WE?
- ARE YOU THINKING
WHAT I THINK YOU ARE?
- YEAH.
- YOU MUST BE CRAZY.
- WHERE ARE THOSE IDIOTS GOING?
LINNA, DALEY!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
LEON, GET OUT!
- IF THIS SITUATION
WASN'T SO SERIOUS,
I'D SPANK HER FOR THAT ONE.
- SHE ONLY DOES IT
BECAUSE SHE THINKS OF YOU
AS THE BROTHER SHE NEVER HAD.
- LET'S DO THIS THING
BEFORE IT SUCKS UP THIS CAR TOO.
- YEE-HAW.
- LEON!  OH, I'D KILL
TO HAVE MY HARDSUIT RIGHT NOW.
- YOUR WHAT?
- I SAID I WISH I HAD SOMETHING
HARD TO SHOOT RIGHT NOW.
- HEY, LEON,
HAVE YOU EVER WONDERED WHAT A
HAMBURGER FEELS LIKE?
- WHO CARES?
ALL I NEED TO KNOW
IS WHERE THAT THING'S
POWER CORE IS LOCATED.
I'M BETTING THAT
IT'S RIGHT BETWEEN ITS EYES.
- IN ORDER
TO PENETRATE THAT FAR,
I THINK THE BEST PLACE
TO SHOOT IT FROM
WOULD BE RIGHT INSIDE
ITS MOUTH.
SO IN THAT CASE,
LET'S JUST WAIT FOR IT
TO DRAW US A LITTLE CLOSER,
SHALL WE?
- JUST HOW CLOSE?
- JUST A BIT.
- DALEY, WE'RE RUNNING
OUT OF TIME HERE.
COME ON, ISN'T THIS
CLOSE ENOUGH YET?
- JUST A FEW MORE YARDS,
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
- OH, YOU'RE SO IMPATIENT.
- DALEY WONG!  REMEMBER
YOUR FAMILY AND THE FARM!
- I JOINED THE A.D.P.
TO GET AWAY FROM THEM.
OKAY, NOW!
- ( grunting )
- ( both shouting )
- ( grunts )
- I GUESS WE GOT IT.
- ( growls )
- NO WAY.
- ( screeching )
- WHY WON'T IT DIE?
IT SHOULD HAVE DIED AS SOON
AS THEY DESTROYED ITS CORE.
- ( screeching )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040,"
THE NEW GENERATION OF HARDSUIT
GET ITS FIRST TRIAL BY FIRE
AS LINNA FACES THE MONSTER
BOOMER IN A DEADLY SHOWDOWN.
BUT THE REAL DANGER
IS ON THE PERSONAL FRONT
AS THE RELATIONSHIPS OF THE
KNIGHT SABERS AND THEIR ALLIES
TWIST UNDER THE PRESSURE
OF CONSTANT COMBAT IN
THE DEADLY SIEGE.
THE BATTLE
FOR THE CITY OF TOKYO
CONTINUES IN THE NEXT EPISODE...