- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( motor revving )
- ( hardsuit thumping )
- HUH?
UH, THAT IS YOU, PRISS.
RIGHT?
- ( motor revving )
- SO YOU'VE CHANGED
THE MOTOSLAVE TOO.
- Leon:
WE HAD TO MAKE SOME CHANGES
SO IT WOULD INTERFACE
WITH YOUR NEW SUIT.
SMALL CHANGES.
- BUT THAT'S NOT TRUE!
THE OLD MOTOSLAVE
WAS JUST A MOTORCYCLE.
BUT THIS IS--
- I KNOW.
IT'S A BOOMER.
IT'LL PLUG INTO MY BRAIN
JUST LIKE THE SUIT.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S BE OFF THEN, SHALL WE?
HUH?
- I'M GOING BY MYSELF.
- HUH?
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?  HUH?
- LOOK,
YOU'D JUST BE IN THE WAY.
- ( gun firing )
- Leon: DAMN IT!
THIS GUN
IS TOTALLY USELESS!
ALL RIGHT.
BUT ONLY IF YOU
PROMISE ME SOMETHING FIRST.
PROMISE ME
THAT YOU'LL COME BACK.
( grunts )
- ( Priss grunts )
- ( suit clomping )
- PRISS?
WE'LL TRY THAT AGAIN
WHEN YOU GET BACK,
WITHOUT THE HELMET.
- ( suit whirring )
- ( motor revving )
- ( explosion )
- DAMN IT.
- ( screeching )
- UGH!
LINNA!  NENE!
- ( both grunting, gasping )
- OH, IT'S GOT ME!
- THIS THING IS TRYING
TO FUSE WITH OUR SUITS!
- NO WAY!  SYLIA!
DO SOMETHING!
- ( grunts )
WHOA!
IT'S NO USE.
I CAN'T EVEN GET CLOSE
TO THE DAMN THING.
THE ONLY CHANCE IS TO CUT OFF
ITS LINK TO THE DRAGON LINE.
ALL RIGHT, HERE GOES!
IT KNOWS
WHAT I'M TRYING TO DO!
- ( grunting )
IT HURTS.
LINNA?
I CAN'T TAKE IT.
Linna:
NENE, HOLD ON.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE FAITH.
- LINNA.
- LINNA?
- Linna: IT WILL BE ALL RIGHT,
NENE.
SYLIA WON'T GIVE UP.
AND I KNOW PRISS IS COMING.
I KNOW SHE IS.
( grunts )
- LINNA,
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO YOU?
LINNA!
- Linna: DON'T WORRY.
I WON'T LET THIS MONSTER
BEAT ME.
- OKAY.  BUT WHY AM I HEARING
YOUR VOICE IN MY HEAD?
- IN YOUR HEAD?
YOU MEAN YOU HEAR IT TOO, NENE?
AH!
- ( blast fires )
- HUH?
- ( motor revving )
- Linna: PRISS!
SHE'S HERE!
- WHAT?  PRISS!
- SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
- THANK GOD.
- SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
- THE ONLY WAY TO STOP IT IS
TO CUT OFF ITS LINK
TO THE DRAGON LINE.
IT'LL HAVE TO BE
RIGHT AT THE BASE.
COVER ME, I'M GOING IN.
- SYLIA! GOD!
- NOW, PRISS!
AH!
THAT'S IT.
AHHH!
( gasps )
IT'S TOO WELL PROTECTED
ON THE OUTSIDE!
AHH!
- SYLIA!
- ( crashing )
- HERE.
- OH.
THANKS.
- THIS IS WHAT I HATE
THE MOST--
THE WAITING AND NOT KNOWING.
- I KNOW IT'S HARD,
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO TRUST THEM.
- AH...
- IT'S NOT LIKE
WE HAVE A CHOICE, YOU KNOW.
JUST HAVE FAITH
AND ANOTHER DRINK.
- ( whirring )
- I HOPE YOU WON'T MIND
IF I JOIN YOU GENTLEMEN.
- Macky: MR. HENDERSON?
- I'VE BEEN SAVING THIS
FOR A SPECIAL OCCASION.
BUT IT SEEMED A WASTE
TO DRINK IT ALL BY MYSELF.
- HMM.
- Macky: OF COURSE
YOU CAN JOIN US.
YOU'RE PART OF THE FAMILY.
- Henderson: YOU'RE VERY KIND,
MASTER MACKY.
- PRISS.
- COME ON, DAMN IT!
WHO WANTS TO BE FIRST?
- ( shivering )
NENE, LINNA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- Nene: YEAH.
- WELL, I'VE BEEN BETTER.
- PRISS?
- ( grunting ) HYAH!
- ( grunting )
DAMN IT!
- Both: PRISS!
- WHAT THE HELL?
HYAH!
- OH, OF COURSE.  OH!
- SYLIA!
OH!
- ( both screaming )
- LINNA!
- Linna: HOLD ON, PRISS.
EVERYONE LISTEN TO ME.
SOMEHOW THE WAY THIS THING
IS TRYING TO ABSORB OUR SUITS
HAS CONNECTED THEM TOGETHER.
WHATEVER FORCE IS BINDING ALL
THESE BOOMER COMPONENTS TOGETHER
IS ACTING AS A CONDUIT
FOR THE IMPULSES
OUR BRAINS
SEND TO OUR HARDSUITS.
I THINK THAT LINNA AND NENE
WERE SOMEHOW ABLE
TO CONTROL THE WORM
FOR JUST A FEW SECONDS.
IF WE WORK TOGETHER, WE MAY BE
ABLE TO CONFUSE IT LONG ENOUGH
TO GIVE PRISS A SHOT
AT CUTTING OFF ITS POWER FLOW.
- Priss: DO YOU KNOW
HOW CRAZY THAT SOUNDS?
- Linna: WE CAN DO IT.
I KNOW WE CAN.
- ROGER.
- Nene: OKAY.
- PRISS, DOWN ITS THROAT.
- I'M ON IT!
- ALL RIGHT,
YOU OVERGROWN WORM!
EAT ME!
I SEE IT.
( grunting )
- ( all shouting )
- SYLIA!
- NENE, LINNA.
- WHERE'S PRISS?
- OH NO!
PRISS!
- All: CHEERS!
- Nene: IT'S GOOD
TO BE OUT OF THAT SUIT!
- I CAME BACK.
- YEP.
- I FIGURED YOU'D BE HUNGRY,
SO I MADE SANDWICHES.
- ( laughs )
THANK YOU.
- HMM.
- JEEZ, LOOKS LIKE
I'M ODD GIRL OUT AGAIN.
- POOR CHILD.
REFILL?
- ( laughs )
UM, THANK YOU, I GUESS.
- THIS IS AN EXCELLENT BLEND.
- YOU KNOW, IT'S AMAZING HOW
THINGS CAN CHANGE SO QUICKLY.
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- A FEW MONTHS AGO,
I HATED THE KNIGHT SABERS.
ALL I CARED ABOUT BACK THEN
WAS HOW BAD
YOU MADE THE A.D.P. LOOK
BY EASILY TRASHING ROGUE BOOMERS
THAT WE COULD BARELY HANDLE.
BUT HERE I AM,
UNEMPLOYED,
DRINKING A TOAST WITH YOU
AND THINKING.
- THINKING ABOUT WHAT?
- ABOUT HOW INCREDIBLY LUCKY
I AM TO BE HERE.
AND IF THIS WAS THE ONLY WAY
I COULD BE HERE,
I WOULDN'T CHANGE
ANYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED.
UM, PRISS?
REMEMBER THAT PROMISE?
- HMM?
- WELL, WHAT I SAID
ABOUT THE HELMET.
- DREAM ON.
YOU WANT ANOTHER DRINK?
- YEAH, I NEED ONE.
- THAT'S GREAT.
BUT WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE ONE OF THE BACON ONES?
HERE.
UM, ARE YOU OKAY?
- IS IT WRONG?
- HUH?
- I MEAN, THE ENTIRE CITY
IS BEING ABANDONED
AND THE BOOMERS
ARE GOING ROGUE EVERYWHERE.
I KNOW THAT ALL OF US
ARE REALLY IN HORRIBLE DANGER.
I KNOW
THAT I SHOULD BE SCARED,
AND YET I'M ENJOYING MYSELF.
IT JUST DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT.
- MACKY?
- I WONDER HOW LONG
I'LL REMEMBER THESE FEELINGS.
- HUH?
- THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT I HAVE TO DO.
- HEY, MACKY!
WAIT UP.
- ( all chuckling )
- NO, OF COURSE
I'M NOT JEALOUS.
- ( chattering )
- ( silent )
- SO HAVE YOU DECIDED
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO YET?
- WHAT I'VE BEEN HOPING
IS THAT WE'LL BE ABLE
TO CONTINUE
FIGHTING THE BOOMERS FROM HERE.
WE NEED MORE TIME
TO DISCOVER WHAT THE NATURE
OF THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN OUR
MINDS AND OUR SUITS ACTUALLY IS.
- SO YOU'LL PURSUE THAT PATH,
NO MATTER
WHAT THE COST MIGHT BE?
- I HAVE TO!
I DON'T WANT TO.
BUT YOU KNOW WHY I MUST.
- YES, I KNOW WHY.
AND I UNDERSTAND.
- I HAVE TO END THIS.
AND I NEED YOUR HELP TO DO IT.
PLEASE, NIGEL.
- ( computer beeping )
- EH, ALL OF THE OUTSIDE LINES
ARE DOWN.
MY TERMINAL IS USELESS.
- ( beeping )
- SO, UM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- BACKUPS.  I'M BACKING UP
ALL THE DATA I CAN
WHILE I STILL HAVE THE TIME
AND POWER TO DO IT.
- ALL OF IT?
BUT THAT'LL TAKE YOU FOREVER.
- YEAH, THAT'S WHY
I HAVE TO START IT NOW.
- MACKY?
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasps )
- ( moaning )
- ( clamoring )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
CAN'T YOU SLEEP?
- NO.
I'M SORRY IF I WOKE YOU.
I'VE JUST GOT A FEELING THAT
SOMETHING'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
OH!
- OH!
WHERE DID IT COME FROM?
- ( alarm sounding )
- OH!  WHAT'S THAT?!
- WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT ALARM FOR?
- AN INTRUSION DETECTOR,
I AM AFRAID.
- ( chirping )
- HMM?
( gasps )
MACKY?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- HUH?
THAT'S THE INTRUDER ALARM.
- NENE, WHERE IS EVERYONE?
- I THINK THEY'RE ALL
STILL UPSTAIRS.
- ALL RIGHT, RUN A FULL SWEEP
OF THE BUILDING.
- YES, MA'AM!
- SYLIA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- THAT'S WHAT WE'RE TRYING
TO FIND OUT.
THERE ARE BOOMERS
UP ON THE ROOF.
- HEY, NOT JUST ON THE ROOF!
THE BOOMER CORE DETECTOR SAYS
THEY'RE IN THE BUILDING AS WELL!
- THERE CAN'T BE.
THAT'S JUST IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( alarm pinging )
- THERE'S NO WAY
THE SECURITY SYSTEM HERE
COULD HAVE BEEN PENETRATED
SO EASILY.
WAIT A SECOND.
THERE'S NOTHING
ON THE SECURITY CAMERA SCREENS.
- I KNOW THERE'S NOTHING
ON THE CAMERAS, SYLIA!
BUT THE PROXIMITY DETECTOR
SAYS OTHERWISE.
- I BELIEVE YOU.
OKAY, BRING UP THE SECURITY
GATES AND FIREWALLS,
THEN SHUT DOWN EVERYTHING
ABOVE THIS LEVEL.
- RIGHT.
- ( pinging )
- Nene: SHUT DOWN COMPLETED.
WHAT?  NO WAY!
SOMEHOW THEY'RE GETTING PAST
ALL OF THE BARRIERS.
- BUT HOW?
WHERE IN THE HELL ARE THEY?
- Nene: THEY JUST HIT
THE GARAGE.
AH!
THIS IS NUTS.
IT'S LIKE ALL OF OUR DEFENSES
AREN'T EVEN THERE.
- THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
- HOW INTERESTING.
THAT IS A NEW CONCEPT.
- Both: HUH?
- HUH?
OH, I--
- ( rumbling )
- All: OH!
- NOW WHAT?
- SO WHAT WAS THAT?
- IT WASN'T AN EARTHQUAKE.
- OH MY GOD! THEY'RE GOING
TO BE HERE ANY MINUTE!
- ( pinging )
- THEY'RE--
THEY'RE AT OUR LEVEL!
THEY'RE RIGHT OUTSIDE
THE DOOR!
- ( grunts )
GO ON!
I'LL HOLD THEM HERE.
- ARE YOU NUTS?
- I KNOW THIS GUN
WILL BE PRACTICALLY USELESS,
BUT MAYBE I CAN
BUY THE REST OF YOU ENOUGH TIME.
GO ON.
I WON'T BE ABLE
TO HOLD THEM HERE LONG.
- YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
- Leon: NENE, IS THERE
ANOTHER WAY OUT OF HERE?
- THIS CAN'T BE RIGHT!
ACCORDING TO THE DETECTOR,
THEY'RE ALREADY INSIDE THE PIT!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( gasps )
- THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE, NENE.
THERE ARE NO BOOMERS IN HERE.
- THAT THING'S DEFECTIVE.
RESET IT.
- I- I DID!
- SOMETHING'S WRONG.
WHAT DID WE MISS?
OH!
- ( both screaming )
- IT'S THE SWIMMING POOL!
THE SWIMMING POOL
COVERED IT IN CLOTHES.
- ( scratching )
- OH!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040,"
THE ASSAULT ON THE KNIGHT
SABER'S HEADQUARTERS
IS ONLY THE BEGINNING
OF A NEW NIGHTMARE.
AS THE CITY OF TOKYO
IS CONSUMED BY A MONSTROUS WAVE
OF BIO-MECHANICAL HORROR,
THE FEW SURVIVORS
FIND THEMSELVES ON THE RUN
THROUGH AN EMPTY
METROPOLIS ABANDONED
TO THE WRATH OF THE BOOMERS.
CAN EVEN THE KNIGHT SABERS
WITHSTAND THE FURY
OF A MILLION RAMPAGING
MAD MACHINES?
NEXT EPISODE...