- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( music playing )
( groans )
- I DON'T KNOW. THE GUYS AND I
HAVE BEEN PERFORMING HERE
SINCE WE STARTED THE BAND.
WE'VE PLAYED AROUND,
BUT I LIKE THIS CLUB.
- Reporter: So what is it
that makes Sekiria different
from other bands?
- IS IT DIFFERENT
FROM OTHER BANDS?
- Mmm... So what's the
inspiration for your songs?
- I DON'T KNOW.
RIDING MY BIKE, I GUESS.
- Do you have anything you want
to say to our viewers?
- YEAH. IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S INSIDE MY HEAD,
COME TO HOT LEGS
AND HEAR ME SING.
- (rock n' roll music playing )
( crowd cheering )
- ♪  OH, THE FLOWING,
WITHOUT HATING  ♪
♪ LIVING PAST
YOUR NORMAL SPAN. ♪
♪ HIGH ABOVE THE CLOUDS
OF HEAVEN ♪
♪ LIFE WAS BURST
INSIDE MY BRAIN. ♪
- ( radio playing )
- DID YOU FIND THE OCTAGON?
I NEED IT NOW.
HMM?
- UM, ARE YOU GOING TO
BE FINISHED SOON?
- YEAH.
- I'M SORRY IT TOOK SO LONG,
IT WAS IN THE WRONG BOX.
OH, HI PRISS.
- I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THAT YOU DIDN'T NEED
ANY ASSISTANCE, NIGEL?
- UH-HUH, OH, BOY.
- I DON'T NEED AN ASSISTANT,
PRISS.
HOWEVER, THE KID NEEDS
SOMETHING TO DO.
AND HE HAPPENS TO BE THE BEST
ASSISTANT I'VE EVER HAD.
- UH, DID SHE...
- YOU FOUND THE GASKET.
- UH, YES SIR.
JUST LIKE YOU SAID.
WHAT NOW?
- TIGHTEN THE BOLT
WITH THE OCTAGON.
BUT DON'T USE TOO MUCH TORQUE.
- RIGHT.
( engine running )
♪ IF YOU COULD JUST MOVE AWAY
I'LL MELT INTO YOUR EMBRACE, ♪
♪ NOTHING LEFT TO SAY ♪
♪ IT'S JUST THE
VICTIMS OF LOVE
WITH WHICH YOU THROW
MY HEART IN ♪
♪ IT'S THAT MUCH TIMES
THAT WE LOSE OUR MIND ♪
♪ THAT SENDS ME TO HELL. ♪
♪ MOTOR'S RACING AS WE
PICK UP THE SPEED. ♪
♪ ASHEN SWEATERS WE FEEL
OUR SKIN BURNING ♪
( sirens )
♪ OUR HEART BEATS
ARE ♪
♪ AS WE SEARCH FOR A WAY TO
GET OURSELVES IN CONTROL ♪
♪ IF YOU COULD JUST
FEEL THE YEARNINGS
THAT I KEEP HOLDING IN. ♪
♪ I COULD LIVE ALL
THAT YOU HAVE WON. ♪
♪ IF YOU COULD LOOK TO THE
LONGING THAT I HAVE IN MY SOUL ♪
♪ FOR EVERMORE
YOU  MY HEART ♪
( engine revving )
- HMM.
- AH, I'M AFRAID THAT
YOUR MACHO CHARM
WON'T HAVE ANY AFFECT ON
THIS ONE, LEON.
- Leon: WHY DIDN'T THIS GUY
GIVE ME A SPEEDING TICKET?
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
WONDERING, RIGHT?
- DO THE AD POLICE MOONLIGHT
AS TRAFFIC COPS NOW?
- OF COURSE WE DON'T.
BUT I WOULDN'T GIVE YOU
ONE EVEN IF WE DID.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- YOU'RE NAME'S PRISS ASAGIRI.
BUT CAN I JUST CALL YOU PRISS?
MY NAME'S LEON.
I USED TO BE A REGULAR COP,
YOU KNOW, HIGHWAY PATROL.
I USED TO SPEND MY TIME
CHASING DOWN CRAZY BIKERS
LIKE YOU, PRISS.
AND I DON'T MIND TELLING YOU
THAT I MISS IT SOMETIMES.
- MM, IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO BORE ME, YOU'RE SUCCEEDING.
- YOU REALLY HATE
THE AD POLICE, DON'T YOU?
( sighs )
WELL I DON'T THINK WE CAN ALWAYS
EXPECT EVERYONE TO LOVE US.
BUT WHY WOULD YOU
HATE US LIKE THAT?
- YOU JUST SAID IT.
IT'S THE "WE."
- HUH?
- DO YOU THINK PUTTING ON
THAT BADGE MAKES YOU SPECIAL,
AND APART FROM THE REST OF US?
- HEY, WAIT, I DIDN'T MEAN
IT THAT WAY.
- AND THE MOST PATHETIC PART
IS THAT YOU DON'T EVEN REALIZE
WHAT YOU ARE.
YOU'RE JUST A TOOL, A MAGGOT
FEEDING ON A DEAD CORPSE.
( grumbling )
( laughing )
- Daley:
CRASH AND BURN.
- Leon: SHUT UP, WONG.
I'M DRIVING.
- WELL, YOU'RE HOME LATE.
- UH, I'M SORRY, SYLIA.
- I LIKE THAT OUTFIT
YOU'RE WEARING TODAY.
IT LOOKS VERY NICE, MACKY.
- UM, THANK YOU.
YOU BOUGHT IT.
- DID I?
THERE'S GREASE ON YOUR FACE.
- ( gasps )
( laughs )
GOTCHA.
( sighs )
( silverware clinking )
YOU'VE BEEN AT NIGEL'S,
HAVEN'T YOU?
THE HARDSUIT UPGRADES
ARE ALL FINISHED,
SO WHAT'S HE UP TO?
- WELL, ACTUALLY, HE'S
MAKING A MOTORCYCLE.
- A MOTORCYCLE?
HM, HOW INTERESTING.
- OF COURSE, IT'S NOT
AN ORDINARY MOTORCYCLE.
HE'S PUTTING IT TOGETHER
A PIECE AT A TIME,
AND HE MACHINED
THE ENGINE PARTS HIMSELF.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLY POWERFUL!
BUT IT'S ALSO
INCREDIBLY RESPONSIVE.
OF COURSE, THAT'S GOING TO
MAKE IT WAY TOO TRICKY
FOR THE AVERAGE PERSON
TO OPERATE.
THAT'S WHY I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT HE'S MAKING IT FOR PRISS.
- FOR PRISS?
- YEAH, SHE HANGS AROUND A LOT.
AND I THINK SHE AND NIGEL
HAVE A LOT IN COMMON, YOU KNOW?
- ( gasps )
- WELL, NEITHER OF THEM
TALK VERY MUCH.
THEY BOTH LOVE MACHINES.
Macky: SOMETIMES, I THINK THEY
COMMUNICATE TELEPATHICALLY.
- ( groans )
MAYBE IT WOULD BE BETTER
IF WE ATE IN SILENCE.
- OH, I'M SORRY, SYLIA.
- ( sighs )
- Macky:
SYLIA?
- I WASN'T LIKE THIS.
I WASN'T THIS WAY BEFORE.
- SYLIA, I STILL LOVE YOU.
- WHAT?
- I LOVE YOU, THAT HASN'T
CHANGED SINCE THE DAYS BEFORE.
BUT SYLIA, I THOUGHT THAT IF I
CAME HERE IT COULD BE THE SAME.
- THAT'S RIGHT, NOTHING
HAS CHANGED.
- BUT IT'S NOT
LIKE IT WAS BEFORE.
AT FIRST I THOUGHT I WAS
DIFFERENT, SOMEHOW.
BUT IT'S NOT ME, IT'S YOU.
- MACKY...
- NIGEL'S AGREED TO LET ME
STAY AT HIS PLACE.
( sobbing )
( phone ringing )
- HM?
- HI PRISS! IT'S A NENEGRAM!
HEY, LINNA'S COMING OVER
TO SPEND THE NIGHT
AT MY PLACE TONIGHT,
AND WE WERE WONDERING IF
YOU'D LIKE TO DROP BY,
LINNA TOLD ME THAT
SHE WANTS TO SEE YOU--
DON'T FORGET TO BRING SOME
MUNCHIES, OKAY?
( humming )
♪ WOKE UP WITHOUT YOU
THIS MORNING BY MYSELF. ♪
( electric guitar playing )
- Linna: OH, MY GOD!
NENE, SOMEONE'S BURGLARIZED
YOUR APARTMENT!
- Nene: HUH? OH, NAH.
IT ALWAYS LOOKS LIKE THIS.
- Linna: YOU'RE KIDDING,
YOU REALLY LIVE LIKE THIS?
( giggling )
- Linna: I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE STILL EATING.
- Nene: I CAN'T HELP IT,
I LOVE THESE THINGS!
( phone ringing )
- HUH?
WELL I'LL BE,
IT'S A MESSAGE FROM PRISS.
- OH? WHAT DOES SHE SAY?
- THAT IF WE WANT TO SEE HER,
SHE'S SINGING AT
HOT LEGS TONIGHT.
BUT WE'D HAVE TO PAY
THE COVER CHARGE TO GET IN.
SEE, I SAID SHE WOULDN'T COME.
SHE NEVER DOES.
I'VE TRIED BEFORE,
BUT SHE'S JUST WEIRD.
- WELL I GUESS I UNDERSTAND.
SOMETIMES YOU
JUST DON'T FIT IN.
( laughing ) BUT I'LL BET
SHE HAS A BOYFRIEND.
- A BOYFRIEND?!
( laughing )
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT PRISS?
- ( gasps ) ARE YOU SAYING
SHE SWINGS THAT WAY?
- HUH?  SWINGS WHAT WAY?
- I MEAN, DOES SHE LIKE...
GIRLS?
- ( laughing )
YOU'RE WEIRD, LINNA!
- Nene: I DON'T REALLY KNOW
THAT MUCH ABOUT HER,
BUT I KNOW SHE USED TO BE
IN LOVE WITH SOMEONE.
BUT SOMETHING HAPPENED.
- Linna:
WHAT?
- Nene:
I THINK HE DIED.
- Linna:
OH, HOW DID HE DIE?
- Nene: I DON'T KNOW, BUT I
HEARD THAT THAT'S THE REASON
SHE SINGS WITH THAT BAND.
HEY! YOU WOULDN'T TELL PRISS
THAT I TOLD YOU ABOUT THIS,
WOULD YOU, LINNA?
- NO, MY LIPS ARE SEALED.
- Reporter: How do you feel
about the world we live in?
Mhmm, okay. If you weren't
a singer, what would you do?
- I THINK I'D JOIN THE KNIGHT
SABERS-- BLOW THINGS UP.
- Reporter: I see, and what
does singing mean to you?
- SINGING? IT MEANS
THAT I'M ALIVE.
THAT I'M NOT DEAD AND BURIED,
THAT'S ALL.
♪ I'm not a square peg
in a round hole, ♪
♪ no way I'm going to
fit in. ♪
♪ I put it back before
I heard the dial tone. ♪
♪ I hung up the phone
and hung up my mind... ♪
- Police radio: All units, all
units. We've got a mad Boomer
that's fused with a racer
tearing up the gulf freeway
and the KS quadrant.
All pursuit units
are instructed to give chase.
- Leon:
WE'RE ON IT.
( shouts )
- LINNA! LINNA, WAKE UP!
( screaming )
( crowd cheering )
( phone beeping )
( tires squealing )
- Nene: SYLIA, WE'RE TRYING
TO CHANGE BACK HERE!
- ARE YOU TRYING TO KILL US?!
- I'M SORRY, BUT THIS BOOMER
IS MOVING INCREDIBLY FAST
AND I HAVE TO FLOOR IT
JUST TO CATCH UP WITH IT.
- WHERE'S PRISS?
- WE COULDN'T REACH HER.
- DON'T WORRY YOURSELVES
ABOUT IT.
I THINK THE TWO OF YOU
CAN HANDLE THIS.
- Nene:
OKAY-AY
- DAMN IT, WE CAN'T
KEEP UP WITH IT.
- Daley: WELL WE BETTER
THINK OF SOMETHING FAST.
IF WE BLOCKADE
ALL THE OFF-RAMPS,
MAYBE WE CAN KEEP IT OUT
OF THE CITY AT LEAST.
- HUH?
- YOU TAKE THE RIGHT SIDE,
I'LL TAKE THE LEFT, OKAY?
- OKAY!
- EAT THIS!
( screams )
- NENE!
( screaming )
- OW!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
IT JUST BRUSHED US ASIDE!
- Linna: IT'S LIKE TRYING
TO TACKLE A BUS!
- IT'S GOT TOO MUCH MASS.
- Macky: SYLIA, YOU'VE GOT TO
GET DOWN TO NIGEL'S SHOP!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- Macky: NOTHING, WE THINK WE
HAVE A WAY TO BEAT THIS THING.
- WHAT IS IT?
- Nigel: THE MOTOSLAVE, THE
MACHINE I'VE BEEN BUILDING.
IT'S AS TOUGH AS A HARDSUIT,
AND THREE TIMES AS FAST.
-I'LL GET LINNA AND NENE.
- Macky: DON'T WORRY, PRISS
SHOULD BE HERE ANY SECOND.
- ALRIGHT THEN,
I'M ON MY WAY.
( sirens )
- ONE MORE TIME!
( screams )
- I THINK WE'RE JUST
MAKING IT MAD!
- I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT,
HOLD ON!
I'M GOING TO POP YOU
LIKE A ZIT!
( screams )
- Macky: WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO ROAD TEST IT YET,
SO DON'T OPEN
THE THROTTLE COMPLETELY.
EVEN SO, YOU OUGHT TO BE ABLE
TO CATCH UP TO THAT BOOMER
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP
IT UNDER CONTROL.
- I UNDERSTAND.
THANKS, KID.
- Macky: UH, SURE.
GOOD LUCK, PRISS.
- Sylia:
ARE YOU READY, PRISS?
NENE, LINNA, AND THE AD POLICE
HAVE GOT THE BOOMER
CONTAINED ON THE BELTWAY.
SO WE'LL CUT ACROSS TOWN
TO INTERCEPT IT.
- RIGHT, SOUNDS GOOD.
- Sylia:
ARE YOU READY TO LAUNCH?
- ANYTIME.
- LET'S ROCK N' ROLL!
( engine revving )
- Macky: OKAY, PRISS.
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD.
CHECK YOUR READOUTS.
YOU'LL SEE THAT YOU'VE GOT
A MOTOSLAVE FEEDBACK MODE
SHOWING IN YOUR VISOR.
- FEEDBACK?
- Macky:
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE MOTOSLAVE'S INERTIAL
GUIDANCE SYSTEM INTERFACES
WITH YOUR HARDSUIT.
THAT WILL ALLOW YOU
TO RECONFIGURE THE SLAVE'S
AIRFRAME ON THE FLY.
- I THINK I UNDERSTOOD
ABOUT HALF THAT,
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
( explosion )
( gasping )
- I CAN'T RUN ANY LONGER!
- DON'T GIVE UP!
- Sylia: LINNA, NENE,
PULL BACK IMMEDIATELY.
PRISS IS GOING TO
RAM THE BOOMER.
- WHAT-TT?
DID SHE SAY "RAM?"
- Linna: SHE REALLY
IS GOING TO RAM IT!
- Macky: PRISS, YOU'RE
GOING IN TOO FAST!
- DON'T WORRY, NIGEL
WOULD NEVER BUILD A BIKE
THAT COULDN'T TAKE
A LITTLE PUNISHMENT.
HERE WE GO!
( yelling )
SECOND VERSE.
( car crash )
( sighs )
( door opening )
( footsteps )
- ♪ ALL ALONE, SOLITUDE
CONSUMES MY SOUL ♪
♪ WITHOUT HOPE, AND SEARCHING
FOR A FACE I'VE LOST ♪
♪ ACROSS THE ENDLESS STREETS
I WALK ALL THE DAY ♪
♪ SEARCHING THE CROWDS
FOR THE ONE I LOVE. ♪
HUH?
- ( clapping )
- ONE, TWO.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040"
A SERIES OF MYSTERIOUS
BOOMER DISAPPEARANCES
HAS BOTH THE KNIGHT SABERS
AND GEMON DIGGING
FRANTICALLY FOR ANSWERS.
WHAT SINISTER SECRETS LAY
BURIED BENEATH THE RUINS
OF THE GREAT EARTHQUAKE
THAT LEVELED TOKYO?
AND WHY IS BRIAN J. MASON
WILLING TO RISK ANYTHING
TO UNCOVER THEM?
SOME SECRETS ARE
BEST LEFT BURIED.
NEXT EPISODE...