- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Priss:
THE WHOLE BUILDING'S MOVING!
- Nene: IT'S THE TOWER!
GALATEA HAS TRANSFERRED HER
CONSCIOUSNESS INTO THE TOWER.
WE'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE!
- YOU MEAN THIS WHOLE THING'S
BECOMING HER?!
- ( exploding )
- Priss: DAMN IT.
HOW IN THE HELL
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO FIGHT THAT?
- ( electrical static )
- HMM?
- HOW'S SYLIA?
- ( sighs )
SHE'S JUST BEEN SITTING THERE.
- MACKY.
- NENE, MACKY IS TOO HUMAN
TO FORGET SOMETHING
AS IMPORTANT TO HIM AS YOU.
- I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT, LINNA.
- IT'S NOT OVER YET, YOU KNOW.
- NOT UNTIL WE FINISH IT.
- BRING ME THE TOOL BOX.
- UM, NIGEL?
- I DON'T CARE WHETHER
YOU WANT THIS BIKE OR NOT.
IT'S THE ONLY THING
LEFT HERE FOR ME TO FIX.
- I THINK SYLIA
COULD USE YOUR HELP TOO.
SOME PEOPLE
CAN HANDLE BEING ALONE.
BUT YOU KNOW
SHE'S NOT ONE OF THEM.
- ( electrical pulsating )
- ( beeping )
- YEAH, ALMOST THERE.
JUST A LITTLE BIT FURTHER.
COME ON.
COME TO NENE.
- ( computer pings )
- I DID IT!
ROMANOVA THE GIRL GENIUS
STRIKES AGAIN.
GALATEA'S IN ORBIT?
- UM, WHERE'S THE CAMERA?
- OH, IT'S A LIVE FEED
FROM THE N.S.A. SPY SATELLITE.
- THAT'S 30 YEARS.
- FROM THE LOOK OF IT,
GALATEA SEEMS TO BE HEADING
FOR THE UMBRELLA.
- BUT WHY IS SHE GOING THERE?
- THE UMBRELLA IS AN ARRAY
OF ORBITING SOLAR COLLECTORS.
IT WAS THE CENTERPIECE
OF GENOM'S SHOWEN PROJECT.
- Nene: THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT I'M AFRAID GALATEA
INTENDS TO USE IT
FOR A VERY DIFFERENT PURPOSE.
- Priss: SOMEHOW I DON'T THINK
I'M GONNA LIKE THIS.
- Nene: THE SHOWEN PROJECT
WAS DESIGNED
TO FUNNEL CONVERTED SOLAR ENERGY
FROM THE UMBRELLA
INTO THE DRAGON LINE
UNDERGROUND.
THE GENOM TOWER WAS DESIGNED
TO ACT AS THE CONDUIT
BETWEEN THE TWO.
DIDN'T YOU READ THE REPORT
I WROTE FOR SYLIA ABOUT IT?
- ( laughs )
I GUESS I MUST HAVE SKIMMED
THROUGH THE PARTS
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND.
- GALATEA USED THE DRAGON LINE
TO SPREAD THE VOOMER PLAGUE.
- FORTUNATELY WE WERE ABLE
TO CUT IT OFF
BEFORE SHE COULD SEND IT
TO OTHER CITIES.
I'M AFRAID THAT'S THE REASON
SHE'S HEADING FOR THE UMBRELLA.
- WHAT? PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE THINKING WHAT
I THINK YOU'RE THINKING.
- IT'S THE MOST EFFECTIVE WAY,
ISN'T IT?
- MOST EFFECTIVE FOR WHAT?
- TO TRANSMIT THE BOOMER PLAGUE
TO EVERY MACHINE ON THE PLANET.
- ( computer beeps )
- WAIT.
IT LOOKS
LIKE SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
TARGET LOCKED?
- WAIT A SECOND.
IF YOUR FEED
IS AN N.S.A. SPY SATELLITE,
- THAT MUST MEAN--
- UH-HUH.
--THE UNITED STATES
IS LAUNCHING MISSILES.
- IF YOU'RE RIGHT,
THEN THEY'RE USING
NUCLEAR WARHEADS.
- NUCLEAR?!
- ( Linna gasps )
SHE'S ABSORBING THEM.
- SHE CAN STOP THOSE MISSILES
SO EASILY.
MY GOD.
- Nene: I'M TAPPING
INTO THE U.N. DEFENSE GRID.
EVERYONE'S ONLINE.
ALL THE DEFENSE NETS
KNOW THAT THE U.S. NUKES FAILED
AND THEY'RE PUTTING
THEIR OWN LAUNCHES ON HOLD.
- THEY ARE FOR NOW.
BUT FOR HOW LONG?
I CAN TELL YOU
EXACTLY WHAT THEY'LL DO
ONCE THEY FIND OUT
WHAT GALATEA IS UP TO.
- AND WHAT'S THAT?
- THEY'LL TRY TO DESTROY THE
SOURCE OF THE VOOMER INFECTION.
- AND NUKING TOKYO
CUTS THEIR PROBLEMS IN HALF.
- WE'VE GOT TO DESTROY HER
BEFORE SHE GETS US.
- Sylia: YOU KNOW,
FOR THE LONGEST TIME,
ALL I COULD THINK OF
WAS LEAVING THIS TOWN.
MY SINGING WAS GOING
TO TAKE ME ALL OVER THE WORLD.
THEN THIS THING HAPPENED.
I WAS MAKING GOOD MONEY,
KILLING BOOMERS,
AND I KEPT PUTTING IT OFF.
I HAD MY BAGS PACKED
EVERY NIGHT.
BUT I NEVER WENT ANYWHERE.
NOW EVEN THIS PLACE
IS GONE.
- SOMETIMES YOU NEED
A KICK IN THE TEETH
TO GET OUT
OF THE RUT YOU'RE IN.
IT'S LIKE FALLING IN LOVE
WITH SOMEONE WHO'S TAKEN.
AS LONG AS YOU STAY NEAR HER,
YOU CAN'T SEE ANYONE ELSE.
BUT INSTEAD OF BEING SMART
AND WALKING AWAY,
YOU KEEP WAITING FOR SOMETHING
THAT WON'T HAPPEN.
YOU KNOW ACTUALLY,
THE IDEAL SOLUTION
WOULD BE IF YOUR FRIEND SYLIA
WOULD DESIGN A HARDSUIT FOR MEN.
OF COURSE, I'D LOOK
PRETTY STRANGE IN HIGH HEELS.
BUT I THINK I WOULD--
- SHUT UP.
- LOOKS LIKE IT'S SERIOUS NOW.
- I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T THINK LEON-POO WILL
ENJOY BEING HENPECKED.
- ( laughs )
OR WILL HE?
- OKAY, I THINK WE'VE
GOT THIS WORKED OUT WELL ENOUGH.
AHEM.
- HMM?
- HOW LONG
HAVE YOU BEEN STANDING THERE?
- WHAT?  WE CAME OUT HERE FIRST,
REMEMBER?
AND ANYWAY,
WE WERE JUST LEAVING.
IT WAS GETTING TOO ICKY.
- IT WAS NOTHING LIKE THAT.
AND I THOUGHT YOU TWO WERE
WORKING ON A WAY
TO STOP GALATEA.
- YOU KNOW, THE DEFENSE FORCE
HAS ITS OWN MISSILE BASE.
- BUT THERE'S NO WAY
WE'D BE ABLE TO STAGE A LAUNCH
ALL BY OURSELVES.
IN ANY CASE,
I THINK LINNA AND I
CAME UP WITH A BETTER WAY
TO BEAT GALATEA TO THE UMBRELLA.
- HUH?
- Priss: THE SKY HOOK.
SYLIA,
WE'RE GOING AFTER GALATEA.
- Linna: WE'VE GOT TO GO NOW
BEFORE SHE GETS
TO THE UMBRELLA.
WE, UM, WE'LL TRY
TO MAKE YOU PROUD OF US.
- Nene: TAKE CARE OF MACKY
FOR ME.
I MEAN, UNTIL WE GET BACK,
OF COURSE.
WE'LL DEFEAT GALATEA AND GET
MACKY'S MEMORY BACK, SYLIA.
EVERYTHING IS GOING TO BE FINE.
I PROMISE.
- IT'S SO QUIET OUT THERE.
- ( engine revving )
- SO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
- KNOW WHAT?
- THE REASON I USED TO HATE
THE AD POLICE.
I'D BEEN LIVING
ON THE STREETS FOR A WHILE,
AND I WAS SLEEPING
IN THIS OLD FACTORY
WHEN A ROGUE BOOMER
TURNED UP.
- I'M PRETTY SURE I KNOW
WHERE THIS IS GOING.
THE A.D.P. SHOWED UP
AND BLEW THE PLACE TO HELL.
RIGHT?
- IT WAS LIKE THE EARTHQUAKE
ALL OVER AGAIN
WITH ARMORED TRUCKS,
GRENADES AND A ZILLION BULLETS
FLYING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
- THAT SOUNDS PRETTY BAD,
ALL RIGHT.
I GUESS YOU GOT HURT
IN THE CROSSFIRE, HUH?
- I GOT SHOT UP A LITTLE--
BROKEN ARM.
BUT THE THING
THAT MADE IT REALLY BAD
WAS THAT MY DISK
WAS DESTROYED IN THE FIRE.
- A DISK?
- IT HAD MY FAVORITE SONG ON IT.
I USED TO LISTEN TO IT AT NIGHT
AND DREAM OF PERFORMING
IN THIS GIANT STADIUM.
- ( laughs )
THAT IS A PRETTY SILLY REASON,
ISN'T IT?
- ( ball smashes )
- THE SKY HOOK MAKES A REGULAR
SUPPLY RUN TO THE UMBRELLA
FROM THE BOSO PENINSULA.
- BUT THOSE PICKUPS ARE JUST
UNMANNED CARGO PALLETS,
AREN'T THEY?
- YES, THEY ARE.
WHICH MEANS THAT THE SKY HOOK
HAS TO AUTOMATICALLY PICK UP
ANY PALLET IN LINE.
AND THAT MEANS ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS GET ON A PALLET AND--
- Both: FLY INTO SPACE!
- ( chuckles )
- HOW'D IT GO?
- HMM?
- I WAS JUST WONDERING
WHAT THAT SONG SOUNDED LIKE.
I WISH I COULD HAVE
HEARD YOU SING IT.
- ♪ I FEEL YOUR PRESENCE ♪
♪ WHENEVER YOU'RE NEAR ♪
♪ THE SADNESS MELTS
FROM MY HEART ♪
♪ WHEN I'M ALL ALONE ♪
♪ AND I CAN'T GO ON ♪
♪ I FEEL YOU WITH ME ♪
♪ RATHER THAN FOLDING
AND JUST GIVING IN ♪
♪ I SUMMON YOUR STRENGTH
IN MY DREAMS ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN YOUR POWER
TO MAKE ALL THINGS WHOLE ♪
♪ LIKE THE OTHER HALF
OF MY SOUL ♪
♪ YOU GIVE ME THE STRENGTH ♪
♪ TO GO ON. ♪
- AH, SOMETHING'S WRONG!
NENE, THE SLIDER PALLETS ARE
ALREADY MOVING ALONG THE TRACK.
- ( laughs )
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
THOSE PALLETS
CAN'T GO ANYWHERE
UNTIL THE SKY HOOK GRABS THEM
RIGHT-- OH MY GOD!
- PRISS, WE'VE GOT PROBLEMS.
MMM!
THE PALLETS
ARE JUST FALLING IN THE OCEAN!
SOMETHING AT THE END OF THE
PLATFORM MUST NOT BE WORKING.
- Priss: LOOKS LIKE THE BOOMER
PLAGUE BEAT US HERE.
- SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW, PRISS?
- THE SKY HOOK
WILL STILL BE COMING THROUGH,
EVEN IF THERE
AREN'T ANY PALLETS TO PICK UP.
- YOU'RE NOT THINKING WHAT I
THINK YOU'RE THINKING, ARE YOU?
- ( engine revving )
- THE SKY HOOK WILL BE GOING
780 KILOMETERS AN HOUR!
THAT'S REALLY REALLY DANGEROUS.
- THE MOTOSLAVE CAN MATCH IT.
AND OUR HARDSUITS
OUGHT TO BE ENOUGH PROTECTION.
OR DOES ANYONE HERE
HAVE A BETTER IDEA?
- ( engine dying down )
- WELL, DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
WE'RE LEAVING.
- ( revving )
- ( inaudible )
- ( dying down )
- WHAT I SAID
WAS THAT I DON'T EVEN CARE
IF THE WHOLE PLANET
TURNS INTO A BOOMER.
JUST REMEMBER THAT YOU
PROMISED ME YOU'D COME BACK.
SO DO IT!
- LEON-POO CERTAINLY SOUNDED
PUT OUT ABOUT BEING LEFT BEHIND.
- HE ALWAYS SOUNDS PUT OUT
ABOUT SOMETHING.
- JUST SHUT UP AND HOLD ON.
HERE WE GO!
- ROGER!
- LET'S DO IT!
- Priss: ROCK AND ROLL!
JEEZ, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU TWO WERE SO HEAVY.
- FOR THE SAKE
OF OUR FRIENDSHIP,
I'M ASSUMING YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT OUR HARDSUITS.
- UH, YEAH.
- Both: BETTER.
- Linna: THERE'S AN OPEN HATCH!
- Nene: AH, COME IN,
COME IN, COME IN!
CAN'T YOU GO ANY FASTER, PRISS?
- I'M TRYING!
COME ON, MOTOSLAVE,
FORGET EVERYTHING I EVER
SAID ABOUT BOOMERS.
JUST DO THIS THING!
- ( revving )
- Linna: WE'RE ALMOST THERE!
ONLY A COUPLE OF FEET MORE.
- Nene: COME ON, PRISS!
YOU CAN DO IT!
- All: AH!
- WE'RE TOO HEAVY!
- LINNA, FIRE YOUR BLASTER!
- ( moans )
LINNA, WAKE UP, SLEEPING BEAUTY.
- UH, WHAT?
WAS THAT A KISS?
NO FRIGGIN' WAY.
- HOW ABOUT YOU, NENE?
- I'M FINE,
BUT I'LL PASS ON THE KISS.
- ( chuckles )
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
GONNA GO AROUND THE WORLD
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT.
- SPEAKING OF WHICH, WE'D
BETTER SEE IF WE CAN GET INSIDE.
IF I RECALL CORRECTLY,
OUR SUITS CAN GENERATE
SOME OXYGEN CHEMICALLY,
BUT THEY CAN'T DO IT FOREVER.
- YOU READY?
- WHO, ME?  SURE.
- AH!
- DON'T SHOOT!
- NOBODY IS ALLOWED TO
RIDE THIS SHUTTLE
WITHOUT SPECIAL PERMISSION.
I SHALL HAVE TO REPORT
YOUR PRESENCE
TO THE OPERATIONS CENTER.
- LOOKS LIKE THE BOOMER PLAGUE
HASN'T GOT THIS FAR YET.
- SINCE THE PALLETS
WERE FALLING IN THE OCEAN,
THERE WAS NO WAY FOR IT
TO SPREAD TO THE SKY HOOK.
LOOKS LIKE GALATEA SCREWED UP.
- DON'T WORRY, MR. BOOMER.
WE ALL HAVE TICKETS
SO IT'S OKAY THAT WE'RE HERE.
- OH, WELL, IN THAT CASE,
PLEASE RELAX
AND ENJOY YOUR TRIP.
YOU SHOULD HAVE JUST SAID SO
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
NOT!
DO I LOOK DEFECTIVE TO YOU?
- WAIT A SECOND,
MR. BOOMER POO.
HAVE YOU HEARD FROM ANYONE
IN THE OPERATIONS CENTER LATELY?
MAYBE YOUR RECEIVER IS FAULTY.
- ACTUALLY, I HAVEN'T
RECEIVED A PICK-UP ORDER
IN NEARLY A WEEK.
GOODNESS GRACIOUS,
ARE YOU SAYING
THAT I'VE BEEN
IGNORING PROPER ORDERS?
- OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE'RE HERE TO GIVE YOU
YOUR NEW ORDERS PERSONALLY.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- LOOK AT THE STARS.
I'VE NEVER SEEN THEM
LOOK SO BRIGHT.
- THAT'S BECAUSE THERE'S NO
ATMOSPHERE TO MAKE THEM TWINKLE.
- JEEZ,
DOESN'T THE FACT THAT WE'RE IN
OUTER SPACE WORRY YOU AT ALL?
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
- I'VE DREAMED OF THIS
FOR YEARS.
BACK WHEN I WAS A KID,
I WANTED TO BECOME AN ASTRONAUT
IN THE WORST WAY POSSIBLE.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU?
IT CERTAINLY CAN'T BE
BECAUSE YOU WEREN'T SMART ENOUGH
TO PASS THE ENTRANCE EXAMS.
- THAT'S NOT
WHERE I CAME UP SHORT, LINNA.
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THE INTERNATIONAL SPACE AGENCY
HAS A HEIGHT REQUIREMENT?
- BUT YOU MADE YOUR DREAM
COME TRUE ANYWAY.
- I GUESS I DID.
SO WHAT'S YOUR DREAM, LINNA?
- WHAT?
UH, YOU MEAN NOW?
WELL, I USED TO DREAM
ABOUT BECOMING A KNIGHT SABER,
BUT SINCE I'VE DONE THAT,
I MAINLY DREAM
ABOUT STAYING ALIVE, I GUESS.
- ( both laugh )
- UH, WHERE DID PRISS GO?
- SHE'S GONE.
- UM, HEY.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU
YOU DID GOOD.
EVEN THOUGH YOU
LOOK LIKE A BIKE,
I KNOW YOU'RE REALLY A BOOMER.
I'M SORRY
YOU GOT ALL BANGED UP LIKE THIS.
IT'S KIND OF WEIRD
TALKING TO YOU.
MAYBE IF WE'D ALL TRIED
TO COMMUNICATE A LITTLE BETTER,
WE WOULDN'T BE IN THE SITUATION
WE'RE IN NOW.
GOD KNOWS WE HUMANS
AREN'T THE EASIEST PEOPLE
TO GET ALONG WITH.
AND TO BE HONEST, I GUESS
I'VE GOT A GUILTY CONSCIENCE.
FOR ALL THE BITCHING
AND MOANING I'VE DONE,
YOU AND MY HARDSUIT
HAVE NEVER LET ME DOWN.
THANKS.
- ( beeping )
- Nene: FOUR MORE HOURS
UNTIL WE ARRIVE AT THE UMBRELLA.
- AND WHERE IS GALATEA?
- I CAN TELL YOU IN A SECOND.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MA'AM?
- HOOKING YOU
INTO THE N.S.A. NET.
- Both: HMM?
- FORTUNATELY FOR US,
THAT ANTI-GRAVITY DRIVE OF HERS
IS PRETTY SLOW.
I GUESS IT'S A GOOD THING
GENOM DIDN'T MAKE MISSILES.
- WE WILL GET THERE
BEFORE GALATEA, WON'T WE?
- IF WE DON'T, THEN
GOD ONLY KNOWS
HOW WE'RE GOING TO STOP HER.
- I KNOW THAT'S RIGHT.
- Boomer: EXCUSE ME?
BUT WHO IS THIS GALATEA?
IS SHE A NEW EXECUTIVE
IN CHARGE OF BOOMERS?
- THAT'S PRETTY CLOSE, ACTUALLY.
WAY TOO CLOSE.
AND IF SHE BEATS US THERE,
SHE'LL BECOME SOMETHING
MORE LIKE A GOD.
- ( Galatea laughing )
- ( static )
- JUST LOOK AT ALL THE STARS.
UP HERE BEYOND THE ATMOSPHERE,
THEY LOOK SO CLOSE
THAT YOU COULD REACH UP
AND TOUCH THEM.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040,"
AS GALATEA
ABSORBS THE SHOWEN PROJECT,
THE SABERS ARE CAUGHT
IN A DEADLY COUNTDOWN.
IF SUNLIGHT
STRIKES THE SOLAR COLLECTORS,
THE VOOMER PLAGUE
WILL BE TRANSMITTED
TO EVERY MACHINE ON EARTH.
AS THE SECONDS COUNT OFF,
THE KNIGHT SABERS
MUST STEEL THEMSELVES
FOR THE ULTIMATE CONFRONTATION
WITH BOTH GALATEA
AND THEIR OWN DOPPELGANGERS.
NEXT EPISODE,
"WALKING ON THE MOON."