- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( screeching )
- ( signal sounding )
- COME ON!
ISN'T THIS CLOSE ENOUGH YET?
- A FEW MORE YARDS.
OKAY, NOW!
- ( both shouting )
- I GUESS WE GOT IT.
- ( screeching )
- WHY WON'T IT DIE?
IT SHOULD HAVE DIED AS SOON
AS THEY DESTROYED ITS CORE.
- MAYDAY!  MAYDAY!
- ( static )
- PREP ME FOR LAUNCH.
- OH.  BUT YOU WON'T
HAVE ANY SUPPORT.
- NIGEL, WHERE DID YOU HIDE
THE BATTERY IN THESE NEW SUITS?
- IT'S INTEGRATED
THROUGHOUT THE HARDSUIT'S BODY.
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE CHARGED UP.
- THEN PREP HER SUIT
FOR LAUNCH, DAMN IT!
AND MAKE ONE FOR ME.
- UH...
- ( screeching )
- WHY DIDN'T THAT THING DIE?
- WELL, I'D SAY THAT
EITHER IT'S GOT ANOTHER CORE,
OR IT'S EVOLVED
TO BE ABLE TO OPERATE
WITHOUT A CENTRAL
POWER STRUCTURE.
- UGH!
BUT IF THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENING,
HOW IN THE HELL
CAN WE STOP IT?
- ( screeching )
- WHAT NOW?
- THAT'S IT.
- AH!  THE SKY HOOK!
IT'S STILL FEEDING POWER
INTO THE DRAGON LINE.
- YEAH, I THINK SO.
- ( screeching )
- IT'S DRAGGING THOSE CONDUITS
FROM THE DRAGON LINE.
THAT'S WHERE IT'S GETTING
ITS POWER FROM, ISN'T IT?
- ( screeching )
- ( exploding )
- ( all grunting )
- ( screeching )
- LINNA?
HEY!
- HUH?
- YOU'VE GOT TO SEVER THOSE
CONDUITS FROM THE DRAGON LINE!
THAT'S WHAT'S GIVING IT
ITS POWER!
IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO KILL IT.
- RIGHT!
THANK YOU, OFFICER.
HA!
- WHAT A SUIT!
I WANT ONE TOO!
- ( light chattering )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW,
GALATEA?
- ( chattering )
- SPEAK ENGLISH! I DON'T
UNDERSTAND THAT LANGUAGE.
DON'T FORGET,
I WAS THE ONE WHO RESCUED YOU
FROM SYLIA STINGRAY.
AND ALL I ASKED IN RETURN
IS FOR YOU
TO MAKE MY VISION COME TRUE.
I WANT TO WATCH AS YOU CHANGE
THIS WORLD, GALATEA.
- YOU WANT TO BE GOD,
DON'T YOU?
- HUH?  ( chuckles )
YES,
I THINK THAT YOU ARE RIGHT.
BUT WHAT KIND OF GOD?
THAT'S THE QUESTION.
NOT A WEAK, PATHETIC GOD WHO
SIMPLY SITS BACK AND WATCHES,
BUT A GOD WHO PASSES JUDGMENT,
A GOD WHO CORRECTS THE MISTAKES
OF A MILLION YEARS OF EVOLUTION.
BUT IF I AM GOD, THEN WHAT DOES
THAT MAKE YOU?
- A CHILD OF MAN.
- HUH?
( laughs )
WELL, IT'S TRUE THAT A MAN
CREATED YOUR SEED.
AND THAT SEED WAS BORN
FROM THE FLESH OF A WOMAN
WHO WAS WITHOUT SIN.
BUT STINGRAY IMPLANTED YOU
INTO THE BODY OF HIS DAUGHTER
MERELY BECAUSE
IT WAS CONVENIENT.
YOU COULD HAVE BEEN CREATED
IN OTHER WAYS AS WELL.
- AND WHAT OF THE SEED
IN YOUR OWN BODY?
- IT HAS NEVER GROWN.
MY BODY CONSUMED IT.
BUT THE EMBRYONIC BOOMER CORE
I IMPLANTED IN MYSELF
WAS NOT LIKE YOURS WAS,
THOUGH I HAD HOPED
IT WOULD FIX MY HUMAN FAILINGS.
- WHY DO YOU REJECT
WHAT YOU ARE?
- AH?
- WHY DOES EVEN THE SISTER
WHO BORE ME
REJECT MY EXISTENCE?
- GALATEA, WAIT!
( gasps )
AH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO ME?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TO MY BODY?
AH!  OH MY GOD, GALATEA!
PLEASE!
- ( machinery clanking )
- Priss:
ISN'T THAT A LITTLE LARGE?
- WELL, IT HAS TO BE THAT BIG.
WE COMPRESSED THEM.
- YEAH, WELL, SAY WHAT YOU WILL.
THEY LOOK WEIRD.
- THEY LOOK STRANGE,
BUT THEY KICK MAJOR BUTT.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN THE WAY
LINNA TOOK OUT THAT GIANT BOOMER
ALL BY HERSELF YESTERDAY.
- THEY BEAT THE OLD SUITS
IN ALMOST EVERY WAY.
BUT THEY ARE EMBARRASSING.
- EMBARRASSING?
- HEY, MACKY?
- HUH?
- YOU AND NIGEL ARE GOING
TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THAT LITTLE ISSUE,
AREN'T YOU?
- JUST WHAT
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- ( whispering )
- MMM, MMM.  WHAT?!
YOU MEAN LIKE TOTALLY NAKED?!
NO WAY!
- ( beeping )
- WHERE IS NIGEL?
- UM, WELL, HE AND SYLIA
ARE HAVING A TALK UPSTAIRS.
- MMM.
- YOU KNOW I APPRECIATE
ALL YOU'VE DONE.
- IT'S MY JOB.
JUST LIKE IT WAS MY JOB
TO ASSIST YOUR FATHER.
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- THERE IS NO MEANING.
- ARE YOU TELLING ME YOU THINK
I'VE ONLY BEEN USING YOU?
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
OUR WORK AND THE FEELINGS I HAVE
FOR YOU ARE SEPARATE THINGS.
THAT'S NOT TO SAY THAT
I DON'T RESPECT
YOUR SKILLS AND ABILITIES.
BUT I THOUGHT
THAT WHAT WE SHARED
WAS MORE
THAN A MATTER OF CONVENIENCE.
I THOUGHT I MEANT SOMETHING
TO YOU.
WAS I JUST ONE MORE MACHINE
YOU HAD TO SERVICE?
OR IS THAT HOW YOU THINK
I FEEL ABOUT YOU?
THAT'S NOT HOW I FEEL.
NIGEL, I--
I LOVE YOU.
- SYLIA,
THE NEW HARDSUITS
MAY USE NEW TECHNOLOGY,
BUT THEY'RE STILL BASED
ON YOUR ORIGINAL BIO-DATA.
MACKY AND I
BUILT A NEW SUIT FOR YOU,
AS YOU REQUESTED.
BUT I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD PUT IT ON.
I THINK YOU SHOULD RETIRE.
YOU'VE CHANGED TOO MUCH,
SYLIA.
YOU'RE NOT THE GIRL
THAT YOU WERE ANYMORE.
AND THE FEEDBACK FROM YOUR SUIT
COULD CAUSE PERMANENT DAMAGE.
- THANK YOU
FOR CARING ABOUT ME.
- ( engine revving )
- ( alarm sounding )
- AHHH!
GAL-- GALATEA!
( grunting )
WHAT DID YOU DO TO ME?
- I HAVE KEPT THE PROMISE
THAT I MADE YOU.
I HAVE PUT YOU THERE
SO YOU CAN WATCH
AS I CHANGE THE WORLD.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
- THERE ARE DRAGONS IN THE EARTH
AND I SHALL SET THEM FREE.
- ARE YOU INSANE?
UNLEASH THE DRAGON LINE?
- ( chuckles )
- ( deep rumbling )
- ( distant chattering )
- HMM?
- ( chattering )
- ( chuckling )
- ( all chattering )
- AHH!
- ( grunting )
- ( laughing )
AH!
- ( all grunting )
- I'M TOO OLD TO PLAY
WITH LITTLE CLOWNS LIKE YOU.
- ( laughing )
- ( grunts )
- ( all laughing, chattering )
AH!
AHH!
- ( laughs )
- ( gun fires several times )
- ( gasps )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- UH... UH-HUH.
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
- WHY IS IT
THAT WHENEVER I RUN INTO YOU,
YOU'RE ALWAYS IN TROUBLE
AND WEARING SOMETHING REVEALING?
- UGH!  PUT YOUR TONGUE
BACK IN YOUR MOUTH, JERK!
- SURE YOU DON'T NEED
TO GO SEE A DOCTOR?
- I'M FINE.
- IT'S NICE TO SEE
THAT YOU OWN SOMETHING
THAT'S NOT MADE OF LEATHER.
SO JUST WHAT IS IT WITH THE
URBAN COMBAT LOOK ANYWAY?
( gulps )
AND LEON THE DORK PUTS HIS FOOT
IN HIS MOUTH AGAIN.
- Priss: ISN'T THERE ANYBODY
LEFT IN TOWN?
- NO, THE WHOLE PLACE
IS SHUT DOWN.
- JESUS.
- WELL, GIANT MAN-EATING ROBOTS
TEND TO SCARE MOST PEOPLE.
- ( static )
- AND BESIDES--
- WHAT KIND OF SOLDIERS
ARE THOSE?
- U.N. R.D.F. TROOPS.
THEY'RE TRYING TO CUT TOKYO OFF
FROM THE REST OF JAPAN
TO KEEP THE BOOMER PLAGUE
FROM SPREADING.
- ( beeps )
- ( grunts )
LEON, JUST WHAT
ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT?
- SHHH.
- ( signal sounding )
- ( sighs )
- There you are!
We need you at the pit.
- UH, I'M KIND OF--
- What? Is somebody there?
- UGH!
NO, NOBODY!
I JUST DON'T FEEL
LIKE COMING IN RIGHT NOW.
- You what?
- Ah!
Damn it, we don't have time
to argue about this!
This thing's huge--
Godzilla sized!
- HUH?
- ( rumbling )
( metal creaking )
- I'M AFRAID WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO WAIT FOR PRISS TO GET HERE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE REASON THAT
GALATEA WOULD SHIFT
SO MUCH POWER TO ONE SECTION
OF THE DRAGON LINE
AND THAT PART OF THE CITY.
SHE'S GOING TO TRY
TO BREAK THROUGH THE BLOCKADE.
- UM, LINNA, I HAVEN'T
DONE THIS BEFORE, BUT--
- AH!  MACKY?
- YEAH?
- CAN'T YOU DO THAT
BY REMOTE CONTROL?
- HUH?
- RUN ALONG, MACKY.
REMEMBER
WHAT HAPPENED LAST TIME.
- AHH!  OH, THAT'S RIGHT!
I WAS JUST LEAVING!
AHHHH!
- ( all chuckle )
- ( motor revving )
- SO WHERE IS YOUR PARTNER?
- I DON'T KNOW.
ON HIS WAY HOME, I HOPE.
THE AD POLICE
HAS BEEN DISSOLVED.
WE RECEIVED ORDERS
TO PULL OUT.
- FIGURES.
SO WHY ARE YOU STILL HERE?
- BECAUSE I'M DUMB
AND STUBBORN.
BUT AT LEAST YOU HAVE A REASON,
RIGHT?
- UH, WELL, TO BE HONEST,
NOT REALLY.
- SO WHY DO YOU HATE BOOMERS
SO MUCH?
I'D LIKE TO KNOW.
- IT'S KIND OF EMBARRASSING.
- NOW I'M REALLY CURIOUS.
- STOP TALKING AND DRIVE!
- ( chuckles )
- Sylia: ALL RIGHT, NENE,
STEP INTO THE SUIT FRAME.
- HMM?
- ( pop song playing )
- HMM?  OH.
- ( machines whirring )
- EEK.
- Sylia: ALL RIGHT, MACKY,
START POURING.
- THIS PART'S
A LITTLE DISGUSTING.
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- ( gurgling )
- EW!
WHAT IS THIS?
- Sylia: INNER METAL.
IT'S WHAT
BONDS EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
- THIS REALLY IS DISGUSTING!
- JUST DON'T GET IT
IN YOUR MOUTH.
- OKAY, HOLD IT THERE, MACKY.
- NOW THINK.
- THINK OF WHAT?
- YOU NEED A MENTAL
CHARM TO LINK THE HARDSUIT
TO YOUR BRAIN STEM.
- SAY THAT AGAIN,
IN ENGLISH THIS TIME.
- IT'S KIND OF LIKE
A COMPUTER PASSCODE, NENE.
YOU'RE TUNING THE INNER METAL
TO RESPOND
TO THE MENTAL COMMANDS
THAT YOUR BRAIN IS SENDING
THROUGH THE SUIT FRAME.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
JUST WATCH WHAT I DO, NENE.
I WANT TO BE STRONGER.
I WANT TO JUMP HIGHER.
- OH, WOW.
RIGHT, LET'S SEE.
I WANT TO BE AN INCREDIBLE
SHINY KNIGHT SABER.
AH!  HEY, WAIT!
( garbled )
OH, SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
- KNIGHT SABERS,
PREPARE FOR ACTION.
- ( electricity booming )
- Macky:
WELL, THERE THEY GO AGAIN.
- I DID TRY TO STOP THEM.
- MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE TRIED
TO STOP THEM TOO.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER, KID.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
A WASTE OF TIME.
- NIGEL?
YOU'RE GOING TO STAY HERE
AND HELP SYLIA, RIGHT?
I DON'T--
I'M NOT SURE IF I'M GOING TO BE
ABLE TO STAY HERE MUCH LONGER.
SO I WAS HOPING
THAT YOU MIGHT BE STAYING HERE
BECAUSE-- BECAUSE SYLIA NEEDS
SOMEONE TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NOTHING'S GOING TO CHANGE
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
MY LIFE SEEMS TO BE LIKE THAT.
- PRISS!
- ( panting )
- MACKY, GET MY SUIT READY!
- SO HOW DID YOU GET
ALL THOSE CUTS?
- ( door whirring )
- UM, THEY LOOK
LIKE TEETH MARKS.
- ( rumbling )
- Linna: WHAT IN THE HELL
ARE THOSE THINGS?
- YOU MEAN BESIDES DISGUSTING?!
- Sylia: THE DRAGON LINE IS
SPREADING THE BOOMER PHENOMENON
INTO EVERYTHING IT TOUCHES.
IT WON'T STOP GROWING AS LONG
AS THERE ARE MORE BOOMERS
AND ELECTRONIC COMPONENTS
TO ABSORB.
- ( rumbling )
- All: OH!
- ( screeching )
- Linna: MY GOD!
LOOK AT THE SIZE OF THAT THING!
- OH, COME ON, LINNA!
YOU FINISHED OFF THAT BIG BOOMER
THE OTHER DAY
ALL BY YOURSELF.
WITH THREE OF US, THIS SHOULD BE
A PIECE OF CAKE. LET'S DO IT!
- Both: RIGHT.
- HA!
HUH?
- HYAH!
- NENE, YOUR TURN!
- ATTACK!  HYAH!
- DO I KICK ASS OR WHAT?
- WATCH OUT!
- UH-OH.
- ( grunts )
- I'M NOT GOING TO LET YOU
WIN THIS BATTLE, GALATEA.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
- ( distant chattering )
- I'LL STOP YOU IF I HAVE TO
DESTROY EVERY BOOMER IN TOKYO.
DO YOU HEAR ME, GALATEA?!
- Voice: Señores y señoras,
nosotros...
( continues, indistinct )
- AH!
AH AH!
MAYDAY!
- Female voice:
Señores y señoras...
- HOLD ON!
- AH!
- ( grunting )  OH!
- LINNA!
- ( grunting )
- Macky ( filtered ):
Those cuts look bad, Priss.
- JUST DO IT, MACKY.
- I understand.
- AHHH!
- ( both screaming )
- LINNA!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
Narrator: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040,"
AS THE KNIGHT SABERS CONTINUE TO
BATTLE THE MUTATED DRAGON LINE,
THE BOOMER OVERMIND
PLOTS A NEW PLAN OF ATTACK
TO DESTROY ITS ENEMIES
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
THE SABERS' LAST SANCTUARY
IS THE TARGET
OF A BIO-MECHANICAL TERROR,
A LIVING WAVE OF
METAL AND MALICE
THAT STRIKES WITHOUT WARNING.
HUMAN AND MACHINE
FACE MACHINE AND MONSTER
AS THE CITY OF TOKYO FALLS PRAY
TO GALATEA'S ONSLAUGHT.
NEXT EPISODE...