- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( door opens )
- I'D LIKE TO SEE
DR. SHAN.
OH!
- HMM?
- UM, I'M SORRY.
- IT WAS ALREADY BROKEN.
MAKES IT HARD
TO SNEAK IN.
- UH, WELL I CAME HERE
TO VISIT DR. SHAN.
- THE WIND MASTER?
JUST GO THROUGH THAT DOOR.
IF THE DOCTOR
FEELS LIKE TALKING TO YOU,
HE'LL MAKE SURE YOU END UP
IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
- OH, REALLY?
- YOU'RE NOT CHICKEN,
ARE YOU?
I WOULDN'T WORRY TOO MUCH.
THE DOC'S OLD,
BUT HE WOULDN'T PASS UP
A CHANCE TO GET
A CLOSER LOOK AT YOU.
- UM, THANKS, I THINK.
DR. SHAN?
ARE YOU IN HERE?
- ( crashing )
- ( chuckles )
DR. SHAN?
- HMM.
MY, IT CERTAINLY HAS
BEEN A LONG TIME.
I'M AFRAID I CAN'T
REALLY CALL YOU
MY LITTLE LADY ANYMORE,
CAN I, MISS STINGRAY?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU ACTUALLY RECOGNIZED ME.
- HOW COULD I FORGET SOMEONE
WHO WAS SO IMPORTANT TO US?
NOW WHAT IS IT
THAT BRINGS YOU HERE?
TO BE HONEST, I HAVE SOME
QUESTIONS THAT NEED ANSWERING.
- I'M SURE YOU MUST.
WHY ELSE WOULD YOU
VISIT SOMEONE
WHO WAS A PART OF
THAT DISTASTEFUL BUSINESS?
BELIEVE ME, MY CHILD,
I'M QUITE GLAD FOR
MY CHANCE AT ATONEMENT.
- AND I'M EQUALLY GLAD
THAT YOU FEEL THAT WAY.
YOU SEE, I HAVE
REASON TO BELIEVE
THAT SOMEONE IS TRYING
TO DIG UP SOMETHING
THAT SHOULD BE LEFT BURIED.
- YOU MEAN BRIAN J. MASON.
- ( gasps )
SO YOU KNOW?
- HOW COULD I NOT?
GENOM HAS BEEN DIGGING
THEIR LITTLE EARTHWORM HOLES
BENEATH THE CITY
FOR QUITE AWHILE NOW.
BECAUSE OF THAT,
THE NATURAL FLOW OF ENERGY
THROUGH THE EARTH'S CRUST
HAS BEEN CONSTANTLY
DISRUPTED.
IT'S ALL PART OF A PROJECT
THEY CALL "THE DRAGON LINE."
- SO MASON IS USING
THAT PROJECT AS A COVER
TO CONCEAL HIS SEARCH
FOR THE WIZ LAB.
- YES.  HE IS INDEED
SEARCHING FOR THE LAB.
BUT ALTHOUGH HE KEEPS
DIGGING EXPLORATORY HOLES,
HE KEEPS MISSING
THE TARGET.
- MISSING THE TARGET?
THEN YOU MUST KNOW...
- NO, I DON'T.
NOT EXACTLY ANYWAY.
THE CATACLYSM CAUSED
A COMPLETE RESHIFTING
OF THE UNDERGROUND MASS.
EVEN MORE SO THAN WAS
INDICATED ON THE SURFACE.
HOWEVER, I'VE BEEN ABLE
TO RECONSTRUCT
THE GENERAL PATTERN
OF THAT EVENT.
- HMM.  I SEE.
- YOU CAME TO ASK ME HOW TO
FIND THE LAB, DIDN'T YOU?
- YES.
- AND WHAT IS IT THAT YOU
INTEND TO DO WITH IT
ONCE IT'S FOUND?
- I'LL DO WHAT
I HAVE TO DO.
THE THINGS IN THAT LAB MUST
REMAIN LOCKED AWAY FOREVER
OUT OF THE REACH OF
MANIACS LIKE MASON.
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
- HMM.
I WONDER HOW DR. STINGRAY
WOULD FEEL ABOUT THAT.
- DOCTOR?!
- I'M SORRY.
A POOR CHOICE OF WORDS.
I BEG YOUR FORGIVENESS,
MY DEAR.
I WOULD BE QUITE HAPPY
TO ASSIST YOU.
PLEASE, DO BE SEATED.
- ( sighs )
- I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST COULDN'T
FEEL THE BIKE
HANDLING THE SURFACE
OF THE ROAD, YOU KNOW?
- AT LEAST YOUR TIRES
ARE STILL OKAY FOR NOW.
BUT THREE NEW PARTS
AND THE SUSPENSION,
PLUS SWAPPING OUT
A CHAMBER.
IT WON'T BE CHEAP.
- LIFE'S A BITCH.
- OH, NENE!
YOU'RE HERE.
- HI, GUYS.
- GREAT.
WHY'S SHE HERE?
NO, DON'T TELL ME.
- I WAS JUST PASSING BY,
SO I THOUGHT I'D DROP IN.
- OH, THAT'S GREAT, NENE.
HEY, AS LONG AS YOU'RE HERE,
CAN YOU TEACH ME HOW TO DO
THAT OVERRIDE PATCH
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT?
- UM, NOT RIGHT NOW.
ACTUALLY, PRISS?
I WAS HOPING I COULD
TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND.
PLEASE?  SORRY, MACKY.
NEXT TIME, I PROMISE.
- ( sighs )
- AS YOU CAN SEE,
THE PATTERN OF MASON'S
DRAGON EXCAVATIONS
MAY SEEM FAIRLY COMPREHENSIVE
ON THE SURFACE.
- BUT?
- BUT MASON'S CALCULATIONS
OBVIOUSLY HAVE NOT
CORRECTLY ESTIMATED
HOW THE UNDERGROUND STRATA
WERE DISPLACED DURING THE EVENT.
AS HE IS OBVIOUSLY
BASING HIS EXCAVATIONS
ON SURFACE OBSERVATIONS,
HIS CHANCES OF ACTUALLY
FINDING THE LAB'S LOCATION
ARE VERY SLIM.
- BUT IF HE KEEPS ON DIGGING--
- YES, HE WILL FIND IT
EVENTUALLY, I'M AFRAID.
BUT IF WE COMBINE OUR KNOWLEDGE
OF THE UNDERGROUND FLOW
WITH THE EXCAVATIONS
MASON HAS MADE,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO
ASCERTAIN THE PROBABLE
LOCATION OF THE LAB.
CAN YOUR PEOPLE
HANDLE IT FROM THERE?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- THEN LET'S GET DOWN
TO BUSINESS, SHALL WE?
I BELIEVE MY ASSOCIATES
CAN HELP US ELIMINATE
A FEW MORE OF
THE VARIABLES,
BUT IT WILL
TAKE SOME TIME.
- I'M IN YOUR DEBT, SIR.
- NO, IT'S SOMETHING
I'VE OWED YOU
EVER SINCE I BECAME A PART
OF YOUR FATHER' AMBITIONS.
I'M AN OLD MAN WHO IS
ALL TOO AWARE
OF HIS IMPENDING MORTALITY.
I'VE DONE MUCH WRONG.
NOW I MUST ATONE.
- THANK YOU, SIR.
- HERE.
- UM, THANKS.
OKAY, I'M LISTENING.
- UM, JUST HOW MUCH
DO YOU KNOW ABOUT
SYLIA'S BACKGROUND?
- IS IT IMPORTANT?
- WELL, MAYBE NOT,
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND,
IT COULD BE.
- LET'S SEE. YOU MET HER ABOUT
THE SAME TIME I DID, RIGHT?
THE FIRST TIME I SAW HER
WAS WHEN I WAS HAVING
A DISAGREEMENT WITH
SOME COPS AT A ROAD BLOCK.
SHE APPROACHED ME
A LITTLE WHILE AFTER THAT.
- I SEE.
WHAT I WAS WONDERING
WAS WHETHER SHE'D EVER TOLD YOU
ABOUT HER PAST OR CHILDHOOD?
- NOT REALLY.
IS ALL THIS GOING SOMEPLACE?
- WELL, THE THING IS,
I'M WONDERING
WHY SYLIA CREATED
THE KNIGHT SABERS
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- UH-HUH.
- I WAS WONDERING EXACTLY
HOW HER FATHER FIT INTO IT.
- HER FATHER?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
ALMOST ALL THE ORIGINAL
BOOMER TECHNOLOGY PATENTS
WERE IN HIS NAME.
- YEAH?
- WELL, SYLIA REALLY
HATES BOOMERS, DOESN'T SHE?
IS IT BECAUSE HER FATHER
CREATED THEM,
OR IS THERE SOME
OTHER REASON?
- NENE, WHY ARE YOU
SUDDENLY SO CURIOUS?
- HASN'T IT EVER
WORRIED YOU?
WELL, NEVER MIND.
I WAS JUST WONDERING,
THAT'S ALL.
- NIGEL,
ABOUT PROFESSOR MASON--
- I TOLD YOU NOT
TO WORRY ABOUT IT.
- BUT, NIGEL...
SYLIA.
- GOOD AFTERNOON, NIGEL.
I HAVE SOMETHING I NEED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
- RIGHT.
WE CAN TALK IN THERE.
MACKY,
FINISH UP OUT HERE.
- Nene: HMM.
"DR. STEVEN STINGRAY.
CREATOR OF BOOMER
AND VOOMER TECHNOLOGY.
KILLED IN THE TOKYO EARTHQUAKE
SEVEN YEARS AGO."
- ( beeping )
- HUH?
HMM.
PASS CODE.
ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
THAT'S THE TICKET.
I'M SO GOOD,
IT SCARES ME SOMETIMES.
HUH?  WHAT?
NO WAY.  IT CAN'T BE.
- ( beeping )
- ( sighs )
JUST AS I SUSPECTED.
THAT CREATURE WAS AN OFFSHOOT
OF MY FATHER'S EXPERIMENTS.
- ( dings )
- IT MUST HAVE BEEN
PART OF THE RESEARCH
THAT LED UP TO THE CREATION
OF THE CORE PROTOTYPE.
- I BROUGHT THE THINGS
YOU ASKED FOR.
- OH, THANK YOU, NIGEL.
- DO YOU HAVE EVERYTHING
SET UP FOR THE TEST?
- YES, IT'S READY TO GO.
JUST PUT IT ON
THE TABLE, PLEASE.
- WHAT NOW?
- WE'LL USE THE RADAR
AND SONAR TOGETHER.
I'M SETTING IT UP NOW.
IF MY HUNCH IS CORRECT,
THAT MONSTER WAS ABLE
TO LOCATE BOOMERS
BY BROADCASTING A SERIES
OF ELECTROMAGNETIC PULSES
THAT TRIGGERED A SPECIFIC
SERIES OF SONIC VIBRATIONS
IT COULD SENSE
THROUGH THE GROUND.
WE KNOW THE FREQUENCY
IT USED TO DISABLE THE BOOMERS,
SO LET'S TRY THIS.
- ( powering on )
- I'D SAY YOU GUESSED
CORRECTLY, RIGHT?
- YES.  SO IT WOULD APPEAR.
THIS OUGHT TO MAKE
THE TASK OF FINDING THE LAB
A LOT SIMPLER.
- UNFORTUNATELY,
THE EFFECTIVE RANGE
OF THAT HANDHELD EMP CANNON
IS BARELY 300 METERS.
IT WOULD TAKE 10 YEARS
TO COVER ALL OF TOKYO THAT WAY.
- NOT QUITE.
UTILIZING THE WIND MASTER'S
DATA,
WE CAN NARROW OUR SELECTION
OF POSSIBLE SEARCH
AREAS CONSIDERABLY.
THERE ARE 27 TARGET ZONES
THAT WE'LL BE FOCUSING ON.
AND THANKS TO MASON,
MOST OF THEM SHOULD BE
ACCESSIBLE THROUGH
THE TUNNEL SYSTEM.
I THINK THE GIRLS AND I
CAN MANAGE THAT.
- TRUE, BUT EVEN ASSUMING
THAT YOU MANAGE TO FIND IT,
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO WITH IT?
- ACTUALLY, GENOM HAS PROVIDED
THE FINAL SOLUTION THEMSELVES.
- GENOM?
IF THEY COULDN'T HANDLE IT
SEVEN YEARS AGO,
WHAT CAN THEY POSSIBLY
DO AGAINST IT NOW?
- IT'S AN APPLICATION
OF TECHNOLOGY
THAT WASN'T AVAILABLE
SEVEN YEARS AGO.
I CAME UP WITH IT AFTER
GOING OVER DR. SHAN'S DATA.
AND THIS TIME,
I'M GOING TO ELIMINATE
THE ROOT OF THE PROBLEM.
- THAT'S THE 1:00 EXPRESS.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
HEAD BACK SOON.
- MM-HMM.  OH WELL.
I GUESS WE'VE
PLAYED HOOKY LONG ENOUGH.
- I'M GLAD YOU
TOLD ME ABOUT THIS.
I KNEW NENE
WAS ACTING ODD,
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW WHY.
- WELL, HOPEFULLY SHE'LL
BE ABLE TO WORK IT OUT
BY HERSELF.
- ( engine revs )
- DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
ASK SYLIA ABOUT THIS?
I KNOW IT WOULD SEEM
LIKE WE'RE PRYING,
BUT TO BE HONEST,
I THINK NENE MIGHT
BE ONTO SOMETHING.
- HUH?
- WELL, JUST WHY DID SYLIA
START THE KNIGHT SABERS ANYWAY?
MONEY DOESN'T SEEM
VERY IMPORTANT TO HER,
SO I DON'T THINK
THAT'S THE REASON.
BUT JUST WHAT ELSE
DOES THAT LEAVE?
- AND I THINK WE CAN ALSO
RULE OUT A BURNING DESIRE
TO PLAY SUPERHERO
AND SAVE THE WORLD.
THAT'S YOUR MOTIVATION,
RIGHT?
- ( sighs ) OKAY, YOU'VE
GOT ME WITH THAT ONE.
UH, HEY, PRISS, LOOK.
THE TRUTH IS, I DON'T CARE
WHAT KIND OF REASON SYLIA HAS.
WE'VE ALL GOT OUR
OWN LITTLE SECRETS.
BUT WHAT WE'RE
DOING IS RIGHT.
SYLIA MAY BE STRANGE,
BUT I DO TRUST HER.
- MACKY, OIL FILTER.
- UH, RIGHT.
NIGEL--
- WRENCH.
- RIGHT.
SO, UM...
WHAT DID SYLIA WANT?
- WHY DON'T YOU ASK HER?
- I DID,
BUT SHE WOULDN'T SAY.
- THEN I CAN'T
TELL YOU EITHER, CAN I?
- I UNDERSTAND.
BUT COULD YOU AT LEAST
TELL ME IF SHE'S PLANNING
SOMETHING DANGEROUS?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST MADE SOMETHING
ACCORDING TO HER SPECIFICATIONS.
I DON'T CARE WHAT IT IS
OR HOW SHE USES IT.
- DID IT HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH PROFESSOR MASON
SHOWING UP YESTERDAY?
- MUFFLER.
GIVE ME THE MUFFLER,
PLEASE.
- RIGHT.
- IT'S TIME FOR A BREAK.
- HI, NIGEL.
- ( sighs )
- UH, HELLO, NENE.
- OH, HI, MACKY.
- DO YOU TAKE CREAM
IN YOUR COFFEE?
OR WOULD YOU PREFER
COCOA TODAY?
- COCOA, PLEASE.
HEY, MACKY?
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
- 15.
- I THOUGHT SO.
AND YOUR FATHER WAS THE FAMOUS
DR. STINGRAY, RIGHT?
SO WHAT KIND OF
FATHER WAS HE?
- UM, I REALLY DON'T
REMEMBER MUCH ABOUT HIM.
I WAS PRETTY YOUNG
AND HE WAS ALWAYS BUSY.
SYLIA COULD TELL YOU MORE.
- OH, YEAH.  OF COURSE.
- HERE'S YOUR COCOA.
- THANKS, MACKY.
SO ANYWAY, I GUESS
YOU LIVED WITH SYLIA
UNTIL YOU WERE HOW OLD?
- OH, WELL...
UNTIL I WAS EIGHT.
BUT WHY?
- EIGHT, I SEE.
WELL, I WAS JUST WONDERING
WHAT SYLIA WAS LIKE
BACK WHEN SHE WAS A KID,
THAT'S ALL.
I MEAN, WAS SHE ANY DIFFERENT
WHEN SHE WAS YOUNGER
THAN SHE IS NOW?
- HMM.
SHE WAS PRETTY SMART,
EVEN THEN.
I THINK SOME PEOPLE THOUGHT
SHE WAS A LITTLE
COOL AND DISTANT.
BUT SHE WAS
REALLY NICE TO ME.
SHE SEEMED TO HAVE
A LOT ON HER MIND.
- HMM.
SO PRETTY MUCH
LIKE SHE IS NOW.
OH, I MEANT THAT ABOUT
THE BEING NICE PART.
( chuckles )
OKAY.  SO WHAT WERE YOU
LIKE AS A KID, MACKY?
- HUH?  ME?
I HAVEN'T CHANGED MUCH
SINCE THEN.
- LET'S GET BACK TO WORK.
- UH, RIGHT.
- THE STINGRAY WOMAN
CONTACTED A MEMBER
OF THE OLD ORDER.
A MAN NAMED DR. SHAN.
- INTERESTING.
OBVIOUSLY THE OLD ORDER
ISN'T AS DORMANT
AS WE BELIEVED IT TO BE.
THEY COULD MAKE THINGS
DIFFICULT FOR US.
- THAT'S TRUE.
GENOM MAY HAVE TAKEN
THEIR PLACE IN
THE SPOTLIGHT,
BUT WITH THEIR ASSETS,
THEY COULD STILL PROVE
TO BE A FORMIDABLE
ADVERSARY.
- BUT THOSE SAME ASSETS
COULD MAKE THEM A USEFUL TOOL.
MISS STINGRAY IS AS RESOURCEFUL
AS I HAD HOPED.
- ISN'T THAT WHY
YOU PURPOSELY ALLOWED KUSUI
TO LEAK INFORMATION TO HER?
- OF COURSE.
I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN THAT
STINGRAY MAINTAINED
AN EXTENSIVE NETWORK
OF COLLABORATORS.
LET'S START USING THEM.
- IS THAT WISE?
THESE ARE SOME
VERY DANGEROUS PEOPLE
YOU'RE PLAYING GAMES WITH,
DR. MASON.
- AND WHAT ABOUT
THE OTHER SUBJECT?
- HMM.
NIGEL KIRKLAND?
WE'VE CONTACTED HIM
AS PER YOUR INSTRUCTIONS,
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY WE NEED TO BOTHER
WITH A NOBODY LIKE HIM.
- I TOLD YOU,
STINGRAY LEFT ME AN INHERITANCE.
I INTEND TO USE IT.
- YES, SIR.
- SO, YOU WANT US
TO GO UNDERGROUND
AND INVESTIGATE EACH
OF THESE 27 SITES?
- Sylia: THAT'S RIGHT.
AND I'LL BE PAYING YOU EACH
DOUBLE THE USUAL PRICE,
ALL RIGHT?
- WELL, I'M SURE YOU CAN
COUNT ME IN, SYLIA.
BUT THIS WIZ LAB, IS THERE
SOMETHING DANGEROUS INSIDE?
IT'S NOT THAT
I DON'T TRUST YOU,
BUT I THINK IT MIGHT
SPEED UP THE SEARCH
IF WE KNEW EXACTLY
WHAT WE WERE LOOKING FOR.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- I JUST WANT YOU
TO FIND THE LAB.
SO IT'S POINTLESS
FOR ME TO TELL YOU MORE.
I'LL HANDLE EVERYTHING
AFTER THAT.
- CAN I ASK YOU
ONE QUESTION?
- WHAT?
- FROM WHAT YOU'VE SAID,
THIS WIZ LABORATORY
HAS BEEN MISSING
EVER SINCE THE EARTHQUAKE,
RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- IS THIS YOUR FATHER'S LAB?
- WHAT?
- YES, IT IS.
- THEN SOMETHING DANGEROUS
MIGHT BE IN THERE.
- PLEASE, PRISS.
I CAN'T TELL YOU ANYMORE.
- OKAY,
YOU CAN COUNT ME IN.
WHO THE HELL AM I
TO COMPLAIN ABOUT GETTING
DOUBLE MY USUAL PAYCHECK?
- THANKS, PRISS.  NENE?
- HOLD UP.  WHY DIDN'T YOU
INVITE MACKY TO THIS BRIEFING?
- WHAT?
- IF IT'S YOUR FATHER'S LAB,
WHY HAVEN'T YOU
TOLD MACKY?
- IT'S NOT IMPORTANT.
TRUST ME.
- I'M SORRY, SYLIA, BUT I'VE
BEEN GOING THROUGH YOUR FILES,
AND I'VE FOUND SOME
GLARING DISCREPANCIES.
NOW I WANT FACTS.
- NENE!
- AT FIRST I THOUGHT
IT WAS JUST A MISTAKE,
BUT THE MORE I DUG
THE MORE IT BECAME OBVIOUS
THAT IT WASN'T JUST
A CLERICAL ERROR.
THERE'S NO BIRTH CERTIFICATE,
NO ADOPTION RECORD,
NOTHING TO INDICATE
HE EVER EXISTED AT ALL.
DR. STINGRAY NEVER
HAD A SON, DID HE?
HE NEVER EXISTED!
WHO IS MACKY, SYLIA?
WHO IN THE HELL IS HE?
- ( both gasp )
- YOU WON'T ANSWER
MY QUESTION, WILL YOU?
- I'M SORRY, NENE.
- WAS HE INVOLVED WITH
THE ACCIDENT AT THE LAB?
- YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT TOO?
- SURE.
IT WAS QUITE A CHALLENGE
CRACKING THROUGH
ALL OF THE SECURITY SYSTEMS
THAT THE GOVERNMENT HAS
PROTECTING THEIR
ONE AND ONLY FILE.
BUT I FINALLY
GOT THROUGH TO IT
USING THE ADP MAINFRAME.
- WAIT, NENE.
WHAT ACCIDENT?
- IT ALL BEGAN
THE YEAR BEFORE THE QUAKE
WHEN THE BIOSCAPE CORPORATION,
WHICH IS WHERE
DR. STINGRAY HAD BEEN WORKING,
WAS BOUGHT OUT,
AND THE BOOMER PROJECT
WAS TRANSFERRED TO GENOM.
DR. STINGRAY HAD
FINALLY SUCCEEDED
IN CREATING A VIABLE CORE,
AND THE MASS PRODUCTION
OF BOOMERS HAD JUST BEGUN.
EVERYTHING SEEMED TO
BE GOING PERFECTLY,
BUT SUDDENLY THERE WAS A
MYSTERIOUS ACCIDENT AT THE LAB.
THE FILES DON'T SAY
EXACTLY WHAT,
BUT IT WAS BAD ENOUGH
FOR THE GOVERNMENT
TO SECRETLY SEND IN
A BATTALION OF POLICE TROOPS.
- SO WHAT REALLY HAPPENED?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THE FILE I WAS
ABLE TO ACCESS
WAS A RECORD OF
THE POLICE MOBILIZATION,
AND IT HAD BEEN HEAVILY
EDITED IN SEVERAL SPOTS.
HOWEVER, EVEN THOUGH
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED,
I KNOW HOW HORRIBLE
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
BY THE WAY GENOM
DECIDED TO DEAL WITH IT.
THE CHAIRMAN OF GENOM
JUDGED THAT IT WAS IMPOSSIBLE
TO SAVE THE SITUATION,
AND ORDERED THE DETONATION OF
AN ARTIFICIAL EARTHQUAKE DEVICE.
- Linna: NO WAY.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT SOMEONE
CAUSED THE EARTHQUAKE?
- Priss:
SYLIA, IS THIS TRUE?
- YES, IT'S ALL TRUE.
THE EARTHQUAKE, EVERYTHING.
- JESUS!  ALL THOSE PEOPLE
DIED IN THE EARTHQUAKE
BECAUSE ONE PERSON
PUSHED A BUTTON?!
MILLIONS DIED!
- SO TELL ME, SYLIA.
WHAT WAS IT THAT WAS
INSIDE THAT LAB
THAT WAS WORTH DESTROYING
A CITY TO TRY TO STOP IT?
- I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T TELL YOU.
HOWEVER, MACKY HAD
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
TO DO WITH
THE ACCIDENT, NENE.
I SWEAR IT'S THE TRUTH.
- YOU SWEAR?!
WHY IN THE HELL SHOULD I
EVER TRUST YOU AGAIN?!
- NENE!
- YOU CAN GO TOO
IF YOU WANT.
- SYLIA?
- WHAT NENE SAID WAS TRUE.
I WITHHELD INFORMATION
FROM YOU.
I'VE ASKED YOU
TO DO THINGS FOR ME
AND NEVER EXPLAINED
THE CONSEQUENCES.
I'VE USED YOU,
AND I'M ASHAMED.
- YEAH, WELL YOU SHOULD BE.
SO...
- HUH?
- NONE OF THIS
CHANGES THE FACT
THAT THERE'S
SOMETHING OUT THERE
THAT WE STILL NEED
TO FIND, RIGHT?
SO LET'S GET WITH THE PROGRAM
AND FIND IT, OKAY?
- PRISS IS RIGHT.
IF THERE'S REALLY SOMETHING
LIKE THIS STILL OUT THERE,
THEN WE'VE GOT NO CHOICE
BUT TO HELP YOU FIND IT.
BESIDES, YOU KNOW I'M A SUCKER
FOR THIS KIND OF THING.
- THANK YOU.
BOTH OF YOU.
- I JUST WISH...
HEY, PRISS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- ABOUT NENE?
I'M THINKING IT'S
A GOOD THING SHE'S NOT HERE
IN HER CURRENT
MENTAL STATE,
AND WE'RE BETTER OFF
WITHOUT HER.
IF YOU AND I EACH SEARCH
THREE POINTS PER NIGHT,
WE'LL BE FINISHED
IN FIVE DAYS.
- ( chuckles )
YOU TALK SO TOUGH.
- EXCUSE ME?
- OH, YEAH.
YOU ALWAYS TALK
SO BIG AND TOUGH,
BUT YOU REALLY CARE
ABOUT THE KID, DON'T YOU?
- I'LL GO FIRST.
- HEY!  WAIT FOR ME.
- ( phone ringing )
- THIS IS SIX.
THEY'RE MAKING THEIR MOVE.
- Mason:
I SEE. EXCELLENT.
( chuckles )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS: TOKYO 2040,"
THROUGH A NETWORK
OF NIGHTMARES,
AND A MAZE OF
UNDERGROUND TUNNELS,
THE KNIGHT SABERS SEARCH
FRANTICALLY FOR THE MISSING LAB.
BUT EVEN AS THEY SCRAMBLE
THROUGH THE DARKNESS,
A NEW HORROR IS AWAKENING
IN THE LABYRINTH.
AS BRIAN J. MASON PREPARES
TO SPRING HIS TRAP,
A NEW GENESIS IS ABOUT
TO BE UNLEASHED.
NEXT EPISODE...