- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( laughs )
- Woman: LINNA, COME ON.
- ( yawns )
AT LAST, TOKYO!
- Woman: LINNA!
- READY OR NOT, HERE I COME.
- Woman: THE ACTING SUPERVISOR
WILL MAKE YOUR LIFE MISERABLE
IF YOU'RE LATE, SO IT MIGHT BE
A GOOD IDEA TO SNEAK IN.
OTHERWISE, THEY'LL HAVE YOU
MAKING AND TAKING TEA
TO EVERY SALESPERSON
IN THE BUILDING.
AND THEY'LL DO IT WHETHER
THERE'S ANYBODY SITTING
AT THEIR WORKSTATIONS OR NOT.
- I'VE SEEN THE CITY A MILLION
TIMES ON TV, BUT IT'S SO MUCH
MORE INCREDIBLE IN PERSON.
IT'S ONLY BEEN SIX YEARS SINCE
THOSE HORRIBLE EARTHQUAKES,
BUT EVERYTHING'S EVEN BIGGER
AND BETTER THAN BEFORE.
IT'S SO INCREDIBLE.
EXCUSE ME.
- APOLOGY UNNECESSARY.
IT WAS MY FAULT
FOR BLOCKING THE PATH.
- OH, WELL, I'M SORRY.
- YOU DON'T NEED TO SAY SORRY
TO A BOOMER, COUNTRY GIRL,
EVEN IF YOU ARE A NEW EMPLOYEE.
- OH!
- ( whirring )
- BUT WASN'T IT THE BOOMERS
WHICH MADE ALL THIS
RECONSTRUCTION POSSIBLE
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
I'VE NEVER SEEN ONE
UP CLOSE LIKE THAT BEFORE.
- DARN, WE'RE LATE,
AND WE HAVEN'T EVEN BOUGHT
OUR LUNCHES YET.
- HEY, WAIT!
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT
WITHOUT LOOKING
AT YOUR WATCH?
- BY THE SHADOW.
- HUH?  THE WHAT?
- Woman:
UNDER THE BENEVOLENT AUSPICES
OF THE GENOM CORPORATION,
THE ORBITAL CONSTRUCTION
OF THE SHOWHAM PROJECT
HAS CONTINUED
TO PROGRESS
AT A RELENTLESS PACE.
EXPECTED TO SOLVE MANY
OF THE ENERGY PROBLEMS
NOW FACING MANKIND
AROUND THE GLOBE,
THE SHOWHAM PROJECT
WILL DELIVER THE HUMAN RACE
FROM THE CONTINUED DEPENDENCE
UPON LIMITED
AND POTENTIALLY DANGEROUS
NATURAL RESOURCES.
IT IS THE HOPE
OF THE GENOM CORPORATION
THAT THIS IMPORTANT ENDEAVOR
BE COMPLETED AS SOON AS POSSIBLE
SO THAT IT CAN HELP CHART
THE COURSE
OF MANKIND'S ULTIMATE DESTINY.
- SOON.
- ( rock music playing )
- MISAE, HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
THEM IN ACTION?
- WHO'S THEM EXACTLY?
- THE KNIGHT SABERS, OF COURSE.
THEY'RE AWESOME.
- EXCUSE ME.
YOU DON'T REALLY BELIEVE THAT
THEY'RE SOME KIND OF VIGILANTE
GROUP PROWLING THE STREETS
OF TOKYO, DO YOU?
THEY'RE JUST AN URBAN LEGEND.
- WHAT?  THEY CAN'T BE.
I'VE BEEN FOLLOWING THEM
ON THE NET FOR MONTHS NOW.
HMM.
- LOOK, IF THEY REALLY EXISTED,
THERE'D BE PICTURES OF THEM ON
THE NEWS, RIGHT?
THERE WOULD AND I'VE NEVER
SEEN A SINGLE PICTURE.
- NO PICTURES, NOT EVER?
- I AM SORRY THAT YOU HAD
TO WAIT SO LONG.
- THANK YOU.
- COME ON, LINNA.
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR PATRONAGE.
- THANK YOU.
- I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT I JUST
DON'T LIKE THESE NEW BOOMERS.
I MEAN, WHY DO THEY HAVE TO MAKE
THEM LOOK SO MUCH LIKE PEOPLE?
IF THEY LOOKED MORE LIKE ROBOTS,
THEY WOULDN'T BE SO CREEPY.
- I THINK IT'S SUPPOSED
TO MAKE THEM LESS INTIMIDATING.
HUH?
OH!
- ( sighs )
WELL, THAT WAS SPECTACULAR.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
ARE YOU OKAY, LINNA?
- GET YOUR ASS BACK HERE!
- I-I THINK SHE HEARD YOU.
- DAMN RIGHT SHE DID!
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
ABOUT MY LUNCH?
- LINNA, CUT IT OUT.
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE ACTUALLY
HIT YOU OR ANYTHING.
- ARE YOU BLIND OR STUPID?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING
DRIVING LIKE A LUNATIC?
- OH, NO.
- YOU OWE ME LUNCH.
HUH?  MY FACE?
OH!
- WHAT IN THE HELL ARE DOING
MESSING WITH SOMEBODY LIKE THAT?
THIS IS TOKYO, NOT SOME
BACKWATER HICK TOWN.
- SHE'S TOAST!
- HELP.  LINNA!
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE FOR WORK.
- STUPID FRIGGIN' HIGH HEELS!
JUST BECAUSE I'M NEW IN TOWN
DOESN'T MEAN I HAVE TO
TAKE YOUR CRAP.
GOING SOMEWHERE?
( screams )
- YOU'RE LATE.
YOUR MAKEUP IS SMEARED.
YOUR HAIR IS UNKEMPT
AND YOUR CLOTHING DISHEVELED.
AND WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR OTHER SHOE?
YOU CAN'T COME TO WORK LOOKING
LIKE THIS, MISS YAMAZAKI.
OUR CORPORATE IMAGE DEPENDS
UPON THE IMAGE YOU PROJECT.
AND YOU CANNOT SEE CUSTOMERS
LOOKING LIKE THAT.
- I THINK I'M STARTING
TO DISLIKE BOOMERS.
- I'M A BOOMER THAT HAS BEEN
SPECIFICALLY DESIGNED
TO EDUCATE, SUPERVISE
AND DISCIPLINE NEW EMPLOYEES.
NEGATIVE COMMENTS INDICATE
A NEGATIVE ATTITUDE
AND WILL BE NOTED
ON YOUR PERMANENT RECORD.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?
- YES, MA'AM.
- ARE YOU NOW SUFFICIENTLY
REPRIMANDED?
- YES, I AM.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WHEN DID THOSE THINGS LEARN HOW
TO UNDERSTAND SARCASM?
WHY ME?!  OH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M BEING
ORDERED AROUND BY A BOOMER.
- HI, THERE.
YOU'RE THE NEW EMPLOYEE
IN THE SECOND SALES SECTION,
AREN'T YOU?
- HUH?
YES,
I'M LINNA YAMAZAKI.
- AND IF THE GRAPEVINE'S
CORRECT, YOU'RE NEW IN TOWN.
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
I THOUGHT I KNEW ALL ABOUT TOKYO
FROM WATCHING TV,
BUT IT'S REALLY NOTHING AT ALL
LIKE WHAT I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE LIKE.
- I'D BE GLAD TO SHOW YOU
AROUND SOME TIME.
- WELL, THAT WOULD BE NICE.
- ALL RIGHTY THEN.
LET'S MEET AFTER WORK AND I'LL
SHOW YOU WHERE THE ACTION IS.
- Man: THIS IS BRAVO TANGO.
WE'VE MADE A CLEAN SWEEP
AND EVERYTHING LOOKS QUIET.
- Woman: ROGER, BRAVO TANGO.
YOU ARE CLEAR TO RETURN
TO THE TOWER.
TALK ABOUT DULLSVILLE.
( sighs ) WAKE ME IF
SOMETHING HAPPENS, OKAY?
- I THOUGHT NO BOOMER NEWS
WAS GOOD NEWS.
- WELL, I'M NOT SAYING I WANT
THE BOOMERS TO GO BALLISTIC,
BUT IF THINGS DON'T
PICK UP SOON,
WE'LL BE UNEMPLOYED.
- YEAH, BUT WOULD THAT REALLY BE
SO BAD, NENE?
- UH-HUH, 'CAUSE THEN
I'D NEED ANOTHER JOB.
- OH, YEAH?
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
- HOW ABOUT
THE KNIGHT SABERS?
CAN'T YOU SEE IT?
- OH, LIKE THEY'D TAKE YOU.
- OH!
- Man: Hey, totem pole,
are you there?
- THIS IS THE AD POLICE
INTELLIGENCE MANAGEMENT CENTER,
NOT TOTEM POLE, AND THE NEXT
TIME YOU CALL ME THAT,
I WON'T ANSWER YOU, LEON-POO.
- Man:
DID SHE JUST CALL YOU LEON-POO?
OH, I LIKE THAT.
- SHUT UP, WONG.
THE LAST THING I NEED IS FOR YOU
TO ENCOURAGE THAT 18-YEAR-OLD
JINX TO KEEP CALLING ME
LEON-POO.
THIS IS MCNICHOLS.  NO UNUSUAL
BOOMER ACTIVITY IN SOTO WARD.
- Nene: So what else is new?
I guess I'm going home.
- HUH?
THEY CUT OUR HOURS AGAIN?
HOW THE HELL ARE THE AD POLICE
SUPPOSED TO KEEP THE STREETS
CLEAN OF ROGUE BOOMERS
WITHOUT A FULL STAFF?
- MAYBE THEY NOTICED THE STREETS
HAVE BEEN KEPT JUST AS CLEAN
BY YOU KNOW WHO?  HMM?
- DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED
ON THOSE AMATEUR VIGILANTES.
DAMN THOSE KNIGHT SABERS
TO HELL.
I NEED SOME COFFEE.
- Man: AFTER THIS AREA SANK AND
FLOODED DURING THE EARTHQUAKE,
THE CITY HAD NO INTENTION OF
SPENDING ANY OF THE RELIEF FUNDS
TO REBUILD SOTO WARD.
YET, AMAZINGLY ENOUGH,
THIS WAS THE FIRST AREA
TO COMPLETELY RECOVER.
- THAT REALLY IS AMAZING.
- MONEY TALKS AND SODOM IS
A PLACE WHERE YOU CAN GET
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
NO MATTER WHAT YOUR DESIRE
OR TWISTED FANTASY IS,
CHANCES ARE THERE'S SOMEONE HERE
WHO CAN FULFILL IT.
- GEE, THAT'S KIND OF SCARY.
- BUT, SIR, WHAT ABOUT--
- HEY, ARE WE STILL
IN THE OFFICE?
CALL ME KAIN.
- OKAY, IF YOU INSIST.
SO DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
THE SECRET CHAMPIONS OF JUSTICE
WHO FIGHT BOOMERS
THAT'VE GONE OUT OF CONTROL?
- OH, YEAH, THOSE KNIGHT THINGS.
THEY'RE A BIG PAIN
IN THE POSTERIOR
AND A MAJOR PR DEBACLE
JUST WAITING TO HAPPEN.
SOMETHING SHOULD BE DONE
TO GET RID OF THEM ASAP.
OUR COMPANY IS
IN THE BOOMER INDUSTRY
AND THE IDEA THAT A BOOMER
COULD GO OUT OF CONTROL
IS INCREDIBLY DAMAGING.
IT'S ALL JUST A SACK OF LIES
BEING DISTRIBUTED BY A GROUP
OF WANNABE VIGILANTES.
DON'T TELL ME YOU BELIEVE
THAT CRAP.
- ACTUALLY--
IT'S HER.
- HEY, WHY DON'T WE STOP TALKING
ABOUT WORK AND HAVE
A LITTLE FUN, HUH?
I KNOW THIS PLACE.
- UH-HUH.
- Man: MISTRESS SYLIA,
PLEASE COME TO THE PIT.
WE'VE DETECTED ANOTHER REACTION.
- OH.
- SO, HEY,
HOW DID YOU HURT YOURSELF?
- I SORT OF FELL.
- YOU OUGHTA BE MORE CAREFUL
WITH A PRETTY FACE LIKE THAT.
- OKAY, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT TIME IT IS?
I FORGOT MY WATCH AND I CAN'T
SEE THE SHADOW OF THE SKYHOOK,
BUT IT'S GETTING LATE.
- YOU DON'T LIVE
WITH YOUR PARENTS ANYMORE.
WHAT DOES IT MATTER WHAT TIME
IT IS AS LONG AS WE'RE STILL
HAVING A GOOD TIME?
- SORRY.
WHY AM I APOLOGIZING TO HIM?
- ( phone beeping )
- OH, MAN, WHY DOES THIS
ALWAYS HAPPEN
WHEN I'M IN THE SHOWER?
COME ON, COME ON.
I'M FREEZING MY ASS OFF.
( sighs )
ALL RIGHT!
- MMM!
- ( growls )
ALL RIGHT, I'M LEAVING NOW.
- HEY, CHILL, YOU CAN'T BLAME
A GUY FOR TRYING, RIGHT?
AND BESIDES--
- BESIDES?  BESIDES WHAT?
- IN CASE YOU DIDN'T KNOW,
I'M THE ONE IN CHARGE
OF ASSESSING ALL NEW EMPLOYEES.
I'LL BE THE ONE
WHO ULTIMATELY DECIDES
WHAT KIND OF POSITIONS YOU'LL
BE ASSUMING FOR THE COMPANY.
- I'M SURE THE COMPANY
WILL APPROVE
OF YOUR HANDS-ON APPROACH.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- ( loud rumbling )
- HUH?
- ( screaming )
- ( shrieks )
- OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S A ROGUE BOOMER.
WHAT DO WE DO?  HUH?
- GET OUT OF MY WAY!
I'M AN EXECUTIVE!
- WHAT A TOTAL JERK.
- Man: McNichols, are you
and Wong still near Sodom?
- ACKNOWLEDGED.
- We got a mad boomer tearing up
a restaurant in Soto Ward.
The regular police have
asked us to step in
and handle the situation.
- YOU SAID YOU WERE BORED.
- ARE YOU HAPPY NOW?
SCREW YOU, WONG.  HANG ON!
- ( screams )
THOSE SABERS AREN'T GONNA
BEAT US THIS TIME!
- ( screaming )
- Linna: ANOTHER EXIT!
OH, GREAT.
WHY IS EVERYONE AFTER ME?
- IT IS BREAK TIME.
EVERYBODY TAKE A BREAK.
- NO, THANKS.
- Nene: Come on, Priss.
We've got to hurry.  Come on!
- Priss: Shut up
or I'm going to spank you.
- Ha.  I'd like to see you try.
- YOU'VE BOTH CHECKED
YOUR AUTO-STARTERS, RIGHT?
I WANT YOU TO PAY ATTENTION TO
EACH OTHER'S GAUGE AT ALL TIMES.
UNDERSTOOD?
- I'm so sick of hearing that.
- Priss:
I'm suited up.  I'm going.
- DESTROY IT.
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING LEFT.
- ( explosions )
- ( gasps )
WHY CAN'T YOU FIND SOMEONE ELSE
TO FOLLOW?
THIS IS BAD.
( screaming )
- NO!
- ( snarling )
- ( screams )
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THEY DO EXIST.
NO WAY!  ARE YOU SAYING
THAT I HAVE TO JUMP?
WAIT A SECOND!
OH!
( screaming )
- WAY TO GO, PRISS.
I'LL GET HER.
- HANG ON.
- ( sirens wailing )
- ( tires screeching )
- UH-OH, LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
TOO LATE AGAIN, LEON-POO.
- DAMN!
- Woman: AND AS YET ANOTHER
PEACEFUL MORNING DAWNS
UPON THE GREAT MEGA CITY
COMPLEX,
LET US ALL GIVE THANKS
FOR THE BENEVOLENT GRACE
THAT ALLOWS US TO LIVE
IN SUCH A TRANQUIL
AND PROSPEROUS CITY.
THIS MOMENT OF AFFIRMATION
IS BROUGHT TO YOU
BY GENOM CORPORATION,
THE COMPANY
OF BOOMER TECHNOLOGY.
- Kain: AND THAT, GENTLEMEN,
CONCLUDES MY REPORT.
I'LL SEE YOU ALL AT THE REGULAR
MEETING NEXT WEEK.
HUH? ( gasps, laughs )
THAT WAS A ROUGH NIGHT,
WASN'T IT?
I LOOKED FOR YOU, BUT I
COULDN'T FIND YOU ANYWHERE.
- I JUST WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR SUCH AN EXCITING DATE.
- REALLY? THAT'S GREAT.
- I CAME HERE TO THANK YOU.
- HOW ABOUT THIS EVENING?
- OH, NO.
I CAN'T WAIT UNTIL THEN.
HERE IT COMES!
- ( shouts )
- Wong: PRISS, BABE,
WANNA GRAB A BREWSKI WITH US?
- NEXT TIME.
- THAT'S WHAT YOU ALWAYS SAY.
THANKS BUT NO THANKS.
YOU KICKED ASS TONIGHT
JUST LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO.
- HMM?  WHO'S THERE?
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
ABOUT MY SCAR, MISS BIG SHOT?
- IT'LL HEAL UP
ALL BY ITSELF.
- YOU'RE ONE OF THE KNIGHT
SABERS, AREN'T YOU?
I WANT TO BE
A KNIGHT SABER, TOO.
AND I'M NOT GIVING UP.
OH!  WAIT UP!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: IN THE NEXT EPISODE OF
"BUBBLEGUM CRISIS TOKYO 2040,"
SEEKING TO JOIN THE MYSTERIOUS
KNIGHT SABERS,
LINNA TRACKS DOWN THE SINGER
KNOWN AS PRISS
AND CONFRONTS HER.
IN A SERIES OF UNEXPECTED
CHALLENGES,
LINNA MUST PROVE THAT SHE
HAS BOTH THE COURAGE AND ABILITY
TO DON THE KNIGHT SABERS'
INCREDIBLE POWER ARMOR.
IS SHE READY FOR
THE ULTIMATE TEST?
NEXT EPISODE...