- MY NAME'S NINA AND I'M A
PRETTY AVERAGE, ORDINARY GIRL.
AT LEAST I WAS,
UNTIL ONE DAY.
I ACCIDENTALLY
SWALLOWED SOMETHING
CALLED THE CRYSTAL PEARL
WHILE EATING
AT MY FAVORITE CAKE SHOP,
AND MY LIFE
HASN'T BEEN THE SAME EVER SINCE.
THIS PEARL IS AN IMPORTANT PART
OF AN OTHERWORLDLY SORCERY TEST.
IT'S DROPPED RANDOMLY
INTO THE HUMAN WORLD,
AND THE TEAM OF TWO EXAMINEES
WHO ARE ABLE
TO TRACK IT DOWN FIRST
WILL PASS THE EXAMINATION
AND BECOME
PROFESSIONAL SORCERERS.
THEN GET THIS THING OUT OF ME!
- STOP CRYING.
- YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO PREPARE YOURSELF, ZERO.
- HUH?
- NOW THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO DO THIS.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL HAVE TO
PROTECT HER ANY WAY WE CAN
UNTIL THE DAY THE TEST IS OVER.
WE'LL KEEP DILIGENT WATCH OVER
HER UNTIL THE MEDICINE IS READY
AND WE CAN EXTRACT
THE CRYSTAL PEARL FROM HER BODY.
WE'LL HAVE TO PROTECT THIS GIRL
WITH OUR VERY LIVES.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- SO YOU GUYS
ARE GONNA STAY HERE AND HELP ME?
REALLY?
JUST LIKE THE PRINCES
IN THE FAIRY TALE
WHO BRAVELY FACE THEIR ENEMIES
NO MATTER HOW FEROCIOUS
THEY MAY BE,
AND FIGHT TO THE BITTER END
FOR THE PEOPLE THAT THEY LOVE,
THESE TWO
ARE HERE TO PROTECT ME.
- ( alarm sounding )
- ( yawning )
I REALLY SLEPT LIKE A ROCK.
THAT'S WEIRD.
FOR SOME REASON, I FEEL LIKE I'M
FORGETTING SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
OH, WELL.
I BETTER HURRY UP
AND GET DRESSED.
( shouting )
NOOOOO!
- Zero: JEEZ,
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
WHY CAN'T YOU GET USED
TO THE FACT
THAT WE'RE YOUR ROOMMATES NOW?
- IT IS A BIG DEAL!
I AM NOT ACCUSTOMED TO WAKING UP
IN THE MORNING
AND FINDING
TWO HALF-NAKED MEN IN MY CLOSET.
AND IF YOU WERE IN MY SHOES,
YOU WOULDN'T LIKE IT, EITHER.
- I'M SORRY, NINA.
WE'LL TRY TO USE
MORE DISCRETION IN THE FUTURE.
- BUT SHE BARGED IN ON US
WITHOUT EVEN KNOCKING.
- BUT IT'S MY ROOM, ZERO.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE TO
KNOCK ON THE DOOR
WHEN I WANT
TO OPEN MY OWN CLOSET.
MAYBE YOU TWO SHOULD JUST SLEEP
IN THE CAR. THAT WOULD SAVE US
FROM ANY MORE EMBARRASSING
SITUATIONS NOW, WOULDN'T IT?
- YOU'RE RIGHT. BUT WE NEED TO
STAY AS CLOSE TO YOU AS POSSIBLE
SO WE CAN PROTECT YOU.
- Zura: NINA.
- THIS IS SO ANNOYING.
- REMEMBER,
DON'T WANDER OFF AGAIN
AND STICK CLOSE TO US
AT ALL TIMES.
I WON'T LET YOU
OUT OF MY SIGHT
'CAUSE I'M SICK
OF YOU CAUSING PROBLEMS.
- BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
BOYS CAN'T GO
TO MY P.E. CLASS.
- EITHER WE GO TO P.E. WITH YOU
OR YOU GET ATTACKED.
GOT IT?
- YEAH, BUT I DON'T KNOW IF--
- ( grunts )
- ZERO,
DON'T WALK AWAY WHILE WE'RE
TALKING. DO YOU HEAR ME?
- ( girl crying )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
CAN YOU WALK?
IF YOU CAN GET THE NURSE,
SHE'LL CLEAN UP
THE SCRAPE FOR YOU.
- BUT IT REALLY HURTS.
AHH!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- SHE FELL.
- AW, DID YOU SCRAPE UP
YOUR KNEE?
DOES IT STING?
- A LITTLE BIT.
- LET'S GO.
YOU FEEL BETTER?
- YES.
- THIS SHOULD HELP
KEEP THE AREA CLEAN.
OKAY, ALL DONE.
- ( giggles )
- OH, YEAH.  HERE.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
NOW MY KNEE
DOESN'T EVEN HURT ANYMORE.
- ARE YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
- YEAH, I PROMISE.
- JUST BE SURE TO HAVE YOUR
SCRAPE DISINFECTED
WHEN YOU GET TO SCHOOL.
- THANK YOU!
- MY PLEASURE, LITTLE GIRL.
JUST TRY TO BE MORE CAREFUL.
YOU DON'T WANNA FALL DOWN
AND SCRAPE UP YOUR KNEE AGAIN.
- 'KAY!
- THAT WAS THOUGHTFUL OF YOU.
YOU HAVE
A VERY SWEET DISPOSITION, NINA.
- OH, ICHII.
- I THINK YOU'RE A--
A VERY SPECIAL PERSON, NINA.
- THANK YOU.
- Zero: HEY, SNAP OUT OF IT,
YOU TWO! WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IF WE DON'T GET A MOVE ON,
THEN WE'RE ALL GONNA BE
LATE FOR SCHOOL!
STOP STARING AT EACH OTHER
AND GET OVER HERE IMMEDIATELY.
LET'S GO!
- I'M COMING, ZERO.  SORRY.
- ( chuckles )
- JEEZ.
- ( all squealing )
- ZERO!
- ICHII!
- THE RUMORS WERE TRUE.
YOU GUYS ARE REALLY HOT.
- WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
ARE YOU BROTHERS?
- WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE FOOD?
- PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE
LET ME BE YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
- Nina: HEY, NOW.
- GET OUT OF HERE, NINA!
- WAIT A MINUTE!
- THOSE GUYS ARE
ALWAYS SURROUNDED
BY A GIANT GROUP OF GIRLS, HUH?
- HATSUKA, YOUKA.
- BUT I GUESS THAT MAKES SENSE.
YOU THREE HAVE BEEN THE TALK
OF THE SCHOOL LATELY.
- Both: WE WANT TO KNOW,
ARE YOU THREE GOING OUT?
TELL US.  HUH?
- WELL, THAT'S--
- ( all screaming )
- Girl: WAIT, DON'T GO.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO RUN!
- ( device beeping )
- HMM, IT'S CLOSE.
- Machine: IT'S IN THE VICINITY.
- THE CRYSTAL PEARL.
IT MUST BE HERE, LADY ROKKA.
- I DON'T CARE, GOU.
I JUST WANNA FIND ICHII.
I MISS HIM.
- I DON'T THINK THAT'S
A GOOD IDEA.
- WHY NOT?
- YOUR FATHER'S ALLOWED YOU
TO TRAVEL TO THE HUMAN WORLD
FOR THE SOLE PURPOSE
OF COMPLETING
THE FINAL SORCERY EXAM.
AND NO MATTER WHAT PERSONAL
MATTERS YOU MAY BE DEALING WITH,
WE MUST FIND THAT PEARL FIRST.
- BUT YOU ARE MY PARTNER, RIGHT?
- NO.
I'M MERELY YOUR HUMBLE SERVANT,
LADY ROKKA.
- OOH!
- I'M GETTING A STRONG READING
FROM THE FINDER.
THE CRYSTAL PEARL
IS RIGHT OVER THERE.
IT'S MOST LIKELY
INSIDE THAT BUILDING.
- FINE, THEN LET'S GO.
I'VE ALREADY WASTED ENOUGH TIME
AND THIS
IS GETTING REALLY ANNOYING.
( squealing )
ICHII, MY LOVE.
ICHII, ICHII!
ICHII!  ICHII!
- IMAI.
- HERE.
- MY DARLING!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU EVERYWHERE
AND NOW I'VE FOUND YOU!
HOW I MISSED YOU.
MY ICHII!
HOW 'BOUT A KISS?
- All:
ICHII, WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
ICHII!  ICHII!
- PLEASE TELL ME
THAT THIS IS ALL A BAD DREAM.
- All: OH, HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY DO THIS TO US?
PLEASE, STOP IT.
YOU HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS RIGHT NOW, NINA.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
- Ichii: ROKKA.
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
YOU'RE NOT ALONE, ARE YOU?
- NO,
GOU IS TRAVELING WITH ME.
TO FOLLOW YOU
INTO THE HUMAN WORLD,
WE BOTH BECAME EXAMINEES
FOR THE FINAL SORCERY EXAM.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- LADY ROKKA.
- GOU?
- LONG TIME NO SEE, ICHII.
I APOLOGIZE,
BUT LADY ROKKA WAS EXTREMELY
EXCITED TO SEE YOU.
WE SHOULD BE GOING NOW, ROKKA.
ICHII SEEMS TO BE BUSY, AND IT'S
NOT NICE OF YOU TO BOTHER HIM.
- NO!
ICHII DOESN'T MIND.
I CAN STAY,
CAN'T I, MY LOVE?
- HEY, NINA.
WHO IS THAT GIRL ANYWAY?
- SHE'S NOT HIS GIRLFRIEND,
IS SHE?
- NO, NOT QUITE.
HE'S MY FIANCE.
- All:
DID YOU SAY HIS FIANCEE?
- THAT ISN'T TRUE.
- I HOPE NOT.
- WOW,
YOU SURE ARE A LADIES' MAN.
- BOTH OF YOU SHUT UP.
- HEY, ICHII MY LOVE, STOP
WASTING YOUR TIME WITH THEM.
LET'S HURRY UP
AND GET BACK TO THE MAGIC WORLD
SO WE CAN GET MARRIED
AND LIVE HAPPILY EVER AFTER.
- ROKKA!  I'M SORRY
ABOUT ALL THIS COMMOTION, NINA.
I'LL GET THEM OUT OF HERE
AS SOON AS I CAN.
- OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
ICHII.
- AND JUST WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU MAKING MOVES ON MY MAN?
IF SO, THEN YOU'RE
IN BIG TROUBLE, MISSY.
- HUH?
IT'S-- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
UH...
- LEAVE HER ALONE, ROKKA.
- HUH?
- SHE'S AN IMPORTANT PERSON
TO ME.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
SHE'S MORE IMPORTANT
THAN ME?!
OH!  THAT'S IT!
YOU'D BETTER STAY
AWAY FROM HIM.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT HE SEES
IN YOUR FLAT CHEST.
NO BOOBS!
- YOU BETTER SHUT YOUR--
- STOP IT RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T WANT YOU SAYING ANY MORE
RUDE THINGS TO MY FRIEND.
- BUT ICHII, SHE WAS TRYING
TO STEAL YOU FROM ME.
YOU BELONG TO ME, ICHII,
ME ALONE,
AND I WON'T LET ANYONE
TAKE YOU AWAY FROM ME, MY LOVE.
I JUST CAN'T STAND
TO BE WITHOUT YOU
FOR EVEN ONE MINUTE LONGER!
- WAIT, LADY ROKKA!
TAKE THIS.
AND IF IT'S NOT ENOUGH,
SEND ME THE BILL.
I'M SORRY FOR THE DISTURBANCE,
EVERYONE.
ROKKA, DON'T RUN OFF!
WAIT FOR ME.
- WHERE IN THE WORLD
DID THEY COME FROM?
- Ichii: THEY'RE NUMBERS 005
AND 006.
ROKKA IS A PERSISTENT ONE,
TO SAY THE LEAST.
AND GOU IS HER BUTLER.
HE CARRIES OUT HER EVERY WISH.
AND, WELL,
NOW I THINK THEY'VE GOT THEIR
SIGHTS SET ON YOU, NINA.
- OH, NO!
- BUT DON'T WORRY.
YOU HAVE MY WORD THAT WE WON'T
LET ANY HARM COME TO YOU.
- NO MATTER
WHAT WE'RE UP AGAINST,
WE PROMISE WE'LL PROTECT YOU.
YOU'RE SAFE.
- OH, YEAH.  HEH.
I GOT THIS FOR YOU.
- FOR ME?
- YEP.
I GOT YOU THIS LOLLIPOP BECAUSE
I THOUGHT IT FIT YOUR IMAGE.
IT'S CUTE, LIKE YOU ARE.
- YOU THINK I'M CUTE?
- OH, YES, NINA.
I THINK
YOU'RE VERY VERY CUTE.
- OH, THANK YOU.
BUT...
WHY DID YOU DO IT?
WHY DID YOU LET THAT MEAN GIRL
ROKKA KISS YOU?
WHY DIDN'T YOU PUSH HER AWAY,
ICHII?
I REALLY THOUGHT ROKKA
WAS LYING
WHEN SHE SAID
THEY WERE ENGAGED,
BUT NOW
I'M NOT SO SURE ABOUT IT.
OH, WHY?!
WHY DOES IT BOTHER ME ANYWAY?
I WISH I HAD NEVER
SEEN ICHII KISS THAT GIRL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- GUESS WHAT?
I'M IN LOVE TOO,
SO DON'T THINK YOU HAVE
A CORNER ON THE MARKET.
- LADY ROKKA,
HAVEN'T YOU HAD ENOUGH YET?
AND BESIDES,
YOU DIDN'T TAKE A NAP TODAY.
I SUGGEST YOU GO TO BED SOON
SO YOU'LL BE WELL RESTED.
- SHUT UP, GOU.
I'M TOO ANGRY TO SLEEP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT GIRL!
I WISH I COULD GET HER
OUT OF THE PICTURE FOR GOOD
SO ICHII WILL COME BACK
TO MY LOVING ARMS.
- I SHOULD MENTION
THE FINDER HAS BEEN GIVING ME
A STRONG SIGNAL
IN ICHII'S VICINITY.
DO YOU THINK THAT MEANS THEY'VE
ALREADY ACQUIRED THE PEARL?
- I KNOW.
I JUST HAD A GREAT IDEA, GOU.
SHE'LL SEE.
SHE'LL LEARN NOT TO MESS
WITH MY MAN.
NO MORE
LITTLE MISS NO BOOBS!
( laughing )
- NO! YOU'RE NOT GOING INTO
THE GIRLS' LOCKER ROOM WITH ME.
- BUT WE CAN'T
LET OUR GUARD DOWN.
- I UNDERSTAND THAT,
BUT YOU CAN'T BE
IN THE SAME ROOM.
WHAT ABOUT
WHEN I'M CHANGING CLOTHES?
- WELL, THAT MAKES SENSE.
LET'S GO, ZERO.
- WHAT?  ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YES.
SEE YA LATER, NINA.
BE CAREFUL.
- HEY, WAIT, ICHII, I DON'T
THINK THIS IS A GOOD IDEA.
- WOW,
ICHII IS SO MATURE AND SWEET.
- NINA,
YOU BETTER GET CHANGED FAST.
- YEAH, HURRY.
- OH, OKAY.
- WE'LL SEE YOU IN A SEC.
- THANKS!  COMING.  AH!
IT'S STILL BOTHERING ME.
- YOU SHOULDN'T
LET IT BOTHER YOU SO MUCH
THAT YOU HAVE SMALL BOOBS.
- AHHH!
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WE CAN'T ALL HAVE AMAZING,
VOLUPTUOUS BODIES LIKE MINE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, NINA?
I'M PRETTY HOT, RIGHT?
- YEAH, DO YOU MIND TELLING ME
WHAT YOU'RE DOING HERE, ROKKA?!
- I'M HERE
TO CAST A SPELL ON YOU.
- A WHAT?
- THAT'S RIGHT!
IT'S A TRANSFORMING SPELL!
WHOAAA!
- HEY!
AHHH!
AHHHH!
( cooing )
- ( baby squeals )
- WHAT?  WHY AM I A LITTLE BABY?
- ( chuckles )
NOT BAD, HUH?
I THOUGHT YOU COULD USE
A LITTLE CHANGE.
SO GOOD LUCK TRYING
TO STEAL ICHII AWAY NOW.
I TOLD YOU YOU DIDN'T WANNA
MESS WITH ME, DIDN'T I?
AND NOW LOOK
AT WHAT YOU MADE ME DO.
THAT'S RIGHT, I WON'T LET YOU
TEAR OUR LOVE APART.
ICHII IS MINE,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
SO JUST BACK OFF
AND LEAVE MY MAN ALONE.
OH, I'M COMING, MY LOVE.
NOW WE CAN BE TOGETHER
AND NOBODY
WILL STAND IN OUR WAY.
- NO, THIS IS BAD.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
- All: YAY!
YOU CAN DO IT, ICHII!
- HERE!
- OKAY.
- ( girls squeal )
- WAY TO GO, ZERO!
YOU'RE AMAZING.
- EXCUSE ME.
WE CAN'T FIND NINA.
- WE BOTH WENT BACK TO THE
LOCKER ROOM TO LOOK FOR HER.
AND WE FOUND THIS.
- ICHII!
- LET'S GO, ZERO!
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE, YOU TWO.
WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
YOU DON'T HAVE PERMISSION
TO LEAVE MY CLASS.
- WE THINK
THAT OUR FRIEND'S IN TROUBLE.
- WE HAVE TO FIND HER
BEFORE SHE GETS HURT.
YOU DON'T WANT THAT
ON YOUR CONSCIENCE.
- THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD REASON
TO LEAVE, ISN'T IT?
CAN WE GO?
- ( girls squeal )
- THE THINGS WE DO FOR LOVE.
- COME ON!
- BUT WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- ( groans )
- ( crying )
- SO HOW DID YOU GET HERE?
- SHE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND ME!
- EXCUSE ME,
HAVE YOU SEEN NINA ANYWHERE?
- UH, NO.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
- COME ON. HATSUKA, YOUKA,
PLEASE RECOGNIZE ME.
HURRY.
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME FIND ICHII.
- WOW, SHE'S SO CUTE.
- YEAH,
IS THIS YOUR LITTLE BABY?
- SHE'S NOT MINE!
I JUST FOUND HER
OUT IN THE HALLWAY.
- SO HAVE YOU FOUND HER YET?
- Both: NO, SIR.
- AND I'M GETTING
REALLY WORRIED.
- ALL RIGHT, WE SHOULD SPLIT UP
AND SEARCH AGAIN.
LET'S GO.
- I HOPE WE CAN FIND HER.
- I'LL GO WITH YOU, COACH.
- IF I HAVE THAT LOLLIPOP,
ICHII'LL NOTICE ME.
IT'S MY ONLY CHANCE.
- Zero: NINA!
- Zura: WHERE ARE YOU?
- HEY, ICHII, MY LOVE!
- OH, NO, IT'S ROKKA.
- I FOUND YOU, ICHII,
AND I'LL NEVER LET YOU GO.
SO DO YOU LIKE MY DRESS?
SEXY, ISN'T IT?
WHAT DO YA THINK?
- I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THIS RIGHT NOW.
- AH!
LOOK, ICHII,
I PACKED A LUNCH FOR YOU.
I WOKE UP EARLY THIS MORNING
JUST TO MAKE IT.
BON APPETIT, MY LOVE.
- DON'T GO NEAR IT.
- THAT LOOKS SICK.
- NOW DIG IN, ICHII,
AND LET ME KNOW
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING AT ALL.
( screaming )
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- EVERYTHING'S FINE.
I JUST FORGOT TO BRING
A SUPER DELICIOUS DESSERT
THAT I MADE FOR YOU.
SO SIT DOWN,
ENJOY YOUR LUNCH.
I'LL RUN BACK TO THE KITCHEN.
BE RIGHT BACK!
JUST WAIT TILL YOU SEE THESE
CHINESE-STYLE ALMOND JELLIES.
TA-DA!
- EW!
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
SO DISGUSTING
AND I'M A SEAHORSE.
- OH, ICHII MY SWEET LOVE,
WHEN WE GO BACK TO THE MAGIC
WORLD AND GET MARRIED,
YOU CAN LOOK FORWARD
TO ME MAKING YOU
THESE DELICIOUS LUNCHES
EVERY DAY.
AND NOT TO MENTION
THE EXCELLENT DINNERS I'LL--
AHHH!
OUR WEDDING WILL BE THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL WEDDING OF ALL TIME.
AHHH!
AND OUR HONEYMOON
WILL BE SO EXQUISITE.
WE'LL TRAVEL-- AHH!
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST BE QUIET,
YOU LITTLE BRAT?
- WHAT'RE YOU DOING IN THERE,
ROKKA?
- AHH!  THAT VOICE IS...
THE VOICE OF MY DARLING.
- UH, ROKKA,
IS THAT A BABY BEHIND YOU?
- ABSOLUTELY NOT.
- AW, COME ON, ICHII!
WHY CAN'T YOU SEE IT'S ME?
LOLLIPOP!  HELLO!
- I FOUND THIS ADORABLE
LITTLE GIRL WANDERING AROUND.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO TAKE HER
TO THE TEACHERS
AND HELP FIND HER PARENTS
BEFORE YOU WALKED IN AND
INTERRUPTED ME.
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE,
LADY ROKKA.
THE FINDER SAYS THE CRYSTAL
PEARL IS INSIDE THAT BABY.
- CRYSTAL PEARL FOUND!
CRYSTAL PEARL FOUND!
- WHAT?  THEN THAT MEANS--
- THAT BABY'S NINA.
- THAT IS CORRECT.
- NOW IT ALL
MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
YOU MUST'VE SWALLOWED THE
CRYSTAL PEARL ON ACCIDENT
OR SOMETHING.
AND THAT MUST BE
WHY ICHII SAID
YOU WERE AN IMPORTANT PERSON
TO HIM EARLIER.
THE ONLY REASON
HE'S PROTECTING YOU
IS BECAUSE YOU HAVE THE PEARL.
WITHOUT THAT, YOU'RE USELESS.
- AHH!
- SO ICHII, MY LOVE,
IF I TAKE HER
TO THE MAGIC WORLD,
WILL YOU COME BACK
AND LIVE WITH ME FOREVER?
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
NOW!
- AS YOU WISH, LADY ROKKA.
PHANTOM MAGIC.
A CHILD'S ROOM.
- WHAT IS THIS?
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
- Gou: IT'S UP TO YOU, ICHII.
IF YOU CAN PICK THE REAL NINA
OUT OF THIS MULTITUDE
OF IMPOSTORS,
THEN YOU WIN AND WE'LL WITHDRAW
QUIETLY FOR TODAY.
BUT IF YOU CAN'T FIND HER,
THEN WE'LL TAKE THE
CRYSTAL PEARL AWAY
AND YOU'LL NEVER SEE HER AGAIN.
SO IF YOU REALLY
DO CARE FOR NINA,
AND NOT JUST FOR THE PEARL, THEN
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE ANY PROBLEM
PICKING HER OUT OF A CROWD,
RIGHT?
HAPPY HUNTING, ICHII AND ZERO.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU BOTH.
- WHICH ONE OF THEM
IS THE REAL NINA?
THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
WE'LL NEVER FIND HER.
- OH, NO.  I CAN'T TELL
WHICH ONE IS NINA.
ZURA!
ZURA!  ZURA!
NO!
( grunting )
- ZURA!
- ( bear laughing )
- GET AWAY!  ZURA!
GET AWAY FROM ME.
PLEASE DON'T COME ANY CLOSER.
NO!
- ( baby squeals )
- NINA!
- ZERO, ATTACK THE TEDDY BEAR.
AND I'LL PROTECT THOSE TWO.
- OH, WELL,
RIGHT, ICHII.
IT'LL BE MY PLEASURE
TO TAKE CARE
OF THAT OVERGROWN BEAR.
DESTRUCTION MAGIC!
- DEFENSE MAGIC!
- AHHH!
MAGIC CANNON!
- ( bear shouting )
- Nina: ICHII.
- NINA, WE'VE GOT YOU NOW.
YOU'RE SAFE.
- OH, ICHII!
- ( baby squealing )
- I GOTCHA.
- HOW'D YOU KNOW?
- ( crying )
- DON'T WORRY.
I'LL ALWAYS
BE HERE TO PROTECT YOU.
- ICHII, YOU SAVED ME!
- KEEP YOUR PROMISE.
WE FOUND THE REAL NINA.
LET US GO.
- THAT WAS THE DEAL.
YOU WON THE GAME, SO WE WON'T
TAKE THE GIRL AWAY FROM YOU.
I JUST HOPE YOU SAVE SOME
LUCK FOR THE NEXT TIME.
- NO WAY! I'LL NEVER LET AN
ANNOYING LITTLE GIRL LIKE THAT
STEAL MY ICHII AWAY FROM ME.
- WE LOST TO THEM
FAIR AND SQUARE.
LET'S GO, LADY ROKKA.
- I CAN'T.
I DON'T WANNA LEAVE ICHII
BY HIMSELF WITH THAT GIRL.
I CAN'T LOSE HIM,
AND I JUST WON'T STAND FOR IT.
TRANSFORM MAGIC!
MAGICAL FORGE!
- ( screaming )
- ICHII?
- I CAST A DEFENSE MAGIC SPELL
ON NINA'S LOLLIPOP.
IT'S SET UP SO IT'LL ACTIVATE
WHENEVER SHE'S IN TROUBLE.
SORRY. GUESS I SHOULDA TOLD YOU
THAT FROM THE BEGINNING.
- YOU DID THAT FOR ME?
- WHY DO YOU CARE ABOUT
A LITTLE GIRL LIKE HER, ICHII?
I'M A MUCH MUCH
MUCH BETTER WOMAN THAN SHE IS
AND I CARE ABOUT YOU
MORE THAN SHE EVER WILL.
WHY WON'T YOU COME BACK HOME
AND MARRY ME?
- BECAUSE
I CAN'T LEAVE NINA NOW.
I'VE SWORN TO PROTECT HER.
- I SEE.
SO THAT'S HOW IT'S GONNA BE.
I HOPE YOU KNOW
THAT YOU'RE BREAKING MY HEART!
( crying )
- SHE'S REALLY A LITTLE GIRL?!
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
LADY ROKKA HERE
IS REALLY ONLY FIVE YEARS OLD.
- OF COURSE.
THAT'S WHY ICHII WASN'T FAZED
WHEN SHE KISSED HIM.
AND WHY HE DIDN'T GET ANGRY
WHEN HE TURNED ROKKA AWAY.
- I THOUGHT
I COULD GET ICHII BACK
IF I TURNED YOU
INTO A LITTLE GIRL.
I THOUGHT WITH YOU
OUT OF THE PICTURE,
HE WOULD COME HOME WITH ME.
( crying )
- SORRY, ROKKA.
BUT I CAN'T GO BACK
TO THE MAGIC WORLD RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO STAY HERE
AND PROTECT NINA
AND MAKE MY DREAM COME TRUE.
YOU UNDERSTAND, RIGHT?
- NO NO NO.
I WANNA BE WITH YOU, ICHII.
I WANNA BE WITH YOU FOREVER
AND EVER AND EVER AND EVER!
- NOW NOW,
WE REALLY SHOULD GET BACK.
IF YOU LIKE, I'LL MAKE YOU A BIG
BOWL OF YOUR FAVORITE STEW.
- ROKKA.
- NO, I DON'T WANNA
GO WITHOUT YOU.
I'LL NEVER GIVE UP ON YOU,
ICHII.
I KNOW THAT WE'RE MEANT
TO BE TOGETHER FOREVER AND EVER
AND I DON'T WANNA LEAVE YOU!
- GOODBYE, EVERYONE.
- NO, I DON'T WANT TO!
GOODBYE, ICHII!
- TILL WE MEET AGAIN.
- FINALLY.
- SWEET GIRLFRIEND, ICHII.
- HEY.
- ( all laughing )
- HEY, ICHII,
MIND IF I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- NO.  WHAT IS IT?
- HOW EXACTLY DID YOU KNOW
WHICH BABY WAS THE REAL ME?
HATSUKA AND YOUKA
COULDN'T TELL,
AND THEY'VE KNOWN ME LONGER
THAN YOU HAVE.
- IT WAS EASY.
THERE WERE A LOT OF BABIES
THAT LOOKED JUST LIKE YOU.
BUT YOU WERE THE ONLY ONE
WHO TRIED TO SAVE ZURA.
YOU'RE REALLY SWEET, NINA.
- HUH?
- YOU'RE A VERY SPECIAL GIRL.
- WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING?
LET'S GET GOING.
I'M HUNGRY
AND TIRED OF WAITING ON YOU.
- OH, ZERO.
- NO, HE'S RIGHT. READY TO GO?
- ( both laughing )
- Zero: HURRY UP.
I'M STARVING.
- YOU'RE ALWAYS SO SWEET, NINA,
TO EVERYONE AND EVERYTHING.
- San: DID YOU KNOW THAT NINA
AND THE OTHERS
ARE PLANNING A TRIP
TO THE HOT SPRINGS?
- Forte: REALLY?
THAT'S OUR CHANCE.
- Rokka: DID YOU HEAR THAT?
LET'S GO TOO.
- Gou: SO WE CAN ATTEMPT
TO OBTAIN THE CRYSTAL PEARL
WHILE THEY AREN'T LOOKING?
- NO, I'VE ALREADY TOLD YOU,
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THE PEARL.
I'VE GOTTA STOP THAT LITTLE
MONSTER FROM GETTING MY MAN.
- LADY ROKKA,
PLEASE CALM DOWN.
- ICHII, MY LOVE,
I'M COMING FOR YOU!
- Nina: NEXT TIME
ON "SAVE ME LOLLIPOP"...
HUH?  WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT DID I JUST SAY?