- Hatsuka: WOW!
- Youka: THAT GUY IS SO CUTE.
I JUST TOOK HIS PICTURE
WITH MY PHONE.
- Nina:
OH, YEAH, HE'S OKAY, I GUESS.
- SERIOUSLY, WHATEVER, NINA.
I'M SO OVER TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOUR TYPE IS.
- I KNOW.
I JUST WANT A GOOD LOOKING GUY
WHO'S REALLY STRONG AND SWEET,
SOMEONE WHO WILL PROTECT ME
AND BRAVELY FIGHT
TO DEFEND MY HONOR.
- Both: WHAAA!
- All: AH!
- SO LET ME
GET THIS STRAIGHT--
YOU ACTUALLY THINK
YOU'LL FIND SOMEONE LIKE THAT.
THINK IT'S TIME
FOR A REALITY CHECK, NINA.
- Both:
TRUST US, HE DOESN'T EXIST.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT I GUESS THAT I--
I'VE ALWAYS HAD THIS DREAM
THAT ONE DAY A PRINCE WOULD
COME TO ME OUT OF THE BLUE
AND-- AND RISK HIS VERY LIFE
TO PROTECT ME.
MAYBE A GUY LIKE THAT
ONLY EXISTS IN FAIRY TALES,
BUT IN ORDER TO PROTECT
THE PRINCESS HE LOVES,
A TRUE PRINCE
WILL BRAVELY FACE ANY ENEMY
AND FIGHT TO THE BITTER END
TO SAVE HIS BEAUTIFUL PRINCESS
AND REALIZE HIS EVERY DREAM.
HUH?
DOES THIS CAKE NORMALLY COME
WITH HARD CANDY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I'VE NEVER ORDERED THAT BEFORE.
- MAYBE THEY'RE ADDING THE CANDY
AS A NEW FORM
OF CUSTOMER APPRECIATION.
I HEARD A RUMOR
THAT A NEW CAKE SHOP
IS ABOUT TO OPEN UP DOWNTOWN.
- I LOVE CAKE!  I LOVE CAKE!
- YOU KNOW,
THEY'RE PROBABLY WORRIED
THIS NEW SHOP WILL STEAL
ALL THEIR CUSTOMERS AWAY.
- I GET IT!  SO THIS IS LIKE
A LITTLE PRESENT.
- Both: HOW IS IT?
- ( grunting )
I'M NOT SO SURE
THIS IS CANDY.
IT'S REALLY HARD TO BITE INTO.
- ( all gasping )
- AHHH!
- ( all shouting )
- Nina: WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Zero: IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE ON YOUR SIDE.
- YOU ARE?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- READY?
- YEAH.
LET'S GET THIS THING STARTED.
DON'T WORRY.
WE WON'T LET YOU GET INJURED.
STAY BACK AND WE'LL PROTECT YOU,
OKAY?
- DID YOU SAY
"PROTECT ME"?
- SHIELD MAGIC!
CRYSTAL BARRIER!
- ( all shouting )
- ( thinking ) I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
THESE GUYS
JUST CAME OUT OF NOWHERE
AND NOW THEY SAY
THEY'LL PROTECT ME.
IT'S JUST LIKE THE PRINCE
IN THE FAIRY TALE
WHO WATCHES OVER HIS PRINCESS,
WHO FIGHTS FOR JUSTICE,
AND DEFENDS HIS DREAM
TO THE BITTER END.
THEY'RE LIKE TWO PRINCES WHO
HAVE FALLEN FROM THE SKY
JUST TO PROTECT ME.
- Ichii: LOOKS LIKE
WE SCARED 'EM OFF.
I DON'T THINK
THEY'LL BE COMING BACK.
- Zero: ARE YOU SURE IT FELL
IN THIS AREA?
WHAT IF THEY FIND IT
BEFORE WE DO?
- THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE, ZURA.
WE, FROM THE SEA HORSE TRIBE
ARE GREAT ADMIRERS OF THE PEARL.
AND I KNOW
EXACTLY WHERE TO FIND IT,
EVEN WITHOUT
THAT RAGGEDY LOOKING FINDER.
SO YOU CAN COUNT ON ME, GUYS.
- YOU'RE POSITIVE?
- IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME,
THEN FINE, ZURA.
BUT EVEN ZERO'S FINDER
KEEPS SAYING
THAT IT'S SOMEWHERE
AROUND HERE, ZURA.
- IT'S SAYS THE PEARL'S
RIGHT IN FRONT OF US.
- ( thinking )
WHAT ARE THEY LOOKING AT?
- AH, MAYBE IT'S BROKEN.
- ( beeps )
- Both: HUH?
- AHHH!
- NO WAY!
- QUESTION--
HAVE YOU SEEN A CRYSTAL PEARL
THAT LOOKS LIKE THIS?
- NN-NNH.  WELL, MAYBE.
I THINK IT CAME WITH A PIECE
OF CAKE THAT I ORDERED.
- AHH!
SO--
SO WHAT DID YOU DO WITH IT?
- I THOUGHT IT WAS HARD CANDY,
SO I ATE IT.
- AHH!
- SAY WHAT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT YOU'VE DONE?
GIVE IT TO ME!
SPIT IT OUT, RIGHT NOW.
GIVE IT BACK.
- ZERO!
- SHE'S GOT THE PEARL, ICHII.
- YEAH, SHE SWALLOWED IT.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO
ABOUT THAT RIGHT NOW.
SO JUST TRY TO CALM DOWN,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU DON'T WANNA DRAW ANY
NEGATIVE ATTENTION TO US,
DO YOU?
- BUT WE HAVE TO GET THAT
CRYSTAL PEARL BACK FROM HER.
HOW ARE WE GONNA
BECOME PROS WITHOUT IT?
- LOOK, I UNDERSTAND, BUT--
- Nina: AHH!
- Girls: WHAT IS THAT THING?
- ( owl hooting )
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
HOW DID SAN AND FORTE FIND US?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT US, ICHII.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
AND WHY ARE YOU GUYS HANGING OUT
WITH THESE PATHETIC HUMANS?
DID YOU FIND A CLUE
ABOUT THE CRYSTAL PEARL?
- OH, THE CRYSTAL PEARL.
IS THIS WHAT YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR?
- SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
- SO YOU DO
KNOW ABOUT IT THEN.
- ( laughing nervously )
- SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT SHE'S SAYING!
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE SWALLOWED IT,
ZURA.
- GREAT.
- WAY TO GO, SEAHORSE.
- WE CAN HEAR YOU, YA KNOW.
- All: AH!
- SOMETHING SMELLS FISHY!
IT LOOKS TO ME LIKE YOU GUYS
ARE TRYING TO HIDE SOMETHING.
- I THINK THEY'RE
HIDING SOMETHING TOO, FO.
- SURE LOOKS THAT WAY.
NOW DOESN'T IT, SAN?
- WELL, GOODBYE.
- THEY'RE RUNNING AWAY!
- Girls: NINA!
- San: WE'RE ON TO YOU!
- Forte: SO YOU DO KNOW
SOMETHING, DON'T YOU?
I'M SURE OF IT.
YOU MUST KNOW
WHERE THE CRYSTAL PEARL IS.
HEY, I'M TALKING TO YOU GUYS.
NOW ANSWER ME!
- HOW'S THIS?
- All: OOH!
- ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY,
HOLD ON TIGHT!
- YOU CAN'T GET RID OF US
THAT EASY.
- Both:
TELL US WHAT YOU KNOW, ICHII.
YOU'D BETTER TELL US
WHERE TO FIND THE CRYSTAL PEARL.
- COME ON!
- Forte: NOT AGAIN!
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DRIVE
A LOT FASTER, ICHII.
THEY'RE GAINING ON US.
OH!
- COME ON, JUST ANSWER ME,
ICHII!
OH, NO.
I'M NOT STUPID ENOUGH TO FALL
FOR THE SAME TRICK AGAIN.
- YOU BETTER DUCK, FO.
- HUH?
AHH!
WHOA, I GUESS FLYING AN OWL
IS A LOT HARDER THAN IT LOOKS.
AHH!
- ( both crying )
- YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS, ZERO!
ICHII!
- Ichii:
THIS LOOKS LIKE A GOOD SPOT.
YOU CAN GET OUT NOW.
WE SHOULD BE SAFE HERE.
- WE LOST THOSE GUYS
REAL EASILY.
- AHH!  SO, UM...
HOW LONG ARE YOU PLANNING ON
CLINGING TO ME, YOU PERVERT?!
- AHH!
( grunting ) OW!
HEY, WHY DID YOU HIT ME?
- ARE YOU REALLY THAT STUPID?
NOW WHO ARE YOU GUYS ANYWAY?
- SHOULD WE TELL HER?
- YEAH.
- I GUESS WE DON'T REALLY
HAVE A CHOICE, DO WE?
- THEN LET ME GET
RIGHT TO THE POINT.
SEE, WE'RE NOT
FROM THE PLANET EARTH.
WE'RE NOT HUMANS, LIKE YOU.
- WHAT?
- WE'RE SORCERERS.
- SO-- SO YOU CAN USE MAGIC?
- All: YEAH.
- THEN, THAT MEANS
THAT YOU GUYS
FLY AROUND ON BROOMSTICKS.
AM I RIGHT?
- All: YEAH.
- PHEW, I'M RELIEVED.
YOU DO KNOW
WHAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I THOUGHT
YOU'D HAVE A HARD TIME.
- AHH!
DO YOU THINK I'M AN IDIOT?!
GIVE ME A BREAK!
YOU DON'T ACTUALLY THINK
I BELIEVE
YOUR PATHETIC LITTLE LIES,
DO YOU?!
- YOU REALLY AREN'T AN EASY
PERSON TO GET ALONG WITH.
- YEAH, DIDN'T YOU SEE
ALL THAT COOL SORCERER STUFF
WE DID EARLIER?
- THAT'S IT!
I WANNA KNOW
WHO YOU GUYS ARE RIGHT NOW.
- WE'RE SORCERERS,
LIKE WE SAID.
- AND RIGHT NOW, THE TWO OF US
ARE ACTUALLY IN THE PROCESS
OF BECOMING
PROFESSIONAL SORCERERS.
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD SAY
WE'RE TAKING OUR FINAL EXAM.
EVERY YEAR THE EXAMINEES
PAIR UP TO TAKE THIS TEST.
IT'S BEEN AROUND
FOR CENTURIES.
SEE, THE TEACHERS DROP A BALL,
CALLED THE CRYSTAL PEARL,
AT SOME RANDOM SPOT
IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
THE FIRST TEAM THAT MANAGES
TO FIND IT BY CHRISTMASTIME
PASSES THE TEST
AND THEN THEY BECOME
PROFESSIONAL SORCERERS.
- OH.
SO WHERE EXACTLY
IS THIS PEARL LOCATED NOW?
- YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS!
YOU ATE IT EARLIER
BECAUSE YOU THOUGHT
IT WAS CANDY!
- SO THE HARD CANDY THAT CAME
WITH THE CAKE I ORDERED
WAS REALLY THE CRYSTAL PEARL?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU PUT IT
IN YOUR MOUTH
AND YOU SWALLOWED IT!
- WAIT.
AND THAT MEANS...
YOU GUYS ARE REALLY SORCERERS?
- THAT'S WHAT
WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO TELL YOU.
- DOES THIS MEAN
I'M GOING TO BE CHASED
BY THE SORCERER EXAMINEES
UNTIL THE TEST IS OVER?
- OH GOOD, GUYS.
- All: I THINK SHE
FINALLY UNDERSTANDS.
- YOU GUYS HAVE GOTTA
GET THIS THING OUT OF ME!
AND I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW THERE
CAN EVEN BE A TEST ANYMORE
WITH THIS CRYSTAL WHATEVER
THINGY INSIDE MY STOMACH.
- EXACTLY.
- OKAY.
I BETTER PUT A CALL
IN TO HEADQUARTERS.
- THIS IS CAUSE OF
YOUR BIG MOUTH.
- WHAT?
- HI.
I THINK WE'RE HAVING
A LITTLE PROBLEM DOWN HERE.
WELL, IT'S...
- Man: IS THAT SO?
THIS IS MOST DISTURBING.
THE CRYSTAL PEARL
ISN'T MEANT TO BE INGESTED.
WELL THEN, THERE IS MEDICINE
THAT CAN REMOVE IT.
HOWEVER A BATCH
CAN'T BE READY UNTIL CHRISTMAS.
- THEN WHY DON'T YOU
JUST CANCEL THE TEST
OR DROP ANOTHER PEARL
FOR YOUR STUDENTS TO LOOK FOR?
- I'M SORRY.
- AH!
- WHAT DID I DO?!
WHAT DID I DO TO DESERVE THIS?!
- STOP CRYING. IF ANYONE SHOULD
BE CRYING, IT'S ME.
WE'VE WORKED SO HARD
PREPARING FOR THIS EXAM.
AND NOW
YOU'VE RUINED EVERYTHING.
I HATE THIS.
NOW I'LL BE A STUDENT
FOR ANOTHER YEAR!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S ALREADY OVER.
I DON'T WANNA THROW AWAY
THE DREAM
THAT I'VE WORKED
SO HARD TO ACHIEVE.
- IF THAT'S THE CASE,
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO PREPARE YOURSELF, ZERO.
- HUH?
- NOW THERE'S ONLY ONE
WAY TO DO THIS.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL HAVE TO
PROTECT HER ANY WAY WE CAN
UNTIL THE DAY
THAT THE TEST IS OVER.
WE'LL KEEP DILIGENT WATCH
OVER HER
UNTIL THE MEDICINE
IS READY
AND WE CAN EXTRACT
THE CRYSTAL PEARL FROM HER BODY.
WE'LL HAVE TO PROTECT THIS GIRL
WITH OUR VERY LIVES.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- SO YOU GUYS
ARE GONNA STAY HERE AND HELP ME?
REALLY?
- REALLY.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- NINA.
- WELL, MY NAME'S ICHII.
AND YOU CAN CALL HIM ZERO.
- SO IF WE'RE GONNA DO THIS,
THEN WE HAD BETTER DO IT RIGHT.
I'M NOT WILLING TO GIVE UP
ON MY DREAM JUST YET.
IT'S SETTLED.
WE CAN PROTECT HER.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
WE HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING
WE POSSIBLY CAN
TO PROTECT NINA AND THE CRYSTAL
PEARL UNTIL THE TEST IS OVER.
- Forte: AHA!
I KNEW IT.
- All: HUH?
- THAT'S WHY YOU RAN OFF
WITH HER EARLIER.
- BUT, YOU'RE--
- WE'RE EXAMINEES 003
AND 004.
MY NAME'S SAN.
- FORTE.
- OH, YEAH.
OF COURSE.
IT ALL MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
I KNEW YOU GUYS WERE
ACTING STRANGE,
BUT I NEVER WOULD HAVE GUESSED
THE CRYSTAL PEARL
WAS INSIDE HER.
- SO HAND HER OVER.
- AW, GIVE ME A BREAK.
SHE'S OURS. WE'RE NOT GIVING
HER UP TO YOU FREAKS.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT YOU'RE GONNA
GET YOUR HANDS ON THIS GIRL.
- THEN I GUESS IT'S MY TURN
TO TAKE ACTION, HUH?
THIS IS GONNA BE SO MUCH FUN.
I'LL MAKE A SPECIAL SUMMONING
OF STEP CAT!
- ( meow )
- YEAH, WHATEVER.
I'LL JUST USE
MY DESTRUCTION MAGIC.
- AH!
- REMIND ME
WHY WE'RE RUNNING AWAY AGAIN.
- BECAUSE WHENEVER
YOU USE YOUR MAGIC,
YOU ALWAYS GO CRAZY
AND DESTROY EVERYTHING.
- WELL, WHAT IF I GO EASY
ON 'EM?
- HE'S CATCHING UP TO US.
SO STEP ON IT!
- ( meows )
- AWW, SUCH A CUTE KITTY.
- JUST SHUT UP.
HE'S TRYING TO KILL US.
- IT'S GETTING CLOSER, ZURA.
- ZERO, I THINK YOU BETTER
TAKE NINA SOMEWHERE SAFE.
I'LL STAY HERE
AND USE MY DEFENSE MAGIC
TO TRY TO TAKE CARE
OF THIS THING.  GO!
- A BLOWFISH?
- Zura: I'M NOT A BLOWFISH.
I'M A SEAHORSE.
- I THINK I'M GONNA FALL.
- JUST SHUT UP.
AND HOLD STILL
OR I WILL DROP YOU.
YOU'VE ALREADY CAUSED US
ENOUGH TROUBLE AS IT IS.
THANKS TO YOU,
ICHII AND I HAD TO RUN AWAY
FROM THOSE TWO LOSERS.
- DON'T MIND HIM.
ZERO'S JUST IN A BAD MOOD
'CAUSE HE DIDN'T GET
TO FIGHT 'EM.
- NOT TRUE.
- WELL, I DON'T
CARE WHAT YOU DO.
JUST PUT ME DOWN.
I DON'T WANT TO BE PROTECTED
BY SOMEONE WHO THINKS
I'M JUST GETTING IN THE WAY.
- HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, NINA?
IF YOU KEEP JERKING AROUND
LIKE THAT,
I'M GONNA FALL AND THEN
WE'LL BOTH BE IN TROUBLE.
AHH!
- NO WAY.
WE'RE A LITTLE TOO CLOSE
TO EACH OTHER.
OH, NO. MY HEART IS BEATING
SO FAST. THIS IS NOT GOOD.
- NINA?
YOU HAVE...
NO BOOBS.
- AH!
AHHH!
THAT JERK!
WHO DOES HE THINK HE IS?
I MEAN, FIRST HE TELLS ME
THAT HE'S GONNA PROTECT ME,
AND THEN HE JUST COMPLAINS
THAT I'M ALWAYS IN HIS WAY.
WHATEVER!  I CAN'T BELIEVE
I ACTUALLY THOUGHT
HE WAS EVER HERE TO HELP ME.
- San: THEN DO YOU WANT
TO JOIN US?
I WOULDN'T MAKE ANY SUDDEN
MOVEMENTS IF I WERE YOU.
- WAIT A MINUTE, I REMEMBER--
- I'VE GOT YOU NOW.
AND I'M NEVER LETTING YOU GO.
( laughing )
- Zero: NINA!  NINA!
- ( Forte laughing )
WELL, THAT WAS EASY.
- YEAH, SHE DID GIVE UP
WITHOUT MUCH OF A FIGHT.
WHERE'S MY REWARD?
- TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I DON'T KNOW
IF I COULD HURT A GIRL,
EVEN IF IT MEANS
ACING THE SORCERER TEST.
- REWARD, NOW!
- I REALLY DON'T HAVE A CHOICE!
I HAVE TO
GET THE PEARL SOMEHOW.
- COME ON, FO,
GIVE ME A TANGO TART
OR ONE OF BUJIYA'S CREAM PUFFS
OR PASTELA'S PUDDING
OR COZY CUL DE SAC'S
STRAWBERRY SHORTCAKE.
JUST GIVE ME SOMETHING ALREADY.
I DESERVE A REWARD!  AHH!
- AHHHH!
OKAY, FINE, TAKE THIS
AND GO BUY WHATEVER YOU WANT!
DON'T HURT ME.
- YAY!
THANKS, FO.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
- I HOPE YOU KNOW
THAT I'M EXPECTING CHANGE,
AND BRING BACK THE RECEIPT!
I CAN'T TAKE THIS.
WHY'D I AGREE
TO BE HER PARTNER?
- DON'T WORRY.
IF YOU KEEP WORKING HARD,
SOMETHING GOOD'S
BOUND TO HAPPEN, SO--
- SHUT UP ALREADY!
- San: FO, I'M BACK!
AND LOOK AT ALL THESE CAKES
I GOT.
BUT I THINK
I SPENT ALL THE MONEY.
- OH!
- HUH?
- NINA!
- WOW!
THIS CAKE IS SO DELICIOUS.
- THIS ONE TASTES GOOD TOO.
- NOW OPEN UP AND SAY "AH."
- AH!
- Both: OH MY GOD,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT CAKE
IS THE MOST SCRUMPTIOUS THING...
- IF I COULD DO NOTHING
BUT SIT AROUND...
- WHAT'S WITH THOSE TWO?
FIRST OF ALL, THEY BOUGHT
THOSE CAKES WITH MY MONEY,
SO WHY CAN'T THEY
BE MORE LIKE--
- Both: HERE YOU GO, FO!
- OR MAYBE LIKE--
- LET US FEED YOU, FO!
- WHY CAN'T THEY
JUST BE NICE TO ME?
- WOULD YOU LIKE
TO TRY SOME YUMMY CAKE?
- NO, THANK YOU!
- OKAY.
- WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS SO MEAN?
- SHUT UP!
AND AS FOR YOU, SAN,
YOU CAN'T SIT AROUND
AND EAT CAKE ALL THE TIME.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GONNA
PROTECT THAT LITTLE BRAT
TILL CHRISTMAS GETS HERE,
EVEN IF SHE DOES
HAVE THE PEARL IN HER STOMACH!
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GET SNIPPY.
- WELL,
IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL,
THEN WHY DON'T YOU
DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO GET THE CRYSTAL PEARL
OUT OF HER BODY?
- HUH?
- I SEE.
- IT MAKES SENSE, DOESN'T IT?
I MEAN
THERE AREN'T ANY RULES
THAT SAY WE CAN'T HURT HUMAN
BEINGS DURING THE SORCERY TEST.
SO I GUESS IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER WHAT HAPPENS TO HER
AS LONG AS WE'RE ABLE
TO GET THE PEARL BACK.
- HEY NOW, PLEASE TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE PULLING MY LEG.
WE'RE FRIENDS, REMEMBER?
WE JUST ATE ALL THAT CAKE
TOGETHER. YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
- I THINK YOU MAY BE
ON TO SOMETHING.
- WHAT?!
- HER LIFE'S MEANINGLESS.
LET'S JUST GET THE PEARL
FROM HER AND BE DONE WITH IT.
- HUH?  BUT-- BUT, FORTE?
- HEY, NINA.
THOSE CAKES--
PRETTY DELICIOUS, RIGHT?
- WAIT, SAN.  OH.
- NINA, WHERE ARE YOU?
- THIS IS NOT GOOD.
IF THOSE TWO FIND HER, THERE'S
NO TELLING WHAT THEY'LL DO.
- IT'S ALL ZERO'S FAULT.
I UNDERSTAND
YOU WERE IN A BAD MOOD,
BUT YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO
BE SO MEAN TO HER.
- HEY SHUT UP.
WE'RE GONNA FIND HER,
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES, ZURA.
- AND HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO THAT, ZURA?
THE FINDER ISN'T WORKING,
AND I'M NOT PICKING UP
ANYTHING WITH MY INTUITION.
HOW CAN WE POSSIBLY
FIND SAN AND FORTE
IN A CITY AS BIG AS THIS?
- I HAVE AN IDEA.
WE HAVE TO FIND A PLACE WHERE
SAN AND FORTE WOULD HIDE OUT.
- IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN I KNOW
WHERE WE CAN FIND THEM.
- AHH!
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
LET ME GO.
- ( blowing flute )
- FORTE.
AHH!
- NOW BEAR WITNESS
TO MY SKILLS, NINA.
BY SIMPLY USING MY FLUTE,
I CAN GAIN CONTROL
OVER ANYTHING IN THIS WORLD.
IT'S HYPNOSIS MAGIC.
- AHH!
( thinking ) I CAN'T TALK.
I CAN BARELY BREATHE.
AT THIS RATE,
I WON'T LAST MUCH LONGER.
- IT'S OKAY.
SHE'S JUST A PATHETIC HUMAN,
AFTER ALL.
- Forte: I THINK YOU MAY BE
ON TO SOMETHING.
- NO.
I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS THE END.
- Both:
WE WON'T LET THAT HAPPEN!
WE'LL PROTECT YOU!
- Zero: WE'LL GUARD YOU
UNTIL OUR LAST BREATH.
WE HAVE TO KEEP FIGHTING
FOR OUR DREAM.
AND ONLY THROUGH DEFENDING YOU
CAN WE ACHIEVE OUR GOAL.
- ZERO.
- Both: SO HAVE FAITH IN US,
BECAUSE WE'LL PROTECT YOU
AT ALL COSTS.
- ZERO, ICHII, WHERE ARE YOU?!
I NEED YOUR HELP.
PLEASE COME AND SAVE ME!
- I THINK I FOUND HER.
I KNEW SAN AND FORTE WOULD
BE HIDING OUT IN THIS AREA.
RIGHT THERE.
- ZERO.
- NINA!
AHH!
- ( both crying )
- I THOUGHT
WE'D FIND YOU HERE.
- ZERO, ICHII!
- SORRY WE KEPT YOU WAITING,
NINA.
- FORTE, DUDE,
DIDN'T YOUR MOTHER EVER TELL YOU
THAT IT'S NOT NICE
TO STEAL OTHER PEOPLE'S THINGS?
- WHOEVER FINDS THE PEARL
WINS THE TEST.
THAT'S HOW THIS WORKS!
IN OTHER WORDS,
THE CRYSTAL PEARL
BELONGS TO US, NOT YOU.
SO JUST LEAVE US ALONE,
YOU GOT IT?
( playing )
COME FORTH.
RAVAGE THIS GIRL'S BODY
UNTIL THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
BUT THE CRYSTAL PEARL!
- Both: NO WAY!
- MAGIC CRYSTAL, HA!
- ( both grunting )
- ZERO, ICHII, NO!
- Forte: I WONDER HOW MUCH
LONGER THEY CAN KEEP THIS UP.
IT MAY ONLY BE HYPNOSIS,
BUT ONCE I'VE GOTTEN
A HOLD OF THEM,
THEY'LL HAVE TO DO MY BIDDING.
- HE'S GONNA KILL EVERYONE!
I'M SO SORRY THAT
I'VE GOTTEN YOU GUYS
INTO ALL OF THIS TROUBLE.
PLEASE STOP.
FORGET ME.
AND JUST GET AWAY
FROM HERE, ALL RIGHT?
- DON'T WORRY.
THEY'LL BE OKAY, ZURA.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- ZERO AND ICHII
WILL NEVER LOSE.
AND THEY'LL NEVER RUN AWAY
FROM DANGER.
YOU SEE, THEY'RE FIGHTING
FOR SOMETHING SPECIAL.
- Zero: WE CAN'T GIVE UP
BECAUSE WE CAN'T LET HIM DOWN.
NINA, JUST AS WE'RE
PROTECTING YOU RIGHT NOW,
SOMEONE ALSO WATCHED OVER US
WHEN WE WERE YOUNGER.
EVEN THE TIMES
I GOT DISCOURAGED
AND EVEN WHEN
I COULDN'T PULL MYSELF TOGETHER,
HE WAS ALWAYS WATCHING OVER ME
AND MAKING SURE I WAS ALL RIGHT.
NOW THAT I'M OLDER
I WANT TO BE JUST LIKE HIM.
HE GAVE ME A HELPING HAND
WHEN I NEEDED IT.
AND NOW IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO BE A PROFESSIONAL.
BECAUSE JUST AS HE HELPED ME,
I NOW WANT TO HELP AS MANY
PEOPLE AS I POSSIBLY CAN.
- NOW DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
IF YOU'RE PROTECTING SOMEONE
AND IF SOMEONE ELSE
HAS PROTECTED YOU BEFORE, ZURA,
THEN THAT CREATES A SPECIAL BOND
THAT CAN NEVER BE BROKEN.
AND YOUR GUARDIAN
WILL STAND BESIDE YOU
AND KEEP YOU SAFE NO MATTER
HOW DANGEROUS THINGS BECOME.
BECAUSE DEFENDING SOMEONE
GIVES YOU INCREDIBLE COURAGE.
- MOTHER, FATHER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHENEVER I HURT MYSELF
OR GOT SICK,
THEY STOOD BY MY SIDE.
THEY WERE ALWAYS MORE CONCERNED
WITH MY WELL-BEING
THAN THEIR OWN.
- PLEASE HELP MY DAUGHTER.
YOU HAVE TO SAVE HER.
- Nina: THEY WERE ALWAYS
PROTECTING ME.
- PLEASE DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
SHE'S EVERYTHING TO US.
- YOU SEE, YOUR MOTHER AND
FATHER WEREN'T ALWAYS AS STRONG
AS YOU MIGHT HAVE THOUGHT,
ZURA.
WHEN YOU WERE BORN,
THERE WERE A LOT OF THINGS THEY
DIDN'T UNDERSTAND.
BUT THEY GRADUALLY
BECAME STRONGER
AS THEY LEARNED
FROM DAY TO DAY, ZURA.
THEY MADE MISTAKES
AND THEY SCOLDED YOU,
BUT STILL THEY DID IT ALL
BECAUSE THEY LOVED YOU, NINA.
AND THEY RAISED YOU THE BEST
WAY THEY KNEW HOW, ZURA.
THEY MAY NOT
HAVE BEEN PERFECT,
BUT THEY WERE WILLING TO DO
WHATEVER IT TOOK
TO PROTECT THE ONE THEY LOVED.
- ZERO, ICHII!
- AND NOW THEY'VE PROMISED
TO PROTECT YOU.
AND THAT GIVES THEM
ENOUGH COURAGE
TO FIGHT WITH EVERYTHING
THEY'VE GOT.
AND THEY'LL NEVER GIVE UP
ON THEIR DREAM,
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES, ZURA.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
THEY'LL NEVER LET YOU DOWN.
- I WILL NEVER GIVE UP
ON MY DREAMS!
- WE'LL ALWAYS PROTECT
THE PEOPLE WE CARE ABOUT.
- DESTRUCTION MAGIC!
AHHH!
MAGIC CANNON!
- ( both shouting )
- Forte: ZERO, ICHII,
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY FOR THIS!
- San: NINA, LET'S EAT CAKE
TOGETHER AGAIN, OKAY?
- THEY'RE GONE!
AND IT'S ABOUT TIME.
I HOPE I NEVER HAVE TO SEE
THEIR ANNOYING FACES AGAIN.
- HEY, GUYS.
- HUH?
I--
I WANT TO THANK YOU, BECAUSE
YOU BOTH WORKED REALLY HARD
AND PUT YOUR LIVES ON THE LINE
TO DEFEND ME,
EVEN THOUGH I SAID SOME
HORRIBLE THINGS TO YOU EARLIER.
I'M SORRY.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
NINA.
- Zero: REMEMBER I TOLD YOU
WE'D PROTECT YOU
NO MATTER WHAT STANDS
IN OUR WAY.
AND WE WON'T LET YOU DOWN.
- YOU CAN COUNT ON US.
- ( thinking ) IT'S JUST LIKE
THE FAIRY TALE.
NO MATTER HOW FEROCIOUS
THE ENEMIES MAY BE,
THEY'LL BRAVELY FACE THEM,
AND GIVE IT EVERYTHING THEY'VE
GOT TO PROTECT THE ONES
THEY LOVE AND TO NEVER LOSE
SIGHT OF THEIR DREAMS.
THESE GUYS ARE--
THESE GUYS ARE MY--
MY PRINCES.
- BUT WE'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU TRIED TO STAY
OUT OF TROUBLE FROM NOW ON.
- NO KIDDING.
AND WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT,
WILL BE STAYING WITH YOU
UNTIL THE TEST IS OVER.
IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE STUCK WITH US.
- WHAT?! WHY DID YOU HAVE
TO SAY IT LIKE THAT?
- ( both shouting )
- Nina: SO ANYWAY,
THESE ARE THE GUYS
WHO ARE GOING TO BE
PROTECTING ME,
AT LEAST UNTIL
THEIR SORCERER'S TEST IS OVER.
AND MORE THAN LIKELY,
THE ROAD AHEAD OF US
WILL BE A BUMPY ONE FOR SURE.
- ( shouting continues )
- I WONDER WHAT NEW DIRECTION
THIS WILL TAKE ME IN LIFE.
( growling )
ARGH ARGH ARGH!
EITHER WAY, I KNOW IT WILL BE
AN ADVENTURE I'LL NEVER FORGET.
- Nina: I ACCIDENTALLY
SWALLOWED THE CRYSTAL PEARL
AND NOW I'M IN BIG TROUBLE
'CAUSE I'M BEING CHASED
BY THE SORCERER EXAMINEES
FROM THE MAGIC WORLD.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU TWO
DOING AT MY SCHOOL?
YOU MEAN THAT YOU'RE GONNA BE
RIGHT BESIDE ME
EVEN WHEN I'M EATING MY LUNCH
OR CHANGING CLOTHES?
AND YOU'LL BE SITTING RIGHT NEXT
TO ME IN CLASS EVERY DAY?
- Zero: WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
SAN AND FORTE
INFILTRATED YOUR SCHOOL
IN ORDER TO CAPTURE YOU.
- ON THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "SAVE ME, LOLLIPOP"...
PROMISE YOU'LL WATCH, OKAY?
- Ichii: YEAH, CAUSE YOU
DON'T WANT TO MAKE ZURA ANGRY.
- Zura: ARGH! BITE BITE BITE.