- Nina: I NEVER REALIZED
WHEN I MET ZERO AND ICHII,
THAT ONE DAY
THE TIME WOULD COME
WHEN WE WOULD
HAVE TO SAY GOODBYE.
I HAVEN'T APPRECIATED
THEIR KINDNESS TOWARDS ME,
AND BECAUSE OF THAT,
THEY'VE GOTTEN HURT.
I DON'T WANT
TO BE SEPARATED FROM THEM,
BUT I CAN'T STAND
TO WATCH THEM
PUT THEMSELVES IN DANGER
BECAUSE OF ME ANYMORE.
- ( grunting )
- HEY, NINA!
- NINA.
- I'M GONNA
HAVE TO SAY GOODBYE NOW.
I HOPE YOU TWO
BECOME AMAZING SORCERERS.
- DON'T DO IT!
- NINA!
- THE TEST
IS GONNA BE OVER SOON.
AND SO IS CHRISTMAS.
AND THAT'S
WHEN OUR SEPARATION BEGINS.
I'M NINA YAMADA,
THE GIRL WHO ACCIDENTALLY
SWALLOWED THE CRYSTAL PEARL
AND WAS THROWN INTO THE MIDDLE
OF A MAGICAL SORCERY TEST.
BUT IT'S FINALLY
BEEN TAKEN OUT OF ME.
AND TODAY IS THE LAST DAY
OF THE EXAM-- CHRISTMAS DAY.
- Forte: WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO THE PEARL,
SAN?
- ( all gasping )
- IT'S SO STRANGE.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- Tomi: IF NO ONE WANTS IT,
I'LL TAKE IT.
AHH!
- Ruby: CAW!
- ( Tomi grunting )
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S ABSORBING MY POWER.
- DEFENSE MAGIC!
- FIREBALL PISTON!
- OH NO!
THEY ALL FELL DOWN THERE.
LET'S GO.
WE HAVE TO HELP THEM.
HURRY!
- ( thinking )
I GUESS I-- I NEVER KNEW.
THAT THE PEARL I SWALLOWED
THAT DAY
WAS CAPABLE OF DOING
SUCH AN UNBELIEVABLE THING.
I JUST NEVER REALIZED
THAT IT COULD DO ALL OF THIS.
HATSUKA, YOUKA!
- IT'S OKAY.
IT LOOKS
LIKE THEY'RE STILL ALIVE.
I THINK MAYBE THE BLAST
JUST KNOCKED THEM UNCONSCIOUS.
- SO WHAT SHOULD WE DO NOW,
ICHII?
- ( rumbling )
- AH!
- NINA!
HURRY, THIS WAY!
- Forte: ZERO!
- San: YAY!
- IT'S BEGUN.
- ( owl hooting )
- All: AH!
- WHAT IS THAT?
- Will: THE BLACK CRYSTAL PEARL.
- Both: WHAT THE--
- Zero: WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Nina:
AND WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I'VE BEEN
WATCHING YOU THREE.
I THOUGHT IT WAS TIME
TO PAY YOU A VISIT.
- SOMETHING AWFUL HAPPENED
TO THE CRYSTAL PEARL
BECAUSE IT WAS
IN THE HUMAN'S BODY FOR SO LONG.
IT'S BEEN TRANSFORMED
INTO SOMETHING
THAT IS QUITE DANGEROUS.
- BUT WHAT HAPPENED TO IT?
- THIS HAS BEEN
A UNIQUE SITUATION.
NORMALLY A PEARL
ABSORBS A SORCERER'S POWER
AND GROWS ALONG WITH HIM
TO BECOME HIS HELPER.
HOWEVER,
THIS CRYSTAL PEARL WAS UNABLE TO
ABSORB ANY MAGICAL ENERGY
AFTER IT ENTERED
THE HUMAN'S BODY.
IT WAS EJECTED
WHILE IT WAS STILL INCOMPLETE.
AND THEREFORE
IT IS NOW ATTEMPTING
TO GROW VERY QUICKLY ON ITS OWN.
- Nina: ON ITS OWN?
- YES, AND IN ORDER TO GROW--
- YOU'RE SAYING THE PEARL
ABSORBED THE POWER
FROM HATSUKA AND YOUKA
AND FROM ALL OF THE OTHER KIDS
IN SCHOOL TOO?
- I'M AFRAID SO.
EVENTUALLY THE BLACK PEARL
WILL ABSORB THE POWER
FROM ALL LIVING CREATURES
IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
- UNBELIEVABLE!
- IT WILL NOT STOP
UNTIL THERE IS NOTHING LEFT
FOR IT TO DEVOUR.
- WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING,
GUYS.
WE CAN'T LET THAT BLACK PEARL
KILL EVERYTHING ON EARTH.
- AND YOU DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME
LEFT TO STOP IT.
- HOW DO WE DO THAT?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE?
- NO, IT'S NOT.
NOT IF WE ALL WORK TOGETHER AND
FOCUS OUR ATTACKS ON THE PEARL.
- Zero: HEY, ICHII?
- WHAT IS IT?
- TELL ME,
HOW EXACTLY ARE YOU PLANNING
ON GETTING THEM
TO FIGHT TOGETHER?
- Zura: YEAH,
THEY LOOK PRETTY UNCOORDINATED.
- THIS IS SO FUN!
- STAY FOCUSED.
WE NEED TO GET OUR HANDS
ON THAT CRYSTAL PEARL
SO WE CAN PASS THE EXAM.
HUH?
- San: OH NO!  WATCH OUT.
- I'VE ALREADY TOLD YOU,
LADY ROKKA.
WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
IF ANYTHING
WERE TO HAPPEN TO YOU,
YOUR FATHER
WOULD NEVER FORGIVE ME.
- OH! BUT I WANT
TO BE WITH MY ICHII!
I'M NOT GOING
ANYWHERE WITHOUT HIM.  WAAA!
- ( all shouting )
- NO!
- ( both shouting )
- AH! ZERO, ICHII!
SAN, NO!  FORTE.
ROKKA, GOU!
THAT'S IT.
I CAN'T TAKE ANYMORE.
JUST STOP IT!
YOU GUYS,
THAT'S ENOUGH.
ALL OF THIS VIOLENCE
HAS GOT TO STOP, ALL RIGHT?
I CAN'T STAND TO SEE YOU
GET HURT PROTECTING ME.
YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DO THIS ANYMORE!
PLEASE!
I JUST WANT YOU TO BE SAFE.
- ZERO, YOU READY?
- I GUESS.
WE DON'T REALLY HAVE A CHOICE.
I NEVER IMAGINED I'D ENCOUNTER
ANYTHING AS POWERFUL AS THIS.
I THOUGHT WE'D ONLY BE
UP AGAINST THE OTHER EXAMINEES.
WHO WOULD'VE GUESSED
THAT THE MOST POWERFUL OPPONENT
WOULD TURN OUT TO BE
THE CRYSTAL PEARL ITSELF?
I'M SORRY.
- Ichii: FOR WHAT?
- FOR WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE.
I GUESS
YOU WERE RIGHT AFTER ALL.
- SO DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN DO IT?
- YEAH. NO MATTER HOW HARD IT
MAY BE, I KNOW THAT I CAN DO IT.
- YOU SURE?
- IT IS OUR ONLY CHANCE, ICHII.
- WE HAVE TO DO
WHAT WE CAN TO PROTECT NINA.
- BUT ICHII--
- GO AHEAD.
- CHARM CAPSULE!
- HEY, WHAT IS ALL THIS ABOUT?
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS PLANNING
ON DOING? I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- WE'RE JUST MAKING SURE
YOU'RE SAFE.
- BUT WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- LISTEN.
NOW THAT THE CRYSTAL PEARL
HAS BEEN SUCCESSFULLY EXTRACTED
FROM YOUR BODY, I DON'T
WANT YOU TO BE PART
OF THIS DANGEROUS
SITUATION ANY LONGER.
THERE'S NO NEED
FOR YOU TO BE HANGING AROUND US
BECAUSE THE EXAM
DOESN'T CONCERN YOU ANYMORE.
- BUT ZERO, ICHII,
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
- IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
YOU NEED TO STAY FAR AWAY
FROM US, NINA.
- NO,
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE YOU!
- YOU'RE JUST IN OUR WAY HERE.
GO AWAY!
- ZERO, ZERO.
- SO LEAVE US ALONE
AND DISAPPEAR.
GET OUT OF MY SIGHT, NINA!
JUST GET OUTTA HERE!
- ZERO?
BUT I-- I DON'T WANT--
I DON'T WANT US
TO EVER BE APART!
- IT'S DONE.
- WE HAD TO DO IT.
IT HAD TO BE THIS WAY.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO KEEP HER SAFE.
BUT I HATE
BEING WITHOUT HER.
AND IT'S-- IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF
THAT DAMNED BLACK CRYSTAL PEARL.
WE HAVE TO STOP IT.
- OH NO.
OH NO!
- YOU NEED TO STAY
FAR AWAY FROM US, NINA.
- GO AWAY!
- I DON'T WANT US
TO EVER BE APART!
- YOU'RE JUST IN OUR WAY HERE.
AHHH!
MAGIC CANNON!
DAMN IT.
- IT'S NO USE, ZERO.
MAGIC WON'T WORK.
IT ONLY INCREASES ITS POWER.
- THEN JUST WHAT
AM I SUPPOSED TO DO, ICHII?
- ( crying )
ZERO!  ICHII!
- THERE'S NO NEED FOR YOU TO
BE HANGING AROUND
BECAUSE THE EXAM
DOESN'T CONCERN YOU.
YOU NEED TO STAY
FAR AWAY FROM US, NINA.
- YOU'RE JUST IN OUR WAY HERE.
- AM I REALLY IN THEIR WAY?
AM I JUST A BURDEN TO THEM?
NO!
ZERO, ICHII!
( crying )
- Riru: ARE YOU OKAY?
- BUT AREN'T YOU RIRU?!
CAN YOU HELP ME?
YOU CAN SEE INTO THE FUTURE,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
ARE ZERO AND ICHII
GONNA WIN?
DO YOU KNOW IF THEY'RE GONNA
CAPTURE THE CRYSTAL PEARL?
AND WHAT DID YOU MEAN
WHEN YOU SAID
NO ONE
WAS GONNA PASS THE EXAM
AND THAT I WOULD NEVER GET
TO SEE ZERO AND ICHII AGAIN?
DOES THAT MEAN SOMETHING'S
GONNA HAPPEN TO THEM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- BUT WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU DON'T KNOW?
YOU DID SAY THAT,
DIDN'T YOU?
- THE FUTURE
ISN'T ALWAYS CLEAR.
AND RIGHT NOW I CAN'T SEE
A DEFINITE OUTCOME.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- I CAN'T SAY EXACTLY.
BUT THE FUTURE IS OFTEN
SUBJECT TO CHANGE, NINA.
AND IT ALL DEPENDS ON WHATEVER
YOU DECIDE TO DO NEXT.
- YOU MEAN THAT MY DECISIONS
COULD CHANGE THE FUTURE?
- YES.
- ( thinking )
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT MY ACTIONS
CAN CHANGE ANYTHING.
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE THEM.
I CAN'T IMAGINE
BEING WITHOUT ZERO AND ICHII.
I WANT TO BE WITH THEM
TO THE VERY END,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU
WANT TO DO THAT?
YOU KNOW THAT IF YOU GO BACK,
ONLY DANGER AWAITS.
IT'S NOT SAFE
WITH THE TWO OF THEM.
- NO MATTER
WHAT THE FUTURE HOLDS,
I KNOW THAT I WANT
TO BE WITH MY FRIENDS.
I WANT TO BE BY THEIR SIDE
TO SUPPORT THEM
AS THEY FACE THEIR CHALLENGES.
BECAUSE I WILL ALWAYS HAVE FAITH
IN EVERY FRIEND THAT I HAVE,
NO MATTER WHAT.
AND ALL THAT I WANT RIGHT NOW
IS TO BE WITH THEM.
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I'VE MADE MY DECISION!
- HEY, NINA!
- ( thinking ) THAT'S RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE ALONE.
EVEN IF THEY PUSH ME AWAY,
OR TELL ME
THAT I'M NO USE TO THEM,
I STILL WANT TO BE
WITH MY FRIENDS.
I WANT TO BE
WITH ZERO AND ICHII.
THAT'S ALL I'VE EVER WANTED.
- AHH!
AHHH!
- DEFENSE MAGIC!
- IT'S NOT GONNA WORK!
- AHHH!
- IT'S NO USE.
WE'RE NO MATCH
FOR THE BLACK PEARL.
- WE CAN'T DEFEAT IT.
- THIS IS TOTALLY CRAZY,
BUT IT'S FOR NINA.
- AHHH!
- OH MAN!
WE HAVEN'T EVEN SCRATCHED IT.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
WE HAVE TO STOP THIS THING.
WHY'S THIS HAPPENING?
WHY?!
- ZERO, ICHII!
- NINA CAME BACK!
- HUH?
- NINA?
AH!  NINA.
- ZERO!
ICHII!
- Zero: SHE'S BACK.
- BUT NINA--
- ZERO, ICHII.
( laughs )
- Both: SHE'S BACK.
NINA'S BACK.
- ( laughs )
- Black Pearl: OH, NINA.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT WE TOLD YOU
TO STAY AWAY?
THE CRYSTAL PEARL
IS OUT OF YOUR BODY,
SO THIS HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU ANYMORE.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA GET YOURSELF
HURT IF YOU STAY WITH US.
- BUT I CAME BACK
TO HELP YOU GUYS.
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN HURT ALREADY
AND YOU'RE GETTING WORN OUT.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- BUT IT'S TOO DANGEROUS
FOR YOU HERE.
YOU NEED TO LEAVE.
- NO, I'M STAYING.
AND I'M NOT LEAVING YOUR SIDE,
GOT IT?
- WHAT?
- JUST BECAUSE THE CRYSTAL PEARL
ISN'T IN MY BODY,
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
I HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH THIS.
YOU TWO GUYS
ARE MY BEST FRIENDS.
AND WE'VE STUCK TOGETHER
THROUGH THIS WHOLE SITUATION.
I CAN'T LEAVE YOU RIGHT NOW,
NO MATTER WHAT YOU SAY.
SURE, WE'VE ARGUED.
AND THERE WERE TIMES
WHEN I WISHED
IT WOULD ALL JUST GO AWAY.
BUT ZERO, ICHII, ZURA,
SAN, FORTE,
GOU, ROKKA,
NANASE AND YAKUMO TOO--
I'VE BECOME ATTACHED
TO EACH AND EVERY ONE OF THEM.
AND I CAN'T IMAGINE MY LIFE
WITHOUT THEM.
I JUST WANT
TO STAY BY YOUR SIDE.
I MAY NOT BE A SORCERER,
BUT JUST LIKE YOU'VE PROTECTED
ME, I WANT TO PROTECT YOU NOW.
I WANT TO BE HERE FOR YOU
WHEN YOU NEED ME.
I WON'T LEAVE YOU.
AND EVEN THOUGH
I DON'T HAVE MAGICAL POWERS,
I CARE ABOUT YOU ALL
MORE THAN YOU'LL EVER KNOW.
AND I KNOW THAT NO ONE CARES FOR
THEIR FRIENDS MORE THAN I DO.
I'M NEVER GONNA LEAVE YOU,
ZERO AND ICHII.
- I UNDERSTAND.
WE SHOULDN'T HAVE
PUSHED YOU AWAY FROM US EARLIER.
- THE THOUGHT OF LOSING YOU
IS JUST TOO MUCH TO HANDLE.
- BUT WE'LL NEVER
DRIVE YOU AWAY AGAIN.  PROMISE.
WE'RE STRONG
WHEN YOU'RE WITH US,
'CAUSE YOUR FEELINGS FOR US
GIVE US STRENGTH.
SO THANK YOU
FOR COMING BACK.
YOU'VE TAUGHT US SO MUCH
ABOUT CARING FOR OTHERS.
THERE'S NO WAY WE WOULD'VE
BEEN ABLE TO PROTECT YOU
ALL THIS TIME IF WE
DIDN'T CARE FOR YOU.
OUR DESIRE TO KEEP YOU SAFE
HAS MADE US STRONG.
- Both: WE'LL PROTECT YOU,
NINA.
WE'LL PROTECT YOU
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
PROMISE.
- I WANT TO DO ALL I CAN.
NOTHING'S MORE IMPORTANT
THAN KEEPING MY FRIENDS SAFE
FROM THE BLACK PEARL.
LET'S DO IT!
- Black Pearl: NOT SO FAST.
- DEFENSE MAGIC!
- All: MAGIC CRYSTAL BARRIER!
- WE WON'T LOSE!
- Forte: WE WON'T GIVE UP!
- SAN?
- FORTE?
- I DECIDED THAT I DON'T
REALLY WANT THE PEARL ANYMORE.
- SOME THINGS ARE MORE
IMPORTANT. WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- Rokka: THAT'S RIGHT!
I DON'T CARE IF I GET
TO BE WITH ICHII OR NOT!
OR EVEN
IF HE GIVES ME ATTENTION.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT HE'S SAFE FROM HARM.
- LADY ROKKA, I UNDERSTAND
EXACTLY HOW YOU FEEL,
MORE THAN YOU KNOW.
- I AGREE.
- YAKUMO?  NANASE?
- ALL I WANNA DO IS PROTECT
THE PERSON I LOVE AS WELL.
RIGHT, NINA?
LET'S DO THIS.
FOR MY PRECIOUS LITTLE NINA.
- All: FOR THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE DEAR TO US!
- Black Pearl: NO!
- Zura: NINA, I NEED
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
DO YOU KNOW WHO IT IS NOW?
DO YOU KNOW
WHO WATCHED OVER YOU
AND WHO WANTED TO KEEP YOU SAFE
FROM HARM NO MATTER WHAT?
- I DO.
IT'S MY PARENTS.
'CAUSE THEY NURSED ME
BACK TO HEALTH
WHENEVER I HURT MYSELF.
AND THEY WERE ALWAYS MUCH MORE
WORRIED ABOUT MY WELL-BEING
THAN THEY WERE
ABOUT THEMSELVES.
- THEY ALWAYS PROTECTED ME.
- DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO SAVE MY PRECIOUS DAUGHTER.
- BUT STILL, MY MOM AND DAD
WEREN'T ALWAYS THAT STRONG.
THEY HAD TO LEARN
HOW TO CARE FOR ME.
- WHEN I WAS BORN,
THEY DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING.
- BUT THEY GRADUALLY
BECAME STRONGER
AS THEY LEARNED
FROM DAY TO DAY.
THEY MADE MISTAKES
AND THEY SCOLDED ME.
BUT STILL, THEY DID IT ALL
BECAUSE THEY LOVED ME.
AND THEY RAISED ME
THE BEST WAY THEY KNEW HOW.
THEY MAY NOT HAVE BEEN PERFECT,
BUT THEY WERE WILLING
TO DO WHATEVER IT TOOK
TO PROTECT THE ONE THEY LOVED.
ZERO AND ICHII, I CARE FOR YOU
JUST LIKE THEY CARED FOR ME.
AND ALL OF YOU!
SAN, FORTE,
GOU, ROKKA,
YAKUMO AND NANASE.
I WANT TO SHARE THIS FEELING
AND PROTECT THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE DEAR TO ME!
- AND TO HELP EACH OTHER
ACHIEVE THEIR DREAMS!
- AND I EVEN WANT TO HELP YOU,
BLACK PEARL.
- ( growls )
- THIS ISN'T ABOUT FRIENDS
AND ENEMIES.
I JUST WANT TO PROTECT
EVERYONE IN THIS WORLD.
- AHHH!
- ZERO!
USE THE MAGIC CANNON!
- TAKE THIS!
- AND NOW, ICHII,
IT'S TIME FOR THE FINAL ATTACK.
USE YOUR POWER AND SWITCH THE
POLARITY OF THE CRYSTAL.
- ( growls )
- COME ON!
THERE'S NO NEED TO BE AFRAID.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE OKAY.
JUST LOOK AT THE LIGHT,
THE LIGHT
THAT SURROUNDS AND PROTECTS YOU.
THE LIGHT FEELS SO GENTLE
AND WARM, DOESN'T IT?
SO VERY WARM.
- NINA.
- YOU DID IT.
- I'M HAPPY
BECAUSE NOW ALL OF MY FRIENDS
ARE FINALLY SAFE FROM THE POWER
OF THE BLACK CRYSTAL PEARL.
- Will: AND YOU HAVE EVERY RIGHT
TO BE.
TRUE MAGICAL POWER
IS NOT CREATED
THROUGH DESTRUCTION AND CHAOS.
AND MERELY PASSING A TEST
DOES NOT MAKE YOU A SORCERER.
INSTEAD, THE DESIRE TO PROTECT
WHAT'S PRECIOUS TO YOU
WITHOUT DISTINCTION
OF FRIEND OR FOE
IS WHAT MAGICAL POWER
IS ULTIMATELY ABOUT.
NINA,
YOU MAY NOT BE A TRUE SORCERER,
BUT IN YOUR HEART,
YOU HOLD THE KEY
TO UNLOCK YOUR POTENTIAL.
YOU'VE PROVEN
THAT YOU CARE DEEPLY
FOR ALL YOUR NEW FRIENDS.
CONGRATULATIONS,
ZERO AND ICHII.
WITH YOUR KIND NATURE,
I'M SURE YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO ACCOMPLISH ANYTHING
YOU WISH.
SAN AND FORTE,
I APPLAUD YOUR CONTINUED SUPPORT
FOR EACH OTHER.
GOU, ROKKA, NANASE,
AND YAKUMO AS WELL,
YOU SHOULD ALL BE PROUD.
THE POWER
YOU'VE HELPED TO ACTIVATE
IS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL THING
IN THE WORLD.
- Zero: YOU MEAN--
- YOU'VE ALL PASSED THE TEST.
UPON RETURNING HOME,
YOU'LL BE MADE
PROFESSIONAL SORCERERS.
- Rokka: WE DID IT!
- San: YIPPEE.
- NOW WE'RE REAL SORCERERS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET BACK
TO THE MAGIC WORLD.
- ( thinking )
ZERO, ICHII,
I'M NOT SAD
BECAUSE YOUR DREAMS
HAVE COME TRUE.
- NINA!
- ZERO, ICHII!
CONGRATULATIONS.
I HOPE YOU GROW
TO BE WONDERFUL SORCERERS.
I WANT YOU
TO BECOME SO POWERFUL
THAT YOU CAN PROTECT EVERYONE
IN THE UNIVERSE.
- Both: NINA.
- ICHII, THANKS SO MUCH
FOR HELPING ME OUT
WITH ALL OF MY SCHOOLWORK.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'LL DO AFTER YOU'RE GONE.
I'LL BE LATE FOR SCHOOL
ALL THE TIME.
ZERO!
THANK YOU
FOR ALWAYS PROTECTING ME
NO MATTER HOW MUCH
YOU WERE UP AGAINST.
IT'LL BE A LOT QUIETER
AROUND HERE AFTER YOU'VE GONE.
ZERO, ICHII!
I'LL NEVER FORGET THE TIME
THAT WE'VE SPENT TOGETHER
AND THE FACT THAT YOU
PROTECTED ME SO BRAVELY.
I'LL NEVER FORGET ALL THE
GOOD TIMES THAT WE SHARED,
LIKE THE TRIP TO THE BEACH
WHERE WE PLAYED VOLLEYBALL
AND THE COURAGE TEST.
I PROMISE
I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU GUYS,
NO MATTER HOW PAINFUL
IT MAY BE.
BECAUSE YOU WILL ALWAYS
BE MY SWEET PRINCES.
- NINA.
- THANK YOU. THANK YOU
FOR CARING ABOUT ME SO MUCH.
- NINA.
- THANK YOU, ZERO AND ICHII.
- Will:
WELL, IT'S ABOUT THAT TIME.
IN ONE MINUTE,
THE CLOCK STRIKES MIDNIGHT.
WITH THAT COMES THE END
OF THE DAY AND THE TEST.
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT ALL OF YOU
HERE REMEMBER THIS MOMENT.
THINK OF THIS NOT AS THE END
OF YOUR TRAINING,
BUT THE BEGINNING
OF YOUR PROFESSIONAL LIFE.
- BUT WILL--
- ONE YEAR FROM NOW, I WANT YOU
TO LOOK AT THAT SAME CLOCK
AND BE GLAD THAT YOU PASSED THE
SECOND HALF OF THE FINAL TEST.
IF YOU ALL MAKE IT, THAT IS.
- All: WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- WELL, IT MEANS YOU PASSED
THE FIRST HALF OF THE TEST.
BUT THERE'S STILL
MORE WORK TO BE DONE.
- All: WHAT?!
MORE WORK?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOUR OBJECTIVE
IS TO GROW THE POOR LITTLE PEARL
THAT NINA HAS SAVED
INTO A FULL-FLEDGED
SORCERER'S HELPER.
AND YOU HAVE UNTIL DECEMBER 24th
OF NEXT YEAR TO DO SO.
ALL OF YOU WILL BE INVOLVED
IN THIS PROCESS.
FOR YOU SEE,
YOU MUST HELP NINA
TO BECOME A
PROFESSIONAL SORCERER
JUST AS SHE HAS
HELPED ALL OF YOU.
- All: WHAT?!
ALL OF US?
- SO DOES THAT MEAN
THAT WE GET TO STAY?
WE GET TO SPEND THE ENTIRE YEAR
HERE HELPING NINA?
- All: THAT'S SO AWESOME!
WE'LL SPEND THE YEAR WITH NINA.
- Will: EXACTLY.
- ( bell tolling )
- NINA, CONSIDER THIS
MY CHRISTMAS PRESENT TO YOU.
I HOPE THAT YOU ENJOY IT.
- WILL, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THIS IS THE BEST
CHRISTMAS PRESENT EVER.
- OF COURSE.
I'M JUST GLAD
I COULD BRING YOU HAPPINESS.
SO MERRY CHRISTMAS
TO YOU ALL.
BE SURE TO TAKE GOOD CARE
OF THIS LITTLE GUY.
- AND MERRY CHRISTMAS TO YOU.
AND I PROMISE
I'LL WORK EXTRA HARD
TO DO EVERYTHING
THAT I POSSIBLY CAN
TO PROTECT HIM
UNTIL HE CAN BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED
SORCERER'S HELPER.
I SWEAR IT.
AND BESIDES, I HAVE EVERYONE
HERE TO HELP ME TOO.
- Girls: MERRY CHRISTMAS, NINA!
SO WHO HAVE YOU DECIDED ON,
ZERO OR ICHII?
- MERRY CHRISTMAS,
HATSUKA AND YOUKA!
I CAN'T DECIDE,
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'VE NEVER BEEN HAPPIER.
'CAUSE THEY GET TO STAY
ANOTHER YEAR.
MY WONDERFUL PRINCES
WILL STILL BE HERE FOR ME.