- MY NAME'S NINA, AND I'M A
PRETTY AVERAGE ORDINARY GIRL.
AT LEAST I WAS,
UNTIL ONE DAY.
I ACCIDENTALLY
SWALLOWED SOMETHING
CALLED THE CRYSTAL PEARL
WHILE EATING
AT MY FAVORITE CAKE SHOP,
AND MY LIFE HASN'T
BEEN THE SAME EVER SINCE.
THIS PEARL IS AN IMPORTANT PART
OF AN OTHERWORLDLY SORCERY TEST.
IT'S DROPPED RANDOMLY
INTO THE HUMAN WORLD,
AND THE TEAM
OF TWO EXAMINEES
WHO ARE ABLE TO TRACK IT DOWN
FIRST WILL PASS THE EXAMINATION
AND BECOME
PROFESSIONAL SORCERERS.
THEN GET THIS THING OUT OF ME!
- STOP CRYING.
- YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO PREPARE YOURSELF, ZERO.
- HUH?
- NOW THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO DO THIS.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL HAVE TO
PROTECT HER ANY WAY WE CAN
UNTIL THE DAY THE TEST
IS OVER.
WE'LL KEEP DILIGENT WATCH
OVER HER
UNTIL THE MEDICINE IS READY
AND WE CAN EXTRACT
THE CRYSTAL PEARL FROM HER BODY.
WE'LL HAVE TO PROTECT THIS GIRL
WITH OUR VERY LIVES.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- SO YOU GUYS
ARE GONNA STAY HERE AND HELP ME?
REALLY?
JUST LIKE THE PRINCES
IN THE FAIRY TALE
WHO BRAVELY FACE THEIR ENEMIES
NO MATTER HOW
FEROCIOUS THEY MAY BE
AND FIGHT TO THE BITTER END
FOR THE PEOPLE THAT THEY LOVE,
THESE TWO ARE HERE
TO PROTECT ME.
( panting, grunting )
WHY AM I ALWAYS THE ONE
WHO GETS CHASED BY THE BAD GUYS?
WHAT DO THEY WANT FROM ME?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING TO THEM.
AHH!
AH!  HELP ME!
HELP ME, PLEASE!
- ( alarm sounding )
- YOU BETTER WAKE UP
AND GET READY FOR SCHOOL, NINA.
THE ALARM'S BEEN GOING OFF
FOR LIKE 10 MINUTES ALREADY.
- AHHH!
- ( both grunting )
- WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
- JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DOING IN MY ROOM, YOU PERVERT?
- PERVERT?
- GET OUT OF HERE!
DON'T EVER ENTER A GIRL'S ROOM
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
- OW OW OW OW OW!
- Ichii: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ICHII, HELP ME.
- SO YOU READY TO GO, NINA?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- REMEMBER,
WE'RE SWORN TO PROTECT YOU.
STARTING TODAY, WE'LL BE
GOING WITH YOU TO SCHOOL.
- Zura: THAT'S THE DEAL.
- EVERY DAY?
- I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GONNA TELL HER, ZERO.
- I WAS GOING TO,
BUT SHE STARTED WAILING ON
ME OUT OF NOWHERE.
- YOU BROUGHT THAT ON YOURSELF.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
IN MY BED.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
- ALL RIGHT,
LEAVE HER ALONE.
NINA, WHEN YOU'RE READY,
LET ME KNOW.
I'LL BE WAITING.
COME ON, ZERO.
- ALL RIGHT, BUT
THIS ISN'T OVER.
- HEY, WAIT!
OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT,
ZERO AND ICHII ARE SORCERERS.
THIS IS AWESOME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE SORCERERS.
WAIT TILL I TELL MY FRIENDS.
- YEAH, BUT REMEMBER,
WE ARE STILL IN TRAINING.
- IF THINGS
GO ACCORDING TO PLAN,
WE WON'T BE HERE
FOR MUCH LONGER.
AFTER WE FINISH THE EXAM,
WE'LL BE PROS.
AND THEN I'LL HAVE THE SKILLS
I NEED TO PURSUE MY DREAM.
- BUT EVEN IF YOU
DON'T BECOME PROFESSIONALS,
IT'S STILL REALLY COOL THAT YOU
CAN MAKE CARS FLY AND STUFF.
- YOU JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
AT ALL, DO YOU?
- SOMEONE'S SNAPPY!
AND HERE'S AN IDEA--
TRY NOT BEING SUCH A JERK.
'KAY?
- ( owl hooting )
- Zero: AW, GREAT.
- Ichii: IT'S SAN AND FORTE.
- GOOD MORNING, EVERYBODY.
- FOCUS, SAN.
WE HAVE TO GET
THAT CRYSTAL PEARL TODAY.
GOT IT?
( playing )
- HEY GUYS, DO YOU KNOW
WHY I'M FLOATING?
- GIVE HER BACK NOW!
- DON'T FORGET ABOUT ME.
I WANT TO PLAY.
SUMMONING MAGIC!
AIR FISH!
GO!
- AHHHH!
NO!  DON'T EAT ME.
- NINA!
CHARM CAPSULE!
- WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
TAKE MY PETS AWAY?
- AHH!
- Ichii: NINA!
- AHHH!
- NINA!  AHHH!
- ( people shouting )
- Man: WHAT'S THAT?
- I HOPE YOU REALIZE
THIS ISN'T OVER YET!
- San: BYE, EVERYBODY.
WE'LL SEE YOU SOON.
- SO THEY'RE GOING
TO COME BACK FOR ME?
- OF COURSE THEY'LL COME
BACK FOR YOU.
- AND THEY'LL KEEP COMING BACK
TILL THE TEST IS OVER.
- BUT THEY WON'T BE
THE ONLY ONES.
THEY WANT THE PEARL.
- PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'RE JOKING, ZERO.
DO I REALLY HAVE TO LIVE
LIKE THIS UNTIL CHRISTMAS?
- All: YUP. YEAH. THAT'S
PRETTY MUCH HOW IT GOES.
- GOOD MORNING, NINA.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT HAPPENED TO US YESTERDAY.
I ALMOST FREAKED OUT WHEN THAT
CAR FELL OUT OF THE SKY.
- THEY SAID
THAT IT WAS FOR A TV SHOW.
- REALLY?
- WEIRD, HUH?
SO HOW DO YOU FEEL TODAY?
- OH, I FEEL JUST FINE.
THANKS FOR ASKING, HATSUKA.
( thinking ) I'M THE FURTHEST
THING FROM FINE RIGHT NOW.
BUT AT LEAST I'LL BE ABLE
TO TAKE A BREAK FROM IT ALL
WHILE I'M AT SCHOOL.
- THESE ARE OUR NEW TRANSFER
STUDENTS, ZERO AND ICHII.
- AHH! WHAT?
WHAT ARE THEY DOING HERE?
- I WANT EVERYBODY
TO DO THEIR BEST
TO MAKE OUR NEW STUDENTS
FEEL AT HOME.
TRANSFERRING INTO A NEW SCHOOL
AFTER THE SEMESTER'S ALREADY
STARTED CAN BE PRETTY DIFFICULT.
AND THE FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS
IS FINDING A PLACE
FOR THESE BOYS TO SIT.
- IF IT'S ALL THE SAME TO YOU,
I'D LIKE TO TAKE THE DESK
HERE BESIDE NINA.
- AND I'LL GLADLY TAKE THIS
OTHER FREE DESK BESIDE NINA,
IF THAT'S ALL RIGHT
WITH EVERYONE.
- ( all squealing )
- Both: WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?!
WHO ARE THESE NEW GUYS?
- ARE YOU LIKE FRIENDS
WITH THEM, NINA?
- YEAH, "FRIENDS" ISN'T QUITE
THE WORD THAT I WOULD USE.
- WHAT ARE YOU HIDING FROM US?
- TELL US
WHAT'S GOING ON, NINA.
- WELL, IT'S JUST THAT--
- IT'S LOVE, ISN'T IT?
- YOU NEED TO
MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS, OKAY?
- AS YOU MAY REMEMBER
FROM OUR LAST TEST--
- Nina: HEY ZERO, ICHII?
WHY'D YOU REGISTER
FOR ALL MY CLASSES?
- WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO LET OUR GUARD DOWN.
YOU COULD BE ATTACKED ANYWHERE,
ANYTIME.
- AS LONG AS WE'RE HERE, WE
WON'T LET YOU GET HURT,
SO DON'T WORRY.
- STILL...
THEIR STARES, THEIR STARES.
THEIR STARES, THEIR STARES,
THEIR STARES!
THEY'RE SO PIERCING.
- ( bell tolling )
- AH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WE'RE TAKING YOU TO CLASS,
NINA.
- YOU HAVE CHEMISTRY NEXT,
DON'T YOU?
- AH, YEAH.
- THIS SHOULD BE FUN.
- ALL RIGHT, I GUESS
WE'D BETTER TAKE OUR SEATS.
- YEAH, THIS IS A GOOD SPOT.
- I'LL SIT HERE.
- AND I'LL SIT HERE.
- HEY.
- YOU'RE IN OUR SEATS.
- IF YOU DON'T MIND,
WE'D LIKE TO STAY AS CLOSE
AS POSSIBLE TO NINA TODAY.
WE CAN'T HELP IT.
WE'RE DRAWN
TO NINA'S REMARKABLE BEAUTY.
- CAN'T GET ENOUGH.
- Both: WHAT?!
- All: WHAT?! WHAT?!
- Girl: HEY, DID YOU HEAR?
NINA AND THOSE TWO GUYS
ARE GOING OUT.
- I HEARD THEY TRANSFERRED
FROM THEIR OLD SCHOOL
JUST SO THEY COULD BE WITH NINA.
- OHHH!
- SO THAT'S WHY THOSE THREE
ARE ALWAYS TOGETHER.
- HOW DID I GET MYSELF
INTO THIS?!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
- ( all chattering )
- SERIOUSLY, CAN'T YOU
JUST GIVE ME A MINUTE TO MYSELF?
I'LL BE OKAY HERE.
- I'M SORRY, NINA,
BUT WE HAVE TO KEEP
A CLOSE EYE ON YOU.
- THE WHOLE SCHOOL'S GOSSIPING
ABOUT ME NOW.
- QUIT COMPLAINING.
THIS IS YOUR FAULT
FOR SWALLOWING THE PEARL ANYWAY.
- WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
IT'S NOT LIKE I ATE IT
ON PURPOSE!
- AND IT'S NOT LIKE I WANT TO BE
HERE GUARDING YOU RIGHT NOW.
- ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU
DON'T WANT TO PROTECT ME?
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT, SO DON'T GO
GETTING ALL HUFFY WITH ME, NINA.
IN ORDER TO PROTECT YOU, WE HAVE
TO STAY CLOSE, UNDERSTAND?
- YOU ARE SO BOSSY!
- HEY, NINA.
- NINA, GET BACK HERE.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
NINA!
- Ichii: I GUESS I CAN
UNDERSTAND WHY SHE'S SO UPSET.
IT'S PROBABLY NATURAL FOR HER
TO FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
SHE'S BEING FOLLOWED AROUND
ALL DAY EVERY DAY
WITHOUT EVEN A MOMENT ALONE.
- YEAH, I GUESS.
BUT WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO LEAVE HER ALONE NOW.
SHE'S IN TROUBLE
AND WE HAVE TO PROTECT HER
FROM THE EXAMINEES
AFTER THE PEARL.
WE HAVE TO.
THERE ARE QUITE A FEW OF 'EM
WHO WOULD HARM NINA
IF GIVEN THE CHANCE
AND REMOVE THE PEARL BY FORCE.
NINA CAN'T USE MAGIC,
SO IF THAT HAPPENS,
SHE WOULDN'T STAND A CHANCE.
AND THAT'S WHY WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO STAY HERE
AND DEFEND NINA
UNTIL THE MEDICINE'S READY.
I DON'T CARE IF SHE HATES US.
WE HAVE TO KEEP HER SAFE
AT ALL COSTS.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- YEAH.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
YOU GUYS?
I TOLD YOU TO STAY AWAY FROM ME,
DIDN'T I?
PUT ME DOWN.
ZERO, ICHII!
( crying )
- Forte: JUST GREAT.
I GUESS WE CAN'T DO ANYTHING
AS LONG AS THOSE GUYS
ARE KEEPING A CLOSE EYE
ON THE PEARL.
- OH, BOY,
I JUST GOT A GREAT IDEA.
- ARE YOU SURE, SAN?
- MM-HMM.  LEAVE IT TO ME.
THIS'LL BE GREAT.
I'M SURE
IT'LL LOOK GOOD ON YOU.
- LOOK GOOD ON ME?
- ( laughing )
I HAVE A QUESTION.
- FIRE AWAY, FO.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- IT'S MY BRILLIANT
DISGUISE FOR YOU.
- I'M DRESSED LIKE A GIRL.
- OF COURSE!
THIS WAY YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO ATTACK NINA
IN THE ONLY PLACE THOSE GUYS
CAN'T GUARD HER--
THE GIRL'S BATHROOM.
- JUST GREAT.
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
I LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT. NOBODY'S
GONNA THINK I'M A GIRL!
- Boy: HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
SOME NEW CLASSMATES.
AND EVEN BETTER,
THEY'RE BOTH CUTE!
WOW, I THINK I'M IN LOVE.
- THAT'S IT!
LET'S JUST GET THE CRYSTAL PEARL
ALREADY
SO WE CAN HURRY UP
AND GET OUT OF THIS PLACE!
- FO!
- SHUT UP, SAN!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- ROGER THAT.
I'M RIGHT ON YOUR TAIL,
BUT LET'S GO
GET THAT CRYSTAL PEARL.
- BACK OFF!
WHY CAN'T YOU
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE?
- HOW MANY TIMES
ARE WE GONNA HAVE TO TELL YOU?
IF WE'RE GONNA PROTECT YOU,
WE CAN'T BACK OFF.
- I UNDERSTAND,
BUT GIVE ME SOME SPACE.
YOU'VE RUINED MY REPUTATION
AND MADE ME THE GOSSIP
OF THE SCHOOL.
WITH YOU TWO ALWAYS AROUND,
PEOPLE THINK WE'RE GOING OUT.
- WELL, I CAN SEE
HOW THAT COULD BE A PROBLEM.
I REALLY WISH THERE WAS SOME
OTHER WAY TO DO THIS,
BUT THERE ISN'T.
I'M SORRY ABOUT ALL THIS,
NINA.
- YEAH. ANYWAY, THIS IS
FRUSTRATING,
SO CUT ME SOME SLACK.
DON'T-- AH!
- NINA!
ARE YOU OKAY?
ARE YOU OKAY, NINA?
DOES ANYTHING HURT?
- I-- I'M FINE, ICHII.
THANKS FOR ASKING!
OH, MY GOODNESS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
MY HEART IS STILL POUNDING.
IS IT POSSIBLE
THAT HE COULD BE--
COULD THE ONE WHO PROTECTED ME
IN MY DREAM BE...
ICHII?
- NINA, I'M GLAD YOU'RE OKAY.
- ( thinking ) IS IT POSSIBLE?
- All: HEY, NINA!
- WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU
AND THOSE TWO GUYS?
- YEAH, HOW WOULD YOU
CLASSIFY YOUR RELATIONSHIP?
- BOYFRIENDS?
- LOVE TRIANGLE?
- DO YOU KNOW
THEIR CELL PHONE NUMBERS?
- DON'T HOLD OUT.
GIVE THEM TO US!
- ( Nina shouting )
- ( Forte laughing )
THIS IS GOING TO BE A WHOLE LOT
EASIER THAN I EXPECTED, SAN.
NOW GIVE US THE PEARL.
- YOU GUYS
ARE SAN AND FORTE!
I HAD NO IDEA.
WOW, I REALLY HAD NO IDEA.
- UM, WHAT?
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE A BOY,
FORTE.  I'M SO SORRY.
- I AM A BOY!
YOU WEREN'T MISTAKEN.
THE ONE AND ONLY REASON
I WOULD EVER WEAR A DRESS
IS TO CAPTURE YOU.
GOT IT?!
- All: WHAT?!
YOU'RE A BOY?!
A BOY?!
- Girl: YOU PERVERT!
- AHH!
- All: AHHH!
WHAT THE HECK IS HE THINKING?
COMING IN HERE TRYING
TO PASS HIMSELF OFF AS A GIRL!
- IF I EVER CATCH UP TO HIM,
I SWEAR I'LL END HIS LIFE!
- WAIT!  OH!
- Girl: IT'S ICHII AND ZERO.
- WHAT ARE YOUR HOBBIES?
- WHAT TYPE OF GIRLS
DO YOU LIKE?
- DO YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?
- CAN I HAVE
YOUR CELL PHONE NUMBER?
- LET'S GET TOGETHER
AND HAVE A PARTY.
PARTY!
- HEY, ZERO,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE
WHILE WE'RE STILL ALIVE.
- WAIT!
- ICHII, ZERO!
- ALL RIGHT. I SHOULD GET OUT
OF HERE WHILE I CAN TOO.
- ( humming )
- AH!
- THAT'S CALLED AN AIR FISH.
IT'S A FISH,
BUT IT'S A CARNIVORE,
SO YOU MIGHT WANT
TO BE CAREFUL
'CAUSE THEY DO EAT PEOPLE
NOW AND AGAIN.
- AHH!
- WANT TO PLAY TAG?
I PROMISE
THAT IT'LL BE A TOTAL BLAST.
AND THOSE STINKY BOYS
AREN'T HERE TO RUIN OUR FUN.
- I DON'T WANT TO PLAY.
AHHH!
PLEASE HELP ME,
ZERO, ICHII!
- Ichii: COME ON, GUYS,
CALM DOWN.  OKAY?
- Girl: WE'LL CALM DOWN
IF YOU STOP RUNNING
AND ANSWER OUR QUESTIONS.
- DO YOU THINK I'M PRETTY?
- DO YOU LIKE BLONDES
OR REDHEADS?
- ARE YOU
IN A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP?
- THAT'S A TRICKY QUESTION.
- GIRLS, GET OUT OF MY WAY!
- AHH!
- WOW, THAT WAS GREAT.
YOU'RE SUCH A REBEL, ZERO.
- I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU THINK
OF ME, JUST GET OUT OF MY WAY.
- Zura: ZERO, LOOK.
- HUH?
- IT'S NINA.
- AHHH!
- AND SAN'S RIGHT BEHIND HER.
MOVE!
- ( grunts )
- ARE YOU HURT?
HE CAN BE A LITTLE ROUGH
SOMETIMES. SORRY.
BUT HE'S NOT A BAD PERSON,
NOT REALLY.
ANYWAY,
I HOPE YOU'RE OKAY.
- I FEEL JUST GREAT
NOW THAT YOU'RE HERE, ICHII.
- All: WE FEEL JUST GREAT!
WE FEEL JUST GREAT, ICHII!
- PLEASE, SOMEBODY HELP ME!
- San: GO GO GO!
- AHHH!
- GO GO GO!  GET HER.
- Zero: SAN, THAT'S ENOUGH!
WAY TO GO, GENIUS.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO STAY CLOSE TO US.
- DON'T BE SUCH A JERK!
YOU KNOW I'VE HAD
EXTENUATING CIRCUMSTANCES
TO DEAL WITH.
- I DON'T CARE
ABOUT YOUR CIRCUMSTANCES, IDIOT.
- DON'T YOU CALL ME AN IDIOT!
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WATCH THIS--
IDIOT, IDIOT.
IDIOT, IDIOT, IDIOT!
- THIS ISN'T A GOOD TIME
TO BE ARGUING, YOU GUYS.
BEHIND YOU!
- HEY, EVERYONE,
CHECK OUT MY AWESOME NEW FISH.
I HAVE A WHOLE SQUADRON
OF THEM NOW.
AND THEY CAN'T WAIT
TO SINK THEIR TEETH INTO YOU.
GET 'EM, FISHIES.
- ( all humming )
- OH NO, YOU DON'T!
- THERE'S MORE
WHERE THAT CAME FROM.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
- AND HERE'S ANOTHER!
AND ANOTHER!
- ( grunting )
- BUT I'M NOT FINISHED YET.
HERE COME A FEW MORE FISHIES.
- ALL RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THIS?
- San:
I'M PRETTY AWESOME, HUH?
I HAVE A WHOLE LOT MORE
IN STORE FOR YOU,
BUT I'M SURE YOU MUST BE TIRED
FROM SHOOTING ALL
THOSE FIREBALLS.
ARE YOU READY BREAK YET?
- IT HASN'T EVEN PHASED ME.
- OKAY.
THEN THIS SHOULDN'T
PHASE YOU EITHER, RIGHT?
TAKE THIS!
- AHH!
NINA!  ( grunting )
- OH NO, ZERO!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HEY, DON'T WORRY.
IT'S JUST A SCRATCH.
- BUT YOU'RE BLEEDING.
- I TOLD YOU, IT'S NOTHING!
- WHY DO YOU TRY SO HARD
TO PROTECT HER, ZERO?
ALL YOU CARE ABOUT
IS THE CRYSTAL PEARL ANYWAY.
SO WHY ARE YOU GOING
TO ALL THIS TROUBLE?
- WHAT I DO IS MY BUSINESS.
- BUT STILL, IF YOU JUST
GOT THE PEARL FROM NINA,
THEN YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO
GO THROUGH ALL OF THIS
AND GET YOURSELF HURT,
YOU KNOW.
- GEEZ, YOU'RE JUST
WASTING YOUR BREATH THERE, SAN.
I'VE ALREADY DECIDED
THAT I'M GONNA PROTECT HER
AND I WON'T LET HER DOWN.
- BUT, ZERO--
- A PROMISE IS A PROMISE.
- OH, WELL,
I GUESS IT'S TIME FOR ME TO
END OUR LITTLE PLAY DATE
AND DELIVER
THE FINAL BLOW THEN.
GO, AIR FISH!
GO!
- THAT'S IT, SAN.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS.
DESTRUCTION MAGIC!
AHHHH!
MAGIC CANNON!
- ( San laughing )
WOW, THAT WAS GREAT.
BUT NO MATTER
HOW MANY YOU DESTROY,
I CAN ALWAYS MAKE MORE.
- WOW,
YOU ACTUALLY FELL FOR IT.
THIS CURTAIN OF SMOKE
WAS PRETTY USEFUL.
GIVE ME THAT.
THANKS.
- GIVE THAT BACK!
- OH, NO,
I HAVE THE WAND NOW,
SO I'M IN CONTROL, SAN.
AND YOU CAN'T CAUSE
ANY MORE MISCHIEF.
- Forte: THAT WASN'T MISCHIEF.
AND NOW I'LL TAKE THIS BACK.
- FORTE?
- MISCHIEF IMPLIES PLAYFULNESS,
BUT I CAN ASSURE YOU
THAT WE'RE BOTH
COMPLETELY SERIOUS.
WE'LL GET THAT PEARL
FROM YOU SOMEHOW.
- YEAH, WORD OF ADVICE--
DON'T EXPECT TO BE
TAKEN SERIOUSLY WEARING THAT.
- JUST SHUT UP, ZERO.
AND PREPARE YOURSELF
FOR THE ONSLAUGHT.
- ALL RIGHT!
TIME FOR ME TO HAVE A LITTLE FUN
AGAIN WITH SUMMONING MAGIC.
READY?
BIG AIR FISH!
ATTACK!
- AHH!
NINA!
- ( playing )
HERE COMES THE HEAT.
FLAMES, BURST FORTH!
- AH!
- LOOK OUT.
- ZERO!
- THERE YOU ARE.
- DEFENSE MAGIC,
CRYSTAL BARRIER!
FORTE!
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT YOU DO TO TRY TO STOP US,
WE WILL OVERCOME YOU
AND PROTECT NINA.
I SUMMON DEFENSE MAGIC.
REFLECTING TORNADO!
AHH!
- ( both shouting )
- Forte: YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS!
- NINA, LET'S PLAY TOGETHER
AGAIN SOMETIME.
BYE FOR NOW!
- Both:
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, NINA?
- YEAH.  I'M JUST FINE,
BUT I THINK ZERO GOT HURT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- ICHII, YOU TOOK TOO
LONG TO SHOW UP.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I THOUGHT YOU'D EASILY
BE ABLE TO HANDLE OPPONENTS
OF THEIR SKILL LEVEL.
GUESS I WAS MISTAKEN.
- ARE YOU OKAY, ZERO?
- LET ME SEE YOUR ARM.
- ( thinking ) ZERO PUT HIS LIFE
ON THE LINE TO PROTECT ME,
AND EVEN HURT HIMSELF TRYING.
HE DID THAT FOR ME.
- AHH!
A PROMISE IS A PROMISE.
I WILL PROTECT YOU.
- ( thinking )
ZERO CAN BE REALLY OBNOXIOUS,
BUT DEEP DOWN,
I KNOW HE'S A GOOD PERSON.
- HEY, BE CAREFUL.
THAT HURTS.
OWWWWWW!
- ( Nina thinking )
HA. ZERO.
- NINA, THERE YOU ARE.
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU.
- YOU HAVE TO SEE THIS.
ISN'T IT CRAZY?
THERE WERE ALL THESE EXPLOSIONS.
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL
WAS IN A PANIC.
- WE HAD THE FIRE
AND POLICE DEPARTMENTS HERE.
IT WAS TOTALLY CHAOTIC.
- ZERO, I THINK
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
- ( all gasp )
- ( laughing )
- WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT?
- NOTHING.
- YOU'RE REALLY GONNA BE
IN SOME HOT WATER LATER, ZERO.
- I'LL PUT YOU IN HOT WATER.
- ( both laughing )
- Nina: I'M HOME!
- GOOD TO SEE YOU HOME, NINA.
- AH!
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU GUYS
TO NEVER ENTER MY ROOM
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
IS THERE ANY REASON
WHY YOU CAN'T RESPECT THAT?
- OH, WELL STARTING TODAY
WE DECIDED
THAT WE SHOULD
LIVE HERE WITH YOU.
- SAY WHAT?
- HA, HA. LOOK, I EXTENDED THIS
CLOSET WITH SOME MAGICAL SPACE
AND MADE A ROOM
FOR ZERO AND ME. SEE?
NOW YOU'LL NEVER EVEN KNOW
THAT WE'RE AROUND.
- BUT WHY?
- BECAUSE WE WANT TO STAY
AS CLOSE TO YOU AS POSSIBLE.
THAT WAY WE'LL ALWAYS BE HERE
TO PROTECT YOU.
- IT'S GREAT.
IT'LL BE JUST LIKE WE'RE
NEIGHBORS WHO SHARE A WALL.
- WE'LL TRY TO STAY
OUT OF YOUR WAY,
BUT HAVING US AROUND
COULD BE PRETTY HANDY TOO.
- WE'LL BE HERE
WHEN YOU NEED US.
SO DON'T WORRY.
- Ichii:
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH, AND IT'S OKAY, WE TOOK ALL
YOUR CLOTHES OUT OF THE CLOSET
AND PUT THEM
IN THAT ROOM OVER THERE.
- THIS IS MY NIGHTMARE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
HOW COULD MY LIFE
GET ANY WORSE?
- Ichii: YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
WE'LL KEEP
THE CLOSET DOOR CLOSED.
- AH!
THAT'S NOT THE ISSUE.
( crying )
MY NAME IS NINA YAMADA.
I'M JUST AN ORDINARY,
AVERAGE STUDENT,
SO WHY DO I HAVE TO DEAL WITH
THIS EVEN WHEN I'M AT SCHOOL?
- Zero: HEY, NINA,
WHERE ARE YOU?
- Ichii: THAT'S STRANGE.
I CAN'T FIND HER ANYWHERE.
- Zero: ICHII,
THERE'S A BABY OVER HERE.
- THAT'S A GOOD BABY.
DON'T CRY, OKAY?
- ( crying )
- Nina: NEXT TIME
ON "SAVE ME, LOLLIPOP"...