- MY NAME'S NINA AND I'M A
PRETTY AVERAGE, ORDINARY GIRL.
AT LEAST I WAS, UNTIL
ONE DAY.
I ACCIDENTALLY SWALLOWED
SOMETHING CALLED
THE CRYSTAL PEARL WHILE EATING
AT MY FAVORITE CAKE SHOP,
AND MY LIFE
HASN'T BEEN THE SAME EVER SINCE.
THIS PEARL IS AN IMPORTANT PART
OF AN OTHERWORLDLY SORCERY TEST.
IT'S DROPPED RANDOMLY
INTO THE HUMAN WORLD,
AND THE TEAM OF TWO EXAMINEES
WHO ARE ABLE
TO TRACK IT DOWN FIRST
WILL PASS THE EXAMINATION
AND BECOME
PROFESSIONAL SORCERERS.
THEN GET THIS THING OUT OF ME!
- STOP CRYING.
- YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO PREPARE YOURSELF, ZERO.
- HUH?
- NOW THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO DO THIS.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL HAVE TO
PROTECT HER ANY WAY WE CAN
UNTIL THE DAY THE TEST IS OVER.
WE'LL KEEP DILIGENT WATCH OVER
HER UNTIL THE MEDICINE IS READY
AND WE CAN EXTRACT
THE CRYSTAL PEARL FROM HER BODY.
WE'LL HAVE TO PROTECT THIS GIRL
WITH OUR VERY LIVES.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- SO YOU GUYS
ARE GONNA STAY HERE AND HELP ME?
REALLY?
JUST LIKE THE PRINCES
IN THE FAIRY TALE
WHO BRAVELY FACE THEIR ENEMIES
NO MATTER HOW FEROCIOUS
THEY MAY BE,
AND FIGHT TO THE BITTER END
FOR THE PEOPLE THAT THEY LOVE,
THESE TWO
ARE HERE TO PROTECT ME.
- HEY,
I TOLD YOU I WANTED THAT PIECE.
- NO WAY!
THIS ONE IS MINE.
- JUST GIVE IT TO ME NOW.
- I'M SURE THERE'S MORE OF IT.
- YOU GOT THE LAST ONE!
- I REALLY WISH THE TWO OF YOU
WOULD STOP ARGUING FOR ONCE.
YOU'RE BOTH DISTURBING
THE OTHER CUSTOMERS.
- ZERO STARTED IT!
- NINA STARTED IT!
( both grunting )
- MMMM!
OH, THAT WAS SO DELICIOUS.
MAY I HAVE PLEASE HAVE ANOTHER?
- HEY, GUYS,
I SAID KNOCK IT OFF.
- Zura: ZURA!
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
GET OUTTA HERE!
- All: YES, SIR.
- HMM.
LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE HAVING FUN.
- RATHER NONCHALANT
FOR EXAMINEES
IN THE MIDDLE OF A SORCERY
TEST. DON'T YOU AGREE?
- YES, THEY'VE GROWN
TOO RELAXED
WITH
THEIR CURRENT CIRCUMSTANCES.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
FOR ME TO TURN UP THE TENSION
AND SEE HOW THEY RESPOND.
SO SHALL WE PAY THEM A VISIT?
- SURE.
- TO THE HUMAN WORLD, THEN.
( laughing )
- AH!  WHY DIDN'T YOU GUYS
HELP ME PAY FOR IT?
- YOU BROKE THE STUFF.
- NO, YOU'RE TO BLAME
FOR THIS AS WELL, ZERO.
- HA HA!
YOU GOT OWNED.
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
- ( both groaning )
- WHY DOES IT HAVE TO
BE LIKE THIS?
ALL I WANTED TO DO
WAS EAT SOME CAKE
AND TALK TO THEM
A LITTLE WHILE.
- ( all grunting )
Zero: NINA!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( all shouting )
- Zero: SAN, FORTE!
- OH, I'M SO AMAZINGLY HAPPY
TO SEE YOU, MY DARLING.
OH, MY ICHII!
- OH, GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOU'RE GONNA TRY
TO STEAL NINA AGAIN.
- WE'RE NOT! WE WERE JUST
ABDUCTED BY SOME WEIRDO.
- WHAT WEIRDO?
- EXCUSE ME, BUT I TAKE OFFENSE
TO YOU CALLING ME A WEIRDO.
( laughing )
YOU MAY ADDRESS ME AS WILL.
I'M A PROFESSIONAL SORCERER.
WHAT'S MORE,
I AM AN INSPECTOR SENT FROM
THE SORCERY TEST HEADQUARTERS.
- AND WHY EXACTLY
DID THEY SEND YOU HERE?
- HEY, WAIT, THE TEST
ISN'T CLOSE TO BEING OVER.
WE HAVE TILL THE END
OF THE YEAR.
- TRUE, YOU STILL HAVE SEVERAL
MONTHS TO COMPLETE YOUR FINALS.
BUT I'VE GATHERED YOU ALL HERE
TODAY TO TAKE A MID-TERM EXAM.
- All: WHAT?!
A MID-TERM EXAM?
- AND, IF FOR ANY
REASON YOU'RE UNABLE
TO PASS THE MID-TERM TODAY,
YOU WILL BE DISQUALIFIED.
- NOBODY TOLD US ABOUT THIS.
- THAT'S RIGHT. AND WHAT IS
THIS MID-TERM EXAM ABOUT ANYWAY?
- HMM, THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
NINA?
AM I CORRECT IN ASSUMING
THAT YOU SWALLOWED
THE CRYSTAL PEARL?
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
- THEN MAY I PLEASE ASK
FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE?
- WHAT?
- YOU ARE THE MOST
IMPORTANT PART.
- NO WAY!
( grunts )
- THE OBJECTIVE
OF THIS MID-TERM IS SIMPLE.
YOU MUST RETRIEVE NINA FROM ME
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
THE TEAM THAT MANAGES
TO GET HER BACK BY SUNSET
WILL PASS THE MID-TERM EXAM.
THOSE WHO FAIL TO DO SO
WILL BE DISQUALIFIED.
SO GOOD LUCK, EVERYONE.
( laughs )
- Both: NINA!
NINA!
- WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
- YEAH, WE'LL ALL FAIL THE TEST
IF WE DON'T GET NINA BACK.
- THEN, I GUESS...
- WE DON'T HAVE A CHOICE!
- All: WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER
TO GET HER BACK.
All: WE CAN DO THIS TOGETHER!
WE'RE COMING TO HELP TOO!
COUNT US IN!
WAIT!  NINA!
- ( Will laughing )
THIS BUILDING LOOKS ORDINARY
TO THE NAKED EYE,
BUT BARRIERS SURROUND IT
SO THAT NO ONE MAY ENTER.
IN OTHER WORDS,
THIS IS MY FORTIFIED CASTLE.
AND I GUESS THAT MAKES YOU
MY CAPTURED PRINCESS.
SO HOW DOES THAT SOUND?
- YEAH, COULD YOU
REMIND ME AGAIN--
WHY EXACTLY DO I HAVE TO WEAR
THIS RIDICULOUS OUTFIT?
- I JUST THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT LIKE IT.
IT'S ONLY COSTUME,
BUT IT DID SEEM APPROPRIATE.
THIS IS JUST A PROP TOO.
- LET ME OUTTA HERE!
- JUST SHUT UP.
- WHAT?
DID THAT CAT JUST SPEAK TO ME?
- I TOLD YOU TO STOP TALKING.
AND HOW DARE YOU CALL ME A CAT?
MY NAME IS AQUAMARINE
AND I'M WILL'S
FABULOUS APPRENTICE.
- WAIT, THEN THAT MEANS
YOU'RE JUST LIKE ZURA, RIGHT?
- AH, NO DEAR,
I'M A PROFESSIONAL
SORCERER'S HELPER.
THAT THING
IS JUST AN EXAMINEE'S ASSISTANT.
- WELL, LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE HERE ALREADY.
AND SO NOW IT BEGINS.
- ( all panting )
- I FOUND HER, ZURA.
NINA'S IN THAT BUILDING,
I'M SURE OF IT.
- HE'S RIGHT.
I CAN SENSE HER.
I CAN SENSE NINA'S PRESENCE.
I'M COMING!
- ZERO, WAIT.
- NO, DON'T DO IT!
ZERO!
- AHHHH!
- HE'S FORMED A MAGICAL BARRIER
AROUND THE BUILDING.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME THAT?
- Will: YOU SHOULD'VE REALIZED
IT YOURSELF, ZERO.
- Ichii: INSPECTOR.
- THAT'S IT! I DON'T CARE
IF YOU'RE A PRO OR NOT.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
- NO, ZERO!
- NO, WAIT!  COME BACK.
ZERO!
- AHHHH!
- I THINK YOU AND I
REALLY NEED TO HAVE A TALK.
- I'M NOT ABOUT TALKING!
I'M ABOUT ACTION.
- Will:
ACTION AGAINST A HOLOGRAM?
WELL, I SUPPOSE I HAVE TO GIVE
YOU AT LEAST A LITTLE CREDIT
FOR MANAGING TO FIND THIS PLACE
SO QUICKLY.
AND NOW AS I'M SURE
YOU ARE AWARE,
BOTH NINA AND I ARE ON THE
TOP FLOOR OF THIS BUILDING.
TO GET TO US, YOU'LL HAVE TO
KEEP YOUR WITS ABOUT YOU
AND USE YOUR ABILITIES
TO OVERCOME THE TRAPS
I'VE SET ALONG THE WAY TO KEEP
YOU FROM REACHING THE TOP.
I WISH YOU ALL GOOD LUCK
BECAUSE, BELIEVE ME,
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED IT.
( laughs )
- Zero: NO WAY.
- Ichii: LET'S GET STARTED.
- Zura: FIRST WE HAVE TO
BREAK THE BARRIER
THAT'S SURROUNDING THE BUILDING.
- EVERYBODY STAY BACK.
LET ME HANDLE THIS.
I SUMMON FORTH DEFENSE MAGIC!
BARRIER RELEASE!
LET'S GO.
- YEAH.
- HMM.
THAT WAS MOST IMPRESSIVE.
BUT STILL, I SERIOUSLY DOUBT
THAT YOUR FRIENDS
WILL BE ABLE TO
OVERCOME THE OBSTACLES
I HAVE PREPARED FOR THEM.
- HANG IN THERE, NINA.
NO MATTER WHAT STANDS IN OUR
WAY, I PROMISE WE'LL SAVE YOU!
- LADIES AND GENTS,
THE FIRST CHALLENGE TODAY
IS AN EXCITING,
FAST-PACED POP QUIZ.
- All: AHH!
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHY DO SORCERERS
NEED TO TAKE A QUIZ?
- THIS IS A TEST TO
DETERMINE YOUR ABILITY
TO THINK UNDER PRESSURE.
THE QUESTIONS WON'T BE EASY,
SO BE PREPARED.
NOW LET'S BEGIN.
HERE'S YOUR FIRST QUESTION.
WHAT MEDICAL PRACTITIONER
IS HATED MORE THAN ANY OTHER?
- All: HUH?
WHAT TYPE OF DOCTOR
IS MOST HATED?
- DENTIST?
- All: OH!
- THAT IS CORRECT.
WHICH MEANS THE TEAM
OF GOU AND ROKKA
ARE THE FIRST TO PASS THE QUIZ.
- I'LL SEE YOU LATER, ICHII.
GOOD LUCK.
- NO FAIR.
- OH, GREAT, THEY BEAT US, ZURA.
- LET'S GO.
- THE SECOND QUESTION--
WHAT TYPE OF CAKE WOULD MAKE YOU
AFRAID OF BEING ELECTROCUTED?
- All: HUH?
- YOU, KNOW, ELECTROCUTION?
- IS IT SHORTCAKE?
- DING DING DING DING.
YOU ARE CORRECT.
TEAM ZERO AND ICHII
HAVE PASSED.
PLEASE CONTINUE
TO THE SECOND LEVEL.
- Both: SAY WHAT?
- SORRY, GUYS.
- LATER, DUDES.
- WE'LL BE WAITING UPSTAIRS.
- Forte: THIS ISN'T GOOD.
IF WE DON'T GET THE NEXT ANSWER
RIGHT, WE'LL BE DISQUALIFIED.
- I'M GETTING HUNGRY, FO.
CAN WE EAT NOW?
- DO YOU THINK YOU CAN WAIT?
WE REALLY HAVE TO
FOCUS ON THIS QUIZ.
- AW!
- THE FINAL QUESTION--
PAN MEANS BREAD IN JAPANESE.
WHAT KIND OF PAN
CAN YOU NOT EAT?
- YES!
THIS IS AN EASY ONE.
OH, THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU.
BECAUSE-- BECAUSE IT
CAN'T BE ANYTHING ELSE.
IT JUST HAS TO BE!
- I'LL REPEAT THE QUESTION
ONE MORE TIME.
IN JAPANESE, WHAT KIND OF PAN
CAN YOU NOT EAT?
- FRYING.
- I WANT SOME FRIED CHICKEN,
PLEASE.
- AH!
- ( buzzer sounds )
- THAT IS INCORRECT. THE
CORRECT ANSWER IS FRYING PAN.
- OH, NO! SAN SAID SHE
WANTED TO EAT FRIED CHICKEN.
SHE WASN'T ANSWERING YOU.
- I'M SORRY, BUT THE TWO OF
YOU HAVE BEEN DISQUALIFIED.
- THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT, SAN!
- Zero: I HAVE TO SAVE HER.
I HAVE TO.
I DON'T CARE WHAT OBSTACLES
WE HAVE TO OVERCOME.
- GOOD LUCK, ZERO.
PLEASE HURRY.
- ( girl screaming )
- WAS THAT ROKKA'S VOICE?
- LET'S GO!
- All: HUH?
- WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU!
- JUST LOOK
AT OUR AMAZING MUSCLES!
- AND NOW
FOR THE SECOND CHALLENGE,
YOU MUST TRY
TO DEFEAT THESE MACHO MEN.
- BUT THIS DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH MAGIC.
- THIS TEST WILL DETERMINE
IF YOU TRULY HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO CONTINUE.
- TRANSFORM MAGIC! ASSUMING
THE SHAPE OF AN ELEPHANT.
- UM, WHAT ARE YOU SUPPOSED
TO BE AGAIN?
- DOI!
A MIGHTY ELEPHANT.
- OKAY.
- I DO LOOK LIKE AN
ELEPHANT, DON'T I?
PRETTY DARN IMPRESSIVE,
ISN'T IT?
- ( all grunting )
- ROKKA,
YOU'RE A BIT OFF THE MARK.
TRY AGAIN, QUICK.
- TA-DA!
- WE'VE GOT YOU NOW.
- ( Rokka screaming )
- OH, NO!  DON'T WORRY.
I'LL CATCH YOU, LADY ROKKA.
- OH!
- Will: THE GOU AND ROKKA TEAM
ARE NOW DISQUALIFIED.
- OH, YEAH!
THAT'S RIGHT.  WE RULE!
- ZERO,
THESE GUYS MAY SEEM STUPID,
BUT YOU CAN'T UNDERESTIMATE
WHAT THEY'RE CAPABLE OF.
SO BE CAREFUL.
- OH, I CAN HANDLE THEM.
JUST LEAVE IT TO ME, ICHII.
- SURE THING.
- NOW THEN, WHO WANTS
TO PLAY ROUGH?
HAAA!
HERE I COME!
DESTRUCTION MAGIC!
HITTING KNUCKLE!
OH, YEAH.
THAT FELT GOOD.
- WELL DONE!
YOU PASSED THE ROUND.
ZERO AND ICHII, YOU MAY PROCEED
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
- ALL RIGHT!
THEY SHOULD BE HERE IN NO TIME.
- Will: I'M NOT SO SURE
ABOUT THAT, NINA.
FOR THE TEST
ISN'T OVER QUITE YET.
THERE'S STILL ONE FINAL
CHALLENGE THEY MUST PASS.
AFTER THE MENTAL
AND PHYSICAL OBSTACLES,
A SINGLE TEST REMAINS.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- ( roaring )
- A DRAGON?
- YEAH.
AND A REALLY BIG ONE TOO.
- ( roaring )
- WELL, ZERO AND ICHII,
DO YOU BELIEVE
YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO OVERCOME MY THIRD
AND FINAL CHALLENGE?
- ZERO!  ICHII, NO!
- READY?
- YEAH.
- ( Will laughing )
- ( roaring )
- YOU GUYS, BE CAREFUL!
- DEFENSE MAGIC!
- ( Will laughing )
I MUST SAY,
I'M PRETTY DISAPPOINTED
IN THIS YEAR'S EXAMINEES.
- WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
ZERO AND ICHII ARE
AWESOME, OKAY?
- REALLY?
DON'T YOU SEE WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- I KNOW THAT THEY'LL SUCCEED.
THEY'LL PASS YOUR TEST AND THEN
THEY'LL RESCUE ME, YOU GOT IT?
- I'M NOT SO SURE.
WEREN'T YOU FIGHTING EARLIER?
HONESTLY,
ARE YOU REALLY SO CONFIDENT
THAT THOSE TWO
WILL RISK THEIR LIVES
TO RESCUE SOMEONE
WHO DOES NOTHING
BUT ARGUE WITH THEM?
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
THAT THEY WILL.
- YEAH,
BUT ZERO AND ICHII PROMISED
THAT THEY WOULD BOTH
PROTECT ME.
- I SEE.
BUT THAT WAS BEFORE THE FIGHT.
- SHUT UP!
YOU DON'T KNOW.
I HAVE FAITH IN MY FRIENDS.
THEY'LL SAVE ME.
- HA.  FINE, THEN.
IF YOU'RE SURE THAT YOU'RE
RIGHT, THEN LET'S SEE.
LET'S TEST YOUR TRUST.
- BUT, WILL, THAT WAS NOT A
PART OF OUR ORIGINAL PLAN.
- WHAT ARE YOU--
- WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY NOW?
- ( squeaking )
( thinking )
MY VOICE-- MY VOICE IS GONE.
BUT HOW?
- AND NOW WE'LL FINALLY SEE
IF YOU CAN TRUST YOUR FRIENDS
AS MUCH AS YOU THINK YOU CAN.
WELL, ZERO AND ICHII,
NINA IS CALLING TO YOU.
COME TO HER.
TRY TO SAVE HER.
( laughing )
- LET'S GO.
WE HAVE TO FIND HER.
- EVEN IF IT'S A TRAP,
NINA NEEDS OUR HELP!
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( grunting )
- NINA?
- Will: SHE CAN'T TALK.
- WHY?
- SHE MADE A PACT WITH ME.
I'VE AGREED TO LET YOU
PASS THE TEST
IN EXCHANGE FOR NINA'S VOICE.
- IT CAN'T BE!
- THE DEAL IS FINAL.
NOW TAKE YOUR FRIEND BACK.
HERE.
- WHAT'RE YOU SAYING?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT IS IT?
- ( thinking )
IT'S NOT TRUE, YOU GUYS.
I NEVER MADE A DEAL WITH HIM.
- SHE SAW
THAT YOU WERE STRUGGLING
WHEN YOU WERE
BATTLING THE DRAGON,
SO NINA BEGGED ME
TO STOP THE EXAMINATION.
SHE THOUGHT THAT
YOU COULDN'T DEFEAT THE DRAGON,
SO SHE GAVE HER VOICE
IN EXCHANGE FOR YOUR LIVES.
- DON'T LISTEN TO HIM!
I BELIEVE IN BOTH OF YOU.
- SHE REALLY
IS QUITE A SWEET LITTLE GIRL.
THANKS TO HER,
YOU TWO HAVE PASSED.
WELL DONE.
- ( thinking ) IT'S NOT TRUE.
ZERO, ICHII,
HE'S LYING, I SWEAR.
- MAN!
THIS ISN'T GOOD AT ALL.
WE MADE A PROMISE TO HER--
TO PROTECT NINA NO MATTER WHAT.
- YEAH, BUT EVEN
IF WE PASS THE TEST,
IF NINA ISN'T SAFE,
IT'S POINTLESS.
- ENOUGH!
WE'RE NOT GONNA LET YOU GET
AWAY WITH THIS, YOU SLIME BAG.
- SO WHY DON'T YOU
GIVE HER VOICE BACK ALREADY?
- COME COME, RELAX.
YOU HAVE UNTIL SUNSET
TO RETRIEVE HER VOICE.
AND SINCE
I'M FEELING GENEROUS,
I'LL GIVE YOU TWO OPTIONS
TO CHOOSE FROM.
- WHAT ARE THEY?
- NINA'S VOICE IS RIGHT HERE.
IF YOU LIKE,
I CAN GIVE IT TO YOU NOW
AND WE'LL CALL
THE WHOLE THING OFF.
BUT THEN THE TWO OF YOU
WOULD HAVE TO DROP OUT
OF THE SORCERY TEST FOR GOOD.
SO WHAT WILL IT BE?
SORCERY OR HER?
- Both: THAT'S NOT--
- NOT WHAT?
- ( thinking )
WHAT ARE THEY GOING TO DO?
- IT'S YOUR MOVE.
ARE YOU GOING TO FINISH THE TEST
OR GIVE NINA HER VOICE BACK?
TELL ME.
- WELL THEN,
I GUESS WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
WE MADE A PROMISE TO NINA
AND I'M NOT ABOUT TO BREAK IT.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'VE MADE OUR DECISION.
- YES?
- I GUESS WE--
- WANT BOTH!
- EXCUSE ME?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HEARD US.
LET'S GO.
- YEAH!
LET'S TAKE THIS GUY DOWN.
DESTRUCTION MAGIC!
- DEFENSE MAGIC!
- MAGIC CANNON!
- DOPPLER CAPSULE!
- I SEE.
YOU'RE PLANNING ON DEFEATING ME
THEN GETTING HER VOICE BACK.
I SUPPOSE THAT COULD BE
AN OPTION AS WELL.
BUT...
YOU'RE TOO WEAK.
- OH, YEAH?
- WE'RE NOT DONE.
DESTRUCTION MAGIC!
- DEFENSE MAGIC!
- ( Will laughing )
- THIS GUY IS REALLY STRONG.
- OF COURSE I AM.
YOU'LL NEVER DEFEAT ME.
AFTER ALL, YOU'RE JUST AMATEURS.
I AM A PROFESSIONAL.
- WHAT DO WE DO?
- ZERO, FOCUS YOUR
TECHNIQUES ON ME.
- WAIT, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- IT'LL BE FINE.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
I'LL MAKE IT WORK.
- BUT--
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN TRUST ME.
- OKAY. JUST DON'T BLAME ME
WHEN IT ALL GOES WRONG.
- FINE.
- LET'S HOPE THIS THING WORKS.
- COME ON!
- DESTRUCTION MAGIC!
AHHH!
MAGIC CANNON!
TAKE THAT!
ICHII!
- Will: INSANE.
WHY IN THE WORLD IS ZERO
ATTACKING HIS OWN PARTNER?
- GOTCHA.
YOU FELL FOR IT.
- WHAT?  NO.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
ZERO ISN'T TRYING
TO ATTACK ME.
YOU MIGHT SAY THAT THIS IS AN
EXERCISE IN TRUSTING EACH OTHER
AND WORKING TOGETHER.
- OH!
NOW I UNDERSTAND.
THEY MUST'VE SUCKED THE MAGIC
CANNON ATTACK INTO THE CAPSULE
AND CONCENTRATED ITS FORCE
INTO THE SMALL SPACE.
THOSE TWO MUST BE MORE
POWERFUL THAN I EVER IMAGINED.
AHHH!
- I'VE GOT IT!
IT'S YOUR VOICE!
- THEY DID IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I WAS BEATEN
BY TWO AMATEURS.
IMPRESSIVE.
- SWALLOW THIS, NINA.
- THAT'S IT.
- MY VOICE, IT'S BACK.
- NINA!
YOU CAN TALK NOW.
- IT'S REALLY BACK.
- I'M GLAD THAT
YOU'RE SAFE, NINA.
- THANK YOU.
I KNEW YOU'D COME.
I ALWAYS BELIEVED.
I NEVER DOUBTED THAT YOU'D
RESCUE ME FOR ONE MINUTE. NEVER.
ZERO!
- DON'T WORRY.
- 'CAUSE WE ALREADY KNEW
THAT YOU HAD FAITH IN US, NINA.
- ZERO, ICHII,
YOU MEAN SO MUCH TO ME.
- Both: THANK YOU, NINA.
- I UNDERSTAND
THAT IT WAS YOUR STRATEGY.
BUT WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE THE BIGGEST
FOOLS I'VE EVER SEEN
FOR ATTACKING EACH OTHER
LIKE THAT.
IT DID WORK, THOUGH,
BECAUSE YOU TRUST EACH OTHER.
WITHOUT THAT SPECIAL BOND,
YOUR ATTACK WOULD HAVE FAILED.
AND YOU DEFEATED ME.
SO NOW, ZERO, ICHII,
IT'S MY PLEASURE TO ANNOUNCE
THAT YOU'VE PASSED
THE MID-TERM EXAM.
I'VE NEVER SEEN MAGIC
LIKE THAT BEFORE.
- Zero: REALLY?
- THANKS.
- YOU TWO ARE BOTH
TRULY SKILLED SORCERERS.
AND NOW,
SINCE I'M SUCH AN AMAZING GUY,
I SUPPOSE I'LL ALLOW ALL YOUR
FRIENDS TO PASS THE MID-TERM.
THEY SHOW REAL DETERMINATION.
SINCE THEY REFUSE
TO GIVE UP,
I'VE DECIDED TO GIVE THEM
A SECOND CHANCE.
THEIR PERSISTENCE HAS PAID OFF
AND NOW THEY WILL CONTINUE
ON WITH THE FINAL EXAM.
THEIR DREAM OF
BECOMING SORCERERS
IS STILL A POSSIBILITY.
AND JUST LIKE YOU,
YOUR FRIENDS WILL NEVER GIVE UP
ON THEIR DREAM.
THEY'LL CONTINUE TO FIGHT
FOR WHAT THEY WANT,
REGARDLESS
OF THE CIRCUMSTANCES,
AND I RESPECT THAT.
I SEE HOW HARD THEY'LL WORK
TO ACHIEVE THEIR GOALS.
SO I WILL ALLOW THEM
TO PASS THE MID-TERM
AND CONTINUE WITH THEIR ATTEMPT
TO PASS THE FINAL EXAM.
AND BESIDES, THE MORE
THE MERRIER, I ALWAYS SAY.
SO THAT MEANS ALL THREE TEAMS
WILL REMAIN IN THE COMPETITION.
EVERYONE'S QUALIFIED.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU ALL.
- All: HUH?
- AND THAT ABOUT WRAPS IT UP.
ADIEU.
- Zero: WILL!
- San: SO DOES THAT MEAN
WE PASSED THE TEST, FO?
- YEAH.
- WE DID IT!
NOW I CAN STAY HERE IN THE
HUMAN WORLD WITH MY ICHII.
- San: HEY, NINA?
- WHAT?
- DO YOU WANNA PLAY A GAME?
- All: LET'S DO IT!
- YOU MEAN YOU GUYS ARE ACTUALLY
GONNA CONTINUE TO CHASE ME?
AFTER ALL OF THIS?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE NOT GONNA STOP, EVER!
- WHAT?  EVER?
EVER IS SUCH A LONG TIME.
( crying )
OKAY, THAT'S IT! SOMEBODY GET
THIS PEARL OUT OF ME ALREADY!
- Ichii: HEY, NINA.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- Nina: THIS CHALLENGE
WILL TEST YOUR COURAGE.
RUMOR HAS IT THAT IF YOU CONFESS
YOUR LOVE TO YOUR PARTNER,
THEN THE RELATIONSHIP
WILL LAST FOREVER.
- Zero: HEY, WHAT THE
HECK ARE YOU?
- Yakumo: WE'RE GHOSTS!
- Nanase: AND I'LL SCARE YOU SO
MUCH THAT YOU'LL WET YOUR PANTS.
- Nina: NEXT TIME,
ON "SAVE ME LOLLIPOP"...
WOW!  TRY TO SAY THAT
THREE TIMES FAST.
NOW THAT'S REALLY SCARY.
( laughing )