- Nina: EVER SINCE THAT DAY,
THAT WONDERFUL DAY
WHEN I FIRST MET
ZERO AND ICHII...
- READY?
- YEAH.
LET'S GET THIS THING STARTED.
- ...THEY TOLD ME
THAT THEY WOULD PROTECT ME,
I THOUGHT THAT THEY WOULD
ALWAYS BE HERE FOR ME.
I THOUGHT
WE WOULD BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
- WHAT'RE YOU GUYS DOING?
- I NEVER REALIZED THAT THE TIME
WOULD ACTUALLY COME
WHEN WE WOULD
HAVE TO SAY GOODBYE.
BUT NOW
THAT TIME IS GETTING CLOSER.
I WONDER WHAT ZERO AND ICHII
ARE PLANNING TO DO?
ONCE THE CRYSTAL PEARL IS
REMOVED FROM MY BODY
AND THE TEST ENDS,
WHAT ARE THEY GONNA DO THEN?
THE TEST IS ENDING SOON.
IT'S ALMOST CHRISTMAS.
WOW!
THIS ONE'S SO CUTE.
- LOOKS TASTY.
- IT HAS A LITTLE SANTA CLAUS
ON IT,
AND REINDEERS TOO!
- YEAH, I CAN'T WAIT
TO EAT SANTA CLAUS.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU CAN'T EAT SANTA.
- WHAT?
BUT WHY CAN'T I, NINA?
- 'CAUSE HE'S A CANDLE, SILLY.
HE WOULDN'T TASTE VERY GOOD.
- IT'S ALMOST CHRISTMAS.
- THAT MEANS--
- IT'S COMING UP SOON, ZERO.
- YEAH.
TIME REALLY DOES FLY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S ALMOST CHRISTMAS.
- YEAH IT IS.
SPEAKING OF,
DO YOU TWO KNOW WHAT--
- HMM?
OH!  NEVER MIND.
( laughs )
- DON'T RUN OFF.
TELL US, NINA.
- NO.
IF I TOLD YOU,
IT WOULD RUIN THE SURPRISE.
- WHATEVER!
- ( thinking ) IT WOULDN'T BE
FUN IF I JUST ASKED THEM
WHAT THEY WANTED FOR CHRISTMAS.
I HAVE TO FIGURE IT OUT MYSELF.
I HAVE TO GET SOMETHING REALLY
SPECIAL FOR ZERO AND ICHII.
- EH?
AH!
- AHHH!
OF COURSE I'LL HAVE TO GET
SOMETHING NICE FOR ZURA AS WELL.
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL
VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
THEY'LL ALWAYS BE MY FRIENDS.
I WISH--
I WISH THAT THIS HAPPINESS
COULD LAST FOREVER,
BUT THE SORCERY TEST
IS ALMOST OVER.
IT'S CHRISTMASTIME.
JEEZ!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
WHAT SHOULD I GET THE GUYS?
CLOTHES?
JEWELRY?
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT KIND OF GIFTS THEY LIKE.
I GUESS HATS AREN'T REALLY
THAT TRENDY ANYMORE.
AND I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO KNIT A SCARF FOR THEM.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST GET ICHII
A FANCY WALLET OR SOMETHING.
AND ZERO, UM,
AN ORANGE VEST?
( moans )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY ARE YOU STARING AT ME
LIKE THAT?
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
- NINA!
MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
- 'CAUSE CHRISTMAS EVE IS
QUICKLY APPROACHING, YOU KNOW?
- SO WHAT?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "SO WHAT"?
YOU KNOW WHAT CHRISTMAS EVE
IS ALL ABOUT, RIGHT?
- NO.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- YOU NEED TO DECIDE
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO, NINA.
- WELL,
I DON'T REALLY KNOW YET.
- WE ARE TALKING ABOUT CHRISTMAS
EVE, DECEMBER 24th, THE BIG DAY.
- BECAUSE THAT'S THE DAY
YOU SPEND WITH THE PERSON
THAT YOU LOVE THE MOST.
- AND IT ONLY COMES AROUND
ONCE A YEAR.
- SO WHO ARE YOU GOING
TO SPEND THE DAY WITH, NINA?
WITH ZERO
OR WITH ICHII?
WHICH ONE?
COME ON, TELL US!
- AHHH!
- WHO ARE YOU GOING TO SPEND
CHRISTMAS EVE WITH? HUH?
- ( thinking ) "WHICH ONE"?
- NINA.
SO YOU'VE CHOSEN ME.
NINA.
NINA, MY LOVE!
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
I WON'T LET YOU HAVE NINA!
- OH YEAH?
I LOVE NINA MORE THAN ANYONE
IN THE WORLD.
AND I WON'T LET HER GO.
- HUH?
- FIGHT ME FOR HER.
- AS YOU WISH.
- ( both grunting )
- STOP IT!  STOP IT!
THIS IS MY FAULT.
PLEASE STOP FIGHTING.
I CAN'T CHOOSE.
I CAN'T CHOOSE BETWEEN YOU.
I JUST CAN'T DO IT.  AHH!
PLEASE STOP IT ALREADY.
STOP!
I CAN'T TAKE ANY MORE OF THIS.
PLEASE STOP FIGHTING.
- HUH?
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- HUH? UH, UH...
( laughing )
OH NOTHING,
FORGET ABOUT IT.
( thinking ) THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN PICK JUST ONE.
I WANT TO SPEND CHRISTMAS EVE
WITH ALL OF 'EM .
- ( grunting )
- EVEN ZURA.
- THIS ISN'T THE WAY
TO THE CAKE SHOP.
I WANT CAKE.
- UH, NINA?
- JUST WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- JUST GIVE ME
SOME TIME TO THINK, OKAY?
- WHAT'S WITH HER?
SHE'S ACTING STRANGELY.
- NEVER TRY
TO UNDERSTAND A WOMAN, ZURA.
- COME ON.
- ( thinking ) THIS IS
OKAY, ISN'T IT?
I DON'T HAVE TO
PICK BETWEEN THEM.
I JUST WANT TO BE WITH EVERYONE
NOW-- ZERO, ICHII, AND ZURA.
- HEY, NINA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YEAH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( thinking ) I WANT TO
SPEND CHRISTMAS WITH EVERYBODY.
OH!  I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT TO GET THOSE TWO GUYS.
WHY DOES THIS HAVE TO BE
SO DIFFICULT?
I MEAN, WHAT IN THE WORLD
DO YOU GET A SORCERER
FOR CHRISTMAS ANYWAY?
AH!  THAT'S PERFECT.
I'VE GOT IT.
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
( laughing )
AND YOUR SPECIAL PRESENT
IS ME, NINA!
NAH. I'D BETTER COME UP WITH
SOMETHING A LITTLE BETTER
TO GET THOSE GUYS.
WELL, I GUESS I COULD
JUST CASUALLY ASK THEM
WHAT THEY MIGHT LIKE.
THERE'S NO HARM IN THAT.
I WONDER IF THEY'RE STILL AWAKE.
I SURE HOPE SO.
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO?
- DO YOU MEAN
ABOUT CHRISTMAS?
- YEAH. I THINK WE SHOULD
GET HER A PARTING GIFT
BECAUSE WE'RE LEAVING.
- I SUPPOSE.
AFTER THE TEST IS OVER
ON CHRISTMAS, WE'LL LEAVE.
- RIGHT.
WE WON'T HAVE TO STAY
AND PROTECT NINA
AND THE PEARL ANY LONGER.
- AND THEN WE GET
TO GO BACK HOME.
AND NINA WILL BE
LEFT ALL ALONE.
- YEAH.
OUR TIME HERE'S JUST ABOUT UP.
BUT BEFORE WE LEAVE,
WE SHOULD DEFINITELY
GET A REALLY SPECIAL PRESENT
FOR NINA.
SOMETHING...
- ( thinking ) WHAT?
A PARTING GIFT?
I GUESS
THEY'RE REALLY LEAVING.
EVER SINCE THAT DAY,
WHEN I FIRST MET ZERO AND ICHII
AND THEY TOLD ME
THAT THEY WOULD PROTECT ME,
I NEVER REALIZED
THAT THE TIME WOULD COME
WHEN WE WOULD HAVE TO
SAY GOODBYE.
- DEFENSE MAGIC!
- I GUESS
THEY'LL HAVE TO GO BACK HOME
ONCE THE EXAM IS OVER.
AND WHETHER THEY PASS IT OR NOT,
I'LL NEVER SEE THEM AGAIN.
AND THEY'LL GO BACK
TO THE MAGIC WORLD,
LEAVING NOTHING BUT THAT
LOLLIPOP TO REMEMBER THEM BY.
( sobbing )
I WISH
THERE WERE NO SORCERY TEST.
I WISH THERE WERE NO CHRISTMAS.
OUR TIME TOGETHER
IS ABOUT TO END.
THE TEST IS ALMOST OVER.
AND IT'S ALMOST CHRISTMAS.
- Female voice: NINA.
- ( bell tolling )
- JEEZ, THAT STUDENT COUNCIL
MEETING TOOK FOREVER.
I'M RUNNING SO LATE NOW.
UH, NOBODY'S HERE.
I GUESS ZERO AND ICHII
HAVE GONE HOME ALREADY.
THAT'S PRETTY RUDE OF THEM
TO LEAVE WITHOUT ME.
NO BIG DEAL. I CAN ALWAYS
WALK HOME BY MYSELF.
I'LL BE JUST FINE WITHOUT THOSE
TWO PROTECTING ME. HA!
( thinking )
BUT NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
I HAVEN'T BEEN ALONE
IN A WHILE.
ZERO AND ICHII
HAVE BEEN WITH ME ALL THE TIME.
SO I HAVEN'T EVEN HAD A CHANCE
TO BE ALONE.
BUT I GUESS I'LL HAVE PLENTY
OF TIME TO BE BY MYSELF
AFTER CHRISTMAS.
I MIGHT AS WELL
GET USED TO IT NOW.
I NEED TO BE COMFORTABLE
BEING BY MYSELF AGAIN.
- Ichii: NINA.
THERE YOU ARE.
HOW DID YOUR MEETING GO?
- WELL, IT SURE TOOK FOREVER.
I THOUGHT IT'D NEVER END.
- NOW CAN WE GO BACK
TO THE CAKE SHOP, NINA?
'CAUSE I'M GETTING
REALLY HUNGRY, YOU KNOW.
- ZERO, ICHII?
- ( all laugh )
YOU TWO WAITED FOR ME?
BUT-- BUT--
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO PRETEND
THAT EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT,
THAT THEY'RE NOT
ABOUT TO LEAVE ME?
( crying )
- HEY, NINA!
WAIT!
- I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T GO
TO THE CAKE SHOP TODAY.
BECAUSE I'M LATE
FOR AN APPOINTMENT
WITH HATSUKA AND YOUKA.
- Ichii: NINA, WAIT.
- NINA!
- LET'S GO.
WE STILL HAVE TO PROTECT HER.
- RIGHT.
- COME ON.
- Hatsuka:
HEY, NINA, OVER HERE.
- HEY, SORRY I'M LATE.
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
- BUT WHERE'S ZERO AND ICHII?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WHAT?
BUT WHY AREN'T YOU WITH THEM?
- I DON'T HAVE TO
BE WITH THEM ALL THE TIME.
- WHAT?
YOU'RE ALWAYS WITH THEM.
- I JUST WANT
TO HAVE A LITTLE CAKE.
- DID YOU GUYS HAVE A FIGHT?
- NOT REALLY.
- Both: UM, SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
IS GOING ON?
- LET'S SEE...
- Zero: I THOUGHT SHE SAID
SHE DIDN'T WANT TO COME
TO THE CAKE SHOP TODAY.
- IT'S NOT FAIR.
SHE'S EATING WITHOUT ME.
- YEAH, WE SHOULD GO JOIN HER.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING, ICHII?
WHY CAN'T I GO AND JOIN NINA?
- JUST LEAVE HER ALONE.
- BUT WHY?
- 'CAUSE SHE MAY NOT
WANT TO DO THIS ANYMORE, ZERO.
- WHAT?
NO WAY.  SHE'S FINE.
- JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
SHE'S PROBABLY SICK OF US.
- BUT, ICHII,
WHAT MAKES YOU SAY THAT?
- LET GO. WE HAVE TO
PROTECT THE CRYSTAL PEARL.
WE HAVE TO.
WE DON'T HAVE A CHOICE HERE.
- BUT IT JUST SEEMS
LIKE A SELFISH REASON
FOR US TO DO THIS TO HER.
- ( all laughing )
- NINA IS JUST
AN ORDINARY HUMAN GIRL.
NEITHER THE CRYSTAL PEARL
NOR THE SORCERY TEST
ARE OF ANY CONCERN TO HER.
AND NOW NINA'S STUCK IN
THE MIDDLE OF THIS MESS
BECAUSE OF US, ZERO.
SHE DIDN'T ASK
TO BE ANY PART OF THIS.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
SO MAYBE WE HAVE TO GIVE HER
SOME ROOM OF HER OWN.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS MAKE SURE SHE'S ALWAYS SAFE,
BUT THAT'S IT.
I GUESS ONCE THIS WHOLE THING
IS OVER,
NINA WILL FINALLY
GET HER NORMAL LIFE BACK.
- BYE, YOU GUYS!
LATER.
- BYE.
- GOOD LUCK WITH
ALL OF YOUR HOMEWORK, NINA.
- WHAT?
WE HAVE HOMEWORK TO DO?!
- Both: JUST KIDDING.
NO HOMEWORK FOR US.
SEE YOU, NINA.
BYE.
- YEAH, THAT WASN'T FUNNY
AT ALL, YOU GUYS.
THANKS, JERKS.
ZERO, ICHII.
HAVE YOU GUYS BEEN
WAITING FOR ME THIS WHOLE TIME?
- OF COURSE.
- WE CAN'T LET YOU
GET ATTACKED AGAIN, NOW CAN WE?
- I'LL BE ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
- Ichii: NINA,
WE'RE SORRY FOR MAKING YOU RUN
AROUND WITH US ALL THE TIME.
- THERE'S ONLY ONE WEEK LEFT,
SO PLEASE JUST TRY TO BE PATIENT
WITH US TILL THEN, OKAY?
- WHEN THE TEST IS OVER,
WE'LL GO BACK HOME
TO THE MAGIC WORLD.
AND THEN YOU WON'T HAVE TO
HANG OUT WITH US ANY LONGER.
- BUT BEFORE WE GO HOME,
ZERO AND I WOULD LIKE TO GIVE
YOU A TOKEN OF OUR APPRECIATION.
- WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE?
IS THERE ANYTHING IN PARTICULAR
THAT YOU'VE HAD YOUR EYE ON?
JUST SAY IT AND IT'S YOURS.
- I DON'T WANT ANYTHING.
I JUST WANT
YOU BOTH TO LEAVE.
YOU'RE GONNA GO BACK HOME
SOON ANYWAY, SO LEAVE.
AND I DON'T NEED PRESENTS
TO HELP ME REMEMBER YOU TWO.
JUST GO, ZERO.
AND ICHII, GO.
( sobbing )
- WAIT, NINA.
- POOR NINA.
I THINK WE REALLY UPSET HER.
THAT'S AWFUL.
- ( Nina sobbing )
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
ALL THEY EVER DID
WAS LIE TO ME.
ZERO AND ICHII
ARE SO HEARTLESS.
- I GOT THIS FOR YOU.
- FOR ME?
- YEP.
I GOT YOU THIS LOLLIPOP
BECAUSE I THOUGHT IT FIT YOUR
IMAGE. IT'S CUTE, LIKE YOU ARE.
- OH, THANK YOU.
AFTER ALL
THAT THEY PROMISED ME...
I WISH THEY'D NEVER COME HERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE,
IF I HAD KNOWN
THEY WERE GONNA LEAVE.
I JUST HAVE TOO MANY MEMORIES
OF THEM BOTH.
ZERO, ICHII,
DON'T GO.
JUST STAY HERE.
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I WOULD DO WITHOUT YOU.
ZERO, ICHII!
- Zura: NINA? IS IT REALLY
THAT PAINFUL FOR YOU?
IF IT REALLY HURTS
FOR YOU TO LOSE ZERO
AND ICHII LIKE THIS.
THEN MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING
I CAN DO TO HELP YOU OUT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I HAVE THE MAGIC
TO ERASE YOUR MEMORIES.
- IF IT'S GOING TO BE HARD
FOR YOU TO COPE
AFTER ZERO AND ICHII
GO BACK HOME TO THE MAGIC WORLD,
AND IF YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO BE REALLY SAD
AND LONELY HERE WITHOUT THEM,
THEN I WOULDN'T MIND
HELPING YOU OUT
AND USING THE MAGIC
TO ERASE YOUR MEMORIES, ZURA.
- IF YOU DID THAT, WOULD I
REALLY FORGET ABOUT EVERYTHING?
EVEN YOU, ZERO AND ICHII?
- THAT'S CORRECT.
YOU'LL FORGET ABOUT THE DAY
YOU FIRST MET US,
AND ALL THE TIMES
WE'VE SPENT TOGETHER SINCE THEN,
ALL THE CAKES WE'VE EATEN,
AND THE TIME WE WENT TO
THE HOT SPRINGS,
AND THE BEACH.
YOU'LL FORGET IT ALL--
EVERYTHING.
ALL THE GOOD TIMES
WE HAD TOGETHER
AS WELL AS THE BAD
WILL BE ERASED FOREVER.
ALL GONE.
- ERASED?
EVERYTHING?
- THAT'S RIGHT, ZURA.
AND IF IT WOULD
MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER,
THEN I WOULDN'T MIND
DOING IT FOR YOU.
BUT IT'S UP TO YOU.
- I SEE.
- YOU HAVE TO DECIDE
FOR YOURSELF.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
YOU HAVE TO MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
NINA?
- I WANT--
- San: HEY, CHECK IT OUT!
NINA!
ISN'T IT GREAT?
JUST LOOK AT THIS DRESS!
IT'S MY CHRISTMAS PRESENT
FOR FO.
I'M GOING TO GIVE IT TO HIM
ONCE THE TEST IS OVER.
I BET HE'S GONNA LOVE IT!
( laughing )
- UH, I SERIOUSLY DOUBT THAT.
- IT'S A SECRET,
SO DON'T SAY ANYTHING TO FO THAT
WOULD RUIN THE SURPRISE.
SEE YA!
- Zero: I REALLY DON'T THINK
FORTE'S GONNA LIKE HIS PRESENT.
- Forte: WHOA!  MOVE MOVE MOVE!
GET OUT OF MY WAY.
AHHHH!
I'M SERIOUSLY HAVING A HARD TIME
KEEPING IT TOGETHER, YOU GUYS.
WILL SOMEBODY PLEASE HELP ME?
ANY-- OH!
( screaming )
THANKS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, FORTE?
- I'M GONNA BAKE A SPECIAL
CHRISTMAS CAKE FOR SAN.
- All: A CAKE?
- YEAH.
SAN SAID THAT SHE WASN'T
GONNA EAT ANY MORE CAKE
UNLESS I BAKED IT FOR HER.
WELL THEN, I'D BETTER GO.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE EVERYTHING'S
READY WHEN SAN COMES BACK.
- GOOD LUCK, FORTE.
- Zero:
IS THAT ROKKA OVER THERE?
- All: HUH?
- I THINK SO.
BUT WHY IS SHE ALL ALONE?
- EXCUSE ME.
- ( all grunting )
- HEY, AREN'T YOU--
- I'M GOU.
( echoing )
I'M GOU, I'M GOU.
- WE GET IT, YOU'RE GOU.
JUST TELL US WHAT YOU WANT.
- FORGIVE ME FOR MY RUDENESS,
BUT YOU SEE, LADY ROKKA IS--
- SHE'S WHAT?
THIS IS SO CONFUSING.
- SHE'S DRAWING A PICTURE AS
A CHRISTMAS PRESENT FOR ICHII.
SHE TOLD ME THAT I
ABSOLUTELY HAD TO
KEEP IT A SECRET FROM
ICHII UNTIL THEN,
SO I'D APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU COULD PRETEND
THAT YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT IT.
- OH!
THIS DRAWING IS MY MASTERPIECE.
- Nina: SHE'S REALLY EXCITED.
- I CAN'T WAIT FOR THE SORCERY
TEST TO BE OVER
AND FOR CHRISTMASTIME
TO BE HERE ALREADY.
- EVEN ROKKA'S GETTING READY
TO GIVE A GIFT
TO THE PERSON SHE CARES ABOUT,
BECAUSE SHE WANTS TO TELL
THAT PERSON HOW SHE FEELS,
BECAUSE SHE WANTS TO EXPRESS
HER APPRECIATION TO THAT PERSON.
ZERO AND ICHII HAVE BROUGHT
SO MUCH INTO MY LIFE,
MORE THAN THEY'LL EVER KNOW.
THEY'VE BROUGHT
THEIR KINDNESS TO ME
AND ALL OF OUR SWEET MEMORIES.
- ARE YOU OKAY, NINA?
- THIS ENDS RIGHT NOW!
- I GOT YOU.
- Nina: WE SHARE A MUCH STRONGER
CONNECTION,
BECAUSE OUR HEARTS
ARE BOUND IN FRIENDSHIP.
- I'M SORRY, BUT I'VE DECIDED
TO STAY WITH THEM.
I'VE THOUGHT EVERYTHING OVER.
AND EVEN THOUGH I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT THEIR PAST,
I KNOW I CAN TRUST THEM BOTH
AND THAT THEY'LL PROTECT ME,
BECAUSE THEY GAVE THEIR WORD
AND THAT'S ALL I NEED.
SO I REALLY
APPRECIATE THE OFFER,
BUT I'M GONNA HAVE TO STAY
WITH ZERO AND ICHII.
- NINA, YOU CAN TALK NOW.
- Nina: IT'S REALLY BACK.
- I'M GLAD THAT YOU'RE SAFE,
NINA.
- THANK YOU.
I KNEW YOU'D COME.
I ALWAYS BELIEVED
AND NEVER DOUBTED
THAT YOU'D RESCUE ME
FOR ONE MINUTE-- NEVER.
ZERO!
- DON'T WORRY.
- 'CAUSE WE ALREADY KNEW
THAT YOU HAD FAITH IN US, NINA.
- ZERO, ICHII,
YOU MEAN SO MUCH TO ME.
( thinking ) THEY'VE BEEN
GREAT TO ME, BUT STILL...
- Zura: NINA.
IF IT REALLY HURTS FOR YOU TO
LOSE ZERO AND ICHII LIKE THIS,
THEN MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING
I CAN DO TO HELP YOU OUT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I HAVE THE MAGIC
TO ERASE YOUR MEMORIES.
IF IT'S GOING TO BE HARD
FOR YOU TO COPE
AFTER ZERO AND ICHII
GO BACK HOME TO THE MAGIC WORLD,
AND IF YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO BE REALLY SAD
AND LONELY HERE WITHOUT THEM,
THEN I WOULDN'T MIND
HELPING YOU OUT--
- IF YOU DID THAT, WOULD I
REALLY FORGET ABOUT EVERYTHING?
EVEN YOU, ZERO AND ICHII?
- ALL THE GOOD TIMES WE HAD
TOGETHER AS WELL AS THE BAD
WILL BE ERASED FOREVER--
ALL GONE.
AND IF IT WOULD
MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER,
THEN I WOULDN'T MIND
DOING IT FOR YOU,
BUT IT'S UP TO YOU.
- I SEE.
- YOU HAVE TO DECIDE
FOR YOURSELF.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
YOU HAVE TO MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
NINA?
- I WANT YOU
TO ERASE ALL OF MY MEMORIES,
BECAUSE IT'S-- IT'S TOO PAINFUL
TO BE WITHOUT ZERO AND ICHII.
REMEMBERING THEM
WOULD JUST MAKE ME TOO SAD.
SO PLEASE, ZURA,
ERASE MY MEMORIES.
TAKE AWAY EVERY THOUGHT OF THE
FUN THINGS WE DID TOGETHER--
THE BEACH, THE HOT SPRING,
AND EVERYWHERE ELSE WE WENT.
I DON'T WANT THERE TO BE
ANYTHING LEFT. ZURA!
- I UNDERSTAND.
NOW I GUESS I NEED YOU
TO GIVE ME THE LOLLIPOP.
- HUH?
- IN ORDER TO DO THIS,
I NEED AN ITEM OF YOURS
THAT IS FILLED WITH MEMORIES.
- YOU NEED IT NOW?
- I SUPPOSE NOT.
YOU CAN WAIT AND GIVE IT TO ME
WHEN WE GO BACK HOME.
I'LL CAST THE ERASING MAGIC
ON THE LOLLIPOP
WHEN WE GET
TO THE MAGIC WORLD.
ONCE WE'RE GONE,
YOU'LL FORGET EVERYTHING
ABOUT ZERO AND ICHII
AND ALL OUR TIME TOGETHER.
SO IF-- IF THIS
IS WHAT YOU REALLY WANT, NINA,
BE SURE TO GIVE ME THE LOLLIPOP
BEFORE WE LEAVE.
- MY LOLLIPOP.
- Ichii:
YEAH?  WHAT ABOUT IT?
- I DECIDED I WANT TO KEEP IT!
I DON'T WANT
TO GIVE MY LOLLIPOP AWAY.
NO MATTER HOW LONELY OR PAINFUL
IT MAY BE,
I WANT TO REMEMBER
THE BOTH OF YOU FOREVER.
I NEVER WANT TO FORGET YOU TWO.
AND WHETHER THEY'RE GOOD
OR BAD MEMORIES,
THEY'RE STILL MEMORIES OF YOU,
AND I WANT TO TREASURE THEM
AS LONG AS I CAN.
I HOPE
THAT I NEVER FORGET YOU.
I WANT TO KEEP YOUR
MEMORY ALIVE.
- NINA.
- ZERO, ICHII!
I COULDN'T IMAGINE
BEING APART FROM YOU TWO.
BUT FORGETTING ABOUT YOU
IS EVEN WORSE.
PROMISE THAT
YOU'LL NEVER FORGET ME,
EVEN AFTER THE TEST IS OVER,
OKAY?
EVEN AFTER YOU GO BACK
TO THE MAGIC WORLD,
DON'T FORGET ABOUT ME.
- NINA.
- AND YOU-- YOU TWO
WILL BE MY PRINCES FOREVER.
- NINA.
- ( thinking ) ZERO, ICHII--
I NEVER WANT
TO BE APART FROM THEM.
BUT THE TEST IS ABOUT TO END
AND THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT IT.
CHRISTMASTIME
IS GETTING CLOSER.
AND THAT MEANS THAT SOON
WE WON'T BE TOGETHER ANYMORE.
BUT I WANT TO BELIEVE THAT WE
DON'T HAVE TO BE APART FOREVER.
AND THAT ONE DAY,
WHEN I LEAST EXPECT IT,
I'LL SEE THEM AGAIN.
ZERO, ICHII,
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU
FOR SO MANY MEMORIES.
- HUH?
- ( grunts )
- Zero: WHO ARE YOU?
- MY NAME IS RIRU.
I'M HERE TO HELP NINA.
Riru:
NOW TAKE THIS MEDICINE.
IF YOU DO, THE CRYSTAL PEARL
WILL LEAVE YOUR BODY.
- Zero: YOU DON'T HAVE TO, NINA.
WE'LL PROTECT YOU.
- Bird: STOP THAT NONSENSE.
IT'S DANGEROUS!
IT COULD BE LIFE THREATENING!
- BUT WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
I DON'T WANT TO BE APART
FROM ZERO AND ICHII.
NEXT TIME
ON "SAVE ME! LOLLIPOP"...
- YOU'LL TAKE IT BECAUSE THAT'S
THE ANSWER YOU'VE CHOSEN.