- MY NAME'S NINA AND I'M A
PRETTY AVERAGE, ORDINARY GIRL.
AT LEAST I WAS,
UNTIL ONE DAY.
I ACCIDENTALLY SWALLOWED
SOMETHING CALLED
THE CRYSTAL PEARL WHILE EATING
AT MY FAVORITE CAKE SHOP,
AND MY LIFE
HASN'T BEEN THE SAME EVER SINCE.
THIS PEARL IS AN IMPORTANT PART
OF AN OTHERWORLDLY SORCERY TEST.
IT'S DROPPED RANDOMLY
INTO THE HUMAN WORLD,
AND THE TEAM OF TWO EXAMINEES
WHO ARE ABLE
TO TRACK IT DOWN FIRST
WILL PASS THE EXAMINATION
AND BECOME
PROFESSIONAL SORCERERS.
THEN GET THIS THING OUT OF ME!
- STOP CRYING.
- YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO PREPARE YOURSELF, ZERO.
- HUH?
- NOW THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO DO THIS.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL HAVE TO
PROTECT HER ANY WAY WE CAN
UNTIL THE DAY THE TEST IS OVER.
WE'LL KEEP DILIGENT WATCH OVER
HER UNTIL THE MEDICINE IS READY
AND WE CAN EXTRACT
THE CRYSTAL PEARL FROM HER BODY.
WE'LL HAVE TO PROTECT THIS GIRL
WITH OUR VERY LIVES.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- SO YOU GUYS
ARE GONNA STAY HERE AND HELP ME?
REALLY?
JUST LIKE THE PRINCES
IN THE FAIRY TALE
WHO BRAVELY FACE THEIR ENEMIES
NO MATTER HOW FEROCIOUS
THEY MAY BE,
AND FIGHT TO THE BITTER END
FOR THE PEOPLE THAT THEY LOVE,
THESE TWO
ARE HERE TO PROTECT ME.
- San:
♪ A LITTLE BIRDIE FLIES AWAY ♪
♪ BAD BIRDIE, BAD BIRDIE,
SHOULD LEARN TO STAY ♪
♪ TURN BACK ♪
♪ AND FLY HOME TO ME ♪
♪ YOU BELONG HERE ♪
♪ IT'S WHERE YOU SHOULD BE ♪
♪ WHY DID YOU ♪
♪ TRY TO LEAVE ME
HERE ALL ALONE? ♪
♪ AND IF YOU DON'T DO
JUST AS I SAY ♪
♪ I'LL TAKE YOUR WINGS ♪
♪ THEN YOU CAN'T FLY AWAY. ♪
- Woman: THAT LITTLE GIRL
FRIGHTENS ME.
- Woman #2:
THEY SAY SHE'S CURSED.
- Woman #3:
STOP, YOU'RE SCARING ME.
- Man:
SHE IS MOST DEFINITELY HEXED.
- WE SHOULD RUN HER OUT OF TOWN.
- GET OUT OF HERE.
- STAY AWAY.
- LEAVE US.
- SHE CAN'T BE TRUSTED.
- All: LEAVE US, CURSED ONE.
LEAVE US, CURSED ONE!
( chattering continues )
- ♪ WHY'D YOU LEAVE ME HERE
ALL ALONE? ♪
♪ AND IF YOU DON'T DO
JUST AS I SAY ♪
♪ I'LL TAKE YOUR WINGS ♪
♪ THEN YOU CAN'T FLY AWAY. ♪
- THE CAKES HERE ARE ALMOST
AS GOOD AS THE ONES BACK HOME.
- Zura: MM-HMM.
- ( thinking )
LIFE IS SO STRANGE SOMETIMES.
NOW I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE
BEING WITHOUT THE THREE OF THEM.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- HUH?  IT'S NOTHING.
I WAS JUST DAYDREAMING.
- OH, NO!
LOOK OUT BEHIND YOU!
- ( San laughing )
- DON'T WORRY, NINA.
- WE WON'T LET THEM
ANYWHERE NEAR YOU.
- IS IT OKAY IF WE EAT MORE CAKE
WHILE YOU PROTECT US?
- I'M STARVING, FO.
I HAVE TO
GET SOMETHING TO EAT.
I'M SO THIRSTY TOO.
BUY ME SOMETHING TO DRINK.
I WANT ICE CREAM.
AND A FRUIT CUP!
I WANT--
NOW I'M EXHAUSTED.
I CAN'T TAKE ANOTHER STEP.
- WHAT WOULD YOU
EVER DO WITHOUT ME, SAN?
- ( laughs ) THANK YOU!
- WHAT WAS ALL THAT?
- NO IDEA.
- ( Forte shouting )
- All: HUH?
- GET AWAY, GET AWAY,
GET AWAY!
- BUT I'M NOT FINISHED
PLAYING YET.
GET BACK HERE, FO.
- I TOLD YOU,
I DON'T WANNA TO WRESTLE
WITH YOU, SAN!
I DON'T WANT
TO PLAY HOUSE EITHER, OKAY?
- BUT TODAY IS DIFFERENT.
COME ON, IT'LL BE FUN.
( laughing )
- AHHH!
- TODAY IS THE DAY
WE PLAY DRESS-UP, FO.
- WHAT THE HECK IS THIS?!
- I KNEW THAT COLOR
WOULD LOOK GOOD ON YOU.
- AHH!
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?!
- IT'S HARD TO SAY.
- IT DOES LOOK AMAZING ON YOU.
- SAN SHOULD PICK OUT
YOUR CLOTHES ALL THE TIME.
- YOU'RE ALL DOLLED UP.
- ( all laughing )
- AHH!
- HEY, FO!
WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
- SAN, YOU IDIOT!
- I WANT SOME TANGO TARTS
AND SOME
OF BUJIYA'S CREAM PUFFS,
A HEALTHY HELPING
OF PASTELA'S PUDDING,
AND COZY CUL-DE-SAC'S SHORTCAKE.
- FORTE'S BEING
REALLY PATIENT WITH HER, ZURA.
- YEAH, SAN MUST'VE DUG UP
SOME DIRT ON HIM OR SOMETHING.
- YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
THEY'VE KIND OF ALWAYS BEEN
LIKE THIS, HAVEN'T THEY?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DOES FORTE ACT SO SWEET
TO THAT ANNOYING LITTLE GIRL?
IT JUST DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
- HEY, FO?
- JUST DON'T ASK.
I CAN'T BUY YOU ANYTHING ELSE.
- BUT THERE'S ONE MORE THING
I NEED TO MAKE TODAY COMPLETE.
AND IT'S MY VERY FAVORITE.
- WHAT IS IT?
WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY LIKE
MORE THAN TANGO'S TARTS
OR BUJIYA'S CREAM PUFFS?
- THEY AREN'T NEARLY AS GOOD
AS YOUR HOMEMADE COOKIES.
WILL YOU PLEASE
MAKE ME SOME COOKIES, FO?
- BUT--
- BUT PRETTY PRETTY PLEASE?
I'LL BE
YOUR BESTEST FRIEND FOREVER.
PLEASE?
- ( oven dings )
- ( thinking ) JEEZ, THE THINGS
I DO TO KEEP THIS GIRL HAPPY.
PERFECT.
SAN?
YOU HERE?
"FORTE, I'LL BE BACK
IN TIME FOR TEA.
LOVE, SAN."
THAT LITTLE BRAT.
SHE LEFT
WITHOUT EVEN TRYING MY COOKIES.
( thinking )
THAT'S RIGHT.
OF COURSE.
HOW COULD I FORGET?
I KNOW WHERE SHE IS.
IT'S BEEN SEVEN YEARS
SINCE THAT DAY.
- ( bell tolling )
- Woman: WELL WELL WELL.
DON'T YOU LOOK SO HANDSOME?
YOU ARE MY PERFECT LITTLE
GENTLEMAN, AREN'T YOU, FORTE?
AND NOW YOU'RE READY
TO ATTEND THE TEA PARTY
AT YOUR GRANDFATHER'S MANSION
TODAY.
EVERYONE WILL THINK
THAT YOU'RE JUST PRECIOUS.
- GRANDFATHER'S MANSION?
- I'M SURE IT'LL BE A LOT OF FUN
FOR YOU, FO.
AND THIS WAY,
YOU'LL GET A CHANCE TO
KNOW HIM A LITTLE BETTER.
- OH.
IF YOU SAY SO, MOM.
- ( all laughing )
- HOW OLD ARE YOU?
YOU'RE SO CUTE.
- I'M SEVEN YEARS OLD.
- AND WHAT KIND OF MAGIC
DO YOU USE?
- HYPNOSIS MAGIC.
MY MOM IS TEACHING ME.
- OH, HOW IMPRESSIVE.
- ( girl screaming )
- ( objects clattering )
- ( squawking )
- ( all screaming )
- ( San laughing )
- THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME...
THAT SAN AND I
MET EACH OTHER.
UH, HEY, YOU,
DON'T GO.
WAIT A MINUTE.
- Mother: FORTE.
FORTE, ARE YOU HURT?
- I'M FINE, MOM.
DON'T WORRY.
BUT WHO WAS THAT GIRL?
- HER NAME IS SAN.
SHE'S LADY SALIA'S DAUGHTER.
- THEN THAT WOULD MEAN
SAN IS YOUR COUSIN.
- SHE IS?
- BUT I WONDER WHY
SHE ATTACKED YOU LIKE THAT.
- SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN THIS WAY.
SINCE I CAN REMEMBER.
- THAT GIRL HAS DISPLAYED
EXTRAORDINARY MAGICAL POWERS
EVER SINCE
SHE WAS JUST A LITTLE BABY.
SHE HAS NO IDEA
WHAT SHE'S CAPABLE OF.
- AND YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT SHE'S GONNA DO NEXT.
- I BET SHE'S THE REASON
LADY SALIA'S FALLEN ILL.
- LISTEN, FO, I WANT YOU
TO STAY AWAY FROM HER.
- Woman: I MEAN,
HAVE YOU SEEN HER LATELY?
- Man:
SHE IS A FEROCIOUS CHILD.
FOR ONCE THE RUMORS ARE TRUE.
- SHE'S SO UNUSUAL.
SHE MUST BE CURSED.
- ( thinking )
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT CAN'T BE.
BAD THINGS HAPPEN
BECAUSE OF HER?
IS THAT WHY EVERYONE
HATES THAT GIRL?
BECAUSE SHE'S CURSED?
THAT MUST BE WHY SHE HAD
SUCH A SAD LOOK IN HER EYES.
- ( San laughing )
- POOR GIRL.  HOW SAD.
SHE MUST BE LONELY.
I CAN'T IMAGINE.
- SHE TRIED TO PUT A CURSE
ON THAT LITTLE BOY FORTE
THIS AFTERNOON.
- I KNOW. HER MAGICAL
POWERS ARE BECOMING--
- ( both gasp )
- THAT GIRL
REALLY FRIGHTENS ME.
- I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
SHE'S SO STRANGE.
- YEAH.
WE'D BETTER STAY AWAY FROM HER.
- NOW FORTE, TRY AGAIN.
- YES, MOM.
- ( playing )
- ( squawking gently )
- THAT'S MY BOY.
WONDERFUL.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
- IT'S SO FRIGHTENING.
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
ALL THESE OMINOUS THINGS
KEEP HAPPENING TODAY.
- Mother: FO, I DON'T WANT YOU
ASSOCIATING WITH HER.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
STAY AWAY FROM THAT GIRL.
FO?  FO.
- ( squawking )
- ( playing )
- ( Mother sighs )
IS THERE SOMETHING
BOTHERING YOU?
- I'M SORRY, MOM.
FORGIVE ME,
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO DO.
- FO, WAIT, NO!
- ( thinking ) FOR SOME REASON,
I JUST CAN'T GET THAT GIRL
OUT OF MY HEAD.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT HER--
HER EYES, HER SMILE.
I MAY NOT BE ABLE TO DO
ANYTHING TO HELP HER,
BUT I NEED TO FIND HER.
I HAVE TO SEE HER AGAIN.
I HAVE TO.
- San:
♪ A LITTLE BIRDIE FLIES AWAY ♪
♪ BAD BIRDIE, BAD BIRDIE,
SHOULD LEARN TO STAY ♪
♪ TURN BACK ♪
♪ AND FLY HOME TO ME ♪
♪ YOU BELONG HERE ♪
♪ IT'S WHERE YOU SHOULD BE ♪
♪ WHY DID YOU ♪
♪ TRY TO LEAVE ME
HERE ALL ALONE? ♪
♪ AND IF YOU DON'T DO
JUST AS I SAY ♪
♪ I'LL TAKE YOUR WINGS ♪
♪ THEN YOU CAN'T FLY AWAY. ♪
WHO'S THERE?
- IT'S JUST ME.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE AFRAID.
I CAME TO FIND YOU.
THIS MAY SOUND STRANGE, BUT--
BUT I WAS JUST HOPING
TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
- MY FRIEND?
- MM-HMM.
DO YOU WANNA PLAY A GAME?
- WHAT?
YOU MEAN YOU'RE NOT AFRAID?
- NO.
- OH.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- WELL, MY FULL NAME IS FORTE.
WHAT'S YOURS?
- WHO, ME?
IT'S SAN.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
( Forte thinking )
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
I MADE MY DECISION
RIGHT THEN AND THERE.
I DECIDED TO TAKE SAN
AS MY PARTNER.
AND I KNEW THAT MY LIFE
WOULD NEVER BE THE SAME.
NO.
I CAN'T TAKE ANY MORE OF THIS!
- COME ON,
DON'T BE SUCH A SISSY.
I'M HUNGRY!
I NEED SOMETHING TO EAT.
I'M THIRSTY!
LET'S GO GET SOMETHING TO DRINK.
OOH, AND I WANT SOME ICE
CREAM TOO, AND SOME FRUIT.
- AH!
- AW, NOW I CAN'T
TAKE ANOTHER STEP.
I'M SO TIRED.
- ALL RIGHT.
GUESS THAT'S MY CUE.
JUST GO AHEAD AND CLIMB ABOARD.
- ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, FO.
YOU'RE SO NICE TO ME.
- GET AWAY, GET AWAY, GET AWAY,
GET AWAY, GET AWAY!
- BUT FO, WAIT!
I JUST WANNA WRESTLE.
OR MAYBE WE CAN PLAY HOUSE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- THEN WE'LL DO
SOMETHING DIFFERENT, OKAY?
COME ON.
I KNOW!
WE'LL PLAY DRESS-UP!
- WHOA!
WHAT IS THIS THING?
- YOU'RE SO ADORABLE.
THAT DRESS LOOKS GREAT ON YOU.
- OH!
- HEY, FO!  WAIT UP.
- ( Forte crying )
THAT IDIOT SAN!
- FO?
- Woman:
WHO'S THERE?
- ( thinking )
WOW, SHE'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
- CAN I HELP YOU
WITH SOMETHING?
- UM, I JUST GOT LOST
AND I'M REALLY SORRY.
- San: ARE YOU IN THERE?
- MY FRIEND'S CALLING ME.
IN HERE, SAN.
I CAME IN THE WRONG ROOM.
I GOT LOST.
- I'M GLAD I FOUND YOU, FO.
- IT'S YOU.
- HI, MAMA.
YAY!
- MAMA?
THIS WOMAN WHO LOOKS LIKE
SHE COULD BE SAN'S OLDER SISTER
IS REALLY HER MOTHER?
- MAMA!
- MY DEAR SAN.
- I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN
SAN SMILE LIKE THAT BEFORE.
SHE LOOKS SO HAPPY.
- WHAT'RE YOU DOING IN HERE,
SAN?
- FATHER.
- I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO STAY AWAY FROM YOUR MOTHER.
YOU MUST LEAVE.
- LET HER STAY, FATHER.
PLEASE JUST LET SAN STAY WITH ME
A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
- NO.
- PLEASE!
LET ME TALK TO MY DAUGHTER.
YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO KEEP HER FROM ME.
- I HAVE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU.
HOW DARE YOU SNEAK INTO YOUR
MOTHER'S ROOM BEHIND MY BACK?
I WILL NOT STAND FOR THIS,
NOT FOR ONE MOMENT.
SALIA IS SICK
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF YOU.
WHENEVER YOU'RE NEAR HER,
HER CONDITION SEEMS TO WORSEN.
SO STAY AWAY, CURSED CHILD.
- NOW WATCH IT, OLD MAN.
I WON'T LET YOU TALK TO SAN
LIKE THAT.
- IT'S OKAY, FO.
I KNOW I SHOULDN'T
HAVE DISOBEYED
MY GRANDFATHER'S WISHES.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THAT MEAN OLD MAN'S
OUR GRANDPA?
IT DIDN'T SEEM LIKE
HE WAS VERY FRIENDLY.
WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM ANYWAY?
- GRANDFATHER DOESN'T
LIKE ME VERY MUCH.
- BUT WHY?
- I'M RESPONSIBLE
FOR MY MOM'S ILLNESS.
THEY SAY I'M A CURSED CHILD.
AND THAT MY MOM WILL DIE IF I'M
CLOSE TO HER FOR TOO LONG.
- BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I THINK I KNOW
HOW TO HELP MY MOM, FO.
- YOU DO?
- MM-HMM.
MY MOTHER ALWAYS TOLD ME
THAT GOOD THINGS WOULD HAPPEN
TO ME AS LONG AS I KEPT SMILING.
SO MAYBE SHE'S RIGHT--
MAYBE I CAN CURE HER ILLNESS
IF I KEEP A SMILE ON MY FACE.
BUT I DON'T ENJOY IT
VERY MUCH.
AND SO FAR,
NO MATTER HOW MUCH I SMILE,
MY MOM'S CONDITION
HASN'T GOTTEN ANY BETTER.
I'M TRYING MY BEST,
BUT IT JUST ISN'T WORKING.
I WONDER WHY MY SMILES
HAVEN'T MADE MY MOM FEEL BETTER.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
- ( thinking )
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT, SAN.
YOUR MOTHER TOLD YOU TO SMILE
SO YOU WOULDN'T BE AFRAID.
THERE'S REALLY NOTHING
YOU CAN DO FOR HER NOW.
I WISH
I COULD'VE TOLD HER THAT.
BUT I COULDN'T FIND THE WORDS
TO EXPRESS IT,
SO I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
ALL I COULD DO
WAS HOLD HER HAND.
I COULD DO NOTHING
BUT COMFORT HER
AND STAY BY HER SIDE.
SO THAT'S WHAT I DID.
I SAT BY HER SIDE.
I TRIED
TO MAKE HER FEEL BETTER,
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW HOW.
- Woman:
IT CERTAINLY WAS SUDDEN.
- I FEEL SORRY FOR HER.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WHY DID SALIA HAVE TO DIE
WHILE SHE WAS STILL SO YOUNG?
- I WONDER IF WHAT THEY SAY
IS TRUE AFTER ALL.
DID THIS HAPPEN
BECAUSE HER DAUGHTER IS CURSED?
- HEY, SAN.
- FO.
- YOU UPSET?
- 'BOUT WHAT?
- YOUR MOTHER.
- Woman: UNBELIEVABLE!
- DID YOU HEAR WHAT SHE SAID?
- THE GIRL'S MOTHER JUST DIED
AND SHE DOESN'T SEEM
TO CARE AT ALL.
- DOES SHE EVEN HAVE A HEART?
- JUST SHUT UP!
STOP SAYING SUCH HORRIBLE THINGS
ABOUT SAN.
SHE'S ONLY A LITTLE GIRL.
AND SHE ISN'T CURSED!
LET'S GO, SAN.
- BUT FO.
FO!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU'RE HURTING MY HAND.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
FO?
- SAN, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY TO CRY
WHEN YOU'RE FEELING BAD.
IT MIGHT MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO HOLD IT IN,
ALL RIGHT?
SAN,
IT'S OKAY TO CRY SOMETIMES.
I KNOW IT MAY NOT BE MUCH,
BUT I PROMISE THAT I'LL
ALWAYS STAY BY YOUR SIDE.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
YOU HAVE A FRIEND IN ME.
AND I'LL NEVER LEAVE YOU.
SO I WANT YOU TO FEEL SAFE
WHEN YOU'RE WITH ME.
I PROMISE THAT I'LL ALWAYS
BE HERE TO WATCH OVER YOU.
AND I WON'T EVER
LET ANYTHING BAD HAPPEN.
PROMISE.
- ( crying )
MAMA!  MAMA!
DON'T LEAVE ME ALL ALONE,
MAMA.
- ( thinking ) YOUR MOTHER MAY
BE GONE, BUT YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
I'LL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
AND I'LL ALWAYS KEEP YOU
IN MY HEART.
ALWAYS.  ALWAYS.
- MAMA, NO!
MAMA, PLEASE DON'T GO.
MAMA!
- Forte: AFTER THAT DAY,
I NEVER SAW SAN CRY AGAIN.
IT WAS THE FIRST
AND THE LAST TIME.
TODAY IS JULY 17th,
THE ANNIVERSARY
OF YOUR MOTHER'S DEATH.
I KNEW YOU'D BE HERE, SAN.
I THOUGHT I WOULD BRING YOU
SOME FLOWERS.
I REMEMBER HOW SHE ENJOYED THEM.
I HOPE THEY'RE ALL RIGHT.
- THEY'RE PRETTY.
- THANKS.
I THOUGHT
THAT YOU MIGHT LIKE THEM.
AND I THINK THAT MAYBE YOUR
MOTHER WOULD'VE LIKED THEM TOO.
- THANK YOU.
- I HOPE YOU KNOW,
I'LL ALWAYS KEEP MY PROMISE
TO YOU, SAN.
WELL THEN,
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO HOME
AND EAT
SOME OF MY HOMEMADE COOKIES?
SOUND GOOD?
( thinking ) SAN...
THE FEELINGS THAT I HAVE FOR YOU
WILL NEVER CHANGE.
AND I'LL ALWAYS
BE BY YOUR SIDE.
I'LL BE HERE FOR YOU,
FOREVER.
- HEY, FO!
I'M READY.
CAN WE HAVE SOME CAKE
AND CUSTARD
TO GO WITH THOSE COOKIES?
- I GUESS SO.
- PROMISE?
- YEAH, WE'LL PICK THEM UP
ON THE WAY HOME.
- NO,
I WANT YOU TO MAKE THEM.
- ( thinking ) SAN,
I WILL ALWAYS BE HERE FOR YOU.
AND I WILL ALWAYS
KEEP YOU IN MY HEART.
- PRETTY PRETTY PLEASE!
- MY NAME IS WILL,
AND I'M AN INSPECTOR
SENT BY
THE SORCERY TEST HEADQUARTERS.
- Ichii and Zero:
INSPECTOR?
- I HAVE COME
TO CONDUCT A MID-TERM EXAM.
- MID-TERM?
- IF YOU FAIL THIS TEST,
YOU WILL NOT BE ABLE
TO CONTINUE ON
WITH THE FINAL EXAM.
- Nina: AH!
- YOU MUST TAKE HER BACK
FROM ME BY SUNSET.
THAT IS THE SOLE OBJECTIVE
OF THE MID-TERM.
- WAIT!
- Will: NEXT TIME, ON "SAVE
ME LOLLIPOP"...
DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO RESCUE HER?
- WILL, DON'T YOU THINK YOU'RE
GETTING A LITTLE CARRIED AWAY?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?