- MY NAME'S NINA AND I'M A
PRETTY AVERAGE, ORDINARY GIRL.
AT LEAST I WAS,
UNTIL ONE DAY.
I ACCIDENTALLY
SWALLOWED SOMETHING CALLED
THE CRYSTAL PEARL WHILE EATING
AT MY FAVORITE CAKE SHOP,
AND MY LIFE
HASN'T BEEN THE SAME EVER SINCE.
THIS PEARL IS AN IMPORTANT PART
OF AN OTHERWORLDLY SORCERY TEST.
IT'S DROPPED RANDOMLY
INTO THE HUMAN WORLD,
AND THE TEAM OF TWO EXAMINEES
WHO ARE ABLE
TO TRACK IT DOWN FIRST
WILL PASS THE EXAMINATION
AND BECOME
PROFESSIONAL SORCERERS.
THEN GET THIS THING OUT OF ME!
- STOP CRYING.
- YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO PREPARE YOURSELF, ZERO.
- HUH?
- NOW THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO DO THIS.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL HAVE TO
PROTECT HER ANY WAY WE CAN
UNTIL THE DAY THE TEST IS OVER.
WE'LL KEEP DILIGENT WATCH OVER
HER UNTIL THE MEDICINE IS READY
AND WE CAN EXTRACT
THE CRYSTAL PEARL FROM HER BODY.
WE'LL HAVE TO PROTECT THIS GIRL
WITH OUR VERY LIVES.
- YOU MEAN HER?
- SO YOU GUYS
ARE GONNA STAY HERE AND HELP ME?
REALLY?
JUST LIKE THE PRINCES
IN THE FAIRY TALE
WHO BRAVELY FACE THEIR ENEMIES
NO MATTER HOW FEROCIOUS
THEY MAY BE,
AND FIGHT TO THE BITTER END
FOR THE PEOPLE THAT THEY LOVE,
THESE TWO
ARE HERE TO PROTECT ME.
- JEEZ, I'M GONNA BE
REALLY LATE FOR SCHOOL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE ZERO AND ICHII
LEFT WITHOUT WAKING ME UP.
THOSE JERKS.
- ( both shout )
- WHAT'S THE RUSH?
SLOW DOWN, GIRL.
YOU ALMOST
KNOCKED US BOTH DOWN.
SEE YA 'ROUND.
- I THINK I COULD
REALLY FALL FOR THAT GUY.
- AHH!
- WHERE'D YOU GO, KUKU?
- WELL, TOTO,
FOR ME TO HAVE ANY CHANCE
AT BEING POPULAR HERE,
I REALLY NEED
TO MAKE SOME FRIENDS.
- WHAT'S THAT BOOK CALLED?
"101 PICK-UP LINES,
GUARANTEED TO GET YOU GIRLS"?
SO, ANYWAY,
SOUNDS LIKE I FINALLY GOT A
READING ON THE FINDER. LISTEN.
- THE PEARL IS IN THE AREA.
THE PEARL IS IN THE AREA.
- GOOD WORK, TOTO.
I SEE. THEN IT MUST BE
SOMEWHERE INSIDE THAT BUILDING.
IT HAS TO BE!
- GOOD MORNING, YOU TWO.
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
- THE DEAL WITH WHAT?
- WHY DID YOU LEAVE
WITHOUT WAKING ME UP?
- WELL, I HAD TO GET UP EARLY
TO GO RUN A FEW ERRANDS.
- YOU MEAN ZERO DIDN'T WAKE YOU?
- APPARENTLY NOT.
- IT'S NOT MY FAULT
YOU OVERSLEPT, DORK.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- DORK DORK DORK DORK DORK!
- HEY!
GET BACK HERE!  ZERO!
- Zura: CAN'T WE GET JUST ONE
MOMENT OF PEACE AROUND HERE?
- HELLO!
I AM HERE.
- HEY, I KNOW THAT GUY.
- WELL WELL,
WHAT'S THIS I SEE?
IT'S THE CUTIE I MET EARLIER.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- YOU TOO.
I'M HONORED
TO BE IN YOUR PRESENCE AGAIN,
MY LITTLE CUTIE PIE.
- ( all squealing )
- WHAT'S GOING ON, NINA?
WHO IS THAT GUY?
- WHY DO YOU HAVE TO
HOG ALL OF THE NEW GUYS?
- BUT IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
I ACCIDENTALLY
BUMPED INTO THIS GUY
WHEN I WAS ON MY WAY
TO SCHOOL THIS MORNING.
BUT WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE NOW?
- I'M HERE FOR MY ZERO.
- AH!  THIS ISN'T GOOD.
IT'S KUKU.
- ( laughing )
- ZERO! I KNEW THAT
I'D EVENTUALLY RUN INTO YOU
IF I WAS ABLE TO TRACK DOWN
THE CRYSTAL PEARL.
LOOK AT YOU.
- YOU'RE A SORCERY STUDENT?
- YUP. WE'RE
EXAMINEES. 009 AND 010.
KUKU, AND...
- TOTO.
- AHH!
I FINALLY FOUND YOU, ZERO!
- HUH?!
- WHAT?!
- SHE'S A GIRL?
- ZERO.
( laughing )
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW HAPPY I AM TO SEE YOU!
- All: WHAT?!  NO WAY!
- GET OFF, KUKU.
- WHAT'S THE DEAL, ZERO?
WHY IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU ACTING LIKE THIS?
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
- ZERO!
JUST WHO IS THIS GIRL?
- COME ON, TELL US.
- WELL...
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
HAVE YOU NOT TOLD YOUR FRIENDS
ABOUT ME?
- SHUT UP.
THERE'S NOTHING TO TELL.
- QUIT STALLING, ZERO.
WHO IS SHE?
- I GUESS THAT I'M--
- All: YOU ARE-- YOU ARE--
- HIS FIANCEE.
RIGHT, HON?
- All: HUH?!  WHAT?!
- SHE'S HIS FIANCEE?
- KUKU, WE NEED TO TALK.
OUR PARENTS DECIDED THAT WE
SHOULD GET MARRIED, I DIDN'T.
SO THAT DOESN'T--
- BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF OUR PARENTS
MADE THE DECISION.
A PROMISE IS STILL A PROMISE,
ISN'T IT, ZERO?
AND THAT'S WHY I DECIDED
TO BECOME AN EXAMINEE
AND FOLLOW YOU HERE
TO THE HUMAN WORLD, MY--
- BACK OFF!
I AM NEVER GOING TO MARRY YOU,
KUKU.
- WHA!
HEY, YOU CAN'T RUN FROM ME.
GET BACK HERE!
- THIS NEW GIRL COULD BE A BIG
PROBLEM FOR YOU.
- YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT.
- IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE IN ANOTHER LOVE TRIANGLE,
NINA.
- BUT IT'S NOT LIKE THAT,
YOU GUYS.
THERE'S NOTHING GOING ON
BETWEEN ZERO AND I.
- All: WELL THEN,
IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL, NINA,
ICHII MUST BE THE ONE
THAT YOU REALLY LIKE THE MOST.
- WHAT MAKES YOU SAY THAT?
GEE WHIZ.
THAT'S RIGHT. I DON'T CARE
IF ZERO HAS A FIANCEE.
I REALLY DON'T.
SO WHY--
WHY-- WHY--
- ( laughing )
- WHY AM I SO ANGRY?!
- JUST DON'T GET IT.
I'M DOING EVERYTHING
THIS BOOK TELLS ME TO DO.
SO WHY ISN'T ZERO
FALLING FOR ME?
- WHAT'RE YOU READING?
( sighs )
"101 WAYS
TO BE THE IDEAL WIFE."
NOW DON'T TAKE THIS
THE WRONG WAY,
BUT I'M NOT ENTIRELY SURE
THAT YOU AND ZERO
ARE MEANT TO BE TOGETHER,
KUKU.
YOU SHOULDN'T MARRY SOMEONE
JUST BECAUSE OF YOUR PARENTS.
AM I RIGHT?
- SHUT UP!
A PROMISE HAS BEEN MADE
AND I AM NOT GONNA BREAK IT.
- BUT--
- ALL RIGHT.
I KNOW WHAT I NEED TO DO NEXT.
- HEY, KUKU!
WAIT FOR ME.
KUKU. ( sighs )
- Kuku: ZERO.
- AHHH!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SO, LIKE WHAT YOU SEE?
- LOOK AWAY.
AVERT YOUR EYES.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, KUKU?!
THIS IS NUTS!
PUT SOME CLOTHES ON.
- JEEZ, WHY DO I HAVE
TO LET ZERO
GET UNDER MY SKIN LIKE THIS?
I'M JUST GOING TO SIT DOWN
AND RELAX
AND EAT A DELICIOUS BUTTER CREAM
SANDWICH AND ORANGE PASTRY
WITH RED BEAN AND MAPLE SYRUP
AND LET MY WORRIES SLIP AWAY.
'CAUSE I NEED A NICE
RELAXING BREAK FROM-- AH!
HEY!  WHAT THE HECK IS GOING ON?
IS THAT FOR REAL?
WHAT IS SHE WEARING?
- UH, NINA,
I CAN EXPLAIN.
- YOU'RE SUCH A HUGE JERK!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
DOING DOWN HERE,
AND WHY IN THE WORLD
IS SHE DRESSED LIKE THAT?
YOU LETCH!  UGH!
- HEY, WAIT.
- DON'T YOU RUN AWAY FROM ME.
- HOLD ON, KUKU.
HEY, YOU SHOULD PUT THIS ON.
- JUST SHUT UP.
- PLEASE, KUKU.
- ZERO!
- WAIT, HOLD ON.
JUST STOP FOR ONE SECOND AND PUT
SOME CLOTHES ON.
IT'S NOT APPROPRIATE FOR YOU
TO BE IN PUBLIC LIKE THAT.
( panting )
I CAN'T CATCH UP.
WHY DOES KUKU
HAVE TO BE LIKE THIS?
MAYBE IT'S MY FAULT.
- Zura:
AW, SO THAT'S HOW IT IS.
I FEEL SORRY FOR HIM.
- ( thinking )
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I FELL FOR ZERO'S LIES.
- I'M JUST GLAD TO
BE BACK TO NORMAL
SO I CAN SEE YOUR SMILE AGAIN.
IT BOTHERS ME.
WHENEVER I SEE YOU
HANGING OUT WITH THAT GUY,
IT MAKES ME FEEL SO JEALOUS.
- I NEVER
SHOULD HAVE BELIEVED HIM.
OH NO,
WHY AM I CRYING?
I SHOULDN'T CARE
IF HE HAS A FIANCEE.
I-- I CAN'T TAKE THIS.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS PAIN
IN MY HEART ANYMORE.
WHY DOES IT ACHE SO MUCH?
( sobbing )
- NINA.
- WHAT IS IT NOW?
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
- OH, IT'S JUST,
FOR A SECOND,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE CRYING.
- YOU-- YOU...
JERK!
- AH!
HEY, THAT COULD HAVE
REALLY HURT ME, YOU KNOW?
SO WATCH IT.
- DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF!
I WASN'T CRYING.
- YOU WEREN'T?
- JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
SPENDING QUALITY TIME
WITH YOUR
FIANCEE NOW ANYWAY?
ARGH!
I HATE YOU SO MUCH RIGHT NOW!
- HATE ME?
- ( thinking ) OH NO.
THAT WAS WAY OUT OF LINE.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- BUT--
YOU KNOW,
I-- I DON'T FEEL THE SAME.
I DON'T HATE YOU, NINA.
I COULD NEVER FEEL THAT WAY.
- I'M SO SORRY, ZERO.
- Kuku: WHERE ARE YOU?!
- OH, CRAP!
- HEY, ZERO!  WAIT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I WILL NOT LET YOU
GET AWAY FROM ME AGAIN.
NO MATTER WHERE YOU RUN,
I WILL TRACK YOU DOWN
AND YOU WILL BE MINE!
I PROMISE YOU THAT!
I'LL FIND YOU, ZERO,
AND YOU WILL BE MY HUSBAND!
- HA.  NOT A CHANCE.
BE QUIET.
- ( thinking ) "BE QUIET"?
COME ON.
LOOK AT THE SITUATION
WE'RE IN AND HOW CLOSE WE ARE.
MY HEART IS POUNDING.
ZERO.
- I SAID BE QUIET.
- WHOA, WHOA!
IT FEELS LIKE MY HEART'S
GOING TO EXPLODE.
- WHERE'D HE GO?
- ALL RIGHT.
I THINK SHE'S GONE.
OH, SHOOT.
SHE'S STILL HERE.
LET ME BACK INSIDE.
- I HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- HUH?
- AHH!
- Both: WE'RE BUSTED.
- YOU HAVE
SOME 'SPLAINING TO DO.
WHY WERE YOU HIDING IN A LOCKER
WITH HER?
PLEASE TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE NOT CHEATING ON ME.
- I'M NOT GOING OUT WITH YOU,
SO I CAN'T EVEN HAVE AN AFFAIR.
- THAT'S IT!
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU FOR THIS.
YOU'VE BROKEN MY HEART
FOR THE LAST TIME, ZERO.
TAROT CARDS!
ANIMAL!  TRANSFORM!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- WHAT DID YOU DO?
KUKU.
- IT'S ANIMAL TRANSFORM MAGIC.
AND AS TIME PASSES, YOU WILL
GRADUALLY CONTINUE TO CHANGE.
AND THEN WHEN THE PROCESS
IS FINISHED,
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO RETURN
TO NORMAL FOR A FULL 10 YEARS.
- ( barking )
- Both: WHAT?
FOR 10 WHOLE YEARS?
- DON'T YOU WORRY.
ONCE YOU'VE FULLY TRANSFORMED
INTO A DOG,
I PROMISE I'LL STILL
TAKE CARE OF YOU, ZERO.
YOU'LL COME HOME WITH ME.
SO I SUGGEST THAT YOU TWO
ENJOY THE REST OF THE TIME
YOU HAVE AS HUMANS
WHILE IT LASTS.
THERE ARE STILL THREE STAGES
REMAINING UNTIL IT'S COMPLETE.
SEE YA!
- WHAT?  THIS IS CRAZY.
SHE ISN'T REALLY GOING TO TURN
US INTO ANIMALS IS SHE, ZERO?
- Both: THIS IS NUTS!
- ( Koko laughing )
- AH.
WHERE DID SHE GO?
KUKU?  KUKU?
- ARE YOU LOOKING FOR KUKU?
- YEAH.  HAVE YOU SEEN HER?
- WELL, I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
BUT I BET SHE'S PROBABLY
CHASING ZERO AGAIN, ZURA.
- ( sighs )
YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
- DON'T BE SO PITIFUL.
- HUH?
- TELL ME, JUST WHEN EXACTLY
ARE YOU PLANNING
ON SPEAKING YOUR MIND TO HER,
ZURA?
YOU HAVE TO LET HER KNOW
HOW YOU FEEL
OR SHE WILL ALWAYS
JUST SEE YOU AS A FRIEND.
RIGHT?
- WHAT?
- DON'T TRY TO PLAY DUMB
WITH ME. I'M NOT BUYING IT.
I'M A PRO WHEN IT COMES
TO LOVE AND RELATIONSHIPS,
SO YOU CAN'T FOOL ME, ZURA.
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING, YOUNG MAN.
- BUT KUKU WILL NEVER THINK OF
ME AS MORE THAN JUST A FRIEND.
- BUT WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT KUKU.  HUH?
HA!
- YOU TRICKED ME.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
- I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP YA,
PAL.
AND I SUGGEST
THAT YOU LISTEN TO ME.
STOP BEING SUCH A BABY
AND TELL HER HOW YOU FEEL.
- I CAN'T.
KUKU WANTS ZERO.
AND I'M JUST HER PARTNER.
I KNOW I'LL NEVER BE
ANYTHING MORE THAN THAT TO HER.
- STOP.
- AH!
WHY'D YOU HIT ME?
- STOP MOPING
AND JUST TELL HER HOW YOU FEEL.
HOW WOULD KUKU
KNOW YOU'RE INTERESTED
IF YOU'VE NEVER EVEN
MADE A MOVE ON HER, ZURA?
YOU HAVE TO MAKE
AT LEAST SOME KIND OF EFFORT
IF YOU EXPECT TO GET THE GIRL.
GO!
TELL HER YOU LOVE HER.
IF SHE DOESN'T
RETURN YOUR FEELINGS,
IT WON'T BE
THE END OF THE WORLD.
BUT I GUARANTEE YOU'LL ALWAYS
REGRET IT IF YOU DON'T.
SO GO AHEAD
AND GIVE IT YOUR BEST SHOT.
JUST TELL KUKU
HOW YOU REALLY FEEL.
- YEAH.
- WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
GOOD LUCK.
YOU'LL NEED IT, ZURA.
YEAH, HE CAN DO IT.
I AM SUCH A GOOD COACH.
- THAT'S NOT GOING TO HELP.
- LET'S SEE, WHAT'S THIS?
- THE ANTIDOTE IS NEAR
IMPOSSIBLE TO FIND
IN THE MAGIC WORLD.
WE'LL NEVER FIND IT HERE.
- WELL, WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
'CAUSE I DON'T WANT TO BE
TRANSFORMED INTO A SQUIRREL.
- AND I DON'T WANT THAT EITHER.
BUT STILL, THERE'S NO
HUMAN MEDICINE
THAT CAN CHANGE US BACK.
WE HAVE TO THINK
OF SOMETHING ELSE, NINA.
- Girl: OH MY GOD,
WHAT IS GOING ON WITH NINA?
- Girl #2: YEAH, I KNOW.
- COME ON.
THIS WAY.
LET'S HIDE HERE FOR A WHILE.
- I GUESS IT'S OKAY.
BUT IN A WAY--
- HUH?
- WE'RE IN BED TOGETHER.
IS SOMEONE IN HERE?
- OH NO.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- WELL, IT'S MY HEAD.
IT HURTS.
I NEED A NAP.
YOU MIND IF I LAY DOWN HERE?
- THAT'S FINE.
GET SOME REST.
FEEL BETTER.
BY THE WAY,
IF I STEP OUT, WILL YOU BE OKAY
HERE BY YOURSELF?
- YEAH, I'LL BE JUST FINE.
THANKS.
- ( Nina thinking )
HURRY UP AND GET OUT OF HERE.
- 'BYE.
- ( sighs )
SORRY, NINA.
- UH, IT'S OKAY.
- ANYWAY, I DON'T--
I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO CHANGE US BACK.
AND I DON'T WANNA BE A DOG
FOR 10 WHOLE YEARS.
- WELL THEN,
IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY,
THE LAST TIME WE WERE IN
A PREDICAMENT LIKE THIS,
WE HAD TO HOLD EACH OTHER
AND UNIFY OUR HEARTS
TO PUT EVERYTHING
BACK TO NORMAL.
- THAT'S IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE TOTALLY RIGHT, NINA. WE
SHOULD TRY THE SAME THING AGAIN.
- AH!
- IF WE BRING OUR HEARTS
CLOSE TOGETHER,
MAYBE WE CAN FIX THIS.
- RIGHT.
- ( heartbeats )
( dings )
- IT DIDN'T WORK
AND THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
LEFT TO TRY.
WE SHOULD--
- THEN WE--
- Both: SHOULD KISS?
( both laughing )
- I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANY WAY
THAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
- YEAH, RIGHT?
- BUT MAYBE WE SHOULD TRY IT
AND SEE IF IT WOULD WORK.
WHO KNOWS FOR SURE?
IT'S POSSIBLE. LET'S KISS.
- WHY WOULD I KISS YOU
WHEN YOU'RE NOT EVEN SURE
THAT IT'LL TURN US
BACK TO NORMAL?
- YEAH, WELL,
I WAS JOKING.
SORRY.
- SURE, WHATEVER.
- I AM SORRY.
IT-- IT WAS JUST A JOKE.
SORRY.
- ( thinking ) I HOPE
I DIDN'T HURT HIS FEELINGS.
IT'S NOT LIKE I DIDN'T WANT TO.
IT'S JUST--
GO AHEAD.
IT'S FINE.
AND I'M READY.
KISS ME.
- BUT-- BUT YOU.
- IT COULD
TRANSFORM US BACK, RIGHT?
SO WE SHOULD AT LEAST TRY IT,
SHOULDN'T WE?
- ( thinking ) NINA.
OKAY THEN, HERE GOES.
READY?
- YEAH, I'M READY.
- COULD YOU CLOSE YOUR EYES?
- AH, YEAH.
( thinking ) OH MY GOSH.
AM I REALLY GOING TO KISS ZERO?
ZERO...
AND ME.
THAT WAS WEIRD!
- AH!
- AH!  WHAT HAPPENED?
- WE'VE TRANSFORMED AGAIN.
- OH, JUST LOOK AT YOU TWO.
HOW'S IT GOING?
YOU'RE LOOKING PRETTY PATHETIC,
ZERO.
NOW DO YOU REGRET
HAVING AN AFFAIR BEHIND MY BACK?
- ENOUGH.
CUT IT OUT, KUKU.
- WELL, LET'S SEE.
IF YOU INSIST, THEN MAYBE I CAN
TURN YOU BACK TO NORMAL, ZERO.
- BUT THEN
WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO ME?
- YEAH.
YOU HAVE TO FIX HER TOO.
I WANT YOU TO TURN US
BOTH BACK TO NORMAL.
AND DO IT NOW
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- ZERO!
- JUST DO IT.
CHANGE HER BACK
OR I'LL NEVER TALK TO YOU AGAIN.
- WHAT'S THAT?
DID YOU JUST THREATEN ME?
IS SHE REALLY THAT IMPORTANT
TO YOU, ZERO?
DO YOU REALLY CARE ABOUT HER
MORE THAN YOU CARE ABOUT ME?
'CAUSE--
'CAUSE I WANT YOU
ALL TO MYSELF!
- Nina: KUKU.
- I WANTED TO SEE YOU.
AND THAT'S REALLY THE ONLY
REASON I CAME TO THIS PLACE.
I-- I REALLY MISSED YOU.
BUT NOW I'M HERE
AND I SEE YOU'RE WITH HER.
AND I JUST DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN HANDLE THIS, ZERO.
IF-- IF YOU WON'T COME HOME
WITH ME,
I'LL TURN EVERYONE
INTO ANIMALS.
- Both: HUH?
- TAROT MAGIC!
ANIMAL TRANSFORM, EXPAND!
- ( all gasping )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?!
- DON'T ASK ME.
- QUIET. ( quacking )
- UH, TEACHER?
- WHAT--
WHAT IS THIS IRRESISTIBLE URGE?
- HEY.
- I CAN'T STOP MYSELF.
I NEED TO WASH SOMETHING.
- PLEASE SNAP OUT OF IT, YOUKA.
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A RACCOON.
YAY!
I'VE GOT A TOY.
- THIS HAS TO BE KUKU'S DOING.
I'VE GOTTA FIND HER.
- HEY, NINA, ZERO.
- YOU'RE HERE.
- ICHII.
- WHY DO YOU TWO LOOK LIKE THAT?
- HAVE YOU SEEN YOURSELF?
- YOU'RE LOOKING QUITE HANDSOME,
ZURA.
- OH! AHH!
I AM HANDSOME.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL IS IN A PANIC.
- SO WHAT?
AS LONG AS THE JERK ZERO
REFUSES TO PAY ATTENTION TO ME,
EVERYBODY'S GOING
TO STAY LIKE THIS.
- KUKU!
- DO IT.
- PLEASE STOP.
THIS IS POINTLESS, KUKU.
IT ISN'T GOING
TO SOLVE ANYTHING,
SO JUST CALM DOWN
AND CHANGE THEM BACK.
- NO WAY. YOU JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND HOW I FEEL, DO YOU?
YOU JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND ME
AT ALL!
- NO.  LISTEN.
I DO UNDERSTAND YOU, KUKU.
EVER SINCE
WE WERE JUST LITTLE KIDS,
I'VE BEEN RIGHT BY YOUR SIDE.
I'VE ALWAYS
BEEN LOOKING OUT FOR YOU.
EVEN ALL THAT TIME
YOU WERE CHASING AFTER ZERO,
I WAS THERE...
- ( laughing )
...LOOKING OUT FOR YOU,
PROTECTING YOU.
I UNDERSTAND HOW YOU FEEL.
- HUH?
- KUKU--
- JUST SAY IT.
- LISTEN TO ME.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT I WILL
ALWAYS BE HERE FOR YOU,
NO MATTER WHAT.
I WANNA BE WITH YOU
ALL THE TIME.
I WANNA BE THAT SPECIAL PERSON
YOU SHARE YOUR LIFE WITH, KUKU.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
- OH, KUKU.
- YOU'RE SO IMPORTANT TO ME.
DON'T YOU REALIZE THAT?
- TOTO!
- I'M HERE FOR YOU,
KUKU, FOREVER.
I PROMISE.
- AW.
- WAS IT ALL JUST A DREAM?
- ( yawning )
- THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
- I'M SORRY, NINA.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- YOU GOING BACK
TO THE MAGIC WORLD?
- MM-HMM.
- I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN THE SORCERY TEST.
AND BESIDES, I HAVE TO NURTURE
MY BRAND NEW LOVE.
- GOODBYE.
- BE CAREFUL.
- SEE YOU LATER.
- HEY, NINA?
I THINK YOU AND ZERO
MAKE A REALLY CUTE COUPLE.
INVITE ME
TO YOUR WEDDING, OKAY?
- AHH!
- SEE YOU LATER.
- KUKU!
- TAKE CARE, NINA!
GOOD LUCK.
- Toto: TILL WE MEET AGAIN.
- AH!
- SO WHAT DID KUKU SAY TO YOU?
- WHAT?!  NOTHING.
- WHAT DID SHE TELL YOU?
- NOTHING!
- YOU'RE LYING TO ME.
AHH!
- HEY!
- SHE DIDN'T TELL ME ANYTHING.
Nina: BUT THE TRUTH IS
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO HAPPEN.
MAYBE.
- JUST TELL ME WHAT SHE SAID
AND I'LL STOP!
- ( bell tolling )
- Nina: KUKU, TOTO,
I HOPE THAT YOU SHARE
A LONG AND HAPPY LIFE TOGETHER.
- Ichii: BACK THEN,
SARASA WAS EVERYTHING TO ME.
SHE WAS THE ONLY PERSON
I FELT I COULD TRUST.
BUT WHEN I MET ZERO,
EVERYTHING STARTED TO CHANGE.
I DIDN'T KNOW IT THEN,
BUT I HAD FOUND
MY PERFECT PARTNER.
HIS PASSION FOR MAGIC HAS HELPED
TO THAW MY FROZEN HEART.
NEXT TIME
ON "SAVE ME! LOLLIPOP"...
- Young Zero: ICHII,
YOU'RE THE ONLY PARTNER FOR ME!