[HARAZY]
Let me go!
[grunting]
[FLAME MAN]
Stop whining!
Look out, Val!
[FLAME MAN]
Why isn't it working?
[grunts]
[VAL]
I don't wish to use violence.
Please, Val, I'm scared.
Help me. Help me!
[FLAME MAN]
Shut up!
[VAL]
Harazy!
[FLAME MAN]
What the hell?
[FLAME MAN yelling]
Another day, another corpse.
Bet this was the work of
a humanoid monster too.
It very well may have been.
Officers.
I saw everything.
A-Annabella?
[BELA]
Huh?
Not much! I mean,
uh, hey, how's it going?
Is that some kind of show?
Transcendent Illusion ?
Yeah, it's totally crazy!
It's the big circus that they
put on in the Outside arena,
but the tricks are
so far beyond anything
I've ever seen before.
Beyond human capability, even!
The members all say
that they're aliens,
and I think it might
actually be true!
Hmm... So they're
beyond human.
Wow. And what about it?
Do you want me to go with you?
Well... I just thought--
I'm in.
No, it's totally fine... huh?
[squeals]
[HARAZY]
Whee!
[BELO]
Huh?
[HARAZY]
Val!
[BELO]
What's with her?
[VAL]
We're going on soon.
But I want a candy.
[VAL] You can have
some after the show.
[HARAZY]
Aww.
It's Gravity Man and Harazy!
Oh, wow!
Harazy's so cute!
No progress on
the latest murder.
We're in the dark.
We're thinking maybe
another humanoid monster?
What now?
Anything new from above?
Val Titan.
He was a foreign astronaut.
[WOODS] What kind of "foreign"
we talkin' about here?
[FELT]
That isn't relevant.
Evacuated from the lunar
surface with a fatal wound.
But it didn't kill him. He
escaped from a military hospital
two years ago
and fled the country.
The incident that caused
his wound also granted him
a special ability.
Great, so it is another monster.
It's too early for
us to assume that.
So you're telling us
to go find him, then?
[FELT] This man is known
to be in Libra City.
He's responsible for the corpse.
Frankly, he's nothing but
a distraction from Alpha,
but we have our orders.
We are to apprehend
Titan and hand him over.
To who?
If he's a suspect
in these murders,
our investigation
should take priority.
You would do well to try
and understand the politics
in play here.
[FELT]
Where are you going?
We spoke to a witness who
said he saw Gravity Man
at the scene,
and I'd like to find out
what he was doing there.
Who's this Gravity Man?
Some kinda monster too?
He's a famous illusionist.
What? Like stage magic?
[ATTENDEES chattering]
Hey, you want some?
I had to stand in line for
three hours to get these,
but it was totally worth it.
There's vanilla, mint, bergamot.
They really are the
Ultimate Bonbons.
[RODDY]
How is it?
Uh...
It's... good?
Glad you like it.
Here we go!
[LEADER]
We are From Enceladus,
and we have come to Earth
tonight to show you feats
of daring like none
you've seen before!
[ATTENDEES chattering]
Oh, wow!
[BELA]
Hmm...
So cool!
[BELA]
Hmm...
She's gone!
--[BELA sighs]
--[ATTENDEES cheer]
Hey, it's Gravity Man.
He's the show's biggest draw.
A lot of people even say that
he actually has superpowers.
[BELA]
Hmm...
Ladies and gentlemen,
are you ready?
Yes! It's the act
you've been waiting for!
[ATTENDEES chattering]
He can make a brick
as light as a feather,
or a grain of sand
heavy as a boulder.
He's Gravity Man!
Up we go. Up we go.
[ATTENDEES chattering]
[HARAZY grunting]
[LEADER] Bit by bit,
the stone ball grows lighter!
Hup. Easy!
Now then. Harazy?
'Kay!
Hup! Hup! Hup!
[LEADER]
Higher and higher they go!
Higher still!
And at last!
[RODDY laughing]
[HARAZY chuckles]
[ATTENDEES cheering]
Val's history?
I couldn't tell you.
He's quite talented,
and that's all I care to know.
Though I can't imagine his
circumstances were pleasant.
And behind the mask, does
he look something like this?
[LEADER] Your guess is
as good as mine, friend.
Then what about his
partner, that little girl.
Are they related by blood?
[LEADER]
Again, I couldn't tell you.
But they're such a lovable pair.
Don't they just warm your heart?
Can I have some
candy, pretty please?
I'm so tired from the show.
[VAL] Sure. You can
have it once we're home.
'Kay. Then let's go!
I know it has to be a trick,
but I really wanna believe
Gravity Man's power
is actually real!
And if it's not, I gotta
figure out how they do it.
I wonder if it's something
to do with the balls,
but what could it be?
Maybe if I go see it a
few more times, I could--
Huh? It's that little girl.
Hello there.
I really liked your show.
Thank you!
[stomach growls]
Would you like a little snack?
Yay! I love
Ultimate Bon Bons!
Here you go, have some.
Thank you.
What's your name?
I'm Harazy.
I know, and I'm Annabella.
Call me Annie.
Annie, you smell really
good, and you're cute,
and you have such pretty hair!
You're sweet.
[POWERMAN]
There you are.
Came to me on your own,
like a moth to a flame.
Don't need these
other bugs, though.
Hey, back off!
What's your deal, guy?
Stay back, Roddy.
[POWERMAN grunts]
Not good...
[RODDY whimpers]
[POWERMAN]
Yeah! You see that?
Now just think about what
I can do to you if you
piss me off.
I'm here to pick you up, Harazy.
Stay away from her, creep.
[POWERMAN] You don't wanna
get involved in this, Kid.
Easy now, come along quietly.
[VAL]
Leave us be.
I do not wish to use violence.
You think I'm scared
of you, punk?
[VAL grunts]
[VAL]
Please stop.
[POWERMAN grunting]
No!
Stop it! Leave him alone!
[POWERMAN]
Like crushing a bug.
[VAL grunting]
Stop it!
[VAL]
Back off!
--Val!
--[VAL] Are you okay?
Yeah.
[VAL]
Thank goodness.
Uh...
'Scuse me. I'll be going.
How'd you do that?
[VAL]
I didn't do anything.
I just wanted to avoid
more violence.
Now let's go home, Harazy.
Are you hungry?
[HARAZY]
Yeah, super hungry!
[VAL] Thank you for looking
out for her, Miss.
Yeah, thank you, Annie!
[VAL]
Let's go.
Bye bye!
Goodbye.
Huh?
[POWERMAN gasps]
[COUPLE gasps]
It says Gravity Man
is a humanoid monster!
For real?
Annie.
Hey! Have you been
on the internet today?
Look. There was another
murder in the park last night,
and now the police are
saying that Gravity Man
is the prime suspect!
And there are rumors
that Harazy's not really
his daughter, and supposedly
he kidnapped her!
Huh?
[sirens]
[MAN 06A] I heard the body
was all messed up.
They're saying Gravity
Man did that to him?
I hope poor Harazy will be okay.
This isn't the first
person he's killed.
Humanoid monster? Seriously?
The police came down
here looking for you,
and it seems that
you're trending online.
I won't ask for any details.
[VAL]
I'm sorry.
You should lie low
until things die down.
Here, a parting gift.
Now...
I know a ship that's leaving
the country at dawn tomorrow.
I'll have them
make arrangements.
[VAL]
Thank you.
Well, bon voyage.
[HARAZY]
We get to ride on a boat?
Yes, a relaxing
vacation across the sea.
How I wish I could go!
[HARAZY chuckles]
[BELO] Your new friends
are in the news.
I don't think
Gravity Man is a bad guy.
He didn't want to hurt anybody.
Everybody's got someone
pulling their strings.
He was telling the truth.
I can sense no evil
intent in that man.
Still, that power's dangerous.
It is beyond his
ability to control.
Please let me handle this one.
You sure?
[HARAZY laughs]
We're goin' on a boat!
[VAL]
You need to get packed, Harazy.
'Kay! I packed everything!
[VAL]
Who's there?
Harazy.
Annie!
[VAL]
What do you want?
Rumors are spreading
that you're a kidnapper.
That every night
after the show,
Gravity Man goes
and commits murder.
[VAL]
I've heard.
[HARAZY]
Kidnapper? Murder?
Val, what does that mean?
They're not true,
though, are they?
That's not who you are.
[VAL]
We have a boat to catch.
The police have
eyes all over town.
You two won't make it down
to the docks on your own.
Will you please let me
help you get there?
[VAL]
You shouldn't get involved.
The whole city's after you.
They want to see you go down.
[VAL]
Nothing new.
All we've ever
had is each other.
I understand, but I
need you to trust me.
For Harazy's sake.
And I'm going to trust you, too.
[SONIA] There was an
explosion at that military
medical facility.
Cause still undetermined.
In the aftermath, the fatally
injured Val Titan went missing,
and an unidentified little
girl disappeared with him.
[ACES 06A]
Target has escaped. Orders?
As we expected.
Continue the search.
[ACES 06A]
Understood!
[INTERNET MALE 06A]
Gravity Man is a murderer?
[INTERNET FEMALE 06A] I can't
believe he kidnapped a child!
[INTERNET FEMALE 06B]
I kind of want to see it!
It smells!
I know.
But we're almost
there now, okay?
It's fine. I can keep going!
The sun will be coming up soon.
Ta-da!
Oh, did you bring a friend?
[VAL] Yes, a friend more
dear to her than any other.
I'd like to meet your friend.
[BELA]
All fixed.
[gasps]
You're amazing, Annie!
[BELA]
Here you go.
Thank you!
You two aren't related, are you?
[VAL] I met her at
a military hospital.
I was the leader
of a lunar expedition,
there was an incident
on the surface,
and I was knocked unconscious.
I was found on
the lunar surface,
and before I knew it,
50 years had passed.
They told me I had been
pulled through spacetime
by a gravitational singularity,
and it changed me,
mind and body.
I couldn't breathe in the
earth's atmosphere anymore.
My own planet's air was poison.
I could no longer be
called a human being.
So they kept me around
as a guinea pig,
and told the world I was dead.
Then one day,
they brought in Harazy.
Even back then,
she already had a reputation.
They called her a witch.
A witch?
[VAL]
It's not true.
She's a good girl
with a sensitive soul.
But to those monsters,
she was just one more subject
for their experiments.
Humans treating
each other as animals.
[VAL]
I could not let it go on.
I had to break out,
for her sake.
We've been together ever since.
We're all we have in the world.
She's not my blood,
but we are a family.
I see, and what
about your powers?
[VAL]
What do you mean?
Your abilities should be
more than enough to fight with,
but earlier, you pointed
a gun at me.
It's fine.
Once you've escaped from here,
I hope you'll never
have to fight again.
[VAL]
Harazy.
Please, let her sleep.
[VAL]
Annie.
I don't know how to say this,
but from the way you act,
you almost seem...
Yeah.
I'm further from human
than you are.
[VAL]
Sorry.
I'm just kidding.
Take care, Harazy.
[VAL grunts]
[VAL]
An ambush?
[ACES 06A]
We have the target surrounded.
[FELT]
End it here.
[ACES 06A]
Right!
Colonel Titan, do not resist.
[VAL]
Please, I just want her safe!
[ACES 06A] The child is to be
captured uninjured at all costs.
Fire!
[VAL grunts]
[SONIA] Cease fire!
Are you trying to kill him?
But why?
[VAL]
Harazy.
[BELA roars]
[VAL]
Could that be--
It's Beta!
[BELA grunts]
[BELA roars]
[VAL grunts]
[SONIA]
That's Colonel Titan!
Val, what...?
[VAL grunts]
What's wrong?
[VAL]
Harazy.
I never wanted
to leave your side.
I'm sorry I can't stay with you.
Please be strong.
Hold on to the kindness in
your heart, no matter what.
I'm scared.
Val, what do you mean?
Please.
I don't want to be alone!
[VAL]
Goodbye.
Please wake up! Val!
[SONIA gasps]
[ACES yelling]
[SONIA grunts]
[GROUP grunts]
Gravity Man didn't have powers.
It was Harazy you were
after from the beginning.
She was the one
who had the abilities.
Val was trying to keep
her safe from people
who wanted to use her.
Unwarranted speculation.
You spread rumors across the
web to turn public opinion
against Gravity Man, right?
And you manipulated Harazy
into using up her power
so you could capture her.
You strong-armed a
little girl into custody.
Was all that under the
orders of the unseen--
That's enough, Officer Summers.
So, what is that girl?
[BELA]
A human being.
Oh, yeah?
Then what's that make us?