Seems to have
been a young woman.
A lot of her bones
were completely crushed.
Can't imagine what
the murder weapon was.
This was found near the scene.
That might help
us find her name.
If not for this constant rain,
she would've never washed up.
Oh, by the way.
Did you eat with the Helmsmen?
Yes, I did.
Why are you asking?
[WOODS] Just wanted to
know how you got along.
[SONIA sighs]
[INSTRUCTOR] We take the word
"terrorism" from the French
"la terreur."
The benefits of terror
were first espoused
by the Jacobin club in the
wake of the French Revolution.
Maximillian Robespierre
of the Jacobin Club
famously stated that virtue
without terror is powerless.
[bell rings]
[INSTRUCTOR]
That's all for today.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[CHRIS]
Annie!
We're headin' for
our regular spot.
Are ya busy? Wanna come?
That sounds good
to me. Just a sec.
[RODDY gasps]
Wow. How obvious can he get?
[We caught him staring
at you again, Annie.
[MEGAN]
Poor boy.
He can't help himself.
[GIRLS laughing]
[RODDY gasps]
How many times
have you drawn her?
Wait, no! Please don't do this!
[CHRIS]
He's pretty good.
Too bad he's such a creeper.
So, this is how
he sees Annie, huh?
It was drawn with love.
Right, Annie?
Oh! I was just sketching
what was in my line of sight!
I wasn't exactly drawing
Annabella, perse.
I mean, I obviously
did draw her,
but I was mostly drawing
her barrette. Mm-hmm.
Yup! No creepin' over here!
Um... What's up?
Come hang out with us.
[GIRLS laugh]
Or don't.
I was just kidding before.
Jeez. So mean.
[CHRIS laughs]
[KATIE] He thought that
was his big chance!
[laughs]
I'll go find us some napkins.
Thanks, you're the best!
How do you keep it up
when you can't understand
the taste?
I'm practicing for when
I turn into a real human.
Don't see you in Upper much.
What're you doing here?
Having a proxy war.
[BOYS laughing]
Still playing the bodyguard.
[MEGAN laughs]
Has that woman just
been staring at you?
Yeah.
She's pretty.
She does have a certain glow.
[laughs]
Mary, you're alive!
Think you've got the wrong girl.
That's Annabella, and
she doesn't seem to know
who you are.
Annabella?
Yeah.
Oh, come on.
I'm Elaine Heiding.
We went to Arc High
School together.
Arc High is pretty famous.
Right? Lots of elites go there.
Okay, no offense, Miss,
but you must've graduated
from high school
ages ago, right?
It has been a while.
But that barrette you're
wearing looks just like
the one Mary made by hand.
And your face, it's--
You look just like her.
And you're saying
that this "Mary" girl
was a classmate of yours.
--Yes.
--There's no way!
All four of us are
still in our teens.
How old are you?
I'm 27.
So then you graduated
like a decade ago, yeah?
Yeah, fair, but...
that barrette of yours.
Can you tell me
where you bought it?
[DAVE]
Keep it up, bud! Good job!
You'll get the high
score in no time!
Stay focused!
[ARCADE KIDS cheering]
[BELA]
Oh, um...
I don't remember that well,
but I think I got it
at the flea market?
[ELAINE] Oh, please let me
know if you remember something.
Thanks, Annabella.
[BELA]
Sure.
[SONIA]
We've identified the victim.
Her name's Mary Russell.
She disappeared at age 17.
Bone erosion indicates that
she's been dead for ten years.
The same length of
time since her parents
reported her missing.
So forensics actually
worked fast for once.
And the cell phone?
We weren't able to
salvage any data from it.
No surprise there.
Let's find her friends.
It's odd. Why would
a nice girl from Upper
sleep in a rough place
like this for ten years?
Hopefully it won't become
any more of a problem.
The way we got
our faces, I mean.
I wonder how the originals are.
Thoughts?
Let go. Leave this behind.
You are who you are, Bela.
You really can be
cold sometimes, Bem.
[BELO] Did you two
even hear what I said?
[DOMINIC]
Hi, Elaine.
What brings you here?
Elaine?
[ELAINE]
Where's your husband?
He's working late, per usual.
Thank goodness.
I wouldn't want anyone
to see this but you.
Okay.
There's no way.
It's not her, right?
It's a girl I met at the mall.
She called herself Annabella.
But how? We both know
that barrette was hers.
I thought about
it for a long time.
And I wonder if Mary
has come back for us.
I know how this sounds, but
what if she's come for revenge?
[DOMINIC]
Stop it!
[WITNESS 02A] Mary? She was
part of Dominic's clique.
But then she stole some
of her jewelry, I think.
[WITNESS 02A] Once word
spread about the theft,
everyone ignored Mary.
There were a lot of rumors.
People said she was shady.
[WITNESS 02B]
Why'd she steal it?
Dunno, I never asked.
Elaine said she did
and that was that.
[WITNESS 02B] Elaine was
Mary's best friend
in that group, right?
I heard she was the one
who calmed Dominic down
during the whole
stolen jewelry incident.
[WITNESS 02C]
What? No!
Elaine was fanning the flames.
That girl was a liar.
She was always acting
like she had money
even though her family was poor.
[WITNESS 02C]
Elaine was an honest girl.
Yeah, I heard the rumors about
her, but that's all they were.
People talk crap about
each other all the time.
[WITNESS 02D]
Nah, that's a load of bull.
You know who was talkin' crap?
Elaine was.
Every time Mary and
Dominic turned their backs.
[WITNESS 02E]
I'll tell ya this.
There's one thing you never
wanna hear Elaine say to you.
"I just wish I'd
met you sooner."
The more I learn,
the more confused I get.
Who are we supposed
to believe here?
Seems Heiding's
a controversial figure.
People hate her or
think she's a saint.
Here we go.
I found Dominic Vali.
Her family's famously
well-to-do.
And her husband is an elite
in the business world.
It looks like Elaine's
husband is an employee
at Mr. Vali's company.
[WOODS] That means
Elaine is lower in status.
There's no caste system.
Keep telling yourself that.
[BELA gasps]
Hey. Wait long?
Please don't touch me.
This uniform tells me
you go to Saint Joseph.
I like Joseph girls.
Please just go away.
Hey there, ya wanna
make some spending money?
Why don't'cha come
play with us, babe?
Please move your hands.
I will call the police.
[MEN laugh]
Go on and try.
[MAN 02B] It's cute how
she's playin' hard to get.
[MAN 02C]
She's just my type.
I love myself a feisty
little redhead--
[ELAINE]
Annabella!
[MAN 02A]
Shit.
[ELAINE] Are you okay?
Did they hurt you?
No. Thanks so much.
I'm really happy
that you contacted me.
I was hoping we might
get to talk again.
[ELAINE] So why aren't
you wearing your barrette?
[BELA]
No reason.
I only wear it sometimes.
It mostly just depends on how
I'm feeling in the morning.
Oh.
Mary said it was the best
piece of jewelry she had made.
She wore it every day.
Should you get that?
It's all right. I can always
call them back later.
You're much more
important right now.
[phone ringing]
Don't think Heiding's
gonna pick up.
Well then, try
your luck with Vali.
After you and I first talked,
I just couldn't stop wondering
about your friend Mary.
[ELAINE]
She was a good girl.
Very honest. And kindhearted.
Her smile was so beautiful.
And when she would
talk about her dream,
she always shone
with blinding confidence.
What dream?
Oh.
She was working towards
her dream of becoming
a jewelry designer someday.
Mary was always wearing jewelry
that she'd made for herself.
But then our friend,
an elite named Dominic,
lost one of her pieces.
She was convinced
it had been stolen.
At first, she blamed Mary,
but I jumped in to
reconcile the two of them.
Dominic agreed to forgive
Mary, on one condition.
If Mary did a test of bravery by
going to the Outside and back,
they'd be friends again.
Everyone was against it.
But no one was brave
enough to oppose Dominic.
She was that strong.
She was like a queen.
[DOMINIC]
Mary Russell, you say?
I think you might know her.
You two were in the
same class in high school.
You might recall
that she disappeared.
[DOMINIC]
I do. What about it?
[SONIA]
We found her body.
[DOMINIC gasps]
[SONIA] We'd like to ask you
a few questions about her.
I'd like to talk to you as well.
No. In person. Not now.
Mary went.
Once we saw her
cross the bridge,
Dominic said we should
teach her a lesson
by going back to
Upper Town without her.
None of us could argue.
If anyone went against her,
they'd lose their friends too.
Yeah.
To be honest,
I think Dominic lied.
I don't think her
barrette was stolen.
Secretly...
I think she must've
hated both Mary and me.
She never believed that we were
part of the same class as her.
No way.
She left Mary in the Outside
over something like that?
Exactly.
That was good to
get off my chest.
Here, take a look
at this for me.
It's a piece of jewelry
that Mary made for me by hand
as proof of our friendship.
There's only one in the world.
Beautiful.
I want you to have it.
Try it on.
I just wish I'd met you sooner.
I would love to hear more
about your friend Mary.
You know, if you
have time to spare.
Mary obviously
meant a lot to her.
I feel like maybe I should
tell her the truth.
[phone chimes]
[CHRIS]
Annie!
At least tell us what's
going on with you.
Did something happen?
You'd be better off
without knowing more.
If you care for the girl with
that face, then stop here.
I'm going because I care.
Elaine?
I can't believe my eyes.
It's really you. Mary.
And you are--?
What? How can you
not remember?
So it's true.
You were the one who
stole that barrette from me.
You're Dominic Vali.
What's going on?
Why would you do this?
Hold on, I got this from Elaine.
She told me Mary made this
barrette specifically for her,
by hand!
Elaine said that?
[BELA] Yes. Now, what
have you done to her?
Did you come here
to tie up loose ends?
You were the one
who called me here.
I came because
Elaine contacted me.
She said she was afraid
that you were planning
to murder her just
like you murdered Mary!
[rumbling]
Slipped right in the pocket.
That's what I
call a strike, baby.
Say, girl.
I'm sure I've seen
that face before.
It belonged to Mary,
one of your victims.
Oh, yeah, I think that
name rings a faint little bell.
Hey! I'm here to
murder you again.
She was crying out
for help as she died.
[BOWLING MAN] He's starting to
make his second approach now.
He's after a double strike!
A gutter ball?
Mary was crying!
[BELA yelling]
What the hell are you?
You turn into some kinda
monster after I killed you?
[BELA]
Shut your mouth!
The real monster here is you!
[BOWLING MAN]
Whoa!
You just might get
me a new high score!
Looks like he's takin' his third
and fourth shot doublehanded!
Well, talk about a
heebie jeebie mama!
Shot five's comin'!
But first,
I'm demandin' a re-rack!
[BOWLING MAN] I've got
one shot that never misses.
This bowler's going
for the bagger!
[growling]
[laughs]
[BOWLING MAN grunts]
But... How'd you beat me?
Tell me who it was
that put you up to this,
both ten years ago and today.
[BOWLING MAN yells]
There's no need
to twist it in deeper!
I'm an Outsider:
this is just a job:
nothin' personal!
I was hired by a woman
named Elaine, okay?
That's a lie!
I'm not lyin', I swear!
This really hurts, take it out!
You said you'd
murder me "again."
Yeah, Elaine hired me
to kill you ten years ago,
and you plus that
rich lady tonight!
I swear!
[yelling]
[BOWLING MAN]
I'm tellin' you the truth!
Hey, this hurts a lot!
It's Elaine who killed you!
I'm just how she did it!
[BELA]
I hate it when humans lie to me.
She set it all up.
Think her plan was to
call you the ghost of Mary
and say that you
murdered Dominic.
Dominic was about
to speak with the police,
and Elaine wanted
to silence her.
Hey.
Annabella. Something wrong?
Dominic was just murdered.
I took care of
the culprit myself.
This wasn't a gift.
You stole it.
And pinned it on Mary.
You're full of lies.
Do you have any proof?
What use would I have
for a thing like that?
Tell me why you murdered Mary.
[ELAINE]
I didn't. It wasn't me.
Yes, I know.
It was the Bowling Man
who did it.
But the fact that you
wouldn't dirty your hands
only makes me hate you more.
You had Dominic
and the Bowling Man
dancing from strings,
while you stood in shadow.
You shed real tears
of sadness for Mary.
What were you trying to achieve?
[ELAINE chuckles]
Dominic was rich, and well...
Rich is useful.
Which is why I let her live.
I killed Mary...
...'cause her happiness
pissed me off!
Her smile was so annoying!
And she was so honest!
I hated her!
[BELA]
But she was your friend.
She was never my friend.
[BELA]
Liar!
[ELAINE gasps]
[shrieks]
Stay away!
Don't come any closer,
you hideous freak! [screams]
[BELA yelling]
[yelling continues]
--[ELAINE gasps, shrieks]
--[BELA growling]
This is the woman who was
behind Mary Russell's murder.
That's why you called me here?
[WOODS] We got statements
from the rest of their friends.
They say it was
Elaine who pushed them
to abandon Mary during
the bravery test.
When they heard
she'd gone missing,
they vowed to keep
that night a secret.
It's awful. They called
themselves her friends,
then they left her to die.
People of Upper
really piss me off.
You never said why
you took her face.
[BELA]
"Help me.
I don't want to die."
Hearing her...
I realized what it
meant to be human.
I like this face,
and I'm glad to know
who wore it before me.
She was chasing a dream.
--Just like us.
--[BELO chuckles]
What are you laughing for?
No reason.
He's back at it again.
What's your problem?
Check it out, Annie!
Hey! Come take a look!
I think she's in a bad mood.
It's probably his fault.
How is it my fault?!
What a hopeless creeper.
His poor heart's fit to burst.
[GIRLS laughing]
[BELA] People who can't
lie put me at ease.
[RODDY]
Huh?
Next time, you can draw
me looking back at you.
[BELA chuckles]