[BEM] I believe you've been
looking for someone like me.
You say this is a sickness?
[sirens]
[DARYL] Who are the
unseen council, Father?
What do they want?
[DARYL gasps]
--[SHADOWMAN] Nin!
--[DARYL gasps]
Belo?
[BELO growls]
Die.
He should be...
in his usual place.
[GAVIN]
I see.
I'd wondered if it might be you.
So this is three
times we've met.
Your trust doesn't
come easy, does it?
That's good.
I understand now why
you reached out to me.
And I think I can help.
Can you tell me your name first?
[BEM]
This is a novel experience.
My name is Bem.
Hi, Bem.
You don't need to do that.
Are you sure?
[GAVIN] Well, that's
your true form, right?
It is.
[GAVIN] I hear there
are two more like you.
You'll meet them in time.
I hope we can be friends.
[BEM]
Friends?
I know that you're in pain
because of what you are, right?
My whole life, there's been
so much pain around me.
But I always thought
I could make it better.
Everything I've done
was for that.
[REPORTER 09A] The Briggs
Foundation is renowned
for its exceptional humanitarian
work in conflict zones
around the world.
But the medical equipment
giant's chairman, Gavin Briggs,
has directed his latest
efforts to the Outside,
where he grew up.
His subjects are the
mysterious humanoid monsters.
Chairman. How are you?
Quite well.
I'll be brief.
Is there anything you
can share with the public
about your company's treatment
plans for these creatures?
Thank you for asking.
Truth is, we call
them "monsters,"
but I see them as patients.
With time and care,
I believe they can be cured
of their affliction.
With the Briggs
Foundation's resources,
I can make that happen.
This site examination
is step one.
[REPORTER 09A] It remains to be
seen whether the humanoid
monsters will respond
to these efforts.
JNN will continue to report.
[RODDY gasps]
Do you think he'll
get to meet the monsters?
I sure wish I could!
They're so cool.
[CHRIS laughs]
Let's go, everyone's waiting.
Sorry. Guess I kinda forgot.
You two have been
hanging out a lot.
We really haven't.
[CHRIS] Careful, you don't
want his creeper energy
rubbing off on you.
The people here
lack imagination.
That's the issue.
And it's worse in Upper Town.
All that privilege is meant
to come with responsibility,
but those people don't care.
If they see something they
don't feel like thinking about,
they just dump it
on the Outside.
The cycle of
violence and poverty.
Innocent people
dying in war zones,
children starving
around the world?
Out of sight and out of mind.
Someone else's problem.
But failing to imagine
all of that pain is a sin.
Violence against our hearts.
We fail ourselves.
And you.
You're just one more thing
for them to look away from.
That's what hurts, isn't it?
This place hasn't
changed at all.
[REPORTER 09A] You grew up
in this neighborhood, correct?
[GAVIN]
That's right.
Could we stop the tape
a moment, please?
[ARCADE OWNER snoring]
Hey, man. It's been a long time.
You remember me?
I was a regular, back when.
I'll take your word for it.
I mean...
It beats school, doesn't it?
What's this guy's deal?
[GAVIN] It's cool.
I used to cut class here too.
And I get that home's the last
place you wanna be sometimes.
Okay...
I grew up in this neighborhood.
I know how it can get.
But still, there are
grown-ups out there
who really are
looking out for you.
We're not old
enough to vote, sir.
[DAVE, KEVIN laughing]
I don't trust this.
But you do, just like always.
[REPORTER 09A] The Briggs
Foundation's research program
has yet to produce any
breakthrough discoveries
about the humanoid
monster phenomenon.
But you contend that
your company's work
is still having
a positive effect.
Human neglect made
this place what it is,
not humanoid monsters.
Stability's what lets
people be people.
I think that's what
the Outside really needs.
He's still got
that old fire in him.
I'm a fighter,
though I may not look it.
Until I crossed that bridge
to Upper when I was 13,
I never once lost a fight.
I brought my dreams across
with me to the shining city
on the other side,
but it wasn't ready.
Those people don't
care about the Outside.
Their world stops at
that end of that bridge.
Everybody needs someone
fighting for them.
So that's what I'm doing.
That's a beautiful
idea, at least.
[ARCADE OWNER snoring]
Do you think the suit
guy will come again?
Who cares? That dude
was full of crap anyway.
Yeah, when's a grown-up
ever been that nice?
I dunno. It didn't really
seem like he was lying to me.
Such a kid.
Did you miss the cameras?
That's whatcha call PR.
[ARCADE OWNER]
Huh?
[grunts]
[GROUP yells]
[SHADOWMAN]
Nin. Nin.
--[BELO] Run!
--[SHADOWMAN] Nin.
Belo!
I'm fine. Just go!
[BELO]
All of you, go home.
You just got stabbed!
[BELO]
I told you, I'm fine. Now go!
Go where? My dad'd beat me!
I'll take my chances.
I'm not goin' home.
Let me stay with you;
you can't disappear again!
There's an old guy
named Johanne at a shop
over on 67th.
Tell him that I sent you.
Now. Run!
But nothing's going to
change just because of some
pretty words,
or the passion
of just one man.
That's why I started a business.
I had to dominate on their turf;
give them no choice
but to hear me.
That's the only way
I could make things right.
In the end, creating real
change takes money and status.
That seems like a pretty
vulgar way of thinking.
Call it whatever you want.
This city, this country,
the whole world,
all of it has to change.
I don't care about clothes
and the cars and the cameras.
It's about doing what's right.
It's about love
for our fellow man.
The love that compels
us to feed the hungry
and protect the weak.
I won't spend
my money on myself.
I will use it to
build a better world.
Bem, you're in pain,
and I want to help.
I want to make you human.
Can you? Even now?
You lost everything, didn't you?
The bribery scandal.
It's been a nightmare.
You know, I used to believe
that there's no smoke
without fire.
Then I started hearing
about meetings with people
I didn't know,
finding my name on
documents I'd never seen.
The press turned on me,
cameras lying in ambush
around every corner.
The public had already
reached its verdict.
"The merchant of death."
I was trying to save
people's lives!
They made the smoke,
and then they lit the fire.
Who are "they"?
Libra City knows them well.
But who they really are,
nobody can say.
They call them
the unseen council.
[BEM]
The unseen council?
This is the first
I've heard of them.
[REPORTER 09A] Public opinion
toward philanthropist
Gavin Briggs
continues to decline.
At this time, accounts of his
organization accepting money
to participate in armed
conflict remain unconfirmed.
Have you been following this?
What do you think?
It's not true!
I've done nothing wrong!
Could it be that he had
the whole world fooled
all this time?
And was he lying to
the humanoid monsters?
I don't know.
But I want to think he
was telling the truth.
Tell me. This council...
How can they stay unseen?
No one knows their
names or their faces,
but you can feel their
grip all over this city,
across the whole country,
and even around the globe.
They can turn lies
into the truth.
Someone wrote me
into their script--
made me a part of
events I can't remember.
It's more terrifying than
any horror movie I've seen.
They turned me into the
godfather of the Outside,
and I never knew a thing.
They even pinned Representative
Carver's murder on me.
And implicated me.
They say that I killed
him on your orders.
Carver was on my side,
but they took me to court
on murder-for-hire.
And got me put away.
[BEM]
I witnessed that firsthand.
[GAVIN]
You came to my hearing. I see.
[BEM]
Why did they want you gone?
[GAVIN] I was in the way of
the real merchants of death.
I tried to move those conflicts
toward a peaceful resolution.
I managed to get a politician
they needed on my side,
and they couldn't allow that.
[BEM]
And that politician?
Erased.
I didn't want to call you out,
but you've hardly
touched your drink.
It does little for me.
We can digest food and drink,
but it's flavorless to us.
We need only water to survive.
Even among allies, we are alone.
We were brought into this world
for reasons we cannot know.
[GAVIN]
That's the same for everyone.
No living thing is
born with a purpose,
and the only thing
promised at the start
is that death is
waiting at the end.
So, our only play is to try
to do what feels right to us.
Live as best we can
in the little time we've got.
But that time is cut
short for too many people.
It pains me.
We three are not promised
even the release of death.
We are carried ever
forward by the flow of time.
In my long years on earth,
I have observed many humans.
They all tried to make
the most of their short lives.
Yeah.
Knowing that our time will
come to an end makes it easier
to see the value of it.
[BEM]
My time is not so scarce,
but what I seek has
never been in doubt.
I want to become human.
I want that, too, and I'm
glad you came to see me.
Oh, uh, hello.
Would you care to get a drink?
Hey, I just remembered.
The humanoid
monsters' ringleader
gets out of jail today.
Their ringleader?
Yeah, you said he was
a friend of yours, right?
Oh. You're talking
about Gavin Briggs.
Aren't you gonna go see him?
After all, they never
did manage to prove
he did anything wrong.
[GAVIN] The other times
we've met up for drinks,
you've been full
of questions for me.
You'd ask why I
wanted to help people
and put their needs
ahead of my own.
Now I think that must have
been a test to make sure
I was somebody you could trust.
I'm not giving up the fight.
Just making bail cost
me everything I had.
It'll be hard starting
over from scratch.
But I have no intention
of giving up on my dream.
No matter what...
I'll help you.
Why would you go
that far for me?
I just can't leave
someone to suffer.
It's as simple as that.
And what about you?
I know you weren't just
sitting around waiting
to talk to me this whole time.
I was doing the same as you.
I was trying to help people.
If we continue to help
humans, one day,
we can become humans ourselves.
That is what we have
always believed.
I couldn't explain how this
transformation might occur.
Nor what led us to
believe that it could.
The idea simply came to our
minds and compelled us to act.
[BEM growling]
[BEM]
Though I can't account for it,
I'm sure this is a
belief worth holding.
I see.
You always stayed close to me.
Watching from the shadows.
You can step into the light.
I'm here with you.
[BEM]
You're not afraid?
Like I said.
I want us to be friends.
[BELO panting]
Come on, seriously?
[SHADOWMAN]
Nin.
Nin!
Do you really think that
thing's gonna scare me?
[BELO growls]
[GAVIN]
Can you show me your true self?
Your whole self.
It's a pleasure, my friend.
[GAVIN gasps]
[BELO]
We're in trouble!
[SHADOWMAN]
Nin!
[BELO]
This guy is an assassin.
He's the one who killed
Carver and Bryson.
[GAVIN gasps]
[SHADOWMAN]
Nin! Nin! Nin!
Ja! Ja!
Ja! Ja! Ja!
Nin... Ja!
Ja! Ja! Ja! Ja!
[SHADOWMAN]
Nin! Shadow!
[GAVIN gasps]
Watch out!
Get down!
[SHADOWMAN]
Nin!
[BELO growls]
[BELA growls]
[SHADOWMAN]
Nin! Nin! Nin!
Nin! Nin!
[GAVIN gasping]
[BEM growls]
[SHADOWMAN]
Nin! Nin!
Nin! Nin! Nin! Nin! Nin!
[BELO]
That man...
Was he trying to protect me?
[BELA] We're supposed to be
the ones protecting them!
[FELT] Beta and Gamma
are confirmed on site.
Continue pursuit as planned.
Come on.
[REPORTER 09A] Gavin Briggs,
disgraced former chair
of the Briggs Foundation,
has been found dead
on the streets of Outside.
Police attribute his death
to humanoid monster activity.
Mr. Briggs had sought
a medical solution
to the humanoid monster problem,
but his efforts were stalled...
[DARYL]
I owe you my thanks, Father.
You came so close to
exposing the unseen council.
In the end, you died for it.
And left my path wide open.
[VEGA]
Welcome, my little knight.