[MAN 1A]
Hit us with that special move!
Aw, yeah, smooth stuff, buddy.
Woohoo!
[MISCREANTS chattering]
Let's see some footwork.
Nice. Keep it up!
[overlapping chatter continues]
[MAN 1D]
Hey, speakin' of beer...
You haven't drank
it all yet, have you?
[MAN 1B]
I might'a.
Why don't you take
a look and see?
[MISCREANTS chattering]
[DANCER 1A gasping]
It's a monster!
[screams]
[MISCREANTS screaming]
[VOICE 1A chuckles]
You went too far, Sonia.
[VOICE 1B]
Thought you were smart.
Insubordination's no joke.
[VOICE 1C] Getting transferred
to the Outside is basically
a death sentence.
[VOICE 1D] Sorry, but
you'll never make it back.
You won't last five
seconds out there
with an attitude like yours.
[MAN 1G]
Who, that guy?
Nah, he didn't stand a chance.
[WOMAN 1A]
Well, let's talk prices.
You're working men, and--
[SONIA gasps]
[WOMAN 1B crying]
You okay? What happened?
[WOMAN 1B]
He robbed me. Please help.
You'll be all right.
Was it a red handbag
he took from you?
Stay here!
This is Officer Summers.
There's been a robbery
on 23rd Street!
The victim wasn't
seriously injured,
so I'm leaving her and
pursuing the suspect.
Please send backup
as soon as you're able!
[ROBBER 1A grunts]
[SONIA gasps]
Have a death wish?
But...
[SONIA]
Wait!
[BEM]
It isn't holding back tonight.
[POLICE chattering]
He hasn't been dead for long.
[BYSTANDERS whispering]
[JANSEN sighs]
[WOODS]
You're late, Jansen.
Would it have killed you
to finish that thing outside?
Oh, right. Forgot you cared.
Summers? Certainly hope
you aren't a smoker.
He hates the smell.
[SONIA]
Uh...
I take it you're the girl
scout who got transferred?
I'm Officer Sonia Summers.
[JANSEN]
This your first time Outside?
Yes.
[JANSEN]
Thought so.
You've got that
Upper Town air to you.
So you were first
on the scene, right?
Right. I witnessed
a robbery and th--
[JANSEN]
Damn.
Why's it always
in our jurisdiction?
[SONIA]
Huh?
[JANSEN] Sixth victim
we've found this evening.
[WOODS] Been an average
of four killings a night
for the past two weeks.
All of them drownings,
in places with no water source.
[SONIA] I never heard
about this back in Upper.
[JANSEN]
Of course you didn't.
Once you cross that bridge it's
like you're in another country.
Why would this
case matter there?
It's a serial killer.
Give this purse back
to the owner, would ya?
We put all the money back in.
Isn't this evidence?
Shouldn't we take
some statements?
[JANSEN] Your assignment
starts with us tomorrow.
Get some rest.
[HOMELESS MAN 1A] You're the
girl who left her car here,
aren't ya?
[SONIA]
Yeah.
[HOMELESS MAN 1A] Sorry,
but an old lady came along
and sold it off.
[SONIA]
Huh?
[phone ringing]
[SONIA]
Hey, Mom.
Yeah, I know, it's late.
I just got to my room.
Yeah. Luckily it was furnished.
I'm fine.
Don't worry so much.
I can make do on my own.
[JANSEN]
Welcome to your new home.
You're with me today.
I'll teach you what ya need
to know to make it here.
[JANSEN]
Rule number one in this town.
Ya gotta be resourceful.
--[WOMAN 1C] Yes.
--[CLERK 1A] And what else?
[BOYS laughing]
[JANSEN]
What some might call "shady"
others call "laid back."
Hold on, this is nowhere
near the crime sc--
[JANSEN]
Just wait a minute.
Cigars? Don't you hate smoke?
[JANSEN] You've heard
of the Helmsmen, right?
They run things
around this block.
As long as we're paid,
we stay out of it.
[SONIA]
What exactly are you saying?
In the Outside, the
Police and the Helmsmen
look after one another.
Citizens are well aware,
and the smart ones
make use of us both.
That's just how things
are done here, you get it?
Sounds like blatant
corruption to me.
Easy, Girl Scout.
We got three more stops.
Stop the car!
We're in a rush.
Hey!
[JANSEN]
Summers! Wait!
[SONIA]
Hold it!
--[TEEN 1A] Shit!
--[TEEN 1C] Ow!
[SONIA]
You okay? What happened?
[TEEN 1C]
It's nothing serious.
But you--
I don't care about how
things are done here.
If I see something
that I know is wrong,
I will call it out.
I'll be damned
if I don't believe it.
That must be why they sent you.
[WATERMAN breathing heavily]
[WATERMAN]
Kill...
I want to kill...
[PROSTITUTE 1A gasps]
What the--?!
No! No!
[CROWD yelling]
[WOMEN whimpering]
[WATERMAN laughing]
So much fun!
[laughing continues]
[WATERMAN]
Wait. Why are you still alive?
[WATERMAN growls]
[WATERMAN yelling]
[WATERMAN chuckles]
You can do some
interesting things, stranger.
Did you throw away
your humanity too?
Personally, it's the
best choice I ever made.
See, I almost drowned once,
but as I was dying,
I realized that nothing's
stronger than water.
So instead of
letting it kill me,
I decided to become
water myself!
Now I can do lots
of things humans can't!
This one is irredeemable.
[WATERMAN]
With this new body,
I can go to Upper Town
and do whatever I want!
But enough about me.
Did you get your powers
from the professor too?
--[BEM] Who's that?
--[WATERMAN] Don't know him?
That's weird. Whatever.
I've done too much chatting
and not enough murdering
the last few seconds,
and I'm blaming you!
[WATERMAN yelling]
[WATERMAN gasps]
[WATERMAN]
Damn.
That jerk pisses me off.
I can't calm down
without killing.
He ruined my fun!
[BELO]
That guy seemed pretty strong.
He'll survive.
[BEM]
Belo.
[BELA] With how we're
fighting, to gain humanity.
Bela.
[BELA] It's kinda funny that
this man threw his away.
Then how good
can being human be?
--Just saying.
--[BELA] Sure.
You always talk like that.
I don't want to become a
human like that water man.
That thing's disgusting.
You think far too
highly of humans, Bela.
And you think
far too little of them.
So what should we do next?
We must chase the scent of evil
before any more lives are lost.
So somber.
[BEM] This corrupted man
is a threat to his species.
If we save enough humans,
then human is what we'll become.
[BELO]
Is that a fact or just a prayer?
[OLD MAN 1A gurgling]
[WATERMAN laughing]
[MAN 1F gasps]
[WATERMAN grunts]
Ugh. That shock is annoying!
[grunts]
[MAN 1F gasps]
[yells]
[JANSEN]
Hey, welcome back.
[WOODS]
How'd it go?
The new girl was makin'
quite the face when she left.
Huh?
[WATERMAN grunting]
Professor!
[grunts]
Professor, please!
I need you to make me stronger!
[WATERMAN yells]
[WATERMAN growls]
What do you want?!
[grunts]
[WATERMAN grunts]
[WATERMAN growls]
This is all your fault!
Look at what you did
to me, you monster!
[WATERMAN chuckles]
That same man...
[WATERMAN laughs]
Hi there!
Welcome, Little Missy,
hope you enjoy the show!
[SONIA grunts]
[WATERMAN chuckles]
Have a death wish?
[WATERMAN chuckling]
[WATERMAN growls]
[WATERMAN]
Ooh!
Ah!
[WATERMAN laughing]
[JANSEN]
Hey, Summers!
Why the hell didn't
you contact me?
[OFFICERS gasp]
[JANSEN]
What is that?
--[SONIA] Watch out!
--[WATERMAN yells]
[BEM (MONSTER) roars]
No... What are you?
This can't be real.
[BEM (MONSTER) roars]
[WATERMAN grunting]
[WATERMAN grunts]
[WATERMAN yelling]
Why do this?!
You must know that you're
no different from me!
[WATERMAN yelling]
[BEM (MONSTER) growls]
You're a monster...
See, Bem?
They're all the same.
[SONIA screaming]
[WOODS]
Summers, you here?
Seemed like you were hoping
you could trust that human.
She's new to this town.
It hasn't had time
to taint her as of yet.
I wonder...
How many have betrayed us?
Thought we agreed
to stop counting.
If we can't convince
ourselves to believe in humans,
there's no way
we'll become them.
Bem's method is
the best we have.
I guess, but...
[BELA] If you don't like it,
find a better way yourself.
[BELO]
No need.
I'm fine with
things as they are.
We've finally tracked him down.
Observe. The Alpha.
[MYSTERY WOMAN 1A]
Alpha.
In time, I'll give
you a proper name.
[WOODS]
Look at that.
Another troublemaker.