[INVESTIGATORS chattering]
Victim was killed by a
high voltage electric shock.
This one was a
young woman as well.
Did you see that?
The culprit left
behind a message.
[SONIA]
"Monster. Your destiny is mine."
Interesting, but it
don't mean much to me.
We just got a report of
another unnatural death
about two blocks down from here.
[WOODS]
Well that's a shocker.
I hear there's been another
spree of unusual murders.
[BEM] I saw a message
near the last victim
addressed to a "monster."
And you think it's
meant for one of us?
You should let it go.
There are lots of
monsters in this town.
Stupid.
When has caring about
humans ever worked out?
Did you kill my father?!
[MAAYA]
Belo!
Hey, where have you been?
We haven't seen you.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, how are ya?
What's going on with him?
I don't know; he's been
acting really distant.
[KEVIN] Do you think he
might've lost against Daryl?
[DAVE]
No way that guy could beat Belo.
[VILLAIN 03A]
Tell me somethin', Sparky.
You're the one who's
behind all these murders,
aren't you?
Why are you only
targeting women?
Doubt someone like you
would understand, ya brute.
[BRUTE grunts]
What the hell?
Calm down,
that was only a love zap!
To loosen that stressful
knot in your heart.
[VILLAIN 03A] I'm curious about
the words you wrote on the wall.
What do they mean?
[SHOCK] You were all hoping
to smoke out that monster,
weren't you?
I thought I'd entwine our fates.
[STARCH]
I wanna do it, too!
[SHOCK] I'll keep killing
till he shows up to stop me.
[VILLAIN 04A]
You cocky punk!
I don't like your attitude!
In fact, it pisses me off!
[VILLAIN 04A yelling]
[STARCH]
Nice! I'll take it from here!
[SHOCK]
That smell.
[BRUTE]
You're the one who caused it.
[CHRIS]
Yeah. It's super morbid.
You actually looked?
Only from a distance.
He's been staring at
that stuff all morning.
[BELA]
Yeah, I heard that earlier.
Okay, so I talked
to one of the boys.
And Roddy told him
that someone weird
was wandering the Outside.
Like weird in a
supernatural kinda way.
So that's why he's looking
at such creepy stuff.
Yeah! 'Cause he's weird too!
[GIRLS laugh]
[CHRIS]
Annie! You coming?
[BELA]
Yup.
What's gotten into you?
Everyone's talking about
how you've been staring
at some creepy site all day.
Are you curious too?
Something weird is
roaming the Outside.
Basically the jist of it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
that's exactly right!
There've been a series
of murders that are all
clearly connected!
I mean for one thing, all the
victims were young women.
And what's more, they all
died from electrocution,
which is weird,
but on top of that,
a bunch of them had a weird
powder scattered around them.
Super weird, right?
There must be something out
there that we don't understand!
And do you think it's... human?
That's what I'm
trying to find out!
People on the internet are
saying this is most likely
a genetically modified
superhuman or something similar.
But I'm still skeptical.
For the time being,
I just need to keep
on pursuing the truth.
Be careful, okay?
You should keep your
distance from the Outside,
since this fiend is
targeting young girls.
[BELA]
You know, Roddy...
I don't think I've met
anyone who can talk
quite as fast as you.
[RODDY whines]
Still.
The boy's onto something.
Don't you agree?
[SONIA] Between the use of the
word "monster" and the victims
being killed by electricity,
I think it's likely that this
relates to the creature
I encountered
when I first came here.
Oh, yeah.
You said it fought
with electricity, right?
Right. I saw it firsthand.
He killed the water monster
with a powerful electric shock.
I wrote as much in my report.
And requested the report
be submitted to HQ.
Ah. Well, about that.
The report didn't make it there.
And why's that?
'Cause you stopped it?
Who would believe that monsters
are disguising themselves
as humans?!
I won't let you make a joke
of the Eighteenth branch.
Think about the victims,
and how they died.
It matches with that
creature's powers perfectly!
If we don't think
of countermeasures
and enact them quickly,
there will be more victims!
Pipe down for a minute.
Keep shoutin' like that and
you'll get shipped off again.
[SONIA] It's my opinion that the
words on that wall are evidence
of a possible conflict
between this city's monsters.
A conflict which the
people of the Outside
are suddenly getting
dragged into.
[CHIEF] Those words
are classified for now.
They may help close
this case later.
As for countermeasures
to protect the people,
we've set a new curfew.
If you want people to take
your monster seriously,
I guess you'll just
have to catch it.
If that's how it is,
I'll prove he's real on my own.
Well let's move on for now.
There were three
other unnatural deaths
all thought to have occurred
at the same time and date
as the electrocutions.
At each scene, a powder was
found near the victim's corpse.
We took that powder
in for analysis,
and apparently, it's made
of starch and human skin.
[SONIA] There was another
monster with him.
Whaddaya need, another fake ID?
Forgot the girl's name.
Anyway, I hope you two
have been doin' well.
I have a question.
You really do like to cut
to the chase, don't'cha?
[BEM] Can you help me
find whoever electrocuted
those women?
Electrocuted...
Who do I know who can do that?
[BEM] Could someone have
given the killer that power?
[JOHN]
Hm?
I heard there was a professor
who could give humans
special abilities.
If rumors are enough,
I got something.
There's a guy who moved
into town about ten years ago.
Dunno if he teaches,
but crazy as he is,
people still call him
"the professor."
Rumor has it,
if you pay him enough,
he'll augment your body
in any way you want.
[SHOCK]
Hello, miss.
[LADY 04A]
Excuse me?
[SHOCK] I think... you must be
destined to be my next love.
Say what?
[SHOCK]
After all...
You've sent such a thrilling
current through my heart.
Let me return the favor.
Let me show you
how you make me feel.
Let me put a spark in your eyes.
[LADY 04A gasps]
[LADY 04A screams]
[SHOCK yells]
[SHOCK]
Were you watching?
Hmm. I may as well ask.
Have you heard
the tale of a monster
that can take human form?
I haven't.
Well then, die!
[MAN 04A, WOMAN 04A yell]
[MAN 04A] Get behind me!
I'll protect you!
[WOODS] First the electrocutions
and now these powder killings.
[CHIEF] That's not all
we're dealing with either.
This town's freaks've
been putting on a homicidal
variety show.
Where did Sonia go?
Ran off on her own again.
Said something about
tracking down that monster.
It's no wonder she got
kicked out of Upper.
Girl's a nuisance.
[WOODS] She's a wild one,
but honestly, Joan of Arc's
doing better here than
I thought she would.
What'd you call her?
First responders gave
her that nickname.
[DR RECYCLE]
Hello. Need some maintenance?
Just came by
for a quick recharge.
Woo! That really does
clear up the mind.
[DR RECYCLE]
This is good timing.
I've created a medicine
that tames unruly hair.
Care to volunteer
for a free trial?
Think I'll pass. Test it on him.
[DR RECYCLE] Due to the
unique procedure required
to fulfill his request,
he won't make
a fitting test subject.
Too bad.
Was it you after all?
Did you make the thing
that killed Water?
Bold question.
Surprised you asked.
Am I mistaken?
[DR RECYCLE] Turning a human
into a heteromorphic monster
would require a technique
I can scarcely dream of.
[SHOCK] Can't be that much
harder than creating
a water elemental
or putting lightning
at someone's fingertips.
[DR RECYCLE]
I disagree.
Anyone can do something like
that with the right knowledge.
But to change your body
from one form to another
and back would be
a marvelous ability.
One which I wouldn't
mind having for myself.
Well if you didn't make it,
what do you think it is?
I would say it's a monstrosity.
[SHOCK]
Monstrosity?
[DR RECYCLE] Someone else
called it that before I did.
[SHOCK]
Okay if I kill this monstrosity?
Of course.
After all, it's been
destroying my creations.
Dispose of it, please.
[INVESTIGATORS chattering]
Hey there, Joan.
You drunk?
My name's Sonia, remember?
You really aren't one for jokes.
Anyway, we found
a couple of witnesses.
They only caught
a quick glimpse,
but the man they described
seemed to match
the one you saw
on your first night.
What a dirtbag.
Preying on women
that are walking alone.
Be careful, or else
you could be his next--
[BELA]
Really?
[BEM] I'm certain that word
"monster" is directed at me.
You're overthinking this.
There's no telling who
that message is for.
[BEM]
No. He's calling for us.
Which means he's blaming us
for the pain all his
victims have endured.
He's only been targeting
young women so far, right?
Maybe we can catch
him if I pose as bait.
[BEM] No point if you
don't catch his attention.
I'll just pretend
I didn't hear that.
It doesn't matter how
many humans you save.
You'll only end up
suffering for them.
And yet, it's better
than standing by.
[SHOCK] Ah! Pardon,
but you're just so beautiful.
It's those piercing
eyes, darling.
They've shot a bolt of
lightning straight through
my fluttering heart!
It's your destiny...
...to be mine!
What did you say?
My destiny, huh?
You must be the murderer!
You know me?
That's just delightful!
Honestly. I can't tell you
how flattered I am.
Wow...!
So pretty!
[SHOCK]
Ooh!
Forgive me, darling!
But my destiny
with you has to wait!
Shockingly, I have a more
pressing engagement!
[SHOCK]
You chose a lovely location.
Oh. You're the one who
saw me with that girl,
aren't you?
Well, then you already
know how I like it.
Here!
[BEM roars]
It's no wonder the good
doctor was so jealous of you.
Even your bone
structure can change.
[chuckling]
[SHOCK]
Why is Starch here?
[STARCH] I'm gonna finish
this one off by myself!
That tickles!
Hey! What was that for?
It's rude to snatch food
from someone else's plate.
[STARCH]
No hurt feelings.
Whoever gets him, gets him.
[SHOCK]
Darling!
I'll be with you once
I kill this monstrosity.
Monstrosity?
[SHOCK]
It's high time you died.
And I would like it
to be by my hands!
[SHOCK]
Get out of the way, Starch!
[STARCH]
You're the one who's in the way!
[growls]
[STARCH]
You've done it now!
Perfect shot!
[STARCH] Stop it, Shock!
That really hurts!
[BEM]
Run.
[STARCH] Just give up!
This one's mine!
If you're gonna be a nuisance,
then you may as well die.
[STARCH yelling]
This was fun.
But let's end it!
Wow! You absorbed
every last jolt.
[STARCH]
I'm the one who's gonna kill it!
Me, not you!
[yells]
[BEM]
You came.
[BELA]
Of course I did.
[STARCH] No way!
There's another one?!
Tardy to the first date?
That's a red flag.
[SHOCK]
Ah! It feels so good!
Get ready!
My lightning will strike
you monstrosities down!
To dust!
[STARCH]
I can't take it!
[BELO] That was your
power source, right?
What now?
This simply isn't fair!
How many of you are there?
[BELO] You're one cocky
idiot, ya know that?
Choosing to fight
in a place like this.
Though I guess you
have your reasons.
[BEM]
Go. Bind him in place.
[SHOCK gasping]
Hey! What the hell
have you done to me?
It's like I'm covered
in stone, or--
[BEM]
This is your lightning.
Take it back.
[SHOCK yells]
[SONIA gasps]
I don't get it.
Why?
Why would a monstrosity
protect me?
That sure was exhausting.
Why'd you decide to show up?
[BELO]
Felt like it.
We're still monsters.
Though that may be the case...
There are certain things
we just have to do.
Beta has appeared.
We've confirmed his identity.
How shall we proceed?
[footsteps]
[VEGA] Excellent work.
You've all done well.
[AIDE 01A] It seems that others
have begun calling them
"monstrosities."
Interesting. But incorrect.
Monstrosity is not
the right word.
Those specimens
should be referred to
as humanoid monsters.
I apologize for
the inconvenience
this will cause you all,
but I must ask that
you capture them
and bring them to me.
[DARYL]
Father.
Please give me strength.
I need to be strong
so I can fight.
[STARCH]
It hurts... It hurts...
Oh, no, no, no,
what's happening to me?
Make it stop!
[SUCTION MAN chuckles]
There. Nice and clean.