[ANNOUNCER 10A] The killer of
philanthropist Gavin Briggs
currently remains at large.
Briggs had recently begun
moving to rebuild his reputation
after he and his organization
were rocked by a series
of high-profile scandals.
In recent years,
Libra City has witnessed
a rash of grisly murders.
These killings have been
perpetrated by the so-called
humanoid monsters.
The facts indicate not
only Representative Smith,
whose death remains
fresh in our minds,
but Representative Carver
and Secretary Bryson
were also killed
by these creatures.
[HQ CHIEF] We have confirmed
that humanoid monsters
are responsible for the
murder of Gavin Briggs.
These hateful,
subhuman creatures.
They're enemies of mankind.
[BELO] So they're blaming
everything on us.
[BELA]
That's how humans operate.
[aircraft approaching]
[HQ CHIEF] Police are searching
for three monsters known as
Alpha, Beta, and Gamma.
We're asking the public for
any information they have.
[CHIEF] What's this I'm hearing
about Sonia running around
with those monsters?
It would appear that she
has made contact with Alpha.
Wha--? I'll call her.
[FELT] No. I'll handle
this matter myself.
[CHIEF]
Huh?
Come on, bud!
This is it.
The council is trying
to bring all of you in.
Do you know the true
face of the council?
[SONIA]
I came in contact with them.
That's why they had
me sent Outside.
I knew too much.
When I was a child,
I never really questioned
the things I saw around me.
Once some thug came
after me in the Outside,
I was terrified.
Then this young cop, he showed
up to rescue me just in time.
He was my hero.
I knew right then that
I wanted to be like him,
to protect the city
from the bad guys.
I thought that I could hold
on to that feeling here
in the Outside.
But this place wore me down.
I'm not Gavin.
I'm not as strong as him.
Through all that injustice,
he never lost himself.
He kept his convictions.
Yes.
In the end, he gave his own
life to protect one of ours.
I had never met
a human like that.
To him, you weren't a monster.
Just another person in need.
Tell me, what are humanoid
monsters, really?
[BEM] That is a phrase
that humans created.
It's not for me to say
what it means.
You saved me more than once.
Instead of thanking you,
I shot at you.
I'm sorry.
I'm a coward.
I was too scared to
let myself trust you.
Humans are weak.
Yet, we envy that in you.
You envy us?
[BEM] That frailty and
fear is what drives you.
It's your reason to fight.
Humans betray their comrades
to save themselves.
And yet, they also
strive to save others.
Some will even give their
lives to protect strangers.
I will believe in you.
I'll embrace humanity
and its contradictions.
Thank you.
I don't think I ever
asked for your name.
I'm Bem.
Sonia.
[HQ CHIEF] We believe that Alpha
is still holding Officer Summers
hostage at this time.
We ask that any sightings of
them be reported immediately
to police.
[MOTEL OWNER 10A]
Huh?
[BELO] They're talking about
Bem like he's a criminal.
[BELA] Why did he run
away with that woman?
He probably fell
for some sob story.
Always does. Idiot.
It's true, and you know it.
Do you have to be
so cynical all the time?
[BELO] You really still
want to be human, Bela?
Even when they
treat us like this?
[BELA]
I don't know.
But the idea of living
forever with no purpose,
never feeling like
anything matters--
That doesn't make such a short,
ugly life worth wanting.
I say let them live
and let them die.
Even if that's all we do,
it's more than we can
expect them to do for us.
Humanoid monsters are
a threat to public safety.
And, if martial law is what
it takes to get these things
off our streets, I say so be it.
Now they're spreading their
propaganda through the news.
What do you plan to do now?
They're after you too,
and their net is closing fast.
We still have one weapon left.
Something that even
they can't stop.
Information.
I sense something.
The ACEs, they've found us!
I swear I didn't call them!
[BEM]
I know.
I called because I was scared
for my guests' safety.
Why are you shooting at them?
We have to get those
people out of there!
The humanoid monsters
are our priority right now.
Alpha sacrificed an
innocent family to escape
the law, along with the
proprietor of this motel.
[MOTEL OWNER 10A]
No! What are you doing?
You can't be serious!
[gunshot]
[FELT]
Detestable creatures.
How much blood will they spill?
[FAMILY whimpering]
Hold your fire! There are
still civilians in the area!
Get them in the car, now.
Understood!
[FELT]
You're to shoot on sight.
The hostages are expendable.
[FELT]
Stop that car!
[FAMILY yells]
The monster!
[BEM]
Go!
[BEM roars]
Damn it.
You're the real power
behind Libra City, right?
[VEGA]
Am I, now?
The unseen council
controls the city government,
law enforcement, the economy.
And the one pulling
the council's strings?
That's you.
You have a keen mind,
much like your father.
He found you out, and that
was why you had him eliminated.
Isn't it?
Mr. Bryson's death
was truly regrettable.
The members of the
council are cowards,
and their greatest fear is
having to look their subjects
in the eye.
My father came up short.
But it's different this time.
Because I have proof.
And if I don't make
it home alive,
that proof comes out.
The whole city, the whole
world learns everything.
My. Well then.
What do you hope to get from me?
I want to take your place.
I want to rule this town.
I see it's power you're after.
It's the way of humans
to seek a master.
For without a master,
they're left with no choice
but to find purpose
for themselves.
And yet, there are
those rare few
who would seek to relieve
others of that burden.
Men like you.
[DARYL]
Flattery will get you nowhere.
[VEGA chuckles]
Perhaps I should
simply give this city to you
as you ask.
[DARYL]
Just like that?
[VEGA] I have a secret that I've
never shared with a single soul.
Would you care to hear it?
[DARYL]
The city's tenth anniversary.
That's me in that picture.
Libra City was built
by my own hands.
[DARYL] But that was more
than a century ago.
[VEGA]
To me it was like yesterday.
My earliest memory
is of an alchemy lab
in the city of Ingolstadt.
A man was there with me,
crying out in ecstasy
that he had touched
the power of God.
And soon after,
the Inquisitors came for him.
The alchemist who created me
was burned at the stake.
I took refuge in Rome with
the noble house of Borgia,
a flower of poison.
And from them I learned much.
Rodrigo unshackled
me from morality.
His son, Cesare, taught me
how to manipulate others.
From his daughter Lucrezia,
I learned the secrets
of love and of poison.
Then you're 500 years old?
I suppose that's right,
if we're counting.
For centuries I've observed
the world of humans.
They have evolved only
in their cruelty.
That's impossible!
Who are you, really?
I'm a humanoid monster.
[HARAZY giggles]
Vega's gonna stay alive forever!
[VEGA] It's a burden, having
no end to look forward to.
There's no way.
Who's that?
[VEGA] This girl is human,
but far from average.
She's quite interesting.
My name is Harazy,
what's your name?
I'm Daryl.
It's nice to meet you!
[DARYL yelps]
Look at you two--so adorable.
All you humans are.
[VEGA] You are to tell Daryl
all about the council.
[AIDE 1A]
Understood, Madame.
All your questions
will be answered.
Ask without reservation.
[phone rings]
[SONIA]
Hey.
Listen, I need all of you
to get out of town.
I can't tell you.
Don't worry about me.
Pass it on to Mom and Dad.
Tell them that
I love all of you.
[BEM] Is the family
from the motel safe?
They're fine.
How can you care so much
about other people, Bem?
[CHIEF] I thought Alpha
took Sonia hostage.
You're saying she's
helping him escape?
[FELT]
In clear breach of her duty.
[CHIEF] And as her superior, the
responsibility is ultimately--
On you, yes.
[CHIEF]
Ugh...
[door opens]
What happened with Sonia?
Uh... Well, we...
[FELT]
Maybe she'll tell us.
Listen. Alpha didn't
kill Gavin Briggs.
I was there.
I know the people
who really killed Gavin.
They're the ones who run
this city from the shadows!
--Sonia?
--What is...?
She just stepped right in it.
[HQ CHIEF]
What did she just do?
It's over. I'm done for!
[CHIEF]
Just calm down a minute.
Nobody is gonna believe some
nutjob from the internet!
Try to imagine how the
council is going to react
to that "nutjob."
Oh, god!
One chance. That's all you get.
Trust your own eyes.
We can all see what's happening
in this city, under the surface.
The problem isn't the
humanoid monsters.
The problem is us!
Are you honestly asking me
to cooperate with the police?
Two wrongs might just
make a right, here.
Our real job is to preserve
public order at all costs
and that can mean
getting our hands dirty.
[DR RECYCLE]
Hmm...
[HQ CHIEF] So, we will ignore
this obviously illegal
medical facility.
In return, you will let us
make use of your skills.
The council will be
overseeing everything.
This isn't a bad deal.
I don't have much patience
for meddling supervisors.
[FELT]
An irrelevant concern.
[SONIA]
The word is starting to spread.
The public is becoming
suspicious of the official story
on the murders.
A lot of like-minded people
are watching the video now.
They think like you?
They all knew
something was wrong.
And they're finally
beginning to act on it.
These people are finding
each other thanks to your
and Gavin's work.
[BEM]
I see.
They want to hear
your story, in your words.
Do they?
If humans would have me speak
to them, then, I shall.
We can change things.
[phone rings]
What?
Officer Summers.
You have made some poor choices.
What do you want?
You put your whole
family in danger.
What if Beta and Gamma
had been targeting them?
Don't worry.
They're safely in our custody,
though it took some
rough handling.
We'll be at the Colosseum.
I didn't think...
he would go this far.
[BEM]
Let's go.
Take me to that place.
You must not waver.
Your family has to come first.
But you finally
have your chance;
there are people waiting
to hear your story,
and I'm taking you away!
There is something
more important at stake.
Something that's
irreplaceable to humans.
Family are the ones closest
to you on your short journey
from birth to death.
And that ephemeral bond is
a beautiful, priceless thing.
But I swore I would protect you,
and now I'm driving
you into their trap!
Don't worry, they can't kill me.
[SONIA yells]
[FELT]
Excellent work, Officer Summers.
[SONIA]
Where is my family?
Relax, I've ordered
their release.
[SONIA cries]
Go.
Is that the chief?
[HQ CHIEF growls]
[SONIA]
But why?
[FELT] He came from HQ
personally to see to your
family's safety.
You should thank him.
[HQ CHIEF roaring]
No, Bem!
[HQ CHIEF roars]
[SONIA]
No!
[chainsaw stops]
[HQ CHIEF grunts]
[clapping]
[VEGA] A masterful show
of fighting prowess.
[FELT]
Madame?
I've been waiting so
long to meet you, Bem.
Who are you?
[VEGA]
I'm here for you.
You must join me.
I will not.
[VEGA]
I wasn't asking.
[BEM grunts]
Does it hurt?
[BEM]
What power is this?
Stop it!
You won't escape.
[BEM grunts]
--[BELO] Bem!
--[BELA] Bem!
Why are you here?
No reason.
Beta and Gamma too.
They've all shown up!
[BELO]
You let them trick you again.
[BEM]
There is no trick.
It was my choice to come here.
[BELO] That woman talked
you into it, didn't she?
[BELA]
She's laughing at you right now.
I swear, that's not true!
[GROUP grunts]
[BELO]
I can't move!
[BELA]
Is this her power?
Madame. I don't believe it.
[BEM]
Who are you?
My name is Vega.
I've been searching for years,
and here you are.
I could always sense that
you were out there somewhere
in this world.
[BEM]
But why?
[VEGA]
Because I need you, Bem.
With you, I can bring
everything to its rightful end.
[BEM]
What rightful end?
[VEGA] There is nothing
that can make you human,
and there is nothing about
humankind worth giving up
all that you are now.
These weak, petty creatures with
their delusions of grandeur.
Do you think there is
room in their hearts
for a thing like you?
You know that they
will never accept you.
Yes, better than anybody.
In your whole
wretched existence,
when have humans
offered you comfort?
Your pain. Your loneliness.
The futility of it.
They've left you
to bear it alone.
Humans fear what
they do not understand.
They vilify and
try to destroy it.
They refuse to learn.
[BEM yells]
[VEGA]
Your prayers will go unheard.
You will not become human,
nor will you die.
You will wander alone
in this hell for eternity.
You are a hideous monster,
unfit for this world!
[BEM]
Monster.
A monster!
[VOICE 10A]
It's disgusting!
[VOICE 10B]
Don't come closer!
[BEM yelling]
Bem?
[BELO, BELA]
Bem!
Your turn.
[BELA]
Harazy?!
[VEGA] That awful monster
is breaking things
and causing problems
for all these people.
Can you help us?
[HARAZY]
Okay!
[BELA]
Don't listen to her!
Bad monster!
Bad!
Please stop!
[BEM yells]
No...
Madame. This whole time.