[SUCTION MAN]
Just get out of my way!
Look at this town. It's filthy!
Are you really okay with that?
[SUCTION MAN grunts]
Oh, look at the
mess you've made!
Now I'll have to clean
it up all over again!
Go.
I'll track him down.
[coughing]
[DRUNK MALE 05A]
Hey there, girly.
It isn't safe out here.
You really shouldn't
be walkin' al--Gah!
[DARYL]
Thank you, Officer.
You went through the trouble
of crossing over the bridge.
[SONIA] I've been summoned
to headquarters.
Listen.
I know who's behind this.
Then call in and report them.
The police are no good.
They would never bite
the hand that feeds them.
I can count on
no one but myself.
I'll avenge my father
with my own two hands.
And who are you
taking vengeance on?
The true enemy of those
who despise corruption.
Called the unseen council.
Oh, hey!
How are ya, Belo?
What's strange is how
I see him sitting nearby
all the time.
I don't get why he doesn't
just come in and say hi.
Guess something must've
happened to him.
Well then he should
talk to us about it.
Maybe we should ask.
But we feel weird about it.
It kinda comes off like he
doesn't wanna be bothered.
Belo's always gone out
of his way to help us
when we needed it.
We should do the same for him.
Well then why don't
you go and talk to him?
I'm a little scared to.
But I also miss my friend.
It's boring without Belo.
[HQ CHIEF] We never would've
found out about all this
were it not for your
efforts, Summers.
I'd like to thank you
for filing that report.
That said...
It seems the chief here dragged
his feet getting it sent to us.
Please allow me to apologize
for delaying that decision.
Uh... Summers was
the only witness,
so it took time to confirm
that the monster was real.
We haven't had time
to build a rapport yet.
I assure you she can be trusted.
I know Summers well.
I'm the one who sent her to you.
That isn't to say I had
much choice in the matter.
Summers had to be transferred.
I did it to protect her
from certain... realities.
I understand completely, sir.
We realize that mysterious
cases like this one
are far more common in the
Outside than in Upper Town.
Although, from
everything I've read,
it seems this case may
belong in a peculiar league
of its own, yes?
Before I proceed,
let me establish one thing.
Officer Summers,
I believe you saw exactly
what you claim you saw.
I've discussed it with my
peers and we've agreed
on a name for such creatures.
From this day forward,
when you're dealing
with a monstrosity
that has a
relatively human form,
you ought to refer to it
as a humanoid monster.
[CHIEF]
A humanoid monster, eh?
To be honest, sir, that sounds
pretty outlandish to me.
You'll get used to it in time.
Our mutual superiors are
quite keen on the term.
--[CHIEF] I see.
--Also...
We've given special designations
to the three humanoid monsters
that can disguise
themselves as humans.
Alpha.
Beta.
And Gamma.
Those creatures
are quite unique.
There's something
else I should mention.
[HQ CHIEF]
By all means.
No one's been in contact with
them as many times as you.
What's your opinion?
I know how this sounds,
but they may our allies, sir.
[HQ CHIEF]
Oh?
They're monsters, Summers.
You think they wanna be friends?
I believe it's possible.
Especially after
this last encounter.
You see...
Alpha has protected me.
More than once.
He's even put himself
into harm's way to do it.
And why didn't you mention
any of this in your report?
'Cause it would've
made you even less likely
to believe it.
[HQ CHIEF] We'll find out
if they're friend or foe soon.
They're most active
in your precinct,
so we're entrusting
you with their capture.
Capture?
You'll be working under
an operational commander.
It's time.
Please come on in.
Well... This is--
Head Operative Felt,
Special First Division.
I'll take over from here.
Hey. I'm the Eighteenth
precinct's poli--
Your name is irrelevant.
Let's begin.
D'you want me to fill you in
on the situation, at least?
[FELT]
I've read the reports.
[CHIEF]
I'm sure you have.
[HQ CHIEF]
Sonia.
Doesn't look like
you've changed much.
You need to try not to act
on your own all the time.
You've got a knack for making
your chiefs look incompetent.
If there's a need for action to
be taken, then I take action.
[sighs]
Overdo it again and there'll
be nowhere left to send you.
[SONIA]
With all due respect, sir.
This is quite the
change of tone for you.
Oh, don't be like that.
To be honest,
I was pleasantly surprised that
you chose to bring this issue
to me.
I'm surprised at
myself for trusting you.
Goodbye, sir.
[BEM]
You lost him.
I would've caught him,
but some lowlife got in my way.
I see.
So what's this
idiot's weird obsession?
He wants to clean.
More than anything.
This old mansion
of yours is filthy.
I could clean it for you if
you made me a proper vacuum.
Hoh!
You want a vacuum?
Well isn't that homey.
Might I ask why you
like cleaning so much?
I like how it feels to make
filth disappear for good.
I want to clean up every fetid
corner of this disgusting city.
That's why I joined the
sanitation department.
I wanted to make
our streets shine
so that no Uppertowner
could call the Outside
a trash dump again.
I just don't understand.
They're all content
to sit in their own filth.
My mother never learned
to pick up after herself.
I didn't have a father.
And each time Mother came home,
she brought a different
man with her.
None of them were kind.
Most were quite
violent towards me.
Mother never stopped them.
But thankfully, she and
her boyfriends spent
most of their time
away from home.
I didn't have much
to do by myself.
So I started cleaning
up that filthy place.
It felt so nice to be
surrounded by clean things.
That's why...
...I cleaned up my mother.
And her boyfriend too.
I felt so refreshed.
Like a completely new person.
You enjoy cleaning
and you're perfectly able to,
so what do you need me for?
[SUCTION MAN] I've realized
that dirty people are trash.
Well...
That isn't an opinion
I care to argue with,
but even now,
your point eludes me.
[SUCTION MAN]
That's all right.
Let me explain it to you.
If I don't remove
the human trash,
this world will never be clean.
[DR RECYCLE]
Ahh.
That's quite a unique
way of thinking.
I know.
That's why it has
to be done by me.
I wish I'd been born
as a vacuum cleaner.
Care to become one?
[SUCTION MAN gasps]
That's possible?
There's a new technique
that I think would be perfect
for you.
You'll love it.
Intrigued?
[SUCTION MAN panting]
[DR RECYCLE] This one will
make a very interesting sample.
--[CHIEF] Something wrong?
--[FELT] No.
[phone ringing]
[CHIEF]
What the hell is this?!
Few guys came by to renovate.
I thought you'd been fired.
This room will be
my center of operations
while I work to capture
the humanoid monsters.
But if you're here,
then where's my office gonna be?
You don't need one.
Where did Officer Summers go?
[WOODS]
Got someplace to be?
[SONIA] The Helmsmen tell
me they might have a lead
on the humanoid monsters.
"Humanoid monsters?"
Apparently that's
the new term for them.
The higher-ups across
the bridge came up with it.
[WOODS]
Which higher-ups?
You know who sent
that Felt guy here?
He's from the Special Division.
That so?
[SONIA] He's a minion
of the unseen council.
And you think they're trying
to take your monster
for themselves?
[SONIA]
No idea.
But I need to go confirm
this lead for now.
Why don't'cha report it
to the special officer first?
Because he wouldn't take
the Helmsmen seriously.
And so, our brave young
Joan of Arc rides on.
Charging off to
battle yet again.
[HOMELESS MAN 05A]
That's him.
Same hat and everything.
Okay, and you thought
you might've seen him
with the other two as well?
[HOMELESS MAN 05A]
Now and then, yeah.
He'd walk around
with a teenage girl,
and a boy younger than her.
They made a pretty
noticeable trio.
[CROWD screaming]
You're all just trash!
That's what I call suction!
[WOMAN 05A]
Someone help me!
[SUCTION MAN]
Oh, my, look, a mess.
[phones ringing]
There's no cause
for us to mobilize.
But sir...
A humanoid monster is rampaging
through the precinct.
You can't plan to ignore all
the people that called for help.
That monster is not my target.
[SONIA]
Got it. I'm heading there now.
What's the special
officer doing?
[WOODS] Well, this isn't one
of the monsters he was ordered
to catch, so it
doesn't look like
he's gonna do
much of anything.
No way.
He's leaving these
people to die?
[gasps]
[SONIA gasps]
[SUCTION MAN]
More trash?
It just keeps coming!
[SONIA screams]
[SONIA]
I found him. Alpha's here!
We'll deploy at once.
Do what you can
to keep him in place.
[CHIEF]
We moving out now?
Odd guy.
Doesn't seem like he
has much work-life balance.
[SUCTION MAN]
It's you again.
Please stop obstructing me
from doing my work!
[yells]
[grunts]
They're all filth!
Why can't you see that?!
This isn't the kind of machine
you can eject from, is it?
Why would I want to leave?
This body lets me clean
faster than any human!
I don't need people!
They're all just garbage!
Your vision has been clouded.
[SUCTION MAN screaming]
[SUCTION MAN gasping]
You're garbage too!
Garbage! Garbage!
Garbage!
[BEM roars]
What the--?
Hold on. What exactly are you?
I've never seen such
a disgusting beast.
You're garbage!
Garbage! Garbage!
Ah, what sweet release.
[SUCTION MAN groans]
[BEM]
You're still a human.
[SUCTION MAN groans]
[BEM]
There are worse things to be.
I don't think you should
go down there right now.
You'll only end up
getting hurt again.
[vehicles approaching]
I told you.
It seems kinda
different this time.
This is rather fortunate.
I've only just begun
my assignment,
and I already have
Alpha in my sights.
Do it.
[SUCTION MAN gasping]
[SUCTION MAN screams]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[BELA growls]
Beta's here too?
[thud]
And Gamma.
[FELT]
Kill it.
We've no use for trash.
[SONIA]
Hold on, sir.
You did well to call me.
It seems you're reliable.
But know that I
disapprove of your methods.
Alpha saved my life
yet again tonight.
And then it protected you too.
An irrelevant detail.
Our job is unchanged.
Alpha must be captured.
Then why did you
have this guy shot?
He was a valuable suspect.
We could've gotten
information from him.
That thing is trash.
[BELA]
Did you see the way he smiled?
I don't know too much about it,
but it seemed like he was happy.
What are you getting at?
He got to become
what he wanted to be.
I feel like maybe that's
the secret to happiness.
He happily vacuumed
people to death.
I don't understand.
How can all of these people
toss aside their humanity
just like that?
If they wanna be us,
why should we
wanna be them?
[VEGA]
How disappointing.
You were almost in my grasp.
I'm waiting.
Hurry and come to my side.
I must have you, Bem.