[crunching]
Thanks for the nice meal.
Um. Sure, no problem.
Off to work?
Ah. Yes I am, like normal.
[CHIHIRO]
Wait, he's never normal.
[chuckles]
[CHIHIRO] He couldn't be more
suspicious if he actually tried.
[MADOKA chuckles]
--[KITTEN 10A meows]
--[CHIHIRO gasps]
Are you keeping
a cat in here?
[MADOKA]
Um, no!
You are so busted, mister!
[gasps]
[MADOKA breathes deeply]
[KITTENS meowing]
[phone beeping]
[MADOKA] Chi, wait it's me!
It's your Uncle Madoka.
Don't call the police, okay?
[KITTENS meow]
[KEIICHIRO]
There we go.
You were some hungry little
kitties, weren't you?
Well, well. Do you know
what you did wrong today?
Do you?
[MADOKA]
Yes.
[CHIHIRO]
Of course you do.
Because you've been in trouble
for this before, right?
So why would you keep
repeating the same mistake?
[MADOKA] I just thought, you
know, if I wear this mask
then I wouldn't
sneeze and stuff.
I asked why you would
keep repeating
the same mistake, Madoka?
[MADOKA]
I'm sorry.
[KEIICHIRO] His scolding power
is over nine thousand!
[KEIICHIRO] That's all of them.
Leave the rest to me.
Thanks for coming here
on your day off.
I appreciate it.
Of course. Now tomorrow,
I'll be sure to stop by
the Cat Lover's Meet Up
and hopefully find
a home for these guys.
[MADOKA] A meet up?
For cat lovers?
No fair, I wanna go!
[KEIICHIRO] I'll let you know
how it turns out.
[MADOKA] Aww. I thought
if I wore this mask
then everything would be okay.
Well surprise,
you thought wrong.
Were you planning
on wearing that
the whole time
you were in here?
[MADOKA] Sure,
it was kind of a pain.
[chuckles]
But I would have endured it
for my kitty harem!
Please don't call it that.
"Kitty harem" makes you
sound like a total weirdo.
It's not like
it matters now anyway.
[sneezes]
[CHIHIRO groans]
Ugh, there's cat hair
all over your bed.
That's just perfect!
[MADOKA]
I'm sorry.
Huh?
What the heck?
They were in your drawers?
[MADOKA] Oh, I used them as
stairs for the fur-babies.
We played hide and go seek!
[CHIHIRO]
What is wrong with you?
Don't answer that.
You've left me no choice.
I'll have to scrub this
whole room spotless. Right?
[MADOKA] Uh. Yeah.
Knock yourself out.
[door knob clicks]
[KEIICHIRO]
I'm home.
[meows]
[KEIICHIRO] Would you like
to check out the new guys?
[KITTENS meow]
There. Does that feel better?
[blow dryer hums]
[KEIICHIRO]
Okay, say "meow"!
[camera shutter clicks]
Having a couple of
really cute pictures
of you guys will help me
find everyone a good home.
That's not the cute factor
I was looking for.
I see. Well that explains
the sudden need
for deep cleaning.
[MADOKA] Yes, at least
it's only my room though.
All of my clothes,
sheets, and curtains
were covered with cat hair.
Chi insisted that
we had to wash everything.
Everything.
[MIYAKO] Oh my, please
don't get sick, okay?
Hey Miyako,
give me the box
when you're finished with it.
Eeh! Hold up, Madoka.
Why are you out here
wearing only a blanket?
It's indecent!
Then hurry and give me
my clothes back already!
Go make some or whatever.
When it comes to weird stuff,
you can work fast, right?
I don't feel like it.
Making my own clothes
is totally boring.
[CHIHIRO] I don't care!
Inside, now!
--[MADOKA] Chi...
--[MIYAKO giggles]
When hanging up
large sheets like this,
they tend to dry faster
if you spread them out.
[MIYAKO]
Okay!
Miyako, I'm sorry to
make you help like this.
No problem! It's such a perfect
day for hanging laundry anyway.
It would be a real waste
to spend it inside.
[CHIHIRO] All right,
we're finished!
[MIYAKO]
Yay!
[CHIHIRO] I typically
use the dryer,
but I just love the way
laundry smells after
it has dried in the
fresh air, you know?
[MIYAKO]
Yeah, me too!
[MADOKA] Definitely. Gotta love
that sun-kissed smell!
Ta-dah! Like it?
[MADOKA]
Behold my kitty tunic!
Don't be so proud.
You look like some
cat-loving Roman.
While we're on the subject,
how much of that
fabric do you have?
I actually bought
the entire bolt! Mhm!
Whoa, seriously?
Talk about excessive.
[MIYAKO giggles]
Considering his
huge love of cats,
its prob'ly not enough fabric!
Oh, I know.
They're so cute!
[gasps]
But, my gas mask
plan failed, so...
...all hope is lost!
[MIYAKO] Oh you poor thing.
I wish we could help!
Get over it.
Ahh! Why are
you so mean to me?
[gasps]
Wait a second.
I think I have the perfect
solution to your problem!
[CHIHIRO, MADOKA]
You do?
Yep. Just leave it to me!
Hey, what's with
the blank stare?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I didn't buy these, you know!
Miyako gave them all to me!
Oh. So that's what was
in the box that arrived earlier.
Correct. You know,
I do love cats,
but a man my age
really shouldn't be
playing with stuffed animals.
But, they were a gift!
It would be rude not to!
I simply must
play with them, you see?
Therefore,
I'm going name them all.
This one's Sir Fluffy Bottom!
[laughs]
[CHIHIRO]
Congratulations, I guess.
I'm happy for you.
[MADOKA]
I can feel you judging me!
[CHIHIRO sighs]
Well, if those toys
keep him busy,
I really can't complain.
[CAT VOICES meow]
[CHIHIRO] Why are these stupid
plushies in my room?
[MADOKA] 'Cause I sleep
in there sometimes.
It makes perfect sense!
--[CHIHIRO] No way!
--[MADOKA] Awww...
[CHIHIRO] Excuse me! I'd like
this cabbage please.
Sure thing, kid!
[HANAKO]
Chihiro!
[CHIHIRO] Hi Hana!
Hello Mrs. Hino!
How are you guys?
[HANAKO]
Yay!
[chuckles]
Good to see you! And
thank you for the macarons
you made us all for White Day.
Those were some
delicious cookies!
Did you really
make them yourself?
Uh, yes!
Wow, that's impressive!
[HANAKO] And thanks
for my present, too!
[chuckles]
[HINO'S MOM] Oh yeah.
Speaking of homemade things,
Memorial Week is coming up.
I'm going to make
a big batch
of botamochi for Higan.
I'd be happy to set some aside
for you, if you want.
Are you sure?
Mommy said I can
be the taste tester.
They're yummy!
Don't be a stranger.
We're always here
if you need us.
Thank you,
I appreciate it.
[CHIHIRO] Wow. Higan really
snuck up on me.
It has been a long time
since I visited Mom's grave.
It's probably in need
of a good cleaning.
Okay so, I'll need botamochi,
prob'ly incense.
What else? Oh, flowers!
[WHITE CAT 5A meows]
--[WHITE CAT 5A shrieks]
--[KAZUSA gasps]
--[CHIHIRO] Um, hi.
Oh, Chihiro.
What a surprise.
How have you been?
Uh... Fine, I suppose.
[KAZUSA]
Well, you see,
the poor thing looked
positively famished.
I only put the food out
in case the cat was hungry,
not because I wanted to pet it.
Yeah, right, of course.
That's super reasonable.
So are you
running errands today?
Yep. There was a really
awesome sale on vegetables.
This cabbage was a steal!
You're like a
penny-pinching housewife!
Uuh...
I have a couple of
errands to run as well.
There's a candy store nearby,
and it's one of my favorites.
I need to go before Higan.
Oh. For botamochi?
That's right.
I've been thinking and
I wonder if it's hard to make.
Ah. So, do you
normally buy it?
Kinda. We used to get
botamochi from the store,
but I just learned to bake,
and even though
I'm not all that great,
I was thinking of making
my own this year.
I thought it would be
a better offering
if I prepared them
myself, you know?
[KAZUSA]
Mmm. Give it a shot.
You'll never know until
you at least try, right?
Besides,
all mothers cherish gifts
given by their children,
especially homemade.
[CHIHIRO]
Thanks!
[MADOKA]
Botamochi, huh?
I've never actually
made it before.
[CHIHIRO]
Okay.
Well, I asked
Hino's mom for the recipe.
Sounds like
you're all set then.
I'm sure you'll do
a great job, as usual.
But I've never
made them though,
and I want everything
to be perfect.
Oh. Would you like
me to help you?
[CHIHIRO]
Mhm.
Ah.
I'd like your help.
[screams]
[MADOKA screams]
[MADOKA hollers gleefully]
[panting]
How's this design work?
[CHIHIRO] I meant
help with the cooking.
Aww!
[CHIHIRO] Baking doesn't
require a costume!
[MADOKA] You're underestimating
the Artisan-style!
[CHIHIRO] It's hard to believe,
but almost a whole year
has passed already.
Strange, but it's like
it went by quickly
and slowly at the same time.
Life sure is
full of surprises.
Especially in this house.
[MADOKA] You know what I've
always wondered about?
Why half-pounding sticky rice
is called "half-killing."
Why do you care?
It sounds so violent.
Know what I mean?
I don't want to
half-kill anything,
much less this
poor defenseless rice.
What'd it ever do to me?
Uh yeah. Just don't
overdo it, okay?
Fine.
[CHIYO] I'm sure you're
probably wondering
what's going to happen
to you after this.
I think you'll be fine,
so don't worry.
[CHIHIRO] Yeah. This year may
have had its ups and downs,
but I am doing fine.
In the end,
you were right.
[MADOKA]
Ta-da! It's so cute!
[CHIHIRO]
I'm okay, Mom.
But you probably
already knew that.
Is the taste too sweet?
No. These are just right.
[CHIHIRO groans]
Knowing sis,
she'd prefer yours
over store bought ones.
Do you really think so?
[MADOKA]
Absolutely.
All mothers cherish
gifts given by their children,
especially homemade.
[CHIHIRO] I think you're
right. They are perfect.
All right,
then it looks like
we're ready for tomorrow!
[CHIHIRO]
Wait a sec.
[CHIHIRO] Strange.
Did I tell her I was going
to my mom's grave?
How did she know?
[crossing gate dings]
[CHIHIRO]
Ah, here we are.
Aw man, I knew
it was gonna be dirty.
I'll go get some water,
so watch our things.
[MADOKA]
"Komiya Family." Huh?
[CHIHIRO]
I'm back.
Okay. Ready to
start cleaning?
Yay.
[CHIHIRO] All right Madoka,
you're on weed duty.
And I'll wipe down
the tombstone!
[MADOKA]
Aye-aye!
--You seem used to this.
--Yeah, I guess.
Mom and I would
come here together.
You know, to say hi to Dad.
That's right.
He's also here.
[gasps]
Yep. We'd always come
and clean the grave
for him, too.
Did you forget?
[MADOKA]
I'm sorry.
Well, I don't really
remember him,
so I can't be sad about it.
I guess.
[CHIHIRO] Mom did try to
show me some pictures of him,
but he was either
always hiding his face
or the photo was
like, super blurry.
It was pointless.
[chuckles] Some people
are just camera shy!
That's true. But Mom sure
did talk about him a lot.
[CHIYO] Your dad was all alone,
and he only wanted one thing.
He wanted a family of his own.
Except then he died
not long after I was born.
[MADOKA] I wonder what Chi
looked like as a baby.
I bet you were adorable.
Can you imagine all
the frilly baby clothes?
Oh, please stop.
Know what I think?
Your dad must have been happy.
I mean, he did have you guys.
I don't know. To be honest,
I can't say I think
of him that often.
Is that bad?
[MADOKA] No. I mean,
I don't remember anything
from when I was a baby either.
But to your dad, you must
have meant the world.
After all, that's what
it's like to be family.
Maybe you're right.
[MADOKA] Well Chi, I guess
now you belong to me.
I'm gonna keep you
forever and ever!
Wha-- Hey, I'm not a pet!
I'm kidding.
If I brag too much,
sis might come back
and haunt me!
Sure.
I'm sorry.
[CHIHIRO]
Dear Mom and Dad,
this is my life now.
I'm happy that
you're together again.
At least you won't be lonely,
and I'm not either.
Here, this one's yours.
[MADOKA] Hey, Chi? Speaking
of photos and stuff,
do you have a baby album?
[CHIHIRO] You're not
allowed to see it.
Aw, if I showed you a
really embarrassing picture
of Keiichiro, then maybe
could I look at it?
[CHIHIRO]
And you call him evil.
Shoot, I forgot the bucket.
Be right back!
[CHIHIRO]
It's her.
Oh. Well hello
again, Chihiro.
You did a wonderful job
taking care of the grave.
This is a surprise.
It's not often I see you
visiting someone's grave
so obediently, Madoka.
Perhaps this means
you've matured a bit.
It was worth
letting you leave, then.
What do you think
you're doing here?
What do you want?
Pardon me, I didn't realize
it was such a crime
for a mother to visit
her daughter's grave.
Your daughter?
[KAZUSA] Though we've
talked so often Chihiro,
I never properly
introduced myself.
I'm Kazusa Takatori.
Your mother was my daughter,
making me your grandmother.
[KAZUSA]
Oh dear.
It wasn't ever my intention
to deceive you.
I'm so sorry for
not telling you sooner.
[crossing gate dings]
Your mother?
My mother. I wonder
what she's thinking.
You know, she'd been
meeting with Chi
without ever telling him
who she was?
[KEIICHIRO]
You don't say?
Was it you?
Did you tell her?
Where Chiyo's grave was.
She asked me and of course
I'm obliged to answer.
I guess so. It's not
as if I can blame you.
I can't believe her.
The sheer audacity.
She's only trying
to get on his good side.
[MADOKA] After all, that's what
it's like to be family.
Then again, look at me.
I'm just as bad.
[CHIHIRO] It's strange.
I thought for sure that if
I ever met anyone
from the main family
I'd be angrier.
Hey, Mom.
I met Grandma today.
[MADOKA] Chihiro, I want to
thank you for everything.
[CHIHIRO]
That sounds weirdly formal.
[MADOKA] Yes, I know.
It feels like
this might be
goodbye, though.
[CHIHIRO]
Madoka.
[MADOKA] Then again,
it's only a feeling,
maybe it won't come true.
[CHIHIRO]
Okay!
[MADOKA] Wait, you could act
a little more sad about it!
[CHIHIRO] The next episode
is "Boys, Be Ambitious"!
Who knows what is going
to happen to all of us?
How will things end up?
[MADOKA] Stop! You're making it
sound like it's really over!
[CHIHIRO]
Don't forget to watch!
[MADOKA] And so,
the boy becomes a man.
Just kidding!