[KEIICHIRO]
Our young housekeeper...
[CHIHIRO]
Chihiro Komiya.
[KEIICHIRO] ...is currently
in elementary school.
Despite the daily stresses,
he still works valiantly
to keep things clean and orderly
in the Takatori household.
[MADOKA]
I'm counting on you!
[CHIHIRO] You're not gonna help?
I'm the maid around here.
I'm trying hard
just like my mother said
in the letter she left for me.
[CHIHIRO]
Her exact words were:
"Those who do not work
shall not eat!"
[MADOKA] I think you're
doing a great job!
[CHIHIRO]
Well, I think you should
pull your weight around here!
[PUPPY 1A barks]
[CHIHIRO]
It's spring already.
Seems like I ran into
Madoka just the other day.
[KAZUSA]
Stop! Go home!
--[KAZUSA] Shoo! Shoo!
--[PUPPY 1A barks]
Can you save me
from this horrible beast?
[CHIHIRO]
Where have I seen this before?
Oh, my.
Sorry! He runs off sometimes.
My goodness.
People should be
more careful when
they walk their pets.
That thing could have
bitten someone.
Yeah, but he
was pretty small.
Beware of furry demons!
[CHIHIRO] I guess people who
hate dogs all act the same way.
Oh dear. Looks like I've
embarrassed myself
in front of you again,
haven't I?
[CHIHIRO]
It's okay.
I think your name
is Chihiro, right?
That's twice that
you've saved my life.
Would it be all right
if I treat you
to a cup of tea
as a thank you?
What? There's really
no need for that!
[KAZUSA]
Oh, too bad.
But I suppose it's not hip to
drink tea with an old woman.
[CHIHIRO] Sorry!
That's not what I meant!
[KAZUSA chuckles]
I'm only joking.
[CHIHIRO] It's just...
I'm supposed to go
right home after school.
I know. How about tomorrow?
I don't go to school
tomorrow so...
Tomorrow.
That sounds nice.
[CHIHIRO hums]
The dishes are clean.
But what do I do
with this stuff?
I can't believe
he made all of that.
[yells]
He reached new levels
of procrastination today.
[doorbell buzzes]
[CHIHIRO]
Coming!
Hana? Hi. What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
It's my big brother!
I hate him!
[CHIHIRO gasps]
[HINO] Seriously? Why would
Hana run to your house?
All right, don't let
her leave okay?
I'm heading over right now!
[phone beeps]
How do I
keep her from leaving?
[CHIHIRO]
Go ahead.
I'm sure you're hungry after
all that walking you did.
--It's so good!
--Great! Help yourself!
[CHIHIRO]
Way to go, Madoka!
[sneezes]
Why'd you run away?
It's all my
big brother's fault.
He invaded my privacy!
Oh. Is that so?
I won't go home
until he says he's sorry
for what he did! Please.
Don't tell anyone
I'm hiding here, okay?
Uh!
[doorbell buzzes]
[panting]
Where's Hana?
[CHIHIRO] Jeez,
your timing is terrible!
Huh?! You're the one
who said she was here!
Hold on a sec,
she's upset right now!
[HINO]
Hana!
I can't believe
that you came all the way
out here by yourself!
You weren't supposed to
tell on me, Chihiro!
Wait, Hana!
Stop! What's your problem?
I hate you, Yuji!
I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
[CHIHIRO]
Hino!
Are you in here? Hana?
Hello?
[rain falling]
[knock, knock]
[CHIHIRO]
Madoka, I'm coming in.
[door knob clicks]
What's up?
[CHIHIRO] Hino's
little sister is here.
Have you seen her around?
I'll just have to
keep looking.
Sorry about that. Let me
know if you see her, okay.
[door squeaks, thuds]
He's gone now.
Not with him. I'm sure
we'll find her soon enough.
Yeah. I'm sure we will.
[CHIHIRO]
Are you okay?
What are the two of you
even fighting about?
[HINO]
Mmm.
[CHIHIRO] So this notebook
belongs to Hana?
She just left it lying
around in the living room.
And so, I got curious.
You read it
without asking her?
[HANAKO]
Shocked!
Uuh!
--[HANAKO sobbing]
--[HINO] Hey! Hana!
[HINO] It's not like
her jibberish
makes any kind of sense.
I don't get why
she's so mad about it.
[CHIHIRO] Didn't you used to get
angry at your older sisters?
It's not the same.
They went out of
their way to be cruel.
Ooh! What's this?
"I Love My Family," an essay.
Put it down!
[MIE]
That's totally adorable!
"I think I have
the bestest family
in the whole wide world."
I'll do anything to keep
Hana from turning out
like the rest of our siblings!
But it looks like I'm gonna be
fighting a losing battle.
Truthfully, you're alot
more like your siblings
than you think you are.
We should probably start
looking for her again now.
Yeah?
[chuckles]
[HINO]
Asleep.
I think she
wore herself out.
--Was she here the whole time?
--Shhh.
When a saddened
young lady comes to you
with one tiny request...
Will you hide me?
...you don't have
much of a choice.
You have to help,
as a gentleman.
[CHIHIRO] Yeah.
I wonder what her parents
would say about that.
As soon as she
found me I went ahead
and told her family that
we'd take care of her!
What?
Or more specifically,
that you'd take care of her.
They seemed really
excited about the break!
But why me?
I guess they
really trust you!
Would you like
to sleep over, Hino?
No thanks. It's fine.
Here. Take this.
Will you give it back
to her for me please?
Chihiro.
Did Yuji leave already?
Mhm. He said he
would be back tomorrow.
Okay.
Do you want to go home?
No, I do not!
[MADOKA]
I'm so glad you're awake!
Would you like me
to make you a dress?
Yes, please!
What kind would you like?
A frilly one!
For a princess!
We had so much fun!
I could probably
sew dresses 24/7
with that young lady!
She's got style!
Aren't there
a few projects
you should be finishing?
How strange. You sound
just like Keiichiro.
[CHIHIRO] Just great. I really
wanted to talk to her
before she went
to sleep tonight.
Talk to her?
For Hino. I want to
help them to stop fighting.
I don't think you
should worry yourself.
People only bicker
with those they love.
Huh? Then why did you
keep her for the night?
Well to be honest,
she went to so much
trouble running away,
I would feel bad
sending her back.
For real?
She lives there.
Well, Miyako
ran away from home
when she was
about that age, too.
[CHIHIRO]
Huh?
I hate you so much, Father!
Shocked!
[MIYAKO sobbing]
[MADOKA] I lived so far away she
had to come with a driver.
[chuckles]
He resisted at first so she
tried walking here on her own.
The man felt so guilty about it
that he gave in
and brought her anyway.
But Miyako was so cute
and little I had to help.
And if I remember right, sis
would side with Uncle Otori.
Why'd she do that?
[MADOKA] She thought it would
only be fair if both of them
had someone to defend
their point of view.
Your father's come all
this way to take you home.
Are you ready to go now?
No! I'm never going back!
Super shocked!
Hm! Poor Hino.
Did you see him?
He looked so disappointed
walking home.
It reminded me
of Miyako's father
when he went home that evening!
[chuckles]
You shouldn't laugh.
[CHIHIRO]
I can't believe this.
You'd think a kid
running away from home
would be taken more seriously.
[knock, knock]
[CHIHIRO] Hey there.
What's wrong? Can't sleep?
Are you okay?
[CHIHIRO]
Wanna sleep in here?
[HANAKO]
Mhmmm.
[HANAKO] This is
a giant king's bed!
Like a fairy tale!
Glad you like it.
Oh! Almost forgot.
Here you go.
Hino wanted me to
give this back to you.
He's mad at me
for not coming home, huh?
He's pretty tough,
so I know he'll be fine.
[HANAKO]
Really?
[CHIHIRO]
Mhm.
I mean,
aside from the crying.
I'm not crying!
[HANAKO] Know what? It was
supposed to be a secret.
I promised Ayu I wouldn't show
anybody our special journal.
We pinky swore!
Yuji looked
and ruined everything.
[CHIHIRO] I don't think
he meant to hurt you.
[HANAKO]
But I said I hated him.
What if he's mad at me forever?
He'll leave me here.
What? That's ridiculous!
He would never leave you!
You think so?
You bet! Don't worry.
Tomorrow you guys are
gonna make up for sure.
Right?
[HANAKO]
'Kay.
[MADOKA]
Ta-da!
Look, she's a magical girl!
Mhm! Looks so cute!
Thanks to you,
Uncle Maddy!
[MADOKA, HANAKO]
Yay!
If only you could
get this enthusiastic
when it comes to getting
your actual work done.
[doorbell buzzes]
[door knob clicks]
--[HINO] Morning.
--[CHIHIRO] Nice to see you.
Hey Hana!
Your brother's here!
Why're you wearing
that weird dress?
[CHIHIRO, HINO]
Huh?
I figured she'd
be over it by now.
I don't think she was.
Let's go find her.
[MADOKA]
Surprise!
It's a real magic wand!
If you ask me,
every magical girl needs one!
Now you can
make wishes come true!
Really?
It's full of magic.
Think hard;
what do you want
more than anything?
The wand will help you
make it a reality.
It will? Anything?
[HANAKO]
I don't hate you.
Thanks, sis. Love ya.
[laughs]
See ya later!
[CHIHIRO]
Oooh. I'm exhausted.
[chuckles] She wasn't
that much work, was she?
All you did
was play with her!
She was really upset last night.
But still, I'm sure
you had no trouble
cheering her up.
Huh?
I think she
really liked you!
There's a sort of
gentleness about you
that people seem to be drawn to.
You'd be a great nanny!
Hey, it's not my fault
that you're so likable!
And then
I had desserts,
and they were yummy!
Wow! Pretty dress!
That's adorable!
We drew lots of pictures
and Uncle Maddy
made this special dress
just for me!
[HINO] I guess everybody
and their dog is gonna
stare at us the whole way home.
Why is she torturing me?
[HANAKO] ...make a wish
it can totally come true!
[KEIICHIRO moans]
So Keiichiro, you seem
a little quiet today.
[KEIICHIRO]
After all I said,
you didn't
do anything yesterday...
I'm sorry! I'll take
care of everything!
[CHIHIRO] I think I'll leave
them alone for this.
Both of us got
distracted yesterday.
[doorbell buzzes]
[CHIHIRO]
I'm coming!
[UCHOTEN BOYS]
I'm not gonna say,
I shouldn't even have to say.
I got some time off
so I wanted
to pay you guys a visit!
Don't you remember me?
I'm Ryuji from
the Uchoten Boys!
I'll aim my charm
straight at your heart.
[CHIHIRO] Of course
I remember who you are.
But why did you
bring so much stuff?
Oh! I didn't know what
I'd need for the sleepover!
The what?
[RYUJI]
I guess nobody told you.
Hino and I decided that
your house would be
the best place
to play video games!
That's news to me!
Sorry! The Hana thing
kinda took over
and I forgot to tell you.
I'll head over soon.
She's doing a lot better now.
And here you go!
I can feel your magic
working on me!
Magical Hana
saves the day!
[KOJI] Ha-ha-ha!
Rescue Mask is here at last!
Will you guys keep
it down, please? I'm busy!
Rescue Mask's
the good guy.
If you wanna be 'im, you gotta
be handsome and rich.
I quit.
[RYUJI] Hold up. Are you
going out or something?
Yeah. Hino will
be here soon anyway.
[yells]
[CHIHIRO] Madoka's got
a deadline coming up,
so don't bother him.
There are snacks
for you in the kitchen,
but please don't try to use
the stove while I'm gone.
Don't open the door
for any strangers, okay?
And you'll need to take breaks
every now and then...
[HINO] What are you,
his mom or something?
Hey.
I'm heading out right now,
but you can hang out here.
I'll be back soon.
[HINO]
Okay.
I'm running late already!
See you guys later!
Wait. Where's
he going anyway?
--Let's go.
--Huh?
This'll be more fun
than a video game!
[HINO] He's going
on a date? No way.
[RYUJI] Look at the signs!
He's heading to town
even though some of his
friends are at his house!
It's definitely a date!
Trust me, Ibuki ditches
me like this all the time!
It's ready to eat!
[IBUKI] I'm actually
going out with Midoriko
for dinner tonight. Sorry!
I had to eat all of
that barbeque by myself.
[HINO] Oh, I feel
so sorry for you.
[BOY 9A laughs]
--[BOYS laugh]
--[BOY 9A] That was fun!
[CHIHIRO] I'm sorry I'm late.
Were you waiting a while?
It's quite all right.
I don't mind. I was
enjoying the scenery.
[HINO] Why would he go on
a date with an old lady?
[RYUJI] Who knows?
Maybe she looks younger
the closer you get.
[HINO]
Are you serious? No way.
She's like a hundred.
So?
Thank you.
Your advice about the birthday
present really helped.
It ended up being
the perfect gift.
My pleasure.
Though I can see no reason
for you to give me
all of the credit.
You obviously did a splendid
job picking out his present.
[CHIHIRO]
I guess so.
But really, I couldn't
have done it without you.
I wanted to make sure to thank
you whenever I saw you again.
[KAZUSA chuckles]
You have such a kind soul.
[HINO] I think we're
officially stalkers.
No. We're super spies.
[HINO]
But why?
What if Chihiro is some
kind of old lady kidnapper?
[HINO] Will you stop
fooling around?
Get down!
Is there something wrong?
I'm fine.
[CHIHIRO] Those voices
seemed very familiar.
[KAZUSA]
I have to admit,
it felt nice to
be able to help you.
I haven't bought any gifts
for a while now.
[CHIHIRO] Why is that?
Don't you have any relatives
to buy Christmas
or birthday gifts for?
I did, but both
my son and daughter
left home several years ago,
and my husband
isn't the type
to get very excited
about much of anything.
[RYUJI slurps]
[HINO] I wonder who she is.
She looks kinda familiar.
But maybe, if I'm lucky,
I'll get to meet my grandson.
I hope so. I would give him
all kinds of gifts.
[gasps]
So he lives really
far away from you then?
That's hard.
I suppose it's
something like that.
It seems as though
he's doing well though,
so that's a comfort to me.
It is a bit lonely
from time to time.
I wanted to ask you.
Would it be okay if I came to
visit you every so often?
Yes it would.
I'd enjoy that.
But wouldn't it bore
a young man like you
to spend time listening
to an old lady?
No. I think I'd like it.
Well, I never actually got the
chance to meet my grandparents.
It's something I've
always wanted to do.
I bet I'd love them.
One day you'll meet them.
They'll love you too.
[MADOKA] Well. She was
estranged from the family
for a long while.
I suppose it's only natural
she'd have considered
herself alone
in the world.
[LANDLORD 1A] Hard to believe
that such a young woman
could die of heart failure.
[LANDLADY 1A]
She struggled day after day
just to make ends meet.
Okay, let's go.
Hey! Why'd you
order that huge thing?
'Cause this super spy can't
work on an empty stomach!
Really? You're
gonna get us caught!
[CHIHIRO] No, being loud
is gonna get you caught.
[HINO, RYUJI shriek]
What are you two
doing here?
[RYUJI, HINO whimper]
Can't believe
you blew our cover.
Whatever.
Why did I listen to you?
Aw man, Chihiro is
gonna be so mad at us.
Ah! Does that mean
we can't play games?
Sorry. My friends
can be nosy sometimes.
[KAZUSA chuckles]
I thought they were
quite charming.
I'm sure they're waiting
to spend time with you.
Please feel free to go on
ahead and play with them.
I'll take care
of everything here.
[CHIHIRO]
All right.
I had such
a wonderful time.
I'd love the opportunity
to have tea with you again.
Sure! Thank you
for everything, ma'am.
[door chimes ring]
[door thuds]
[CHIYO]
Mom, I made my choice.
I love you, but I have to
follow my heart right now.
I'm leaving with him.
Forgive me!
[KAZUSA] Chiyo, your son
is such a sweet boy.
I'm unsure if Madoka
can raise him properly.
Now I wonder: would
Chihiro be better off with us?
[MADOKA]
Finally finished!
[sighs]
You actually
hit your deadline.
I'll be glad to deliver it to
the client now. Excuse me.
Thanks a lot.
[RYUJI groans]
I'm starving to death.
Please tell me maids
get a break for food.
No slacking off!
You only get to eat a nice
big dinner once you earn it.
Aw!
Keep going! If you'd
stop that whining and work
we'd already be done by now.
[groans]
I have no idea
what their crime was,
but can we forgive
them just once?
No way!
[chuckles]
[HINO]
They really do look alike.
I wonder. Could she be...
[CHIHIRO] You over there!
Pick up the pace!
[MADOKA]
So you went on a date?
[CHIHIRO]
No I didn't!
[MADOKA] Who is she?
I have to know
all about her!
[CHIHIRO]
I said it wasn't a date!
But her name is--
[CHIHIRO] I forgot
to ask her name.
[RYUJI] Hi there! I'm Ryuji
from the Uchoten Boys!
[HINO]
Just call me Hino.
[RYUJI] Is there a reason
you sound so sleepy?
[HINO] Yeah, because I
hung out with you all day!
Or do you not remember
dragging me
all over the place?
[RYUJI] All I remember
is that we were caught
because of how loud you were!
[HINO]
Will you let it go?
[RYUJI] Can we address how great
I looked in that maid outfit?
I didn't realize housekeepers
had that much leg room!
To be honest I may need a few
aprons for the concert tour.
[HINO]
Get over yourself.
[RYUJI]
Next episode:
"No Heat or Cold
Lasts Past the Equinox."
[HINO]
We'll see you then!