[CHIHIRO]
Finally! I'm finished.
--Okay, what next?
--[clatter]
[MADOKA yelling]
Oops, sorry...
It was an accident, I swear.
[CHIHIRO]
Really?
Well, there's about
to be a second accident!
[MADOKA]
You're so mean!
[CHIHIRO]
I can't believe this!
How can one guy make
such a huge mess?
[doorbell buzzes]
Hi. Can I help you?
Hello?
Look at you! What an
adorable little girl.
Um, actually...
Oh, whoops. You're
a boy, aren't you?
Hello, Miyako.
[MIYAKO] I'm sorry to barge
in like this, dear brother!
[CHIHIRO] Did she just
say "dear brother?"
[MADOKA] I see you ran
away from home again.
Indeed! It's all Father's fault!
He always ignores me.
I had no choice but to leave!
Be that as it may,
I'm not sure running away
is the best solution
to your problem.
Huh? Why not?
So, is she your little
sister or something?
Actually, no. It's complicated.
Pardon. Master Madoka?
[gasps]
[KEIICHIRO] It's concerning
the bridal fair details.
Uh-- Oh, Miss Miyako?
Help me, Keiichiro!
[KEIICHIRO grunts]
My day has been awful!
--My father couldn't care less
--[KEIICHIRO] Ow, my lungs.
about my feelings
or what I want!
He's such a brute!
[MIYAKO sobs]
What's her problem?
Again, it's complicated.
Long story.
[MIYAKO] Come on, Madoka,
you don't wanna marry me,
and I don't wanna
marry you either!
[crash]
[CHIHIRO gasps]
Chihiro, you might be getting
the wrong idea about me,
I'm afraid!
Chihiro? Oh, then you
must be Chiyo's son!
Huh?
[MIYAKO] I'm sorry; I should
have introduced myself sooner.
Hello, my name is Miyako Otohri.
You see, my family
and Miyako's family
have been friends a long time,
so it seems that
we're stuck together.
How very crass.
Well, um, my name's
Chihiro Komiya.
[MIYAKO]
It's lovely to meet you!
I was wondering...
Is there a reason why you're
wearing such a cute maid outfit?
--[CHIHIRO grunts]
--[KEIICHIRO gasps]
[CHIHIRO]
Why?
Because apparently I've lost
what's left of my dignity.
--Forever.
--[KEIICHIRO] There, there...
Yes, it's because
I hired Chihiro
to be our new
live-in housekeeper!
Oh, he's working
at such a young age!
But why?
Well, I'll tell you.
Hark, child!
Come, live in this
gorgeous mansion.
I, your sweet uncle,
shall spoil you rotten!
[MADOKA imitating CHIHIRO]
Never! I couldn't possibly
be in your debt!
Please, allow me to work
for room and board at least!
[MADOKA]
Oh, Chihiro!
[imitating CHIHIRO]
Uncle Madoka!
You're so kind-hearted!
Thank you!
Wow, What a beautiful story!
[CHIHIRO groans]
I think I'd rather be homeless.
[MIYAKO]
How impressive.
Even though he's still young,
Chihiro is so independent.
I don't know what
that's like. Must be nice.
Yes, he works hard.
Keiichiro and I know we can
rely on Chihiro for anything,
isn't that right? Right?
I agree with you.
He's very reliable.
[MIYAKO]
Hm...
That's it!
I know now what
needs to be done!
If I want my Father
to take me seriously,
then I have to show him
that I can be responsible!
I've decided I must
be more independent!
I'll be just like Chihiro!
I need your help.
I want to learn to do
everything that you can do!
Won't you teach me?
'Kay...?
Okay then! I'm ready, teacher!
What's the first
thing on the list?
You can do it, Chi!
[CHIHIRO]
Get lost, slacker!
Right. Let's start
with the basics.
Think you can sweep
off the stairs?
No problem!
[MIYAKO]
Sweep, sweep, sweep!
[CHIHIRO]
Start from the top!
[yelps]
[CHIHIRO] You have to
wring out the mop first!
[yelps] Sorry!
Don't clean the windows
with a dust rag!
[yelps] There's a difference?
--[BOTH gasp]
--[clatter]
[gasps]
[MIYAKO shrieks]
So sorry!
[CHIHIRO]
Watch out for the mop water!
[crashing, screaming]
[CHIHIRO]
Be careful!
It sure is lively today.
[crashing, screaming]
[CHIHIRO]
Are you okay, Miyako?
Yes.
I'm terrible at
cleaning. I'm so sorry.
[KEIICHIRO]
Miss Miyako.
You didn't get hurt, did you?
[MIYAKO]
Oh, Keiichiro! Of course not!
I'm sturdier than I look!
Don't you worry about me!
[KEIICHIRO]
Uh, I'm glad to hear that.
Well then, I'm done for the day,
so I'll just be leaving.
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye! Have a good night!
It was so nice seeing you again!
Okay then! What's
next on our list?
[CHIHIRO]
You sure perked up.
We should probably get started
on cooking dinner soon.
[MIYAKO]
Aye-aye, sir!
Wow.
I used to only bake,
desserts and sweets,
but then I practiced until
I could cook a complete meal.
That's awesome!
So, can I count on you
to finish up with dinner?
Sure!
[MADOKA]
What a remarkable feast!
Miyako, you made all this?
Wow, it's delicious!
Thanks, I'm so glad you like it!
By the way, where's
Chihiro run off to?
Oh, I'm not sure.
I think he said
he might eat later.
He did try a lot of food
while I was cooking.
[MADOKA]
Hm.
I should probably mention that
I was the one who taught
Miyako how to bake.
No duh!
I can help out if you want.
No thanks, it'll be
faster if I just do it.
In fact, you'd probably
make it worse.
[MADOKA]
Fine.
[MIYAKO]
Um...
Do you think I
should offer to help?
No, he told me that
class is finished
for today, so...
You can take the evening off.
[MIYAKO sighs]
All done!
Um, I guess I got
a little carried away.
[CHIHIRO yawns]
[door creaks]
[CHIHIRO]
It's cold out here.
[MIYAKO]
Oh, Chihiro.
I didn't know you were still up.
Have you been working
this whole time?
Me? Uh, yeah, but only
because I'm a real stickler
when it comes to cleaning.
It's because of me, right?
I've done nothing but
cause you trouble today.
Looks like I'll
never be independent.
At this point, I should
probably give up
and do whatever Father tells me.
[MIYAKO] A while back, our
families made an agreement.
And they decided that,
when I turned 16,
Madoka and I would get married.
Don't get me wrong,
he's really nice and all,
but I want--
Well, I tried to tell my
family I wanted to choose
who I would marry,
but they called me selfish.
[CHIHIRO]
You aren't being selfish!
What?
Why would anybody force
you to marry that guy?
What cruel and
unusual punishment!
[MIYAKO] You are truly
wise beyond your years!
[MADOKA sneezes]
And, more importantly,
I get the feeling that
maybe you like Keiichiro
more than my uncle.
What? Why would you think that?
[CHIHIRO]
Just a hunch.
[MIYAKO]
The secret's out!
I guess I can't hide
my feelings anymore!
Were you trying to hide them?
You fooled me.
Come on, be honest.
Did you do all this house work
stuff to impress Keiichiro?
Yes, I wanted to, but,
well, you saw me today.
I was terrible. Really terrible.
All I did was make
a mess of everything.
I'll never impress him.
Like I said, I should give up
and do whatever Father
tells me, like always.
[CHIHIRO] "You should
never betray yourself.
Sometimes in life,
compromise is necessary,
but don't do anything that
goes against your heart."
So Mom said.
There's only one way to fail--
and that's giving up
before you've tried.
Except I did fail.
I couldn't do anything right.
No, not true--you made
an amazing dinner.
It tasted great!
If I can teach you how to clean
as well as you cook,
then you'll be golden.
That means a lot.
You know what?
From here on out,
I'm going to start putting
more faith in myself.
[MADOKA sneezes]
Hello, sir.
Yes, right. I think
things should be fine now.
Okay then, why don't you stop by
and pick her up tomorrow.
[MADOKA]
Perfect, now do a turn!
[giggles]
[MADOKA]
Oh, you're too cute for words!
Wear this uniform while you're
training with Chi, okay?
[MIYAKO]
'Kay!
And I promise to
keep working hard!
It's surprising how
fast he manages
--to make stuff like that.
--[doorbell buzzes]
I'll get it this time.
[doorbell buzzes]
[MADOKA] By the way,
guess what else I made?
Mini Miyako and
Keiichiro cookies!
Those are too adorable!
I know!
Wait a sec--
Does that mean you
wrecked my kitchen again?
[MADOKA] "Wrecked" is such
a destructive word.
There's only a little
flour here and there.
I just cleaned in there!
I can't leave you
alone for five minutes!
[MADOKA whimpers]
Stop yelling at me!
[MIYAKO] Don't be mad!
I'll help clean it up!
[MIYAKO'S FATHER] I'm not
sure what to do with Miyako.
I hope she hasn't
caused you any trouble.
[MADOKA]
Chi, I said stop it!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Miyako, It's time--
[BOTH gasp]
Time to do what?
Huh?
Huh? Madoka!
What is the meaning of this?
Explain yourself!
Well, I guess the
cat's out of the bag.
I like maids.
[MIYAKO'S FATHER] We're leaving
this instant, young lady!
[MIYAKO] Uh! Wait,
what's your rush? Father?
[MIYAKO'S FATHER]
Madoka, I believed you were
a high-caliber man.
Clearly that was a mistake.
I'm calling off the engagement!
It's a good thing you found out
sooner rather than later.
[MIYAKO'S FATHER]
I forbid you from ever seeing
that miscreant again!
Do you understand me, Miyako?
Just because he likes cosplay
doesn't mean he's
a miscreant, Father!
I'm sorry, everyone!
Sorry, Keiichiro!
[KEIICHIRO, CHIHIRO]
Uh...
Yeah, you are crass.
That's rude; I was only
trying to be heroic.
[CHIHIRO] You could've just
refused like an adult, idiot!
[MADOKA] No name-calling!
I worked hard!
Hey! Look who it is.
Komiya! Up here!
Hey!
[HINO] I haven't seen you
at school in a while.
Everything okay?
Someone told me that you
moved in with your uncle.
Is it true?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, I really
meant to tell you guys.
But I'll be coming
back to school
after the Golden Week holiday.
Yeah?
That's cool.
Hey, tell us all
about your new place!
And what's your
uncle like? Is he nice?
He's kinda weird, but I
suppose he's nice enough.
Except for the mai--
[CHIHIRO] Wait, I can't
tell them about that!
They'll just make fun of me!
"May?" May what?
Uh--
May-be I'm over thinking it!
In fact, everything
is fine! Totally normal!
And boring! Yep!
Well... Okay.
Hey, Komiya, what's wrong?
You're acting kinda strange.
[yelps] Me?
No, the other Komiya.
Of course I mean you!
What? No, I'm cool! Ha.
Look, if you need
help or whatever--
Seriously guys, I'm just
fine! Everything's good!
Ah, gee, it's gettin' late!
I should probably be going now!
[HINO]
Hey, what's the rush?
[CHIHIRO sighs] Man, I feel
bad for ditching them,
but what else could I do?
This isn't something
that's easy to explain.
Nope.
[door clicks]
Wow... This place is huge!
You gotta be kidding.
He lives here?
It's like a modern day
Orphan Annie story.
Well, he's okay.
So let's go, I guess.
[door clicks]
[TAKEI, HINO, AMAHARA]
Huh?
Komiya?!
[shrieks]
[HINO] Man, I knew something
strange was going on.
[CHIHIRO] Can we pretend
this didn't happen?
[HINO, TAKEI, AMAHARA]
No way.
At the park, you told us
everything was just fine.
Come on, fess up. Is that true?
Yes, absolutely!
Then, what's up with
the whole maid outfit?
Are they forcing you
to work for them?
No, they're not! It's
nothing like that at all.
You'd hate to be indebted
to the Takitori family,
so I'd like to offer
you an opportunity.
In the end, I only
have myself to blame
for all this.
So cosplay's your thing, huh?
--[CHIHIRO yelps]
--Talk about surprising.
[TAKEI, AMAHARA]
Yep.
[CHIHIRO]
I am not into cosplay!
This happens to be
my work uniform!
[TAKEI, AMAHARA]
Your work uniform?
[HINO] Well, I guess it's cool,
as long as you're okay.
And the clothes aren't
half bad, either.
You actually pull it off.
Thanks a lot, but you guys
don't have to lie to me, 'kay?
[HINO]
We're not.
Think we'd make fun
of you for working?
That would make us
pretty crappy friends.
In the future, just be
honest with us, okay?
We're supposed to
stick together and stuff.
[MADOKA]
So true!
It warms my heart to see that
you have such caring friends!
[HINO, TAKEI, AMAHARA yelp]
By the way, I'm Chihiro's uncle.
Nice to meet--
[CHIHIRO] How many times
have I said to knock?
Dumb idiot!
[HINO]
See ya!
[TAKEI]
Yeah, see ya at school!
[AMAHARA]
Bye, Komiya!
[laughs]
They seem like a good group.
Yeah. I'd like to invite them
back over again sometime.
Of course!
When you do, I'll be sure
to bake them some cookies!
[CHIHIRO]
You stay out of my kitchen!
All right, teacher!
I'm finished!
[CHIHIRO]
Food's done. Cleanup's done.
Good. A-plus work!
[laughs] This is
the best day ever!
Yes, yes, wonderful work!
I was wondering...
Can we eat? I'm starving.
Next we need to work on
finishing it a little faster.
Yes, sir!
[MADOKA] So, you two have a
cooking class every Sunday?
I'm impressed by how
hard Miyako's working.
Yep!
Oh, yeah, I was wondering if
Keiichiro is off on Sundays?
[MADOKA]
Hm?
[CHIHIRO] Do you think he
would come over for dinner?
My only wish in this
world is to cook dinner
for Keiichiro one evening!
That'd be a dream come true!
Why, you're like
Miyako's fairy god-parent.
Well, I'm sure Keiichiro
would come over
if we asked him, but your
chances would be better
if pudding was on the menu.
Oh, so he prefers pudding?
Uh-- For real?
Yep! It's definitely
his favorite!
Isn't that adorable?
Yeah, sure. Adorable.
Anyway, we can't exactly
make pudding the main dish,
so I'll just put it
down for desert.
Let's see, he's also
a big fan of sushi.
But I'm not sure if Miyako
knows how to make it. Hm.
[CHIHIRO] Hold up.
Now that I think about it...
I don't know what
kind of food he likes.
Even though I've cooked
for him every day!
[CHIHIRO]
Okay.
[MADOKA] Well, we're feeding
a small army today.
Yeah, I accidentally
made too much.
You don't have to
eat it all, though.
[MADOKA]
Sounds like a challenge!
[CHIHIRO]
Heh! He totally bought it!
This is a surefire way
to find out what he likes.
[MADOKA]
I am so stuffed!
[CHIHIRO]
Uh-huh...
[MADOKA]
Hm.
You're emitting a scary aura.
You're seeing things!
Anyway, which food
did you like the best?
Everything!
Nobody likes everything!
You've gotta have
some sort of preference!
[MADOKA]
What are my favorite foods?
Why are you so curious?
Well, I'm the one who
cooks for you after all,
I should know.
That seems like
a valid enough point.
I like to eat
whatever my dear nephew
wants to make for me, of course!
What kind of answer is that?
[laughs nervously]
If you won't tell me
your preferences,
then I'll just be forced
to make you nothing at all!
I really don't understand
your logic though.
Come on, I'm serious!
There must be
something you want!
Tell me and I'll
make it for you.
[MADOKA]
Hm.
Maybe a bento?
You're going back
to school tomorrow,
so you can just make mine
when you make yours.
A bento lunch, okay.
[CHIHIRO sighs]
Wait, I still don't know
what food he likes!
[groans] Guess I'll
just pick something.
I suppose I could use
some of the
leftovers from dinner.
Oh, and we already have
the stuff for meatloaf,
so I could make meatballs--
or should I make fish?
If he were in kindergarten,
I could make those
octopus-shaped hotdogs.
[sighs] Maybe not.
[CHIHIRO]
Rolled omelets.
[CHIHIRO] I've never made them,
but Mom was great at it.
[CHIYO]
What do you think?
Looks pretty awesome, huh?
[CHIHIRO]
Whoa!
How did you get so good
at making rolled omelets?
Practice makes perfect, dear!
Oh, yeah?
Could you practice
making other food then?
How rude!
If you chase two rabbits,
you won't catch either, Chihiro!
Sounds like an excuse.
Do you think you could
teach me to cook them maybe?
[CHIYO]
No way!
Then I won't have anything
else to do around here!
I'm the official omelet
maker, so back off, buddy!
[CHIHIRO]
You gave yourself a title?
Anyway, why decide to focus
on omelets of all things?
I'll tell you why.
[inaudible]
[grunts]
[CHIHIRO growls]
You are such a creeper!
[MADOKA groans]
[CHIHIRO] In the end,
I never learned how to do it.
I really wish I had tried
harder to get Mom to teach me.
It's too late now,
I'll just have to do my best.
Today I will become
the official omelet maker
in your place.
[MADOKA]
Good morning.
[CHIHIRO]
Morning.
[MADOKA]
Hm?
Is this my bento?
[CHIHIRO]
Yeah.
Yay! You're the best!
[CHIHIRO]
Sorry.
[MADOKA]
Eh? About what?
I messed up today's lunch.
Oh?
[CHIHIRO]
Hey, don't open it now!
What are you doing?
[CHIHIRO]
I burned them.
I really wanted to
make them pretty
like mom's rolled omelets.
But I haven't practiced
enough, so they look nasty.
[MADOKA munching]
This is delicious, Chi.
[CHIHIRO]
That's for lunch!
Doesn't it taste burnt?
[MADOKA] It reminds me;
when we were kids
we'd have picnics in the garden.
Huh?
And sis would always volunteer
to make the bento for all of us.
But her lunches mostly consisted
of weirdly-shaped rice balls
and burnt rolled omelets.
[KEIICHIRO]
Um, what is this?
[MADOKA]
Is it supposed to be burned?
Excuse me?
[MADOKA]
Never mind the rice balls--
those rolled omelets
were a disaster.
She had used way too much sugar.
The flavor was all wrong,
[MADOKA]
But to tell you the truth...
In spite of all that,
I actually liked her cooking.
[gasps]
[CHIHIRO] Anyway, why decide
to focus on omelets
of all things?
[CHIYO]
I'll tell you why.
Because I was tired
of having my failures
always eaten as if
they were delicious.
Chiyo, you must have learned
to make them quite nicely.
[CHIHIRO]
I'll practice, too.
Huh?
[CHIHIRO] I won't give up
until they look like Mom's!
Wait and see!
They're gonna be better
than those failures
I made this morning!
You got that?
[MADOKA]
Sure.
Like it or not, you're going
to be my taste tester
for them, Madoka!
Uh--
[MADOKA]
Count me in.
[KEIICHIRO]
Moving on.
The next item on our list
I'd like to discuss is...
---Are you listening?
--[MADOKA] ...to... Bento...
--Master Madoka?
--Earth to Madoka!
--[MADOKA] ...to... Bento...
Is it lunchtime already?
Time for my bento, right?
If that bento box
will get you to focus,
then sure, by all
means, bon appétit.
[MADOKA]
Yay! Time to eat!
By the way, if you
don't have plans,
then you should come eat
dinner with us on Sunday.
And there's going to be pudding!
[KEIICHIRO]
Pudding?
[CHIHIRO] Anyway. These are
all my failed attempts.
You guys go ahead and
help yourselves, okay?
[HINO]
You told us to skip breakfast
for some burnt omelets?
[laughs]
[HINO] Hey, Komiya, I heard
the girls in our class
talking about you.
Know what they said?
[CHIHIRO]
Uh, no?
[HINO] They all think that you'd
make a really great boy bride!
[CHIHIRO]
What? Boy bride?
[HINO]
Right?
Don't they know boys are
supposed to be the groom?
Anyway, I think I found
the perfect partner for you!
[CHIHIRO]
Huh, who?
[HINO] I'll give you a
little hint. Next time in
"Feed a Dog for Three Days
and He Will Remember
It for Three Years,"
she may or may not make
a special appearance!
[CHIHIRO]
Then why mention it at all?
[HINO]
Ready to know who it is?
It's my little
sister, Hanako Hino!
[CHIHIRO]
Whoa, spoiler alert!
[HINO]
Until next time!