[MADOKA]
Hm.
Plain bun. Plum?
Plain Bun without plum--
Bun, bun, bun plum?
But I didn't make any buns.
[HINO]
Is that like a tongue twister?
[CHIHIRO]
I guess.
He always acts strange
around deadlines.
[HINO] Oh, okay. So who's
the client this time?
Dunno, but I think
it must be for a guy
or something, 'cause there are
a lot fewer frills than usual.
He sure likes frills.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[HINO, CHIHIRO]
Whoa, stranger danger!
[RYUJI] Hey, kids, come on!
Help a guy out!
Ow! Stop that!
Look, I'm desperate!
I lost my wallet and my phone,
and I'm on the
brink of starvation!
I just need directions!
Directions?
Yeah, I'm looking for
a man named Takatori.
What? Hold on.
Do you mean Madoka Takatori?
Huh?
I actually kinda live with him.
[yells]
No way! What luck?
You're my hero!
Thank you so much!
Can you please put me down?
Who the heck are you?
[RYUJI]
Oh, sorry about that!
You're Ryuji from the
Uchoten Boys, am I right?
What? Is it really that obvious?
I thought my
disguise was perfect.
You're who?
See? And they're constantly
on TV and stuff, too.
Oh, I don't really
watch much television.
[HINO] Hayato is the lead
singer, and then there's Ibuki.
And he's...
Ryuji.
That's me!
[RYUJI]
Cool! I have this game, too!
I just beat the boss
on the third level!
[HINO]
Yeah? Was it hard?
[KEIICHIRO]
I'm confused, I knew
that Master Madoka
was designing the band's
new stage costumes,
but why would Ryuji
need to come here?
[MADOKA]
Yeah, it's unusual for a client
to just show up at my house.
[CHIHIRO] I thought you knew
him personally or something!
[MADOKA]
I only know him through work.
Go see what he wants, Chi.
What, why me?
I don't like
talking to strangers.
[CHIHIRO]
Huh.
Whoa! That looks amazing!
It's for me?
Yeah. Didn't you say
you were starvin--
[RYUJI]
Thank you!
You're a saint, a life saver,
and my new best friend!
Ah!
But I'm his best friend.
So, what's up with that outfit?
Are you like a cosplayer?
No, I am not!
[RYUJI]
Are you sure?
Yes. Look, this happens
to be my work uniform.
Madoka is the one who made it.
Oh! No kidding,
he really made that?
How cool!
Madoka's one of the
most popular designers
in the country,
y'know, but he's famous
for not taking on a lot
of jobs. It's rare.
Honestly though.
I totally thought he'd
be some stuffy old guy.
I wasn't thrilled about
meeting him. Until...
[gasps] He turned out
to be so awesome!
He's all sophisticated
and stuff!
He's, like, the
coolest adult ever!
Uh, Madoka? An adult?
Wait, that reminds me!
I didn't come here for food!
Delicious!
Listen. I really gotta
speak to Madoka!
Yeah, about what?
[RYUJI] Well, I need to tell
him that I hate... my shorts.
[CHIHIRO]
Uh...
That's right!
All the costumes we wear
during our performances
make me look like a little kid!
I came to ask him to
change things up a bit!
No more shorts!
I'm going on a bare leg strike!
You don't understand my pain!
Even when I land a great pose,
the girls squeal "so cute!"
I just wanna be cool
like the other guys!
You're right. I don't
understand your pain.
[MADOKA]
I can't. Sorry.
[gasps] No way.
Why can't you change it?
[MADOKA] Because they already
approved the design.
The most I can do is play around
with the smaller details,
but I can't make
any major changes.
That's the way it is.
I won't go home
until you fix it!
I'm afraid there's
nothing I can do.
Look, I don't care!
I refuse to wear
any more stupid shorts!
I'll never perform in that!
--[RYUJI yelping]
--[crashing]
He hasn't even tried it on yet.
[gasps]
[RYUJI whimpers]
I thought he was the kind of guy
who would listen to me.
Why on earth would you
think something like that?
I'm short, and just
because of that,
people always treat me
like a little boy.
Whenever I meet someone new,
they pat me on the head!
How insulting is that? I'm 16.
I'm practically a man already!
[CHIHIRO]
Throwing a tantrum probably
doesn't help your image.
[RYUJI] But not Madoka--
he treated me like an adult.
He's different, and maybe that's
why I thought he could help.
He gets me.
[HINO] Yeah, I hate to
interrupt this daydream, but...
I think the only thing Madoka
gets is a love for frills.
Exhibit A.
[yelps] He tricked me!
Oh, yeah, and how
exactly did he trick you?
You're the one jumping
to conclusions here!
A boy in a maid outfit
wouldn't understand!
Why do you actually wear
those stupid clothes anyway?
You look like a girl!
How dare you!
These clothes happen
to be very practical!
Not only are they
easy to work in,
they're also machine washable!
Whatever!
There's no way
you're not embarrassed
by that ridiculous outfit!
Bet you wouldn't
even wear it outside!
I'm not embarrassed!
Just watch!
I'm going to the store!
You know, for a guy
claiming to be an adult,
you act super childish.
You don't like
being made fun of,
but that's exactly
what you just did.
He was really embarrassed
the first time
we saw him in those clothes.
[HINO]
Well, I'm outta here.
[door clicks]
[RYUJI] A boy in a maid
outfit wouldn't understand!
You look like a girl!
He's right.
I can't believe I really said
the things I would hate to hear.
[RYUJI]
I need to apologize to him.
[CHIHIRO]
Hey, I'm back!
Um, I'm sorry for what I said!
Look, I got some awesome deals!
[RYUJI]
Huh?
Yeah, it was like this:
Whoa, cuteness overload
on aisle four!
Wow, that outfit makes the cut!
This one's on the house, okay?
Holy carp, you're adorable,
I'll give ya a free fish!
Everyone kept saying I was cute
and giving me free stuff!
Maybe I should shop
in my uniform more often.
[RYUJI]
He's happy?
♪ Don't be afraid,
little shonen maid! ♪
[RYUJI]
What the heck?
I said such horrible
things, and yet,
he didn't let any of that stop
him from doing what he wanted.
He's the cool one.
What exactly is going on here?
Uh?
[KEIICHIRO] It's unusual
to see Chihiro out shopping
while still in his uniform.
Typically, he changes first.
Well?
Uh...
Wait, Chihiro is
your nephew? No way.
[MADOKA]
Yes.
I took him in when
his mother passed away.
But he's very independent, so
instead of living here for free,
he became my head housekeeper.
[CHIHIRO]
The kitchen is my domain!
Okay...
Who did you think he was?
Like, your secret love child?
Really?
There's no reason I'd
ever keep him a secret,
he's such a good kid,
I wouldn't be ashamed
to bring him anywhere.
[RYUJI]
Freaky.
Like he's a doting
father or something.
[MADOKA] Here, would you
mind trying this on for me?
Sure, okay!
[RYUJI]
More shorts...
[MADOKA]
I think it suits you.
Huh?
The shorts, I mean.
[RYUJI]
Is it because I look like a kid?
[MADOKA]
Because you have nice legs.
Huh?
No, I'm serious.
They're very lean and muscular.
And they don't make you
look childish at all.
I won't budge on the design.
It's my job to
make you look good.
I'm a professional.
And you are, too.
You have to show people
what they want to see.
That's your job.
[FANGIRL 6A]
You're so cute, Ryuji!
Tell me. Does your
job embarrass you?
You're leaving? But I
just started on dinner.
Yeah, sorry, but I left
without saying anything,
so everyone's probably worried.
It's okay, but how are
you gonna get home?
Didn't you like, lose
your wallet and phone?
[RYUJI] Oh my gosh! That's
right! What am I gonna do?
[doorbell buzzes]
Hi, can I help you
with something?
Huh?
There you are.
Oh. Are you also
from the Uchoten Boys?
I'm Hayato.
I hope Ryuji hasn't
caused you any trouble.
But how'd you even
know where to find me?
[HAYATO]
Heh. Seriously?
We found Takatori's
business card right next
to the note you
left at the agency.
[RYUJI yelps]
So obvious!
Look, Ibuki is making up
an excuse for you,
but we should
probably head back.
Do you think Ibuki's mad at me?
[HAYATO]
Let's see...
Well, I don't always love
acting like a prince, you know,
but sometimes you
have to suck it up.
Is what he said.
[yelps] He's going to kill me!
[HAYATO]
Ah...
I'm very sorry, but I appreciate
you taking care
of him. Thank you!
[RYUJI whimpering]
He's really shiny.
What the--? We're
from the same band.
I could be super shiny
if I wanted to be!
[HAYATO]
Come on, let's go.
[RYUJI]
Okay, fine.
Hey, listen. Let's
hang out again sometime.
Yeah, sure, whatever.
Okay. And I am gonna
wear Madoka's costume.
So be sure to watch us on TV!
Sure, I will.
[MIYAKO]
Wow!
Ryuji from the
Uchoten Boys was here?
That's so neat! I see
them all the time on TV!
They're doing a live
TV special soon,
and Ryuji asked me to watch.
I think it's the
Tuesday after next.
The Tuesday after next?
It falls on the same
day as his birthday!
Uh, okay?
So, we should do
something special!
I've got the perfect idea.
We could have a big
birthday bash at the house!
That's it!
If you want, you could
come over one day next week
and we could plan the
surprise party together!
So this birthday party.
Who's it for?
Huh?
[KEIICHIRO]
Ah, yes.
I suppose it is just
right around the corner.
Master Madoka's
birthday, I mean.
Hold on, are you saying
you already knew about it?
Yes, of course I did.
Well, how come no one told me?
Master Madoka doesn't
typically announce
when his birthday is coming up.
Oh, really?
[CHIHIRO] So how does
he usually celebrate?
[KEIICHIRO] Honestly, we don't
really do much for it.
We just give him presents.
Oh.
He's never shown any interest
in having a party before.
Okay.
[KEIICHIRO]
But I think if you were planning
something special, he'd love it.
I'm just throwing
that out there.
Oh, yeah? That's good to know.
Any idea what kind of
present I should get him?
[KEIICHIRO] I imagine
he would love anything.
You could give him an empty
tissue box and he'd be happy.
Rectangles are the best!
Wow, thank you!
[CHIHIRO sighs]
Madoka already has a ton
of clothes and stuff.
Maybe I could get him
a watch or a necktie?
No that's dumb--
I doubt he'd use them.
Huh?
A vacuum?
[CHIHIRO] Ah! No way! Light
weight and energy efficient?
Wait, this is something
I want! Focus, Chihiro!
[CHIHIRO sighs]
I am seriously
drawing a blank here.
[CHIHIRO] This is where
Miyako actually lives?
[barks]
Hello there! Sorry if
I kept you waiting!
Hi! It's no problem!
[ANTARO barks]
Hey, Antaro, you're
looking cuter than ever!
Well then, if you'll
just follow me, please.
[ANTARO barking]
You're popular here.
[MIYAKO]
Hm?
[CHIHIRO] Oh. Is this
where you live, Miyako?
This is more my speed.
[MIYAKO] The main building
has a much larger kitchen,
but this is my personal one
to use whenever I like.
Father had it built for me as
a birthday present last year!
It's nice.
[CHIHIRO] Wow, he gave
her an entire house?
Anyway, let's go
ahead and get started.
[CHIHIRO]
Um, yeah!
[ANTARO panting]
[CHIHIRO]
Hm. I think this will be enough.
And we could make
chirashi sushi.
[MIYAKO]
Oh, look!
Here's a recipe
for roast chicken!
But it might be
difficult to make it.
Our house has a huge oven.
If we work together,
I think we could do it!
Yay!
[CHIHIRO]
Hm?
[MIYAKO] I'm so glad you're
here to help, Chihiro.
Because there's no way
I could have made
this much food all on my own.
With you here, we can actually
have a proper party this year!
[CHIHIRO]
What do you mean?
[MIYAKO] Madoka has always
accepted the gifts I gave him.
But not once have we ever
thrown him a party.
Actually...
What's up?
So, uh, what kind of present
do you usually give him?
Every year, I always bake him
a homemade cake from scratch!
When I was little,
Madoka taught me
how to bake one.
So it became our tradition
for me to make him one
for his birthday every year.
[CHIHIRO]
That's sweet.
[MIYAKO] This year,
I'm going to try my hand
at baking one of those
multi-tiered cakes!
[MIYAKO]
What about you?
Have you decided on a gift yet?
[CHIHIRO]
Not exactly.
To be honest, I don't really
know what to get him.
[MIYAKO]
He's a simple man.
I think he would
probably be happy
to get any gift from you at all.
[CHIHIRO]
Yeah, Keiichiro said that, too.
Still, he's given me so much.
A place to live and my own room.
I just really wanna
return the favor.
Then maybe you
could just tell him
how you're feeling.
I think that would be
the best present of all.
Really?
[barks]
Looks like Antaro wants
us to take a break.
[MIYAKO]
I'll make us some tea.
in the meantime, do you
think could play outside
with Antaro for a little bit?
There's a gazebo in the back
garden. You can go there.
[CHIHIRO]
Okay then!
[MIYAKO]
Hey, Chihiro?
I'm sure whatever
present you end up
getting him will be
amazing. You'll be fine.
Yeah.
[ANTARO barking]
[CHIHIRO groans] Why did I tell
her all that embarrassing stuff?
Worst of all, I still don't know
what kind of present to buy!
[ANTARO barking]
[KAZUSA yelps]
[KAZUSA]
Shoo! Shoo!
Huh?
[KAZUSA yelping]
Get out of here,
you devilish monster!
Go on! Get!
[CHIHIRO]
This feels vaguely familiar.
Oh! You there, please
save me, I beg of you!
[KAZUSA] I didn't realize you
were a friend of Miyako's.
Yes, ma'am.
For a minute, I thought you were
one of the maids.
Please forgive me.
[CHIHIRO]
Who is this woman?
Could she be Miyako's mother?
I came out here because
I wanted to get a few roses,
but Kayako went back in
to get some scissors
and hasn't returned yet.
Ah, Kayako is actually
the lady of this house.
[CHIHIRO] Not her mom.
Maybe she's just a visitor?
[CHIHIRO] So, uh, are roses
in bloom right now?
[KAZUSA]
Indeed, they are.
[CHIHIRO] Wow. But these
aren't roses, are they?
They're not.
They're awayuki flowers.
Their name means
"a light snowfall."
I find their simplicity
to be very charming.
[CHIHIRO]
That's it!
I could totally
give him flowers!
[CHIYO] Oh, are these
for me? Thank you!
[MADOKA] Oh, are these
Never mind.
Knowing him, he'd probably
just let them die.
[KAZUSA] So, you're looking
for a birthday present?
Ooh, is it for your girlfriend?
[CHIHIRO] Uh, no, ma'am,
it's for an annoying old man.
[KAZUSA]
Oh, my.
I want to find him a good gift,
but I'm really struggling.
I'm so sorry.
This is my problem.
I really shouldn't
be bothering you.
Tell me, dear,
what's your name?
[CHIHIRO]
Oh, I'm Chihiro Komiya.
Well then, here's my advice.
Does the present necessarily
have to be a physical object?
[CHIHIRO]
Huh?
[KAZUSA] We get too wrapped
up in the physical things,
but the point of a birthday
is to celebrate someone's birth.
[CHIHIRO]
Um, yeah, I guess that's true.
If you're this worried about it,
you must truly care
for him a lot.
So try to remember
what he likes,
and what sorts of
things make him happy.
I'm sure you'll find you
already know what he wants.
The answer is there,
you just haven't
looked hard enough yet.
[CHIHIRO]
Do I know what makes him happy?
Think hard.
--[ANTARO barks]
--[KAZUSA] Oh!
Goodness, that nearly
scared me to death!
Ah, sorry about that!
I swear. If Miyako
had to have a pet,
I wish she had gotten
a cat instead.
A cat?
[gasps]
I know!
Thank you, ma'am!
Ooh!
[MIYAKO]
Hello, Meow-doka!
Oh, and Happy Birthday!
Birthday? You did all this
just for me, really?
Ah!
[KEIICHIRO] We wanted to
throw you a little party.
[MADOKA]
Wow. It's amazing. I mean it.
Listen, since it's
your birthday,
I won't get mad at you today.
No matter what you do.
That's my gift. Have at it.
Thanks a lot, Chi!
Oh, Chihiro, turn on the TV.
Yeah!
[FEMALE MC 6A] And we are
live with the Uchoten Boys!
Hello there, Madoka!
I hope your birthday
really rocks!
Thank you for making
our costumes, they're amazing!
[laughs]
This song is just for you!
When I told them
about the party,
they wanted in on the fun!
And now performing live,
give it up for the Uchoten Boys!
[UCHOTEN BOYS]
♪ I'm not gonna say, ♪
♪ I should even have to say ♪
♪ Thank you, 'cause ev'ry
time you already know, ♪
♪ So I am not gonna
say it, no way! ♪
[gasps]
[UCHOTEN BOYS] ♪ I thought
you knew me so well, ♪
♪ our hearts are
so connected, girl, ♪
♪ I know you can tell ♪
♪ Wha-at's on my mind ♪
♪ when I look in your eyes! ♪
Okay, who's ready for cake?
[MADOKA]
Aw!
Isn't it lovely?
I made a really
big one this year!
[MADOKA]
It's purr-fect!
[CHIHIRO]
Can we even eat all that?
[UCHOTEN BOYS]
♪ ...you already know, ♪
♪ So I am not gonna
say it, no way! ♪
♪ Whoa-oh, uh-oh' ♪
[sighs] I never knew
birthday parties
were so a-meow-zing!
Maybe I'll start celebrating
my birthday on a daily basis!
[KEIICHIRO] Then you'd grow
old at an alarming rate.
Talk about worth it!
And look! Chi doesn't get mad
at me either, I'm so happy!
[CHIHIRO]
Don't get angry.
Just keep it together
a little longer.
Only three more hours.
Aw! Wait!
Are you saving it
all up for tomorrow?
Does that mean you're like
a time bomb of meanness?
Aw! I knew all this
was too good to be true!
[CHIHIRO] Oh, well.
I'm glad he had fun today.
And it was all thanks to her.
[CHIHIRO]
But who was she, anyway?
[RYUJI] What's up? I'm Ryuji
from the Uchoten Boys!
[HAYATO]
I'm Hayato.
[IBUKI]
And I'm Ibuki!
[RYUJI]
What did you think of our music?
Pretty awesome stuff, huh?
Thank you, thank you,
hold your applause!
[HAYATO]
What's that?
You think Ryuji has cute legs?
Hey, they like your legs!
[RYUJI]
Thanks I guess?
[IBUKI] Well, we had
to give you something.
Every dog has his
day, am I right?
[RYUJI]
Absolutely--
W-Wait a second,
what does that mean?
[HAYATO]
Never mind that.
Next time: "Learning Does
Not Happen in a Day."
[IBUKI]
The Uchoten Boys really hope
to see you all again next week!
[RYUJI]
We're counting on you!