[MADOKA]
Hmm. Pink or blue.
I can't decide.
Pink or blue?
Chi, I wonder,
which do you think:
is pink better than blue?
Yellow.
[MADOKA]
Interesting...
Hmm. Perhaps saffron.
Saffron: that's crazy.
So do I even wanna know?
Oh, he's just
in creative mode.
I really wouldn't worry
about it too much.
Instead, worry about this
problem you missed.
We can't all be
math whizzes.
What kind of stuff is
he even working on anyway?
More idol outfits?
[CHIHIRO] Nope. This time
it's wedding dresses.
[MADOKA]
Yellow...?
[CHIHIRO]
Good morning, Keiichiro!
Well, good morning to you!
[CHIHIRO] Is it just me,
or does Madoka
seem busier than usual?
[KEIICHIRO] Spring is always
a hectic time for him.
But this year has been a bit
more problematic than normal.
[BRIDE 12A]
I got fat.
[BRIDE 12B]
I lost ten pounds!
[BRIDE 12C] We moved
the ceremony to next week!
[BRIDE 12D] My dress has
to look better than hers!
And you just can't say no
to a woman in bridezilla mode.
Sounds scary.
Oh! Hello.
Want something to eat?
Sure thing. I've decided
on pink after all.
Okay?
[CHIHIRO] On second thought,
maybe I'll make him
a bento so he can
eat in his workroom.
He really is impossible.
Sorry for the trouble.
Oh please,
I'm used to it by now!
--All right.
--[MADOKA] Here, Chi.
It was great, thanks!
[CHIHIRO]
You can leave it there.
Are you going to
eat dinner with me?
[MADOKA] Mmm.
I just finished eating,
so probably not. Sorry.
It's fine, I'll make you
a snack for later
in case you get hungry.
[MADOKA]
Oh! Thank you!
Well, it looks
like he ate everything.
That's good, I guess.
[whispers]
You can do it!
[door squeaks, clicks]
[CHIYO]
Hello there!
[CHIHIRO] Oh, hi!
Where'd you come from?
[giggles]
Your hair is sticking up!
[CHIHIRO]
Whoa. Who is this girl?
She seems familiar somehow.
[screams]
[screams, gasps]
[alarm clock rings]
[CHIHIRO groans]
[CHIHIRO]
Madoka, Madoka!
Oh. Morning.
[CHIHIRO] Wouldn't your bed
be more comfortable?
Yes. Suppose it would,
but then I'd
probably fall asleep.
[CHIHIRO]
That's the point!
What time is it?
You feel like you might
be running a fever.
You think so?
That's funny,
I don't feel sick.
But still.
Don't worry,
I'm seriously fine!
Oh and thank you
for making that bento!
'Kay, back to work!
[CHIHIRO] He barely
touched his food.
[indistictive chatter]
[CHIHIRO] I wonder if these
cooling sheets actually work.
Maybe I should
buy some medicine, too.
I don't think he said anything
about his head hurting, though.
Then maybe
just an energy drink?
I wonder which one's best.
Why hello, Chihiro!
Need some help?
[gasps]
[CHIHIRO] Madoka doesn't
really seem to have much
of an appetite today, but he
needs to eat something.
Don't people eat soup
when they're sick?
I've never had to take care
of anyone before now.
I'm kind of in the dark
on this one.
[meows]
[KAZUSA]
Behold!
[CHIHIRO]
Uuuh...
[KAZUSA] Ooh, so fluffy!
Fluffy, fluffy!
[WHITE CAT 5A shrieks]
[KAZUSA]
Oh.
--[CHIHIRO] Hello.
--[KAZUSA shrieks]
Oh. Good afternoon.
How have you been?
Fine. How's stuff with you?
[sighs] How is it you
always manage to catch me
in an awkward moment?
Aww. It's not fair.
I'm losing all my cool points.
[laughs]
That white cat is always
escaping from you, isn't it?
Indeed. It's a very
skittish creature.
Anyway, are you out
running errands today?
Yes ma'am. I was buying
some medicine for Madoka.
I've known
them a long time,
and their relationship has
always been turbulent.
[gasps]
I see. I suppose
he hasn't changed much
these past years.
I'd hoped that by now
he might finally
have his act together.
When he was little,
every time the seasons changed
he would manage to get sick.
I'd hate for him to cause
too much trouble for you.
[CHIHIRO]
Trouble?
[CHIYO]
I'm seriously fine!
[KAZUSA]
Hm?
[CHIHIRO] He's not! Madoka has
been super busy with work,
so I decided to help him out.
It's not like he's laid up
in bed or anything.
[KAZUSA]
Well, that's good to hear.
[KAZUSA] The skies look
like they could open up
at any moment.
You'd better hurry home
before the rain hits.
Yes, ma'am.
Uh, wait!
Yes, what is it?
[CHIHIRO]
Oh, um...
Take care.
You as well. Bye, Chihiro.
[CHIHIRO] I still have
so many questions.
I wanted to ask why she
and Madoka don't get along.
And I wanted to ask how
she really feels about Mom.
And I wanted to ask
"What should I call you?"
[KEIICHIRO]
Oh welcome back, Chihiro!
[CHIHIRO] Whoa, do you need
some help with that box?
No. I think
I've got it, thanks.
[CHIHIRO] It's supposed to rain,
so I'll grab you an umbrella!
[CHIHIRO]
Here.
Much appreciated!
Sorry to be in such a rush.
[car door thuds]
[engine hums]
Drive safe!
I guess everyone
is working overtime.
[CHIYO giggles]
[CHIHIRO]
Huh?
Hmmm.
[CHIYO laughs]
[knock, knock]
Madoka, here.
Hey Chi, come on in.
A letter?
Yes. One of my most
recent clients sent it,
along with some pictures.
They're of her wedding ceremony.
Well that's cool!
She looks so pretty!
[MADOKA chuckles]
Tell me, have you ever
been to a wedding before?
Me? No, I haven't.
Well, they're even more
gorgeous than that picture.
It's like...
there's this happy aura
surrounding everyone
in attendance.
[CHIHIRO]
Yeah?
It is beautiful
and I believe a woman
shines her brightest
on her wedding day.
So that's why...
...they're so darn picky
about every minute detail.
[CHIHIRO] Oh yeah,
makes perfect sense.
Heh. Not really.
But no matter what,
I will always do my best
to make their wishes a reality.
[MIYAKO] It's perfect,
thank you so much, Madoka!
[HANAKO]
Yay, Maddy! I love it!
[BRIDE 12E] It's exactly
what I wanted!
Come here.
Let me see your head!
[MADOKA groans]
[CHIHIRO] I got this, too.
It's medicine.
If your fever doesn't
go down, take some.
And drink this.
It's full of
nutrition and stuff,
so it'll keep you
going if you're not
hungry enough to eat.
I also bought some gelatin
and put it in the fridge,
but if you want something
hot, let me know.
You may talk a big game,
but you're sick
and you need to
take care of yourself!
I'm glad you're working
hard for others,
but your health
is important too!
You got that?
Yes.
And if you need something,
you'd better ask me!
[MADOKA]
Yes, sir.
Okay!
Thank you.
[AMAHARA] Hey, wanna
play games at my place?
Sorry, I can't today.
Why, 'cause Madoka's
still super busy with work?
Mhm! Next time
for sure, though!
--Yep!
--Go get 'em!
Yeah, good luck!
[BOTH gasp]
Sorry, I didn't see you there!
[CHIHIRO] Is there more
to carry? I'll help you!
[KEIICHIRO]
Great, thanks a lot!
That one is heavy.
[CHIHIRO]
I noticed!
[CHIHIRO] Keiichiro, wait!
Don't forget your jacket!
Ah, thank you!
[CHIHIRO]
Drive safely!
[exhales]
[CHIHIRO yells]
Madoka! Please!
Speak to me!
I'm finished...
...with my work!
You mean it?
Yup. I'm pretty sure anyway.
[BOTH]
Hooray!
Let's sleep forever.
[CHIHIRO] Don't sleep
in the hallway!
[knock, knock]
[CHIHIRO] Madoka?
I made you some soup.
Um...
[CHIHIRO]
Madoka?
What are you doing?
I thought you were
done with work.
[MADOKA] Oh, I am.
This was for Chiyo.
[CHIHIRO]
For my mom?
Yes. It was the very
first dress I ever made.
I've remade it so many times.
It barely resembles
the original design.
This is probably version
five hundred and three.
[CHIHIRO] Can you really
call it the first dress
you ever made, then?
[MADOKA chuckles]
I'm not crazy. I know
she's never going to wear it.
But this time of year, I like to
bring it out and look at it.
Mom told me
that she and Dad
didn't have a wedding ceremony.
[MADOKA]
True.
So there aren't
any pictures.
[MADOKA]
I know.
[CHIHIRO]
For what it's worth,
I think this would've
looked great on her.
[CHIYO]
Isn't it beautiful, Madoka?
[MADOKA] Do you want
a dress like this?
[CHIYO] Yes, definitely.
When I get married!
Okay, then I'll
make it for you!
[CHIYO]
Huh?
Don't worry!
I promise, it'll be perfect!
[CHIYO] Really? I hope
I'll be pretty in it!
Just like Mom was!
[MADOKA]
Uh!
--[CHIHIRO] Something wrong?
--[MADOKA] Nothing at all.
By the way, Madoka
--[MADOKA] Hm?
--[CHIHIRO] Jab.
[CHIHIRO] You can worry about
that when you're not sick!
Back to bed!
Chi, what's the matter?
Well uh, it just seems
like a waste, is all.
What's a waste?
You know, the dress for
no one to ever wear it.
[laughs]
I'll just save it for your
wedding day then.
Sound good?
Uh, no! And that's
way in the future!
[MADOKA] Do you think so?
Time has a way of flying.
Who said I'll even get
married in the first place?
[MADOKA] Well, if you
don't get married,
I'll make you wear
the dress as a penalty.
It's a win-win!
[CHIHIRO]
What? That's not fair!
[MADOKA chuckles]
[MADOKA]
Thanks for dinner!
[CHIHIRO] Okay,
time to get some rest!
[MADOKA]
Yes, mother.
[CHIHIRO] Where'd the
cooling sheets go?
I had them
in my workroom.
[CHIHIRO]
Seriously?
[thud]
You hear that? I think
something hit the window.
[CHIHIRO]
Huh?
You're probably
delusional from fever
and lack of sleep,
so close your eyes!
[MADOKA]
Fine. Good night, Chi.
Sleep well.
[CHIHIRO] Let's see, where
are those cooling sheets?
Ugh!
Ow! Man, why is
he so friggin' messy?
Where are they?
[CHIHIRO] That's them!
Thanks a lot!
[CHIYO laughs]
Surely... I'm just...
hearing things?
[yells]
[CHIYO laughs]
[CHIHIRO screams]
[panting]
Ah!
Hey, quiet down.
[CHIHIRO] Did you
turn the lights on?
[thud]
I think that was the
same sound I heard earlier.
It's an evil window ghost!
Oh, yeah?
[shrieks]
It's open a little.
Well that explains
why it's so cold.
Hey Chi, would you mind
closing the window for me?
Huh?
You scared? Uuh!
Now go to sleep!
[MADOKA]
'Kay.
[CHIYO laughs]
[screams]
Window Ghost!
Sh! Be quiet, or you'll
wake him up, scaredy-cat!
[CHIHIRO]
It's that girl
[CHIYO] After I went through
all that trouble to help,
you're calling me
an evil window ghost?
That's quite rude!
It's been one year exactly now.
That's why I came to visit.
[CHIHIRO]
One year?
[CHIYO] Let's have
a chat. That okay?
[CHIHIRO]
Huh?
Just tell me anything.
Like what's happened
in the past year?
[CHIHIRO] Even though
I don't know who she is,
I feel like I know her.
Okay. I ran into Madoka
and he brought me here.
[CHIYO]
Yeah?
That's when
I met Keiichiro,
oh and Miyako
ran away from home.
I learned things...
...like how to
make rolled omelets.
I found the cutest
little dog,
Miyako and I made
pudding together,
I watched a scary movie
with my friends.
I met all the members
from the Uchoten Boys Band.
Oh, we threw a birthday
party for Madoka!
And then he came to
my open house at school.
I read an essay that I wrote
called "My Future Dream."
My friends helped
me clean on Christmas,
and then I learned
to skate! Kinda.
We watched the first sunrise.
I made some macarons
for all of Hino's family.
But then his sister, Hana,
ran away from home
and I helped take care of her.
Madoka and I made botamochi
and cleaned Mom's
grave together.
And then...
...I met...
I met my grandmother,
Madoka's mom.
[CHIHIRO] In the spring, we had
a huge flower viewing party
and I started sixth grade!
So much has
happened this year,
and it wasn't always easy
but still not once
did I ever feel alone!
I see; that makes me glad.
I'm glad you're happy, Chihiro.
[CHIHIRO gasps]
Oh. I guess
it's time to go!
[CHIYO] Hey you!
Be good or else!
Uh.
[CHIHIRO]
Mom.
[CHIYO]
Chihiro. See you later.
Mom, wait!
[MADOKA moans]
[MADOKA]
Ouchie...
Chi, did you flick a sick guy
while he was sleeping?
Hey look, my fever's gone!
[chuckles]
Well you can thank my mom
for both of those things!
[CHIHIRO]
Yep. Looks great!
Ah! Yay!
Yes! Take this!
And this! Ha!
Amahara, I thought you said
you were good at games?
[NAKAJIMA] Yeah,
Hino's crushing you!
[CHIYO] Remember that life
usually works out
okay in the end,
so you don't have to
stress about it too much.
[KEIICHIRO] ...finished
in time for delivery.
What should I do?
[HANAKO] And go!
Sparkle Starbeam!
Magical girl. True power!
Muahahahaha!
You'll never defeat me!
[HANAKO]
Eat my justice!
Oh no! Justice tastes
terrible! I'm dead.
[HANAKO]
I win again!
[MADOKA chuckles]
[CHIHIRO] Madoka! While you're
up here slacking off,
Keiichiro is turning gray!
You haven't grown up
at all this year, have you?
Time to shape up,
mister! Listen!
Those who do not work,
shall not eat!
[MADOKA] You're so mean.
I just got over being sick
and you're picking on me!
[CHIHIRO]
Stop whining!
I watched you playing with Hana,
and you were fine!
Don't make excuses!
Get to work or no dinner!
Wah, Keiichiro,
Chi's being mean to me!
[CHIHIRO]
Oh, I'll show you mean!