Done! Looks good!
The hall's finished!
[ENOMOTO]
For real?
You guys need help
with anything in here?
Heh! Not today, clean machine!
[ENOMOTO] Yeah, your cleaning
access has been denied!
What?
[KINOSHITA]
Ta-dah! Floor's clean!
[GOTO]
The desks, polished!
[KINOSHITA, GOTO, ENOMOTO]
Yeah!
[CHIHIRO]
Then I guess I must be imagining
this dust on my finger?
He's like a mom!
Yeah, meanie!
[CHIHIRO]
Wipe it all down again.
[GOTO] No way! I'm only
in charge of the floors!
[ENOMOTO] Who died and
made you boss, anyway?
[SAKURA] Nomura, are you
done with the windows yet?
[NOMURA]
Uh, a-almost.
[SAKURA]
Finish up so we can go home.
Oh, I'll try and hurry.
Window washing?
I'll give you a hand!
[KINOSHITA]
No fair, Komiya!
[GOTO] If you wanna help,
you can come dust.
No! Do your own dirty work!
Uh!
Uh, I'm sorry.
About what?
I dunno, for being slow.
In my opinion it's better
to do quality work
than speed through things.
I mean, the places you
already wiped down look good.
Um... Wow, thanks so much.
--[CHIHIRO hums]
--[NOMURA giggles]
[MATSUKI, NAKAJIMA]
Hm...
[NOMURA gasps]
Looks like Cupid
got you with his arrow.
Uh--
Musta been pretty sharp.
No! Geez, we're
just friends, y'know?
[NAKAJIMA, MATSUKI]
Yeah, whatever.
[NAKAJIMA]
Don't lie to yourself.
So, what exactly are
you planning to make him?
Make him what?
It is February.
Oh! Wait, what?
The best way to
confess your love,
is with something
that's homemade.
Also, if you have any
extras, I get first dibs.
'Kay...
[CHIHIRO humming]
[MIYAKO]
All right, Madoka!
It's time to start preparing
for "Operation Valentine's Day"!
We definitely need a solid
battle plan for this year.
We already tried truffles,
and then last year
I even baked him
a cake from scratch!
How did he react?
I'm not sure because
Keiichiro always
says the same thing.
You made some for me,
as well? Thank you.
We need to step things up, then.
Maybe you could make
some of those candies
that are filled with
liqueur, ya know?
Really show him you've matured.
Great idea! I could
try making bonbons!
[CHIHIRO]
What's going on?
We're having a strategy meeting.
It is February.
Oh, so bean throwing?
[giggles] Chihiro's so innocent.
Very cute! We can do
bean throwing, too!
[HINO] Valentine's Day? It's
only the beginning of the month.
[CHIHIRO] Yeah, I know.
But Miyako and Madoka were
treating it like a war meeting.
They must love Valentine's.
Well, I'm glad we don't
have to worry about it.
I dunno, you might
get some chocolate
this year, Amahara.
Huh? Why?
Look at our class rep, Sugita.
I heard that last year she gave
all the boys in
her class chocolate.
No way!
[HINO] Also, Hayase's
family owns a cake shop.
She said she'd bring in
some of their new stuff.
Then you've got
Nakamura and Kawaii
who are in the Cooking Club,
so you can count on them
making something, too.
Whoa, creep alert.
It seems like you've done
an awful lot of research.
Well, the thing is...
[WOMEN, GIRLS
fawning, chattering]
These are from the
bakery near my school.
Help yourself to some
dried persimmons.
Aw, you ladies are too kind!
Yeah, they are too kind,
and you really don't deserve it.
Jealous much? I don't blame ya.
[HINO] Whatever. Besides, I'm
like super popular at school.
Well then, how about
we have a friendly match?
What kind?
A Valentine's contest.
Whoever receives the most
chocolate is deemed the winner.
If you manage to win, I promise
to buy you whatever you want.
Fine, bring it on, old man!
So that's the story.
I've gotta get a lot of candy
so I can beat
that gloating geezer!
Your grandpa sounds cool.
He really is!
Grandpa Hino is truly
a prince among men!
[TAKEI] Wow, he's even
managed to charm Komiya!
[HINO] Hey now, you're
supposed to be on my side!
Oh, what about this one?
You think I should make ganache?
That's way too hard!
Just stick with
chocolate cookies,
you can cut 'em
into fun shapes.
That's true, but I
wonder what shapes
Komiya would like.
Wash cloth!
Or a broom and a dust pan!
Stop kidding around,
this is serious!
All right, so something else.
Oh, I heard Komiya
really likes dogs.
Sounds kinda hard.
Come on, nothing good in life
ever comes easy, right?
[MATSUKI] And you have
a lot more rivals for him
than you might think.
Wow, really?
[GROCER WOMAN 6A]
Oh, Chihiro, you're better than
a buy one get one special!
You're so cute,
I beefed up your order!
Thank you so much!
I bet all the girls
wanna reel you in.
[NOMURA]
Oh, I see.
Anyway, we're totally
rooting for ya, pal.
[MATSUKI]
Go get 'em, tiger!
Aw, thanks, you guys.
[NOMURA] Is this really a
good idea? What should I do?
What if he doesn't
like what I make him?
Uh...
Huh? I get double
Valentine's this year?
[NOMURA] If I chicken out, I can
give the other one to my dad.
[NOMURA]
Huh?
[NOMURA, MIYAKO gasp]
[gasps] Oops! Excuse me!
[MIYAKO]
No, no, excuse me.
Here, sorry.
Oh, thank you, Miss.
[NOMURA]
She's so beautiful.
Maybe she's buying chocolate
for Valentine's Day, too.
So I'm curious, are you shopping
for Valentine's Day, too?
[gasps] Uh, yes.
Aha, I thought so.
That's also why I'm here!
Let's give it our best
this year, okay?
Right!
Huh? Hey, Miyako.
[NOMURA gasps]
Oh, look who found me!
Hi, Nomura.
Do you two know each other?
Yeah, we're in the same
class. Whatcha doin'?
Um, I'm just here
picking up some milk,
you know, for my mom.
Well, good news, this milk
is actually on sale!
It's limited to two
per person, though.
Oh, cool. I guess
I'll get that one.
Thank you.
Huh?
[MIYAKO] Oh, me, oh, my! Could
this be what I think it is?
[CHIHIRO] You can find
the milk downstairs. Bye!
Huh?
Just between us girls,
Chihiro prefers milk
chocolate over dark.
[shrieks]
[NOMURA] Oh, my gosh, I must
have been super obvious!
I'm so embarrassed.
[NOMURA]
I won't give up, though.
[UCHOTEN BOYS] ♪ My heart's
beating so fast for you, ♪
♪ the whole day through, ♪
♪ won't you give me a sign? ♪
♪ Everyday I count the things
that I can't wait to do ♪
♪ once you 'are mine ♪
♪ I wont give up, ♪
♪ at break-neck speed
I chase my dream ♪
♪ and everywhere I turn
I'm face-to-face with you ♪
♪ and our future,
makes my heart burn! ♪
[HINO]
Komiya, here, for you.
Aw, thanks a lot!
[HINO]
Mm?
I'm so dumb.
I never even noticed!
That's why you guys
are so close.
[HINO] Um, no, those are
chocolates from my sisters.
Weirdos.
--[TAKEI] Sure, sure.
--[AMAHARA] Whatever!
[NOMURA] I really thought
he'd be alone this morning.
Now what should I do?
I could put it in
his shoe locker!
But what if a teacher thinks
it's something suspicious
and decides to confiscate it?
Good morning!
[NOMURA] Calm down. I still
have all day to give it to him.
I'm sure I'll be able to catch
him alone at some point.
[NOMURA]
Not alone.
Here, for you.
--[NOMURA] Not alone.
--[CHIHIRO] Wow, thank you!
Not alone.
[school bell chimes]
[CHIHIRO]
Bye, guys!
See ya!
[NOMURA]
Why isn't he ever alone?
[CHIHIRO] So do you think you
managed to beat your grandpa?
[HINO] Mm... I did get
quite a few chocolates.
But it's hard to tell.
For an old guy, he sure gets
a lot of Valentine's candy.
[NOMURA] What am I doing? I'm
no better than a crazy stalker.
Huh?
Later.
Yep, good luck.
[NOMURA]
Finally, now's my chance!
[gasps]
Except that I never
stopped to think about
what I should say!
[NOMURA] I can't believe I
followed him all the way home.
This is crazy.
I'll never be able to
give it to him like this!
Maybe I should try
some other time.
--[door clicks]
--[NOMURA yelps]
Hello? Oh, Nomura!
--[gasps]
--Can I help you?
[NOMURA]
What do I do? What do I do?
He's gonna think
I'm a weird stalker!
Quick, say something to
make this less awkward!
Hey!
[NOMURA]
Uh...
Uh, it's cold out.
Yep! Hence the
sweater and stuff!
Anyway, what's up with you?
[NOMURA]
Mm... Um...
For you!
[NOMURA] Uh... It, uh, just made
me happy when you helped me.
Ya know, the other day.
So... That's all, see ya later!
The other day?
Well, good news, this milk
is actually on sale!
Oh!
Wow, that was really
nice of Nomura.
[NOMURA]
I gave it to him! I mean sure,
it was kinda weird,
but I did it! Yay!
[MIYAKO] Oh, are you
talking about the girl
we saw at the store?
Yep. I think it was
a thank you gift.
I was really surprised.
[laughs]
[MIYAKO]
I'm so happy for her.
It looks like she was able
to do her best after all.
[CHIHIRO]
What about you?
Huh?
Did you give
Keiichiro your gift?
Yes. Just like I do every year.
Aw, you made some
for me, as well?
Thank you.
[MIYAKO] It's fine.
As long as he accepts it,
I suppose that's
all that matters.
[CHIHIRO] Wow, your
chocolate might be the most
amazing thing I've
ever laid eyes on!
You really think so?
I don't wanna brag or anything,
but it might be
my best dessert yet!
So great.
Hah! Yours are kinda tiny, huh?
Whatever, cheater! Manju buns
don't count, you know!
The wrapping shows the
giver's true feelings.
It qualifies.
Ah!
[GRANDPA HINO]
The old man wins!
Ha!
[HINO whimpers]
[knocking]
[MADOKA] I'm coming in!
Here, Chi, this is for you.
[CHIHIRO]
What?
Well, I got a bunch of
chocolates from my clients,
and sharing is caring!
I guess.
[MADOKA] Hey, did you get
any good candy today?
I got a bunch of
"None of your business."
[MADOKA]
How mean, I'm just curious.
Fine.
[MATSUKI]
All right, so something else.
Oh, I heard Komiya
really likes dogs.
[CHIHIRO, MADOKA]
Uh...
[CHIHIRO]
Maybe it's a monster?
[MADOKA] No, no, it's clearly an
ancient hieroglyph or something.
It's a dog!
Oh, well, just don't
forget to give her a gift
on White Day, Chi.
[CHIHIRO]
I won't, jeez! Now get out!
[CHIHIRO] Only, I'm not sure
what I should give her.
[typing]
[KEIICHIRO] Hm. I suppose
I should really start
thinking about a White Day
present for Miss Miyako.
[meows]
[KEIICHIRO]
If you have any ideas,
I'm certainly open
to suggestions.
[HINO]
Tastes fine.
It kind of reminds me
of my mom's baking.
Yeah, it definitely has
that special homemade flavor.
Thanks, I guess.
[AMAHARA] Aw, yes,
Komiya made some snacks!
[GOTO]
Gimme one!
[KINOSHITA]
Me, too!
I dunno, do you think maybe
they're missing something?
Like, are they too bland?
[HINO] Look, if you're
that worried about it,
just ask Madoka for help.
The guy's practically a genius
when it comes to
baking and stuff.
[TAKEI] For sure, he always
makes really amazing sweets
when we come over to hang out!
If you gotta eat it,
why not make it delicious?
[CHIHIRO] Fine then. No more
cookies for you traitors.
[AMAHARA, HINO, TAKEI]
What a sore loser.
[KEIICHIRO] Basically, you can't
figure out your White Day gifts.
Is that what you're
worried about?
[CHIHIRO]
Mm-hm.
I think a homemade
gift is a fine idea.
Though I have to admit,
I usually end up
buying mine from a store.
A store, huh?
[KEIICHIRO] Although, this
year I am a little stumped.
Why's that?
Well, because
Master Madoka said:
What? You're gonna
have to do better
than a stuffed animal.
Only little kids like those!
And that's what he pointed out.
Yeah, he's one to talk.
[KEIICHIRO] Now what? I don't
have the faintest clue
of what sort of things a high
school girl would even like.
I searched the internet...
[CHIHIRO] I have a feeling
he could give Miyako
just about anything and she'd
be over the moon for it.
Anyway...
Did you know that
Master Madoka prefers
to make homemade
gifts every year?
Maybe ask him for advice.
[groans]
[CHIHIRO]
Stare...
[MADOKA] Uh... Hi.
Did you need something?
[CHIHIRO]
Are you baking?
I am. I thought I would go ahead
and get started on
my White Day presents.
Am I... in the way?
Nope, go ahead.
Uh... If you insist.
[CHIHIRO]
Clean up as you go!
I'm sorry!
[ding]
[MADOKA] Hm... Chi, which one
of these do you like best?
I'm too busy cleaning to look!
[MADOKA] Aw, don't be
like that, just try one.
[CHIHIRO]
It's good.
Um, hey.
[MADOKA sighs]
Yeah?
Listen. I was just
wondering if you'd
teach me how to bake.
Huh?
Ooh... Yes!
All righty, ready
to get started?
What is this?
They're for pastry chefs.
I made them in case
we baked together,
and now we get to be twinsies!
Hooray for us.
[MADOKA]
So what should we make, Chi?
How about macarons?
What are macarons?
[MADOKA]
Feast your eyes!
Girls love these cookies.
Maybe because they're so cute.
Could I learn to make them?
Oui, mon amie.
That's why I'm here!
Step one, separate the
egg yolks from the whites.
'Kay.
[MADOKA] Now we have
to freeze the egg whites.
[CHIHIRO] What? Why do
we have to freeze them?
Because when
egg whites are fresh
they can make the batter runny.
[CHIHIRO]
Huh.
Uh...
But waiting for them
to freeze is super boring.
[CHIHIRO]
Huh?
So here's some egg whites
I froze yesterday!
Take those out first!
[MADOKA]
Next, measure everything out,
combine the dry
ingredients and sift,
then put them into the fridge.
[CHIHIRO]
Again?
Yep! It's kind of like
a really neat
science experiment!
If you mess up the
measurements even a bit,
it'll ruin everything.
[CHIHIRO]
Uh...
There's only a little left,
so I'll just throw it all in!
Okay, the next
part is important.
Once you're done mixing
everything, macaronage time.
Maca-what-ty?
You know! Swirly twirly!
"Swirly twirly"?
[MADOKA]
Do it like this.
Uh, this way?
Kind of, but try to make
it more floopy-whoopy!
Can you use real words?
Huh?
What's the matter?
[CHIHIRO] Well, I might be
having an identity crisis.
[ding]
[CHIHIRO]
Hm...
Those look pretty good,
'specially for your first try.
You think so?
[MADOKA] It's okay that
they're not exactly perfect.
You did your best and it's
a gift from the heart,
which makes it perfect in
a different kind of way.
I guess that's true.
[MADOKA] If you're really
that worried, you could still
make them look nice by
dressing them up a little.
What's that thing?
It's a handmade pouch.
You could put
the macarons inside
to add a charming touch.
They're mostly made
from my sewing scraps,
so it's like killing
two birds with one stone.
Do you have anymore
of those scraps?
[CHIHIRO] Unfortunately,
I only know how to make
a simple drawstring pouch.
No problem, I'll just use some
cute fabric to make up for it.
Uh--
What's the heck? Are those cats?
I swear. He's like
a crazy cat lady.
[gasps]
[MADOKA chuckles]
Done!
[HINO] So you were up
all night making pouches?
[TAKEI]
You look tired.
I'm fine. Will you
please give these
to your older sisters, and Hana?
Yeah, man, sure thing.
[CHIHIRO]
Nomura.
[NOMURA yelps]
Who, me?
Here, thank you for
the Valentine's chocolate.
Oh, thanks so much.
All right!
Wow! Isn't that wonderful?
Yeah.
[MIYAKO] Oh my! It looks
just like my sweet Antaro!
It's beyond cute!
Thank you so much, Chihiro!
Sure thing. And, by the way.
What's with the bear?
It's a White Day
gift from Keiichiro,
isn't it precious?
[CHIHIRO] He ended up giving
her a stuffed animal after all?
[MIYAKO]
See this chain here on its neck?
It's actually a bracelet.
Know what else?
This is the first time
ever that Keiichiro
has given me any
type of jewelry.
[CHIHIRO]
That's awesome!
[MIYAKO]
Yes!
[knocking]
[MADOKA]
Come in.
[CHIHIRO]
Thanks for letting me use these.
Sure. Did you make
some cute pouches?
[CHIHIRO] Uh... I dunno, Miyako
seemed to like it at any rate.
I wish I could have seen them.
You know, maybe
next year I could
teach you how to gather frills.
No thanks, I think I'll pass.
[whines]
[CHIHIRO]
Anyway, I'm gonna go ahead
and get some sleep. Goodnight.
[MADOKA]
Sweet dreams!
[door clicks]
What's this?
[CHIHIRO] "Thanks for
teaching me how to bake.
It was a big help."
He really is a good kid.
[NOMURA] I wonder if
Komiya's into monsters?
[CHOCOLATE DOG 8.5A]
Woof, woof!