[KEIICHIRO]
Chihiro?
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but would you mind
bringing the tea?
Sure!
Oh, are you doing homework?
In that case,
I'll serve the tea.
It's no big deal.
I just finished up.
--How does Assam sound?
--[KEIICHIRO] Great.
This counter isn't
exactly an ideal place
to do homework.
No, but I usually
don't bring any home
'cause I finish it
at school during breaks;
which leaves plenty
of time to clean up here.
Is that a fact?
[MADOKA] So it bothers you
that he won't study at home?
He'd rather work hard
at school so he can
start cleaning
as soon as possible.
He should be a good student
first and a maid second.
The very least we
could do is give him
a desk for his room.
[MADOKA]
Under normal circumstances
I would agree with you, but...
...what can I say
when his grades are so high?
Oh.
He's excelling in every subject
like some kind of prodigy.
There's no denying
he's an excellent student.
Do you think he might act
like too much of an adult?
I can't stand the thought
of him sweeping the floors
while his childhood passes by.
But Chihiro
loves this so much,
I couldn't take it away.
[CHIHIRO hums]
Ha!
[laughs]
I'm not sure if
there's anything
we can do for him at this point.
I think you're right.
[CHIHIRO, TAKEI]
Bring it on!
Look, 98 percent!
One hundred!
Aw. I lost.
[chuckles] I felt pretty good
about my answers this time.
I don't get it.
Explain to me how you guys
can get such good scores
without studying.
I study! In the classroom!
You're kidding me.
All right, class.
Please quiet down.
Next week we're hosting
our yearly open house.
I hope you'll all remember
to pass this note on
to your parent
or guardian.
That means you, Komiya.
Me?
[SAKAMOTO] A little bird
told me that your note
didn't make it home last year.
Let's not have
a repeat of that.
[STUDENTS laugh]
Pay attention.
Here is your homework.
Get your gears turning
and write an essay
to read aloud
at the open house.
Your topic is...
[CHIHIRO]
Our future dreams?
I expect you to
write about what job
you'd like to have
when you're older,
including your reasons
for picking that job.
So what's my dream?
[AMAHARA] Essays are like the
worst thing on the planet.
Yeah, to be honest
I feel like the topic
is a little
too complicated.
Really? I figured you'd
be good at writing essays.
Well, it's just
that I have no idea
what I want to be
when I grow up.
It's not like you've
never thought about it.
There's gotta be something
you'd like to be.
I did have this idea once.
[PRESCHOOL TEACHER 7A] Can you
tell us what you'd like
to be when you're
all grown up, Chihiro?
[PRESCHOOL TEACHER 7B]
You like books,
so maybe you'll be a teacher?
No. I wanna be rich!
Well, you can't really
fault the kid for having goals.
Try to think big!
You could be a soccer player,
a prime minister,
or even a voice actor in the
greatest anime of all time!
Could we try
to be realistic here?
I think you
should pick a job
that fits your personality.
That would be
a good place to start.
A dream for the future
that will fit my personality.
[AMAHARA]
See ya!
[TAKEI]
See you tomorrow!
[CHIHIRO]
Later!
[HINO]
So, what have you decided?
[CHIHIRO]
About what?
[HINO]
The open house next week.
Are you gonna tell
Madoka about it?
[CHIHIRO]
I haven't figured it out.
To be honest, he's pretty
busy most of the time,
plus he doesn't
like crowds all that much.
He might not like it.
[CHIHIRO] I mean, it's not like
he's my parent or anything.
Komiya.
I just remembered
that I still have to
go grocery shopping! See ya!
Hey, will you
wait a minute?
He's gonna have some kind
of breakdown one day.
[phone beeps]
There's an open house soon.
At Chihiro's school?
Yes. Got a text from Hino.
Just wanted to let you know
that next Monday
we're having an open house.
We all hafta present essays
about our "future dreams."
Komiya seemed a bit nervous
about telling you,
so you should probably go ahead
and ask him about it.
He says it's
this coming Monday.
That should be fine.
You don't have
anything scheduled.
[MADOKA] I wonder if
he even wants me to go.
I can't force him.
Maybe he doesn't want me
to know it's happening.
[KEIICHIRO] There should be
no harm in asking him.
Honestly, I don't know
if my heart could stand it
if he doesn't
want me to be there.
[sighs]
What's your problem,
Keiichiro?
[KEIICHIRO] Nothing.
It's almost time for me
to head home for the evening.
If you could do one thing,
please act like
a sane adult around him.
Hm!
[MADOKA]
I have feelings, you know!
[BOTH]
I wanted--
Go ahead.
I wanted to ask
how school went today.
I made a one hundred
on the social studies test.
That's great to hear!
Anything else?
Nah, not really.
My day was dull.
Nothing to report.
[CHIHIRO]
Madoka.
Uh. Yes, Chi?
Look down.
There's food on you.
Aah.
[CHIHIRO]
Just give it up already.
Madoka really doesn't
like going outside.
And it isn't exactly
a matter of life and death
whether he comes
to the open house or not.
It'll be a live-in position
with three meals a day
plus snacks
and cover school fees!
Sound good?
What do you think?
I guess I still feel
kind of guilty about
how much he's already
done for me.
I don't want him to feel
pressured to do anything
he doesn't want to do.
Hey, Chi?
[CHIHIRO]
Yeah? What's up?
Just got out. The bath's
free if you want it.
Sure! I'll do that now.
[groans]
[CHIYO]
Chihiro, what's this?
Seems there's an
open house I'm invited to?
It's nothing much.
[yells]
Did you really think you
could hide something
like this from your mother?
[CHIHIRO] I was trying
to do the right thing!
[sighs]
Why didn't you want me
to know about it?
I'm sorry. I thought
you were too busy.
I can always
take time off work
for important
events like this.
Please don't
keep things from me.
Sweetheart. I'll always do
my best to be there for you.
[MADOKA] There's no need
to hide things.
Did you really think
I wouldn't consider the idea?
[door clicks]
Hey there.
What about your bath?
This is for you.
We're having
an open house next week.
It's not that big of
a deal if you can't come.
There are gonna be
a lot of people.
So, yeah, anyway,
I promise I'm not gonna
be upset if you aren't able
to go to this thing, but...
...would you like to?
Madoka?
Eh!
I'll definitely go!
You're sure you're not
too busy with work?
[MADOKA]
Work's no problem!
I'll have Keiichiro
take care of everything!
You're making him do it all?
Now that all this
is cleared up,
I think I'm going
to make a new suit!
What kind of look
do I want for this?
Is violet a bright enough
color to wear?
I wonder. Maybe some
lamé this time.
There's no reason
to do anything like that!
I want you to be proud
to have me at the open house!
I'm more than willing to
go the extra mile for you!
[CHIHIRO] Just dress like
you normally would!
[MADOKA] But this is
a special occasion!
I'll have to take
the entire silhouette
into consideration.
Maybe lace trimming?
[CHIHIRO] Wow, I guess I didn't
have a reason to be nervous.
I'm glad I told him.
Honestly, I'm just
thrilled you invited me!
You have to present an essay,
isn't that right?
So, have you managed
to figure out
your future dream yet?
How do you know
about the essay?
Uh.
[CHIHIRO] The note never
mentioned anything about
us presenting our essays,
so you better tell me
right now how
you found out about it!
Didn't you tell me?
I forget. I, uh.
Sure it wasn't in the note?
[CHIHIRO] Stop goofing
around and confess!
[MADOKA] What do you want
to be when you grow up?
Anything you come up
with should work.
It's not that big of a deal.
That's easy to say
when you're not
the one presenting it!
I wanted to grow up
to be Francis Xavier.
What? The missionary?
[XAVIER]
Xavier.
[MADOKA] I figured he was
some fashion guru
with that Elizabethan collar.
Please don't
tell me that the frills
were all you cared about!
[MADOKA] Then one day Keiichiro
brought me information
about joining mission schools.
Do you know which seminary
you'd like to attend?
[MADOKA]
Uh...
I might have been a priest.
It's sort of crazy
to think about now.
I can't see that happening.
Let's brainstorm a little.
Can you think of anything
you'd like to achieve?
That's a good place to start.
Hmmm. Well, I think being
able to clean up after you
is an achievement.
But I've been working hard
to keep my stuff organized!
Piling all of the junk
you don't wanna deal with
in one box isn't organizing!
I don't mean
picking up after us.
When you were little, what
was something you wanted
more than anything else?
Remember?
[CHIHIRO]
Hmmm.
When I was little...
[CHIHIRO] After they were
reunited, the princess lived
happily ever after
with the king and queen.
From then on, there was
joy and celebration
throughout the land.
No one was ever sad again.
[CHIHIRO] I liked
the idea of being rich.
[MADOKA]
Hey, Chi.
I thought money
could solve it all.
I wanted to be wealthy so Mom
wouldn't have to work as hard.
But that probably
isn't something
I should put in my essay.
[MADOKA]
How rich?
How rich? What kind of
wealth are we talking here?
You mean like mogul-type money?
Uh, maybe?
Is that a lot?
Running a conglomerate
takes a special
type of person, but
you're extremely
responsible and organized,
so you would be perfect.
You don't think
that's an immature goal?
Not at all.
I don't believe that
you should ever
be embarrassed about
wanting to make life
easier for your family.
Plus, it's a lot
of fun earning money!
Are you serious?
Mhm. I remember when
I was first paid for my work.
Even though it wasn't a lot,
it was still very satisfying.
Hooray!
We just need to figure out
what kind of business
you'd like to start.
I think the best idea
is to stick to something
you're good at.
'Kay, like what?
[BOTH]
Hey, I know! Cleaning!
Then... I should be
a housekeeper?
[MADOKA] There's no denying
you're good enough
to get paid for doing chores,
but let's think
more along the lines
of making a business out of it.
I could oversee
a team of window washers,
or be a server
at some fancy inn.
What about running
your own hotel?
[MADOKA] Hotel tycoons are some
of the richest people around!
The hallways
are lined with rooms,
so you could clean
as much as you want!
I could clean
as much as I want?
I think me living in a
penthouse on the top floor
is another great idea!
Hold on, live in a hotel?
[MADOKA]
Mhm.
My essay paper isn't
a sketchbook you know!
[MADOKA]
Reservation for one!
[CHIHIRO]
Stop drawing!
I can make all of
the employee uniforms
coordinate with yours!
We can start designing now!
Would you get your own
paper to write on?
[MADOKA]
Here. Do you like it?
Seriously? You'd be
unstoppable if you were
this fast on your own projects.
There's also the matter
of deciding what food to offer.
So much to choose from!
Might I suggest an
international gourmet menu?
[CHIHIRO] Weird.
I've never talked to anyone
about this stuff.
It's fun. I guess
I never let myself
think about my future.
I could do anything!
Check it out! What about
something like this?
Yeah! Great idea!
[laughs]
--[CHILDREN laugh]
--[CHIHIRO giggles]
[indistinctive chatter]
I can't believe
so many people showed up
on a Monday afternoon!
It's a little weird
how excited they are
to see where their kids are
stuck learning every day.
I figured your family
would have come today, Hino!
[HINO] No one in my family
can really take off work.
[GRANDPA HINO]
Hey, Yuji!
--So this is your classroom?
--What's up, Yuji?
What the heck are all of
you guys are doing here?
Are you kidding me?
We wouldn't wanna miss this!
We were all so excited
to come to your open house!
An event like this
has gotta be a family affair!
Yeah, we had to
check in to make sure
you aren't causing too much
trouble for the teacher!
Who would we be if we
didn't come support our bro?
[babbles]
I understand Mom,
Dad, and Grandpa,
but why aren't Koji
and Yoko at college?
What's your excuse?
[KOJI, YOKO]
We took a sick day!
You shouldn't be
skipping class!
His whole family is here.
I can't believe
everybody came
just to watch your presentation!
Almost.
There are two missing.
My older sister Miei
is in high school right now,
and my little sister Hanako
is in kindergarten.
[TAKEI]
Wow, there are so many!
[CHIHIRO]
Madoka isn't here.
I wonder if he ended up
working after all,
or maybe he got a stomachache
before he even left the house.
What if he ended up taking
a wrong turn somewhere?
[meows]
[MADOKA] Dead end? I didn't
see this on the map.
[sneezes]
No. I'm probably
just overreacting.
[groans]
[KEIICHIRO]
Ah. Here we are.
I think this is Chihiro's room.
--[MADOKA] Mm-hm.
--[CHIHIRO gasps]
[chuckles]
Hi, Chihiro!
He looks nice.
Who's dad is that?
[MATSUKI] Well he
just said "Chihiro"!
[HAYASE]
So that's Komiya's dad?
Or maybe his older brother?
[KAWAAI] He's the
handsomest guy ever!
[ENTOMB]
I bet he's a model.
I'm glad he's here, but
he seems so out of place.
I didn't know you
were coming, Keiichiro.
Sorry I didn't ask first.
He seemed confident
on the drive over,
but I thought it might be
best if I came in with him.
Hopeless. He's going
to embarrass himself.
Hi there! I'm a fan!
Would it be all right if I
took a few pictures with you?
Geez, could you be
any more embarrassing?
[NOMURA] "My Future Dream"
by Yu Nomura.
After high school and college
I want to be a homemaker.
Recently, women have
taken on essential roles
and leadership responsibilities
outside of the home.
However, I believe that
managing a household
can be a very
rewarding job as well.
[CHIHIRO] I wonder if
Madoka's feeling okay.
He's looking kind of pale.
[NOMURA] ...cleaning up,
making appointments...
Don't do that.
If you wave at him,
he may get distracted.
[WOMEN giggle]
[CHIHIRO] Truthfully,
compared to all
the other kids' parents
he really doesn't fit in
all that well, but I'm
so glad he came!
Great! Thank you
for sharing, Nomura.
All right now, who's next?
Komiya? Will you
read your essay?
Sure.
"My Future Dream,"
written by Chihiro Komiya.
At first I wasn't sure
what I wanted to be
when I grew up,
so I got a little help.
I decided that I'd like
to be a hotel tycoon,
because it would let me do
a lot of things I'm good at.
Organization, for instance,
comes easily to me.
I also like to
keep things clean.
[MADOKA] Okay then! Are you
allowed to go home?
[CHIHIRO]
Yep!
Great! Then let's
head to the car.
[SAKAMOTO]
Komiya?
Yes, ma'am?
Your essay was great.
Very impressive.
I must admit, a hotel tycoon
wasn't what I expected!
Yeah. I was a little
surprised myself.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Chihiro's teacher,
Ms. Sakamoto.
It's a real pleasure.
I was wondering
if you could possibly
spare a moment of your time.
I wanted to speak
to you about some of
the recent changes that have
happened for Chihiro.
I'm sure it's been
hard at times,
but what can you tell me about
your home life right now?
[BOTH] You want us to tell
you what we're like at home?
[CHIHIRO] If you take
it out, put it away!
Well, I'll just be going, then.
What do you want with me?
Don't leave! We need you!
You know I can't
depend on Madoka
to make us look normal
in front of my teacher!
I suppose you wouldn't need
me for very long, right?
Right! Just a teeny bit of time
that'll be over
before you know it.
It'll be easy!
[BOTH]
Okay?
No. I'm not
speaking for you.
You've taken on
the responsibility
of being his guardian.
Participating in meetings
makes you look capable!
[SAKAMOTO]
Hm?
And as Madoka's guardian,
it's your obligation
to make sure he doesn't
say something stupid!
Believe me, I've been trying
to do that for years.
Though I appreciate the offer,
I must politely decline.
Good luck.
So! Will the two of you
please come this way?
[SAKAMOTO] All right then,
Mr. Takatori,
if you don't mind,
can you tell me
how Chihiro
spends his time at home?
Of course I don't mind.
[CHIHIRO] Don't say too much.
Don't say too much.
He stays busy.
What do you mean by that?
Does he help with the housework
at all, for example?
Yes! He's a huge help!
And not only that,
he does all of the cook--
[wails]
Yes. Was there
something you needed?
You shouldn't
tell her that stuff.
[MADOKA] What's the matter
with telling her the truth?
[CHIHIRO]
Be quiet!
[SAKAMOTO]
Excuse me?
Well. I spend
a lot of time reading!
I love to learn!
Someone's pants are on fire.
[CHIHIRO grunts]
[SAKAMOTO] Do you
eat meals together?
[MADOKA] Yes, Chihiro always
makes the best foo--
[MADOKA wails]
--Will you be quiet?
--I'm supposed to answer her!
Yeah, but you're making us
look like we're all messed up!
[MADOKA] We never rehearsed
this, so how would I know
what you want me to say?
[CHIHIRO]
You know how to talk,
so just say the stuff
grown-ups like!
[MADOKA] Do you realize how much
sense that doesn't make?
[CHIHIRO] Don't tell her that
I clean and cook so much!
I mean, I enjoy it, but that
makes us look super weird!
[MADOKA] Well maybe
you should take the lead!
You're supposed
to be the adult here!
Can't you see I'm trying
my best here?
[SAKAMOTO] I'm glad.
They really get along well.
I don't have to worry.
[CHIHIRO]
I can't believe you!
You have no idea
how much trouble
you could have gotten us into!
I was honest. You're
a huge help around here.
Why is that bad?
People might get
the wrong idea if they hear
that an elementary schooler is
taking care of the housework
and cooking all of
your meals for you!
But you really
are doing all that.
You're totally
missing the point here!
[MADOKA] Calm down
before you hit me!
[KEIICHIRO] Chihiro.
Your essay touched my heart.
You did a wonderful job.
I had no idea
that you were interested
in business administration!
[CHIHIRO] What's with
all the books?
A Beginner's Guide
to Management!
Strategy Guide
to Acquiring an MBA!
Management Basics
and Applications!
Stock Portfolios Made Easy!
I've got a lot more
if you need them!
Since it's your goal
to be a proprietor,
it may be in your best interest
to start working on your degree.
But before that,
have you considering
a study abroad program?
Keiichiro, please,
calm down.
Hey. Do I read all of these?
No matter what dream
you decide to chase,
I'm certain you'll have to work
hard to make it come true!
But you'll be fine.
Do you believe that,
or are you being polite?
[MADOKA]
Both! I have faith in you!
If you want proof,
I've recently put
an early investment
in your bedroom.
[CHIHIRO]
What is it?
[MADOKA]
Oh. You'll see!
Wait a second.
Now that I think about it,
who was that man
in the glasses?
[AMAHARA] Did you guys
have fun at the open house?
[TAKEI]
Yeah!
[AMAHARA] I'm glad
I finally met Hino's family.
[TAKEI] His big sister sure
was pretty, wasn't she?
[HINO]
Don't make me laugh.
What's so pretty about her?
[AMAHARA] She's a babe!
Wait a sec, Hino.
Is that her standing
behind you? She looks angry!
[HINO]
I was just fooling around!
My sister is as kind
as she is beautiful.
And smart! And perfect
in every way!
[AMAHARA]
Oh. Now she's nodding.
[TAKEI]
She's smiling too.
[HINO]
Good. Then I'm safe.
We're calling the next episode
"Sisters Scuffle"!
I mean, "The Devil Scoffs When
You Talk of Next Year."
[AMAHARA]
Please watch!