[alarm rings]
[yawns]
[MADOKA]
Can you turn that alarm off?
I'm trying to sleep.
What?
Ugh.
[MADOKA yelps]
How could anyone
expect me to sleep
in my own bed when it's
completely buried underneath
all my work stuff?
Maybe try taking
responsibility for your mess
instead of dragging
everyone else into it!
This might help. Take it.
Even the most
aggressive annoyance
is stopped by pepper spray.
What exactly are
you trying to say?
As if barging into his room
without asking makes me
some sort of degenerate.
[CHIHIRO] I have to figure
out a way to keep him
out of my room.
Maybe I just need to
get a big guard dog.
Huh...
Aw, man. I'd love to have a dog.
We weren't allowed to have
pets at our apartment.
[barking]
Whoa. How's that
for a coincidence?
Aw! I bet keeping a puppy
your size in my room
would be no trouble at all!
I should stop kidding myself.
Cleaning up after Madoka and
a pet would be more trouble
than I could handle.
I'm sure someone really
great is gonna adopt you.
[PUPPY whines]
[PUPPY barks]
[CHIHIRO]
Hey, I'm home!
[MADOKA sneezes]
[CHIHIRO]
Madoka?
Are you okay in--?
[KEIICHIRO] Master Madoka,
would you care to explain this?
[meows]
Well, that's a kitten.
[sneezes]
Hello, this is Keiichiro,
and I'm afraid he's
brought in another cat.
I'm not sure where
he found a kitten.
I would say it's about
a month old and male.
He's a black short-hair.
One white paw and blue eyes.
Yes, it's very cute.
Thank you again for your help
and we'll see you soon.
I have to ask.
How many more times
must we go through this?
You aren't allowed to
bring cats into this home.
You know you're
severely allergic!
[MADOKA] It's been crying
in the garden since yesterday.
I couldn't just ignore it!
[KEIICHIRO] Yes, well, if you
try to rescue every stray
with a sob story, you'll
end up in the hospital.
[MADOKA] I can't believe you're
being so selfish, Keiichiro!
This kitten needs me!
[CHIHIRO sighs]
What should I do?
[PUPPY whines]
Stay strong.
Just go downstairs
and talk him into it.
One look at that sweet
face and he'll give in.
[MADOKA] Please go away!
I'm on borrowed time here!
Who am I kidding,
that'll never work.
[whines]
Okay! I'm sure it's
gonna be just fine!
I can keep you up here
until I find someone
who wants to adopt you!
Keiichiro took my kitty away.
The only choice I have is
to use you as a substitute
until my grief subsides.
I'm feeling better already.
You are the cutest widdle thing!
So tell me.
You really like cats, don't you?
Yep.
And dogs, too?
Beasts from Hell!
If you so much as
look at them wrong,
they'll turn vicious
and attack you!
Someone help! He's gonna eat me!
I can't figure out why
such malicious animals
aren't locked away
in the city zoo.
I'll go start the tea!
Wait, could you
put this on first?
[AMAHARA] Sorry. My apartment
doesn't allow pets.
Our cat's like 100, so it's
probably not the best idea.
[HINO] We would, but we
have three dogs already.
[CHIHIRO sighs]
When did you get so
interested in finding homes
for stray animals?
You probably should
have just kept walking.
Now you're stuck
with it when someone
would have taken
it home eventually.
I couldn't just
leave it like that.
I didn't know what else to do.
I hope you at least found
a good hiding spot for it.
[CHIHIRO]
It's in my room.
You are kidding, right?
If you're uncle finds out,
he'll send the poor thing
straight to the pound!
[CHIHIRO yelps]
Is it just me or has Chihiro
been acting off lately?
I can't say I've
noticed anything.
It seems his mind
is someplace else.
I put those cat ears on him
yesterday; he didn't bat an eye.
He may still be adjusting
to all the changes.
I wish I knew how
to get him to open up
about his feelings.
[CHIHIRO]
Hey, I'm home!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Chihiro, you're home
quite early to--
[KEIICHIRO]
Hm.
[pants, laughs]
[CHIHIRO]
You're still here!
Such a good boy.
[KEIICHIRO]
Not another animal.
[KEIICHIRO] All right then.
Have you found it a home?
Not yet.
I'll see what I can do.
Though my network of
pet adopters consists
mainly of cat lovers.
But we have to start somewhere.
Really?
Well, I'm grateful you
told me the truth.
Now it'll be easier for me
to help you with this.
Sorry, should've
told you sooner.
There's someone else who
might deserve an apology.
Um... I--
I'm sorry for not
asking your permission.
Did you hear me?
Uh--
[CHIHIRO]
Wait, Madoka!
Its beady eyes are
staring into my soul.
Can you put him in another room?
Please stop that.
Do I look like a chew toy?
[CHIHIRO]
Should I ask him?
He's already looks angry, but I
have to do the right thing.
You told me how much
you hate dogs,
but is there any way you'd
allow me to keep it here
until I can find a good owner?
[MADOKA]
Of course.
[CHIHIRO gasps]
You're a member of
this household and,
as such, have every right to
make requests without fear.
There's no need to hide things.
Did you really think I
wouldn't even consider the idea?
[CHIHIRO] I was wrong.
He's not angry at me.
I hurt his feelings.
Madoka, I'm sorry!
I won't hide anything
from you next time!
Trust me. I'll trust you, too.
I-I-I believe in us!
[MADOKA laughs]
[CHIHIRO]
Hey! Don't laugh at me!
Sorry. I believe in us, too.
[MADOKA] There's no way
I'm going to clean up
after that thing!
[CHIHIRO] You don't even
clean up after yourself.
[knocking]
[MADOKA]
I knocked!
I thought a sleepover
might be fun
now that we've made... up....
[barks]
[yells]
[CHIHIRO] A sleepover might
be fun with the three of us.
Is that okay?
[MADOKA] He'll eat me
as soon as I shut my eyes!
Lately I've been
letting this little guy
sleep in the bed
with me at night.
So you have to be careful
when you climb in, okay?
Why does that fleabag
get priority over me?
This is ridiculous!
[CHIHIRO] Come back here,
boy! Where'd you go?
[barks]
[CHIHIRO]
Thought I lost ya for a second.
It's so overgrown.
The gardeners sure have their
work cut out for them today.
[doorbell buzzes]
Ah, I'm coming!
[HINO] Hey there!
Hino Landscaping here!
You got a job?
No way. Who knew?
[HINO laughs]
You don't think I can handle it?
[GRANDPA HINO] Manners!
Be respectful to the clients!
How ya doin', Chihiro?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Yeah! It's great to see you!
[GRANDPA HINO]
What a mess.
From the looks of this place,
we've got a full
day ahead of us.
I guess the master of the house
has more important things to do
than pull up some weeds.
[MADOKA]
Is that so?
I had no idea you were
the gardener's grandson.
It's a small world after all.
I help out sometimes.
Shouldn't you head
back over then?
As long as Chihiro
keeps him company
I'm gonna take
it easy. It's funny.
Those two have always gotten
along with each other.
[MADOKA]
I wonder why...
[gasps] It's the goatee!
[HINO] I don't think that's it.
And you couldn't pull it off.
Aw...
You two must be getting
a lot closer lately, huh?
Do you really think so?
Sure, I mean he sneaked
that puppy in the house.
He'd have to feel
pretty comfortable
around here to try that.
[KEIICHIRO]
Now listen here.
Things would go much
smoother if you'd cooperate!
[HINO] Honestly, I've never
seen him let loose like that.
Chihiro's usually too
high-strung to take many risks.
In my experience,
he's mostly angry.
Between you and me, I think
he's big control freak.
[CHIHIRO]
Hino!
You need to go get the
fertilizer out of the truck!
'Kay.
[CHIHIRO] Grandpa just said
he's taking your cut
if you don't start helping!
Uh-- Coming! Wait, do what now?
[CHIHIRO]
Seriously?
[GRANDPA HINO] I've been tryin'
to teach that boy the value
of a hard day's work.
I wish he'd learn even a little
from your example, I mean,
you're giving your all,
even while wearing that
pretty maid outfit.
That's impressive dedication!
Dedication. Yeah. Thanks a lot.
Always thought that young fella
who owned this
place was eccentric.
Who could've guessed he was
Chiyo's little brother?
I have to tell you.
The wife and I had been
discussing whether or not
we should take you in.
Huh?
[GRANDPA HINO]
Hino said that you didn't have
any other family members.
If you need anything at all,
just let me know, okay?
[CHIHIRO]
He really meant it.
The offer still stands
if you ever wanna come.
--[CHIHIRO] Huh?
--[MADOKA gasps]
We love a full house!
It's great having kids around.
Right now we have six of them.
Plus three dogs, if pets
are up your alley!
[laughs]
Wow. I don't even
know what to say.
Thanks, but... I think
I'd like to stay here.
[gasps]
If I left,
the house I've been
working so hard to clean
would probably
end up messy again.
And I can't believe
I have my own room.
I've sorta gotten
used to seeing Madoka
and Keiichiro every day.
Thanks a lot for the offer,
but this is home.
That's just fine.
I'm happy for you.
[laughs]
Well, keep 'em in line!
[gasps]
[MIYAKO]
You're adorable!
Like a cute little
bean bun filled with anko !
You're so sweet!
So, I have no choice
but to call you...
Antaro!
[barks]
[MIYAKO laughs]
[CHIHIRO]
And just like that,
he had found himself an owner!
[HINO]
Whoa!
[AMAHARA, TAKEI]
A happy ending!
I bet you're still kinda bummed
that you couldn't
keep it though.
[CHIHIRO laughs] To be honest,
I don't think Madoka
was handling the
stress very well.
[screams]
He probably felt
like he was trapped
inside a haunted house!
Considering how he's
scared of dogs,
it was really cool he let you
keep the puppy in the house
while you looked
for a new owner.
[gasps]
That was pretty cool.
I don't even remember taking
the time to say thank you.
[MADOKA]
I said no!
I'm not going anywhere
and that's final.
[KEIICHIRO] You can pout all
you want, but the arrangements
have already been made.
It would be in bad taste
to change them now.
I didn't even know about this.
Feign ignorance, but I confirmed
all this with you
twice last week.
I see you weren't even
listening, were you?
What's going on in here?
Master Madoka believes
if he whines enough
he won't have to go
on this business trip.
[CHIHIRO]
A business trip? When?
Today.
[CHIHIRO] Huh?! If you
have somewhere to go,
why are you sitting around here?
Stop whining, hurry up,
and go change your clothes!
Why must you be
so cruel to me, Chi?
This isn't him.
Making a good first
impression is essential.
I'm being sent away
for three whole days.
But I want you to know,
you're going to be just fine.
I'll try to find the will
to survive without you.
I almost forgot.
I have something for you.
It's a hand-me-down,
but it still works.
You're giving me a cell phone?
[MADOKA]
Always try to keep it with you.
You can call any time
you need, okay?
Morning, afternoon,
even late at night.
[CHIHIRO]
I won't call.
Now try to relax
and do your job.
I don't wanna!
[KEIICHIRO]
Goodbye, Chihiro!
Thank you for taking care of
the house while we're away.
Somebody call the police!
I'm being taken against my will!
[CHIHIRO]
I'm all alone.
I can't believe how
silent this place
is when there's nobody around.
I feel...
...so excited to clean
without anybody bothering me!
I'll start with the drains
and ventilation fans
in the kitchen,
then I'll wash all the
windows on the terrace!
They'll be sparkling!
Oh, yeah!
I can do the curtains
and cushions, too!
I'm so ready for this. Woo-hoo!
[CHIHIRO sneezes]
So, you're telling me
you took a bath
and got so busy cleaning
afterwards, you caught a cold?
I got a little carried away.
I could have sworn
I saw a bit of mold
between some of the tiles.
I started scrubbing and before
I knew it, it was midnight.
[CHIHIRO sneezes]
Sounds like you.
I'm not surprised.
You said you'll be on
your own a few more days.
Should I worry
about your sanity?
No, I'll be fine.
I pushed myself too hard is all.
Is there any way
you could teach me
how to use this thing?
A cell phone?
[CHIHIRO] Madoka gave
it to me before he left,
but I don't know
what to do with it.
It hasn't stopped beeping
at me since last night.
It looks like someone has
been sending you messages!
First, push this button
to go to your... mail...
Uh...
Next, you press open.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night, sweet child! Heart!
I pray you have the
sweetest of dreams tonight.
Sparkle!
Hit this button if
you wanna reply.
If ya got somethin'
to say, say it!
It's not like I
want him to baby me!
[HINO] What are you so
upset about, you sweet child?
[CHIHIRO]
Don't call me that!
Hey, I'm home!
It's kinda weird coming
home with nobody here.
I'm not used to it
being so quiet.
[sneezes]
Could someone please
shift that mannequin
a little to the right?
The fabric really pops
in the spotlight.
[STAFF 3A]
Yes, of course, sir.
What a talented young man he is!
His hard work is sure to make
this bridal fair a huge success!
Thank you so much.
Always happy to help.
I'd be honored if he'd attend
the press conference tomorrow.
You'll make that
happen, won't you?
I'll do everything I can, sir.
Please excuse me.
Oh-- Sure!
[phone buzzing]
Another one?
[CHIHIRO] Doesn't he have
anything better to do?
What a weirdo!
So, Hino said just press reply.
What's the point of even
telling him about it right now?
[TAKEI] Considering how
he's scared of dogs,
it was really cool he let you
keep the puppy in the house
while you looked
for a new owner.
[CHIHIRO] I guess I'll
just go back to cleaning.
I'm so exhausted!
I wish Chi was here to
cook us something delicious.
I thought I saw you
eating earlier.
I'm not counting
that meal because
I couldn't fully enjoy it
while worrying about home.
I'm sure he's so lonely
he doesn't even know
what to do with himself.
Except...
I've sent him several
messages, but no response.
[KEIICHIRO]
Maybe you sent too many?
Well, so?
I'm sure he'll
reach out to you soon.
See you tomorrow.
[MADOKA]
Right. See ya.
[CHIHIRO sneezes]
Ugh, I feel hot.
Hope I don't have a fever.
I should get in bed.
[CHIHIRO] It's kinda
creepy in here at night.
[CHIHIRO sighs]
Aw, man.
Could have got some real
work done but, naturally,
I come down with a stupid bug.
No one's around. I'm freezing.
[CHIHIRO]
The house is so... empty.
Everything's too still.
I can't relax.
[phone buzzes]
Unreal.
I told him he didn't
need to worry about me.
[MADOKA] You can call
any time you need, okay?
[phone rings]
Ah! I just missed Chihiro!
[ringing]
[OPERATOR 3A] The person you
have called is unavailable.
Please hang up and try again.
[CHIHIRO]
Ah...
Don't be dumb.
There's no reason
to bother him at work
just because you feel
like you're dying.
I'll rest.
It's not a big deal.
It's just a little cold.
I'm okay.
If I sleep now,
morning will come soon.
[CHIYO humming]
What are you doing, young man?
You're too sick
to get out of bed.
Are you trying
to cook something?
Some rice porridge
for my sick boy.
I hope you're hungry,
because it's almost ready!
Ah! Uh, maybe you should
use the rice cooker next time!
[CHIHIRO] Aren't you worried
you'll be late for work?
I took the day off
to be with you.
A little cold isn't
that big of a deal.
Listen up. If you
underestimate a "little" cold,
it could come back to bite you!
Less worrying and more rest.
But, wait--
[CHIHIRO]
Please.
I'd do anything to have
you here with me, Mom.
[CHIYO] Everything will be fine.
There's no need to worry.
Chihiro? Are you
feeling all right?
Huh?
[yells] Wha...?
I think you have a fever.
When did you get sick?
[CHIHIRO]
H-How did you get here?
Easy! Taxi.
And it only took me three hours!
A taxi? How much did that cost?
You're insane! You realize
how ridiculous that is?
[MADOKA]
You called me. Isn't that right?
Then I couldn't reach you.
So that's why you came home?
It was just a phone call.
Ah.
I'm glad you came back.
[MADOKA]
Yes. Me, too.
[CHIHIRO] Oh, yeah.
I still have to thank him.
The dog. I'm sorry.
You really wanted it.
Don't worry about it.
Not like I have time
to take care of a dog
when I'm always
cleaning up after you.
Oh, I see.
I apologize for all the trouble.
Listen.
It means a lot that you let
the dog stay here at all.
So thank you.
Uh--
[sighs]
It was nothing.
[MADOKA humming]
Oh! Good morning!
I hope you're hungry,
because this rice porridge
is almost ready!
You're kidding me.
Is this what it's like
to have déjà vu?
[laughs]
Seems like your fever went down.
What a relief.
What about work?
Aren't they expecting you
to get back there?
Uh-- It's no problem!
I handled everything.
You got out of it after all.
[laughs] If the shoe fits!
[MADOKA]
I'm leaving the rest to you!
When push comes to shove,
feel free to use
this if you need.
When he gets home,
he's going to be
really angry with me,
so I need you
to play up the sickness, okay?
No way!
All you did was gripe
about that trip!
You probably got me
sick on purpose!
[MADOKA]
What are you saying?
I'm the innocent one here!
[CHIHIRO]
Sure you are!
You owe both of us an apology!
[KEIICHIRO]
Chihiro.
I'm very happy to hear that
you're feeling better now.
[CHIHIRO]
Thanks a lot, Keiichiro!
How did things go at the
bridal fair after he left?
[KEIICHIRO]
All right.
I put on the terrible
wig Madoka left for me
and said "Thank you
all so much!"
and a few other things
in an annoying voice.
[CHIHIRO] I still can't
believe he expects you to do
stuff like that.
[KEIICHIRO] I do what I have to,
to fulfill my obligations,
but if he ever wants
to me do something
like that again, I'll stuff
the wig down his throat.
[CHIHIRO] I really feel
for you, Keiichiro.
Putting all that
aside, next time is
"What One Likes,
One Will Do Well"!
[KEIICHIRO]
Everyone.
We would be pleased to have
you join us again soon!
[CHIHIRO]
Please do!