[NIHONGOU]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
Born from the heart of swords,
we travel through time
to intercept and eliminate them.
But not till I get my saké!
[KASHUU, YASUSADA]
This is a tale of the legendary
Sword Warriors
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in a certain citadel.
Finally, we're all right here.
Three great spears
together at last.
All right, so what
should we do now?
Ha. Only one thing to do!
[NIHONGOU]
Get wasted!
No, we stab things!
It was a joke, man.
Yeah, right.
[laughing]
Okay, party's over!
Don't you have
something better to do?
[NIHONGOU]
♪ Time for saké. ♪
♪ Let's all drink. ♪
That's handy!
Now I've got a
high vantage point!
[OTEGINE laughing]
[TONBOKIRI] And then,
they lived happily ever after.
The end.
Thank you for reading
the story to me.
That's my favorite book
in the whole citadel.
I'm glad you shared it with me.
Did you get it from the master?
Uh-huh.
It's kind of a shame;
I've never seen a bluebird
around here, though.
[TONBOKIRI] What do you think
the lesson of the story was?
[GOKOTAI]
Oh! I just remembered something!
[TONBOKIRI]
That was sudden.
Does it have to
do with the book?
[GOKOTAI]
Not exactly.
I need to grab
a thing from my room.
I'll be right back.
[NIHONGOU gasps]
I'm sorry!
Stop that!
Uh...
What's wrong?
[TIGER CUB mewling]
I'll take him away.
[NIHONGOU]
Hey!
Gokotai!
What in the hell?
He's sensitive, that's all.
And he was doing
so well today, too.
Come on. It's not my fault.
[HAKATA]
Then whose fault is it?
All right, fine,
I'm afraid of tigers, okay?
My former master had
a lot of trouble with them.
More trouble than he had
with his enemies, even.
So when I see a tiger,
I'm forced to relive
some very
uncomfortable memories.
Even a little baby
tiger like that?
It's pretty much a house cat.
Either way, it's a shame,
'cause Gokotai wants to be
friends with you really bad.
"Ni-Nihongou's so cool.
He's like, everything
that I'm not," he said.
[MIKAZUKI]
Simply tell him the truth--
that the tiger startled you.
An explanation and a simple
apology will rectify everything.
Everything except for my pride.
[HAKATA gasps]
Look, it's a bluebird!
[TONBOKIRI]
Oh, is it?
[OTEGINE]
I'm not the expert.
How lucky!
The Bluebird of Happiness
has come here to see us!
That is lucky!
A bluebird is a bluebird.
Aren't good things supposed
to happen if you catch one?
Guess he's way ahead
of me on that one.
[TONBOKIRI]
What's the plan?
You wanna grab it for Gokotai?
Can we drop it, already?
[NIHONGOU grunts]
Otegine!
Come over here and help!
With what?
[NIHONGOU]
With the damn bird!
Just to remind you, I'm only
good at stabbing things.
Don't stab it!
I'm not!
[NIHONGOU]
Okay, kneel down here.
[BLUEBIRD yawns]
[NIHONGOU]
Now stand.
[OTEGINE]
This seems kind of iffy.
Okay, looks good.
Whoa...
[yelling]
[groaning]
[NIHONGOU] All right,
we'll get it next time for sure.
[OTEGINE]
What?
[NIHONGOU]
Kneel down again.
[OTEGINE]
I didn't sign up for this!
[MIKAZUKI laughs]
[NIHONGOU]
Eh, tough it out.
C'mon, walk forward a bit.
Aw, jeez!
[grunting]
Whoa!
Could you stop with
the dancing, please?
[grunting]
You're mine now, bird.
Son of a--
[gasps]
[NIHONGOU]
You gotta be kiddin' me!
I think it's making fun of us.
We should call it quits.
I mean, look, it's way up there.
Tonbokiri, come here!
Then what?
You climb on me, too?
[NIHONGOU]
Come on, we got this.
Him, then you, then me.
[TONBOKIRI]
Is that even possible?
Wait!
Could I not be on
the bottom this time?
You're always lugging around
that big, heavy spear,
aren't ya?
We're way lighter than that!
[OTEGINE growls]
There's no way
this will end well.
Uh, hey, are you all right?
[OTEGINE]
Yeah...
[TONBOKIRI] Being in the
middle's a lot harder
--than I thought.
--[OTEGINE] Whoa!
[NIHONGOU] Stop wobbling
and start marching!
Okay!
[TONBOKIRI]
Why are you dancing?
If I were younger, I'd
like to try that myself.
[NIHONGOU]
We're almost there!
One more step!
Hurry up!
Almost!
Got ya!
Huh?!
[yelling]
[NIHONGOU yells]
Otegine! No! Stop!
Not likely!
[NIHONGOU yelling]
Okay!
Wow, they're so incredible!
I love his droopy little
eyes; they're super cute.
Are you sleepy, Hanatarou?
[KASHUU]
What a good boy.
[yelling]
[KASHUU]
Ow!
Kiyomitsu?
Are you okay?
[yelling]
Kane...
Can you go ahead and hang
the clean sheets out to dry
on that clothesline over there?
Of course!
Just leave it to me!
[yelling]
The sheet got away!
Uh-huh.
This sucks. Why do I
have to do this crap?
[yelling]
Huh? What the--?
[yelling continues]
[OOKURIKARA grunts]
[distant yelling]
[HASEBE yelling]
[HASEBE grunting]
Stop that!
Whatever it is, stop it!
[OTEGINE]
I can't stop it!
[NIHONGOU]
There he is!
We can salvage this!
Make us fly, Otegine!
[OTEGINE]
Not happening, man!
The clothesline!
Use it like a pole vault!
I told you!
I'm only good at
stabbing things!
I was never meant... to... fly!
[yelling]
[NIHONGOU]
I won't lose this time!
Gotcha!
[NIHONGOU]
Damn you, bird!
[yelling]
Bluebird! Don't sit there!
My spear is so sharp
that even a dragonfly
would be cut in two
on its point!
[gasp]
[BLUEBIRD laughs]
What the hell?!
[NIHONGOU]
Oh! Aww...
[laughing]
Seems like the bluebird
is the winner this time.
[MIKAZUKI laughs]
Too bad for them, but
at least we got a good show!
Gokotai?
Um... I'm back.
[NIHONGOU]
What've you got there?
[GOKOTAI]
I-It's a protection charm.
Uh, everyone in the citadel
is making their own these days.
You pick out something
that's special to you
and you put it inside the pouch.
I-I thought you
might not have one,
since you haven't been
at the citadel for long,
so I brought an extra.
Could I maybe
borrow that feather?
[NIHONGOU]
Oh. Sure.
[GOKOTAI]
I... I hope you like it.
Thanks, kiddo.
Happiness is always
there waiting.
You only need to look.
That's the lesson
of the story, isn't it?
Umm...
Speaking of happiness, I really
enjoyed your acrobatics.
[NIHONGOU]
Acrobatics?
Do... Do you think
you could do it
one more time for me?
Once was enough already!
[ALL laughing]
Ah, splendid.
Life is splendid.
[crying]
You hear that?
Someone is crying.
It's kinda creepy.
It's awfully late.
I wonder who it could be?
Wha--What if it's a ghost?
[crying continues]
It's getting closer.
Hey, guys?
[sniffles]
[HIRANO]
Akita?
What's the matter, Akita?
What are you doing up so late?
I just saw a ghost
in the hallway.
Are you sure?
[AKITA]
I was walking to the bathroom
when I saw this floating
white shadow thing.
It's like it was walking,
but it wasn't making any steps.
It was scary,
but I followed it anyway.
--And then--
--[NAMAZUO] Bwah!
[scream]
Don't scream like that;
people are sleeping!
It seemed like the thing to do.
Please... don't scare
me like that.
So, continue the story.
All of a sudden,
I lost sight of it--
it was like it vanished!
Then I knew.
It's a ghost!
Oh, yeah?
Oh. Please, no...
So, does this mean that
the citadel is haunted?
How are you even
supposed to deal with this?
We gotta do something.
How 'bout we ask
Ichi for advice?
No way.
We'll handle this on our own.
[HIRANO gasps]
Yeah, we'd better.
We were just bragging
about getting strong.
We have to walk the walk, too.
Yeah, we can't let Ichi down.
What's one ghost, anyway?
Well...
It's scary!
[YAGEN] Unfortunately,
we have no experience
dealing with the undead.
If only we knew where to start.
I think I know
someone who does.
We'll go and ask the expert.
We'll be right back.
[HAKATA]
Who were they talking about?
Nikkari Aoe,
if I had to guess.
I don't think I know this story.
[YAGEN] They say that
he was used to strike down
the ghost of a laughing woman.
That's actually how
he earned his name.
So yeah, he's the expert.
Then there's nothing
to worry about after all!
He'll make that ghost
double-dead in no time
and then we can all get
right back to sleep!
Let's hope so.
[NAMAZUO]
Hey, Nikkari?
Are you awake?
Yes? What is it
at this late hour?
We've got a ghost emergency.
How intriguing.
There's a haunting
in the citadel?
[NAMAZUO]
That's right!
Akita saw some white
floaty thing in the hallway.
[NIKKARI] I can't say I've
ever experienced anything
like that here,
but I'll take your word for it.
Think you can slay it?
[NIKKARI]
Well... maybe.
I've defeated one.
Bet I can defeat another.
[YAGEN] I know it's late.
Thanks for coming.
Think nothing of it--
I'm quite curious about
this ghost myself.
It's a rare opportunity,
if nothing else.
We'll call ourselves the
Ghost Extermination Rangers!
The Ghost Extermination
what, now?
Me first!
Namazuo! Blue Ranger!
Huh?
No good?
Oh, I get it,
we need to pick a color!
Hakata, Gold!
Midare. I'm pink!
And I'm pink too!
[ATSUSHI]
Guess I'll be black.
Silver, of course.
Purple Ranger.
Yellow Ranger!
And I'm brown!
I'm the White Ranger!
Green Ranger,
reporting for duty.
We don't have a red one!
There always has
to be a red one!
Ah, we'll be fine.
Yeah, probably.
We are Nikkari Aoe and
the Awataguchi swords!
Ghost Extermination Rangers, go!
Everyone, take good
care of your candles.
We'll split up to search faster,
but call me immediately
if you see the ghost.
Aw... This is too scary!
Maybe we should stop.
What, after that long intro?
Good one.
Maybe I'll start a
ghost busting company.
Wait till the ghost
is busted, at least!
Let's go.
Right! Come on!
Silver and Blue.
Here!
I think I have just
the plan to settle this.
We'll lay a net
joined to a pulley here.
And when the ghost comes out,
we'll tug on the rope and
capture it in the net.
[NAMAZUO] Wait...
You can catch ghosts in nets?
Slaying it would
be such a waste.
I'm trying a different
approach this time.
We can save extermination
for later, if we'd like.
I'm dying to see what a
surprised ghost looks like.
That didn't answer
my question, but okay.
Nikkari, I think
I found the ghost!
[GOKOTAI]
It's this way.
[yells]
[NIKKARI] It seems there
really is a ghost here.
I didn't suspect we
would find it so easily.
Huh?
Wait. Tsurumaru?
Are you guys having
some kind of night party?
[GOKOTAI]
Is that Nakigitsune's fox?
[TSURUMARU]
Uh-huh.
I guess he must have
gotten lost and wandered
into my room by accident.
I woke up covered in sweat,
'cause this little fuzzball
decided to fall asleep
right on top of my head.
[GOKOTAI] So you were just
taking him back then, huh?
You know it really does
take a lot to surprise me.
But a surprise from this
guy is always welcome.
[yawns]
I'm gonna go return him
now and get back to bed.
[MAEDA]
Nikkari!
Uh... I think the ghost
is talking now.
[NIKKARI]
Interesting!
And did you happen to
catch what it was saying?
It sounded like
it was counting.
Then perhaps it's
the ghost of Okiku,
counting the plates she
was accused of stealing
before she was murdered.
Is that real?
[VOICE]
Seven...
Would any ghosts
like to and come play?
[VOICE]
Nine...
You'd better answer,
or I'll cut you down.
[DOUDANUKI]
And ten!
[NIKKARI] Why are you
doing midnight pullups?
I was bored and I
couldn't really sleep.
Now, only 970 to go!
You realize if
you do that many,
it'll be morning before
you're finished.
[DOUDANUKI] Wanna have
a sparring match instead?
[MAEDA]
Uh...
I never knew it was
so lively at night.
[HAKATA]
It's the ghost!
Do something, Nikkari!
Okay.
[NIKKARI]
Looks like a big one.
Might I ask what
you're doing over there?
[screaming]
I'm entirely too drunk
to be cooking in the dark.
Oh! Goodness!
It would seem I have
an audience! [hiccup]
Jirou!
What the heck are you
doing with that knife
in the middle of the night?
Tomato juice?
I'm making midnight snacks!
I'll clean up when I can
actually see what I'm doing.
But for now, it's drinking time!
[humming]
We have found the target!
White ghost, straight ahead!
[gasp]
[menacing chuckle]
You had better not
let me down this time.
[NIKKARI]
Face me, apparition!
I'll send you to the afterlife!
[KASEN]
Huh?
Kasen?
Surely the laundry
could wait until morning.
Normally, yes.
But this time it's a
covert laundry operation.
I'm afraid that you've lost me.
[KASEN]
This is Yamanbagiri's cloak.
As I'm sure you've noticed,
he never lets it out of
his sight during the day.
So I'm required to
take extreme measures
and wash it while he's sleeping.
Of course, I'd prefer
if the white was brighter.
But if I'm too obvious
about it, he'll notice.
So "clean," but not
"suspiciously clean."
Feels like you're
doing us all a favor.
I always wondered why
that thing smells so nice,
even though it looks so awful.
I fear it's too clean this time;
perhaps I should dirty it up.
[NIKKARI] I think it's safe to
say now that there is no ghost.
I don't blame Akita, though--
it's late and he was tired.
We caught the ghost!
I set the trap like you
said and it worked out!
[NIKKARI]
Huh?
I know it was my idea,
but still, that's a surprise.
[AKITA gasps]
That's it!
That's the ghost I saw!
[NIKKARI]
It's not moving.
Let's see your face, shall we?
Kosetsu? What's going on here?
Oh, no, why's he up there?
My apologies.
I appears I've caused
quite the commotion tonight.
[KOUSETSU] I had gone
to the bathroom with Sayo.
But because of the
recent room change,
I was unable to navigate back
to our quarters in the dark.
Thus, my wandering
in the hallway.
That's why you
fell for the trap.
Hold on. I'll help you.
[KOUSETSU]
No, that won't be necessary.
We're fine.
In the net?
Oh, I see.
Sayo does seem rather
comfortable in there,
doesn't he?
Your trap is rather
like a hammock, actually.
It makes for a suitable bed.
And it would be a
pity to disturb Sayo.
Cut us free in the morning
if we're still here.
All right.
Well, there you have it.
Now, time to go back to bed.
[GROUP]
Okay!
Thanks for helping
us solve the case.
Someday the Ghost
Extermination Rangers
may be needed again.
The Green Ranger shall
be happy to heed your call
at any time.
See you in the morning.
[NIKKARI]
Three.
[AKITA]
Good night.
[NIKKARI]
Four.
[ATSUSHI yawns]
Good night.
[NIKKARI]
Five.
[MAEDA, HIRANO]
Good night.
[NIKKARI]
Six, seven.
[GOKOTAI]
G-Good night.
[NIKKARI]
Eight.
--[MIDARE] Night.
--[NIKKARI] Nine.
--[HAKATA] Sleep well.
--[NIKKARI] Ten.
[GHOST]
Good night.
[NIKKARI]
Eleven.
Who was that last one?
[GHOST laughing]