[UGUISUMARU]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
Born from the heart of swords,
we travel through time to
intercept and eliminate them.
I know. It's complicated.
[KASHUU, YASUSADA]
This is a tale of the legendary
Sword Warriors
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in a certain citadel.
--[YASUSADA grunts]
--[swords clash]
[KASHUU]
Ha!
[YASUSADA grunts]
[bird chirps]
[UGUISUMARU whistles]
[HASEBE]
I thought that was a real bird!
[UGUISUMARU] I was trying
to call a nightingale,
but it seems I
called you instead.
[HASEBE] I was trying to catch
a nightingale for the master,
but I caught you instead,
so thanks, Uguisumaru.
Does that mean I have
to be the master's pet?
Hmph. I would
need a bigger cage.
[UGUISUMARU]
On an unrelated note,
that tree paints
quite the picture.
Do you know what it's called?
[HASEBE] You mean what
kind of tree is it? Hm...
[UGUISUMARU]
It must be quite rare if even
an old sword like me
hasn't seen one before.
How peculiar.
What are they
looking for out there?
There's nothing.
[HIRANO]
I found one!
[MAEDA]
So they are real!
Of course!
The master was
the one who told me.
It's the first I've ever seen.
They are pretty rare.
I think they're only
one in ten thousand,
so you could look all
day and not find one.
They say they're good luck.
Wouldn't hurt to keep one
around in case that's true.
Wow.
[HIRANO] I was thinking of
giving it to Uguisumaru.
I'm sure he'd be happy,
but does he actually
need any good luck?
I've been too nervous
to talk to him,
and this would make
for a good excuse.
[HIRANO humming]
--[crashing noise]
--[yelling]
[DOUDANUKI]
Son of a--
Is something wrong?
I dropped a weight on my
foot and it hurts like hell!
Oh, man, are you okay?
[DOUDANUKI] And when I
jumped in the bath earlier,
the water was ice cold!
Then the lid came
off my spice jar
when I tried to put
some on my udon!
[HIRANO]
Ugh!
I've had nothing
but bad luck today!
That does sound
rather unfortunate.
I was going to give
this to someone else,
but I think maybe
you need it more.
What, a flower?
Consider it a good luck charm.
So do I, like, eat it?
How does this work?
[HIRANO]
Um, no, it's not food.
You don't have to do anything.
Four-leaf clovers are lucky
just on their own.
Uh-huh...
[DOUDANUKI]
Well, all right, then.
So why don't you take this?
No, offense,
but you've got wimpy arms.
You might wanna work on that.
I think I'll be okay.
[DOUDANUKI]
We're weapons.
It's our job to
be strong, right?
[nervous chuckle]
[HIRANO]
Okay, then. Thank you.
[DOUDANUKI]
No prob.
[KASEN gasps]
[KASEN]
Oh, Hirano.
You have a paperweight!
Perfect timing if
I've ever seen it!
Could you bring that
over here for me, please?
[HIRANO] I'm afraid
it might be too heavy.
No. It's just lovely!
The wind has been a pain.
Well if that's the problem,
wouldn't it be easier to
close the sliding door?
I must be in tune with the
seasons to create my work.
Bothersome though it may be,
the breath of nature
guides my hand.
[KASEN]
Ha!
[TIGER CUB mewls]
Oh! Hold on, wait a second!
I'm so sorry,
they're crazy today!
--[KASEN, HIRANO chuckle]
--[TIGER CUBS mewl]
[GOKOTAI]
I really am sorry.
It's fine.
Also...
Since you were kind enough
to give me that weight,
why don't you each take
one of my books in return?
[KASEN] And take the tigers
with you too, please.
[GOKOTAI] I'll watch them
more closely, I promise.
Ah... This was
very kind of you.
[HIRANO]
Hmm...
I'm sure this is fascinating.
But I think it might
be a little much for me.
[HIRANO]
Yeah, no thank you.
I'm too young.
What's that?
Oh, it's an anatomy
book, I guess.
There are lots of pictures.
[YAGEN]
Well, that's handy.
Where did you get it?
[HIRANO]
Kasen gave it to me.
Ah. How generous of him!
I bet my medical practice
would be much safer
if I had a book like this.
Do you think you could
lend it to me, perhaps?
Huh?
[YAGEN]
I'll give you this in exchange.
What am I looking at, exactly?
My latest masterpiece,
of course!
It lowers fevers
and stops coughing.
In theory, that is.
You're not quite
selling me on this.
Well, it's guaranteed
to help more than it hurts.
[HIRANO]
Uh-huh...
[TSURUMARU panting]
Hirano!
This is so bad,
even I'm stressing out!
It's Yamanbagiri!
[HIRANO]
He isn't dying, is he?
[TSURUMARU] I don't know
how this stuff works,
but it should heal
you up just like magic!
Let's see.
[TSURUMARU]
Come on!
Take it in one shot!
I don't know about "magic,"
but Yagen said that
it should lower fevers.
So I'd be careful though--Uh!
Off I go.
[groans]
[TSURUMARU]
Aw, crap! Yamanbagiri!
[HIRANO]
Please, say something!
[TSURUMARU]
Yaman--
Don't touch my cloak!
No one's touching
anything. Are you okay?
They said they wouldn't
let me into heaven
unless I cleaned my cloak!
Then you keep it as
dirty as you want to!
Anyway, I'm better now.
That cleared my
hangover right up.
[HIRANO]
Wait, what?
He had way too much to drink
at the last welcoming party.
[HIRANO]
Oh. I... see.
[YAMANBAGIRI]
Here, as thanks.
Ah!
Are you sure? It's beautiful!
It was Kasen's.
He thought if I put it on,
he could steal my
cloak and clean it.
He should've known better; that
thing is way too fancy for me.
You take it.
[HIRANO]
Thanks!
[NIKKARI] That cloak you've
got looks nice and warm.
Are you saying
you're cold, Nikkari?
[chuckles]
[NIKKARI] That cloak you've
got looks nice and warm.
[HIRANO] Wow, not being
very subtle is he.
Oh, wait. Here.
Why don't you
take this in return?
Okay, but what is it?
[NIKKARI] A beloved companion
to embrace at night,
healing your worries and
giving you the comfort
of a mother and lover alike.
It's a body pillow.
You've never heard of them?
I've got this lovely
gold ball, too,
but I won't let anyone
else touch it.
Can you please just
call it gold armor?
I can feel your warmth.
What's that?
[HIRANO] Oh, uh...
It's a body pillow.
I don't really have
any need for it, though.
[SAYO]
Big brother.
[SOUZA]
Do you like it?
Other brother.
Do you mind giving
him this, Hirano?
It seems that it reminds him
of our brother from long ago.
Fine with me.
[SOUZA]
Here, let's trade.
This is the key to an
old playmate of mine.
Thank you, I think.
I'm clearly a
national treasure.
How could they put someone
like me on field duty?
It's awful.
[HIRANO]
Um, is this it?
[HACHISUKA]
Hirano!
Please tell me you've come to
save me from this drudgery!
[HIRANO]
Oh, hi, Hachisuka.
Souza gave me the key to this,
whatever it is.
That machine's a
little big for you.
Perhaps you should let me
take it for a spin instead.
[HACHISUKA laughing]
[HACHISUKA] There. Now that
is much more glamorous.
I daresay that was even fun.
If you would
let me have this,
I would be deeply
indebted to you.
If it means that much to you,
then sure, you can have it.
Please, take this.
It's nothing fancy, but I assure
you, it's quite delicious.
Uguisumaru.
[UGUISUMARU]
Hello, Hirano.
[HIRANO] Here. Some cake
to have with your tea.
How very thoughtful of you.
These were originally
from Portugal, I believe.
[HIRANO]
Oh...!
I spy some castella !
I've never actually
had castella before,
but I feel as if we were
brought together by fate!
I'm sure he wouldn't
mind sharing with you.
[MUTSUNOKAMI] This is western
civilization's greatest
contribution to Japan!
I'm truly enlightened! Yes!
And you know what else
came from the west?
Photography! So let's
commemorate this with a picture!
[HIRANO] Ah! What are
you doing to my face?!
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Just one sec.
Faces show up
better with this stuff.
Okay, now eat cake
and look happy!
Is this good?
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Yeah. Now freeze and smile!
Can I have a little
sip of tea, at least?
[MUTSUNOKAMI] That'll
make the picture blurry.
Just, uh, a little bit longer.
[UGUISUMARU, HIRANO laugh]
[HIRANO] It was kind of
a long road to get here,
but taking a photo with
both of us smiling together
is worth a thousand
four leaf clovers.
Sometimes, things just work out.
[UGUISUMARU]
Can we move now? Please?
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
No. Stop talking.
[KASHUU]
Ugh, I'm exhausted.
[YASUSADA]
Good job, though.
Something going on?
Just tigers.
[YAGEN] I wish Ichi was
here to share this with us,
to see how happy everyone is.
[YASUSADA]
Who is Ichi?
Ichigo Hitofuri. Yagen and
the others' older brother.
Sayo seems to be
having fun, too.
Our brother Kousetsu would be
pleased to see his smile,
I'm sure.
For the record, Souza
has an older brother,
but he doesn't talk
about him very much.
Is there a reason?
Because Sayo misses him.
And they don't know if and when
they'll ever see him again.
We don't know who will
make it here, after all.
[HASEBE]
Can you spare a minute?
I have a question for you.
Does anyone here know
what kind of tree this is?
[KASHUU]
Uh...
[HASEBE] Kashuu, you've
been around the longest.
I pride myself
on being informative,
but you probably know things
about the citadel that I don't.
Not about trees.
And I've barely
been here a year.
Uguisumaru asked me earlier.
It's been bugging me all day.
I know it's not a zelkova.
Not a hackberry tree, either.
And if it was a cherry tree,
wouldn't it be blooming by now?
Aww...
I was looking forward
to cherry blossoms!
[HASEBE]
Can't help you there.
So it's not a cherry tree, huh?
Well, that's a letdown.
I'm so sad now.
You guys really
like cherry trees.
[HASEBE] As soon as its leaves
come in, we'll have our answer.
I feel like I'm the
bearer of bad news,
but it's not looking good
for Team Cherry Tree.
I won't give up hope.
Yeah. It sure would
be nice, huh?
I agree! That's just
what this place needs.
Cherry tree.
There's not some way to make
it a cherry tree, is there?
Would you stop being ridiculous?
You know better than that.
Wasn't there a fairy
tale about an old man
that made trees bloom with
the ashes of his magic dog?
I've heard of that.
Oh, yeah!
Oh.
Would you get your
head out of the clouds?
That story is absolute nonsense.
It'll be fine;
we'll figure something out.
I doubt that!
What if we tried
hypnotizing the tree?
[HONEBAMI]
You are a cherry tree.
I-I am a cherry tree...
[HASEBE] This is getting
disturbing! Stop it!
There is one option left,
but it isn't a pretty one.
What is it?
[SOUZA] I once heard
that beautiful cherry trees
often have corpses
buried beneath their roots.
[ALL]
Huh?
So if we could produce
one such corpse...
[ALL]
No, no, no.
[HASEBE] That's far too
morbid, and you know it!
That's so cool.
What if, instead
of killing someone,
we make a wish on
the tree itself?
[KASHUU]
I'm afraid I don't follow.
You all have one?
[ALL]
Uh, yes?
So, what are we
doing with these?
If we want cherry
blossoms to bloom,
we should write that on
these papers and hang them
on the branches of the tree.
[HASEBE] Ha! And what's that
supposed to accomplish?
If enough people wish
for the same thing,
then maybe the tree can
make a miracle happen.
The tree is fine.
Can we stop it with
the fairy tales already?
Oh, I don't know.
It wouldn't hurt
to try, at least.
I have heard that if you put
your feelings into writing,
it can make a wish come true.
You think so?
You're just making this
stuff up, aren't you?
It's worth a shot!
If we each place all of our
wishes directly on the tree,
it just might work!
Probably.
[ATSUSHI]
We won't know till we try!
[GOKOTAI] So, is that
like wishing on a star?
[MAEDA]
We're making it up as we go.
Great!
We'll write so many that we'll
cover the tree in wishes.
That sounds like a plan to me.
Ugh. I give up.
Okay!
If we're all in agreement, I'll
go get the writing supplies.
We'll do a hundred papers each!
[ALL]
A hundred?
[YASUSADA] The more wishes
the better, right?
[ALL chattering]
[KASHUU]
'Kay! Better get writing.
[YAGEN] I hope you're
ready to bloom, tree!
[NAMAZUO] I wish that cherry
blossoms would bloom on you.
"Blossoms, please."
"A whole bunch of them, please."
Okay. That's three down!
[GOKOTAI]
Uh, me too! Almost done.
[AKITA]
Yamatonokami!
More paper, please!
[YASUSADA]
You got it!
I wish cherry blossoms
would bloom on your branches.
And soon.
[UGUISUMARU chuckles]
This is sort of fun, isn't it?
[YAGEN] Hey, look!
I drew a picture on mine.
How did they rope
me into this mess?
[YASUSADA]
Here's some more, Hasebe.
We're counting on you!
Keep up the
good work, you guys.
We've gotta do a thousand each!
[ALL]
A thousand each?
[NAMAZUO yawns]
I'm beat.
[HONEBAMI]
I can't feel my hand.
[NAMAZUO]
Wait, that's not about the tree.
[ATSUSHI]
Hey, don't look!
In full bloom already.
So pretty.
It was worth the effort.
So that was your plan.
The backside of
the paper is pink,
so it looks like
cherry blossoms.
[chuckles]
They worked hard.
I have heard that if you put
your feelings into writing,
it can make a wish come true.
You think so?
[YASUSADA] All these wishes,
like shining petals.
Everyone's dreams.
Wait, is that... a bud?
They're... real!
Real cherry blossoms!
[ALL]
Hm?
What? Really?
He's right! They're real!
Guys. They're everywhere!
They weren't here
just a second ago.
Huh... Guess wishes
do come true!
Oh, my, we actually
managed to wish the tree
into blooming somehow?
Yeah.
I-I-I have to tell
the master right now!
[HASEBE]
Master!
Someone once said to me,
"If you ever find a tree
you've never seen before,
it might be a ten thousand
leaf cherry tree."
[DOUDANUKI]
Yeah? What does that mean?
It's a miraculous
tree that only blooms
every ten thousand years.
And those who see its blossoms
will have their wishes granted.
[DOUDANUKI]
Don't see that every day, huh?
[YASUSADA] I don't know if this
tree really is magic or not,
but it sure would be nice if
everyone's wishes came true.
[YASUSADA]
Including mine.
[YASUSADA] Until then, all I can
do is keep getting stronger.