[YASUSADA]
Souji!
Damn it.
Why is Yamatonokami late?
Maybe he's hiding somewhere
so he won't get spotted
and change history.
Meeting up here was his idea.
[HORIKAWA]
You look worried.
Do you know something
that we don't?
You're imagining things.
[NIHONGOU (SONG)]
♪ Saké all night, all day ♪
♪ and some the next day
and the next. ♪
Heh. ♪ Drink away
all your tears. ♪
[HAKATA (SONG)] ♪ Drink till
you can't hold your spear! ♪
[NIHONGOU (SONG)] ♪ Drink till
you don't have no fear, ♪
♪ something something
rhymes with spear. ♪
♪ I may bleed
and I may bruise, ♪
♪ but nobody can
take my booze. ♪
That was a good one!
Okay, let's have the
Shinsengumi swords sing next!
Have you forgotten?
They went on a mission
together to the Ikedaya Inn.
[JIROUTACHI]
Oh yeah, that thing.
They sure are taking
their sweet time.
Here, lemme do
one in the meantime.
[JIROUTACHI]
Knock yourself out, Otegine!
Four rhymes and the next
round of drinks are on me!
Heh! Any less and you're paying!
[OTEGINE]
Say what?
[laughing]
We've never played
outside with the master.
Do you think they
would enjoy that?
We won't know unless
we ask, I guess.
I know you don't want to
leave your room, Master,
but you really shouldn't
spend the whole day
in your sleepwear.
I sewed this for you myself.
Perhaps you'd like to try it on?
Also, you've been wearing your
bedclothes for several days now.
Sounds like the master has
their hands full with Hasebe.
Or maybe it's the
other way around.
I hope I can be
attendant someday
and spend time with the master.
That would be nice.
Huh? Is something
wrong with the picture?
Actually, I think there is!
[AKITA gasps]
[GOKOTAI]
Y-Yamatonokami?
He... He disappeared!
Whoa, you're right!
What does it mean?
I don't know, but he's
gone in all these, too.
[NAKIGITSUNE]
That's weird.
It's just Yamatonokami
every time.
You don't think something bad
happened on their mission,
do you?
I wouldn't worry.
This is probably
nothing but a prank.
Who would do that?
[ICHIGO] Someone who
wants to get a reaction
out of Yamatonokami,
I would assume.
That's fine, but the
timing is kinda bad.
I hope you're right.
But how can we tell?
[MAEDA]
Let's find out who did it.
[AKITA]
We'll ask around.
[ATSUSHI]
Let's go.
--[MAEDA] Good idea.
--[MIDARE] Let's do it.
[ICHIGO] Let's hope this isn't
just an empty reassurance.
[SHISHIOU]
Me?
I swear on my old man,
I didn't lay a finger on them!
And even if I did want
to make him disappear,
I wouldn't know where to start.
[KASEN]
Who let Yamanbagiri drink?
You know better!
Stop it!
Your cloak will get
filthy rolling like that!
Grass stains are
serious business!
I'm just a copy.
Who even cares
if I'm filthy, huh?
[KASEN]
What does that even mean?
No more, please,
I'm begging you,
this is complete torment for me!
Have mercy!
Stay clean!
[URASHIMA]
Hey! Hachisuka!
Did you see this photo?
[HACHISUKA] Ah, you
look quite splendid shining
in the summer sun.
I would expect no less from
an authentic Koutetsu.
No, not me!
Look at who's
not in the picture!
[HACHISUKA]
I don't know.
Is this a riddle?
It's Kamekichi!
We need to see your
handsome face, don't we?
[HACHISUKA]
I see...
That's not the reaction
I was hoping for.
[URASHIMA]
It's like you read my mind!
[AIZEN] If I messed with
those pictures, may Aizen Myoou
strike me dead!
I guess this photo's
ruined for good now, huh?
Akashi. Was it you, maybe?
[AKASHI] I wouldn't go to
that much trouble for anything.
[sigh]
[HIRANO] And look,
he's not in this one either!
You really think
this is a prank?
[UGUISUMARU]
Either that, or...
[HIRANO]
Or what?
Never mind.
He'll come back.
And we'll have castella cake,
just like before, right?
Why, of course.
You needn't worry about a thing.
'Kay!
[YAMABUSHI grunts]
Once again...
My roaring muscles
are in impeccable form!
[GOKOTAI]
Um, excuse me.
If you aren't too busy
with your manly stuff,
could you look at this?
[YAMABUSHI]
I must commend you, Doudanuki!
Your figure is splendid,
from your pectoralis major
to your serratus anterior.
I have absolutely no idea
what you're talking about,
but as long as I'm
strong, I'm happy.
I don't mean to brag,
but did either of you
notice how nice
my trapezius muscles are today?
[DOUDANUKI, YAMABUSHI]
Ah!
[SOUZA]
He's not in any of them.
[KOUSETSU]
No.
It's as if he's
completely vanished.
Do you know any reason
why someone might do this?
Huh. No.
[chuckles]
Well, okay then.
[LAUGHING BAG laughing]
I've got my own problems
to deal with here.
This thing is broken
and it won't stop.
[laughing continues]
[NIKKARI laughing]
You guys are freaking me out!
Just get rid of that thing!
Quick, before it spreads!
[GOKOTAI laughs]
Wish I could get
my bubbles to do that!
[YAGEN]
Fess up.
How did you erase Yamatonokami
from those photos and why?
You just assume it's me?
[laughs]
Nothing personal, Tsuru,
but it just seems like
something you would do.
[TSURUMARU]
For one, that's rude,
and for two, your
detective skills stink.
The culprit is always the one
who's least likely to do it.
So who is the last
person you think
would pull a prank
on Yamatonokami?
C'mon, you know
I don't like fun.
Don't you?
[RUBBER DUCK quacks]
[IMANOTSURUGI]
Yep. That is pretty weird.
All right. So now what?
I have a feeling this
isn't just some prank.
[ISHIKIRIMARU]
What do you think?
Frankly, I fear this means that
something has gone amiss
at the Ikedaya Inn.
Could you be more
specific, perhaps?
[MIKAZUKI] I believe it may
be the result of Yamatonokami
altering history in some way.
Do you think he
did it on purpose?
Then what would happen?
To begin,
a powerful new enemy
would be drawn into the battle.
One I fear they may
be unable to defeat.
You think he's already lost?
I wouldn't believe
that for an instant.
The bond of the Shinsengumi
swords will carry them
through any trial.
And besides,
whatever goes wrong,
I know Kashuu can fix it.
Yeah, you're right.
He's gotten through every
other mission just fine.
And in his case,
that makes for quite
a number of missions.
He has been at the citadel
the longest, after all.
[MIKAZUKI]
Let us keep the faith.
[RONIN 12A grunts]
[SOUJI growls]
Souji!
Are you okay?
[SOUJI coughing]
[YASUSADA grunts]
Please, be careful!
[SOUJI grunts]
Souji!
[SOUJI]
Stay back!
What are you doing?
Don't get sentimental now.
We're here to do what we must,
no matter what the cost.
Draw your sword.
[KONDOU]
Huh?
[SOUJI]
There's nothing to regret!
[SOUJI yells]
This is starting
to get worrisome.
[KEBIISHI growling]
I've never seen them before.
The Kebiishi?
Kebiishi?
They only appear whenever
they sense someone
severely meddling with
history, on either side.
[MUTSUNOKAMI] Does that mean
we did something wrong?
[KANESADA] They look like
they're out for blood.
How strong are these guys?
[KASHUU]
About my level, I'd say.
[KANESADA]
Oh, yeah?
[RONIN 12D groaning]
[KASHUU yelling]
[KEBIISHI 12C growling]
I'll be damned.
I'm all out.
[KEBIISHI 12D roars]
Kashuu!
Hold on!
I'm not finished yet!
I'm sorry.
Not everything is about you.
Kashuu!
Leave them to us and find him!
We won't let them step
foot inside the Inn!
All right!
[NAGASONE] Take care
of Yamatonokami for us.
[KANESADA grunts]
[HORIKAWA]
Kane!
Come on! Get up!
You're too strong and too cool
to let it end like this!
Besides, you're my partner!
Hijikata's swords
can handle anything
you throw at them, right?
We have to show the
others how it's done!
[KANESADA]
Kunihiro...
Don't make some fancy speech
like I'm already dead.
You're okay!
Course I am.
Can't leave my
partner alone, can I?
Gun or not, I must admit
you're pretty good.
[chuckles]
A fake like me's
gotta work twice as hard,
but I manage somehow.
I have to. I can't let
my little brothers down.
[NAGASONE grunts, yells]
[NAGASONE grunts]
[NAGASONE yells]
I thought you weren't
gonna let your brothers down.
Get up, tough guy.
[chuckles]
Gimme a sec, would ya?
[KASHUU gasps]
[KASHUU grunts]
What the hell are
you trying to do?!
Kiyo... mitsu...
I can't!
Look at me and focus!
Okita Souji is not
your master anymore!
[KASHUU] You think I didn't
want to protect him, too?
To fight there at his
side until the very end?
Just like you, I love him,
because I'm his sword, too.
But even if this
is the end for him,
it's not the end for us.
Try to remember
all your friends.
All the people waiting
for you back at the citadel!
Don't they matter to you?
Souji, It's you.
[SOUJI] What is it that you
want more than anything?
[YASUSADA]
I admire you so much.
I just wanna be
strong like you.
[SOUJI] And what would
you do with that strength?
[YASUSADA]
I would protect my friends!
And my new master!
They're all waiting for me,
back in the citadel, my home.
That's good.
It sounds like your
path is clear, then.
[YASUSADA]
You're right.
[SOUJI]
It's strange.
This feels like it isn't
the first time we've met.
Like we're old friends.
Seems we have
a lot in common too.
In my case, I shall wield this
sword in the name of my comrades
until illness claims me,
a fate that I proudly accept.
Until you finish
what you need to do,
carry that sword with honor.
[YASUSADA crying]
[YASUSADA]
Kiyomitsu.
Let's go.
Back where we belong.
Souji?
[KANESADA]
I am Izuminokami Kanesada!
Those who are
devoted to practicality
are weak in appearance.
Those who are devoted to
appearance are impractical.
Yet here I stand,
both handsome and effective.
Am I right?
Yep!
If I get any more sentimental,
it wouldn't be cool.
So I'll let my sword
do the talking!
[yelling]
He did it!
Sure kept us waiting!
[YASUSADA]
Master...
There's something I need
to discuss with you.
I hope now is a good time.
[KASHUU]
You're really leaving, huh?
Yeah.
[KASHUU]
Where to?
Dunno yet.
[KASHUU]
And when will you come back?
Can't say.
[KASHUU]
I see.
So I'll have to wait
on you again, it seems.
I wonder if this is what
the master had in mind
when they sent you
to the Ikedaya Inn.
You said you wanted
to become stronger, right?
Well get as strong as you like
and come back when you're done.
When it comes to elegance,
there is no finer specimen.
I admit, it is nice.
I thought this was a ten
thousand leaf cherry tree.
But I think I might've
been mistaken.
Well, think...
Maybe instead of blooming
every ten thousand years,
this one blooms
ten thousand times.
And in the winter.
It really is a miracle.
There's no other answer.
No one knows what
this tree is thinking.
Maybe, but that's
what makes it fun.
Nothing in the world
beats a good surprise.
Guess not.
No matter where we go,
this tree is always here to
greet us when we return.
Almost feels like
it's watching over us.
[laughs]
Indeed, it does.
Our citadel is fortunate.
It has this beautiful tree,
and a kind master to nurture it.
Come on!
How long are you going to keep
everyone waiting out there?
[YASUSADA]
Hold on a sec!
It's been a long time, okay?
I'm nervous!
Take this.
[YASUSADA]
Wow, you fixed it!
[KASHUU]
I improved it.
I had a lot of spare time
while you were gone.
[laughs]
[KASHUU]
Here we are!
Yamatonokami!
So good to see you!
Good to be back!
You certainly took
your time, didn't you?
Glad you're home!
I trust you found what
you were looking for?
Yeah.
[YASUSADA] I was once the
beloved sword of Okita Souji,
but now I am proud to
serve a new master.
I hope that I can
keep growing stronger,
to protect my friends,
and to protect our home.
[JIROUTACHI]
Hey, Yamatonokami!
Stop spacing out and
get your butt over here!
'Kay, I'll be right there!
Thanks for being
patient with me.
Oh!
The cherry blossoms
are welcoming you!
Okay!
We finally have
everyone here now?
Line up in front of
the cherry tree!
Do we have to sit still
for another dumb picture?
You complain now, but you'll
be happy when you see it.
Right?
Don't worry, you guys.
It's a brand new SLR camera--
you don't have to sit still.
The master spared no expense!
[HASEBE gasps]
[HASEBE]
Why, Master?
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Come on, squeeze in!
Long swords in the back!
Except Hotarumaru.
You can be in front.
[HOTARUMARU]
Got it.
[KASHUU]
Get up here already.
We need to be front and center.
Okay, here we go!
It's got a timer,
so I'm sneaking in too.
You all better smile!
[AKITA laughs]
[ATSUSHI laughs]
[YASUSADA] I don't know,
this seems a little too cutesy.
Well, I think it suits you.
And what's wrong with cutesy?
If you say so.
[KASHUU]
The master likes cute things.
Don't you want to be popular?
[YASUSADA]
Nope.
Way too flashy.
[ALL] This was a tale of the
legendary Sword Warriors
and the Hanamaru days they
spent in a certain citadel.
The end!