[HAKATA]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
Born from the heart of swords,
we travel through time to
intercept and eliminate them.
And you can take
that to the bank.
[KASHUU, YASUSADA]
This is a tale of the legendary
Sword Warriors
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in
a certain citadel.
[YASUSADA yells]
Watch out, Kashuu,
it went that way!
I'm on it.
Wow, nice one!
Heh! I'm popular today!
Watch, 'cause this is
how you do business!
Keep yapping and I'm
gonna steal your customers!
Hey, you big cheater!
No cutting!
[YASUSADA] If I want
to be strong like Souji,
practicing my swordplay
won't be enough.
Souji was kind,
with a good sense of humor.
He met every challenge
with a smile.
Whenever there's a
nice day like this,
it makes me want to take a nap.
Well, you can't.
Remember, we have an
expedition coming up today.
Yeah, you don't
need to remind me.
We have to investigate Edo;
it's very important.
Who is our captain this time?
I wasn't listening.
Oh, let me think.
Mutsunokami?
Ugh, I don't want to hear that.
All that pointless enthusiasm
rubs me the wrong way.
[laughs] It's not
just an expedition!
Think of it like a field trip!
Positive thinking doesn't turn
a mission into a vacation.
I was fine till you said that.
Way to kill my joy.
[HASEBE]
Absolutely terrible!
A living nightmare from
which I cannot awaken!
Did something bad happen?
Our poor master
has fallen ill!
[KASHUU]
What?
They've been
planning expeditions,
managing smithing,
and equipment,
assigning duties, and more!
All of that work
has taken its toll,
and now they've
contracted a fever!
They never leave their room,
and I'm sure they don't
get any exercise.
It was only a matter of time.
Regardless, I've failed
as the master's attendant.
I should have prevented this and
now I don't know how to fix it!
It's okay.
Let's just calm down and
look at what we can do.
Medicine, of course!
Let's go and see Yagen.
[YAGEN]
Asiatic dogwood fruit is good.
Do you eat it?
I've never heard of that.
[YAGEN]
Here.
It relieves fever,
supplements nutrition,
and reduces fatigue.
[HASEBE]
Okay, great.
Make some medicine from that
and I'll give it to the master.
You misunderstand.
I'm all out of it right now.
In that case, I'll go pick
some up at the general store.
[YAGEN] They wouldn't
carry something like that.
Then tell me what
I'm supposed to do!
[YAGEN] We'll need to
gather some ourselves.
[HASEBE]
Where? I'll go straight away!
[YAGEN] This tree was brought
from outside the country
and used in pharmacology
during the Edo period.
As for today, I'm not sure.
That's fine, we're about to
go on an expedition to Edo.
Can you give us
an idea where to look?
[YAGEN] You'll be in the
woods surrounding the city.
You might be able
to find the tree there.
[KASHUU]
What are you thinking, Hasebe?
[HASEBE] Your mission
is to investigate Edo.
The master's
orders are absolute,
so that's your priority
whether we like it or not.
However, if you happen
to find one of those trees
during the mission,
you won't hear any
complaints from me.
You got it!
Let's go.
The master's fallen
sick with a fever?
I can only blame
myself for this.
I don't know if
I'd go that far.
I mean it.
One of my jobs is to look
after the master's health.
Either way, there's no
need to beat yourself up.
I bet a nice meal
will raise their spirits.
"Let food be thy medicine
and medicine thy food."
I'm sure they don't have
much of an appetite, though.
What sort of food are
you supposed to make
for someone when they're sick?
Something easy
to eat, obviously,
and nutritious, I assume.
Like grouper!
We can find some
of that, can't we?
Wait, what?
[HASEBE]
Or maybe udon?
Now there's an idea!
[HASEBE] Even if they don't
have much of an appetite,
they can still sip
on the broth, right?
It's healthy,
and it'll be easy
on the stomach
since it's not too heavy.
♪ Udon indeed. ♪
♪ Just sit back,
leave it to me. ♪
[HASEBE]
Wait.
This was my mistake; let me
try and make up for it.
I will prepare the udon myself.
You can watch and make sure
I get everything right.
Okay.
HASEBE (SONG)] ♪ The first
step is to make the brine. ♪
♪ Pour in the flour and
we're lookin' just fine. ♪
♪ Stir it up till
it all combines. ♪
You're making the
noodles first, huh?
♪ Now watch me knead
the dough like a pro. ♪
[humming]
You really know what
you're doing, don't you?
♪ I only wish what
you said was true. ♪
♪ When I don't know
what to do. ♪
♪ Can ya give me a clue? ♪
Will do.
♪ Now that we're through, ♪
♪ let it sit for
an hour or two. ♪
♪ Then we'll start the stew. ♪
A whole hour?
Afraid so. No less.
♪ I don't think I can wait! ♪
♪ If we don't hurry,
it could be way too late! ♪
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
You're right.
Good thing I've got
some finished dough.
But why?
♪ This was going to be
our dinner tonight. ♪
♪ I made it just right,
so you can use it if you like. ♪
That's perfect;
thank you very much!
[SHOKUDAIKIRI (SONG)]
♪ Place the dough in a bag ♪
♪ just like so. ♪
♪ Knead it nice and slow
with your toes. ♪
I can't believe I'm stepping
on the master's dinner!
♪ May seem odd at first sight, ♪
♪ but stepping on dough
makes the texture just right. ♪
♪ If you want noodles
firm and nice, ♪
♪ then don't think twice. ♪
Okay, now what do we do next?
We have to let it sit
for a while, don't we?
No, not again!
You have more?
[HASEBE (SONG)] ♪ Spread some
flour and give it a pat ♪
♪ Stretch and roll it
till it's nice and flat ♪
♪ Fold it just like that ♪
♪ and cut! ♪
♪ What a sight to see,
Shokudaikiri. ♪
♪ [SHOKUDAIKIRI (SONG)]
Those look just perfect to me. ♪
Now that we're done
with the noodles,
what should we put in the broth?
Healthy is the priority, but
it should taste good also.
[NAKIGITSUNE]
Fried tofu! Yeah!
[HASEBE]
Nakigitsune!
♪ Kitsune udon is an
awesome choice for anybody. ♪
♪ If you don't like it then
you're crazy, baby. ♪
♪ Like a fox. ♪
[HASEBE (SONG)]
♪ Now that sounds good to me. ♪
♪ Fried tofu tastes lovely. ♪
♪ I've got some sitting
in the pantry. ♪
♪ Mikazuki? ♪
♪ If you would
like some advice, ♪
♪ I think an egg or two
would be quite nice. ♪
[MIKAZUKI]
Tsukimi udon.
A hearty meal with poached eggs
reminiscent of a harvest moon.
[HASEBE]
I see.
That would certainly give
them the nutrients they need.
Guess that settles it!
[HASEBE] Master, when
we return from battle,
bruised and beaten, you're
always there to comfort us.
And when we complete our tasks,
you never fail to
greet us with a smile
and share with us kind words.
I owe you a great
debt of kindness,
and I swear that
I will repay it.
No matter what it takes!
So Master, don't die!
It sounds as if the
master is quite ill!
I think it's just
a cold, actually.
It was made with love.
The perfect udon!
I'm a little concerned, since
there's so many ingredients.
But taste is all that matters.
[NIKKARI]
There's only one suitable way
to make that judgment.
My tongue!
Let me try some.
Nikkari Aoe.
We've all been singing,
and somehow,
you're still the weird one.
Oh, I get it.
Your original masters
were the Kyougoku Clan,
and they made their home
in the Sanuki Province.
That place is famous
for their udon.
[HASEBE] Oh. In that case,
please proceed!
[NIKKARI]
Thank you very much.
Remarkable!
The noodles are short and
thin, but their flavor is rich,
a symphony cascading
gently down your throat.
Reminds me of banshuu udon
eaten in the hometown
of Kuroda Kanbei.
[NIKKARI] Hasebe, you served
the Kuroda Clan, didn't you?
Could it be that their history
has manifested itself
through your hand in
this udon's creation?
I have no idea.
I just made the noodles
as best I could.
But if they're tasty,
then I'm happy.
[NIKKARI laughs]
[HASEBE] Master, I've never
prepared udon before,
but my desire to help you
brought out something new in me!
[OTEGINE]
So this is Edo, huh?
Whoa. Bet I could
make some good deals
with all those business
men down there.
[MUTSUNOKAMI] We have a lot
of rookies on this mission,
don't we? Okay. So...
Remember, our goal is
to investigate this area.
Gather as much info
as you can on the people,
the city layout,
and the surroundings.
We have two hours.
[YAMABUSHI]
Ka ka ka!
I have trained my body
and I shall train my mind.
Tell me where to begin,
Captain, and I shall go.
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Let's see...
[KASHUU]
Wait a second.
Something wrong, Kashuu?
I won't mince words.
The master has a fever.
This is terrible news!
Just a cold?
Or worse?
We don't know for sure.
At any rate, we were
told that the fruit
from the Asiatic dogwood
could help them recover.
[YASUSADA] Yagen made it
sound like it was common
in this time period.
If we searched the forest,
we could probably find the tree.
But I know that's
not our mission.
Ha ha! The investigation
is complete!
As captain, I'll write
the report myself!
The master's health takes
priority over anything
and everything else, right?
We'll find this stuff.
Two hours is plenty of time.
[MUTSUNOKAMI] All right, then,
forget about the city.
[YAMABUSHI]
And head into the woods!
Ka ka ka!
Traversing nature just so
happens to be my specialty!
We're just looking
for a tree, Yamabushi,
I don't think it's gonna be
some death-defying adventure.
[YAMABUSHI]
Ka ka ka!
And yet, one must
always be prepared!
[MUTSUNOKAMI] He really likes
the great outdoors, I guess.
[OTEGINE]
Hey.
By the way, Kashuu, any idea
why the master got sick?
I didn't think much of it.
But they have been staying up
awfully late this past week.
I wonder...
What were they doing?
[HAKATA]
Isn't it obvious?
They were busy checking
the stock market!
The stock...
...market?
They want to be prepared
for when the market opens
the next day,
so they stay up all night
researching their stocks.
Of course, there are also
global markets to consider,
so maybe they're doing foreign
trading in a different time zone
and have to keep odd hours...
We're gonna leave you here.
C'mon, it was a joke.
Otegine, are you
searching or sight-seeing?
Can't I do both?
Though, to be honest with you,
I'm really only
good at stabbing things.
[YASUSADA]
Wow, that looks heavy.
Eh, you get used to it.
It's only weighs
like forty pounds.
[YASUSADA]
Wow.
Anything need stabbing?
Uh-oh.
Wow, they're really fired up.
Must be a race, huh?
[yelling]
This is a no-stabbing
mission from here on out.
Sorry to take away the
only thing you're good at.
[OTEGINE]
I'll behave.
Where'd everyone go?
Guess it's just
you and me now, huh?
We need not worry.
In fact, splitting up
may even aid our search!
Onward we go!
Yeah, but we're kinda stuck.
It's a long way up there.
[YAMABUSHI]
That it is.
[HAKATA yelling]
Wait, what are you doing?
Let my roaring muscles
deliver you upwards!
Heave-ho!
[HAKATA yelling]
[YAMABUSHI] Hakata, you're
supposed to yell "bombs away"!
[HAKATA] C-Couldn't we
have discussed this first?
[YAMABUSHI]
Ka ka ka!
Now find a vine so that you may
aid me in my egress as well!
[HAKATA]
Uh... vines?
Ah! Like this one?
[YAMABUSHI]
Hold on tight!
[HAKATA]
No problem!
All right, coming up!
I got this.
Or not!
[YAMABUSHI]
If at first you don't succeed,
then my roaring muscles
shall deliver you once more!
--Heave-ho!
--[HAKATA] Bombs away!
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Hey, these things are red!
Maybe so.
But I don't think
that's the right fruit.
They look good.
I'm gonna try one.
Ugh! If you get sick,
don't blame me.
I gotta try.
I mean, it could be awesome.
Then I'll grab some
for Shokudaikiri.
[retching]
[KASHUU]
Oh, wow, that's nice.
I was thirsty.
[OTEGINE yells]
Help! Kashuu!
What's wrong with you?
Whew, that was a close one.
Ha. Nice save.
[yells]
Well... So long.
[OTEGINE]
Kashuu!
Plenty of trees, but
not the one that we need.
[HAKATA]
Ouch!
What's wrong? A trap?
I'll be okay.
Just gimme a minute here.
Careful!
Don't push yourself!
Well, I suppose we
had better head back now.
[HAKATA]
Are you kidding me?
I'll do whatever it takes.
We can't abandon the mission
when we've come this far.
It's only been a few days
since I've come to the citadel,
but I want to help the
master however I can.
I want to be strong like
all the other Sword Warriors.
I don't want to let them down.
[YAMABUSHI]
I understand your sentiment.
I feel the same.
Now, ride upon my back and
we may continue our journey!
[HAKATA yelping]
I know I'm not heavy, but I
feel bad having you carry me.
[YAMABUSHI]
Ka ka ka!
No matter the hardship,
I shall greet it with a smile.
This is the way that I have
chosen to honor our master.
It might serve you well
to do the same.
So let's see a smile
on your face, Hakata!
You must strive
to gain the strength
to laugh away every challenge!
Ka ka ka ka!
Onward!
Ka ka ka!
[YASUSADA] We only have
so much time here.
Are you sure we'll be okay?
Come on. Stupid tree,
where are you?
Don't stop like that!
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Shh!
Yamatonokami, wait.
Stay behind me.
Keep your sword in its sheath.
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Are you listening?
Better to finish it
before it finishes us.
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Compose yourself.
[YASUSADA]
Why don't you just shoot it?
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
I only have a few bullets.
It wouldn't stop it in time.
Besides, we just want
to pass through.
There's no need
to kill the thing.
[YASUSADA gasps]
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
I'll ask you one more time--
please put your sword away.
Noble bear, I beg that
you let us pass.
Our master has been beset
with illness, you see.
And we owe this
master a great debt.
Without them, we wouldn't
even have a body.
We would do anything
to save their life.
Not only because we are
loyal to their cause,
but because we love them dearly.
We don't want to fight.
We only want to search
for medicine in the forest.
So please...
You need not bare your fangs.
We only want to pass.
Our hearts are the same.
[MUTSUNOKAMI] Surely we can
walk this earth together.
I mean you no harm.
[MUTSUNOKAMI] Sakamoto
Ryouma guided the Satsuma
and Choushuu clans
to a reconciliation,
when before they got along
like cats and dogs.
You can win without
swords or guns.
all that you have to do
is open up your heart.
My old master's
wisdom came in handy,
even at a time like this.
Anyway, we'd
better get moving.
[YASUSADA]
Right.
This is the final stretch--
you still holding up?
[YASUSADA]
Of course!
Here I thought we
wouldn't make it on time.
[KASHUU]
Hey!
You didn't get lost after all.
[HAKATA]
We did it!
Now we just need to
make our way back!
[grunts]
Does your foot hurt?
I'm finally doing
something for the master!
A little bruise won't stop me!
Also, I bet I can make a killing
selling this weird fruit!
[KASHUU]
Yagen!
We got the thing
that you asked for!
Hmm... Let me see here.
Well...?
Looks great, and you
gathered a whole lot, too!
Will the medicine
take long to make?
[YAGEN]
Not at all.
We did it!
[KASHUU]
Of course.
I finished the purification.
I hope it helps.
I'm sure it will.
Thank you for everything.
You don't need to thank me;
we all help the master
in any way we can.
Like with that udon
you have there.
[HASEBE]
Well, I gave it my best.
We'll see how it goes.
Excuse me, Master,
your humble attendant
has brought you udon,
made with love and care.
I hope it's to your liking.
What, it's still too hot?
My apologies.
[MAEDA]
Uh, hey.
I wrote a letter
for the master.
Do you think it would be
okay if I brought it up?
Yeah, sure,
bet they'd love that.
Great!
[HASEBE] Everyone,
the master ate the udon!
I gave the master
Yagen's medicine
and they seemed happy enough,
so that's a start.
Now we wait.
Okay.
[HASEBE]
They said it was so-so!
After all, we are still swords.
We can't serve our purpose
if our master is ill.
Our greatest joy is
to be put to good use.
That's why everyone
is fighting their hardest.
[YASUSADA]
You're right.
Our master...
...just like Souji.
[KASHUU]
You okay?
What's the deal?
It's just like you said!
We have to fight our hardest
and grow even stronger!
I want the master to
know how much I care!
[HASEBE] Yamatonokami,
the master is still sick.
Whatever you want
to say can wait.
No! No, it can't!
What has gotten into you?
You're only going
to make matters worse!
Idiot.
[HASEBE] If you have a
message, I'll pass it along!
Swimsuits?
And a loincloth.
Ah! I wanted to go to
the beach with everyone,
so I requested these.
Looks like the master
was cool with it after all!
[KASHUU] Wait, they made
all of these by hand?
Couldn't we buy them?
[HASEBE]
No, because we're poor.
And do you know why that is?
Because you all
used up the allowance
buying crap at
the general store!
That's no good.
I didn't realize I was causing
the master so much stress
over some silly vacation.
[YASUSADA]
Handmade, huh?
[HASEBE] Yeah, and they
said it was their first time
sewing clothes, no less.
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
We all care for the master.
And they care for us.
This citadel truly is blessed.
We'll return the favor somehow!
Of course we will.
[KASHUU]
We have bigger issues here.
Like this loincloth.
Who's gonna wear it?