[TSURUMARU]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
Born from the heart of swords,
we travel through time to
intercept and eliminate them.
You're not even listening,
are you?
Go figure.
[KASHUU, YASUSADA]
This is a tale of the Legendary
Sword Warriors,
and the Hanamaru days they
spent in a certain citadel.
Did you think you were Souji?
[YASUSADA]
I don't know.
[HASEBE panting]
Yo! Sorry to keep you waiting.
[HASEBE]
Master!
Tsurumaru has arrived!
[HASEBE]
Good morning, gentlemen.
[ALL]
Good morning.
The snow has piled up
considerably overnight,
though you can
see that for yourself.
A few spots are solid ice,
so take precaution.
[ALL]
Yes, sir.
[NAKIGITSUNE]
Sir, yes, sir!
[HASEBE] I have two new Sword
Warriors to introduce today.
The uchigatana , Doudanuki
Masakuni, joined us last night,
and the tachi , Tsurumaru,
joined us this morning.
Nice to meet you.
Glad I could make it here.
I came here to fight.
Where's the enemy?
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Tsuru! Nice to see you again!
Lookin' good!
Wow, is that you, Mitsubou?
The master has placed
their faith in you,
so I expect excellence.
As for everyone else, you
remember what it was like
when you first came here,
so show them the ropes.
Moving on now,
I will announce
today's assignments
as appointed by our master.
Ta-da!
Horse duty:
Ishikirimaru and Akita.
Field duty:
Aizen and Nakigitsune.
Sparring: Maeda and Gokotai.
Laundry duty:
Kasen and Yamanbagiri.
Cleaning duty:
Hachisuka and Midare.
Cooking duty:
Shokudaikiri and Nikkari.
Naturally, I will attend to
the master, as I always do.
So do the rest of us
get to go on a mission,
or what?
Well, if you need me,
I'll be polishing my guns
and shooting holes in stuff!
[YASUSADA] I guess they
don't need me, then.
[HASEBE]
Oh, and lastly, Kashuu.
Take the new
recruits and show them
around the citadel.
Why? Get someone else.
Be grateful the master
has faith in you.
Try to stay in good standing.
Ha. One of the downsides
of popularity.
Very well, then.
[clears throat]
Now, although we
haven't heard word
of any enemy attacks yet,
you should all
remain ever vigilant
in case an emergency...
[KASHUU]
Hey, you wanna help me out?
It's not like you're doing
anything else today, right?
Would you stop ignoring me?!
You'll be sorry
when I say something
really important!
Oh, never mind.
[KASHUU]
I'm Kashuu Kiyomitsu.
I was the first sword
to be summoned here.
Anyway, nice to meet you.
[TSURUMARU]
Nice to meet you.
[DOUDANUKI]
Uh, yeah.
And he's another one of
Okita Souji's beloved swords,
like me.
He hasn't been here
much longer than you two.
Yamatonokami Yasusada.
It's a pleasure.
Hello.
Hey.
Well... Let's start
the tour, then.
I'll try to make it quick.
On your left, you can see
our fine, open air baths.
Oh, wow, the citadel has
warm baths for all of us?
That is so incredible!
[laughing]
Can't wait to get in.
Yes, it's very thrilling,
now let's go.
[KASEN] Elegance, thy form
is a freshly washed shirt,
blowing in the wind.
That cloak...
Oh, how my hands long to
wring the filth from its folds.
[KASEN]
Yamanbagiri.
What's up?
Let's wash your cloak.
Don't even bother.
I'm just a copy...
a duplicate sword.
I don't see what that has
to do with clean clothes.
Give it up.
Have it your way.
Your heart is clouded, just
like your clothes are soiled.
Someday, I will give that
cloak the elegance it deserves.
Someday!
And over here,
we have our laundry area.
[TSURUMARU]
Ah!
What's the blue bottle?
[KASHUU]
That's fabric softener.
A modern convenience
our master is fond of.
It makes things soft?
[YASUSADA]
Nuzzly soft!
[yawns]
[NAKIGITSUNE] Whoa, nobody
told me they have cabbage
fresh for the taking!
Feels like you could
dig right in, doesn't it?
[NAKIGITSUNE]
If it's growing in this weather,
it must be snow cabbage.
I heard it's so good
you can eat it raw!
Do it, Nakigitsune! Grab one!
Do it! Do it!
Well, why not?
Hold on!
This food is for
everybody here, right?
We can't take it!
[NAKIGITSUNE] Nakigitsune says
it's okay, so it's okay.
I'll keep your secret,
but you've gotta share.
[NAKIGITSUNE, AIZEN]
Let's dig in!
[KASHUU]
And here...
...is where we grow our food.
Wow, that's great,
the whole citadel's
self-sufficient.
Something sure smells nice!
[YASUSADA]
What is it? Must be close.
There! You can't hide from me!
[AIZEN, NAKIGITSUNE gasp]
[YASUSADA]
Are they vegetables?
That plant is called an herb,
and the master's
been really excited
about growing it
in the citadel.
But I'm sure the novelty
will wear off eventually.
So are these extra fancy,
or are they just like the
stuff we put in porridge?
Might as well find out.
Mmm!
One little taste, and my
sinuses are cleared right up!
[DOUDANUKI] Bet I could use
this as a weapon, if I had to.
Why don't we move on?
[AKITA]
You sure are cute, Mr. Horse.
What's your name?
[KASHUU]
And these are the stables.
[TSURUMARU]
It's Ishikirimaru!
Hello, Tsurumaru.
Nice to meet you in person.
I never would've thought
that you of all people
would be tending horses.
People sure can change.
[laughing]
I'm only doing this because
no one needs healing.
That sounds more like you.
Nice to have something
familiar to latch onto.
[YASUSADA] Hey, check out
Tsurumaru and the horse.
Look, their eyes are sparkling!
[KASHUU chuckling]
[AKITA]
Kashuu.
Do you know the horse's name?
No one ever told me.
Oh it's... Hanataro.
Hanataro?
[TSURUMARU] Sounds kind
of floofy if you ask me.
[KASHUU] You're gonna
have to take that one up
with the master.
I'm not the one who named it.
[AKITA]
Hanataro.
[GOKOTAI, MAEDA grunting]
[KASHUU] And this would
be the training hall.
[DOUDANUKI] Hitting things!
Now that's more like it!
Maybe I won't be
so bored after all!
[GOKOTAI, MAEDA grunting]
[DOUDANUKI] Training's not
as fun as kicking ass,
but the more you train,
the more ass you can kick.
You guys look pretty small.
Have you ever been
in a real fight before?
Yes, sir.
[DOUDANUKI]
All right, then... come at me!
[yelling]
[KASHUU] Could you wait until
the tour is over with, please?
Well, that's everything.
You didn't tell me
there were girls here!
And they live with us?
The new recruit!
Oh and, your name was
Doudanuki Masakuni, I believe?
Anyway, I'm Midare Toushirou.
It's nice to meet you!
Oh. You're a... dude.
[HACHISUKA]
Kashuu, I have a question.
What is it?
There are too many boxes here.
Can I throw them away?
Why? Who cares?
They are taking up
the whole room.
The master wants to
keep them for some reason.
Said they might be
important someday.
I won't criticize
their hoarding tendencies,
but at least let me store
them in the warehouse
for the time being.
Doudanuki. Perhaps you
could help me carry them?
Uh, yeah, sure.
[DOUDANUKI]
That's gonna mess me up.
I can't believe...
that's not a girl.
[TSURUMARU]
Hey, Kashuu,
what kind of person is
this "master" of ours?
[YASUSADA] Actually, I've been
wondering the same thing,
but since I haven't been
invited to meet them,
I was afraid to ask.
Mmm... Let me think.
They're sloppy and
they're clumsy.
You can't rely on them
for anything at all,
and I have no idea what's
going on in their head.
Then again...
It's cute how they
always give it their best.
That's worth something.
Why don't we go
and pay them a visit?
[TSURUMARU chuckles]
That's a good idea!
It's not like we're doing
anything right now,
and their room is
around the corner!
We might as well...
No, that's a terrible idea!
Tsurumaru!
You think it'd be funny if
I jumped in and screamed?
Hold on a second!
What's up?
[HASEBE] Master, the state of
your desk is simply deplorable!
I carefully arranged
these books for you.
[KASHUU] Hasebe is doing his...
uh... thing in there.
[TSURUMARU] I see.
He sure is a hard worker, huh?
[HASEBE]
Oh, Master, why?!
[YASUSADA]
That was delicious!
Wow, Mitsubou, that
was an excellent meal!
I try my best.
I've always longed
for something more.
I can't just fight all the time.
[dishes rattling]
[TSURUMARU]
The wars that we fought in
have long since passed,
so it seems strange to
be summoned to battle
after so many years of peace.
That's not the only
thing we have in common.
Now that you mention it,
a lot of us came from the same
period and had the same master.
[TSURUMARU]
Oda...
[GROUP]
...Nobunaga.
So serious!
You got some bad memories?
It's complicated, that's all.
Go ahead. If you've got
something to say, then say it.
Actually, I would quite
prefer if you went first.
[clears throat]
Well, if I'm being
perfectly frank,
just thinking about the
man makes me sick.
One day, when he became
angry with a tea servant,
he decided to slay him
with his own hands.
Or with me, rather.
When the young boy
hid in a cabinet,
he cut straight through
the whole thing.
[SOUZA] Well, at least he
displayed your capabilities.
It's what he did next
that I'm so angry about!
He granted me a name for my
cabinet-smashing prowess,
then simply passed me off to
somebody who wasn't even
a vassal!
How dare he?
[TSURUMARU laughs]
[HASEBE]
It's no laughing matter!
Souza, you had the same master.
Did you hate him too?
I mean... that's
more or less true.
[YASUSADA]
What happened?
Tell him.
I don't have any good memories,
that much is true.
My master was
obsessed with power.
He believed that this
world and everything in it
was destined to be his.
I was handed over to him after
the battle of Okehazama.
He kept me at his side
and polished me often.
He must have been
quite pleased with me,
in his possessive sort of way.
That is to say... he saw
fit to engrave his own name
onto the base of my blade.
Now, it's as if it's
engraved upon my very soul.
In the end, I was just another
treasure for him to brag about.
I was forged for battle,
but scarcely saw it.
I feel as if I was robbed
of my purpose.
You don't have to
look at it that way.
It seems like you were loved.
Is that wrong?
Not everyone likes to
be loved in the same way.
So, what about you, Yagen?
You probably hold
a grudge too, right?
I mean, you were nestled right
next to his heart all the time.
I suppose, though I never
thought of it like that.
I don't know.
What do ya mean?
He was straightforward.
That was comforting in a way.
--[door opens]
--[KASEN] Hasebe.
The master is calling for you.
It sounds important.
I see. I'll be there
promptly, then.
[HASEBE]
Honnouji?
The battle where
Nobunaga was killed?
Ah, forgive me, it's just
a coincidence, that's all.
What is the lineup?
Ah. I see. Very well.
Prepare for a mission,
or in this case,
a reunion with Nobunaga!
And this time...
I'm the captain.
It looks like the
team is assembled.
I will be your captain.
You said that already.
[HASEBE] Our dispatch
location will be Honnouji.
The year is 1582.
Perfect timing.
I'm not quite sure
how that makes me feel.
It's certainly
nostalgic, at least.
So what exactly does
the History Retrograde Army
hope to accomplish
by going there?
[HASEBE] The master assumes
that they will target
Akechi Mitsuhide's forces.
Heading him off before he can
launch his surprise attack
on Nobunaga.
Do they think Nobunaga
could rule the nation
if he didn't die that night?
[HASEBE] The details are
irrelevant to our mission.
All we need to worry about is
destroying the enemy, you mean.
We cannot allow
Oda Nobunaga to live.
This will be his ending.
It sounds like you
wanna kill him yourself!
History decided that, not us.
Our feelings just happen
to align this time.
[HASEBE]
I will not tolerate defeat.
Is that understood?
They really hate
their old master.
I can hardly imagine that.
Their feelings for him aren't
as simple as you might think.
At any rate,
they're ready to fight.
So this time around, we should
definitely give it our best.
That's not funny!
[HASEBE] Oh, I forgot
to mention something.
Master said that we
should take our time.
Nobody here has a
problem with that, right?
I don't understand.
You're still a rookie, huh?
Most of us have long since
given up trying to figure out
what the master thinks.
It's likely just
for nostalgia's sake.
This battle does hold
a lot of memories for us.
That's an unnecessary
consideration.
Let's defeat the enemy
and return home quickly.
[HASEBE]
I agree.
As our master's attendant and
as the first division commander,
I will expect you
to follow my orders
without your usual
bellyaching and mockery!
Now off... to battle!
[KASHUU]
I see.
So this is Honnouji,
where your master died.
It's upsetting to think
that Nobunaga's so close.
I much prefer him dead.
That's harsh.
Ha. This could be
your last chance.
Are you sure you don't
want to go pay him a visit?
No, thank you.
That would only
disturb me further.
I don't want nightmares.
You were right.
Their feelings are complicated.
I shouldn't think about it.
More importantly, Captain,
I don't suppose you know
where our enemies are hiding?
I'll leave the scouting to you.
The attack came while
Nobunaga was sleeping.
They'll likely
infiltrate the area,
then launch an ambush
when Mitsuhide's troops
enter at night.
Since the sun is setting,
they should be here any second
now... on the outskirts.
And just like magic,
our little friends appear.
You know what to do.
Wipe them out and
don't look back!
[YASUSADA yells]
Like old times!
This new job isn't half bad!
Does get the
blood pumping, huh?
[SOLDIER 2B growling]
Well, you're certainly
big enough, aren't you?
[SOLDIER 2B growling]
I hope you're
taking this seriously.
'Cause if you let your
guard down... you're dead.
[chuckles]
I told you.
[SOUZA grunts]
Souza, you're not hurt, are you?
A little pain isn't
going to kill me.
I'm used to it, after all.
Don't you dare, Souza.
Pull back.
Hey, we got one
hiding behind that tree.
There's no use trying
to conceal yourself.
[SOLDIER 2A growls]
You can't escape me!
You think you're
pretty sneaky, huh?
Sorry, but you've gotta
get up really early
to pull one over on me!
Not too bad for
my first mission!
I was nothing but
a bird in cage,
but now, my new master
has given me a body,
freedom and a
purpose to fight for.
Even though I still bear the
seal of the demon king upon me.
He shall perish.
His fury and madness buried
here... as history intended!
[SOUZA yells]
[YAGEN]
Are you hurt?
On the contrary,
I feel quite liberated.
Nice work, everyone.
We've completed the mission.
[SOUZA]
Hasebe.
Perhaps we should stick
around for the show after all.
[HASEBE]
Mitsuhide's ambush, you mean?
Huh? You're gonna stay here just
to watch your old master die?
We'll see it through to the end.
We've been given
this opportunity,
so we'll take our
time as advised.
What about your injuries, Souza?
Will you be all right?
We can return, if you like.
I wouldn't dream
of running home
over a tiny scratch
like this one.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
I thought they all
just hated Nobunaga,
but now I don't
know how to feel.
Words don't necessarily reflect
how someone truly feels inside.
Contradictory, isn't it?
I understand now.
I see, Master.
That's why you gave us the
instruction to take our time.
Oh, yeah.
You might be right.
[chattering]
Nice work out there today.
And nice work patching me up.
It's fine.
You seem well.
No lasting injuries, I presume?
You were fighting
pretty hard back there.
Are you asking as my
captain, or as my friend?
Either way, I'm lovely.
Though I have to ask why
we're eating nabe outside
when the weather's so cold.
We're having a welcome
party for all the new
sword warriors, apparently.
Hasebe. Mind if we converse?
[HASEBE] Even though we
watched to the bitter end,
we never saw how
Nobunaga died, did we?
He was always
such a proud man.
He would have
preferred it that way.
[YASUSADA] Hey, I heard
this story about Nobunaga.
Maybe you can confirm it for me.
Go ahead.
Even though history says
that he died at Honnouji,
I heard that when they
sifted through the rubble,
they never found his body.
Maybe not.
Many people assumed
he committed suicide.
But since there
were no witnesses,
they could never confirm
his actual cause of death.
Well, maybe that's because
he never really died at all.
He escaped from Honnouji
under the veil of chaos,
turned to the power of darkness,
and obtained immortality,
becoming a true demon king!
Scouring the earth, he searches
for revenge, even today!
[laughing]
I dunno.
That's quite the fairy tale.
It does sound like something
he would do, though.
I suppose you're right.
[YASUSADA] But if it was true,
I'd be kind of jealous.
And why is that?
If Nobunaga was alive
and here with us right now,
if you could speak
with him in person,
what do you think
you would say to him?
I don't need to see him and
I don't need to say a thing.
Well... it's not as though he'd
listen to a word we said anyway.
[HASEBE, SOUZA laughing]
[HASEBE] Enough of that;
let's have a drink.
[SOUZA]
What, just one?
[YASUSADA]
I still miss Souji.
It would be really nice
he were still alive.
[YASUSADA] I wonder what
I would say to him.
Thinking of our
old master, huh?
How'd you guess?
Because anyone can
read you like a book.
One look at your face
and it's obvious.
[YASUSADA gasps]
It's a shooting star!
No, really? Where is it?
Huh? Don't tell me I missed it!
[YASUSADA] Aw, jeez!
I forgot to make a wish!
This is all your fault!