[HORIKAWA]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
Born from the heart of swords,
we travel through time to
intercept and eliminate them.
Hey, has anyone seen Kane?
[KASHUU, YASUSADA]
This is a tale of the Legendary
Sword Warriors
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in
a certain citadel.
[squelching noise]
[gasps]
[YASUSADA]
That dream again.
Ah!
[laughs] All done with
my chores for the day.
All done stuffing my face.
Now, what's next?
Cherry blossoms!
Oh! Good idea!
[TAROUTACHI] Didn't you watch
the cherry blossoms yesterday
and the day before?
What are we supposed to do?
We've got this beautiful
cherry tree here.
If we didn't watch
its blossoms fall,
wouldn't that be
rude to the tree?
I dunno what to think
about you, Jiroutachi.
Except you've got
a way with language!
I know!
Well, sounds like a date, then!
Sword Warriors, assemble
beneath the cherry tree!
We're watching the blooms!
[HASEBE]
Cut that out!
Our sacred bell is
for official business,
not your foolish whims!
The master would be
deeply disappointed
if they heard of this!
Let's have a picnic!
Sounds like fun!
Why not, right?
Well...
Like it or not,
the bell gets the job done.
[KASHUU]
The Ikedaya Inn?
And you've had this dream
a bunch of times before?
Uh-huh.
With me by Souji's side.
As a normal sword, that is.
No mistaking it.
Sure. I mean, you can't
argue with a dream, right?
[HORIKAWA] But you're the
one who was actually there,
right, Kashuu?
I don't get it.
C'mon! Tell me!
What does it mean?
It's gotta be something, right?
I don't know,
maybe you just wanted him
to take you instead of me?
That's not it!
Although I would've
been honored to go.
I know it was you that
Souji chose, not me,
and I respect that decision,
even if it does make me upset.
Don't be dramatic.
That doesn't mean that
you're any less worthy.
He just wanted me that time.
Is that so awful?
[YASUSADA] No, but this dream
thing is still bugging me.
[HASEBE]
Excuse me.
Do you have a moment?
Sure.
Oh. Must be
another lecture, huh?
[door opens]
Horikawa, you were made
the secretary, correct?
[HORIKAWA]
That's right.
I have a job for you.
[HASEBE] This is your
first time on the job,
so I'll be frank with you.
The master of our citadel,
to put it nicely,
is a bit of a homebody.
[HORIKAWA]
They're as big as a house?
[HASEBE] No! Why would
you--never mind.
The point is they don't
like to leave their room.
That is why they
made this shiki ,
which can recreate
the powers of the Sage.
With it, anyone can
manifest Sword Warriors
in place of the master.
[HORIKAWA]
This is all you need?
Our job is to
care for the master.
So if they want to stay in
their room and relax all day,
we'll help them with that.
We must perform duties
both great and small
to show our boundless
loyalty and...
[KASHUU]
I hope he shows up soon.
[YASUSADA]
Izuminokami Kanesada?
Kane, Kane, Kane,
all day every day.
Only thing Horikawa
ever talks about.
That's only natural.
Well, 'cause of their owner.
I'm sure they were
close to Hijikata.
So were we, since he was in
the Shinsengumi like Souji.
[KASHUU]
I suppose.
Were you lonely?
I mean, you had to wait
a long time for me.
Ugh! No!
It wasn't like that.
How can you say something like
that with such a straight face?
[HORIKAWA] C'mon, Kane,
Kane, Kane, Kane, Kane...
I am Hijikata Toshizou's
beloved sword.
Both strong and cool.
Obviously, my reputation
speaks for itself--
[HORIKAWA]
You made it!
Jeez, at least let me finish.
Kane!
Sorry to make
you wait, Kunihiro.
[HORIKAWA]
Let me give you a tour.
Oh, hey, Hasebe!
Well! That was fast!
I am Master's attendant,
Heshikiri Hasebe.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
I'm happy I could make it here.
If there's anything you're
unsure of regarding the citadel,
feel free to ask me.
Can I meet my new master?
Maybe. Shall we go and find out?
It's okay.
I can show him around myself.
Come with me.
All right.
Nice to see Horikawa so happy.
[KANESADA]
Thanks, I guess.
But where am I supposed
to put this thing?
Sorry 'bout that.
Let me take it; I'll come
up with something later.
So, our job as Sword Warriors
is to travel through time
and protect history.
You heard it straight from
the master's mouth, right?
Did you still have
some questions?
Nah.
In that case, I'll show
you to our room, c'mon.
"Our" room?
We don't have to share
with anyone else?
[HORIKAWA chuckles]
[KANESADA]
Kunihiro, could I get--
[HORIKAWA]
A snack?
I'll take care of that.
You're gonna spoil me.
Come on.
[yawns]
Here.
[KANESADA]
Thanks, but back off a little!
[KANESADA] Wow, that's one
heck of a tree you've got.
[HORIKAWA] It's a ten
thousand leaf cherry tree.
[KANESADA] What's that?
Never heard of one.
It only blooms once
every ten thousand years,
but it can grant
wishes, they say.
[YASUSADA]
All right, I'm ready!
[KANESADA]
What's over there?
[HORIKAWA]
The training hall.
[KASHUU]
Let's do this!
Normally, with a
three-step thrust,
you would stab high,
then middle, then low,
but Souji would
strike three times
in the exact same place instead.
It was so fast that it only
looked like one attack.
So the enemy would
be overwhelmed.
You're right.
I remember that now.
[KANESADA] Hey!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I am the beloved
sword of Hijikata,
Vice Commander
of the Shinsengumi.
Famously strong and cool,
clearly, my reputation
speaks for itself. I am--
[YASUSADA, KASHUU]
Kane!
[HORIKAWA laughs]
[KANESADA]
Uh, yes.
Yasusada and Kiyomitsu.
You guys got here early, huh?
Actually, you were just late.
Uh-huh.
Either way,
it's good to see you.
[KASHUU] Hijikata was
a pretty scary guy, huh?
He was like a demon, for real.
Yeah, "The Demon Vice
Commander from Hell."
Born a demon, raised a demon.
[KASHUU] They say he
didn't even have a soul.
You bastards!
Are you trying to piss me off
or does it just come natural
to you jerks?
You know damn well Hijikata
only acted the way he did
so he could be a
better commander!
Back me up, Kunihiro!
[laughing]
Stop laughing, you traitor!
Not bad.
So, seems you have
to train pretty hard
for these missions of yours.
No different than before.
The Shinsengumi had a
training hall like this as well.
[KANESADA] All right,
I'm just gonna ask you--
Why are you fighting?
It's our sworn duty to stop
the History Retrograde Army--
[KANESADA] So you just do
whatever the master tells you?
You're not just swords
now--you're men.
Hijikata fought for the
shogunate because in his heart,
he believed that was
the right thing to do.
Now, we have a voice
to speak our minds.
So why we're here, what we want
and who we're fighting for
are things that we
should question.
Well, for starters,
I want to be strong, like Souji.
That's why I fight.
And I hope that he
would be proud of me.
Because I loved him and I
admired him as a swordsman.
Protecting history is protecting
his legacy as well.
[KANESADA]
Well spoken.
And a worthy goal, too.
But let me be frank.
I saw you sparring before,
and you've still got
quite a long way to go.
That's fine.
'Cause now you've got a cool
and strong sparring partner
to show you how it's done.
What d'you say?
[laughs]
Let's see what you've got.
All right, then.
The Tennen Rishin Style
includes fencing, hand-to hand,
staff techniques and uh, uh...
Iai !
Iai .
Quick-draw sword techniques
to round out your arsenal.
Hijikata's method for
striking is the best, I think.
Couldn't agree more!
He used me as his blade
for quite some time,
so I can explain.
Normally, because a
sword handle is held firmly
by the pinky and
the ring finger,
the pinky is always
the first to get injured.
However, with my handle,
he would get hurt near
his index finger and thumb.
That's because he'd put all his
strength in his index finger
every time he would strike.
No one could withstand a blow
from his striking stance.
Without hesitation,
he would thrust like lightning.
Whether it met its mark or not,
he would prepare a
second strike immediately,
then a third and a fourth,
never relenting.
You must rain blows upon your
opponent until they submit.
The Tennen Rishin Style
provides an answer
for every possibly outcome.
[KANESADA] All right,
repetitions have their place,
of course.
But nothing can compare to a
real battle with a real weapon.
[KASHUU]
This is a training hall.
Not a murdering hall.
[KANESADA]
Gimme all you got.
Don't worry, I don't think
you're capable of hurting me.
I don't need you to egg me on;
my sword always finds its mark.
[KASHUU groans]
[HORIKAWA]
You ready? Begin!
[YASUSADA]
I'll warn you.
I've been training with
Kiyomitsu every day.
[YASUSADA grunts]
With my technique,
I can handle anything
you can throw at me.
Two on one?
That's hardly fair!
You said you could
handle anything.
[HORIKAWA yells]
[JIROUTACHI] Forget it.
I'll just go myself.
[YASUSADA gasps]
Damn!
I haven't had any time
to train using this body.
What are you idiots doing?
They're not fighting
for real, are they?
Stop it!
You just got here today and
you're already acting up?
[YASUSADA yells]
Ha! You said you
wanted to be strong
like your old master, right?
Then what exactly do you
think made him so strong?
[SHINSENGUMI 4A laughing]
[YASUSADA]
What made him strong?
Either way, you sure know
how to make us laugh!
You're not just a swordsman;
you're a man of
many talents, huh?
[SHINSENGUMI chattering]
You ready?
Always!
Hijikata's Double attack!
[BOTH grunt]
[KANESADA yells]
[HORIKAWA chuckles]
[YASUSADA laughs]
[KASHUU] Okay, I don't
think anyone's bleeding.
That's good.
[laughing]
That was decidedly not cool.
Still, It can't be a coincidence
that we're all here.
Fighting alongside you
is enough for now.
What's with that face?
Did you remember something?
[YASUSADA] Souji wasn't a hero
because of what he accomplished
in battle.
He was a hero because
he was a good man,
a kind one,
every day of his life.
I don't know if I
can be strong like that,
but I'll try.
By the way...
Who are you?
Must be new.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I am the beloved sword
of Vice Commander Hijikata.
Famously strong and cool,
clearly, my reputation
speaks for itself.
The one and only...
Sword of the Demon
Vice Commander from Hell!
I'll show you punks
who's a demon!
Yeah, you like that?
Huh? Huh? Yeah?
How 'bout this?
[KANESADA] I'll show you
punks who's a demon!
Yeah, you like that? Huh?
[KANESADA] Wow, that's
one heck of a tree you've got.
[HORIKAWA] It's a ten
thousand leaf cherry tree.
[KANESADA]
What's that?
Never heard of one.
[chattering]
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
One more!
I've lived such a
short and sheltered life.
In my ignorance, I never
imagined that this world
could possess such beauty.
Jiroutachi, you reek of alcohol.
What do you mean "I reek"?
It smells great!
Am I supposed to not
drink when we're having
such a nice party?
Is there no drinking
under the tree?
Is that a rule that I
was not made aware of,
because everyone here hates fun?
Then who let me get drunk
in the first place?
It was you, wasn't it?
Seductress!
Just kidding!
I know you and I have a
relationship of mutual respect!
Muah!
We have an understanding
because my body is 95% saké.
[JIROUTACHI]
Huh?
Where'd you go?
What's the deal, Shokudaikiri?
Why did you let me
run out of saké?
That's your fault.
I told you that
was the last of it.
Our human bodies have
brought on a wealth
of new experiences,
but we may be overindulging.
You have been drinking
almost every day.
[JIROUTACHI]
Ah!
Tough luck, Jiroutachi.
You gotta cut back!
[JIROUTACHI] That is the last
thing I ever wanna hear!
You can't pull the rug out
from under me like this!
[sobs] If I can't have saké,
I'm gonna die!
I think his health
may really be in danger!
We can't afford for him
to lose his divine power!
Someone run to the store
and get some saké, quick!
Okay, leave it to me!
C'mon! You too!
Why not? Sounds like fun.
Count me in, you guys!
[HASEBE] Get permission
from the master first,
and buy enough to get
him drunk as a fish!
--[MAEDA] Yes, sir!
--[MIDARE] Okay!
You have our thanks, General!
We won't be gone
too long, promise!
[MIDARE, ATSUSHI]
Shopping time!
[MAEDA]
Don't get carried away, guys.
They sell all
kinds of neat stuff!
[ATSUSHI]
They've got desserts!
I'm buying some for everyone!
[MAEDA]
Atsushi, come on.
There's too much!
I don't know what to get!
It's cool.
I'll buy some snacks
for us while you decide.
Hey, stop that!
Please, let's just get what
we need and hurry back now!
[MIDARE]
Atsushi!
What's this? I want it!
[ATSUSHI] It won't hurt if we
only buy one thing each, right?
I know what I'm going with!
[MIDARE]
Umm... well, your choice.
[MAEDA]
Stop it!
Hasebe's going to be mad
if we get a bunch of junk!
[MIDARE, ATSUSHI]
Eh, it'll be fine.
[ATSUSHI, MAEDA, MIDARE]
We're back!
[JIROUTACHI]
Oh, good!
I was at death's door, for sure!
All right, mission accomplished.
Now bring it here and we--
[gasps]
Look, guys!
They call this thingie
a face pack!
I bet Ichi would love one, huh?
[HASEBE]
Uh...
Look what I got! Osaka Castle!
[HASEBE]
Hmm...
'Kay, one last shot.
Maeda, I trust you
got what we need?
Yep!
And here you go!
[SHOKUDAIKIRI laughing]
Yes. "Drunk as a fish."
I know that's what I told you,
but it's just a saying.
[MAEDA whining]
Look what you've
done to this poor man!
[JIROUTACHI sobbing]
Don't worry, I'll go to
the store and get the saké!
I wonder if you can
be trusted on your own.
I think I should tag along.
If you wanna go that bad,
why don't you just say so?
Whoa, I need this, and
this thing too, definitely!
If you're not careful, all that
greed might consume you.
[NAMAZUO] Oh, I have
to have this thing.
Are you kidding me?
[chuckles]
What do you think?
[NIKKARI] I think you should
consider the feelings of others.
[NAMAZUO]
Oh, good idea!
Let's buy a whole bunch
of these lunchboxes!
I bet everybody'll love them!
[NIKKARI]
Hopefully Hasebe at least,
since you're spending his money.
You don't see anything
you're interested in?
I don't know.
[LAUGHING BAG laughing]
[NAMAZUO]
What's that?
[NIKKARI]
We've returned, bearing gifts.
Like saké?
Something far better,
I assure you.
Here, give it a little squeeze.
[LAUGHING BAG laughing]
It's a laughing bag!
It puts your heart
at ease, right?
Like seeing a dear old friend.
You're right.
It is quite reassuring.
[MIDARE]
Huh?!
[LAUGHING BAG laughing]
I am absolutely
frothing with rage!
Octopus, squid, conger eel,
young yellowtail...!
He's so upset he
can only speak in sushi.
Don't worry, buddy,
I'll get that saké for you.
C'mon, Yamanbagiri, let's go.
But why... me?
I see.
This one suits me
best after all.
[MUTSUNOKAMI]
Hey, man! Smile!
Now, let's see.
[chuckles]
Yep. We need this.
[YAMANBAGIRI]
If you say so.
Well hello, there.
[YAMANBAGIRI]
I'll take you.
[JIROUTACHI]
What is happening?
C'mon, Mitsubou,
we gotta fix this!
We'll save you, okay?
Just hold on a sec!
Your saké is on its way now!
[HASEBE]
You just want an excuse to go!
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Oh, that reminds me,
we're out of eggs.
I should've checked
the refrigerator to see
if we needed anything else.
[TSURUMARU]
Hey, it's that dancing flower
Yamanbagiri bought!
Should we get another one?
Can't have too many, right?
Never mind!
Check out these glasses!
Now it's night!
Hey, that's handy!
These must be training
glasses for swordsmen,
so they can practice night
battles even during the day!
The future really is bright.
Oh! These make it
look like sunset.
[TSURUMARU]
And they make you look awesome!
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
You think so?
Thanks!
I know they're awesome,
but did you have to
buy the entire rack?
It'd be a shame
if I didn't get enough
to share with everyone.
Forget it.
I'll just go myself. Huh?
What are you idiots doing?
They're not fighting
for real, are they?
[JIROUTACHI sighs]
[HASEBE]
Stop it!
You just got here today and
you're already acting up?
I've returned from
the gates of hell!
[KANESADA]
You little pests!
[ALL laughing]
You're the new
recruit, aren't you?
Here! Have a little drinky!
You stink!
[JIROUTACHI]
I'm fragrant!
Don't be shy!
[KANESADA]
Stop touching me!
[HASEBE gasps]
[MAEDA]
There we go.
[laughing]