[KOGITSUNEMARU]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
Born from the heart of swords,
we travel through time to
intercept and eliminate them.
But you'd rather dance
with this little fox, right?
[KASHUU, YASUSADA]
This is a tale of the legendary
Sword Warriors
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in a certain citadel.
[AKASHI]
This is for me?
Thank you.
And what's it for?
Okay, of course.
Right. If I think
of anything else,
I'll ask Hotarumaru
and the others.
Now, if everything is
in order, I'll take my leave.
[AKASHI]
Oh, hello.
They certainly like to run
their mouth, don't they?
Well, never mind that.
More importantly, when's dinner?
We're all alone, right?
Yeah.
What's this about?
That's a rather serious look
you're both aiming at me.
Listen, Kuniyuki...
[AKASHI]
Hm?
We still need to take
you to greet everyone
at the citadel.
Think you could be bit
more proper, please?
"A bit more proper?"
Like... the way I act?
[AIZEN]
Yeah.
[AKASHI]
That's not my thing--
I don't care what
people think of me.
But first impressions matter!
Just be friendly
and polite, you know?
I'm confused.
What's not to like about me?
[HOTARUMARU] Okay, "friendly"
might be too much to hope for.
[AKASHI]
Come on, stop whispering.
Why is this such a big deal?
We're just kind of worried
about you fitting in
and making friends here.
That sort of thing.
You're serious. Am I
really that much trouble?
[HOTARUMARU] You do
hate working an awful lot.
[yawns]
Motivation isn't my strong
point-- that much is true.
That's exactly what
we're talking about!
Caring for each other is an
important part of living here!
We both agree.
[HOTARUMARU]
Mm-hmm.
Maybe just don't...
expect so much from me?
[AKASHI sighs]
Stop giving me that look.
I can't magically start
caring about something
just because you tell me to.
Start with the
simple stuff, you know.
Like helping people
when they're in trouble.
Yeah, easy!
Or pitching in with the
chores like everyone else.
Do some weeding.
Or sweeping.
Fold some laundry, maybe,
or wash some dishes.
[AKASHI]
My specialty is eating.
Can I do that?
I want you to like it here,
and I want everyone
here to like you.
Is that too much to ask?
Kuniyuki?
[AKASHI]
Bathroom.
[AIZEN]
Oh, here, I'll show you the way.
[AKASHI] It's just down
the hallway, right?
We passed it earlier. I know.
You sure?
We might have
overdone it a little bit.
I mean, he just got here.
You and I both know that
subtlety wouldn't work on him.
I guess you're right.
But still.
You just want the best for him.
Same with me.
If we don't help,
he'll just hole himself up.
"I don't need to meet people and
people don't need to meet me"
sort of thing.
Maybe I was a little hard
on him for his first day here.
He's been gone a while.
Uh-huh.
Do you think he got lost?
[HASEBE screams]
[AIZEN]
What wrong?
[YASUSADA] I took my eyes
off the field for a second,
then this happened.
[HASEBE]
Ruined! The crops are ruined!
And we were just
about to harvest them!
Yeah, that looks bad all right.
This is a tragedy!
What could've done this?
Some sort of wild animal.
I suppose the traps
that I set weren't enough.
[YASUSADA]
Wait, that's a shoe print!
[GROUP gasps]
Something wrong?
We're roasting sweet potatoes,
or we were about to.
Uh-huh. We collected a
bunch of dried leaves to burn,
but when we came back,
they weren't here anymore.
Maybe someone thought
they were trash
and threw them away.
[KASHUU]
Guess we'll gather some more.
[KASEN]
What is this madness?
They were so clean
only moments ago--
their pure whiteness
shining in the sun.
Now they're perfectly filthy.
You must be dead inside.
It's just laundry.
That's his whole life.
This is odd.
[ALL]
Hmm?
They were clearly
knocked to the ground,
and yet they're
folded so neatly.
Is this someone's
idea of a joke?
You don't think
it was him, do you?
It could be, but why?
He doesn't care about laundry.
Unless it's food, it might
as well be invisible.
What are you muttering about?
Do you two know something?
No, sir!
You don't think it's
the new recruit, do you?
If not, it could be the enemy!
They've infiltrated our base?
We've gotta go find him fast.
What if it was Kuniyuki?
I know he's not very friendly,
but this seems like
a stretch to me.
Only way to find out
is to ask him ourselves.
That's odd.
I could've sworn I left
the rice balls here.
Did someone steal
the plate, too?
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Who would do that?
[AIZEN] Okay, missing food?
Now I'm worried.
Wasn't he eating
before he left, though?
[HOTARUMARU, AIZEN]
Kuniyuki!
[AKASHI]
You two are pale as ghosts.
What's the problem?
Are you the culprit?
Let's go.
If we apologize together,
maybe they'll understand.
[AKASHI]
What are you talking about?
You stole those rice balls,
then there's the laundry
and the crop fields.
[HASEBE] I think it's
time for an explanation.
I haven't seen
you around before.
You must be the new recruit.
The name is Akashi Kuniyuki.
A pleasure to meet you all.
What's that?
This plate?
Sorry, I was really hungry.
[KASEN] Are you the one
who dirtied the laundry?
[AKASHI]
Yes, my hand slipped.
[YASUSADA] And did you
damage the crops, too?
Uh-huh.
[KASHUU] And threw away
our dried leaves?
[AKASHI]
Indeed--Guilty as charged.
This guy's certainly
a troublemaker, isn't he?
[AIZEN]
He's not!
[HOTARUMARU]
I promise!
[AIZEN]
He was just running an errand,
and he got confused, is all.
It's just 'cause he's new here.
You don't have
to lie for my sake.
Listen to me!
[YAGEN]
Hey!
Some of my medicine is missing.
Who took it?
Wait, what's up?
You stole medicine too?
Yes, I did.
[HASEBE]
Care to tell us why?
[TANUKI howling]
What is that?
[AKASHI]
I told you to hide, didn't I?
So that's it!
[YASUSADA]
A-ha!
[KASEN]
They're tanuki .
[KASHUU]
We found the leaves.
What happened?
You're gonna make me
explain, aren't you?
[AIZEN]
That would be nice, yeah.
[AKASHI] I heard them crying
when I was coming back
from the bathroom.
[TANUKI howling]
[AKASHI]
Two children under the porch.
I wondered where
the mother went,
so I went searching, just in
case something bad had happened.
[AKASHI]
What a mess.
[AKASHI] You're not gonna make
this easy for me, are you?
[HASEBE] Then, it was the tanuki
that caused all this mischief,
not you.
[AKASHI]
Not quite.
I still borrowed a couple
of things, after all.
You did it for the tanuki ,
so we'll forgive you.
Thanks for understanding.
I'm glad it all worked out.
You really had us freaking
out for a second there.
It is a bit out
of character for you.
[AKASHI] I'm supposed to
be your guardian, right?
Maybe I related to
this mother a little.
And we care for each
other at the citadel.
That is what you told me, right?
[NIKKARI]
All's well that ends well.
[KASEN] No harm in doing
the laundry again.
[AKASHI chuckles]
You know what this means.
Time to start prepping for
Akashi's welcoming party.
I'm not too busy;
let me help you out.
That's really unnecessary.
It's nothing to celebrate.
No, really, we insist.
It's not every day a new
comrade joins us, you know.
That's right!
Here, let me see it.
I might be able to help its leg.
That would be great.
[AIZEN chuckles]
He's going to fit in just fine.
[HOTARUMARU] Guess we didn't
need to worry that much anyway.
Guess not.
Hey! Hotarumaru, Aizen!
I think I'd like to meet
everyone else after all.
[BOTH laugh]
--[AIZEN] Okay!
--[HOTARUMARU] Sure!
[YASUSADA]
Whoa, that looks tasty!
I told you to wait
till it cools, didn't I?
[BOTH laughing]
[AIZEN laughs]
If you're really awesome,
you put red bean paste on top.
[AIZEN]
Mmm! Mmm!
So good!
Okay, I get it!
You don't have to spit!
Bean paste, huh?
That's fine, but I was told
that this mayonnaise stuff
goes with everything.
Disgusting!
The modern world is full
of lies and deception!
[HOTARUMARU] Maybe try
some moderation next time.
[AKASHI] Suffer with me.
I'm lonely. Here.
Suffer alone!
[laughs]
What a delightful
group they are!
Indeed.
I do like them.
[ISHIKIRIMARU] Akashi is
our 46th Sword Warrior.
It feels like the citadel
gets more lively every day.
Aren't those so hot?
Is your tongue made of lava?
[MIKAZUKI chuckles]
I would expect nothing
less of Benkei's polearm.
His master was rather tough.
[IWATOOSHI laughs]
Wait a second!
If he's like Benkei,
does that mean I'm handsome
like Yoshitsune?
[MIKAZUKI laughs]
That seems to be the case.
[IMANOTSURUGI]
Yay!
And Yamatonokami
here is like Ohkita Souji
from the Shinsengumi.
Kind of.
[KASHUU laughs]
"Kind of."
[laughing]
[IWATOOSHI laughing]
Yamatonokami's as
good with a sword as Okita,
and that's all
that matters to me.
And with Kashuu around, it's
almost like having two Okitas.
They've got more
experience than anyone else.
You guys don't need
to change a thing.
Of course not.
But thank you.
Glad we pass.
[KASHUU]
Something on your mind?
Not really.
I was just wondering
what Kogitsunemaru's
previous master was like.
[ISHIKIRIMARU]
Oh, hello.
How long have you been here?
Honebami Toushirou.
You're the master's attendant
right now, correct?
What's that in your hand?
Our dispatch orders.
Ah.
[HONEBAMI] Yamatonokami
Yasusada, Mikazuki Munechika.
Kogitsunemaru.
I will be happy to serve.
Mm-hmm.
Shall we prepare to depart?
And also, Tsurumaru Kuninaga,
Yagen Toushirou,
and your captain this time,
Ichigo Hitofuri.
I'll go inform them while
everyone else gets ready.
Don't waste any time.
An uchigatana , a tantou ,
and four tachis this time.
I don't think I've ever
seen a team composition
like this before.
Any comments, Captain?
If the master
wants to get creative,
then I'll do my best
to accommodate that.
I'm not worried.
I know you'll take care of us.
I'm honored to battle beside
one of the Five Great Swords
of Japan.
So give us a good show!
[MIKAZUKI laughs]
We'll see if this old man
has any tricks left in him.
Is that festival music?
[YASUSADA]
I don't hear anything.
You must have good ears, huh?
I am a wild beast.
[gunshot]
That's gunfire.
I do like a surprise,
even if it comes during battle.
As long as I survive, that is.
We let our guard down.
Is everyone ready to go?
Are you all right?
I'll be fine.
Sadly, I can't say the same for
the comb the master gave me.
We've got some surprises
lined up for them too, right?
I hope so.
We have to earn our
wages somehow, don't we?
Ready?
Charge!
[YAGEN]
You're mine now, monster!
[TSURUMARU]
Ha!
Tsurumaru.
Would it be all right
if I left the rest to you?
What's up?
It's Kogitsunemaru.
I fear his lack of
real combat experience
may place him in danger.
[TSURUMARU]
No problem.
I got this under control.
[SOLDIER 10D growls]
[WHITE FOX howls]]
I'll run you through the hilt.
Keep your focus!
Let's back him up!
I didn't want to show off,
but you've left me no choice.
Whoa!
That... was so cool.
Splendid, my friend.
Is that all of them, then?
There's one more.
Ichigo and Yagen are handling
it, so I'm sure it's fine.
It's raining?
Yeah, that's weird,
since the sky is clear.
[YASUSADA]
I hope this isn't a bad omen.
[TSURUMARU] Like you said,
Ichigo can handle things.
He's got Yagen with him too.
They'll be fine.
[KOGITSUNEMARU]
Is that a--?
[YASUSADA]
Kogitsunemaru.
You're not injured, are you?
If you need first aid,
say something.
No.
I'm fine.
Whoa.
It's our lucky day, guys!
There's a house right there.
Let's get out of the rain!
[TSURUMARU]
Anybody home?
A blacksmith?
Interesting.
Their fire is still
burning, no less.
I'm sure they'll return shortly.
[TSURUMARU]
Who gave you permission
to enter my
abode, trespassers?
[MIKAZUKI laughing]
I never thought I'd
see a crane become a fox.
C'mon, put that thing back.
We can't just make
ourselves at home here.
[laughs]
Don't worry about it.
Besides, if we don't change,
we're going to catch a cold.
We already let ourselves in.
[YASUSADA]
Here you go.
Strange how everything fits,
but I'm not complaining.
It's nice that we've
been able to rest for a bit,
but we really should look
for Ichigo and Yagen.
[MIKAZUKI] "When Munechika
strikes with his hammer..."
[KOGITSUNEMARU] "...the fox
god becomes a longsword."
What is that, a poem?
Kokaji .
A play about Kogitsunemaru.
Wow. You're a celebrity!
How does it go?
Must be about a fox, huh?
[MIKAZUKI] Emperor Ichijou
had a mysterious dream,
urging him to forge a blade,
so he sent his envoy
to the famous swordsmith,
Sanjou Munechika,
in hopes that he
could do the job.
However, the sword of
dreams was not something
Munechika could
craft on his own.
Therefore, the troubled
swordsmith sought help
from the great god Inari.
Upon hearing the pleas
of Sanjou Munechika,
the god took the form of
a white fox and appeared
before him to
assist in his work.
And so, with
the god at his side,
the master blacksmith
forged a sword
worthy of the emperor's dream.
[MIKAZUKI] And that is our
dear friend, Kogitsunemaru.
This tale has been passed
on throughout the ages
and is even known
during the master's time,
believe it or not.
So, in a sense,
you're correct in saying
Kogitsunemaru
is a celebrity.
So it's not just his old master,
but people through all
the ages who have loved him.
It's no surprise that he's
become such a powerful sword,
and he even looks
like a superstar.
Or a fox.
What, is your hand
supposed to be a fox face?
[TSURUMARU]
Isn't it obvious?
[KOGITSUNEMARU chuckles] If you
keep telling stories about me,
I'm going to need a drink.
[laughing]
Wha--?
[TSURUMARU]
I wonder what that feels like.
To have your story passed
down from generation
to generation like that.
Well, I would be proud.
Though it's a little
humbling too, I guess.
I don't know,
how would you feel?
[TSURUMARU]
Me?
I don't surprise easy, but...
[YASUSADA]
You'd be surprised.
[ALL laughing]
Hello?
Wait...
What happened?
Why are you all
holding those leaves?
I thought it was saké.
[laughing]
Now that's a surprise.
This time, I think
that's my line.
Is there a reason you're
all sitting on the ground?
[YASUSADA]
Um, yes?
I mean, not really... Uh...
[TSURUMARU] I think the
foxes played a prank on us.
[KOGITSUNEMARU]
My wounds have all healed.
The comb!
Huh? It's fixed!
[KOGITSUNEMARU]
My, what a conscientious fellow.
[MIKAZUKI laughing]
Today was a grand adventure!
I'm still confused.
Can you explain this again?
I'm going to have a hard time
with my mission report.
Don't ruin the moment.
We'll tell you later, 'kay?
I wonder if this story
will be passed down too.
Maybe.
[KOGITSUNEMARU] The legend
is given life through me
and I am given life
through the legend.
It is only because
people remember
that I am able to exist.
Therefore, I must cherish
these memories all the greater.
[YASUSADA]
My memories aren't just my own--
they're the story
of the Shinsengumi
that the entire world shares.
But that doesn't make
them any less special.
Just the opposite.
[NAGASONE]
I am Nagasone Kotetsu,
beloved sword of Kondo Isami.
Commander of the Shinsengumi.
Glad you finally made it.
I may be a fake,
but I'll work twice as hard
as the real thing.
Oh, it's you!
You're Yasusada, right?
[YASUSADA]
Yeah.
It's like the Shinsengumi
is back together again!