[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
The year is 2205 AD.
The History Retrograde Army
seeks to control the world
by altering its past.
Born from the heart of swords,
we travel through time to
intercept and eliminate them.
Sounds cool when
you put it that way.
[KASHUU, YASUSADA]
This is a tale of the legendary
Sword Warriors
and the Hanamaru days
they spent in a certain citadel.
Finally.
If there's anything
else you need,
don't hesitate to ask.
[SHISHIOU laughing]
Would you please be quiet?
Hey!
[SHISHIOU]
Master!
I summoned a new sword for you!
He should be here about
four hours from now!
You... did... what?
And... there.
I outdid myself this time.
Like it?
Sure. They're cute.
Oh, they're "cute"?
Kind of a weak
compliment, isn't it?
If you're gonna say something,
try being a little
more specific.
Notice anything
different, maybe?
Uh, the color?
It's brighter!
That's more like it!
I have to make sure I
look my best at all times.
Otherwise, the master might
not choose me for missions.
You think looking
cute matters that much?
Well let me put it this way.
If you have to choose between
something cute or ugly,
cute always wins.
I was the first one summoned
here to the citadel,
so I have a standard to upkeep.
I'm very grateful
for the master's favor,
though I doubt it will last.
[KASHUU]
In fact,
I have a feeling I'll be
old news any day now.
[YASUSADA]
What do you mean?
[TSURUMARU sighs]
So? What'd you need to discuss?
You don't usually invite me
to take a bath with you
unless you've got
something to talk about.
Like what to make
for dinner, maybe?
An omelet's good.
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
No. It's not about dinner.
It's about Kara.
He joined last week,
but he's not fitting in.
[TSURUMARU]
Ookurikara. Right.
Making friends
is a waste of time.
Yeah, I see what your sayin'.
We're pretty tight-knit here.
So he's gonna be miserable
with an attitude like that.
Well, hopefully something'll
come along to change his mind.
Uh-oh.
[KASEN]
Lovely.
[NAKIGITSUNE] I took a peek
outside, but it's still pouring.
I know there's
nothing I can do,
but they never
dry properly indoors.
As long as we don't get called
on a mission, we'll be fine.
But if something does come up,
we'll either be very
soggy or naked.
At least my
tattered cloak is dry.
Why don't we stop
stressing and have some tea?
We could just borrow
something, right?
Borrow their battle clothing?
[YAMANBAGIRI] I don't even like
people touching my stuff.
I suppose we should
ask around a bit first.
I know!
Let's find someone with
lots of battle clothes.
Maybe they'll share.
Wait! We still have
clothes to hang up.
Are you trying to
get out of helping?
[AIZEN]
Sure, I'll share!
No deity looks better on
a tee shirt than Aizen Myoou!
You made him fat!
He's supposed to be
super cool and buff!
[ripping noise]
Who did that?
Somebody is ripping up
my namesake!
I'm a little
on the big side.
My apologies to
the short swords.
You won't win
any fights like that.
[NAKIGITSUNE]
Do you have any baby clothes?
[KASEN]
Forgive me, Shokudaikiri.
I assure you, I wouldn't be
rummaging through your closet
if it wasn't an
emergency situation.
[NAKIGITSUNE] A whole closet
of these weird clothes?
Creepy, huh, Nakigitsune?
[YAMANBAGIRI]
What's the point?
He keeps them in
immaculate shape, too.
I-I don't think we should
wear these; we'll get them--
Never mind.
Oh, I see!
These suits make us
look just like employees
in a fancy service restaurant.
What's a service restaurant?
I don't get it.
I saw it in one of
the master's magazines.
Well-dressed men serving drinks
and chatting with women.
Everyone quite happy.
Host, or something.
An honorable profession,
for gentlemen, I'm sure.
Huh...
[door opens]
What's going on?
[KASEN]
Uhh...
It's not what it looks like.
[TIGER CUB yawns]
Wait.
Please explain this
host thing to me again.
It's a hospitality service.
I didn't know.
Don't worry, wearing the
uniform is a nice thing.
It seemed like a quaint,
friendly business.
That sounds like
just what we need.
If we can show him a
good time, he might open up!
[KASEN]
Who do you mean?
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Kara, of course.
Ohkurikara?
[NAKIGITSUNE]
Oh.
Well, I don't know.
[TSURUMARU laughs]
It's a tall order, but why not?
As I'm certain you've noticed,
he's had a difficult
time fitting in.
This could change everything!
I'm not sure.
[SHOKUDAIKIRI] Then I'll need
you to return my clothes,
please.
[ALL]
D'aw!
[KASEN] It seems they've
taken a liking to them.
We could at least
give it a try, right?
I don't know how this
is supposed to go,
but we can provide some
sort of hospitality, I'm sure.
Understood.
Might as well.
We can start out
with tea and dumplings.
If Shokudaikiri is for it, fine.
I'm confident that I
can be very hospitable.
I appreciate it.
All right, if that's the plan.
I'll start setting things up.
Hospitality.
[YAGEN]
Hmm...
[YAMANBAGIRI]
What should I do?
[OOKURIKARA]
Whatever it is, I don't care.
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Come on! Just humor me.
We're happy to have you!
[OOKURIKARA]
This is torture.
[KASEN] Let us begin
with a presentation.
[OOKURIKARA]
Please, no...
Gaze upon this vase, and
imagine what flower it holds.
[ALL]
Huh?
Huh? But this presentation
was devised by Sen no Rikyuu,
revered master of
the tea ceremony!
Even Nobunaga praised his
elegance and creativity!
[KASEN] Perhaps it's a bit too
much elegance right off the bat.
I should have warmed
them up a bit first.
The most important part of
the ceremony is still the tea.
My presentation was
a bit avant-garde.
Let's stick to the basics,
shall we?
I'm confident that you will
enjoy its refined flavor.
[KASEN]
It's not for you.
[YAGEN] Lord Nobunaga
was actually a master
of hospitality.
He would offer his
guests unusual fruits
gathered from all
over the world.
[ALL]
Whoa!
[YAGEN]
Now please, indulge.
[ALL]
In what?
I suppose it's my turn now, huh?
[YAMANBAGIRI] I thought I could
entertain him with a funny story
or something,
but that's obviously
not going to happen.
What'd they expect
from a copy like me?
Crap, this is getting awkward.
Say something clever,
damn it! Hurry!
He's acting weird.
Is he okay?
[NAKIGITSUNE] They say that
animals have the ability
to heal your spirit.
You're not allergic
to foxes, are you?
I hope not.
[NAKIGITSUNE] Give my tail
a pet and see if it makes you
feel any better.
So fluffy.
[koto music]
I know that sound.
[koto continues]
[TSURUMARU laughs]
I'm sorry, I'm not good
enough to play a whole song.
Masamune's wife played
the koto, didn't she?
I thought maybe you heard it
in the time you spent with them.
[koto music]
I like it.
It's a nice sound.
One filled with kindness.
He's smiling!
Yeah.
[OOKURIKARA]
Just like Lord Masamune.
[SHOKUDAIKIRI] One who has not
experienced the joy of cooking
is the owner of a poor heart.
There is no greater hospitality
than a meal, lovingly prepared.
I hope that it's to your liking.
I see.
So this is the
flavor of kindness.
[YAGEN]
Could I have a taste as well?
[UGUISUMARU]
Then me, please.
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
There's plenty to go around.
Not bad.
Delicious.
Kara.
Let's talk about old times.
So, here's a Masamune story.
This one's my favorite.
[BOTH gasp]
[HASEBE]
This... this is it!
[BOTH yell]
[SHISHIOU]
Master! He's here!
[laughing, chattering]
C'mon, boys, more saké!
[GROUP]
He's gonna be so mad.
Wait. There's a good
explanation for this.
[HASEBE]
He's here.
[ALL]
Huh?
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Uh... Who?
Guess he wandered off.
[HASEBE]
Great.
Well, hopefully someone showed
him to the master's room.
[UGUISUMARU] The weather
cleared up just for you.
[MIKAZUKI]
Did it, now?
How lovely.
Any luck?
Although it might
help if he'd tell us
who we were looking for.
Wait a second,
who are you talking to?
[UGUISUMARU]
Oh.
That would be my new
tea-drinking associate.
[MIKAZUKI laughs]
An introduction is in order.
I am the sword called
Mikazuki Munechika.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Mikazuki?
His creation marked the
beginning of sword-making
as we know it today.
He's hailed as the
most beautiful of the
Five Great Swords of Japan.
An unparalleled masterpiece.
[YASUSADA]
He doesn't act like it, though.
He seems kinda like an old man.
[MIKAZUKI laughs]
I was forged during
the eleventh century.
That would make me quite old.
[TSURUMARU] Hey, we finally
got a Sanjou sword, huh?
I'm a Goujou.
The name's Tsurumaru.
Well!
A sincere honor.
[TSURUMARU] This place
is called the citadel,
if you haven't heard.
It's pretty big, so let me
show you around later.
I should have said so,
but I am Uguisumaru.
Did you happen to see
Ookanehira before we met?
No, only Hasebe and
Shishiou, I'm afraid.
Ah, if you don't mind me asking,
what are the strange black
clothes you're all wearing?
Maybe you heard, but the
master's been looking forward
to his arrival more than
any other sword out there.
I'm glad he made it.
Yeah? Not as glad as
the master, I'm sure.
You say that like
it's a bad thing.
Come on.
Could you be any more naïve?
The master loved us before,
but that's no guarantee
now that he's here.
Huh?
I guess we'll find out.
All right, I hope you
guys are ready to rock!
[laughs]
Bam!
'Cause we got
ourselves a mission!
That's sudden.
My laundry nightmare
is coming true.
[SHISHIOU]
I'll read the dispatch.
The captain is...
Tachi Mikazuki Munechika.
[KASHUU] He just got here
and he's captain already?
[SHISHIOU] Next up, Uchigatana
Kashuu Kiyomitsu.
Oh. Uh, right.
[SHISHIOU]
Tantou... Gokotai!
That's all.
--[SHOKUDAIKIRI] Only three?
--[YAGEN] That's odd.
Hi, Shishiou,
do you need something?
[SHISHIOU]
You've been called on a mission.
O-Okay.
And...
Looks like you guys're headed to
Utsunomiya Castle for this one.
1868.
[ALL] Huh?
[YAGEN] Again?
This isn't the first time
we've been sent there.
The enemy must have
something in mind, huh?
They keep intruding
on the battle
between the shogunate's army
and the new government's army,
but I don't know why
that's so important.
The soldiers they send
aren't very strong, either.
We've beaten them
dozens of times.
I don't get it.
[SHOKUDAIKIRI]
Still, why a three-sword team?
I stopped trying to figure
out the master's plans.
I just go with it.
Enough small talk!
Go get ready for battle!
Only thirty minutes
till you take off.
Good luck!
Utsunomiya Castle again?
You got this.
[KASHUU] The master is
already favoring Mikazuki.
They probably want to
train him to be captain
on as many missions as possible.
I knew this would happen.
I'm just there for support.
To help him grow stronger.
Speaking of which,
that's probably the plan
with Gokotai, too.
He hasn't been on many missions
lately and he lacks confidence.
Let's hurry up and
get this over with.
[MIKAZUKI]
Pardon the delay.
I love your battle clothes!
You look super cool!
From the master. Carry it.
A gift of some sort?
It's a protection charm.
If something bad happens,
it'll keep you safe.
[MIKAZUKI]
I see.
Then I shall treasure it.
It's your first battle,
so there's still a great
deal you don't know.
If you have any questions,
ask Kashuu.
Thank you, I will.
I'm grateful to
have you, Kashuu.
Yeah, yeah.
First, you have to
operate that device.
Oh.
Don't worry. Just watch me.
The date, time,
and then the place.
Right, let's do this.
Come back safe.
[HASEBE]
Stay vigilant.
Huh... So this is
Utsunomiya, is it?
My, what a splendid castle.
We start off by
scouting the area
to form a strategy of attack.
Very well, then.
Let's see.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hmm...
Captain...
There's a gate right behind us.
Why don't we start with that?
[GOKOTAI gasps]
[GOKOTAI]
Th-The enemy is here!
[MIKAZUKI]
Are they, now?
Hello, there!
[SOLDIER 5A growls]
[MIKAZUKI]
Kashuu?
[SOLDIER 5A grunts]
Oh, my. Excellent swordplay.
[KASHUU] I've been working
on that one with Yasusada.
These guys don't stand a chance.
[GOKOTAI yells]
[SOLDIER 5B growls]
Gokotai!
Damn it!
He's not gonna hold out.
[SOLDIER 5C growls]
[GOKOTAI yells]
Mikazuki!
[MIKAZUKI laughing]
I'm sorry, I suppose
I shouldn't be laughing.
[MIKAZUKI]
There's a fire inside me.
Time to let it burn.
[MIKAZUKI]
Ha!
[KASHUU] What the hell
does he need me for?
Mikazuki's in a class
of his own.
[KASHUU grunts]
[KASHUU] I wonder if the master
was trying to teach me a lesson
in humility.
[YASUSADA]
Huh?
[KASHUU] I've gotten too
arrogant, and sloppy.
This was a simple mission
and I let the enemy ambush us.
[YASUSADA]
It happens.
I put Gokotai's life in danger.
Mikazuki suffered those
injuries because of me, as well.
I was shown how
weak I really am.
It was a test and
I failed it miserably.
[sighs]
The master must hate me now.
Come on.
[MIKAZUKI]
You're greatly mistaken.
[YASUSADA] Oh, wow, finished
with your repairs already?
Indeed.
They took excellent care of me.
[MIKAZUKI]
May I have a seat here?
[KASHUU]
Sure.
[MIKAZUKI] I just returned
from the master's room,
where I delivered
the battle report.
Aditionally, I was told why
you and I were chosen
to carry out this
mission together.
It's quite simple.
The master wanted me to see
our strongest warrior in action.
The master was ceaseless
in their praise of your methods
and stressed that there is no
finer model for me to emulate.
You're quite popular, it seems.
How can you say that
when I wasn't able
to protect you or Gokotai?
We all played our parts
well in that battle.
Your efforts allowed me
to protect him instead.
And to show you what
I'm capable of, of course.
I may be an old man,
but I can be rather useful.
I wish you had been
there, too, Yamatonokami.
Though I'm sure we'll
practice together soon.
[MIKAZUKI] And I hope that
you'll share your wisdom
with us both, Kashuu.
How do you do it?
How are you so kind to me?
Where does that come from?
[MIKAZUKI laughs]
I never thought
of myself as kind, but...
"Kindness" is understanding
another person,
much like seeing
through an opponent.
Perhaps I've tempered this
understanding through time.
I should be flattered.
Kindness is strength, after all.
[KASHUU laughs]
You sound like an old man
when you say stuff like that.
[MIKAZUKI]
Because I am!
[laughs]
Splendid. Life is splendid.