[HARUHIRO panting]
[roars]
--Gee, watch where you're going!
--Oh, it's you. Shut up!
You're not the only
one who's fighting here!
Sometimes I think
I might as well be.
[MOGUZO]
Thank you!
[HARUHIRO] This is Yume's new
skill. It's called Star Strike.
I've got this one.
Go help that idiot. He needs it.
You're the only idiot I see.
[yells]
[HARUHIRO]
Ready... Spider!
[MOGUZO]
Huh?
Stay back!
[HARUHIRO]
Huh?
Exhaust, now!
I call upon your power,
Dark Skullhell!
Bring never-ending fear
to those who refuse to obey!
Dread... Terror!
[HARUHIRO]
This generates fear,
making it difficult for
your opponent to fight
with a clear head.
It's magic only a
Dark Knight can cast.
This isn't how it's
supposed to work!
Exhaust!
He does seem confused,
but that's only making him
fight more fiercely.
[RANTA]
Exhaust! Exhaust! Exhaust!
Anger! Exhaust!
So... should I
still "stay back"?
[RANTA] Exhaust! Mind your
own business, will ya?
He's mine! My prey!
My nemesis!
[SHIHORU]
Um...
Are you sure you
don't want help?
I can handle this on my own!
Hatred!
All right, now's my chance!
Die!
[KOBOLD D groans]
[MARY]
Do you see that nose ring?
It's a kobold's
protective charm.
Every kobold has one.
They're like talismans to
keep the wearer from harm.
Really?
Well, for something
so important,
that ring sure doesn't look like
it would be worth very much.
[MARY] The kobolds in
the first level of the mine
are outsiders among
their own kind.
Sort of low-level ruffians.
They're poorly equipped
and by far the weakest
of the creatures.
Obviously, that means they're
also the easiest to defeat.
Volunteer Soldiers refer
to these as lesser kobolds.
[HARUHIRO] So these guys are
the poorest of the bunch, then.
I guess the others we face
will have better talismans.
[MARY]
Yes.
[RANTA] Hmph.
That's all very interesting.
I'll be taking this now.
What's that look for?
Nothing.
[HARUHIRO] I'm pretty sure
there's a nicer way
of claiming the spoils
from a fight.
But that's Ranta for you.
What can I do?
Whatever. Its fine.
[HARUHIRO]
This is where they live.
The mine is the kobolds' home.
So as far as they're
concerned, we're invaders.
But what does it matter
if we feel guilty?
It doesn't change anything.
We can remove their
talismans respectfully
or rip them off violently.
The end result
is still the same.
The outcome's the same.
It's us who are different.
Ranta takes what he
wants without hesitation.
But I'm trying to make up
for the guilt I feel.
Maybe that means
I'm a hypocrite.
Oh well.
That's not going to
make me change the way
I handle this sort of thing.
Doesn't matter if we're talking
about a friend or an enemy.
I think that all the dead
deserve respect.
C'mon, let's go.
[MARY] The Cyrene Mine
has more than ten levels.
Its population is broken
down into three castes.
There are lesser kobolds, normal
kobolds, and elder kobolds.
Status determines a lot.
Only the elders may
freely use the gondola.
[HARUHIRO]
The gondola?
[MARY] There is a gondola
installed in the mineshaft.
It operates from
the third layer down.
But when it comes to
navigating between levels,
we'll mostly be using the wells.
[MOGUZO] The gondola
must be heavily guarded,
so it makes sense to avoid it.
[MARY]
Exactly.
Now, the Elders are the leaders,
the normal ones are the workers.
As for the lesser kobolds,
they don't really have
any status to speak of.
[YUME]
Sounds like life's pretty tough
unless you're one of the elders.
We've only fought the
lesser kobolds so far,
but that's going to change.
The higher castes
are further down.
That means we all need
to keep our guards up.
[howling]
[gasps]
Wow, they sure are noisy.
What's all the howling about?
[MARY] They do a lot of howling,
especially certain times of day.
But don't worry.
Sleeping kobolds only wake up
if something big's going on.
Does anyone else hear that?
It's like a low rumbling?
[RANTA]
Whoa!
[HARUHIRO]
They really are heavy sleepers.
Think I should kill 'em?
It'll be nice and quick.
It wouldn't take a lot of effort
or put us at much risk.
Easy money.
What's wrong with you?
Are you some kind of demon?
Come on, you know
better than that.
I'll tell you some stuff about
my class; maybe that will help.
Dark Knights aren't demons.
Just warriors serving
the Dark God Skullhell.
Our beliefs are simple.
Everyone's equal in death,
good or bad, rich or poor.
You've all heard me talk
about collecting Vices before,
haven't you?
Well, Vices are what
Dark Knights value.
They're the antithesis of
what you narrow-minded people
care about, like "morals"
or "good deeds," you follow?
The antithesis.
It's important so I'll
say it one more time.
Antithesis! Got it?
We're all gonna die anyway,
so why should we be
bound by stupid ideals
that do nothing but make
our lives a whole lot harder
and less enjoyable?
We should be driven by
our instincts, our impulses,
our desires.
Not some useless moral
code dictated by society.
We live our lives and
then we die. All of us.
We're equal in the end.
See what I'm saying?
[HARUHIRO]
You coming?
[RANTA]
Hey, listen to me!
[HARUHIRO] Yeah, yeah.
I'm listening, I'm listening.
[RANTA]
Ugh. You're so full of it!
Ohm, Rel, Ect. Nemun, Dash!
[HARUHIRO] Shihoru learned
a new skill, too.
It's called Shadow Bond.
It binds enemies' legs to
the ground so they can't move.
Like Sleepy Shadow,
it becomes less effective
the more worked up
an opponent is.
And strong opponents
can break free of it.
Shadow Bond isn't a foolproof
weapon, but it sure is handy.
Thank you!
[KOBOLDS groaning]
[HARUHIRO]
There it is. I know what to do.
[HARUHIRO] If I trust
the light, it will guide me.
I need to concentrate,
but stay calm,
and keep my breathing even.
If I move too quickly,
the light will disappear.
But I can't hesitate, either.
There's no time to worry
about whether I'm doing
everything right.
When I see the streak,
my body should already
be moving with it.
Almost like they're connected.
Otherwise, it won't work.
[YUME]
That spell is amazing!
It was like those guys
were glued to the ground.
Oh... Um, thank you.
These are the normal kobolds?
They weren't much tougher
than the other ones.
The third layer won't
be quite so easy.
That's where the elders are.
They're better equipped and
they know how to strategize.
[RANTA]
Hey, what're you waiting for?
Aren't we going down there?
[HARUHIRO]
No.
I think that we should head
back to Ortana for now.
[RANTA]
Wha?
We've done enough
here for today.
We'll come back, don't worry.
I just don't want us
to wear ourselves out.
[RANTA] Speak for yourself.
I'm not tired at all.
[HARUHIRO]
Mary?
I'm okay.
Really. I'm all right.
[HARUHIRO] Ranta and I
are having some issues.
Our personalities aren't
exactly what you might call
"compatible."
We barely avoided having
a full-on fight today.
From what I can tell, he doesn't
seem to be getting along
with Yume, Shihoru,
or Mary either.
Should I be doing
something about him?
Is it my job as the leader?
What would Manato do
if it were up to him?
It's hard to know for sure.
Honestly, I don't think
he liked Ranta very much.
But maybe liking him
wasn't important to Manato,
as long as he still
got the job done.
Ranta wasn't nearly as
disrespectful or defiant
with Manato as he is
now that I'm the leader.
And even if he tried to hide it,
he was pretty shaken up
when Manato died.
[sighs]
[HARUHIRO]
Why are things so different now?
Is it something I'm doing?
Hey, Ranta?
[RANTA]
What do you want?
Good, you're awake.
Think we could talk
about some stuff?
[RANTA grumbles]
Here might not be
the best place.
Why don't we go outside?
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
[HARUHIRO] I started this, but
now I don't know what to say.
I probably should've
thought it through more.
But I feel like we have
to talk to each other
if we ever want
things to get better.
I was just wondering...
[RANTA grumbles]
How are you feeling?
About our party, I mean.
Do you think we're doing well?
I guess. Our party's our party.
We earn enough to stay
alive, so that's good.
Really? That's all?
Do you care about anything
besides how much money we earn?
Why should I?
Get off my case.
What do you want from me?
I fulfill my duties
as a party member.
[HARUHIRO]
You think so?
Yeah. Haven't you been watching?
Like when we were fighting
in the mine today.
I proved I could take on
an opponent single-handedly
and win.
That was reckless.
It would've been
over a lot sooner
if all of us had
surrounded the kobold.
Can you guarantee
we'll always be able
to work as a group like that?
I don't think so.
But if I can reliably deal
with one opponent on my own,
well, that allows us to broaden
our tactics, doesn't it?
I just don't see how
that's a bad thing.
You can't just decide--
[HARUHIRO] I need to calm down.
I'm getting too worked up.
Even if I don't agree
with his actions,
at least he's given
them some thought.
Ranta does fight at
the front with Moguzo.
He's one of our lead
attackers. I respect that.
It's not a role I could take,
or Yume or Shihoru,
and we wouldn't
ask Mary to do it.
We've been through some changes
since Manato died
and Mary joined us.
Ranta's been reassessing
his role in the party,
just like the rest of us.
But that can only go so far.
Okay, I get what you were doing
since you told me,
but I didn't before.
It might've been better
if you'd said something
during the fight.
[RANTA]
And should I check with you
before I go and
take a leak, too?
Hey, come on. You know
that's not what I'm saying.
What I'm getting at is
that I won't always know
what you're doing or why you're
doing it unless you tell me.
On top of everything,
you're just...
Well, you're easily
misunderstood,
you know what I mean?
Hah.
Misunderstood, right. Like
that's actually what you think.
What?
What you're really saying is
that I'm wrong. It's my fault.
Let's blame it on poor,
misunderstood Ranta.
Well, if it's not your fault,
then whose is it?
Is it mine? Is it Yume's?
Or Shihoru's maybe?
Or Moguzo's?
No, wait its Mary's!
Easy.
Like it or not, we're a party,
so we're in this together.
We're supposed to be a team.
I wish we would act like it.
[RANTA] You don't think I'm
working as part of the team?
Well, do you think you are?
[RANTA]
Hell, no.
Do you wanna try?
Why bother? Everyone's got
their strengths and weaknesses.
Maybe teamwork's my weakness.
What about you, Oh Great One?
Don't you have any weaknesses?
Of course I do.
[HARUHIRO] Weaknesses?
I have plenty of those.
If anything, it's my strengths
I would have a hard time naming.
[HARUHIRO]
I know I have weaknesses.
I don't see why I need
to talk to you about them.
So we can talk about my faults,
but yours are off limits?
I think it's about time to wrap
up this little heart-to-heart,
okay?
Listen, Haruhiro.
You're the one who brought
all this stuff up, not me.
Remember that.
I wasn't gonna say anything,
but you wanted to talk,
so hey, here we are.
Fact is, I'm not interested
in being all buddy-buddy.
Play at being friends all you
want. Just leave me out of it.
If you want to spend your time
and energy hating me,
you're welcome to.
Really, I couldn't care less.
We're just a party,
not a family.
I'll do my duty, don't worry.
That's what being
a team is about.
But don't expect me
to be your best friend.
I'm goin' to bed.
--[YUME grunts]
--[thud]
[HARUHIRO]
Nice!
I've been practicing.
You use knives too, right?
Yeah, but I'm not
as good as you.
That's some serious aim.
Oh, and thanks for the blanket.
That was nice of you.
I thought you looked cold.
Why'd you sleep out here?
I... must've dozed off.
[YUME] I'm still getting the
hang of knives, you know.
There's so much
to learn about them.
I had no idea which kind
was best for throwing.
Luckily, Master offered to take
me to the market and show me.
Oh, yeah?
It was so great.
We went to a merchant and
Master picked out two knives.
He said I had to choose
the one I liked best.
So I did, and Master bought it
for me. Nice, right?
Anyway, I was really happy
with the quality of the knife,
so happy that I went back and
bought the other one myself.
It looks like a good one.
That was really nice
of your master.
Yep!
[HARUHIRO]
Hm?
[MARY] O light, return
to Lumiaris' protection.
Blame, ready!
[HARUHIRO] This is the new
Light Magic that Mary learned.
Its range isn't very long, and
it doesn't do a lot of damage,
but it numbs the opponent,
slowing him down considerably.
Mary wanted to
increase her ability
to support Moguzo and
Ranta at the front.
[MOGUZO]
Thank you!
[RANTA]
Anger! Hatred! Hatred!
You won't have enough breath
to fight if you keep shouting.
Shut it!
I'm not complaining
about how you fight!
[gasps]
[yelling]
That was too close!
What if you had hit me, huh?
Well, if you'd have died,
I would've gotten an extra Vice.
Seems like a win-win.
[HARUHIRO]
What the hell is his problem?
No, I have to calm down.
That's just the way he is.
There's no point
in getting angry.
Too bad. I am angry.
Furious, actually.
I have to find a way
to get past it.
[MOGUZO]
Here I go!
[HARUHIRO] This is
Moguzo's new Fast Thrust.
It's a one-handed attack
with longer range.
He also learned Back Thrust,
an attack he can perform
while backing away.
Okay! Let's go for the elder!
[SHIHORU]
Marc, Em, Parc!
Quick, surround him!
Let's get through
this unscathed!
[yelling]
[MOGUZO]
It's pretty different, huh?
Now that we're past
the third level.
[SHIHORU] It looks like
this is... farmland.
Aww. Hey, look
at these little guys.
I almost wanna take
one home with me.
They're pretty cute,
aren't they?
[RANTA grumbles]
[SHIHORU]
Um... I guess so. A little bit.
[HARUHIRO]
Hey.
What? Don't give me that look.
I was just poking at it.
It's not like I was
actually gonna do anything.
That might be easier to believe
if I didn't know you so well.
You've got a real violent
streak, Ranta.
You can believe whatever you
want; I know what I intended.
[grumbles]
[sighs]
Okay, then.
Seriously, I was just teasing.
I wasn't gonna hurt it.
Fine. Let it go.
I will after you say
you believe me.
You weren't going to
hurt it. I believe you.
There, was that so hard?
[MARY]
Shh!
[RANTA] They don't know we're
here. We could ambush them.
[MARY] I don't think
that's a good idea.
From the fourth level down, it's
best to make an instant kill.
Otherwise, we risk
causing a commotion.
[clanging]
[gasps]
They know there are
ntruders now.
We should get down to
the fifth level quickly.
Kobolds have the advantage
in open fields like this.
[gasps]
Are you okay?
[HARUHIRO]
Mary!
What's up there?
What did you see?
A kobold with black
and white patches.
Looks like Death Spots is here.
[SHIHORU]
The Death Spots?
Are you sure?
[HARUHIRO]
Get down!