[MANATO]
Sorry, could you wait a second?
[MANATO laughing]
[MANATO]
Come on. You try.
[SHIHORU]
No, that's all right.
I'll just watch from here.
It'll be okay, I promise.
They won't hurt you.
[MANATO]
You okay?
Yeah, thanks.
[SHIHORU]
Sorry.
I'm just so clumsy.
[MANATO]
No, I'm glad.
[SHIHORU]
Huh?
[MANATO] It gives us
more time together.
[ANIMAL meows]
[MANATO laughs]
You want some too, huh?
You really seem
to like animals.
Yeah.
We should go back.
[SHIHORU]
Oh, okay!
[MANATO]
And, fight!
[ALL]
Let's go!
[HARUHIRO] Does anybody
even know why we say that?
[SHIHORU]
I don't.
[MOGUZO]
It seems familiar, though.
Like I've heard it
somewhere before.
[YUME] Yeah, I feel like
I've heard it before, too.
Wonder what that's about.
[HARUHIRO]
Ranta!
There's one heading your way!
[RANTA]
I've got eyes, thanks!
C'mon, Anger!
[HARUHIRO]
That's Ranta's new skill.
Pretty feisty.
You're no ordinary goblin, huh?
[GOBLIN 4A chuckles]
Looks like a totally
ordinary goblin to me.
[HARUHIRO] Ranta isn't
the only one who learned
a new skill recently.
We earned enough
money for all of us
to go to our respective guilds
and improve our abilities.
Since they're still new skills,
the idea of using them in
a real fight is pretty scary.
But if we don't try them out,
we'll never perfect them,
so we don't really
have much of a choice.
[RANTA]
Whoa!
[YUME]
Ranta! What are you doing?
One!
[HARUHIRO]
That's Yume's new skill.
Diagonal Cross.
She chose to learn a skill
for a short-range weapon
rather than a bow.
[HARUHIRO]
Now!
[GOBLIN 4A yells]
[HARUHIRO]
Back Stab.
Wait, did I get the right spot?
--I think maybe I missed.
--[RANTA] All right!
You Dark Knights are
a bunch of savage beasts.
I'm surprised you're
not growing fur.
Don't call me savage.
I prefer "monstrous."
It's cooler.
I am a monstrous Dark Knight
in service to the
Dark God, Skullhell.
I'm cold and ruthless and
know nothing of blood or tears!
Ohm. Rel. Ect. Well. Dash!
[HARUHIRO]
Shadow Beat Magic.
Mages can use the power
from magical beings
called "elementals."
When Shihoru
chose her new skill,
she decided to learn how
to use shadow elementals.
[HARUHIRO]
Smash.
Members of the Priest Guild
can't use weapons
that have a blade,
like swords and daggers.
In our party, Manato is
both healer and vanguard,
so this is an especially
critical skill for him to have.
Hatred, go!
[GOBLIN 4B yells]
[HARUHIRO]
Good, they've locked blades.
Moguzo has the advantage now.
[HARUHIRO] This is
Moguzo's new skill, Wind.
Go on! Get him!
[MOGUZO yells]
Thank you!
[HARUHIRO] Rage Blow,
or the Thanks Slash.
For some reason,
he always says "thank you"
when he does it.
That's where the
nickname comes from.
The strength of that blow
definitely should not
be underestimated.
[GOBLIN 4C]
[RANTA]
Woohoo! Yeah!
[GOBLIN 4C groans]
Got it! My third Vice!
This'll give my demon
some good power!
Now it'll whisper to enemies
and lower their defenses.
If it feels like it.
[chuckles]
Dark Knight demons
seem pretty useless to me.
I mean, do they
even do anything?
Hey.
You know I can't
let that slide, man.
Don't talk about my little
buddy Zodiaco like that.
Or I'll curse you.
[HARUHIRO] Ranta's kinda
sensitive when it comes
to his demon,
which he named Zodiaco
for some reason.
Actually, his real
name is Zodiac.
Zodiaco is his nickname.
Not that it really matters.
I think Zodiaco's
actually kinda cute.
Which is a whole lot more
than I can say for his owner!
[HARUHIRO]
Seriously?
[RANTA]
I'm not his owner!
Don't be stupid!
You can't own
a demon like a pet.
That's not how it works.
It's more like Zodiaco
is possessing me.
[YUME] I really just
couldn't care less.
[HARUHIRO]
Neither could I.
Manato?
[YUME] Oh, I forgot.
I need to pray!
My Dear White God Elhit.
Thank you for everything.
Here's some of my food.
I hope you like it.
Please keep watching
over me, okay?
That was nice.
So is it a standard
Hunter Guild practice?
Yeah, it sure is.
Dear Elhit is our god.
The one who protects Hunters
while we hunt and stuff.
So it's good to pray and make
offerings once in a while.
Dear Elhit?
That's what you call your god?
[YUME]
Uh-huh!
I don't think I'll
get in trouble for it.
See, my Dear White God
Elhit is a huge wolf.
And wolves are noble
beasts, you know.
They're fierce and strong,
but they have big hearts and
care a lot about their pack.
Besides, Master
never scolded me for it.
[HARUHIRO]
Hmm.
[SHIHORU]
That's really nice, Yume.
I bet your god understands
how you feel and respects it.
And, you know, so do I.
Because, well, feelings,
they really matter.
[YUME]
Well, that's a good thing,
because I've got lots
and lots of feelings.
When I lay down at night,
I'm really tired, you know?
So I fall asleep quick,
and a bunch of the time
my dreams are of Dear Elhit.
I ask "Hey, can I
ride on your back?"
Then Dear Elhit leans down,
and lets me climb right on!
And we take off
running super-fast.
And I'm like,
"Whoa, this is so cool.
Let's keep going!" And we do.
We spend all night long
just running and running.
Hey, are we gonna get to
the point anytime soon, Yume?
I mean, there is a point
to this story, isn't there?
Because I've been listening
patiently for, like,
twenty minutes.
So if there isn't one,
I'm gonna be pissed.
A point? Not really.
[RANTA]
Gah!
Okay, that's it!
I'm never listening to
another one of your stories.
[MANATO laughing]
Oh, man.
Here I was thinking about
what a good party we've become.
We're consistently
defeating three goblins
at a time these days.
If we tweak our strategy,
we might be able to do four.
Moguzo is our reliable shield.
A stalwart defender.
He's big, strong, and steady.
Perfect for overpowering
our enemies.
His sword strikes
aren't flashy,
but they're
powerful and accurate.
And don't forget--
He's also very deft
with his hands.
Oh, you think so?
I don't know why, but...
I like doing detailed work,
like cooking and carving.
[RANTA]
It doesn't fit you.
You're amazing, too, Ranta.
I really admire your
willingness to attack.
The rest of us tend to be
a little more cautious.
If it weren't for you,
there were some times we might
never have advanced at all.
You, uh, really mean that?
See, now that
doesn't fit you.
That's enough outta you.
[YUME giggling]
[MANATO] And Yume,
you're never afraid.
Nothing fazes you.
I think you're probably the
bravest one out of all of us.
As the party's healer,
I always have to be careful,
so I'm glad I can
count on you to step in
and act when I'm not able to.
You think I'm brave?
Well, I guess there
aren't too many things
I'm afraid of, huh?
I'm just glad you've
all been patient
with a Hunter who's
no good with a bow.
Everybody's got things
they're not very good at.
You aren't alone there.
But we cover for each other.
'Cause we're a party.
[YUME]
Mm-hmm.
And Shihoru.
You're quiet, but you're
smart and observant.
And shadow magic--
It mostly employs spells
used to confuse
and bind enemies, right?
Those spells are usually
used to provide support
for other fighters.
That's why you
chose shadow magic.
So you could look out
for all of us.
[MANATO] I didn't realize
how long we'd been here.
It's getting late.
Heh. So it's time to
get back to work, huh?
Yeah, let's go.
[RANTA]
All right!
[HARUHIRO]
Hey, wait.
What about me?
Oh, well. I'll ask him later.
There's plenty of time.
[HARUHIRO]
Or... there should've been.
[HARUHIRO gasps]
[MANATO]
Haruhiro!
[HARUHIRO screams]
[MANATO]
Haruhiro!
[YUME]
Haru!
[HARUHIRO]
It really hurts.
--Stay back!
--[HARUHIRO] I can't breathe.
[HARUHIRO screams]
Return to Lumiares'
divine protection. Cure.
[YUME, SHIHORU scream]
Damn you!
Shihoru, fall back!
Right!
[RANTA yells]
Guys!
There are too many of them!
We need to retreat!
Quick, this way!
How's the shoulder? You okay?
Mapping this area
was pretty smart.
[laughing]
Manato?
I'm okay...
[ALL panting]
[HARUHIRO]
Manato?
Manato? Manato!
Hurry up! Heal yourself!
[MANATO groaning]
It's not working!
[HARUHIRO]
No! What are you saying?
Make it work!
Uh, if he meditates
for a while--
There's no time
for that crap!
Listen.
You're our leader.
You've gotta tell us what to do.
Come on, Manato! Tell us!
[MANATO]
Haru...
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Why are you apologizing?
You have to--
"Have to"? I don't
know what you're saying!
Manato!
You have to tell me or
I won't know what to do!
Tell me!
Manato!
You can't do this! Manato!
Well! Come on, hurry!
Don't just stand there!
We have to stop the bleeding.
[RANTA]
Lay him down! Gently!
[HARUHIRO]
Pull the arrow out!
[RANTA]
Okay, I'll do it.
You ready?
[MOGUZO]
Be careful!
[RANTA]
And pull!
[squelching noise]
[footsteps]
[HARUHIRO]
You have to save him!
Please! Help us!
Manato's been shot.
He'll die if he
doesn't get help.
I'll do anything!
Save him!
I'm begging you! Please!
Please, you have to help us!
Help him!
[HARUHIRO]
Come on!
Do something!
There is nothing
I can do for him.
No one can bring
the dead back to life.
Manato, how could
you be so foolish?
You showed such promise.
Now your life has ended and that
promise will never be fulfilled.
Bastard!
You're messing with us,
aren't you?
Ranta, don't!
It's okay.
This is all just a mistake.
We learned our lesson.
We let down our guard, but we'll
be more careful from now on.
Okay?
It won't happen again.
Really. We'll do better.
Hey, uh, are you okay?
Yeah, we're all okay.
Manato said this world
was scary and dangerous,
but we'd all be okay
if we just stuck together.
That's what he said.
Overcome today's problems
and move forward.
There's always tomorrow.
Right?
Isn't there? Isn't there?!
[HONEN] You must be sure
to give him a proper funeral.
The borderlands are
cursed by the No Life King.
Those who aren't laid to rest
properly become his servants.
I'm sure you agree
that Manato deserves
a better fate than that.
What are you saying?
What will happen to him?!
[HONEN]
You have five days at most.
There have been
instances of corpses
reanimating as soon
as three days after death.
[MOGUZO gasps]
Reanimating?
As I said, that's not
a fate Manato deserves.
I'm certain you want
better for your comrade.
[MOGUZO]
So when you say
that we need to lay
Manato to rest properly,
you mean he has to be
cremated instead of buried.
That is correct.
Cremation...
I assume that's not free?
If you do not
have adequate funds,
I will see to--
No! We'll do it!
But thank you.
Manato is our...
He was our...
Manato...
...was our friend.
[SHIHORU crying]
[crying continues]