[HARUHIRO]
Good news. They had them.
[MOGUZO]
Breakfast is gonna be a feast!
You must really like cooking
to go to all this trouble.
I mean, you aren't
even on breakfast duty.
What do you like better?
Eating food or making it?
[MOGUZO]
Oh, no!
I can't choose. I like both.
I think I always have.
Cooking for people must've
been a hobby of mine.
You know, before Grimgar.
Even if people don't
like the stuff I make,
I like to make it.
What? Are you crazy?
Everybody loves your cooking!
It doesn't matter what you make.
It's delicious.
Do you mean it?
Of course I do!
Thanks for that.
[clock chiming]
I'll go wake everyone up.
[MOGUZO]
'Kay.
[HARUHIRO, MANATO, MOGUZO]
We're very sorry!
I'm not sorry.
It was an accident.
An unfortunate accident.
[YUME] Walls don't just
"accidentally" fall down.
[RANTA]
Sure they do.
It happens all the time, stupid.
[YUME]
What did you just call me?!
[HARUHIRO]
Quit digging the hole deeper!
Just apologize!
Y'know, I don't get why
you're making such
a big deal out of this.
We weren't even looking!
You liar!
You're a peeping tom,
and you know it!
I should call the police!
[RANTA]
What police?
There aren't any here.
And besides,
we didn't see squat.
Your damn towels were
covering all the good bits.
Stupid, useless towels.
I thought you weren't looking!
Come on, you're
as flat as a board.
It's not like you've got
anything I'd really wanna see.
Oh, yeah? Really?
Tell you what.
I'll give you one chance to
admit the complete truth.
Do it right now and I
won't get angry with you.
Okay, cool.
Then yeah, you're right.
I tried to climb
the bath house wall
and it just kinda crumbled.
I've learned my lesson, though.
Next time I'll do a test run.
[YUME growling]
[RANTA]
You said you wouldn't get mad!
I didn't see anything, remember?
[YUME]
I'd rather break your neck,
but I guess this'll
just have to do!
[RANTA yelling]
[HARUHIRO]
Everyone's really on edge.
[FROG croaks]
[HARUHIRO gasps]
[HARUHIRO]
Feel that? It's still warm.
[YUME]
Maybe we can catch up.
[HARUHIRO]
Footprints.
I count two,
maybe three of them.
[YUME]
Not a lone boblin, then, huh?
I'm just gonna assume
you meant "goblin."
Let's go back.
[YUME] I think Shihoru might
be pretty upset for a while.
[HARUHIRO]
I know. I really am sorry.
[YUME]
It might be okay if it was you.
I'm not saying it would
be okay if you saw stuff,
'cause it wouldn't.
Not at all.
But if you did see stuff,
I know you would apologize.
Not that apologizing
makes it okay,
because it doesn't.
What's seen is seen.
You can't take it back.
[HARUHIRO]
I'm sorry, but to be honest
I'm not entirely sure
what you're saying.
[YUME]
Yeah. Neither am I, actually.
[HARUHIRO]
Well...
I'm just guessing here,
but maybe,
what you're saying
is that you forgive me?
That sounds good.
[laughs]
[HARUHIRO laughs]
But that doesn't mean
what happened was okay.
I know that.
[RANTA]
So what's the plan, then?
What do you mean?
What plan?
All we can do
is go back to Ortana.
[YUME] Gray pains
but all's a shame, huh?
Uh... [chuckles]
I think she meant
"Great pains but all in vain."
Am I right?
Yeah, but isn't
that what I just said?
Did it come out wrong?
[HARUHIRO]
A little bit.
That's it, then.
No money today.
[HARUHIRO] The next day,
the day after that,
and the day after that,
we barely earned
anything at all.
And when I say barely,
what I really mean
is next to nothing.
Okay, fine.
To be honest, we made nothing.
We bought new clothes
when we got here,
but they're already
starting to wear out.
They're sturdy enough,
but they aren't really
made for fighting goblins
and hiking mountain
trails every day.
We're trying to make them last,
but we can only do so much.
I'd give anything for
a new pair of underwear.
But the clothes in this
world are really expensive.
At least relatively.
Given how little we've made,
we can't afford
to buy anything new.
Not even underwear.
So we've got no choice but
to wash them every night
and go to sleep without them.
We put them on again
in the morning,
even if they're a little damp.
Damp underwear
is better than none.
No! Enough is enough.
Tomorrow I will make enough
money for new underwear!
[creaking noise]
[HARUHIRO]
Hm?
Uh... Sorry.
I'm finished up now.
It's all yours.
[HARUHIRO]
She smells nice.
Kinda sweet and flowery.
[HARUHIRO]
Hold on...
The guys have been
going commando at night,
but the girls?
[HARUHIRO gasps]
[HARUHIRO]
Stop it!
You're going to sink down
to Ranta's level!
[YUME]
Huh?
Uh...
I'm just going to bed now.
Okay. Good night, Haru.
Sleep well.
[HARUHIRO]
Uh... Right.
You too.
[YUME laughs]
[HARUHIRO]
Not good.
They can't go around
dressed like that--
Wandering the halls at night
without any underwear on--
It won't work.
It won't work at all.
They're too vulnerable.
And I'm too weak.
I don't think I can handle--
You seem weird.
What's wrong?
I'm fine, okay?
[RANTA]
Hm?
What the hell?
No point washing
your clothes in this rain.
Nothing's gonna dry.
Why don't you just
do it tomorrow?
Who knows if it'll
let up tomorrow?
Besides, you're
the one who told me
I should wash my clothes
out once in a while
to get rid of the stink.
Why the change of heart?
[HARUHIRO]
I'm just trying to help you out.
I wish I hadn't washed
my stuff, y'know?
[laughs]
[HARUHIRO]
Whatever I do,
I can't let Shameless
the Great here
get close to
the girls right now.
I don't know what he would do,
but I doubt it would be good.
[RANTA]
I guess you're right.
Doing laundry sucks, anyway.
Yeah, totally.
Good call.
I was hoping that I might
run into the girls, though.
[cackles]
Oh, yeah?
That doesn't surprise me.
[HARUHIRO]
That was a close one.
I don't think it's a good idea
for them to go commando.
I should tell them.
Or should I?
No! I'll tell them.
[HARUHIRO]
This is Damuro.
It was the second city
of the Arabakia Kingdom.
Damuro was much
bigger than Ortana.
But now it's in ruins,
and overrun by goblins.
There are a lot of goblins
in the new city area,
but they're strong
and well organized.
Too difficult for us.
So we're headed to the old city
to target the ones who
have gotten separated
from their groups.
[HARUHIRO]
We're careful,
but this isn't
the forest anymore.
There's more of a chance
for encounters here,
and that means there's
more of a chance to get hurt.
[HARUHIRO]
Guys, we've got a loner.
And he's sleeping.
[MANATO]
All right. Let's do it.
[MANATO] Moguzo's armor will
make his approach noisy.
So Haruhiro, Ranta, and I will
handle the initial attack.
If we can close in on the
goblin without waking him,
the three of us will finish it.
If we do wake him...
Yume, use your bow.
Shihoru, back us up with magic.
And Moguzo, take the front.
If it becomes a head-on fight,
we'll use the same
formation as before.
Surround him so
he can't get away.
[GOBLIN yells]
[MANATO]
Keep at him!
Oh, crap!
[RANTA]
Dammit!
Is he dead?
[HARUHIRO] It's a lot
easier this way--
Going after them in their sleep.
[RANTA] I need to get
a claw or something.
For my Vice.
[coins clinking]
[YUME]
Wow! Look at all that!
This is our best haul yet!
Of course, I guess it is
only our second, huh?
Four whole silvers.
[MOGUZO]
Whoa.
We did well, but we
can't celebrate just yet.
We got lucky.
Today was easy, but it
won't always be like this.
Stay sharp and look
for our next target.
[RANTA]
Aw, c'mon, Manato.
Don't be such a killjoy.
Thanks to my skill and daring,
we killed ourselves a goblin
and got our biggest score yet.
But that's not a good enough
reason to celebrate for ya?
You're right, Ranta.
Maybe we should
enjoy today's success.
You did a really
good job back there.
I know, right?
And didn't I seem totally
like a Dark Knight,
the way I stabbed that
dirty gob in the neck
and smiled cruelly while he
struggled and bled all over?
[HARUHIRO] That's not how
I remember it happening.
[RANTA]
Shut up!
I got him good,
with one clean blow.
Come on, Haruhiro,
where are your eyes?
Oh, wait, there they are!
They're so small I almost
thought they'd disappeared,
but I see them now!
[HARUHIRO] Seriously, are we
going to do this again?
[RANTA]
Is that all you're gonna say?
Come on, man, defend yourself!
[HARUHIRO]
How many times is that now?
It's getting old.
[HARUHIRO] We'd defeated an
enemy and earned some money.
That seemed to lighten
everyone's mood a little bit.
Not completely though.
We still have a lot
of work ahead of us.
But at least
we're getting better.
Who knows, before long
maybe we'll be thinking
and acting like real
Volunteer Soldiers.
[HARUHIRO]
We'd found a system that worked.
We targeted lone goblins
and defeated them
by working together.
In Damuro, we'd
sometimes run into groups
of five or more of the monsters.
A pair was hard enough
for us to handle,
so five would have
been ridiculous.
Fighting kept us busy,
but we had another
task to work on.
As we roamed the old city,
we added to a map we'd begun.
We explored new places
whenever we could,
learning our way around.
Before long, we were navigating
the ruins pretty well.
It was always nerve-wracking
to map a new area,
but bit by bit,
our map expanded.
Our confidence grew.
Finally, things were going well.
[CLERK]
That'll be thirty coppers, boy.
[HARUHIRO]
Thirty?
It's secondhand!
I might consider it
for fifteen, but no more.
It'd go for a hundred new,
but since I'm in a good mood,
I'll let you have it
for twenty-eight.
[HARUHIRO] I could go
as much as twenty coppers,
but even that's stretching it.
I've still got more
things left to buy.
Twenty-five,
and not a copper less.
Though this is robbery
if you ask me!
You've got a deal!
[HARUHIRO]
Woo-hoo!
[slurping]
[RANTA] Man, I could eat
a whole bucket of this stuff.
What's it called again?
[MOGUZO] I think I heard
somebody call it soruzo.
[RANTA]
Whatever it is, it's awesome!
[slurping]
[MOGUZO]
Can we get another order?
[CHEF]
Comin' up.
[SHIHORU gasps]
[YUME]
Huh?
Why are you hiding?
[SHIHORU]
I... I can't.
I'm still too embarrassed.
[YUME giggles]
Huh? Oh, I see.
You were hoping he actually
would stop and talk to you.
[YUME chuckles]
[MANATO] The blade
was pretty nicked, huh?
It's taken a beating.
Before I do anything
else at night,
I like to make sure that my
weapons are in good condition.
I get antsy otherwise.
Yeah. I understand that.
Just listen to us,
talking about cleaning weapons.
We sound like Volunteer
Soldiers already.
Well, that makes
sense, doesn't it?
We are Volunteer Soldiers.
Just trainees, technically.
[door opens]
[MANATO]
Wow. Good job!
I'm sorry.
We would have been back sooner,
but Ranta just
kept haggling, so...
[RANTA]
Of course I haggled!
That's what you're
supposed to do.
And look what it got us.
Are you sure you
didn't get too much?
Some of it might go bad
before we can finish it.
Anything that rots is yours.
[MANATO] We can buy weapons,
clothes, and food.
That's fine.
But you know what I've
been thinking lately?
What if we tried
saving up a little
so we can learn new skills?
You sure about that?
I don't think you guys
could handle it
if my skills got any sharper.
Oh, please!
And what do you mean "skills"?
You've only got
one skill right now.
Shut up, you!
That just means I can
focus on polishing
that one skill
as much as possible.
Until it shines with dark light!
[MANATO]
Did you buy that, too?
[MOGUZO]
This? No, I made it.
You carved this?
You're better with your hands
than I would've expected.
[HARUHIRO] You know, Moguzo,
you could sell that.
Oh, I'm not really
doing it to make money.
Carving just helps me
relax, that's all.
[MANATO]
Oh.
I bet Yume would
like something like this.
[HARUHIRO]
Yeah?
What made you think about
Yume all of a sudden?
Nothing.
Girls just like
that kinda thing.
[YUME] You know,
Haru had a great idea.
He said if we earned
a little extra money
we could buy some
spare sets of clothing.
That way we wouldn't have
to do laundry nearly as often.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Yeah. That sounds
like a good idea.
Doing laundry all
the time is a pain.
Isn't it?
[SHIHORU]
Yeah.
[YUME]
Oh, look at that!
What a pretty hair clip.
You have great taste!
Oh... You mean this?
Thank you.
[YUME]
Yup.
Shihoru...
I know that you have a really
hard time talking to the guys,
but maybe you should
try once in a while.
Join in a conversation or two.
I think it would
do you some good.
[SHIHORU]
Yeah, you're probably right.
[YUME]
You don't have to.
It's not like I can
tell you what to do.
I just worry about how
quiet you are sometimes.
I don't want you to feel like
you're not part of the group.
You know?
I'll try to talk more.
Glad I didn't upset you.
You know me.
I'm not always
so good with words.
[HARUHIRO]
Manato?
Yeah?
[HARUHIRO]
Uh...
Just... thank you. That's all.
[MANATO laughs]
Where did that come from?
[HARUHIRO chuckles]
Sorry, I was going
to say something
completely different,
and that just came out.
[MANATO laughs]
You shouldn't thank me.
I'm the one who's
grateful to all of you.
[HARUHIRO]
Huh? Really?
You feel grateful to us?
What for?
Plenty of stuff, but
mostly for being my friends.
It means a lot.
I don't know.
Maybe I didn't say that right.
It came out sounding
kinda cheesy or fake.
It didn't.
That was actually a
really nice thing to say.
It's just...
How should I put this?
Anyone can see that we need you
more than you need us.
If you weren't around,
we wouldn't have the
first idea what to do,
you know?
And that's assuming
we'd even still be alive.
Trust me.
I need all of you, too.
If it wasn't for our group,
I don't know what
would've happened to me.
We wouldn't last very long
in this world by ourselves.
None of us.
[HARUHIRO]
I totally agree, but, well...
I don't want you to
take this the wrong way
or anything, but...
Don't you think
you could've joined up
with another group pretty
easily if you'd wanted to?
You might not
have been the leader,
but you could've asked to
join someone else's party.
[MANATO] That never
really occurred to me.
Honestly, I'm not sure
it would've worked.
I think I kind of
like being a leader.
Who knows, maybe I
used to have problems
with authority or something.
[HARUHIRO]
Heh. Nah.
I can't see that.
I bet I did, though.
Well, anyway,
that's why I'm grateful.
I get the feeling I'm
not the kind of person
who makes friends easily.
I don't think that's true.
[HARUHIRO]
That's easy to say,
but the fact of the matter is
I have no way to prove it.
I only know the Manato
in this world,
not the one you were before.
But still...
It doesn't really matter
what you were like before.
Nobody cares.
We're in Grimgar now.
The Manato in this world
is our friend and leader.
The guy we count on.
That's all that matters to us.
Let's get some sleep.
We have an early day tomorrow.
[HARUHIRO]
Did I say too much?
I hope I didn't
embarrass him or anything.
I just...
I just wanted him to know
we really are his friends.
[HARUHIRO]
Day twenty-three in Grimgar.
I'm actually getting
used to the red moon.
I guess people can adapt
to pretty much anything.
Maybe it just takes time.