[KOBOLD growling]
[MARY]
I'm sorry!
I can't do anything! I'm sorry!
[HAYASHI]
Heal Michiki.
Mary, please. Hurry!
I can't do it.
I'm sorry, Hayashi! I can't!
I don't have any more magic!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
[KOBOLD growling]
[MICHIKI groaning]
[MARY]
Michiki!
[HAYASHI]
[MICHIKI] You two go!
Get out of here!
No! I can't just abandon you!
--[MICHIKI] Hayashi, please.
--[MARY] We can't leave them!
[MARY]
Let's all go together!
[MICHIKI] I said
get out of here! Go on!
Stop it! Let go of me! No!
Michiki!
[MARY crying]
[MARY]
No!
You're mine now!
[MARY screaming]
[HAYASHI] I don't know how
we made it out of the mine
and back above ground.
It's all a blank.
Maybe my body remembered
the way on its own.
After that,
Shinohara took us in,
and we joined up with Orion.
But it wasn't long
before Mary left.
It was too painful
for her to be around me.
She never said anything,
but I could see it in her eyes.
Looking at me,
she saw that awful day
and a past that was lost to her.
She had to get away.
It was just too much to bear.
So...
After leaving Orion,
Mary kept moving around,
jumping from party to party.
She never stayed with
any of them for very long.
She's changed.
From what other
people say about her,
she's nothing like the
person she used to be.
I was pretty sure
I had brought Mary
out of the Cyrene Mine
with me back then,
but now I wonder
if that's really true.
These days she mostly
just seems hollow.
like an empty shell.
Maybe the real Mary
is still down there,
trapped underground somewhere.
If you can find
a way to help her,
you'll have my thanks.
[HARUHIRO]
Oh, well, I dunno--
I understand losing a comrade.
I've been there before myself.
Please don't run away from it.
I promise.
That pain is something
worth holding on to.
Move forward, but
remember that pain
and treasure the
companions you have now.
Because once they're gone,
they're gone for good.
The cruelty of death
is its finality.
It doesn't offer second chances.
Seems obvious, I know.
Most don't realize it
until it's too late
to make a difference.
[RANTA]
Ugh.
What a complete
waste of our time.
[HARUHIRO]
How can you say that?
We learned a lot.
[RANTA] So now we know
all about Miss Mary's past.
So what?
I don't see what any
of it has to do with us.
[HARUHIRO] It's not like it
hurts to learn more about her.
[RANTA] And now that
we know all that, what?
We have to be nice to her
because she had it
rough in the past?
You've gotta be kidding me.
I didn't say that.
Calm down, okay?
You didn't have to say it.
It's what you meant.
But tell me this: how is
she any different from us?
Are you saying we haven't
had it rough so far?
I don't see us getting
special treatment.
No, I guess not.
So why are we supposed
to bend over backwards
to be nice to someone
who has no interest
in being nice to us?
That's just dumb.
Hey, what is it?
Losing Manato was hard.
On all of us.
His death still hurts.
And it will, for a long time.
But...
I think we can
make it better
by doing what he
would want us to do.
[sniffs]
He'd want us to try.
If we keep trying with Mary,
then maybe she'll
keep trying too.
When you get
right down to it,
Mary's the same as us.
That's what you said,
isn't it, Ranta?
Why? What does it matter?
By that logic, things
will never be any different
than the way they are now.
If we don't make an effort
to get to know her,
she won't make an effort
to get to know us.
If we aren't friendly to her,
she won't be friendly
to us, either.
Is that what you want?
For us just to
continue on like this?
[RANTA] You know Haruhiro,
for all your talk,
I don't see you making
an effort to get to know me.
[HARUHIRO]
Wh--?
[RANTA]
Admit it.
You guys never listen to me.
You ignore my opinions like
they don't mean anything to you.
[YUME]
Well sometimes, Ranta,
the stuff you say just
seems kind of unnecessary.
What do you mean by that?
[YUME]
Now that I think about it,
all the stuff you say
is unnecessary.
[RANTA]
Hey, that's just harsh!
Okay, well, you're
harsh all the time,
like when you talk
about my chest.
There's no reason to say
hurtful stuff like that.
I see!
[RANTA]
You see what?
[HARUHIRO]
That's how Ranta feels?
For how long, I wonder?
And I had no idea.
I guess Mary's not the only one
here I don't know very well.
I guess I've got a lot
of things to work on.
Sorry about that, Ranta.
I'll work on it.
I'll start listening
to you more.
[RANTA]
Y-You will?
Yeah. You're my friend.
You deserve better from me.
[RANTA]
Your friend?
Well, then... Start
acting like it, you idiot!
You see? That was unnecessary.
Well, I don't see what's wrong
with calling an idiot
"idiot." Idiot!
[HARUHIRO]
Ranta?
[RANTA]
Leave me alone.
I need some time to think.
[HARUHIRO]
You?
Thinking something over?
[RANTA]
Why you--!
Ugh. Anyway, I
need to think about
how to face Mary
when we see her tomorrow.
And, uh, just so
you know, Shihoru...
I'm sorry about before.
I didn't mean to make you
talk about Manato.
I know it's hard on you.
He apologized?
Maybe it'll rain tomorrow.
Hah! You say useless stuff, too!
Yeah, you're right.
It's supposed to be
"snow," isn't it?
[MOGUZO] "Maybe it'll snow."
I think that's how it goes.
[RANTA]
Not the point!
[HARUHIRO]
Ranta's right about one thing.
I'm not sure how any of us
are going to face Mary tomorrow.
It won't be easy.
[rain pouring]
[HARUHIRO]
What do you know?
It really is raining.
[YUME]
What did you say, Haru?
[HARUHIRO] Oh, I just said
that it's actually raining.
[YUME]
Not snowing, though.
Look at that.
You see his dagger?
[HARUHIRO] Yeah. I dropped it
the day Manato died.
[GOBLIN growls]
Sorry about that.
It was dumb.
I don't know what got into me.
I'm okay now, really.
We should follow him.
He might lead us
to their hideout.
We didn't see
any good targets.
Okay, then.
Let's get out of here.
Go someplace dry.
Before we go, Mary...
I'd like to talk to you.
You want to talk now?
All right,
let's make this quick.
There's no need to drag it out.
If you want me to leave
the party, go ahead and say it.
[HARUHIRO gasps]
I'm sorry.
That's not it at all.
[HARUHIRO]
Now that I think about it,
we have been acting
strange today.
After hearing her story,
we don't know how
to treat her anymore.
We see her in a different
light than before,
but we aren't sure how
to deal with that change.
Mary could tell
something was off.
How could she not?
She's probably
been preparing herself.
Getting ready to move on. Again.
If you'll listen,
there's something I've been
wanting to tell you about.
You know, we used to have a
Priest in our party before you.
Well, his name was Manato.
[HARUHIRO] You know, we used
to have a Priest in our party
before you.
Well, his name was Manato.
A little while ago,
Manato died.
Although it feels
closer to the truth
to say that we let him die.
He would heal us even
when we didn't need it.
He used his magic to
take care of every scratch.
On top of that,
he served with Moguzo
on the front lines
during battle.
And he was our party leader.
So basically, he was
doing three different jobs.
I thought he was pretty amazing.
I'm only now starting
to realize how much
we took for granted.
Doing all that work
couldn't have been easy,
but Manato didn't let
the strain of it show.
I never offered to help.
It didn't occur to me
that he might need it.
And now, of course,
it's too late to offer.
Manato's never coming back.
He's gone for good.
At first, after he died,
it was hard to imagine
how we were going to go on.
But we didn't really
have a choice.
If we wanted to stay alive,
we needed to keep working.
So that's why I
asked you to join us.
Because we can't do much of
anything without a Priest.
I don't know if
that's a good reason,
but it's the only one I've got.
The thing is,
we're the leftovers.
The people that
nobody else picked.
But Manato brought us together.
He made us into a party.
And we became friends.
True, we don't always
get along very well.
When you're in a party together,
there are times things
don't go smoothly.
You get angry.
You fight with each other.
But you're still friends.
That's something
that doesn't change.
Whatever came before,
whatever comes next,
you support each other,
because that's what friends do.
And I want you to know...
I consider you
a friend too, Mary.
Um, so do I.
You're one of us now. A friend.
Yeah, totally.
And you're also
really cute, by the way.
Um, it's nice
to have you here.
You're a good Priest. Thanks.
I guess you're not that bad.
From now on, if you
decide not to heal me,
I won't make a
big deal about it.
I'll trust your judgment
since we're friends and all.
[HARUHIRO]
Oh, wow. Ranta's playing nice.
It'll start snowing
any second now.
[RANTA] Come up with some
new material already!
[HARUHIRO]
Mary...
Uh, if you're not busy,
we're all going to pick out
a helmet for Moguzo.
You're welcome to come.
I don't think so.
[HARUHIRO]
All right.
Well... You've still got to eat.
Have dinner with us, at least.
Come on. It'll be fun.
I'm sorry. I don't
think I can. Not yet.
What do you mean, not yet?
[MARY]
Thanks for asking.
See you tomorrow.
[HARUHIRO]
Yeah. Tomorrow is a new day.
As long as you're
still alive to see it.
[MOGUZO]
Thanks, everyone. Really.
[YUME]
Sure!
I'm just glad we were able
to find you a cute one.
[SHIHORU] I was kind of
worried we wouldn't be able
to afford it.
[HARUHIRO] Especially since
Ranta didn't pitch in
a single copper.
[RANTA]
The discount I scored us
counted as my
contribution, idiot!
[HARUHIRO]
Moguzo got his helmet.
At first it didn't
seem possible,
but Ranta's haggling
brought the price down.
From forty-two silvers
to eighteen!
[HARUHIRO]
Mary's still with our party.
And slowly, very slowly...
I feel like we're
actually starting to get
a little closer to her.
[HARUHIRO]
And then, there's this place.
We come here once
a day, every day.
[VOLUNTEER SOLDIER 7A]
Hey, goblin slayers!
The fearsome goblin slayers!
How's the hunting?
What are you
warriors up to today?
Headin' to Damuro, huh?
They keep this up,
there aren't going to be
any goblins left around here
before much longer.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
They better shut it
or I'm gonna get pissed.
Calm down. Let it go.
It's not like it isn't true.
[YUME]
This soup's delicious!
I could eat a whole bucket!
Yeah.
If you want,
I could try making it.
That would be great!
You could do that?
I can probably get close. Sure.
[HARUHIRO]
Day after day after day...
It's goblins, goblins,
goblins, goblins.
Rain or shine, hot or cold.
It's goblins, goblins, goblins,
goblins, goblins, goblins.
At first they all
looked the same:
A bunch of interchangeable,
ugly monsters.
But recently, I've started
being able to tell them apart.
There are a lot of males
and relatively few females.
According to Mary,
most of the females live
in Damuro's new city area.
They're kept well protected,
surrounded by high-level males.
[RANTA] Man, that is one harem
I wouldn't want any part of.
[HARUHIRO] Well, I doubt
the female goblins
would want any
part of you, either.
You know, if people
don't understand my charm,
there's nothing
I can do about it.
It takes somebody with
sophisticated taste.
What do you say, Mary?
Who would you choose?
Between the three of us, I mean.
[MARY]
Hm?
Come on, you
can answer honestly.
There's no need to be shy.
I don't get it. What is
there to be shy about?
[SHIHORU giggles]
That's a good question.
Hey, hey, hey!
[chuckles]
How're you kids
doin' these days?
[HARUHIRO] I really don't think
I've ever seen Mary smile.
I wonder if she remembers how.
[HARUHIRO] We eat plenty,
but nothing fancy.
And we're fine staying in the
Volunteer Soldier housing.
Any extra money we have
should be spent on
equipment, not lodging.
I especially want to
invest in Moguzo's armor.
Obviously, we can't
afford anything
that's custom made
from start to finish.
Instead, we used our money
to buy something used,
and had a blacksmith
fit it to his size.
Even though we were frugal,
the pieces all cost
a couple silvers or more.
Then there are skills.
We could all use more of those.
I learned Swat and Sneaking
to mute my footsteps.
Sleepy Shadow
uses Shihoru's magic
to put enemies to sleep.
Let's go! Exhaust!
[HARUHIRO] That skill
immediately creates distance
between you and the enemy.
And... Avoid!
[HARUHIRO] Ranta likes
shouting out his skill names.
It's annoying,
but that's Ranta for you.
Moguzo's War Cry
temporarily paralyzes the enemy.
[HARUHIRO]
Yume learned Swift,
which increases her
accuracy with a bow.
And with Mouse Hole,
she can dodge an enemy
attack very quickly.
[HARUHIRO] Mary's always
been levels above us,
so she has less to learn.
We're lucky to have her.
Sometimes I can see
right where I need to hit,
like there's a path lit up
for my dagger to travel.
My blade slides
cleanly along that path,
moving closer to its target.
When it touches,
I know I've struck
the right place.
And then suddenly,
it's all over.
[HARUHIRO] I'm not really
sure what's going on.
I have no idea what
that weird light is.
Teacher Barbara might know.
I'll ask her
next time I see her.
Okay, Haruhiro,
what do you say?
Is it time?
Yes! Finally!
[MANATO]
Trouble sleeping?
Yeah. Excited, I guess.
The anticipation you
feel the night before
a field trip. Like that?
Um, I don't really know.
[MANATO laughs]
[HARUHIRO chuckles]
It's funny...
...but I'm not really
worried or nervous.
The main thing I feel
right now is ready.
Ready. That's good.
[HARUHIRO]
Yeah.
[MANATO chuckles]
[HARUHIRO] We've been in
Grimgar for how many days now?
I'm not sure when,
but at some point I must
have stopped counting.
Well, I know one thing for sure.
Wherever we came from before...
We're all here now.
And we're friends.
Whatever happens,
we'll face it together.
[HARUHIRO]
Manato...
Our party's doing well.
I think you'd be really proud.
All right, then.
See you tomorrow.