[HARUHIRO]
Oh, right... I forgot.
We're not going hunting today.
[HARUHIRO] We talked it over,
and it was unanimous.
We decided to take the day off.
We've been working
hard for a long time,
preparing for yesterday.
It feels like a good day
to take a breather.
Resting does sound nice,
but I'm not really
sure I know how to.
There are so many hours to fill.
What do you do on a day off?
Huh, relaxing is
kind of hard work.
You seem distracted.
[HARUHIRO]
Ah, it's nothing.
Just, now that we
actually get a break,
I don't know what
to do with myself.
[MOGUZO] I guess Ranta
didn't have that problem.
He went out early.
Really? He did?
That's weird.
[MOGUZO] I think there are
some people who only like
to sleep in when the other
option is going to work.
[HARUHIRO chuckles]
Oh yeah.
That sounds like Ranta.
[HARUHIRO spits]
[HARUHIRO]
This bread's really good!
My timing's still a bit off.
I'm supposed to change
the temperature as it cooks,
but it's tricky.
I haven't figured out
how to do it
with a wood-burning fire...
I'll keep trying, though.
We're taking the
day off, you know.
You don't have to
worry about cooking duty.
Of course...
I'm still gonna eat
every bite of it.
[MOGUZO]
It's not a big deal.
I was hungry too,
so why not make extra?
[HARUHIRO]
Where did Ranta go, anyway?
[MOGUZO] Not sure,
but he took his fishing rod.
[HARUHIRO]
What about Yume and Shihoru?
[MOGUZO]
I don't know.
I haven't seen either
of them yet this morning.
[HARUHIRO] Maybe they're
still in their room.
[HARUHIRO]
I bet they stayed up late,
so they're sleeping in now.
Shihoru was really
upset after yesterday.
She and Yume probably needed
some time to talk about Manato.
So, what about you?
Oh, me?
I'm still deciding, actually...
I thought I might bring my
armor in to get patched up.
It took a beating
in our last fight,
so it really needs some work.
My sword was in bad shape,
so I left it to get sharpened.
I should probably
pick it up soon.
You sure you don't want to do
something a little more fun?
It's pretty rare
that we take a day off.
Well, what about you?
What are you gonna do?
Uh... Um... I don't know yet.
[MOGUZO] We're all meeting
up at Shelly's tavern
later on tonight, aren't we?
[HARUHIRO]
Mm-hmm.
What should I do?
[HARUHIRO]
Oh, hey.
I didn't know you were up.
Feeding birds?
You an animal lover?
It's just something I do.
Kind of a habit.
Oh yeah?
[HARUHIRO] Well...
I don't know if you're hungry,
but Moguzo baked some
fresh bread this morning.
Did he? That must be
what smells so good.
You can smell it?
[SHIHORU]
Yeah.
Wow. Good nose.
This is a great spot...
Remember when we all
watched the sunset from here?
[SHIHORU]
Yeah...
Um, hey, Haru...
I just want to say...
I'm glad we get to
keep working together.
Uh... yeah.
I mean, so am I.
But why do you say that?
[SHIHORU]
I just felt like it.
[HARUHIRO]
Oh.
[SHIHORU chuckles]
Sunrise is nice here, too.
It is a great spot.
[HARUHIRO]
It sure is.
I can see why you
come here so much.
[SHIHORU]
Mm-hmm.
[YUME groans]
So sleepy...
I just want five more minutes.
Then I promise I'm gonna get up.
[ANIMAL meows]
[HARUHIRO]
Oh.
Hey, Hiro.
You want to sit down?
[MARY]
This is where I've been staying.
It's been my home since I left
the Volunteer Soldier housing...
It's a pretty nice
place, actually...
Women only.
Then I shouldn't be here!
You're fine out on the deck.
[MARY] If the rest of you ever
decide to leave your quarters,
I can tell Yume and
Shihoru about this place.
They might like it.
[HARUHIRO]
Yeah...
I'm sure they'd be really
happy to hear about it.
Although...
I think we're all pretty used to
it there, to tell you the truth.
Not that we're
gonna stay forever.
We'll have to move on...
eventually.
I have some
good memories of it.
It's not that bad.
[HARUHIRO] I guess it's
not surprising that Mary
would want to live
somewhere else.
When she stayed in
the soldier housing,
it was probably with
her original party-mates.
[HARUHIRO]
It must have felt so empty...
...after they were gone.
[HARUHIRO]
What? This was in Damuro?
[KIKKAWA]
Yep, that's right.
And from the stories I've
heard, it was pretty gnarly.
Mm-hmm. Seems the gobsters
are gettin' more ferocious.
[HARUHIRO] Wait a sec,
what are you saying?
Gobsters? You mean goblins?
[KIKKAWA] Anyway, looks like
some rooks got themselves
in big trouble.
[HARUHIRO]
Hold on, "rooks"?
Oh, rookies...
Volunteer Soldier trainees?
It's what I said, isn't it?
A party of newlings tried
their luck in Damuro.
Turns out they weren't so
lucky, if ya know what I mean.
Things got really ugly.
It was bad, man.
You remember that band
of goblins we took down?
I'm pretty sure they
were from the new city.
I could tell that they were
different from their equipment
and the way that they fought.
Maybe we stirred them up.
[KIKKAWA]
Oh, you did that, all right!
Mad gobsters from the new city
are patrolling all
over the place now.
You kicked a beehive, and the
bees aren't happy about it.
So what are we supposed
to do with them now, huh?
Lay low and wait
for them to buzz off?
That sure sounds like
the easiest plan to me.
Personally, I'd
rather not get stung.
[HARUHIRO]
Nice talking to you...
[KIKKAWA]
Hey, boys! How's it going?
Hanging in there?
[RANTA]
Two more over here!
[YUME] So the gobs
are making trouble, huh?
[HARUHIRO] Yeah, it sounds
like Damuro's not a good place
to be.
Have you heard?
[YUME]
Yep.
All right, what are
we gonna do then?
[HARUHIRO]
Well, honestly, I don't know...
I haven't really
thought about it yet.
We were planning to go to
Damuro tomorrow like always.
The way things are now,
it could be a total bust
if we go there tomorrow.
So you ready to take
responsibility for that?
[HARUHIRO] What do you
mean, "take responsibility"?
If we earn squat,
you better fork over
your portion to pay
for bad decision-making.
[HARUHIRO]
Seriously, Ranta...
Sometimes you say
the stupidest things...
Think about it.
If we make nothing,
my share is also nothing.
[MOGUZO]
Maybe...
We should think about
changing our hunting grounds.
There's the Cyrene Mine.
Oh... no.
Sorry... I was just thinking--
Hey! Haruhiro!
Once in a while, a very
long while, you make sense!
I'm totally up for it.
I say let's go!
I'm not so sure about that...
It sounds dangerous.
Isn't Tetra Pod
in the Cyrene Mine?
The bounty on him
is thirty gold.
Think how much
that could buy us!
And, um, I think
you mean "Death Spots,"
not "Tetra Pod"...
The Cyrene Mine monster.
[HARUHIRO]
Well, the bottom line is
we need to change
our hunting grounds,
at least for a little while...
We don't really
know too many places
outside of our regular area,
so the mine just kind
of popped in my head.
[HARUHIRO] Obviously,
Death Spots is a danger,
but we'll be careful
to avoid him.
And does anyone else
feel like staying
in the same area
can get a little boring?
Plus... Sticking to a routine
can make you careless.
It's easy to stop
paying attention
and start making mistakes.
Maybe it would be good for
us to get some excitement--
to see how well we
perform under pressure.
So there you have it.
That's my take.
I think we should try
our luck in the Cyrene Mine.
That's that, then.
[YUME] Is it really
such a bad thing,
following the same
routine every day?
I sorta like that things haven't
been as dangerous lately,
and I've been able to save
money a little at a time.
I just don't see why
things have to change.
[HARUHIRO] Well... we can't
go to Damuro right now,
so that's part of it.
I forgot about that...
So we don't have much
of a choice, then, do we?
Hm... Well, if nothing else,
I guess switching up
our prey could make
for a nice change of pace.
[MARY panting]
[HARUHIRO]
Mary?
[MARY panting]
Excuse me. I need a moment.
Hold on...
[MARY]
I'm sorry about this.
[HARUHIRO]
No...
I should apologize.
[HARUHIRO] If we go
to the Cyrene Mine,
Mary will have to
confront her past.
She'll be forced to
set foot in the place
where her friends died.
That's a lot to ask.
It'll be difficult,
and very painful.
At least, I imagine it will be.
It's not like I'm
speaking from experience,
considering we haven't
been anywhere near the spot
where Manato died
since that day.
If it was up to me,
I would erase it entirely--
Forget that place even existed.
[MARY] You want us to
go to the Cyrene Mine.
That's the place
of my nightmares.
I don't know if I could
go in there calmly,
without my hands shaking,
and my heart racing...
I would be afraid.
Now... and maybe even
for the rest of my life.
I understand.
[MARY]
But even so...
I want to be able
to face my fear.
You know?
I have to try...
I've got to find the
courage to walk in there.
Otherwise...
I'll be stuck.
Unable to move on with my life.
I can't face it alone.
I know that.
But maybe if I have help...
Maybe if you guys
are down there too...
I can do it.
[MARY]
At least I think so.
It feels possible.
Because you called
me your friend.
Or maybe...
I'm just holding you back.
[HARUHIRO] We've never
thought anything like that!
You aren't holding
us back at all.
[MARY]
Hiro?
I don't know
why I'm crying...
They're happy tears, I guess.
I feel like an
idiot now... Sorry.
For what it's worth...
I don't think you're
an idiot at all.
[MARY]
Thanks for this.
[HARUHIRO] We knew the Cyrene
Mine was going to be dangerous.
We wanted to make sure
we were as prepared
as we could possibly be.
We polished our equipment
and honed our skills.
I decided to learn
the sneak attack "Spider."
It cost me forty silvers
and a whole lot of pain.
[BARBARA]
Welcome back, Old Cat.
Good to see you.
Are you ready to get started?
[HARUHIRO]
Yes, ma'am. I'm ready.
[BARBARA] You've gotten a
little stiffer since last time.
That's not what I
look for in my students.
Well, not for the
most part, anyway.
Um... I'm not stiff there--
[HARUHIRO yells, groans]
Good thing, too,
or you'd have a big,
red smile right in the middle
of your neck...
And if I didn't have
my dagger with me,
snapping your spine would do.
[HARUHIRO yells]
[BARBARA] Now, then,
you'll want to become
intimately acquainted
with my Spider
before you try it on your own.
Be warned: I plan to
give you a hard time.
[HARUHIRO] You're not going
to kill me, though, right?
No. I wouldn't do that.
I'm always careful not to
be too rough with my students.
Very few have died as
a result of my training.
"Few"? So there
were some, then?
[BARBARA chuckles]
[HARUHIRO yells]
[HARUHIRO groans, yells]
[HARUHIRO grunts, groans]
There's no point practicing
if you can't stand.
Why don't we mix things up?
There are lots of
things we can do
while you're lying down.
We could work those
abs with sit-ups...
Or we could review the best
ways to withstand torture.
Please! I'm dying here.
Seriously.
[BARBARA]
All right.
If you're going to be a baby
about it, we can just chat.
[HARUHIRO]
I don't think I can.
Okay, so you want
to do sit-ups then?
Chatting. Right.
Sounds good... About what?
I don't know.
Just tell me a little story.
[HARUHIRO] But...
I don't know any stories.
You are a spectacularly
boring man.
I guess that's why you're
no good with the ladies.
[HARUHIRO]
That's not nice.
True, but not nice.
[BARBARA] You've got girls
in your party, right?
Not just guys?
Yes... three of them.
[BARBARA] So why don't you
go out with one of them?
Well... all three
would be better,
but it's best to start small.
You know, I think I'd
rather not, honestly.
Oh, come on. You're interested
in at least one, aren't you?
[HARUHIRO grunts]
You are!
You just pictured her.
Oh, hey... um,
I almost forgot...
There... There was
something I've been wanting
to ask you about.
Why am I not surprised?
Something about women?
Well, no, actually.
That's not it at all.
It's not?
In that case, I don't
know if I'm interested.
You might be once
you hear what it is.
At least give me a chance.
The light, huh?
If you're seeing it at this
stage, that's a good sign.
[HARUHIRO]
A sign of what?
Easy now.
It's not like it's
something super special.
I wouldn't want you getting
the wrong idea or anything.
How... can I
get the wrong idea...
...when I don't...
...have any idea what
it is in the first place?
[BARBARA]
You really are slow, aren't you?
You're even more like
an old cat than I thought.
[HARUHIRO]
I am? Agh!
[BARBARA]
Yeah, you are.
You've got decent intuition,
but you're slow.
Like a cat past his prime.
But back to the
streak of light...
Anybody who's got
enough experience
will see it once or twice.
I see it pretty often, actually.
Not every day or anything,
but fairly frequently.
Is that normal?
[gasps]
It's certainly not unheard of.
It differs from thief to thief.
And what about you?
[groans]
I see it here and there,
but not all the time.
It's not something you can do
just by concentrating
hard enough.
Oh...
f you want to see it
more consistently,
your best bet is
to hone your skills
and increase your
physical strength.
Yes ma'am!
You've got enough breath
in your lungs to talk?
We'd better work harder.
[HARUHIRO yelling]
Is this really it?
It looks like a
normal mountain to me.
Yeah.
[HARUHIRO]
Long ago,
the Cyrene Mine was established
by the Arabikia Kingdom.
A nation of humans.
It was part of their
effort to take control
of the frontier lands.
Unfortunately for Arabikia,
their dominance
would be short-lived...
Under the command
of the No Life King,
kobolds assaulted
the Cyrene Mine,
seizing it and
ousting the humans.
The kobolds have inhabited
the mine ever since.
All right. Let's do this.