[KOBOLD A growls]
[RANTA groaning]
Ha. I promise
I don't taste good.
Huh, didn't see that coming.
They're ugly, but
they sure are friendly.
Maybe they like Dark Knights.
Ew, gross!
O Darkness, Master of Vices.
Call forth my demon.
[ZODIAC] Wimpy Ranta!
Wimpy, wooly caterpillar!
Caterpillar,
caterpillar, caterpillar!
Why the hell are you
calling me "caterpillar"?
Hey, Zodiaco, come on. I really
need to get out of this mine.
Think you could
help me with that?
[ZODIAC]
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Die, die, die. Just die...
[RANTA]
Yeah, thanks.
I'm already halfway
there, I think.
[ZODIAC]
Don't you want to die
and feel Lord
Skullhell's embrace?
Doesn't that sound nice?
[ZODIAC laughing]
[ZODIAC]
Caterpillar, caterpillar...
[RANTA] All right! Fine!
I'm a caterpillar. Whatever.
[MARY] O light, return to
Lumiaris' divine protection.
Cure.
All right, let's focus
and talk about what
we're going to do next.
We've made it this far.
Let's keep being smart, okay?
We will do all we can
to rescue Ranta.
But that doesn't mean we should
start getting reckless.
He wouldn't thank us for that.
Hey, guys.
I wanna say... Ranta isn't
my favorite person.
I think everybody
knows that by now.
He says mean things
about my appearance.
No matter how many times
I ask him to stop,
he keeps on doing it.
I don't think anyone can blame
me for not liking him very much.
Let's be honest, he's just kind
of a jerk, you know? But...
...jerks can still get scared.
I would be,
down there all alone.
I hate even thinking about
what he must be going
through right now.
Poor Ranta, facing
Death Spots by himself.
We should be down there,
helping him. It's not fair!
[YUME crying]
I wouldn't worry too much.
If Ranta could be
killed that easily,
he'd have died a
hundred times by now.
Let's go.
Ranta's waiting for us.
[thud]
Vice, Vice, Vice, Vice, Vice...
Stop worrying about Vices.
[RANTA]
Uh-oh!
[howling]
[YUME]
Ranta?
It does sound like
his kind of trouble.
Look! There!
[HARUHIRO] Is it really him?
He managed to get away?
That's incredible! He was
basically surrounded by kobolds.
His will to live is greater than
anyone else's I've ever met.
The rest of us are strong, too,
but no one can
rival his tenacity.
Stay alive, Ranta.
[ZODIAC]
Die! Die, die, die!
Die, die, die, die, die!
Die, Ranta! Die, Ranta!
Die, die, die, Ranta!
[ZODIAC laughing]
Flat-chest.
[ZODIAC] Flat-chest,
flat-chest, flat-chest...
[RANTA] I shoulda made a move
for it when I had the chance!
[RANTA screaming]
Let's go, Exhaust!
[HARUHIRO]
Ranta!
What the hell
are you doing here?
You can't just show up
out of nowhere like that.
I didn't need you, Haruhiro.
I coulda handled this
on my own, you know!
[MOGUZO yells]
[MOGUZO]
Thank you!
Marque, Em, Parc!
[MARY] O light, return to
Lumiaris' divine protection.
Heal!
[YUME]
Haru!
So you know,
this is my last arrow!
This way, everyone! Come on!
We need to go. Can you run?
Of course I can run.
Do you think that
I'm that helpless?
[yelling]
Shihoru!
Marque, Em Parc!
[KOBOLD A roaring]
[MARY] O light, return to
Lumiaris' divine protection.
Cure.
Hey, look at me.
Are you crying, Ranta?
No, I'm not!
Your eyes are all red
and watery, though.
Yours would be too
if you were hurt.
Well, you better be careful.
If I didn't know better,
I might almost think that
you're glad to see us again.
Of course I'm glad to see you!
[RANTA grunts]
Nevermind!
I don't care about
you morons that much!
When I thought I would never
see your ugly faces again,
my chest just got a little
tight, that's all.
Talking about your chest now?
That's a nice change of pace.
Come on, you know what I meant!
No, I don't.
I just felt a little,
well, you know--
[YUME]
Yes?
A little...
[YUME]
Hmm? Go on. I'm waiting.
I felt...
[YUME]
Tell me all about it.
[grunts]
Just let it go, flat-chest!
Don't call me that, you jerk.
[RANTA] Just try to stop me!
I'll call you whatever I want!
Flat-chest! Flat-chest!
[YUME yelling]
[MARY]
Enough!
You need to be quiet
and stay still.
Or if you want, I can
just stop healing you.
Um... no ma'am.
I'm sorry.
I'll be good, I swear.
[BOTH chuckle]
[HARUHIRO]
Hey, everyone!
I think we're all clear.
Let's go home.
What do you say, guys?
That sounds like a great idea.
Yeah, we've been down here
forever. I'm glad it's done.
[HARUHIRO]
It's not over quite yet.
Nobody let your
guard down, 'kay?
We still have to
make it back to Ortana.
[HARUHIRO]
Back there in the well,
Ranta said, "You're our
leader, aren't you?"
That felt strange to me.
Because as hard as I've tried,
it's always felt like Manato
was still our real leader.
And until I became like him,
I would only be pretending,
like a kid playing
dress-up or something.
But...
But the thing is,
I'll never be Manato.
Sorry, just thinking out loud.
[HARUHIRO]
Everyone's different.
We all have strengths
and weaknesses.
That's what Manato believed.
Although, as much
as I've thought about it,
I still don't know what
his weaknesses were.
I can't say the same
about myself.
I know there are a ton of things
I still need to work on.
Fortunately though, my friends
are always there to help me.
Their strengths balance out
my weaknesses, and vice versa.
I think that's why we
work so well as a party.
Except, if I was a real leader,
wouldn't I be stronger?
Able to manage on my own?
I dunno.
If things are running
smoothly enough,
I guess that's all that
really matters, isn't it?
Like with Ranta.
We may not always get along,
but if we fight well together,
who cares about that?
Surviving each day is what
matters most in the end.
[MARY]
Hiro.
I'm pretty drained. I won't be
able to use magic for a while.
I might be able
to manage one Cure.
I need to get
somewhere to meditate.
[HARUHIRO]
I don't know much about magic,
but I can tell Mary's
serious about this.
Shihoru looks drained, too.
All right. We should
get moving, then.
We'll try to make
it out of the mine
without bothering
the lesser kobolds.
[KOBOLD A growling]
You've gotta be kidding!
Will he ever quit?
Marque, Em, Parc!
Thank you!
You have to be careful!
The more damage he takes,
the stronger he gets!
You mean he can get
stronger than this?
[roaring]
[HARUHIRO]
What should we do? Run?
It's our only choice,
but can we outrun him?
I don't think that will work
now that he's found us.
Our best bet at this point
is to leave somebody behind
to slow him down.
[yelling]
[HARUHIRO] I didn't think
about it for long.
My body just started moving.
[HARUHIRO]
Spider!
I'm counting on you!
Got it, Ranta? Get going!
[gasps]
[MARY]
Hiro!
Are you crazy, Mary?! Come on!
Let go of me!
We're leaving now!
[MARY crying]
[HARUHIRO]
Mary, are you crying?
Please don't cry.
Go on... Get out of here...
Everyone...
[HARUHIRO]
Is he saying something?
Don't you dare give up!
[gasps]
And don't die either.
Or I'll be pissed!
Get out of the mine. Hurry. Ah!
Damn. It's broken.
[KOBOLD A growling]
[HARUHIRO]
That's what I'm up against,
and you're telling me
not to give up?
Pretty ruthless, Ranta.
[HARUHIRO]
Still...
You didn't give up
when it was your turn.
So I guess I can't either, huh?
[HARUHIRO]
Mary, will you come back for me?
And cast Dispel like
you did for the others?
At least that way I'd
get to see you again.
Maybe. Someday.
[HARUHIRO] This is it...
a battle of life and death.
[HARUHIRO] I can't give up.
I can't stop fighting now.
As long as there's
still breath in my body,
I'll keep the battle going.
I won't give up.
Not until I'm dead!
Come on!
[HARUHIRO]
Huh?
[HARUHIRO] That's strange.
He's standing still.
No, that's not it.
He is moving, just very slowly.
[HARUHIRO]
Don't think. Act.
[MARY humming]
[HARUHIRO]
Huh?
Mary... is this Heaven?
[MARY laughing]
Not Heaven. Home.
Haru! You're awake!
It's about time!
Sorry, I didn't mean
to keep you waiting.
I bet you're hungry. Here.
[HARUHIRO]
Great, thank you.
Is something the matter?
Oh. I was just wondering
what happened.
You really don't remember?
[chuckles]
Take a look.
[RANTA]
That's 30 gold.
It's the bounty on Death Spots.
That oughta jog your
memory a little bit.
We agreed that we wouldn't
make any decisions
about how to divide it
until after you woke up.
Ranta said to wait.
He wanted to hear what you
thought since you're the leader.
[HARUHIRO]
Ranta said that?
[RANTA] Yeah. You don't
have to look so surprised.
Anyway, when we went
back to get you,
we took a little
souvenir with us.
[HARUHIRO]
You came back for--?
Right. I guess that
explains how I got here.
Given the way he looked,
we didn't think that
Death Dots would miss it.
[HARUHIRO]
"Dots"?
Yume, I think you
mean Death Spots.
Oh, so you mean that's--?
[MOGUZO]
Yeah.
My sword was broken,
and his seemed like
a good quality piece,
so I thought I would
try it out, you know?
[HARUHIRO] Seriously?
You're amazing, Moguzo.
[MOGUZO]
Oh, not really.
I mean, I can't
use it like this.
I was thinking I might
take it to a swordsmith.
[HARUHIRO]
Ha.
I guess that's one of the ways
we'll use the bounty, then.
[MOGUZO]
Would you mind?
[YUME] When it's done,
we have to give it a name, okay?
And it should be something
that's really cute.
[MOGUZO]
A name? Like what?
[YUME]
I don't know.
Like Cleaver Number One
or something.
[SHIHORU] Yeah, that's kind
of cute. I guess...
[chuckles]
[BRITTANY]
Not too bad, little ones.
[MARY]
Hey. Here.
I fixed it for you.
[HARUHIRO]
The slight weight of the badge
settled against my chest,
and somewhere deep inside,
I felt myself grow calm.
And when that happened...
it suddenly became clear to me.
I really am home now.
[chuckles]
Took long enough.
[KIKKAWA] Hey! I heard all
about it, Haru-Haru!
You crazy kids killed Spots,
huh? That's amazing!
I'm super jelly jealous! Way to
go, man! Way to go, go, go!
Australia!
Yeah! To Australia!
[RANTA laughing]
Ha. I never know
what he's saying.
[SHINOHARA]
Hm.
They brought her back.
I'm so glad.
[MAN A]
Renji.
Renji, what's up?
[RENJI]
I wanted to say sorry.
For the way I acted
when Manato died.
[HARUHIRO]
Oh...
No. It's all right.
You don't need to apologize.
[RENJI]
I don't? Really?
I was in denial.
What you did helped me
to start facing the fact
that he was gone.
It woke me up.
So, I don't know, maybe
I should thank you.
All right, then.
[RANTA]
Ha!
Listen up! The drinks
are on us today!
So what d'ya say
to another round?
[MANATO]
What're you doing here again?
Why?
You don't want me coming?
No, that's not it.
You're welcome to.
[HARUHIRO]
Well anyway,
I came today because there's
something I wanted to ask you.
[MANATO]
What is it?
[HARUHIRO] I never thought
to ask while you were alive,
but was being a
leader tough for you?
[MANATO]
Has it been difficult for you?
I'm not sure.
You know, Haru,
you've really grown
since we first met.
Oh, really?
[HARUHIRO] Well, I am different
from the person I was yesterday.
I know that much.
And I guess I'll be a different
person again tomorrow.
That's how it is.
We change every day because
we learn something every day.
We live in the present,
but we work toward the future.
Goodbye for now. I'll be back.
[HARUHIRO] I arrived in this
world with no real memories.
Just echoes of
things I once knew.
And I'm discovering that
the longer I live here,
the fainter they become.
Like they're being
erased by time.
Wherever I came from,
I'm forgetting it more and more
completely every day I'm here.
I used to constantly feel
like I was forgetting
something important,
but not anymore.
Things are different.
There's the solid feeling
of stone beneath me,
and the soft rush
of air as I breathe.
Those things ground me.
They help me stay present,
and I'm thankful for that.
I have new memories now.
And they're more
than just echoes.
Much more.
These are memories that
I won't allow time to erase.
They're for me to keep.
Well, you guys. Let's go.