To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
You guys hear that?
Whoa!
Aww, crap! What are
you guys doin'?
I'm here in Shibuya,
where you can see
a RAPT mobile unit
conducting an urban...
Let's see here...
120 grams of cake flour...
442 calories...
2 eggs... 170 calories...
So, the metabolic
rate is 1.02 times...
What's going on?
What's happening... to Tokyo?
We have no need for wolves
or stray dogs in this city.
All our ranch needs... is a
flock of gentle little sheep.
Obedient, mindless,
ignorant sheep.
You seem to be doing well.
I'm glad to see it.
Thank you for coming, Sei.
Just seeing your face
is the best medicine
for me at this point.
How have you been? Well, I hope.
I am... Thank you for asking.
Sei... Ever since
you were a child,
you have had a strong sense
of responsibility to others.
But you always try to carry
the burden by yourself.
Grandfather...
You needn't any longer, Sei.
I can't help but
feel responsible
for placing such a weight
upon your shoulders...
It is my fault.
Nothing in this world
lasts forever.
Everything in existence
undergoes change...
Even with Bai-Lan,
nothing is absolute.
I had a dream this morning.
In it, a golden dragon ascended
from a sea of crashing waves,
through a storm,
and up into the heavens.
Sei... For once,
forget you are the grandaughter
of the Bai-Lan Elder...
And instead, follow
the path that you,
as a human being,
believes to be best...
It is on that path
where you will find
what it is you must do.
Hello? Amy? It's been awhile...
Hey Sei! Long time no hear!
Heck, I'm surprised
you even found me.
Never mind that...
I've had something urgent come
up, and I could use your help...
Are you up to it?
I dunno...
Is this a Bai-Lan job?
No, it's for me.
A personal request.
I want you to locate Jo and Meg.
Well yeah, of course I'll do it.
I'll be at Leo's.
Keep me posted.
I would kill for a nice,
hot cup of coffee right now.
Jo, are you all right?
Meg? Where are we?
Not sure. On a beach somewhere.
What happened to Maria?
She died... So that you and
I could get off the ship.
She's dead?
I see.
But... I'm really
glad you're alive, Jo!
Sure, I feel sorry for Maria...
but you're the most important
person I have in my whole life.
Once my clothes are dry,
I'll head into town
and pick up some food
and stuff for you to wear.
You just stay here and
rest until then, okay?
Yeah, sure... My head
still feels a little hazy...
I'll try to sleep
it off for a while.
Jo, I was thinking.
'Bout what?
When you're feeling better,
let's take a trip somewhere...
You know, just get away
from all this craziness.
Find a place with
no bad guys to kill
where we can have a happy
life, just you and me...
What do you think? Sound good?
Sleep well, Jo.
From now on, I'll protect you.
This doesn't make sense.
Fighting is all I've ever known.
I can't even comprehend
not wanting to fight...
What am I supposed to do, Jo?
Live on and you'll
find the answer.
Maria.
Is it true...? Are you
really gone forever?
Jo! Hit the dirt!
Oh yeah, now that felt good.
I mean that
felt real good...
O-kay...
Ugh. Gross!
What are those things?
Puppets... Controlled
by monster brains.
Anyway, how did
you find me here?
Oh no, please, there's
no need to thank me.
I only saved your hide
from certain death.
Not yet!
There's one more left. Above us!
Friend of those other
guys, I take it.
Looks that way...
This one's a bit tougher.
Who is that in there?
It's Leo.
What is that?
It's a micro-beacon
they implanted in her...
This is how they were
able to find her.
But... Thanks to
this little bugger,
we were able to
find her as well.
Sei sent you?
Yeah.
She told me where she had
Jango and the trailer stashed.
And she had Amy hack the
micro-beacon to track you down.
I see... Well then... Did she
happen to say anything else?
All she said was that she's
going to RAPT headquarters.
Don't get me goin' 'bout RAPT.
They're pretty much
runnin' Tokyo now...
And they got no concept
of proper law enforcement.
Haulin' in anyone who
breaks even the tiniest law.
Last I heard, Sei's group
was working with RAPT...
Why the hell would they
willingly give Jango back to me?
Ah... I almost forgot. Sei left
me one more thing for you.
Here.
This is... from Sei?
Here's the deal...
I have been requested to assist
RAPT in a special operation...
Bai-Lan's new leadership has
decided to merge the syndicate
with the organization
that's been controlling
RAPT in secrecy.
So are you a member
of RAPT now, Sei?
No! It's not like that at all...
The situation
I've been put in...
I know.
So tell me your plan.
Wait for me, Sei.
Just hang on 'til I get there.
I'm going to RAPT headquarters.
That's my girl!
Naturally, we'll have
your back the whole way.
Now this makes beating up
Daddy and running away worth it!
Don't do this!
This is RAPT
we're talking about!
You can't possibly beat them!
There's no reason
for you to do this.
Like I was telling
you earlier...
We can just get out of here...
Go far away and have
a happy life together.
You're always fighting...
always risking everything...
always tearing yourself up.
But there's no reason for you
to hurt yourself anymore, Jo!
Come with me!
Please Jo.
Meg... Sei plans
on fighting alone.
She's taking on RAPT, trying to
free Tokyo from their control...
Then she can get to the true
enemy pulling the strings,
and destroy them too...
I'm going... I have to.
I can't let Sei die.
Then... then I'm
going with you...!
I'll follow you to Hell
and back if I have to...
I'll never leave your side--
no matter what!
Listen to me, Meg.
I'm not... a normal human being.
I was built for war. I'm no
more than a living weapon.
Believe me, I didn't
ask to be this way...
But I am...
And if I can do something
with these abilities
I've been given...
something positive...
Then I have to try. It feels
like it's what I'm fated to do.
And I can't run from my fate.
What happened to you...?
It's like you're not even
the Jo I know anymore!
My Jo was always kind and
she always protected me...!
Whenever I was in trouble,
she came to my rescue...
And she never, ever
let me leave her side...
Goodbye Meg... I'm sorry.
From now on, Meg...
You must fight for
someone who needs you...
That is what your
future holds...
It's the future you
must now search for.
No!
That's not the kind of future
I want. Without you, I... I...
I know... You can
stop crying now, Meg.
Really?
So you mean... I can,
come with you then?
No.
I'll go prep the trailer...
We gotta move.
Forgive me... Meg.
Amy, do you copy? This is Jo.
We're on our way to
demolish RAPT headquarters.
Bring me up to speed.
Roger that, Jo...
My end of the operation
is underway...
RAPT has set up blockades on
every road leading into Tokyo.
There are large barricades
on the Mega-Highways
being defended by Guard Cybots.
Plus, they have a whole bunch of
brand new models guarding
RAPT headquarters.
Jo, if you can break
through the barricade...
I can totally fry their
com circuits into oblivion.
Sounds like a plan.
I'm Sei, from Bai-Lan...
Please, inform Mr. Glenford
I've come on an urgent
business matter.
Jo, please don't go!
Was it a dream?
J-Jo.
Jo! You idiot!
Target acquired.
Leaving downtown,
heading for Shinjuku fast.
Son of a bitch...!
Outta the way!
Special delivery, bastards!
This one's straight from Osaka!
Okay everybody. Are you ready?
--You know it, Amy!
--I'm all set, girl!
All right...
Begin upload... Now!
[TEXT]
"Fools"
[TEXT] "Fools" "Idiots"
"Imbeciles" "Stupid"
Alert! Alert! Deploy all units
and secure the perimeter.
Here they come!
'Kay, Jo... This is your cue!
What?!
Oh, you're just asking for it!
Aw, shit!
Jo, watch out!
This wouldn't happen to be the
urgent matter you spoke of...?
Don't tell me you came all
the way down here for this.
Yes. That's right.
I arranged the whole thing
so I could get you
right where I want you.
Really...? Are you sure...?
In doing this,
you are guaranteeing
Bai-Lan's future
will be forfeit.
Yes, but so will yours.
This is it! Go time!
[TEXT] "Fools" "Idiots"
"Imbeciles" "Stupid"
We're back on line!
What the--?!
Do you really think you've won?
If you take my life,
it will accomplish nothing...
I am merely a part
of the program.
When damaged, the program
will repair itself
and return to normal...
And the cycle will continue.
We will feed the
sheep of this nation.
We will shear and slaughter
them as we see fit...
And they will live their lives
completely oblivious
to this fact.
You and your cause
will be crushed...
Your deaths will be pointless...
You can't possibly
hope to change a thing.
Sei!
Jo.
Shoot that thing!
You just entered
a whole new world...
Welcome to Hell!
Jo... Keep fighting.
Farewell. Jo.
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky