To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
How are you feeling... Jo?
What the hell do you want?
Tell me what you're
doing with Meg.
From now on, she's going
to do what I tell her.
I see. Did Meg tell you that?
No, but she will soon enough.
I'm quite certain of it...
I am going to kill you soon.
And when she sees that,
she'll come around.
Don't screw with me.
You should know where I am.
I'll be waiting.
I'm coming... Just hang on, Meg.
This is so exciting...
I'm going to tear your
girlfriend to shreds.
And you...
No way. Never happen.
I already told you
I'm stuffed...
I can't eat another bite.
But that's Jo's food.
Go keep Jo company until
she finds her way to me.
All of the guard cybots on
board have been activated...
They're under Maria's
direct control.
Uh... Professor, I don't
understand Maria's logic.
Why doesn't she just
take the fight to Jo?
Think about it...
It makes perfect sense
for Maria to lure
Jo aboard Moon Empire in order
to stage their final battle...
Maria... most likely
is trying to recreate--
and resume--that final test.
Is it possible it's due to
Jo's memory-related trauma?
You're partly right.
It seems that Jo has
no memory of the powers
lying dormant within her.
Maria instinctively
knows this and wants
desperately for Jo
to regain her memory.
Then, hopefully, this
will shed some light
on the hidden power
Maria herself holds.
And when she taps into it
and stands in absolute
dominance over Jo,
she will devastate Jo
in body and mind.
Maria has no concept
of fear, so she thinks
with a completely rational mind.
She is amazingly calm
in battle and can make
only strategic decisions
towards winning.
We should expect nothing less.
After all, she is
the Genocide Angel.
And we created her.
Attention, citizens of Tokyo.
When traveling outside city
limits, be sure to carry
your RAPT-issued
Citizen Registration Card
with you at all times.
Non-citizens of
Tokyo will require
a Residency
Authorization License.
If asked for your
permits, please follow
the officer's instructions
promptly and respectfully.
Furthermore, evaluations for
firearm license applications
have also been revised.
From this point forward,
those wishing to carry
firearms will be required
to pass government-prescribed
tests of physical and
psychological fitness.
Thanks to RAPT's new "Peaceful
Purification" Initiative
hitting the streets this week,
nearly two hundred criminals
were arrested last night alone,
totaling almost 600
in the last five days.
To help increase the
efficiency of these patrols,
RAPT officials have imposed
a mandatory curfew
for all citizens and business
owners from sundown to sunup.
This curfew will be
strictly enforced.
Later this month, Tokyo's
Reconstruction Committee
will begin
investigating all leads
dealing with illegal residents,
jobs and organizations
in an effort to further
the city's development against
the UGP, or Underground People.
This includes a plan of
selection and isolation
of the growing
underground rebellion.
The committee will
coordinate with a team of
international sociologists
in this effort.
At a conference earlier
today, the city of Tokyo
announced an ordinance
requiring all residents,
including foreigners,
to undergo regular
medical checkups...
Through ongoing
investigations by RAPT's
Environmental
Preservation Section,
violators will be
located and punished.
We have now infiltrated
every major media outlet
and control 100%
of what they say.
All video and audio will
be routed through us
so we can edit them as we
see fit before they air.
Excellent work...
There's something else I need
you to take care of immediately.
Maria has taken control
of Moon Empire.
Make sure not one word of this
slips out until the
situation is dealt with.
Understood. I will
make it my top priority.
Status report please, Professor.
Yes, Mr. Glenford. Unfortunately
it appears that a change
even we couldn't
predict is taking place.
Maria has begun to act on
her own, of her own volition.
She wants to secure her desires.
I don't understand. She is a
genetically engineered soldier.
What desires could
she possibly have...?
Maria and the others like her
are no more than weapons
given human form...
We designed and programmed
each and every cell
of their bodies...
Neither the fear of death,
nor the joy of living
are even possible for them...
The sole purpose of
their existence--
everything that they know--
is to seek out enemies
and destroy them.
Desire was never part
of the equation.
The efficiency and
accuracy of a machine,
combined with the survival and
battle instincts of a beast...
That is what the Angels
were intended to be...
But unfortunately,
they were never able to escape
from one simple truth...
They were still human...
Fueled by an unconscious
desire to seek out enemies
stronger than themselves
and unknowingly find happiness
in destroying them.
Once Maria tastes victory in
the most extreme of situations,
it is possible she will evolve
into an even greater asset.
And if, she loses?
She will most likely experience
a loss of her identity
as a living battle weapon.
I expect she would then
choose to kill herself.
Where are we?
The ocean?
No one can interfere
with us out here.
This is insane!
What am I doing out here?!
And Jo... Where is Jo?!
I'm not sure, but I would
guess somewhere on this ship.
What, you guess?!
It is here that I will
finally destroy her.
And once I have...
You will belong to me, Meg.
M-M-Meg...?
Bitch, you have no right
to call me that name...!
Anyways, Jo would never
lose to someone like you!
Never!
What are you gonna do to me?
You may think you're
holding me hostage,
but I'm warning you now:
those games won't work on Jo!
Someone's gonna get slaughtered
here, but it's gonna be you!
How can you keep
talking to me this way?
You know I'm stronger
than her... And yet...
I don't understand.
How...?
How can you always rely on Jo?!
Ow...! Hey, let go of my arm.
I've changed my mind.
I will kill Jo... right now!
And then... I will kill you.
Wait, no... What'd you--?!
You're cute...
but you're weak, Meg...
However...
If you will truly have
no one else but her...
Then I have no use for you.
I... I can't move.
Be a good little girl and
stay right there, will you?
She's... coming... Damn it.
They're converging at
Nuclear Storeroom One.
No! Maria! You mustn't
fight there!
Wait a minute... These are all--
She's here.
What's the matter?
Miss me already?
No, not quite...
Now die!
Amazing. Maria's combat
neuron production
is increasing exponentially.
If this continues, her synapses
won't be able to keep up.
Amazing... This must
be why the Angels
were forbidden from
fighting each other...
Won't work!
I know!
Professor. Is there any way
we can stop them from fighting?
Even our own override
program has been blocked.
We cannot intervene until
the battle has come to an end.
Are you telling me
that it's not possible
to hack into the Moon Empire?
There's nothing we can do.
Moon Empire is a crewless mother
ship with an artificial brain.
And is currently under
Maria's complete control.
However, there is a
prototype cybot on board
that doesn't have
such limitations.
I win.
How is this possible?
Maria's combat neurons
have completely disappeared.
Wh-What is this...?
What's happened to me?
I don't understand it...
but for some reason, I've
lost the will to fight you.
Same here...
I've hit my limit, too.
No, wait...! Why don't
you want to fight anymore?
Because you don't
wanna fight anymore.
This doesn't...
This doesn't make sense...
Fighting is all I've ever known.
I can't even comprehend
not wanting to fight.
What am I supposed to do, Jo?
Jo, no!
A perfect being
who knows no fear...
Wasn't that what a Genocide
Angel was supposed to be?
Regardless of upbringing,
those who are born human
cannot suppress
their humanity...
Even if they are
created in a lab,
that is a barrier I'm
afraid we will never break.
It's far too early to draw
conclusions, Professor.
What I find most surprising
is the extent of
Jo's latent abilities,
which surpassed even
Maria's combat programming.
Amazing... The more Jo fights,
the greater the power
that is awakened within her.
And all for the sake of saving
that ridiculous partner of hers.
Jo... You can beat her...
It can't be... Jo lost?
No, that's impossible--
Jo doesn't know how to lose.
Jo... Wake up...!
Please wake up!
Please Jo, you can't die
like this! Answer me!
Jo is not dead.
Damn you! How dare you hurt her!
Give her back to me!
There's nothing to
worry about, Meg.
She simply expended too much
energy while fighting me...
It's all right.
She'll be unconscious
until her cerebral
programming has been reset.
But aren't you and Jo enemies?
No, not anymore.
Believe it or not, I've
realized I want Jo to live...
Because... I like her.
What are you saying?
Maria. Obey your orders and
return for additional
programming immediately.
If you refuse these orders,
we will have no choice
but to eliminate you.
Maria... Respond!
I will not subject myself to
your programming any longer!
So be it...
With those words, you have
chosen your own execution.
Do it.
Meg! Take Jo and
get out of here!
Jump into the ocean...! Hurry!
Maria!
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
Here in this Hell on Earth...
where an immense
evil reigns supreme...
the Angels begin their
ultimate mission...
The final Burst Angel:
"Angels, Explode!"