To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
And a-one! And a-two!
And a-three!
Huh? Yeah... No, I tried...
Well, I'm trying to write
a report on Osakan food...
Yeah, I know... 'Kay, bye.
Hey what's up...? That yer
lady friend from home?
No, it's my teacher...
From my cooking school
back in Tokyo.
You're goin' out
with you're teacher?
That's sweet!
Tell her to get on out here too!
We can all have a good time!
Uh, I think I've had
enough fun for one trip.
Say, man...! Y'ever
see a frog rocket?
It's where you shove
a buncha fireworks
up a frog's butt
and send 'im flyin!
Oh man, when scrawny dudes
like you ignore me...
They get to fly
like the frogs!
And a-one! And a-two!
And a-three! Fly!
Ow... That hurt.
Well, Hells bells!
I didn't know folks from
Tokyo could sit on water...!
Shoot, I could do that!
Hey, kid...! Check me out!
I can sit on top
of the water, too!
Why...? Why can't
I sit on water...?!
Help! I can't swim!
What's your name...?
I asked you a question!
Get it...?!
Can the act, Tokyo!
What's the matter? Need me
to draw you a picture...?
You deaf or somethin'...? Huh?!
It's Jo.
Now was that so hard? "Jo" what?
Mamasfat.
Jo... Mamas... fat.
Do not screw with me!
Your pencil broke.
I've about had it
with you...! Now talk!
You were at the D.D.D.
fights last night...
You know, a lot of
people were very upset
with Mega Rider's defeat.
So tell me, what were
you doing there?
Part-time job.
What kind of part-time
job requires you to carry
big guns like this around and
interfere with police business?
Cut the crap and start talkin'.
You could try to
be more ladylike...
This is Hanshin
Police Incorporated.
A top-rate law
enforcement company.
I was just...
Going off like a
big-shot biker chick...
I know, but that
ain't the way to do it.
You're better than that.
I'm sorry.
You ever heard of the Kanbaku?
Piss off.
Watch your mouth!
Iriki!
They're a Kansai biker gang...
And li'l Takane here
was their deadly leader.
If I were you, I would
try not to make her angry.
That should teach her.
Thought she was just
some dumb biker chick.
The Hanshin Police Department
has been in operation
since the days of the
Bakuto gambler class...!
We have since risen
above our dark past
and gained the trust
of the people!
In other words...
We are the ones who
hold this city together!
Takane--
If you go and make enemies of
the people in this room...
Then you've gone and made
enemies with all of Osaka.
Understand?
I wasn't listening--
You want a thrashin'?!
I got bad news!
Bad enough we gotta deal
with flying trains,
but now it's flying lunches?
Oh... Sorry...
I didn't mean to...
So, what's the big emergency?
They found some kinda
crazy, giant insect corpse
down in Dotonbori...
Some big-city kid jumped on top
of it and hurt his dumb self.
Let's go--
Right!
Oh yeah, Tokyo! There's
some lady here to see ya.
Hurry up Masa-yan!
Well lemme wash my face first!
Quite a mess you
managed to cause.
Caused itself.
Thanks to you,
I got a stern lecture
and we got our budget cut.
Sorry, I'll buy you some udon.
Really? Well if you're buying...
Let's go get okonomiyaki.
All right, so let me guess.
About this creature--
Yeah, it was like the ones
we've seen before...
It had that same glowing
brain on its head.
But a mutant bug and a subway
attack both on the same day...?
That seems like an
odd coincidence.
There has to be some kind of
connection between the two.
In which case, we're in
for some more action.
Well, the D.D.D. job's over
so there's no reason
to stay in Osaka.
We'll head out today.
Hey. You see that
huge beetle they found?
It ain't a beetle.
It's a mutated cockroach!
I'm telling you,
it's one of them
big ol' Hercules beetles
from Australia...
I should know, I lived down
there for almost four years.
Looks like they're prepping
for a showdown...
Guess pretty girl
does have a death wish.
A professional killer
will aim for your head!
You cannot rely on your vest!
Aim quickly and fire...!
Stay calm and focus!
Hey, there y'are.
Good work today.
Yeah? Ain't no thing.
Y'know, I love a good cuppa joe.
Ever since I was a little kid.
I guess you do.
We have to protect it--
This city... our home, Osaka...
We'll die doin' it if we hafta.
Yeah--
Welcome back, Chief Inspector!
Thanks... good to be back.
Welcome back, sir!
We've been expecting you.
Hi, Dad!
That's Chief--
Sorry, Dad.
Wish I had time for you,
but I have to leave town.
What for?
The National Public Safety
Council wants to gripe at me
about these recent
unfortunate events.
I'll be countin' on y'all
to hold down the fort.
Count on it, sir.
We've got the
festival coming up...
And there's no way
I'm going to cancel it...
We gotta get this under
control... Got me?
Understood.
Oh and, Masa-yan?
Yeah?
Today was your daughter,
Milly's birthday wasn't it?
That's right... her third.
My wife's throwing a party.
Being away from your family
on days like today is tough...
I thank you.
Oh, no, no thanks
necessary... I, uh...
Oh, Takane?
Yes?
Don't forget to take some
flowers by your mother's grave
while I'm outta town.
I won't.
All, salute!
Good luck, sir!
Bye, dad...
Hey! Eyes on the road!
Freakin' moron!
Sorry 'bout that...
You two girls all right?
We're fine.
I didn't mean to shake you up
but that guy pulled out
right in front of me.
It was like he was
trying to hit us.
Hell, ever since that
subway incident...
I've seen lots of those trucks.
One of these days they're gonna
cut in front of the wrong guy
and then they'll be sorry.
People in Osaka don't like
getting pushed around
by outsiders. And you
know how payback can be.
Hey, listen...
I don't suppose you could
follow that truck for me?
Well, I reckon I could.
♪ Oh, Jango! How I love you! ♪
♪ You're the best. My Jingy,
Jangy, Jang-Jang-Jango! ♪
Yeah... Okay... Got it.
Oh, Amy!
You awake in there?
Oh Meg, is it morning already?
Um... Amy...?
What are you doing?
Nothing... Just working out some
issues with our optic cables.
Geez,... if you're
this weird now,
what are you gonna be
like when you grow up?
Anyway, Sei just called
and she needs us all
in Osaka right away.
Osaka? Let's go! Let's go!
But, who's gonna
drive the truck?
Leo.
All right, I got a line on
that truck you're after...
Just turned west
onto Ninjo Avenue...
You should be able to
spot him any second...
Hold on, he's
stopped at a light
about a half a block
ahead of you.
Okay, thanks fellas,
I just spotted him!
Yeah, that's right,
the girls from Tokyo.
Best be careful,
one of them carries
a pair of mean-looking
guns... Handle it.
I'm live at the National Diet...
where inside, representatives
from all branches
of law enforcement and many
concerned citizen's groups
have gathered to discuss
the recent acts of terrorism.
Earlier today, Chief Katsu
arrived from Osaka
for a briefing that
preceded the conference.
After the accident, an
anonymous call was received.
What follows is a
tape-recording of that call.
If you got a point, you
better get to it darn quick!
You're not taking me
seriously, that hurts...
Doesn't matter...
What you fail to understand
is that all of this
is far from over.
In fact, I'm just
getting started!
Be warned, I will
utterly destroy
the Hanshin Police Force.
And that's not all.
I will bring down
all of Osaka with you!
I'm sure you'll all going
to be looking forward to it.
We gotta stop him.
Chief Katsu, is this a
claim of responsibility?
Did the caller identify himself?
Please, everyone calm down!
Later today,
Chief Katsu will meet with
top officials from R.A.P.T.
to discuss strategies for
combating the terrorist threat.
From The National Diet
Building, I'm Sean Billings.
This can't... be real?
Can it, Inspector?
Wish I could tell ya.
Hey, I got a lead to
check out, all right?
Time to do a
little detective work?
You recognize that logo?
It was on that train we were
chasing a few weeks back.
Yeah, so?
This might have something to do
with that creature you ran into.
You did say it had
the same glowing brain.
But why did the truck come
here to this abandoned park.
That's what we're
about to find out.
What is it?
The driver's been shot!
What? It's a set up?
A trap...
Get down!
Take it easy. You don't have
to be so rough about it.
Sorry, didn't mean to be...
Stay under the truck
and keep your head down.
No problem.
There he is!
Hey Sei, you can come out now.
Sei!
Hey check it out. I'm picking
up a huge EM signal!
And despite its crazy-big size,
my readings say it's flying.
Where's it headed?
Let's see...
Tracking toward something
that looks like Tokyo Tower.
What is that thing?
It's gone berserk!
It's some kind of robot!
You think it can see us in here?
What is that thing
tryin' to do?!
You are witnessing the debut
of the cybot Giganits.
Cool, isn't it?
Let's cut the small talk.
What are you trying to do?
You're a smart guy.
Why don't you figure it out?
How original.
You're gonna blow up
Tsutenkaku Tower, aren't you?
You know, I hadn't
thought of that,
but it's an interesting idea.
You wouldn't dare...!
I will hunt you down!
Ooh, scary!
The detective who's too busy
for his own family has
a really nasty temper.
What? What did you say?
Attention, we have an
emergency situation.
All mobile and attack
units report to the tower
and establish a defensive
perimeter immediately!
A rogue cybot is attempting
to destroy the tower!
Roger!
You sons of bitches...!
I'll turn y'all into
sashimi, you hear me?!
Yeah! Get the hell
out of our town!
Dang! That thing's huge...
Well, go get him!
I love the way an
historic structure can
captivate the public and come
to symbolize an entire city...
Tsutenkaku Tower
is one of those.
Why are you making me
sit here and watch this?
No real reason, my good Chief...
I just wanted you to
have a front row seat
for the collapse of Osaka.
When this is over,
a great opportunity will
have presented itself.
And, what's that...?
Are you gonna take over Osaka?
To be perfectly frank...
I've always been a little bit
jealous of you out there.
How's that?
Osaka's great sense
of community...
How can Tokyo even
hope to compare?
Our streets are littered
with worthless vermin
and unchecked immigrants.
You see, that's the
reason I created RAPT.
To eliminate those
unwanted elements
and rebuild a solid community.
Interesting... Y'know
you're quite insane.
If you go along with us,
we can avoid
the real unpleasantness that
most certainly will follow.
I'm sure we can work out
a suitable "bargain."
We must defend the tower!
We must defend Osaka!
Honor our history...!
Remember Osaka Castle!
Don't get upset.
Who the hell do
you think you are?
You and your corruption made
Tokyo into the cesspool it is!
The will of the
people still thrives
on our side of the Hakone Wall!
If you want Osaka...
then fight us!
I'm sure you'll fight bravely,
but you just can't win.
This is Inspector
Masa of Tiger-1!
All units open fire!
Aim for the torso!
Yeah, kill it!
Die you gravy sucking pig!
Hell, yeah!
Takane...
Inspector Iriki...! Inspector,
where are you...? Inspe--
Masa-yan.
Hey... I can't--I can't
find Inspector Iriki.
Is he with you...? Masa-yan?
Takane... will you
do me a favor?
My daughter turned
three today...
When she's old enough,
tell her about me.
Tell her about what
kind of cop I was.
It would mean a lot...
Oh, yeah... Don't take any
shit from those traitors!
Osaka's justice will never die!
Masa-yan!
Milly...! I was...
a good cop...!
I lived to serve
the city I loved...!
Your father died so
that you could live!
How ya like that...?!
Here! Y'want another taste?!
What the--?
Hurry!
I know, I know!
Who the hell are you guys?
You're Takane of the Elite
Division, Hawk Squad, right?
Yeah...
That's Jo taking care
of things for you.
Not good...
You let go of Jo...!
Let go! Let go!
Gigantis, go ahead and crush
that thing like a tin can.
C'mon! We need to get
to the trailer now!
Why...? You traitor...
You traitor!
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
Justice spoiled; trust
betrayed; sadness endured...
And unlikely heroes
who rise from the brink of
despair and destruction...
Next Burst Angel:
"Showdown in Osaka."