To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
Nestled deep in a remote forest
stands St. Luciana's Academy,
an elite prep school
for the well-to-do.
After a series of
bizarre occurrences
and unexplained
psychological traumas,
Meg enrolled as
a transfer student
to investigate the school
from the inside out.
One night, Meg discovered
a young girl on the roof
and stopped her from
committing suicide.
The girl, Yoko, was fraught with
terror and seemed possessed,
as if tortured by
some unseen phantom.
At the center of it all
was the Ishtar Club,
a highly secretive and
exclusive student organization.
Meg was invited to join,
and immediately had
suspicions about Angelique,
their beautiful and
intelligent leader.
Her curiosity piqued, Meg's
investigation pressed forward.
But, before she knows it,
she's attacked by a monster
and running for her life.
Oh, Jo! Thank you!
So, where the hell did
that thing come from?
The dormitory,
I think. I'm not sure.
Well, the sneaky detective
bit's not gonna work anymore.
But things are definitely
getting interesting.
No, they are not getting
interesting! I wanna go home!
I don't wanna be here anymore!
This is not fun!
Startin' today, I'm going
undercover with you.
Really?
Yeah. You'd have had a hard time
fighting that thing by yourself.
But, Jo...
That uniform's not your style.
Oh. You think?
Ladies. I would
like to introduce
our new transfer
student, Jo Carpenter.
Jo has been overseas for the
last few years with her father,
an important Japanese diplomat.
So, Kyo, my little devil...
How do you suppose Jo
is doing in there so far?
She gets points in my book
just for wearing that uniform.
--So not her!
Yeah, yeah.
I got it. Understood!
I just got some news.
The drug tests on the Bai-Lan
girl came back positive.
It looks like she's been taking
them daily for some time now.
Stop! Stop!
It turns out there's a
compound present in the drug
that sends the subject
into an extreme manic state.
It's like they're
in some trance.
So then--
Yes, we need to get
word to Meg and Jo
not to eat the food there.
Listen Kyo, I know it's crazy,
but we're counting on you.
Oh, sure!
Well we know Jo can
take care of herself,
but do you think
Meg's gonna be okay?
Dear Lord, please make this food
taste just a little bit
better than yesterday's.
Only one way to find out.
Gotta dig right in!
Bon appetit, me!
Don't eat any of the food here.
Ahh, this is getting
worse everyday!
This sucks. The biggest
danger in this crappy place
is starving to death.
Dig in if you
enjoy hallucinations.
Halluci-- So, are you saying
all the food here is drugged?
More than likely.
Amy contacted me.
No way. So, everyone here has
been eating poisoned food?
Hey, Meg. What's up?
Oh, hi, Yoko.
You're eating lunch
with Jo, I see?
You guys are friends already?
But you're in different grades.
Um, yeah! Y'know we're
both pretty new here, and...
We just hit it off
right from the start!
Oh, well, if you're good
enough to be Meg's friend,
then you're good enough
to be my friend too.
Great.
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to eat?
Lunchtime's almost over.
Uh, I really wasn't
very hungry today.
--Oh, my!
--Uh, you see...
Meg's on a new diet.
Hey! Watch the hands!
She was just telling
me how careless she is
about what she eats.
Oh, Jo, you crack me up
almost as much as Meg does!
Maybe I should be on a diet.
What do you think?
Ladies! I need a moment
of your time please.
Earlier this morning, someone
broke into the Ishtar club,
and with extreme prejudice,
vandalized it!
This is a horrible blight
on our entire school.
Some miscreant devil
thought it would be funny
to destroy the harmony
of our environment!
Miscreant devil?
Exaggerate much, Drama Queen?
She's completely mental.
And those gloves she was
wearing were so obvious.
You know she's hiding
that wound you gave her.
Totally suspicious.
Once I discover her
true identity-- Ha!
I'll give her a good
pounding and teach her
not to mess with us!
Megumi.
Would you kindly
come with me, please?
We have some questions
we'd like to ask.
I'm kinda busy now. Later?
Just go.
But I...
Get moving.
All right, all right. Whatever!
Tell me. Where do
you come from, Meg?
You know, I moved around a
lot with my dad. So, all over.
Your transfer papers here,
say you're from Okinawa,
is that correct?
Yeah. That's right. I was
born and raised in Okinawa.
What is she doing
with my transfer papers?
Oh, you know what?
I misread that.
It actually says you
were born in Hokkaido.
What? Oh, yeah.
That's right. Hokkaido.
Wait one second. My mistake,
this isn't even your file.
Cut the crap!
You think you're special just
'cause your daddy's rich?
If you've got something to say,
why don't you spit it out?
All right, let's
cut to the chase.
So uh, what are you gonna do?
Not like that little butter
knife scares me or anything.
Not too much.
This is no way to handle things!
How can you be certain
Meg was the intruder?
Are you prepared to
take responsibility
if you're mistaken?
What do you mean?
Meg was with me this morning.
After breakfast, we
enjoyed a leisurely walk
in the courtyard in
front of the school.
Now, put down the knife.
This matter is settled.
Thanks for helping
me out back there.
Don't worry about it.
Angelique can definitely
get carried away sometimes.
I didn't think you'd
mind me stepping in.
This school can be pretty
rough on new kids,
and I hate seeing
people get picked on.
So, the underclassmen have
swim class next period, right?
You better hurry
so you're not late.
Yeah. I better get going.
And thanks again.
I'll return the favor, if I can.
Jo? What are you doing?
Nothing.
Are you trying to embarrass
me in front of Nadesico?
No one here but me.
What the... Where'd she go?
She was just here.
Man, I'm getting sick and
tired of those prissy snobs
picking on me all the time!
I am not the kind of girl
that gives in to threats.
No sir-ree.
Are you even listening to me?
You're wearing my
favorite pair of panties!
Sorry. I was in a rush so I
just grabbed whatever was clean.
But that's my underwear! Who
takes other people's panties?
Who cares? We share
everything else.
Take 'em off!
I was going to.
I said off!
Take it easy! What if an
enemy showed up right now?
What do you care?
You're the one who prances
around half-naked all the time!
It's easier to fight that way.
Hey. You okay?
I guess. That swim
really wiped me out.
I think you're right.
Maybe I do need to go on a diet.
I'm feeling really heavy today.
Meg!
Meg? Jo?
Just stay out of our way,
or you'll be getting another
visit from the monster.
Meg, stay with me!
Get out of the pool!
You're okay now.
Jo!
Meg!
Jo, help!
Ahh! No!
So, what now? Jo?
Get a hold of Sei right away!
Tell her we've got a really
mean algae problem in the pool.
Are you okay?
Get out of here right now!
Run for the trailer.
Right!
Oh my god, oh my god,
it's here, it's here!
And it's like,
totally going nuts on Jo!
Meg, what are you talking about?
Calm down and tell
me what happened!
There was like,
this giant algae problem!
I mean, it was, like, a monster!
And it attacked us in the pool!
And then the other
students went all
"Night of the Living
Schoolgirl" on us!
This is really bad!
Oh, and now Jo's fighting
that monster thing!
What did this monster look like?
Meg are you there? Meg?
Not again.
You're not getting
away that easily.
Hey, let me go!
Take me down! You jerks!
You have been chosen.
It was my sworn duty
to watch over you.
I have fulfilled my task,
and now I have been allowed
to return to the fold.
Hey, that's the soup
they serve at lunch!
Just drink it, Meg.
We have done as
you have commanded.
Why are you here?
Where did you come from?
I don't...
I used to... I, uh...
I lived in New York.
What else?
That was where I met Jo.
Jo? The other transfer student?
Yes, that's right.
She's usually laid-back,
but Jo always protects me.
When she's angry,
she's unstoppable.
Meg!
Wha... What's going on?
Stop! I will not allow
any further violence.
Unless it's retaliation for
this wound. I'll make you pay!
See that?
She's the one controlling
every one of those crazies.
No way!
Nadesico, we need to
get you away from them.
Quickly!
Jo, don't shoot!
They're not in control of
themselves! You'll kill them!
They work for the demon girl.
I know. But still,
we have to help them!
You can make it,
just a little further.
Yoko! Get a grip!
It isn't reality.
Meg, the only choice
is to kill Nadesico.
Jo!
Looks like she's
finally lost control.
The cerebral mutation
has peaked at only 88%,
but her life signs are strong.
Then let's watch
and see how it ends.
It'd be a shame to abandon
one of our top students.
Here! Choke on this!
Wait. There's no head.
Don't tell me... Jo!
Jo!
It's me! It's Meg! Jo?
Thank you, Meg.
Why do you always have
to play the cowboy?
Don't scare me like that!
Did you shoot this?
Well, yeah! You were in danger.
Ta-da! What's up?
Thank you for everything.
You're too kind to me.
Oh hush. I just hope
you're feeling better.
You'll be out of here
before you know it.
Meg, are we... Are the two of
us still going to be friends?
Yeah, you bet we will!
Once you get out
of the hospital,
I'll take you some place where
we can eat some real food, okay?
Great.
Jo?
I... I just had to lie to her.
Sei said they shut down
that school for good, right?
Why did it happen?
Why do you think Nadesico
turned into that monster?
Some bad people took advantage
of her. It's sad, really.
What's that supposed
to mean, "Bad people"?
The weak who are consumed
by the demons inside themselves.
What? What are you,
a fortune cookie or somethin'?
Jo, wait up for me! Wait up!
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
An evil bird preys on the young.
Jo and the gang are confronted
by minions of the night
as they try to stop
these terrible attacks.
Next Burst Angel: Black Sky.