To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
So, like, then I said to him,
like, I just don't think
we should be, like,
going out any
more, you know.
And, he goes, like,
I bought you a lot of stuff
and took you out
like every night,
and then he starts crying!
If he only knew, like, I
hated the junk he bought me.
I threw it all away!
And then he's like asking,
why don't you like me anymore?
What's wrong with me?
Tell me! Tell me!
And, now he keeps calling me.
He's, like, left me like
a million messages!
Seriously, men are such
little babies these days.
If only they could see like
how totally pathetic they are.
Yeah. Like, no duh! You should
totally come with me next time!
It's like the
coolest dance club.
Guys are like always
buying me drinks and stuff.
Oh! Okay. Later!
Aw, it's too bad Ichimonji
couldn't come too.
Yeah. His dad is in town today,
so I guess he couldn't.
Maybe next time.
Oh, well, his loss!
Hey, check it out!
Whoa!
This looks good!
Oh! What is this?
Snake!
These are tasty, too!
Unbelievable, some people
will eat anything.
Uh-huh.
That was fun, though. The food
was great and I learned a lot!
I'm glad we came!
Really? I had fun too,
so I'm glad I invited you.
It is nice being around a
normal girl for a change.
You know, I was
actually kinda worried.
You've been missing a
bunch of classes lately
and half the time you're there,
you seem sorta spaced out.
I thought maybe something
was bothering you.
Well, yeah, kinda,
but it's nothing really.
Do you think it would help
if you talked about it?
As team leader, I'd be happy
to lend a friendly ear.
Because you're the team leader?
Is that the only reason?
If you screw up on
our next group project,
then everyone on the team
winds up with a bad grade.
Yeah, I see.
That is a good point.
But, seeing you back
at the food fest
made me feel a little better.
You really got into all the
different cuisine styles,
just like you used to,
when class first started.
Well, what did you expect?
You know, my goal
is to study abroad
and become a
world-renowned patissier.
Is this a shortcut?
What's the matter, Kyo?
You afraid of ghosts?
You have nothing to
worry about, I promise.
Oh, did you hear? They said
there's been a buncha sightings
of the giant
Crow-Man in Ikebukuro.
The... the Crow Man?
They say a crow
the size of a man
snatches girls
right off the street.
A bunch are already missing.
Don't tell me you buy into
those ridiculous urban myths.
No way.
This is getting creepy.
I-It's the Crow Man!
Come on! Let's get out of here!
Damn you!
Kyo, help me!
Kazami!
Kyo!
Seriously! You have to
believe me! It was huge!
It's out there!
You gotta... You...
But, I'm telling the truth!
Do we look like complete idiots?
You expect us to believe
a giant bird swooped down
and stole your
little girlfriend?
There are stories on the
net about the Crow Man.
But the only sites referring
to it are urban legend boards
and weird occult
sites. Nothing legit.
Then where's, Sei?
She would listen to my story
and not think I'm crazy.
Sorry Crow Boy,
you're outta luck there, too.
She's off prepping
for our next job
and she won't be
back anytime soon.
Hey Kyo, since
nobody's listening
to your stupid story anyway,
why don'tcha go in the kitchen
and whip us up some dinner?
This isn't the
time for that, Amy!
You said this was in Ikebukuro?
Lead the way, New Guy.
Jo, don't!
You're not really
going to go are you?
Come on, Jo!
Thank you, Jo.
Jo what are you doing?
Let's do it.
Yeah!
What's the matter, Meg? Jealous?
You afraid they're gonna
run off and get married?
If anything happens to
her it'll be all my fault.
We have to find her, Jo!
Shut up.
Don't shoot! It's just me!
Look who's here!
You're supposed to
watch the trailer.
Don't worry about it!
Besides, I want to check out
this giant Crow Man of his.
Come on, Jo,
don't be mad!
It's not like I get captured
all the time or anything!
O-Okay. Let's not get crazy
with the gun there, Jo.
Hold still!
What the--
Okay! I believe your story now!
Looks like it's
hunting for its dinner.
Don't shoot! We have to
find out where it took Kazami!
Don't think he's talkin'.
Jo, look out!
Get out of here, Meg!
I'm coming, Meg!
I can handle it!
Put me down! You'll be sorry!
Help me Jo!
Hate sayin' "I told you so!"
Yeah, what?
It's me. Listen, about that
bodyguard job we discussed...
Save it for later.
Meg's in trouble!
There's a huge mechanized crow
flying southeast from Ikebukuro.
Have Amy track
for a destination!
Okay, listen up!
This is how we're going
to handle the situation.
The client is
already in the air.
I'll have them land
somewhere in your vicinity.
The client has received
multiple death threats.
He is our top priority and
must be protected at all costs.
Forget that!
We have to help Meg!
Amy and I will
track Meg from here.
In the meantime, I need you
to handle the client.
We'll let you know as soon
as we get a fix on her.
Trust me, Jo; just do
as I say until then.
That was our agreement.
You tryin' to give me an order?!
I told you!
A crow the size of a small
truck just kidnapped Meg!
I've got my mission.
I know you're worried, Jo.
But Amy and I will find Meg.
Your only responsibility is the
protection of Bai-Lan's client.
Got it?
Rendezvous at the landing
point in Sector 3110.
We're heading that way as well.
What's a landing point?
Just come on!
Amy, what've you got?
Well, I've told her repeatedly
to keep her Nav-System
online at all times, but...
I'm not picking them
up on aerial scans.
The crow may have
landed somewhere.
Course, it's
entirely possible
she's not even wearing
her Nav-Sys today.
I knew I should've gone
with the sub-dermal implants
while they were sleeping.
One minute, twenty seconds late.
Just be glad I'm here
at all. You find Meg?
Amy's working on it right now.
Um, Sei.
Please, tell me
you can find them.
I'm sure Kazami's with her.
Not to worry. I'll mobilize
the entire Organization.
We'll scour all of Tokyo
and the surrounding areas.
I am certain they'll turn up.
The "Organization"?
So, you're the contact
from the Japanese Branch?
Yes. Technically, I'm Commander
of a detached strike force.
I understand you've acquired
one of the glowing brains.
If I hear right,
it's quite astounding.
Who's the kid?
It's the new guy.
He's with us. That a problem?
Sei!
Hurry! Inside the trailer!
Let's go! Move!
Back off! Don't get near it!
New Guy! Get him
the hell out of here!
Get down!
You okay?
This is what they're after.
This right here.
What is it?
Hey!
Your body will make just as
good a hiding place as any.
Hiding place for what?!
Stay down!
Come on, Jo! Shoot it!
Should've known.
Whoever's got Meg
are the same ones
who issued our
client's death threat.
Gotta admit it is
a good hiding place.
He said that too. What exactly
was I injected with, Sei?
An experimental nanobot virus.
Nanobot?
They call it the NI-50.
It's an array of
microscopic machines
that kill you from
the inside out.
Once injected,
it mutates your DNA
and within six hours,
you will be dead.
Six hours?!
That's what was in the
case the crow grabbed?
Sucks to be the New Guy.
Lemme get this straight.
That bird thing isn't just
kidnapping girls at random?
Not a chance. Someone is
definitely controlling it.
For now, we need to
get you into surgery.
With Bai-Lan's tech at our
disposal, it can be removed.
Tell me straight,
am I gonna make it?
Of course. But we'll need as
much of that time as possible.
It's coming back!
Did it forget something?
Hand over the NI-50 at once.
And, we will return your
friend to you unharmed.
There's Meg!
Hold on, that looks like--
Yes. It's the Tokyo Tower.
Jo, wait, what are you doing?
Come on, Jo. Don't do this.
What's going on?
Step away from
Kyohei right now, Jo.
We need to let Bai-Lan recover
the NI-50 from his system.
If we don't, then
he is going to die!
Yeah, well if we do, Meg dies.
I promise you,
we'll find another way
to get Meg out of there.
Now stop this foolishness.
Come on!
Damn it, Jo!
Don't force my hand!
You're gonna be my collateral,
so I can go fight that crow.
I don't give a damn
about anyone but Meg.
If you try to run,
I'll kill you.
Attention all Tokyo Units!
All points bulletin!
All units assist
in the apprehension of
an 18 year-old male.
Suspect is reported
to be traveling
with an 18 year-old female.
The female is to be considered
armed and extremely dangerous.
Use of lethal force in their
apprehension has been approved.
Less than six hours left
until the NI-50 takes over.
Jo, you stupid, stupid girl.
You can't do this on your own.
And now, you've made it
so I can't help you either.
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
Traps set all over the
late-night metropolis
attack with a snarl,
and Jo races against time!
Will Kyo and Meg survive?
Next Burst Angel:
The Wounded Fugitive.