To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
You can eat it, chief!
Now, pay up!
Shut your mouth! Like I'd ever
pay a cheating punk like you!
Drop the tough act, old man!
Take a swing at me! I beg you!
If I did, they wouldn't
be able to identify the body.
You talk big for a cheat!
How do you walk it?
I'll walk it right
over your grave!
Well I'm still standing
here, ain't I?
What the heck is going on?!
Eat this!
And all of the sudden,
it's like pow, pow, pow, pow!
Machine gun fire was everywhere.
I swear, I thought I was dead.
Yeah, well, ever since
they signed the law
that says anyone can
carry a weapon around,
things began crashing.
I hear the higher-powered
guns are selling the most.
You would think we would
start to be a little safer
with the new RAPT
headquarters in town.
The criminal apprehension
rate's gone up,
but the arrest rate's gone down.
Wait a minute. Apprehension
is up, but arrests are down?
How's that?
It means that the number
of crooks caught alive
has decreased,
all thanks to RAPT.
Hello, Kyouhei.
I heard word that you're
seeking new employment.
Yeah. That other place
wasn't challenging.
A job builds character,
but be sure not to neglect
your regular schoolwork.
Of course. I won't.
Hey, teach, what's that?
This? Oh, nothing. I get
a ton of spam email everyday.
Most are just pranks
from former students,
so I don't even know
if this is real.
"Desperately Wanted:
A wonderful man to make
fancy and delicious cuisine.
Great pay, superb
working conditions.
First come, first serve.
Give us a call ASAP."
Is this for real?
In a world of
violence and greed,
one man is given
a second chance.
--Released from New Alcatraz
--No! You can't!
after 10 long years, he faces
an even harsher reality:
--Broken bonds, betrayal,
--What have you done with her?
--and bitter rivalry.
--Stop this now.
Starring Hiroki
Machikata as Kibei.
With Shinichi Kiba,
and multiple award winning
actress, Yuka Salmon.
"Skyscraper Godfather Saga."
Coming soon to
theatres everywhere!
And now for the news.
Last night, a road crew
working on a raised highway
south of the city was attacked
by an unmarked work cybot.
Several materials were
taken from the work site,
and this isn't the first
time this has happened.
Since the beginning
of the month,
at least four such incidents
have been reported and verified.
Jurisdiction of this
matter has been taken
from the police by RAPT.
Kyouhei Tachibana
from the Love and Happy
Culinary Design School?
Uh, yeah, that's me.
You were saying
you wanted to save up
so you could study abroad?
Well, I'm studying
to be a patissier.
Oh, a patissier is a pastry
chef, makes cakes and things.
Patissier, huh?
I've never heard of that.
To be a great chef,
I really should study in France.
It's the only way to
get a foot in the door.
But they've got this huge tax
on studying overseas right now.
And I can't really ask
my parents for help, so...
That's admirable.
You may be young,
but you're smart enough
to have a goal.
I like that in a person.
Uh, thanks.
My specialty is pastries,
but I also know
Japanese, French, Chinese,
and Italian style dishes,
so I'm pretty
versatile in the kitchen.
I think this price tag
has an extra zero.
Yes.
Sei? Where are you?
Grocery shopping
with our new cook.
Just be patient.
We'll be back soon.
Give me that! Hurry it up!
My stomach is starting
to make strange noises.
Let's hurry.
'Kay.
Man, We bought so much stuff.
How many people am
I cooking for anyway?
You guys must live
in a huge mansion.
Something like that.
It's felt empty since
our previous cook left.
Had to go back to
his home country.
Here?
Hey, it's me. And I've
brought the new cook along.
I'll be right down.
It's about time! I take it
that's our new master chef?
It is.
Uh, hello.
And this is where
you'll be working.
Your job will simply be to cook
nutritious meals for all of us.
So, do you, like,
take this motor home
on picnics or something?
Uh, no. This is our home 24-7.
We all live here.
And by 'all' you mean
your families live here, too?
Left to their own devices,
these girls eat only junk food.
They need a cook like you
who can whip them up
something substantial.
That's Meg.
And this is Amy.
Turn around.
Turn around a hundred
and eighty degrees.
Okay. Like this?
Don't you think he's too young?
Can the attitude.
You wouldn't know it,
but he's an excellent cook,
attending a certified
culinary school.
Well, I don't know
about excellent.
He smells like cake!
Oh, yeah, I was
practicing earlier.
So, hey! Didn't you think
our little flier was cute?
Was that your work?
Yeah! I was kinda worried
about who would respond
to such a cool flyer,
but I guess you're all right.
And besides, it looks
like you could handle
a little pain now and again.
Don't get your hopes up.
He's got a pansy-looking face
and he's thin as a rail.
He won't last two weeks.
Girls, Kyouhei is
saving up to study abroad.
Wouldn't it be wonderful
if through this we could
help him achieve his dream?
He takes this job,
he can study four of 'em!
Achieve his dream! Funny stuff!
Geez, Sei, when did you
grow a sense of humor?
Just ignore them.
So how about it?
Would you like to
come work for us?
Yes, of course,
if you'll have me.
Wait a minute!
Doesn't Jo get a vote?
Jo?
Oh, is she here?
Yeah, she just got back.
Said something about
finishing that pro-bono job
she was talking about.
I bet she's somewhere
watching videos.
She always does
that after a job.
Aha!
Hold on a sec!
Look away.
Huh?
Don't you say anything
besides 'huh' or 'what'?
Sorry about that.
She may be rude,
but deep down
she actually cares
for others quite a bit.
Meg cares for others?
Man, Sei! Your jokes are
really on the money today.
Um, so you are all sisters?
No. We're just
very close roommates.
Jo, so this is the new cook.
What do you think of him?
'Cause I think he's a tool.
It's a guy.
Whatever. Like I care.
Okay then.
Mr. Kyouhei Tachibana,
we will be counting
on your services.
Oh, thanks.
Excuse me for a moment.
Excuse me, miss. But, did you--
What kinda line is that?
'Excuse me, miss!'
You better not be
trying to hit on her.
I was just talking!
It couldn't be.
[TEXT]
"Acquire Data Disc"
We've got a job.
Everyone get ready.
What? A job?
Oh! But I'm starved!
I haven't eaten all day!
Can it, Miss Selfish!
The world doesn't revolve
around your stomach!
When the job's over,
you can have
whatever it is you
want for dinner.
All right! Let's get
to work! W-O-R-K!
So, what should I do until then?
I apologize. But would you mind
going home until I call you?
It shouldn't be long.
Jo, we got a job.
Jo, stop it! You!
Get out of here, already!
Why don't you stop by
after school tomorrow?
Okay...
See you then.
What the heck are you
staring at? We said scram!
What just happened here?
Those girls have gotta
have some serious cash.
I wonder how they
know each other.
They're nice looking and
seem cool, but something's off.
What is this job that they--
Wait! What are--
What do you s'pose
the cook would think
if he knew what we do?
He'd probably run.
He had that gutless coward
look down to a science.
Jo, you ready?
Let's do it.
The job is simple. There's an
exchange between weapons dealers
in a warehouse down in Harumi.
One side is selling a disc.
That's our target.
What's on it?
Not sure. But Bai-Lan
wants us to get it.
Maybe the plan is to copy
it for mass production.
Don't turn around, but
you've got a car following you.
Uploading satellite images now.
Great, we've got a tail.
What do we do?
Nothing for the time being.
We don't want to cause a scene.
They can't do anything
out here anyway.
Just like our intel said.
The deal's going down right now.
Good. Proceed as planned.
Can I mow 'em all down?
Negative.
Don't make a big scene.
I want you to be discreet.
It's verified.
Same here.
Don't move.
Behind you, too.
I thought our
target was the disc.
Call it a perk.
You're Bai-Lan's gang.
We knew you broads would
come after the disc.
And we got another surprise.
We took your little
buddy as insurance
for just such an occasion.
Buddy? What are
you talking about?
Freakin' Sei let
her guard down.
No, she wouldn't.
What's he doing here?
Who is it?
That pansy-ass cook!
Now hand over the case,
or the kid's head
splatters and stains
both of your trendy,
teenybopper outfits.
Go ahead and shoot.
--Gladly.
--You'd like that. Wouldn't you?
He's got seconds here!
Make a decision!
I told you to shoot.
What just happened back there?
Doesn't matter! Just run!
What the heck is going on?!
Do not leave my side.
Right.
Meg, no!
Ow, hot!
Don't move!
Don't shoot me!
You'll have to escape
by yourself. Got it?
Thanks.
Meg!
Quit playing around
and get down from there!
I-I can't get loose!
Meg! Jo! Status report!
What's going on down there?
Where the hell did
that cybot come from?
What? You don't know either?
Well, he's not on our side.
It's got Meg. Bring out Jango!
Jo!
Wakey-wakey, Jango.
Jo's waiting for you.
This isn't over yet,
you son of a bitch!
That's the mark
I saw in Shinjuku!
You just entered
a whole new world.
Welcome to Hell!
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
After a mysterious cybot
appears during their mission
and abducts Meg, Kyouhei is
drafted into the rescue plan.
The next step: at Jo's side,
sneak into the lawless
district of Shibuya.
Next Burst Angel:
The Heartless Gunfighter.