To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
Time to get going.
We need to find some food.
Would you stop
looking at her...?
You know she's not an angel
because she doesn't have wings.
Besides, we don't even
know if she's dead or alive.
Let's go.
Come on, let's get
back to the bus.
What are you doing?
Shirley!
This is ridiculous!
Why do I have to save her?
She'll just be
another mouth to feed!
You know we can barely
take care of ourselves.
And what if she's dead?
I'm not touching a dead body!
Don't you remember what
Sis always tells us...?
Do not help anyone, unless
it's your friend... Sheesh.
Don't! You're gonna fall!
Are, are you okay?
Now hold still. I'm gonna
start pulling us up.
Shirley!
This'd be a whole lot
easier if you quit moving!
I'm sorry.
This card has expired.
You may purchase a new
card at our main office,
or insert exact change.
Oh great.
Stop you piece of junk! Damn!
Valued customer, we
appreciate your business,
but please refrain from
striking the machine.
Ah, cram it!
Get back here you little brat!
All right kid. Hand over
my bag... Right now.
Come on, nice and easy.
Catch!
Have a nice day, sir!
Damn it!
We're home.
Welcome back, you two.
I see you got the loot.
And did you two behave
yourselves today?
Well, anyways we were
at that old cafe.
If you jack with
the machine a little,
it overflows the coffee cup,
giving us just enough
time to make the grab.
Really... That's a nice trick...
You screwed up last time
when you were with me.
That's because you
slipped and fell
on a pile of
dog crap, remember?
Oh, yeah...
It was right in
the middle of that
plaza full of tourists, too.
They even took pictures of you.
That old British couple
had to help you up.
And then you cried.
Yeah, you looked so lame.
Okay, whatever.
Still doesn't make it my fault.
No...? Coulda fooled me.
It was a freak accident!
And you're the freak!
Too funny.
I've never seen a bag
locked up like this before.
There must be something valuable
inside. Like cash or jewels.
What is this?
I thought you said
there'd be jewels in here.
I never said that.
Whoa! Check it out!
Awesome... It's loaded too.
Maybe he... deals
guns for a living.
Yeah, I betcha that's it.
He did look kinda sketchy.
Huh.
It looks real banged up...
Hey, Shirley. Here.
You know with this gun,
we could take on bigger jobs.
Make a lot more money.
I don't know about that.
Sounds pretty dangerous.
I'm not down for that.
Only bad guys do robberies.
Fine...
Then what if we all agreed
to only rob bad people...?
That would make us good
robbers, on the side of justice.
Is something underneath there?
Yeah... Shirley.
It's nothing, Sis. There
must be... a draft in here.
Right...
You guys took in another
stray animal, didn't you...?
Why don't you ever listen to me?
Holy crap!
Okay... It's making
grunting noises...
Oh no...! It's a pig!
A gorilla! A rat!
I don't think rats grunt.
No means no.
Where did you find her?
Passed out in the river...
Floating underneath
the freeway bridge.
Listen... All of us were
abandoned by our parents,
so we have to help
each other out,
but this girl you picked
up isn't one of us.
She's an outsider.
We can barely take
care of ourselves.
What are we supposed
to do with her?
Shirley...
I told you, God and angels
don't exist in our world...
Although, sometimes
I really wish they did.
Hey you...!
You're the reason we're
having this discussion,
so you can at least
pretend to be interested!
Whoa! What's happening?
Who the...
What the hell is that?
Is it even human?
It's bad, whatever it is.
What should we do?
What do you mean we...?
You found her!
No! Shirley!
Shirley! Are-- Are you okay?
Damn you!
Sis! Toss me the gun!
I'm gonna teach
this thing a lesson!
Right, uh... Gun, uh...
Where is it?!
I-It's there...! On the floor!
No way!
That... book is... is
Shirley's... Give it back.
Thank you, thank you, daddy.
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
We love you so much.
Sam... You still have
the day off, right?
'Fraid not... I just got a call.
Peter can't make it in,
so I have to cover for him.
Oh... Too bad.
Of all the days
to get called in.
Isn't there someone
else that can do it?
All right. Here's our stop.
Hurry up, Shirley.
Damn it.
What are we supposed to do now?
I wish I knew.
We don't even have a roof to
stay under because of her.
Why'd you bring
her along anyway?
Don't blame me.
It was Shirley's idea.
Guess we didn't
have a choice then.
So, just who the hell are you?
I don't remember.
Oh! How convenient.
Hey, so that was really
cool watching you fight.
You had some really
awesome moves.
What was that?
Karate or kung fu?
Was I in a fight?
Come on... That just happened
like two hours ago!
I know!
You must have lost your memory
when your spaceship
crashed in the river.
I didn't see the wreckage,
so you must have
ejected from the ship.
And that thing that
attacked our bus must be
a cyborg assassin
sent by the government
to eliminate alien threats!
That sound about right?
Charlie. That's the same plot
for that TV show
Galaxy Untouchable.
Does that mean I'm
a Galaxy Untouchable?
Um, no!
Last night, a neighbor reported
hearing some strange noises
followed by the sounds
of kids screaming.
Apparently the kids are normal,
but the sound she
heard beforehand
was unlike any
she'd heard before.
This area is a popular spot
for young squatters to hang out.
Some of them even work
for the mafia to get by.
Was that done by a kid too?
Beats me...
Maybe they used a crane
to pull the roof back.
Kids using a crane
on their own...
Hell, I don't know,
it was just an idea...
I mean, I've seen some
pretty crazy stuff
in my time on the job...
Kids pulling crimes that'd
put any adult crook to shame.
Okay, so once Charlie and I
get the cash from the register,
you make your move, got it?
Are you even listening?
You'll need to hold
them off, all right?
If you can't do this simple
task, we won't let you join us.
Hold them off?
What she's saying is
if we get into trouble,
you'll have to do your awesome
kung fu thing on them.
Just like you did to
that chick yesterday.
Got it.
Listen up! Open the register
and hand over the cash!
We know what you guys are up to.
Every one of these movies
you're selling is bootlegged!
And we also know
that your dirty money
can't be reported
stolen to the police.
Listen little girl,
you don't know jack!
Your turn... rookie...
Go teach these crooks a
lesson on how to behave.
What the heck are
you doing? Get them!
Stop!
What happened back there?
I don't know.
Let's just get the
hell out of here!
We're all dead if they catch us!
Well, what do you know?
D'you think you could
get away from us?!
Oh no!
I'm really sorry.
Kill her!
Why youse...
So you're telling us one boy
and four girls did this?
And you said one of them had
long silver hair, correct?
You gotta believe me here,
that ain't no kid!
Don't you get it...? We're the
ones being victimized here!
Okay, we get it.
Only advice we can give is next
time some kids attack you,
try baking them some cookies,
or maybe tell them a story.
Lava... Were you able to
get a fix on her location?
Not yet, but if I can
get within range,
we'll be able to
sense one another...
There's no need to worry.
I'm not worried.
Now you can atone for your
failure of the final test.
You do make the
perfect candidate.
The pain you're feeling is
from the cellular fusion.
It'll be over soon.
This time... you're
not getting away.
I can't believe this!
We didn't even take
a single dollar,
but now for some reason
we're wanted criminals!
That's it, this is goodbye.
Just get outta here.
Shirley.
Oh, leave with her
for all I care.
Be reasonable, Sis...
You saw how she
handled those guys...
This city isn't getting
any safer for us.
We could use the protection.
Yeah, come on...!
She did help us out when
we were in trouble today...
Give her time. I'm sure
she'll be more useful.
You got a name?
I forgot.
Whatever.
I'll start by teaching you
the simple stuff first.
Not right now.
Huh?
She's back.
This is Unit 55. Go ahead.
All available units.
Gunshots reported in Block C.
East side. Respond immediately.
That's Chinatown! Step on it!
I will not lose this time.
I will destroy you!
This is it! Stop the car!
What's going on up there, Sis?
I hope she can handle herself...
Maybe I could...
Charlie! Dorothy!
You guys get out of here.
Don't let Shirley get hurt!
What about you?
Aren't you coming?
I'm gonna give our new
friend some back-up.
All right... Now just calm
down and try this again...
What's going on up there?
Look out!
Charlie! Shirley!
Wait a minute,
you're that criminal!
Criminal...?
I'm a cop you idiot!
Now, what did you kids
do with my sidearm?
Our "Big Sis" has it.
She's upstairs fighting the
monster with our friend.
What friend's that?
Galaxy Untouchable!
I'm gonna bash in your skull
and tear out your
brains with my teeth!
You ugly freakshow...
Get off of my friend!
I guess Number Two
survived after all.
I wonder where Sis
and that girl went to.
All I know is, with
all that's happened,
these last two days are nothing
but a big blur in my head.
Yeah...
I think you're
right little girl.
Do you like that doll?
You guys hungry?
What do you say I treat you to
some hamburgers and milkshakes?
Why aren't you going with them?
Huh?
Oh, I don't know...
I just figure...
...they're better off
with him than with me.
They deserve better than
what I can give them.
Besides, I've found
myself a new partner.
A partner?
That's right. I took care
of you so you owe me one.
More importantly,
I think we work well
together, don't you agree?
Oh yeah... I guess
I never got around
to telling you my name...
It's Meg. How about you?
Oh, sorry, I forgot.
You lost your memory.
No, I remember.
It's Jo.
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
When our heroes are
invited to a new waterpark,
they're expectin'
a day of relaxation.
But naturally, danger
rears its ugly head.
Is it Mother Nature, or
something more sinister?
Next Burst Angel: Slingin' Oil!