To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
You sure are hard
on this thing, Jo.
It's creaking like
rusty old bucket.
Well, it's still in one piece--
No thanks to you.
Aw, I hurt your baby!
Change its diaper,
it'll be fine!
No, it will not be fine!
I swear, Sei. Every time
those two get together
it always ends up
in an argument.
Well, Leo built Jango,
and Jo likes to play rough...
Can't be helped.
At any rate, I can't do
nothin' 'bout it here.
I'll have to take
it to my shop...
You know... major re-fit.
So, how long will it take?
That depends,
how fast do you want it?
You've got three days...
You never know when we
might see some action.
Special attention like
that will cost you extra.
Don't worry ladies, I'll have
him back to you in no time!
Great, I'll have to ask for more
money from my grandfather.
Cool, we're off
for three days!
Hey Jo...?
You want to go hang out at that
amusement park up the street?
What kind of enemies
are there to shoot at?
Could you stop thinking
about work for five minutes?
I'm talking about
having some fun!
I'll pass.
I can't believe you'd
pick bounty hunting
over roller coasters!
What is this...?
Oh, now that's just
downright disgusting...
I don't know who
you think you are...
but no one messes with Amy!
What do you need at
the Cyber-Market?
Um... I need to get some new
components for my computer.
Why don't you just order them
online and have them delivered?
That's no good...!
I have to be there to
check them out first hand!
Last time you tried that excuse,
you blew a small fortune
on a bunch of useless crap.
You're a classic example
of impulse buying.
I can't let you do
any more shopping until
you learn some self-restraint
and financial responsibility.
But, that's not fair...!
I promise I'll think
before I buy today!
Aw, just give it a rest, Amy--
It's rare we get Sei
in such a good mood...
So chill out, huh?
Hey wait a minute...
You're all dressed up!
Cool, let's go.
What is going on here?
What? I can't just sit
around here all day long,
I'll go all mush-brain!
You and Jo can
hold down the fort.
That's not fair!
Why do you guys always
get to do the fun stuff?!
Um, because...
Sei and I are grown ups and
you are still a little kid.
The city's dangerous, Amy!
So no sneaking out on your own!
Thanks for nothin'.
Even if I did wanna leave,
I don't have any money to spend!
So, you'll be in
Osaka next week?
Yeah, I wanted to
talk it over with Sei
before I left, but she's gone.
Ahh, I wouldn't bother
if I were you...
She's out blowing a small
fortune impulse shopping
for useless junk...
No self-restraint or
financial responsibility.
You need to find a
good, cheap market
to stock up before you
skip town... I'm your girl!
Sounds perfect! I'd greatly
appreciate it, young lady.
No need to sound so formal...
Jeez, and I was just starting
to think you were cool!
Um... What is this place?
Doesn't look like there's
much food around here.
Sure there is...!
Just trust me okay?
There's so much good stuff
at these resale shops.
Here, it's the latest
Security Interface module.
I've been holding on to it
for you in case you came by.
Well, I guess I should
take it and try it out.
Now, how about the
stuff you promised me?
Maybe next time!
Whoa, dude! I want to buy
that rig you're wearing.
Go on! Beat it, you punk!
Hey, check out what I got...
Look familiar?
It's the one they never
released in stores.
Enter a world of
dragons and danger.
Of fantasy and illusion.
The Destiny Brothers
take on 101 dragons in
Dragon Bomber Brothers!
Yeah, maybe when I'm
having trouble sleeping.
Well, maybe you'd
be interested in
the latest of the Alien Ninja
Detective Fighters series?
Time to leave your
mom's basement, dude.
Nobody plays that
kinda junk anymore.
Been puking a whole lot
cuz of the chemicals lately.
Sounds like you're trying
to run a chem.-based medium
through a non-bio
system--not gonna work.
What you need to do is
convert your non-bio system
with organic uptake servos
and see if that helps.
Yeah, maybe...
I think that would work!
Amy, you're brilliant!
What on Earth are
they talking about?
It's weird, you sure do know
a lot of people around here.
Yeah, I've been hanging
around here since I was little.
"Was little?"
As if it's past tense?
How are you folks today?
Just two of you?
Yep...
And, we need your biggest
Modem-Bot, please.
It'll cost you a little
extra. Is that okay?
No prob...! Kyo--money!
Why do I hafta pay?
I'll get Sei to pay you
back when we get home...
C'mon, cough it up already.
I really hate using
my credit card
at these back-alley
kinda places.
Welcome, Amy and Kyo.
Follow me please.
Connection verified. Please
enter your destination.
What's up?
C'mere a sec! Help me move this!
Move it where?
Heavy!
And... stop...!
Put it down right there.
Should you be doing that?
Don't worry, I won't get caught.
Time to let my fingers
work their magic.
This computer is super-powerful
but totally easy
to hack in to...
I'll enter a coded
algorithm loop that will
take down their firewall,
access their mainframe
and trace their signal.
Firewall...?
This doesn't sound--
Yes!
That's you... This is what
you do with your free time?
Now, why would I do something
like that, you idiot...!
Someone out there
is jacking with me!
Well that can't be legal!
We need to report this to RAPT!
And what would that accomplish?
What the hell?
Hello...? Hello?
Oh, What have you done now?
Shut up! It wasn't me!
I got caught!
By who?
I have no idea. Someone
was monitoring my upload...
We have to get out of here!
What are you trying to pull?!
We were right in the
middle of a business deal!
I demand you refund our money!
I have no idea what's going on!
We're experiencing
technical difficulties.
Aw, yeah. Finally...
A demo reel that's
gonna make me a star...
Tomorrow I'll get it to a
producer and the legend begins!
Hey! Wait up!
Wait a minute! My legend!
Where are you going?
Stop!
Ohh, lucky!
No! No, don't do that.
Come back. My legend!
Isn't that the girl?
Yeah, that's her!
Let's go!
No pictures, you jerkwad!
Where you goin'?!
You all right, Amy?
Ohhh, now you've done it.
It was almost funny at first,
but then you went
and made me angry...
You hear me? I'm coming for you!
You don't have to come
if you don't want.
I can't leave you alone in
a dangerous place like this.
We're not quite open yet.
Who's there?
It's me, Amy. C'mon open up!
Oh, Amy, how are you, darling?
Good and you?
Right as rain, dear...
So, who's this
young whippersnapper
you have with you, a boyfriend?
You kidding...?
He's my personal chef.
A personal chef-- how marvelous!
What am I doing here?
It was so weird earlier...
Your face was on
every sign in the city.
I know, that's
why I came to you.
I need you to help
me catch the guy
who's transmitting the signal.
I see...
Well you know I'd love
to help you, darling.
But that would put me
in a very tight spot!
Although...
There is some data
you could send my way...
Again?
C'mon, Amy...!
What'd you go through
all my stuff for?
I needed that Security
Interface Module I got earlier.
Oooh, you look
good enough to eat!
Oh my stars, that's
the tastiest thing
I've put in my mouth... ever!
So, um... Who is that guy?
He's like an underground
tour conductor...
For a price, he has
ways of getting people
wherever they want to go.
Sooo... Any place
special you wanna go?
I'm in! I got you now!
Marvelous!
It's Amy's turn!
This is where all of
the tours begin...
Each door leads to a distinctly
unique underworld environment.
Okay, so which one
of them do we go in?
This one.
The place has been
abandoned for some time now
but I just recently monitored
some renewed activity.
Your data was streaming
from beyond that light...
I'm guessing their
processor is over there.
Oh, and here, take this.
What is it?
A data gun that's loaded
with compressed viruses.
A little "thank you"
for bringing that
adorable boy with you.
Thanks.
Good luck! You're gonna need it!
You know, maybe we should
just head home now.
Chickening out already...?
Whatever happened to
protecting me with your life?
I never said that!
You're pathetic, you know that?!
It's like we're
inside a computer.
Hate it when there's
no real dataflow...
I guess we can never
totally get rid of all this
Stone Age pre-quake tech.
What is that?
A spy-bot! They've been
watching us the whole time!
Oh, no you don't!
We've been waiting
for you, Amy dear.
Welcome! Welcome, to our world!
Yes, welcome dearest
Amy... (Yeah.)
Who are you guys?
How do you know who I am?
Where am I?
You're inside the main processor
that controls our
virtual planet.
Yes... And now you have
been digitized as well!
And, you guys would be who now?
We are the caretakers
of this world.
What's up with the monitors
you have on your faces?
We've undergone
cyborg transplants
to better commune
with the network.
Our consciousnesses have
been joined together
via a virtual Hyper-LAN. (Yeah.)
We anxiously await the time when
the rest of the world
catches up to us. (Yeah.)
One day soon we
will reconnect with
your world and reveal
ourselves to everyone.
Of all people, you, Amy,
are the most qualified
to evolve with us!
Evolve?
You got it!
That is so pathetic!
You're all nuts...!
Going through life
trapped in a machine.
In this state we have
no need for food, water,
or even restrooms.
We can simulate any sensation
via our electronic sensors.
Your simple, organic body
will someday weaken and die.
Come with us, Amy! (Yeah.)
Stop it!
You can't possibly
enjoy life inside those
cold metallic shells.
What-what did you do to him?
Organic brains are
very inefficient
processors of information.
He's so data-heavy
he's experiencing lag.
Hey! What are you
guys doing to Amy?
Darn you!
Oh! Huh-huh...
We should delete this
meatsack's memories
and speech functions,
then send him back outside!
Okay...
Maybe it would be cool to
evolve with you four studs.
This lame body will only last
a hundred years or so anyway...
I could live forever,
and I'd love to see how
cyber-tech progresses.
Right! Right!
You're exactly right!
Oh, wait...!
I have a super-cool gift
I want to give you guys...
It's in my bag,
back in the real world.
Any chance you can
drop us off there?
It's a dump for old electronics.
Correct! Most impressive, Amy!
All right, Kyo,
give me the bag now.
Amy, you can't be
serious about this.
Just shut up and
gimme, Cube-Head!
Okay, take it easy!
Where is it? That's not it.
It's in here somewhere...
Found it!
That's-that's Dragon
Bomber Brothers!
They never even
released it in stores!
We searched every file-share
but could never find it.
It's incredible! Where on earth
did you find it? (Yeah?)
Oh, I just picked up from
an old friend of mine.
It's sweet. You guys should
really check it out.
Load it up! (Yeah.)
It's amazing!
Utterly unbelieveable!
Hurry up!
Let me try, let me try!
Stop hoggin' it!
What happened?
Did you lose already?
Come on, we want to try it, too!
Today, I'll be
preparing roast chicken
with mashed potatoes
and green beans.
What's wrong?
Something's
definitely messed up!
Oh, no! Fatal error!
Complete system crash!
Don't tell me there
was a virus in there...
It's a virus all right!
Prepare to go off line you
sniveling data-faced dorks...!
Now I'll crash your
hard drives for good
with this little number courtesy
of the unevolved world.
Amy, you can't be serious!
You're acting like a total human
and it's making me very upset!
I don't care what you
overgrown toasters think!
Me neither!
Come on, let's go...!
You guys want a
piece of me, huh!
Amy, how could you?
You have betrayed
our emotion chips.
After this, we'll never be
able to trust you again.
Just get out of here!
Get out! Get out!
H-Hey...!
Th-That's dangerous...!
Watch it...! Idiots!
Holy crap...!
We gotta get out of
here right now, Amy.
I can't!
I-- I can't move my legs, Kyo.
I'm... I'm scared!
Hey, wait! What are
you doing?! Stop!
Kyo, stop!
I thought I said
no sneaking out...
I was worried.
Sei has been waiting
here all night.
Were you trying to
kidnap her Kyohei?
No, way! What are
you talking about?!
I couldn't help it that
she got into trouble.
It's okay, I'm just glad
you're both all right.
C'mon... Let's go
back inside, now.
What's wrong? Are you
feeling sick or something?
Amy?
Amy...
Hey.
What's wrong, hon?
All right, what happened?
I know this is all your fault.
What'd you do?
Who? Me? Nothing.
There was this weird computer
world that she took us to
and these guys with
TV's on their head and--
What the hell are
you talking about?
I'm telling the truth! Really!
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
The city of Osaka is
overrun by terrorists.
And as Jo investigates
another monster outbreak,
she runs afoul of
the local constabulary!
Next Burst Angel: "Eastern
Angel, Western Hawk."