To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
Wakey-wakey Jango!
Jo's waiting for you!
Traffic routing online, check!
You just entered
a whole new world.
Welcome to Hell!
Jo!
Jango, stop!
Meg! You okay?
Jo, remember your
primary objective.
You must get that disc.
Screw you.
Saving Meg comes first.
Move, kid. You're in the way!
Jo, are you alright?
Alright, Jo!
Let me out of here,
you stupid cybot!
Oh, no you don't!
Amy. Eye-in-the-sky!
Where the hell did he go?
I can't find him. I'm hitting
a level 5 magnetic field.
Sei, do you read me?
This is Meg.
Anyone?
Come on, fess up!
What group are you spying for?
And where did they take Meg?
I swear I'm not a spy!
I'm just a student.
Don't play dumb with me.
No gunfire inside here.
You promised me.
I don't remember that.
It seems to me the boy
is telling the truth.
The way I see it,
he's an innocent victim
that was caught up in
our work, not some spook.
Who the hell are
you people anyway?
A secret RAPT squad?
Female Yakuza commandos?
You are, aren't you?
So, Jo...
Whatever the case,
we need to identify the
cybot that stole the disc.
And track down the owner.
It's an extra request
from Bai-Lan.
Hey, guys! We just got
a transmission from Meg.
She couldn't talk so she emailed
us some images of her location.
Have you had any luck
finding out where that is?
No, nothing solid.
So that leads me to believe
she's in an area with
no transmission relays.
These pics should be
in chronological order.
Looks like they took
the downtown loop,
then down
Roppongi Boulevard.
Hell of a drive.
Where was that cybot heading?
This is the last one
that came out clear.
What is that thing?
Get ready.
You're coming with me.
But wait. I'm the
helpless victim here.
Besides, it's late
and I need to go home.
I-I have a big
assignment tomorrow.
Listen up.
Meg was taken hostage
because she tried to
save your sorry ass.
A real man would
return the favor.
I'm a real man.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Why aren't we taking a car?
Where we're going you
can't get to by car.
Mmm...
What?
I'm impressed you got
a permit to carry a gun.
I heard there is a really
tough background check
before you can get one.
So what's in the bag?
It sure is heavy.
Say one more word
and I'll kill you.
In case you didn't notice,
I'm in a bad mood.
No way! Is this--
Shibuya? The Anarchy District?
Let's go.
Hold on!
This place is a No-Man's-Land.
The government abandoned
the entire district
after the big quake.
If we get into some
kind of trouble,
the police won't be
able to help us.
We could be killed
if we go in there.
Any more whining
out of your mouth
and I string you up
next to that mannequin.
We're very close to Meg.
I don't know about this.
Everyone looks so rough
and they all have guns.
He looked at me.
Oh no, I made eye contact.
Look. Fresh meat.
I see you got some luggage
with you. What's inside the bag?
Why don't you leave that
for us and head home.
Then we won't have
to carve you up.
Your face is alright,
but you ain't got no titties!
You've gotta have at
least this much up top
or ya ain't gonna
get no customers.
Funny girl here looks
like she wants to fight.
You're gonna take
me to your boss.
It's been a long time, Jo.
I swear I was gonna come visit,
but you know how it is.
I wanted to thank you for
taking out that psycho for me.
Sure makes this place
a lot easier to control.
Psycho?
Take a look in the mirror.
Forget the reward money.
I'm here for information.
Oh, yeah? Nothing
goes on around here
without me knowing
about it, honey.
So, what would you like to know?
I'm looking for
a giant cybot
that's using your turf
as a hiding place.
Not like the RAPT ones.
Probably military.
That sounds like a
dangerous piece of machinery.
And I don't wanna brag,
but our mics can pick up even
the fanciest new-tech cybots.
'Specially them military ones.
Their engines got a
very unique sound.
Right boys?
It's unwritten code here
to never stick our
heads in too deep.
So with that said,
we don't know nothing
about the cybot
you're looking for.
We ain't heard nothing either.
Sorry we can't help.
If you're lying to me,
I'll come back here and
personally cut your throat.
That girl's got
some serious balls.
She's fearless. Who is she?
Yeah, she a relative
of yours, or something?
She's whatcha call
an angel of death.
I could still take her.
She's all bone.
She got the wings of the
Devil himself on her back.
Anyone who sees 'em... gets a
one-way ticket straight to Hell.
You wait here.
What?! All by myself?
If you run, I'll have
Amy track you down.
You can hide in Peru,
or the Himalayas for all I care.
Either way, I'll find
you and kill you.
Okay.
How dare you tie up a young girl
like this against her will?
I swear, if I get one bruise,
you're gonna pay.
That's the disc
we were sent for.
Ooh, pretty colors!
My phone!
Okay, I finally got the data.
And it was a pain to track down,
so I hope you appreciate it.
Good work, Amy.
So what is this place?
An underground highway
that was being constructed
with plans to connect
to the Downtown Loop.
But then the big quake hit
and construction was halted.
Later the project was
abandoned all together.
We also got some
intel on the enemy.
The cybot you're dealing
with was secretly developed
by RAPT for deployment
sometime later this year.
RAPT, huh?
It's still in design stages.
Seems a third party
got ahold of the plans
and built one ahead of
schedule with stolen parts.
This related to the
groups trading the disc?
Negative. We have
reason to believe
the cybot was attempting to
retrieve a spare part it needed.
We're checking the contents
of the disc right now.
Or you can save us the headache:
find the guy and
ask him yourself.
Your jokes aren't funny.
You don't mean that.
It's no use.
Don't tell me that green blob
was the cybot's brain!
Almost there.
Wha-- No, wait! Stop moving!
I found Meg!
It was only for a split second,
but I picked up her GPS signal.
Where?
Um... A side tunnel about
500 meters ahead of you.
Your ad promised
you could connect
from anywhere you stupid phone!
This does not look good.
Jo!
Take cover, Meg!
Wouldn't it make more sense
to fight a cybot
with another cybot?
Amy! You heard the lady!
Jango's on his way!
What's taking them so long?
I wonder why she wanted
to bring canned food along.
Maybe she was hoping to take
a lunch break or something.
What's that?
Run, you idiot!
What about the food?
Here it is, boys. Hell on Earth.
We have an explosion
in the Shibuya District.
Alpha platoon
deploy immediately.
Heavy resistance expected.
That's not your everyday
run-of-the-mill cybot.
It has a brain in it.
I saw it glowing earlier.
Really?
But it's got the
mentality of a T-rex.
Great! You made it angry.
This sucks!
Don't stop! Keep going!
Jango!
Here's where the fun starts!
Jango's loaded with
super armor-piercing ammo,
so blast away!
I found out what's on the disc.
It's a dump of the
newest combat protocols
used in the conflict
in West Africa last year.
They want to max out
this cybot's abilities,
so they busted up the deal
and stole the disc.
So don't expect this thing
to act like it did
at the warehouse.
This cybot has a whole
new operating system.
Yeah, it's a whole
different beast all right.
Jo, when you're done...
Recover as many of its
parts as possible.
Another request from Bai-Lan.
Oh, that'll be real easy.
I got your spare
parts right here.
Oh yeah! You rock, Jo!
Great, looks like
the fuzz finally arrived.
Don't move!
This is the RAPT Mobile Unit.
Stand down and
follow our instructions.
We're saved! Now I can
go home! Over here!
No, wait!
Stay right there! Now lie
down on the ground slowly.
What the--?
We're in Hell.
Told ya.
This is Mobile Unit
number 7 reporting in.
We're currently investigating
the source of the explosion
in Shibuya District, H Block.
Blast radius approximately
70 meters of total destruction.
We have confirmed
existence of an armed group
we believe is connected
to the incident,
but are unable to identify.
Retrieval of the cybot
is a negative;
looks like it self-destructed.
Unfortunately, one male and
one female, both unidentified
but believed to be
with the armed group,
were able to escape
in the commotion.
That's it?
Best I could do.
So we spend time,
money, and ammunition;
we don't get the
enemy's identity
and this pile of junk
is all you brought back?
Grandfather is so not going
to be happy about this.
It wasn't a total wash,
I can identify the parts
once I run a trace on this!
Ooh! What've we here?
"I'm sorry I caused you
guys so much trouble.
To make up for it, I made
you dinner before I left.
Enjoy and goodbye."
Crazy. Maybe he's not
such a bad guy after all.
Meg, try this! Oh, yummy-yummy!
She's right. Did he really
make this all by himself?
I guess the kid
does have talent.
I want to eat like
this everyday!
I'm sure we can
convince him to come back.
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
What happened to this man?
Who set him up?
Through a concrete jungle
born of dark intrigue,
Jo's anger will reach
its boiling point.
Next Burst Angel: "The City
Where The Beast Howls."