To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
Why are you doing this?
Please just leave me alone!
Jackass shoulda
stayed outta our way!
Attention motorcyclists:
It has been determined you are
in violation of RAPT Traffic
Regulations, Articles 5 and 8.
You are hereby advised
to stop immediately
and surrender yourselves
to the authorities.
Like that'll happen.
This is your final warning.
Any further violations will
result in summary execution.
You have 20 seconds to comply.
Whatta you gonna do about it?
Just try and stop us.
Judgement issued: All verbal
warnings have been ignored.
Initiating Summary
Execution mode.
What the frig?
He's fast.
Execute.
This can't be real!
What--What kind of cop are you?!
Someone help!
Suspect has ignored
all verbal warnings
and has interfered with
official RAPT duties.
Suspect forfeit's his
right to an attorney
and an official hearing.
Judgement:
Execution.
Execution complete. Removing
Mega-Highway lockdown.
In regards to our
recent field tests
of the new mega-highway patrol
vehicle, we have been met with
overwhelming gratitude
from Tokyo's residents.
With this new project, RAPT
continues its devotion
to the people of this city
in our continuing effort
to maintain order and improve
the quality of life in Tokyo.
It's so weird looking,
like a praying mantis.
Kinda...! But the specs are
more amazing than that, Meg.
Its high-speed
combat configuration
is just as good as
Jango's, if not better.
We currently have one
prototype deployed...
If mass-produced,
emergency dispatches would be
available across the city
twenty-four hours a day.
That would be ideal.
As the population grows so
does the number of vermin.
From now on people won't
choose their cities...
The cities will
choose their people.
Thanks again for the ride,
I owe you one...
I reckon it's about time I got
back home to Osaka, anyway.
It's quite a surprise,
seeing you...
I never thought I'd run
into you here in Tokyo.
Talk about surprises.
You're the one who's
married now, Mika.
We all gotta settle
down sooner or later...
Isn't that right, Tatsuya?
That's right.
Best watch out for those
lovers' quarrels...
Mika gets mad enough,
she'll shove a knitting
needle up your nose!
She'll do what?!
Now that's mean, Boss.
Aahhh! I'm sorry,
me and my big mouth!
You know I didn't mean it!
[TEXT]
"TRAFFIC VIOLATIONS"
"RECKLESS DRIVING"
You stupid pigs don't scare me!
You are interfering with
RAPT business and have
ignored all verbal warnings
to cease and desist...
You will now be removed
from the premises by force.
Disperse!
Damn you, bastards!
What the hell is that...?
All right Tatsuya,
just drive casual...
We don't want any
trouble from that thing!
I see it.
Oh man... This can't be good.
All right you two...
Listen up...
You're gonna have to jump!
C'mon, Boss! Jump!
You picked the wrong girl
on the wrong day, pal!
Boss! Are you all right?
Oh, that is it...!
You are not gonna
get away with this.
You heard me!
Send out your boss... now!
Miss, I'm gonna have to ask
you to calm down, please.
Don't you tell me what to do.
One of your stupid cruisers
busted the crap out
of my friend's van!
So turn around and go
get your head honcho!
Model One has gone haywire?
Possibly.
The girl claims she was suddenly
attacked without provocation.
I can't be bothered
with this now.
Just get rid of her.
Yes but... If what
she's saying is correct,
then that would mean the
prototype was operating
beyond our programming
specifications.
Are you questioning me?
You do know...
the amount of research, talent,
and funding that have been
invested in the development
of the Road Radar project.
Of course, sir.
The Third Neuron portion
of the onboard AI program
was developed by the
world's top scientists
in complete secrecy...
And the result is
something amazing...
quite possibly the
ultimate evolution
in scientific progress...
That is why I have
poured my heart and soul
into this project.
We all feel the same way, sir!
Sacrifices are an inherent
part of the scientific method.
They are to be expected...
If we fret over every one,
our dreams of a perfect future
will remain but dreams.
I'll say it again...
There's nothing wrong
with Model One...
Now get that troublesome girl
out of here immediately.
I ain't leavin'
till he comes out.
I see how it is...
Shoulda known you'd
resort to this.
All right-y then.
We do it the fun way!
I'm gonna show you Tokyo trash
how we do things out West...!
This means war!
Sorry, I have to take this...
Whaddya want? I'm in the
middle of somethin' here!
Uh... What did you say...?
Behind me?
Why'd you stop me?
Things were just getting' good!
Hate to break it to you,
but you were way outnumbered.
I coulda handled it...
I been itchin' to pound on some
of them crooked Tokyo cops...!
Besides... I ain't the kinda
girl to back down from a fight.
It's my sworn duty to protect
and serve the people.
So there's no chance of you
returning quietly to Osaka.
Why would I do that?
If you decide to
take on RAPT now,
it will make our jobs
a lot more difficult.
See? That's the problem
with you Tokyo people.
That's right. You're in
Tokyo now, not Osaka.
There's an invisible power
struggle going on here...
Nothing is as it seems.
Yeah, whatever...
But... I have been hankerin'
for some good takoyaki.
I knew you'd see things my way.
I have your ticket right here.
What would you have done
if I refused to go?
I would have found you a
nice seat in a freezer truck.
Ouch.
There's no mistake?
No sir... I just received
confirmation...
Model One's program data
is being hacked into.
What've they gotten?
Over fifty percent so far.
It appears our
Information Control Center's
encryption has been compromised.
Has the hacker been identified?
We're hitting a
snag there, sir...
They seem to be on the move.
Switching relay stations before
we can get a trace on them...
Definitely not the
work of an amateur.
Ah... If this is
a professional job,
we may be dealing with
some new terrorist threat.
Shall I inform the
Governor-General, sir?
No, not yet...
This is not the time.
Put Model One on
the dock and shut down
the control center link before
any more damage is done.
We are currently making
preparations for
mass production at a number
of private factories.
Please assure
Governor-General Ishihara that
Models Two and Three will roll
out on schedule, as promised...
In addition, Model
One will be undergoing
several readjustments
before we move on to Stage 2.
Readjustments...?
Has Model One been exhibiting
complications with
its programming?
Not at all... We're simply
installing a device to record
the unit's combat activities
so we may continue to upgrade
the Models capabilities.
[TEXT]
"Slippery When Wet"
The buildings here look
like giant tombstones...
Shoot, in this city even
the sun looks kinda sad.
You picked the wrong girl
on the wrong day, pal!
Come again?
Model One is ignoring
our commands,
and is currently traveling
on the Mega-Highway, sir.
Is this the work of
that damn hacker?
We don't know, sir.
Where is Model One heading?
We don't know that either, sir.
It's not responding
to our communications.
Send a chopper out to
find it immediately...
And until this is resolved,
I want all access to the
Mega-Highway shut down.
What...? Are you
absolutely certain?
Yes sir, I'm afraid so...
Both models suddenly
awoke from standby-mode,
destroyed their hangar
doors and escaped.
They uh, they appear to be
heading for the Mega-Highway...
Sir...? Sir?!
Model One...
It's controlling them.
Hey...! That's where
it happened...!
That's where that no-good RAPT
bastard attacked us earlier.
How exactly did it attack you?
I can't say for sure, but all of
a sudden it came outta nowhere
and latched onto
the back of the van...
Then... Right as I turned
around to get a look...
Aw, crap! It's back!
What?! Are you serious?!
Yeah, and it looks like
it's comin' after us!
No way! We didn't
do anything wrong.
I know, that's what I'm sayin'!
The thing's a
no-good RAPT bastard!
Y'know... It could be
that thing likes you.
That's the worst
thing I've ever heard!
Attention tractor trailer: A
suspect wanted for interference
of RAPT duties has been
detected aboard your vehicle.
Stop the vehicle immediately and
await further instructions...
Failure to comply or
attempts at resistance
will be viewed as aiding and
harboring a known fugitive,
and will be met with
the use of force.
This doesn't look promising.
Here it comes.
Eat lead!
Impossible...
Model Two is performing in
ways it shouldn't be able to
without completing its
battle simulation program.
We believe that Model Two is
under the guidance of Model One.
Damn it... What the hell
has happened to Model One?
Oh, crap!
Sei, don't slow down.
Why not?!
Take that hard turn
at this speed...
And when I give the word,
lower the rear hatch!
Got it!
Do it now!
I knew it. That patrol car
was no ordinary cybot.
A glowing brain.
What is it?
Stupid thing had one of those
glowing brains driving it.
Well that explains it...!
Must've been some kind of
psychopath behind the wheel!
No, I just told you!
It was a sentient,
pre-programmed bio-device!
Eh... Sorry, you lost me...
But what I still don't get
is why it attacked us.
Y'know, Takane might
have been partly right.
What if they built it using
the brain of some psychopath?
That would definitely explain
why its Thought Control
systems went haywire.
It sort of reminds me of
Frankenstein's monster.
I'd like to gather more data
before we make any
major decisions,
but I think we should get
off the highway first.
Might not be an option!
Looks like they wanna
play another round of tag.
So you've determined Model One's
target is this trailer truck?
According to our files it's
an unregistered vehicle...
And I'm just guessing here,
but it might be related
to the hackers somehow.
If that's so... then perhaps...
Model One assessed the vehicle
as some sort of a threat...
and acted on its own volition to
bring the drivers to justice.
I see...
Model One's objective
is to remove any and all
suspicious vehicles...
In order to do that
it needed to enlist the help
of Models Two and Three.
Indeed... Model One is not
out of control after all...
It simply called for backup.
Execute.
Amy, where's an exit?
Right side. 200 meters ahead.
Hang on tight!
Oh, my head.
I get the distinct feeling
they don't want us to leave.
They're tryin' to
shut us up for good!
Amy, can you disable the
locks on the exit gate?
I think I can, but...
it might take a while.
That's what you call a while?
Way to go, Amy.
But I didn't do anything yet.
Aw, man...
Just how many are there?
I'm making a break for it.
This is Sky Fish
Four-Zero-Four...
Model One is currently in
pursuit of an unknown cybot...
Now entering the
Red-Blue Bridge.
No good.
I can't move...
Damn thing's got us.
Jo, save yourself!
Get out of here!
No, Sei... I won't...
I won't run...
But, Jo...
C'mon... Gun it!
Hang on, Sei! What the
hell are you doing?!
Are you trying to kill us?
Jo... You can do this--
I trust you!
Execute. Execute. Execute...
Four-Zero-Four reporting...
Models One and Three
have been destroyed...
The unknown cybot and trailer
are headed for the coast...
Repeat... Models One and three
have been destroyed...
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
When the city glows
red in the evening sun,
the Angels, stripped
of their wings,
will soar into
the sky once more...
Next time on Burst Angel:
New Sheriff in Town.