To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
The radius of this artificial
island is just over 3 miles.
We plan on constructing an
amusement park with a dome
from about two levels below
the sea to eight levels above.
What's that?
Red tide.
It's the remains of plankton.
There's no need to worry though,
the development plans
took this into account.
It's completely harmless.
Of course I have
nothing to worry about.
Huh?
It's your asses on the
line here, not mine...
If anything happens,
you're responsible.
If you value your jobs,
you'll see to it
this opening goes
without a hitch.
♪ The ocean green is crying. ♪
♪ And the sky of
blue is sobbing. ♪
♪ The future of-- ♪
Damn hippies.
Why should you even
bother worrying about
a future where you
won't even exist?
It's been years since
the previous Governor
broke ground on this project,
or I should say "broke sea"?
After overcoming numerous
obstacles, I'm very proud
to announce the completion
of Tokyo Fortune Island.
And now, the doors to a
Utopian dream will finally open.
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One!
Damn... lot of fine
ladies out there.
Or haven't you noticed?
Uh, yeah.
Come on... What's your deal?
It's just not my thing.
Check it out!
This place is great.
Sure is.
Hey boys. Are you two
having a good time?
It's nice to see you
getting along so well.
Uhh... Hi Sei!
Looks like you barely fit
into that suit, Leo.
Yes, I'm aware...
It's been awhile since
I've gone swimming.
Y'know, I've been thinking.
You and I should get together
and have some adult time,
if you catch my drift.
I just might take you
up on that sometime.
Leo...! Heads up!
Meg!
What...? I warned him.
It's not my fault
he didn't move.
Come on, Leo. Get up.
Want a chance at revenge?
I wouldn't be a man if I
backed down from that...
Let's go, Kyo.
Here comes the power serve!
Where are you aiming?
That wasn't even close.
What...? You're not
gonna play with them?
Hey! Over here!
I think I'll sit this one out.
How's everything going?
Swimmingly, if you
pardon the pun.
The bigwigs keep blabbing
to the press about the
state-of-the-art gaming machines
and the automated food court.
But the real masterpiece of
innovation has got to be this:
our Super-EM electric plant,
which harnesses ocean water
to power the whole island.
Once the public catches on,
they'll never want to go to
a real beach resort again.
What a gorgeous day.
What are you doing Amy?
I'm digging for some
insider dirt on this place.
You know you should be
having fun with the other kids
instead of playing
around on your laptop.
What do you know...?
This just happens to be my most
favorite thing in the world!
Suit yourself.
Oh, and speaking of suits...
That one you're
wearing is so lame.
You really think so?
Totally. It's not cute at all.
Oh.
Well, I have to disagree.
I think... that suit looks
incredible on you... Right?
Most definitely...
You wouldn't happen to
be a model, would you?
Or maybe an actress?
Now that you mention it,
I think I have seen
you somewhere before.
Like on a magazine cover.
Are you boys trying
to flatter me...?
Because I like it.
If you're not an actress,
then you could totally
be one if you wanted.
Yeah, you must be
someone important
to be invited here today.
This Grand Opening has a
super exclusive guest list.
Ugh. You guys're so
outta your league.
Oh! You must be
her little sister.
I love your sunglasses.
You look so cute in them.
Bet you're in
grade school, right?
You want me to check
your homework for you?
Moron.
Whoa... What happened to Kyohei?
The game got a little bit
rough and he passed out.
You see his face?
Yeah.
Hello. Sei here.
Hey. It's been awhile...
Yeah, we'll take the job.
So you've got half a
dozen gangs in a turf war
and you want us to
take out the whole lot?
South Point
Shopping Mall? Got it.
I'll send my best girl
to take care of it.
It'll take half a day at
the most. Talk to you then.
Jo, we got a job.
Ready to go whenever you are.
Not yet... You'll
act as a bodyguard
for the city's vigilante
corps tomorrow morning...
You can relax for
the rest of the day.
I should get some info
on those three losers
from the invitation list
and mess around with 'em.
No, you should put
your computer away
and go play with the other kids.
Aww, come on!
Kyohei. You should
go play with Amy.
Okay.
Yahoo!
Yay!
This rules!
Scared? You should be!
I am unstoppable!
It's Leo time!
What the hell... You're
a grown man, not a child.
Don't you have any common sense?
Oh, yeah, sorry about that.
You guys wear me out.
Here you go.
Oh, Sei.
It's nice and cold... Drink up!
Thanks, you didn't
have to do that.
Oh, before I forget, Kyo,
I have a favor to ask of you.
Huh?
My grandfather's friends are
having a party tomorrow night
and they're... picky
eaters, so I was hoping
I could borrow your
culinary expertise.
I'd be happy to help...
So, what should I
have on the menu?
That special dessert of yours,
for a thousand people.
A thousand?
I don't know, that's a little--
Great! I'm counting on you.
But, w-wait!
Good luck with that sport.
You're young.
Just pull an all-nighter.
Oo! I want to have
some dessert, too!
Yeah, me three. Dessert's
my favorite meal of the day!
Isn't that great, Kyohei?
No. There's nothing
great about it.
Sorry. I was just
messing with you.
Sei...
That's right. The noise
isn't coming from the motor.
It must be something else.
No, I don't think
that'll be necessary...
It's probably just the machines
not being used to
these conditions.
No prob. I'll go ahead and
put it on the top of the list.
Must be hearing things.
I've been looking
all over for you...
Hm?
Feels nice and cold, doesn't it?
Yeah, a little.
You're so weird sometimes.
You know you haven't changed one
bit since the first time we met.
Ever since I came
to this country,
so many different things
have surprised me...
Never thought I'd
make it this far.
In fact, being here like this
almost seems like a lie.
I wish everyday
were like this one.
Oh yeah?
Say, Jo...
I...
Sometimes I wonder what you
were like before we met...
If I had to guess,
I would think you were
probably fighting every day...
But, whether you're working
or not, you always seem to be
fighting in some
way or another...
It's like you're just not
interested in anything else...
But I suppose that's
not a bad thing!
I fight for you, Meg.
Really?
Yeah. You saved
my life after all.
Really...? You mean that?
Yeah, I do.
Jo...
I'm happy...
I'm very happy to have met you.
Hah! I'm in!
Wow, this place is huge!
Jo. What are you
doing down there?
I can hear it.
I don't understand.
You can hear what?
What is this?
Your attention please.
We will now be resetting
all of the facilities here
at Tokyo Fortune Island.
We are terribly sorry
for the inconvenience...
Meg. Let's go.
What?
Please gather your
belongings and make your way
to the park's exit in
an orderly fashion.
Shuttle buses will be
waiting there to drive you
back to the mainland
and to your vehicles.
For security reasons,
we ask that you help us
avoid any possible dangers
by refraining from smoking.
No smoking?
This must be the reason.
That looks nasty, ugh.
No one's talking,
but it looks like there was
an oil tanker accident nearby.
Oh, okay. So that's
why we can't smoke.
Try lightin' up a butt here,
and one stray spark
could turn the place
into a blazing inferno.
Seriously?!
"Any possible dangers?"
If they know there's trouble,
they should just say so!
The truth would only cause
unnecessary panic, Meg...
C'mon... We should
get moving too.
The oil fence is 60% complete.
However, the flow rate
is accelerating faster
than anticipated.
The shuttle buses have arrived.
Commence evacuation.
What the?!
Everyone please line
up single file here.
Remember to keep hold of
your children at all times.
You guys need to
learn to chill out
and enjoy yourselves sometimes.
You got a point but how can we,
when all the chicks are gone?
Look dude, I had to work
for my dad for a whole month
so he'd use his
connections to get us in.
You could show a
little gratitude...
Whoa, dudes, check that out!
Please tell me it's a couple
of hot, young mermaids
looking to party.
Whoa! Mermaids?
What?
Crap!
No way!
This can't be good.
Yeah, and the trailer's on
the other side of the bay.
With these flames
as high as they are,
there's no way we can get to it.
What's gonna happen?
I dunno. Probably nothing.
I don't get you people!
How can you be so calm
at a time like this?
Let's get to the roof for now
and hope a rescue team
comes to get us.
Good idea. Let's hurry.
We're in luck!
Everyone get to the chopper!
What, so you're
a pilot now, too?
Heh. Yeah!
What the hell?!
Ah, shit...! Not the chopper!
What...
...is that?
I think it's an octopus.
You saw its tentacles.
Or a gigantic squid.
It's a damn tentacle beast.
What do you mean a few
people were left behind?
That's what the shuttle
bus driver reported.
I'm afraid it's hopeless
to attempt a rescue
in that flaming ocean.
Understood... but
the real problem is in
whom to blame for this...
gross negligence.
I seem to recall an
environmental preservation group
who opposed this project.
Pin it on them... Got it?
Yes, sir.
Gather all of the
evidence we'll need
and release it at tonight's
press conference.
I'm counting on you.
Let me go!
Sei!
Sorry for being so heavy.
We got ourselves one
slimy situation...
This is no time for
stupid jokes, Leo!
How are we gonna
get off this island?
You probably made it angry
when you ate its parents
for dinner the other night!
Shut up, Amy! That
doesn't even make any sense!
Hey boys.
Why didn't you get on the bus?
We--We were just
sneaking around...
And...
I was smoking a cigarette...
Then the whole place
just went up in flames!
Ah ha. So you're the ones
that started the fire.
Yeah? Well, this
wouldn't have happened
if we had just left
with everyone else!
Shut up, assface! Don't try
to blame all this on me!
I didn't force you
to stay behind.
But you were--
Shut your traps.
I'm sorry!
Please don't shoot me!
Gimme that.
What are you
planning on doing, Jo?
Amy. Be ready to go as
soon as I get in the air.
Ready for what?
We're gonna kill that
damn tentacle beast.
She's so cool!
Jo!
Oh, no, no!
She let herself
get thrown on purpose.
What for?
What for...?
Because she needed a way
to get past the flames...
Damn, she can be
reckless sometimes.
Amy. Get on your laptop
and open the trailer's
hanger for Jo.
Oh okay. Now I see what
Jo was talking about!
Someone might want
to fill in Meg.
I don't think she gets it.
I think the oil has
seeped into the building.
This whole place
is going up soon.
No, please make it stop!
I don't want to die a virgin!
Someone save us!
Knock it off you twerps!
You're whining like
a bunch of little girls!
Ah, there she is!
I don't believe it! Jo's alive!
--You made it!
--She's alive!
You guys okay?
The bastard's regenerating.
What the...?
I can't see a thing!
Gross!
Uh...! He's covered in oil!
I can't believe this, I just
waxed him the other day.
Sorry Leo, couldn't avoid it.
You can at least
help me re-wax him.
Come on you two.
What matters is that
we're safe now.
But my poor Jango!
Looks like you need
a waxing too, Leo.
Thankfully, those
that we couldn't save
before the fire erupted
managed to escape unharmed.
While we are
currently investigating
the exact cause of this
horrible accident,
we have received
word that the ONPOT,
the Organization for the
Nature Preservation of Tokyo,
were directly involved.
If these accusations
are found to be true,
then the ONPOT is guilty of
multiple terrorist acts,
and I assure you all,
we will prosecute them
to the fullest
extent of the law.
You should just be thankful
you weren't seriously
injured, or worse!
No kidding!
That's what happens
when you decide to go
somewhere fun without us.
Squid! Not squid!
What's wrong, Kyo?
Oh man. Get a grip!
I hate squid.
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
An unknown enemy hiding
in the darkness.
A battle that's not quite
nightmare or illusion.
And Jo is drawn
into another world.
Next Burst Angel:
The Man With No Name.