To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
Come on!
Ease up, will ya? It's hard
to do this with just one hand.
All right! Come on, baby!
Mama needs a new pair of shoes!
Keep it rolling and you
could double your money
--on the next spin.
--Oh yeah! Come on!
Let's go! Big money!
There they are!
Pay me! Pay me!
Hey! That's supposed to pay
my rent! Someone help me!
Hey! What are you doing?
Get back here!
Target has fled on foot, leaving
the High Stakes Pachinko Parlor,
traveling east on Third Street.
Move your ass!
I'm going! I'm going!
Attention all Ikebukuro units!
Target sighted near the
Fourth street subway station.
Secure all entries!
No use trying to get
lost in the crowd, Jo.
There's no escape
from my subordinates.
Meg's trapped in the crow's
nest at the top of Tokyo Tower
and the NI-50 in
Kyo's bloodstream
will activate at 6:00 am.
Less than five hours left.
So, do you think
Kyo's gonna make it?
If we can get the
NI-50 out in time.
But, then what
will happen to Meg?
We will get Meg back,
of course. Trust me.
But right now, Jo is hell-bent
on rescuing her by herself.
Unfortunately, that means
she's willing to put
Kyo's life in danger as well.
Take the airship and see
if you can get a fix on them.
Um... I'll be right back.
Again? Lay off the sodas, Amy.
They're bad for your bladder.
Sorry. It won't take long.
This is terrible.
Without Kyo around
we'll be back to eating
fast food and cold pizza,
not that I don't want Meg and Jo
to make it through this, too.
What to do, what to do!
We need to hurry, this thing
inside me's ticking away!
We get hasty, we could
walk right into a trap.
Great. Perfect. Sei's little
minions are all over the place!
Just my luck.
What did I ever do in
my measly little life
to deserve something like this?
Well, sitting there whining
about it isn't gonna get
that thing out of you any
quicker. Get a grip on yourself.
Get a grip on myself?
You're not the one who's
gonna burst in four hours.
Look, once I kill that
bird and get Meg back,
I'll hand you over to Sei.
Until then, calm down!
So, now we have to figure out
a way to get to Tokyo Tower
before we all run
out of time! Got that?
Here's the deal: if you help me
with this now, you get to live.
Fine, it's a deal.
I'll try my best.
Hello!
We're looking for a rave
that's supposed to be going
on in this neighborhood.
Judging by the handcuffs,
I guess you're going too.
So, where's it going down?
We're not from around here
and I think we're kinda lost.
Ask those guys over there.
Oh yeah, they're working
security for the party.
Come on. Ogitagi is supposed
to start in like ten minutes!
Why don't you tell us man?
What the hell are
you talking about?
I get it! They're testing to see
if they should let us in or not.
Look, we already know
it's a secret party.
Okay, enough! Don't you
brats have parents?
No way, you guys
have to let us in!
Yeah, we got all dressed up
and everything!
You could've fooled me, lady.
Jo, no! You can't shoot in here!
Jo!
I'm sorry! The station
was just too crowded!
Yeah, I know.
♪ Hmm, hmm, hmm, Loosey
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, Crazy ♪
I sure cleaned up tonight.
Sorry, mister!
Hey, man! That's my bike!
Dammit!
Okay, I finally picked
them up! Sorry Jo.
That's odd. Why are they staying
out in the open like this?
It's not like Jo
to be so concerned
for the safety of
innocent by-standers.
Attention! All units!
Target is traveling north on
Kasuga Street by motorcycle.
Report to Bai-Lan operatives
in the vicinity at once.
Be careful, Jo.
Your greatest asset, Kyo, could
become your biggest weakness.
Sei here.
What've you got for me?
Roger that. I'll send
back-up right away.
Secure the perimeter
and seize the equipment
before the police show up.
So? What did they say?
They've got a location on
the Crow's hiding place.
It put the girls it snatched
into power plants
that extract lymph fluid
from their bodies.
Ehh? What for?
Probably because the
crow needs it to survive.
It's an essential
substance for the growth
of any organically
based machine.
I gotcha. Because the
crow's body is so huge,
and it keeps burning off energy,
it needed more and more fluid
in order to stay functioning.
So, does that mean it's
an animal or a cybot?
Maybe an evolved form
of both. But for now,
I need you to stay focused on
keeping track of Jo
and Kyohei, all right?
Hello. Excuse me!
She's been hurt.
I need some bandages.
Yeah, sure. Hold on a minute!
We do not have time for this.
But, you're bleeding pretty bad.
You need medical attention.
Let's have a look, here.
Oy, this is really bad.
What happened to you?
It's time to die.
Let her go!
Outta the way, dumbass!
Not so fast.
Punk-ass kids.
They just escaped on foot.
They're moving north
toward the dome.
One of them is
seriously injured.
Hate sayin' "I told you so."
I'm sorry. It's just your
arm was... Is it okay?
C'mon Jo, stay with me! Jo? Jo!
You lost them?
Yeah. They disappeared
somewhere around Jinbou-cho.
Amy! Please tell me you're
not purposely ignoring them.
No, no way. I'm on
your side! I promise.
For real! I'd never
do something like that.
How you feeling?
What time is it?
About five minutes after three.
You look better. I was
starting to get worried.
You passed out on me.
Lucky for us,
those guys came along.
That guy over there
removed the handcuffs,
said he used to be a locksmith.
Say, you guys
care for a cocktail?
We got soup over
here if you want it.
You kids don't start
any trouble here
or the cops'll trash our camp.
I got my eye on ya'.
The truth is,
we lose this place,
we ain't got no
wheres else to go.
We gotta keep a low profile,
if you know what I mean.
Here, have some.
Don't know your story, but you
ain't gonna get very far in life
gettin' shot fulla
holes like you did.
And, the law don't give
two cents about nobody.
No wonder there' so many
youngins runnin' off to be cops.
It's sad. Everybody
wantin' to be a cop
so they can push others around.
Yeah. But none of 'em
are Japanese folks.
This country don't belong
to the Japanese anymore.
Not like that's
anything new, though.
Why didn't you run?
Well, how could I?
You were hurt really bad
and I couldn't just
leave you by yourself.
It was my fault you
got shot, after all.
You know, you're a
very strong person, Jo.
I would've given up long ago.
I admire you for that.
Give it a rest.
I don't take
compliments too well.
Make me all sick
and itchy inside.
Yeah, so, what was
your name again?
It's Kyohei. Kyohei Tachibana.
Never caught it before.
Oh, really?
Oh, your appetite's back.
That's always a good start.
You want more?
I can always run out to the park
and hunt down some more meat,
if there ain't
enough there for ya.
No, thank you.
We have to go now.
We're leaving, Kyohei.
She sure keeps him on
a pretty short leash.
Ahh, he's all right.
He wouldn't be runnin'
around with her
if he didn't want to be.
We have to run. Can you keep up?
Yeah. I'll be just fine.
Here goes.
Hot noodles, get your
hot steaming noodles!
Hey! Hold up a minute, would ya?
You can do it.
You made it. Good work.
How'd you get here?
Outta my way Sei.
Be smart Jo.
The enemy is right above us.
Besides, do really think you
can make it past all of us?
If that's how you
want to play it.
You know I can go the distance.
But, when I go down, keep in
mind, you go down with me.
The enemy's hideout
has been secured, Jo.
There's no place
left for it to escape.
If we work together we can
both have what we want.
Honestly, how did you plan
to fight it without Jango?
Work with me here.
Hand over Kyo.
No deal! The Crow's
not going to play ball
unless we trade both
of the hostages.
I can beat it!
Just let me have Jango and
stay the hell out of my way!
All right, then.
We'll let Kyo make the choice.
So, what do you think?
Do you want to take
your chances with Jo?
Or stay and get
the NI-50 out now?
It is your life on the line.
So it's up to you.
It's not... I can't
just choose like that.
I... I, um...
I think that... Well...
We should let Jo go and, um...
I think... she can do it.
I know Jo can save Meg!
Damn it, Sei.
Calm down, that dart
may save his life.
It'll slow down his
metabolism for a while.
Which will in turn
keep the NI-50
from activating when
it's supposed to.
But, keep in mind Jo,
it won't last long.
All this is just so
you can get your hands
on the crow's brain,
isn't it? Tell me.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have
been here waiting for us.
I just want to see Meg and Kyo
rescued safely, that's all.
But, I need you Jo.
I need your strength.
And, I need your uncanny ability
to kill two birds
with one stone.
Right now, I'm gonna
make sure Meg is safe
and kick that crow's ass.
But then I'm coming back
to knock that damn
smirk off your face.
I suppose that's fair.
What you're after is
inside this man's body!
Meg!
Meg, can you get over here?
Jo.
Look out!
What is that?
No way!
Jo can't lose!
This isn't happening!
How can you sleep
at a time like this?
We've got to figure something
out here! Jo just fell!
You damn crow!
Now you've done it!
Yeah, Jo!
Where you think you're going?
Jo, do you read me?
I'm trying to locate
the central core lock
that houses the
crow's control systems.
Better make it quick!
Amy, whatta ya got?
Jo! Uploading to your screen.
That's the crow's weak spot!
All right! You did it, Jo!
Well, at least you left us a few
scraps of metal we can analyze.
Most of it's charred
beyond recognition though.
Didn't have a choice.
I know. Recovery'll be tough,
but we'll make the best of it.
How's Kyohei?
Concerned? He's fine.
We got it out in time.
And all the girls the
crow took are okay too.
That's a new one for
you, saving people.
It's new for you too.
Don't patronize me.
That reminds me, weren't
you saying something
about knocking the
smirk off my face?
Well, I'm waiting.
I'll have to get
back to you on that.
I gotta go check on
a friend of mine.
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
An old man who
desires eternal peace,
and a youth entrusted
with that hope.
But when all becomes fiction,
the bloodshed begins.
Next Burst Angel:
Party of the Dragon