To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
Startin' today...
This town belongs
to the new King.
What, is this a joke?!
I can assure you... it's not.
I'm the new law in town,
and those who oppose
me get no mercy.
And this pathetic excuse
for a cybot is an eyesore!
If you try to send
another my way,
I'll kill the girl
without hesitation.
As long as he has a hold of Meg,
we can't afford to make
any careless moves.
You're the only ones left!
All work and low pay is
nothin' to give yer lives for!
Damn you. How could you
betray us like this?!
Because of incompetent
morons like you.
Made me sick.
What you called a "police
force" was no more than
a gang of sniveling twits
clinging to their titles.
He's taken credit for a
number of terrorist incidents
in Osaka to prove how worthless
the Hanshin Police Force is.
Then he took his cause
to the National Diet.
So the government was behind
all the terrorist activity?
That's right...
We believe this cop,
Togo Iriki was promised
a position giving him control
of a large portion of Osaka.
But there must be a
powerful political figure
that's working
behind the scenes.
All these guys Jo's fought
have had cutting edge tech,
and trust me,
that isn't cheap.
I'd bet the group
backing them is huge.
Amy... You think you can
pinpoint their hideout?
We came across an
underground cybot factory
beneath that truck
we chased down...
Once again, they were
using a glowing brain
to control the bot...
Based on its size,
my guess is it came from
the last beast Jo took on.
I had Bai-Lan's men
look into it,
but by the time they showed up,
there wasn't anything left.
I also noticed they
used a strong EM signal
to create a sort of
a magnetic storm...
So unless we're right on top of
'em, our sensors are useless!
Then why don't you do
something about it... genius.
Hey, that's mean...!
I'm not stupid.
I could read an entire book in
binary code if I wanted to.
Leo. Start prepping Jango.
We need him right away.
No problem.
It'll be a good chance to
test out his new upgrades.
But with his pilot
in this condition...
Do me a favor.
And what's that?
About Jango... I want you
to put wings on him!
We really appreciate
your assistance.
Sure, that's one private jet
engine and a whole ton of ammo.
Looking to start
a war or something?
No... We're just planning to put
the hurt on the new
sheriff in town.
I see... Good luck with that.
All right...
Bring in the trailer!
C'mon Leo... You really
gonna put wings on him?
What? You don't think I can?
No way.
Hey Mama... How come
Daddy won't wake up?
Mama?
Because... Milly.
Your daddy... He can't wake up.
He's gone to sleep forever.
But I don't want him to!
Mr. Katsu gave me
a bunch of toys
and I wanted to
show them to him!
Daddy, please!
Please! Wake up...
Why won't you wake up?
Milly. I know this
is hard for you,
but you'll understand some day.
Takane...
What is it?
My husband... Did he at least
die bravely? With honor?
Osaka's justice will never die!
Yeah... He most certainly did.
Really?
Your daddy was a hero.
Mom... I'm sorry.
Your name... is Jo, right?
You really did it this time.
The symbol of Osaka
is now in ruins.
Are you going to
arrest me again?
I'm not in the mood.
So lemme skip the awkward small
talk and get to the point...
Thank you for trying
to save Masa-yan.
I truly appreciate it.
I won't rest until
he's avenged...
I'm gonna make that
bastard, Iriki, pay.
And then I'm goin' after
whoever was drivin' that cybot.
That cybot didn't have a pilot.
What do you mean?
Remember the monster
that escaped?
Its brain was put
in that cybot...
That's what's controlling it.
Is... that even possible?
Go ahead.
I see. I'll be
right there...
Jo. I don't know how yet,
but I'm going to pay you
back... I promise you.
Ugh. Déjà vu.
So what do you think?
Quite a shiny brain, uh...?
Do you have any idea how much
it costs to make one of those?
How the hell should I know?!
You sick pervert!
Long as this cybot has
that brain installed,
Bai-Lan's pathetic dolls
won't stand a chance.
No good king would
ever cause suffering.
As such, I'll have to plow the
entire town in one fell swoop,
before I can cultivate
it in my own image!
And I got me a big old
bulldozer to do it with!
My associates were
quite ecstatic...
when I told them I had
gotten my hands on
one of these here brains.
Next week...
That bulldozer's goin' into
the shop for a full upgrade!
Whaddaya say, sweet thing?
Wanna be a part of it?
No, no! I don't want
to be bulldozed!
Tomorrow's festival
cannot be canceled
under any circumstances!
If we did so... Osaka's
spirit would vanish!
We have to locate
that cybot's hideout.
If we fail, we won't
stand a chance.
Use any means necessary.
Just get out there and
find that cybot...!
The som'bitch is
definitely hiding out
in this city somewhere!
Leave it to us, boss girl!
We'll have that ugly beast's
head on a platter for you.
Didn't you say
those exact words
when your third husband
decided to split town?
Listen up! This is war!
The greatest battle since
the formation of the Kanbaku!
At all costs... defend our city!
Yeah!
Keep it moving people!
Do not stop in the
middle of the road!
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
Whoa! They just ran
into that house!
That house gets
hit every year...
Funny thing is... They never
even seem to complain about it.
Huh... Hey, wait a minute,
what happened to Tetsuzo?
You don't mean the Tetsuzo?!
Uh, yeah, I just met him.
Now you listen...
This is for your own good!
Get your ass back to Tokyo!
What?
Ahhhh... This sucks.
We're missing the entire parade.
Would you can it, already?
I want to see it too, you know.
It wouldn't hurt to take
a small peek, right?
That's true...
What the hell, let's do it.
From the ocean?!
What the...
That poor house just
got nailed again!
Well, looks like the
owner might actually
file a complaint this year.
Damn you cybot!
--Hey look!
--It's Tetsuzo!
We're saved!
Beat the crap out of that cybot!
Listen you sonuvabitch!
I'm gonna shove a handful of
roman candle's up your ass
and send you straight to the
Grand Canyon! You got that?!
The Grand Canyon?
Tetsuzo seems to think the
Grand Canyon is in Hiroshima.
He just won't listen.
Look!
He stopped it with his head!
A recent chain of terrorist
attacks in Osaka
has brought the city
to a standstill.
In response, Tokyo's RAPT
Squadron has been deployed.
A source within RAPT
was quoted as saying
their only objective is to
suppress the violence quickly
without causing further damage
to the city's infrastructure.
Man that really
tightens my jaws...
We don't need them to save us.
Course we do, the force don't
have the firepower for all this.
Besides, that robot
can hide in the ocean,
so there's no way we
could possibly find it,
and even if we did...
Cap'n, you're back.
Looks like the cavalry's
heading in from Tokyo.
What you think we should do?
I don't...
I don't know!
Captain, wait!
What should I do?
Are we unable to defend
Osaka by ourselves?
Yeah, Takane speakin'.
Takane--
Daddy?
There's no time
so listen carefully.
I'm listenin'.
The Hanshin Police Force
has lost its way...
It's gotten so lost, in fact,
it's just going in circles.
I fear this is the end.
In times like these, you need to
go back to where you started.
Where we started?
That's right. Return to where
this whole mess began.
Search the scene
a hundred times.
That's the heart of
good investigation.
Remember the monster
that escaped?
Its brain was put
in that cybot...
That's what's controlling it.
That's--!
Damn it...! The monster
pulled a fast one on us!
It hid and waited 'til
we were all gone...
Then it just waltzed
right out of here!
This is Takane.
Get forensics over to
Grand Osaka Station right away.
We need to find out exactly
where that monster
lost its brain!
That was hilarious!
The tourists finally
got some action
out of that stupid parade.
Damn it! You're a cop.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?!
I've heard that line before
and it's a bunch of crap.
Any reasonable man
with an ounce of dignity
would prefer being
a king over a cop.
And by the way...
That pretty mouth of yours says
such nasty things to the king.
Bitch!
I've tried to be nice with you,
but I see that's
getting me nowhere.
Get up! C'mon!
You wanna break
an arm or a leg?
Or how 'bout both?
I'm falling!
Uh, no you're not.
Oh, um, hi there!
Iriki!
Nice work.
I was hoping to play
hide-and-seek a little longer,
but it looks like you found
me sooner than I expected.
Smart girl. My compliments.
Shut your mouth...!
I won't be forgiving
you this time around.
Nah... Really...?
I wouldn't expect such
kindness from you.
Only the king can decide who
is forgiven and who is not.
And you're looking at him!
Now, hail to the king, baby!
You refuse, eh?
Then I'll take it upon myself
to crush you and
your pathetic fort!
Pissants! Now you kids
go to your rooms
and think about
what you've done!
It's that cybot! Run!
It's coming right at us!
You'd best be gettin'
back to Jo now.
Tell her my debt's been paid!
She said her debt is paid, huh?
Uh-huh.
So he said he's going to
destroy their fortress?
Yeah.
Sei, let's go!
Of course.
Get him good, Jo, and don't
forget to bring me a souvenir.
Whatever. I'm not
holdin' back on this one.
From now until sunset...
Your lives are in the hands
of the Kanbaku Hawk!
Now, fire!
Never mess with a pissed
off cross-dresser!
You don't know pain 'til
you squeeze into a girdle!
I put a whole can of
whoop-ass in my muffins!
Come have a bite!
Let's see how they like
frozen tuna heads!
Osaka has been defendin' itself
since the days of
the Tokugawa Sieges!
We cannot give up!
Hold on... I call this one
Operation: Angel Wing.
Playtime is over!
Stupid trash.
Not just you folks...
This whole city is a trash heap!
Osaka carries the stench
of sweaty old ladies!
And it's up to me to make
this place clean again!
And now it's time
for you to die!
Listen up, prick...
If you want to kill our boss,
you'll have to go
through me first!
So go ahead and
try, you bastard!
That's right! We ain't
gonna let you touch her!
Ah, well isn't that
just adorable...
Is that what they call
friendship among trash?
You can all die together!
You're the one
who's going to die!
What the...
Hey, watch it! Thought
you were on our side!
That a friend of yours?
A little help from back East.
Sweet!
Thanks for saving me some.
Sorry 'bout that.
Oh man... Y'all're good!
That girl is insane!
I've had just about enough
of this game of tag.
It's time for an old
fashioned gunfight!
Oh, no! It hurts, it hurts!
Yeah, right!
Now the other arm!
Think so!
You're gettin' cocky!
Keep it up, you'll just
be part of the trash dump
I've begun accumulating.
What the...
Show some freakin' respect
for Osaka's landmarks!
Pot and the kettle, psycho!
You started this mess,
I'm finishin' it!
There it is!
This is for
disobeying your king!
I'm gonna rip your head off
and hang it at Osaka Castle!
You're pathetic, Tokyo!
Lose to that slimeball,
and you'll never make
it out of Osaka alive!
Stay back...! You won't make it!
Somethin' you should know, Jo...
Don't underestimate
the Kanbaku Hawk!
Say your prayers Iriki,
I'm coming for ya!
Now choke on Masa-yan's
last words...
Osaka's justice will never die!
Did we get 'im?
Yeah, we got him.
Quick! Jump!
I guess I'll see you next time.
Won't be a next time.
I won't be back.
Then maybe next time I'm
in Tokyo, I'll look you up.
Move it, Princess!
Places to go, people to see!
Catch ya later, Hawk Lady.
It's been real!
Seems like y'all have
a lot of fun together.
Stay outta Tokyo.
It's dangerous... and noisy.
That sounds like even more fun.
I'm proud of you,
Takane... Good work.
I'm sorry. I couldn't
visit Mom's grave...
You don't have to say a thing.
You made her proud too.
I'm sure of it.
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
Children who live bravely in
the valley of the metropolis.
A young soul who
awaits a ray of hope.
Can a miracle emerge?
Next Burst Angel... Wild Kids.