To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
Aw, man. Clouds have it so easy.
The crime rate in most of
the major metropolitan areas
has been steadily dropping
since the year 2020.
Most of this success
can be attributed
to a prevention program
initiated at the time.
Who's she kidding?
Nobody believes this crap.
Maybe the truth would keep
me from falling asleep.
As the program
became less centralized,
its integration with R.A.P.T.
has become much more fluid--
Achoo! Ahh!
My bad. Allergies, you know?
Uh... Wh-What do you want?
Meg, you just don't seem to
fit in here very well, do you?
Just being around you makes
me want to get into trouble!
What?
Oh, yeah, Meg!
You're full of surprises,
plus we think you're so funny!
Y'all really think I'm funny?
Absolutely.
Oh, you! What can
I say? You got me!
I'm just a regular
comedian, I tell ya!
You know, I really appreciate
you guys welcoming me.
Well, honestly,
we wanted to find out
if there was something
wrong with you.
Whadda you mean?
Like, maybe you've been sick
and missed a lot of school.
Or maybe you were
a real troublemaker
and you got kicked out of your
last school and sent here.
But, now that we've met
you, you seem to be okay,
nothing weird.
Look, don't get the wrong idea.
Things are just really
boring around here
and you're something
new and interesting.
We just wanted to make
sure you weren't going to
bust up our circle of friends.
Hey! That's cool, I understand.
You guys got nothing
to worry about!
We'll just have to make the
circle a little wider. Right?
Oh, Meg!
You're so funny!
I am?
Come on, our next class is
in the upperclassmen wing.
Make sure you greet them
if you pass them in the halls.
How are you ladies doing today?
We're doing wonderfully.
Thank you very
much for asking.
You're new here.
Uh... Uh, yeah.
Yes. Sister Angelique,
this is Megumi Mitarai.
She's a new transfer student.
She just started last week.
Well, there is still
much for you to learn
about our fine academy.
I'd be happy to show you around.
Won't you please
stop by our dorm room
when you have some free time?
Good day, then. Ladies.
Stop by her dorm room?
That's great, Meg!
They must really like you!
You've been invited
to the Ishtar club!
It's quite an honor!
The... The Ishtar Club?
It's an exclusive
members-only club
founded by Sister Angelique.
It was set up to serve
as an exemplary model
for the rest of
the student body.
Only the top students
are selected to join up.
She even got a special charter
from the head of
the school board.
I'm so jealous!
Uh! Well I guess...
...some people just know
how to recognize greatness
when they see it!
Oh yes, it's finally over!
How can y'all stand to sit
here so quietly for so long?
They say that 'truth lies in
the words of your teachers.'
They also say that
idle chatter and gossip
only attracts laziness
and ignorance.
Yeah! We take it very seriously.
The students of St. Luciana's
believe class is a holy ritual,
in which we commune with
the spirits of our instructors.
If this prayer gets any
longer, we'll never eat!
Aww, same food all week!
I've had it with all these
strict rules and regulations!
This stinks!
Keep it down in there
young lady! It's lights out!
Oh, sorry!
Oh, shoot! It's time!
Oh wow, this Indian
curry is so super yummy!
Don't you like it, too, Jo?
Yeah, but this soup
is a little spicy.
That's not soup, you
savage, it's curry sauce!
You're not supposed to drink it!
I swear. You have no concept of
fine cuisine, whatsoever, Jo!
Calm down. I made another
one 'specially for you.
And, this one's all mine!
Whoa! This is awesome!
I love you, Kyouhei Tachibana!
Yeah. Um, Amy? I appreciate it.
Really, I do,
but I think I might be just
a little too old for you.
You know?
Aw, geez. Am I the only one
here with a sense of humor?
Okay y'all, I'm hungry
and I want to come home!
You're busy stuffing your
faces with the good stuff
while I starve
on cafeteria food!
Well, Kyo did make some
killer curry tonight!
Meg! Give us your report!
Everything is going
as planned, Jo.
But this place is like
filled with total whackos.
What do you mean?
It's just that the girls
are all so prissy!
They're like,
'How do you do?'
And then they look
down their nose and say,
'Ooh, you're so funny!'
It is so obnoxious!
Oh, and you have to be polite
to the upperclassmen
and no one says a word
in class or at meal-time!
Hey, are you guys there?
What'd you expect? It's a
school for spoiled rich kids!
Spoiled is right!
Just don't forget
why you're there.
I won't forget!
I don't want to end up like that
poor girl either, you know.
Help me!
Stay away! No!
Stop! Stop! Help me,
please! Get away!
The hallucinations
were driving her insane.
But, no matter what
the doctors tried,
she just got worse everyday.
They suspect that
drugs may be involved,
but they don't know
anything for sure.
All we are sure of, is that
whatever happened to her,
it started at
St. Luciana's Academy,
and it's slowly eating
away at her mind.
That, and we know her
father's connected to Bai-Lan.
You know, there's drugs out
there that leave no trace.
No matter how nice
those girls are
you can't let your guard down.
Well, I haven't seen anything
out of the ordinary yet.
There is something odd going
on with the older girls.
They formed this club, Ishitaw,
Ishidai... Oh, yeah, Ishtar!
It's all exclusive
and members only.
I think they get
special privileges too.
You think you can you get in?
Yeah, I met the leader
today, and she invited me,
so no problem.
Meg? What's going on? Meg!
No, don't hurt me.
No don't. Please, stop.
No, don't take me!
Leave, me alone!
Please, no!
Wait! Hold on!
What are you doing?
You could fall!
I'm sorry, please forgive me!
Whoa! Hold on. Just calm down.
Leave me alone!
Just hold on!
I gotcha!
These girls really are a...
...a bunch of nutjobs.
I'm so hungry.
What the--
Hey!
Are you feeling any better yet?
Who's that?
I don't know.
Wait up! Don't just walk away.
Let go!
Oh, sorry.
But, how are you feeling?
What do you mean?
I was wondering if you'd
pulled yourself together.
I was kinda
worried this morning.
Do I know you from somewhere?
You don't even... Last night,
up on the roof you--
Look, I'm not asking for a big
thank you or anything like that.
It's just weird that
you don't remember.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Come on! You don't remember
trying to jump off the roof?
You shouldn't say such things.
Spreading bad rumors like
that will ruin my reputation!
Got it?
I don't know why I can't move.
My mind is lost in this crowd.
No one even hears...
Geez, what am I doing here?
This place is driving me nuts.
And this lame get-up
is getting really old.
Megumi Mitarai?
Hi there. Are you
missing something?
I can't believe
you didn't notice.
You're lucky a teacher
didn't catch you without it.
Actually, it was
Sister Angelique
who found your ID card.
I imagine you would like
to thank her in person.
Come this way.
Only a very select
few are allowed
the privilege of
admittance here.
Ah, Megumi.
But you prefer "Meg?"
Right.
Welcome to the Ishtar club.
I'm delighted you could drop by.
Yeah. Those girls said you
made sure I got my ID back.
I really can't thank you enough.
No thanks are necessary,
I assure you.
We are all friends here.
And I'm sure
you'd do the same.
Won't you please make
yourself at home?
Oh, great!
No way!
My, you certainly have
a unique way of eating!
Bordering on primal!
Relax, we've got plenty of time.
Why don't we all enjoy
a soothing pot of tea.
This one has a truly
wonderful aroma.
Ah, so that's how you do it.
You are so right! It smells
absolutely enchanting.
Aah! Hot!
I... I'm so sorry! I am such
a klutz, are you all right?
Wha--
Honestly Meg, don't worry
about it. I will be fine.
We shall get this
mess cleaned up.
Your only concern should be
to get to your next class.
But--
I totally blew it today.
But I got candy, so big deal!
Meg?
Who's there?
It's you.
I'm sorry about earlier today.
So, you do remember
what happened last night.
Kinda. But I'm
still so confused.
My memory of last night
is really fuzzy.
I do remember one thing, though.
You tried to help me,
but I was just a burden to you.
It's okay.
If something like
that happened to me,
I'd probably be a little
wigged out too.
But I am concerned. What made
you try to commit suicide?
Well, I...
It's okay if you don't feel like
talking, I understand, however--
We were all put on this
earth to enjoy life.
Suicide will never
solve anything.
You really think things
will be better if you die?
Do you know what happens
when you jump off
a building like that?
Your head busts open
and your brains splatter
all over the place
like bad Italian food.
You don't want to
end up like that.
Suicide is just running
away from your problems.
You just end up dead.
Your only real option
is to suck it up
and get on with your life.
I may not be as proper
and refined as you guys,
but I do have friends.
Friends who helped me
learn that fact the hard way.
Thank you for your help.
I think it's really good
that I got to meet you Meg.
I've never had anybody really
talk to me like that before.
Can I see your hand?
It's really warm.
If you don't bring
me some real food,
I'm bustin' outta this joint!
Not another jumper?
Aren't you the new transfer
student, Megumi Mitarai?
How do you know who I am?
It's quite a small school.
Rumors about new
arrivals tend to spread
rather quickly around here.
I'm Nadesico, the President
of the senior class.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, of course.
Nice to meet you too.
You know, it's forbidden
to leave your room
after lights out.
And here you are on the roof.
Oh, I didn't know.
See, I was just looking
for another restroom.
The one on my floor's
all backed up.
Well, you certainly
won't find any up here.
It's okay. I won't tell anyone.
I'm like you,
I couldn't sleep either.
So, I came up here
to look at the stars.
Why don't you and I keep our
flagrant little violation
of school policy strictly
between the two of us? Okay?
Here. Take my jacket,
you look like you're
starting to get cold.
Thank you, Nadesico.
Nadesico, huh...
Smells good.
Hey Meg! Over here!
Over here!
Laugh it up, Meg.
I don't think the whole
school heard you yet.
Sorry, I can't help it!
They made me wear it this
just in case I was spotted.
Enough! Have you found
anything out of value?
There's definitely
something going on
with the girls in
that Ishtar club.
They seem to have a lot of pull
with everyone at the school.
And, the leader,
Angelique, has this
really nasty scar on her arm.
Maybe she's a lot
tougher than she looks.
Speaking of Angelique,
I discovered her father
was an important player
involved in Tokyo's
4th Reconstruction Plan.
One other thing: The name
of that club, "Ishtar,"
was the ancient Babylonian
goddess of love.
Oh! How cheesy!
New guy, show it to her.
Yeah, right.
What are you doing, you perv?
I'll have you know I have
no interest in you like that,
so keep your clothes on!
Look, there's a miniature
camera built in the button.
Yeah. Not too shabby.
This is the main lecture hall.
Wait a minute. Why am I
talking to the camera?
What is she taking pictures of?
Who knows?
That should about do it-
Oh, I almost forgot
the most important place.
Perfect. There's nobody here.
Might as well get
a shot of everything.
Damn it, Meg.
Stop goofing around!
She can't exactly
hear you, y'know!
Yeah, I know.
Now where do
they keep the candy?
I know! Maybe it's hidden
behind one of these books!
What's this?
Meg!
Gimme a break.
I didn't sign up for this!
Holy--
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
Is it an illusion
or is it reality?
Jo's bullets echo within
a strange world of dreams
against a demon without a face.
Next Burst Angel: "Wash this
Garden Away with Blood!"