To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
Commencing link.
Right, men! Move out!
Wanna tell me who you are?
My name is Liang. That man
you shot is my twin brother.
His name is Wong.
What's all the fuss over
this one little guy?
You ask me, he's
just some crazy bum.
Hinode Pharmaceuticals was
conducting secret experiments.
They used human test subjects
at their facility in Shinagawa.
My guess is that Wong
was one of their lab rats,
one of their "samples."
I'd also be willing to bet
RAPT is involved, too.
Other than that, I don't know.
Got it!
It's beneath Tokyo Terminal,
hooked up to a freight train.
Destination?
Heading north!
We going after it?
Are you kidding?
Tell me the truth.
You're working for Hinode
Pharmaceuticals, aren't you?
Hinode? I wouldn't work
with a company like that.
Stop lying!
I'm telling the truth!
We were sent to find your
freaked out brother! That's all!
So if you're gonna
shoot me, then shoot!
Don't think I won't jump
and take you with me!
It's Liang, right? What are
you trying to accomplish here?
I want my brother
back. That's all.
That dude's a total basketcase.
I don't see why anyone would
bother trying to save him.
Yeah. So he wasn't
exactly a model citizen.
But, he wasn't
always so messed up.
He helped me a lot.
He even loaned me the money
to open my first restaurant
in this country.
Hey, brother-man,
any business today?
You always show up when
the food's hot, don't ya?
Liang, this is great! It's the
best fried rice I've ever had.
You wanna keep eating
my fried rice,
you better keep your nose clean!
Don't worry about me, bro!
I got it all figured out.
I'm destined for
greatness in this town!
I don't why, but he
got into some trouble
and RAPT hauled him in.
When he got out,
he was different.
He wasn't the brother
I knew before.
C'mon, bro! What is your deal?
He hated taking medicine,
but now he was popping
pills everyday.
He said they were just vitamins,
but when I realized the
truth, it was too late.
He's my brother,
so I had to try and figure
out what they did to him.
Turns out the dealer he
was getting his stuff from
was working for RAPT.
It was obvious they
were intentionally
trying to get him strung out.
That way he'd do anything
they wanted him to,
as long as the
drugs kept coming.
Experiments, tests,
I don't know.
I took the pills away
and he just disappeared.
Hey Jack, today ain't your
pick-up day! Go home.
Come back on Thursday,
and I'll set you up.
Wait! Please stop this.
What did you say? Stop?
I'm begging you to stop
peddling this trash.
You wait! Who do you think
you are, you little shit?!
No!
Why? Why do this--
Shut up!
Don't mess with me! I'll make
your life miserable, ya hear me?
Back off!
You wouldn't!
If I'd killed him
right there and then,
my brother might
still be around.
Now, sleep.
They took him to a secret
lab in Shinagawa.
The facility is owned
by Hinode Pharmaceuticals.
They perform live
human experiments there.
I think they're after something
inside my brother's body.
Something he developed.
Developed? Huh?
Do you think he's
telling the truth?
He seems pretty sincere.
We're on our way now. You
just stay right where you are.
'Kay. Meg out.
Don't know about you,
but I'm going in.
That's a bad idea.
Wait! What are you doing?
I'm gonna cut this cable
and force the train
to stop in the tunnel!
The tunnel's dark.
I should be able
to sneak onboard
while they're trying
to fix the train.
Uh, wait! Maybe we should...
Oh, no!
All right, hold on!
Yeah. Right! Just don't drop me!
Don't let go.
I can't hold on much longer!
Wong!
Damn you! That's my brother!
Let him outta there! Let him go!
Liang! What did you--
Shut up! Or you'll
end up the same way!
They bring in the test subjects
when the desired effects
begin to manifest physically.
In order to get
detailed data,
they have to transport
them to a proper facility.
After that, well, who knows?
Bingo!
At the end of
that freight line
there's a Hinode research
and development lab.
Did Bai-Lan tell us
to protect Wong
because they knew about
the ongoing experiments?
Are they after the same
information as Hinode?
Check it out!
We caught up to 'em!
Amy. I need you to
contact Meg, right away.
Are they ready
for him at the lab?
Yeah, they're ready,
but this guy's bio levels
are going through the roof.
I'll try and adjust
the regulator balance.
Now you guys call me.
Open fire!
What is that?
You call for backup?
I wish. That's not Bai-Lan.
It's someone else.
Whoever they are, they can
only be after one thing.
But what exactly? What is
hidden inside of Wong's body?
Attention! This will be
your only warning!
Stop the train and lay down
your weapons immediately!
Attention!
A Ratman has engaged an enemy
cybot in cargo area three!
Stay clear!
Heavy assault is imminent!
All medical research
personnel are instructed
to remain inside
the bio-transport car!
W-What's going on?
Um, short version?
Things are getting ugly.
Hey! You two keep quiet!
Chill out!
I said, shut yer traps!
All Hell's about to
break loose. Ready?
That's what I was
born to do, baby!
What the--?
They're closing in!
Release car number 3!
Meg!
Amy, there anywhere up ahead
we can get off the Mega Highway?
Yeah, I think so, why?
All aboard.
Line up with the train
as close as you can.
Okay, I'll give it a shot!
I've never seen
anything like this before.
The cellular structure is
active, like it's alive.
The mutation has reached
the secondary stage.
Let's increase the density
of the bio-solution.
So, this the new
lab rat? Ugly bastard.
We've upped the dosage
considerably on this guy.
I look forward to
seeing the results.
What the--!
The assault is over. How are
things in the bio-transport?
Bio-transport respond!
Come in bio-transport!
My god, Wong!
Are you in there somewhere?
You serious? That's not
your brother anymore.
Wong! Say something if you can!
Oh, don't do that!
He'll come over here!
Brother! It's me, Liang!
You have to remember me!
Br... Brother.
That's it, brother. Come on.
What is that?
You monster!
You tore these men to shreds!
He's coming at us!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
Wait! I'm your brother.
I won't hurt you.
Wong... I'm sorry.
Guys this is really bad!
We found Liang's brother,
but then he turned
into a monster,
and then there was
blood everywhere,
and he killed Liang
and the other soldiers,
and then it went
up front and... and...
Meg, calm down!
What are you saying?
I'm perfectly calm!
Now listen to me!
Wong turned into a monster,
killed everyone, and
now he's in the cockpit!
Oh, so he's the one
speeding up the train!
Jo, it's going too fast!
At this rate it's gonna
smash right into the lab!
He's got that thing
at full throttle.
Suicidal son of a bitch!
He wants revenge against
the company that turned him
into a mutant, into a monster.
Oh, so killing us too
makes perfect sense!
But you know, it's okay.
We die together, twin brothers.
There we go,
pull up that section.
These are the last roads
that will lead to the facility.
Now zoom in on
that intersection!
Actually, it's not a road.
It's an old railroad bridge.
What's underneath the bridge?
How should I know?
It's not like satellite
cams have X-ray vision!
Then what good are you
and your computer?
Can you catch up to it?
I think so. But that
old iron railroad bridge
probably can't hold the
weight of our vehicle. Ideas?
Yeah, I got something in mind.
Meg here.
Meg, I need you to get to
the rear car! Right now!
Okay!
Wh-What on Earth
happened up here?
Hey! Let go!
Meg!
You wanna die?! Next stop: Hell!
In other news, an alligator
escaped from its pen
in a West Azabu club and
made its way to Shinjuku
through the city's
underground sewer system.
Tragically, a hot dog vendor
was killed and a mime's legs
were gnawed off as a
result of today's attack.
A young infant
made history today
with the release of his
debut full-length album.
The implantation of an
intelligence-accelerator chip
in the language center
of the infant's brain
--made it possible to translate
--Whatever.
the young idol's
thoughts into song.
Here Meg, eat this.
It'll cheer ya up.
Huh. What is it?
It's Kyo's fried rice
and steamed dumplings.
Twin brothers...
Huh? What did you say?
Oh, nothing. This looks good.
Down the hatch!
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
In a remote area,
the Saint Luciana
Academy For Girls
becomes the site of
an evil spirit's trap.
Meg is snared by the demon
and must fight it alone.
Next Burst Angel: "The
Mansion Where Lurks The Demon."