To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
Stop hiding!
Come on out here
and show yourself!
Damn. How did I get
myself into this?
So, what's his deal?
He's wanted for multiple
abductions and murders...
including children.
What a scumbag!
Take care of him...
Do it your way.
I need this thing fixed
while I'm gone...
Maybe have Amy give it a look.
Aw, man! Jo and Meg left?
Jo was hoping you
could fix her TV.
Sheesh, this whole
place is a dump!
That just means he's got
a lot of places to hide.
I like what he's
done with the place.
We'll probably find him
faster if we split up.
And Meg... Watch yourself.
What was that?
Who's there?!
My partner's on the way, so if
you're smart you'll let me go!
I'm not doing anything wrong.
You're the one waving
the gun around.
That's not very smart!
I have been wrongly accused!
But, if you insist on
pointing that gun at me,
I'll have to do
whatever it takes
to protect myself and
I do mean whatever.
You have no idea
what a huge mistake
you're making right now...
Let her go or
it'll get real ugly.
The only mistake'll be
when you force me to...
slice up this pretty
little face over here.
I'll tell you what I'll do,
if you just walk away now,
I'll let her go;
and I'll throw you a little
cash for your trouble...
It's a good deal for you
and a good deal for me.
It'll be a real pleasure
doing business with you.
Here's an idea...
How about you let her go then I
put a bullet between your eyes!
That's no good...
If you try to shoot me...
then my hand might slip
and this bottle might go
right through her tender neck.
Jo, wait a minute!
This guy's crazy!
I think he'll really do it!
Ouch...! Damn...! I can't
believe you just shot me!
I want to speak to my attorney
right now, you hear me?!
You're going to speak
to somebody all right,
it just won't be a
lawyer, you maniac!
Get a hold of Sei--
Right.
Oops, I slipped!
Let me down, you
crazy little bitches!
Get me down from here...!
You two are going to regret
this, I promise you that!
My attorney's gonna sue you
both and send you to prison...!
Jackass!
Wh-What is it?
Not again--
Jo?
Is it fixed?
Well, I switched out all of the
major components with new ones,
but it didn't make
much difference.
The insides were all melted.
Here's your culprit...
What is it?
Um... To be honest
with you...? No idea.
Jo...! Heads up...
Leo's on the phone for you.
What's the old man want?
I appreciate you
helping me out, Jo.
What exactly is it
you need me to do?
Wherever there's cybot action,
there's gonna be a crap
ton of combat data...
I download this stuff from
all kinds of sources...
I find it comes in
handy with Jango.
Downloading with permission
or just helping yourself
to whatever you want?
Hey! These files are
collectors items!
I graciously archive
them for fun and profit.
So you're a data thief.
Oh, don't make me out
to be such a bad guy...
I take only one a day...
A real pro utilizes all
resources at his disposal.
We got about
thirty minutes left.
What's wrong?
Nothing... Just a headache...
Hurry it up... I got a bad
feeling about this.
What now?!
Bad guys, obviously.
Let's move!
It's Leo! We got a situation!
I don't know who these guys are
but they're armed to the teeth!
Jo's still here, send Jango!
Make a hard right, now!
Whaddaya think I am?
Some kinda racecar driver?
Old man...
Stay here, Leo, don't move!
Yeah...
These are my-- No...
they're not my memories...
Someone--someone's
watching me...!
But who?!
Ah-ha!
Found you, bastard!
Don't be shy!
Quit playing hard to get
and come down from there!
Can't get down by yourself?
Then let me help you!
Great! Just what I need!
Son of a bitch!
It's about time
you showed yourself!
Don't do it!
Wha--?!
Why are you... doing this?
What will this accomplish?!
That figures...
Just like all the rest...
You got a death wish!
Damn, he's strong...
and well trained...
Doesn't seem like a cybot pilot.
What's the matter?!
Lost the will to fight?!
Listen buddy, I am in no
mood to fight you either...
I think maybe we just got
off on the wrong foot.
Don't suppose you've seen a
giant cybot pass through here.
My hands are still tingling...
That's a hell of
a sword you've got.
No... I see now, it's not
the sword that's mighty,
it's the man who wields it...
Huh? Of all the times...
Yeah, I know...
Real tough girl, huh?
What's wrong?
You're not eating?
This village is ancient.
Are you alone here?
Have you been here a long time?
You're a pretty quiet guy...
Were you born here
in this village...?
Then why are you here?
What happened to everyone else?
Thanks. The fish
was really good...
Have you got any water?
He doesn't talk at all...
Bet something terrible
happened here.
I understand ...
You were brought to this
village get rid of that demon.
But, you couldn't defeat it.
You and the others...
fought that thing...
with everything you had
to try and save the people
of this village...
But you couldn't protect
them, could you?
And, now you alone remain
here... to exact your revenge.
Tell me... Is that thing still
hiding in the mountains?
Finally decided to come out
and show your face, huh?!
No, wait!
You can't kill it with a sword!
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
The roars of the steel demon
echo across the battlefield
and stir a hidden
memory from Jo's past.
The ancient warrior awakes!
Next Burst Angel:
"Dueling Angels."