To the rhythm!
Check it!
OK, fellas!
Yeah yeah party people
let's go let's turn it up
Let's rush in let's send it
flying let's attack let's dash
The battlefields are sacred,
Bakuretsu Tenshi,
Crazy Burst Angel
They're a bother, they're
cheeky, come on, blast 'em good!
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
We are the risma so charisma
We soar, really prisma (bomber)
Hey! It's danceable OK
shake it right now let's go
Gutsiness let's go beat
let's ride the rhythm tension
It goes flying frustration
Alright let's go let's get it on
loosey beauty get your body
Everybody, loosey
Be in full bloom, bluesy
Vividly, crazy
Fly up, angel
This is the place where
they're having the party?
It's totally luxurious!
Funny. I'd call it
totally tacky.
What...? Just Look at it!
It's super mega-cool!
I dunno, Amy. I don't
think I'm up for this...
These clothes, the limo,
I'm a little uneasy as it is.
but this is just too much.
So, what? You're not going in?
What do you mean?
Of course, I'm going in.
There's a five course Chinese
feast waiting in there for me.
I wouldn't miss
that for the world.
Let's make tracks to that food.
I swear, food is the only
thing you get any joy from.
It's food...
Nobody knows what's going to
happen from moment to moment.
You got to eat whenever you can.
Don't worry about it, Meg.
I'm sure you'll
live a long life.
You think so?
Yes. So you should try to
actually enjoy it a little.
I'll have you know
I'm using this body
to the fullest to
enjoy life every day!
You're only using two parts:
your mouth and your stomach.
You brat! When we get home--
Young ladies,
if you wouldn't mind
entering the ballroom this way.
See? He called me a lady.
Shows what you know!
Idiot.
So that's Don Laoban's
granddaughter, Sei?
What a beautiful young
woman she's become.
She just glows.
And that dress is perfect
for such a momentous day.
Wow... Sei's like a
celebrity in this place.
Hey, Meg, are you watching this?
Yep, she really is just
a mouth and a stomach.
You look more and more
like your mother every year.
If only she was still alive,
you wouldn't have to bear
so much on your own.
I don't really think
about Mother anymore...
Being raised by you
has made me into a truly
happy person, grandfather.
I am both proud and honored
to have a granddaughter
such as you: beautiful,
intelligent, and full of life.
If only all of our
young countrymen
could be half the
person you are.
Many have changed
in recent years,
I believe, because of this
country's poisonous influence.
You heard about the
bombing last week?
Yes... Of course.
The work of a radical
faction. Deplorable.
We value discipline, and
honor our pledge to the clan.
Our organization is a family.
For the family's prosperity,
each member has devoted
what strengths and
abilities they possess.
And the mark of the person
who puts the organization
above all else, who holds
the family together...
Is this, the Bai-Lan
Seal of the Dragon.
It is something I intend to pass
on to you someday, my child.
But Grandfather!
I would imagine you
know about the Kokuren.
Of course, our sister
organization from Japan.
But it's been years since
they severed their ties.
Yes. However, in order to
stamp out the radicals,
I have decided the time has come
to reunite the two families.
White Lotus and Black Lotus
will once again be one.
The best way to
ensure such a union
is through the bonds
of wedlock...
And I have nominated you as our
representative in this regard.
I have also invited
the man nominated
by the Kokuren aboard
this ship today.
So that's what
this party is for.
Of course, today is
just a formality.
I don't know
anymore than he does
if he will accept you
as a lifelong partner...
I just hope that you can try to
understand this old man's wishes
for his only granddaughter, whom
he loves more than life itself.
I understand. And as your
nominee from this family,
I will do my best
to represent us.
Thank you...
I'm very happy to
hear you say that.
Sir, the other party
has just arrived.
Yes. Thank you.
Grandfather, I can't.
As favor to me, wear the Seal
upon your chest today,
and represent Bai-Lan proudly...
And we shall forever
keep it our little secret.
I am grateful for your
invitation, Don Laoban.
It is I who am grateful...
I would like to introduce you
to my only granddaughter, Sei.
It is my pleasure.
No, The pleasure is all mine.
My name is Jay.
And I must tell you,
you are just as beautiful
as all of the rumors I've heard.
Wow... Sei's actually blushing.
Oh, man! We'll probably
never see that again!
Whoa! Check that out!
There's a ton of totally
hot boys guys over there!
Now, that's what
I call eye candy!
Yeah... Don't get your hopes up.
I bet those losers follow
their pretty-boy boss
around like mindless sheep.
Poor child, when will you learn?
With men, good looks
are all that matter!
What are you talking about?
Everyone knows brains
are more important.
No, it's looks that count!
You believe that?
Talk to them for five minutes,
tell me how it goes.
Come everyone...!
Let us all raise a toast to
Bai-Lan's beautiful young bride!
Look out!
Are you all right?
Oh, no. You ruined
your nice suit for me.
No way.
I wonder... What's that
party they went to for?
I bet the food
there is five-star.
What I wouldn't give to
learn from those chefs.
Then I'd spin your
heads with my cooking.
You hungry?
Oh, gosh, uh...
Don't be shy.
Sorry, I uh...
I had a late lunch!
That obnoxious little
walking computer...
She's been in the
bathroom forever.
Ohhh... That sofa looks
comfy enough to sleep on.
Isn't there anyone here...?
Ah, they're silk flowers.
All that food made
me so sleepy...
Oh man, but that move
Jay pulled was so cool!
I wish I could do
something like that!
I could be all like...
"Jo! Bad guys,
twelve o'clock...!
Got your back! Hiyaa!"...
That would so rule!
Who's there?!
Oh, no...!
That's the most expensive
vase on this ship!
What should I do?
Nothing to be done,
I suppose. After all...
"That which has shape is
ultimately destined to crumble."
How much do you think its worth?
Let's see... Ming Dynasty.
I'd say about a million.
Dollars?!
No!
Uh...
You wanna explain what
you're doing there?
The price of my silence.
Huh?
If I keep quiet, they won't
know who to pin the blame on.
Amy!
So, Meg. I see you
got a new boyfriend.
No, wait! It's not
what it looks like!
Don't just stand there.
Come on in.
It's great that you've found
someone you can connect with.
Ow!
And I got plenty more
where that came from,
if you don't watch
your mouth, kiddo.
Young girls are just
so cute when they argue.
Yeah, understood.
Now, I'm just waiting
for the signal, right?
Yes. Our preparations
are finished.
Who's that?
Dunno.
Something smells fishy.
Who's there?
What are you doing
here, little girl?
I... I can't find
the bathroom anywhere.
The bathroom?
Yeah, I can't hold it anymore.
Bathroom's that way,
if you gotta go so bad.
I don't understand.
What's 'that way' mean?
It means, it's at the stern.
Can you... Carry me there?
You can't be serious.
Ah... I'm gonna burst!
All right! Fine! I'll carry you!
Climb on... Hurry up, let's go.
Thanks, mister.
Whatever...
That girl's a
natural born devil.
But I swear that
bodyguard looks familiar.
Like one of Don Laoban's men...
Whatever he was saying
about 'preparations'
and a 'signal'
doesn't sound good.
Ooh, they're so hot!
Well, Sei...
I would very much
agree to my father
and your grandfather's plan,
as long as you are not
opposed to the thought.
If you do believe in this,
then we, the younger generation,
will be the new leaders.
I plan to crack the shell
of the old and begin anew.
You're quite the assertive one.
Got everything
figured out, don't you?
In my opinion, a great
organization can only
come into its own through
years of hard work...
That is the discipline my
grandfather always taught me.
"In the absence of
harmony with tradition,
the organization cannot grow."
I've heard that one a lot.
I can tell.
Looks like the conversation
is getting lively. Good, good.
Don Laoban...
Sei is not only beautiful,
but a very sagacious young lady.
Oh, thank you...
You are correct, but she
is still inexperienced.
I hope you will give
her your guidance.
As long as we are here together,
I'd like to ask a favor of
you, if you don't mind.
And that is...?
As a symbol of the era
when The White Lotus
and The Black Lotus
were one and the same...
The Dragon Seal of Bai-Lan
pairs together with this,
the Seal of Kokuren...
I would like them to be
displayed here together.
If I may have permission.
The Seals are passed down
through the generations
by the leaders
of both clans.
I am hoping that you
will allow me to
experience the depth
of that responsibility.
You fail to understand.
The Dragon Seal is a
mark of high lineage
bestowed upon us by the Emperor.
All members of
Bai-Lan have sworn
undying loyalty to
whomever possesses it.
And it is for that reason,
its use in public is
strictly forbidden.
Please accept my apologies.
That is unfortunate.
Perhaps we can begin
the next performance.
What are you doing?
Grandfather!
What is the meaning
of this, Jay?
I said it was a performance.
A performance...?
What the hell are you planning?
I guess you could say I'm
staging a coup, "Grandfather."
What?
See? I told you those hot guys
weren't worth the trouble.
Yeah... Reality can really
bite sometimes... Right.
Meg, wait!
"Trust in your superiors."
"Follow the
organization's customs."
I've heard every one
of your ancient sayings.
You're living in
the wrong century.
I can make the organization
greater than it has ever been...
Now, where's the Dragon Seal?!
Leave my grandfather alone!
I don't think that
hard-headed girl
quite understands
this situation.
Or maybe you want
to die together
for the sake of a measly
rock. In which case...
I'll be happy to help you out.
How dare you pull this
in front of family!
Grandfather...
Are you trying to toy with me?
Hand over the pendant, Sei.
Hang on, Sei, I'm coming!
Who are you, girly?
Y'know? I surrender.
Sei, you must protect the Seal!
Do not let her off this ship!
Get after her! Topside, now!
Let me go... That hurts!
Okay, I'm kidding--
Post guards outside the door.
Have the rest come with me.
Yes, sir.
Hang on, Stephanie!
I'm here to save you.
Noooo! You moron! Look!
They're right behind you!
Ah, I told you!
Meg, please, you gotta wake up.
Aw, such senseless
violence... Now...
What are you doing to her?
Observing... her chi.
But isn't that, like,
unscientific voodoo?
Do not judge! They say,
"Illness begins with energy."
She has quite an appetite...
It's so strong that her chi
flow is out of balance.
You hit that nail on the head!
I can make her better than
she was. Stronger. Faster.
Huh?
Get back!
Come on, not you again.
You, hold it right there!
That's unreal.
She is far more powerful
than even I predicted.
You gotta tell me
what you did to her...
Did you use a modifying
chip or something?
Oh, no...
What I did was simply open
her "battle chi" pathway,
and direct all of her
tremendous hunger into it.
That's amazing!
Who are you anyway?
Who, indeed...
I was in the movies once.
Long, long ago.
[TEXT] This feature film is
a story based on true events.
What? It's over? That stinks.
Hello, Jo?
Yeah, it's me,
what do you need Amy?
It's terrible!
You've got to get here now!
What's terrible?
Some airhead pretty-boy betrayed
Sei, and then he hit Meg,
and then some freaky old dude
turned Meg into a wild tiger
and she tore through a
whole line of hot guys!
Amy, pretend I don't know
what you're talking about...
and try to explain it again.
Look... Sei's in a pinch.
She needs you.
We're on a ship...
It's in the harbor.
The one with the big
dragon's head on top.
What was that?
Something about a
pretty-boy and a tiger?
That scooter I saw outside
belongs to you, right?
Uh-huh. Why?
Gotta little favor t'ask.
Go easy! It's not paid off yet!
Have you gotten it out
of your system yet, Sei?
Or do you want the
suffering to really begin?
That's right. That's my girl.
Smart move.
Quit trying to worm
your way out of this!
So, this is the Dragon Seal.
From now on the
organization is mine alone!
Uh, Meg? You're the
only one left now, Jay!
Even if you could escape,
we'd just hunt you down.
So... What is it you
plan to do with me?
It's not up to me.
I'll have to wait for
the elders to vote.
If you are still deemed an
asset by the Organization,
you will be allowed to live.
There you go with the
organization again.
You know, you still
don't get it.
I believe A person should choose
his or her life as their own...
And living in the
shackles of tradition
and obligation is not the
life I choose for myself.
I have no intention of
letting this end here.
And I'll be taking the Seal!
Whoa, what just
blew up down there?!
Oh, it's Jo!
Hey, Jo!
Aw, crap!
Jo, that guy up
there's the bad guy!
He's the one who hit Meg!
I've done it!
I have beaten destiny!
Nice move, Jo!
Meg was totally off the walls!
Even Jo was shocked
at what she did!
Next party, you're taking
me so I can see up close.
Just one problem...
I don't seem to
remember a thing.
And, Kyohei...
Sei said she'd reimburse
you in full for the scooter.
Isn't that nice?
It is... But Sei's not
coming today, right?
Didn't she have other plans.
We value discipline, and
honor our pledge to the clan.
Our organization is a family.
And living in the shackles
of tradition and obligation
is not the life I
choose for myself.
I won't run...
I would never run
from my own destiny.
I don't know why I can't move
My mind is lost in this cloud
No one even hears my voice
and my tears fall to the ground
It's like my feelings of
loneliness are falling too
The truth is that we
all just want to smile
and smile with each other
It hurts inside
when we don't...
we don't... we don't
know what to say
I only hope that
someone will be there,
and be watching over me
so take my hand,
we'll walk tonight
underneath the sky
Amy is lured into an electronic
labyrinth teeming with desires.
What awaits her on this
mysterious and untamed frontier?
Next Burst Angel:
Uncharted Cyberspace.