I said that... I didn't
wanna see you again...
'Cause... We've
never gotten along...
But... I need... your help.
Maybe things'll be
different this time.
Maybe we'll have a
happier relationship...
Oh, who am I fooling?!
I've gained weight again!
Why am I always such a
fatso after New Year's...?
What's Karasuma gonna say
if he sees me like this?
You're too fat.
You're right,
I am fat! That's it!
I'm going on a strict low-cal,
low-carb diet as of this moment!
If I had known, I wouldn't have
made these rice
cake pizzas for lunch.
I'll just go make something
healthier for you, okay?
Don't bother!
Um, hello...?
Hey, Mikoto...! What?
A ski trip?! Hell's to
the yeah, sista! I'm down!
Wow, that sure was short notice.
Yep... Someone got sick
and couldn't make it,
so that opened up
a spot. Lucky me.
Well, you said you
wanted to exercise...
So this is perfect.
Yep! I'm gonna
burn up the slopes
while I burn off the calories!
Bye! See ya, Sis!
Have fun now and be careful.
Don't you worry.
I'll be fine.
I just need to warm up.
Thank you. Come again.
All right! Got my screentones!
But, man, were they pricy!
I gotta have 'em, though,
if I'm gonna pull off this
assignment Gotou gave me.
I'll give you thirty pages
in the annual spring special.
Draw me something with drive!
With spirit! With passion!
Yeah! I'll draw it, all right!
You'll draw what?
Draw?! I'm not drawing,
your face is drawing, shut up!
Sorry... Kinda freaked
out a little there.
Yeah... I noticed.
Let's see if we can
make it happen again.
Huh?
Some friends and I are leaving
for a ski trip later today.
So, what's it to me?
Tenma's going.
Good one.
Tenma skiing?
And bundled up like an Eskimo?
She'll be the cutest
little snow bunny ever!
Oh, man, I'd love to see that!
I wanna go, too! Crap! I can't!
I got a deadline
to meet, and besides,
I don't have the money
to go. Damn it all...!
Guess I'll have to
bide my time here away
from my little arctic fox.
I hope you ladies
have a good time.
Interesting.
Hey, Itoko. I'm home.
Gone on a trip to
Okinawa with Youko.
Back in three days. Take care.
I can't wait to have
some Soki-soba noodles.
Hang in there, Kenji.
You gotta be kidding me!
So you took off and
locked me out again, huh?!
Well, I'm not as dumb as I look.
I had a feeling you'd
pull this crap on me again,
so I took the liberty of
getting a key made.
Checkmate, Itoko!
For you to be reading this,
you must have secretly
made a duplicate key.
When I get back,
I'm going to get you for this.
And here she is.
Figure skating's star of
the moment, Fukuda Kyoko,
with her first-ranked
short program.
What a surprise!
She's already launched
into an incredibly
steady Biellmann Spin!
Look at that form!
She's not shaking at all!
Look at her go!
The crowd is going absolutely
wild with excitement!
She's still spinning!
How long can she keep this up?!
Maybe I should try that...
What a performance!
I will! I'll do it!
I'm going to learn
the art of ice skating!
The ice may be chilly,
but the audience
reception is anything but.
What do I do?!
What do I do...?! Ichijo!
Yeah!
Woo-hoo.
Oh, man! I just love the feel
of fresh snow in the morning!
Yeah, me, too!
It feels even better
when your whole body's in it.
Yeah... I'll pass.
Hey... Guys, where's Tenma?
Yippee!
That was so fun!
Hey, what are you
guys looking at?
You're incredible... OMG!
Ya think...?
Hey, maybe I could even teach
Yakumo a thing or
two about skiing.
I'm no good at this!
Please help me!
I'm sorry you're such
a klutz, Yakumo.
Guess what they say about people
having hidden talents is true...
Check it... What do
you think of my talent?
Uh... I don't know
what do you mean Akira?
You wouldn't understand.
That was awesome!
That jump totally kicked ass!
And we should know!
We're on the ski
team at Otowa U!
College boys!
Oh cool, a heart!
I gotta admit, he's good...
So, ladies...?
Want some close, personal
instruction...? What the--?
I don't think
they're into us, dude!
Hey!
Come on! We were
just getting started!
Come back!
I guess they were kinda fun...
But we could so do better.
You can't deny they knew
how to rock those ski jumps.
They'll be back.
Let's play hard-to-get.
Tenma, how scandalous.
I love it!
Better watch it...
Karasuma finds out,
you'll be in big trouble.
Oh, he won't know
about it! He's not here!
Except I'm right here.
He's here!!!
Whoa, Karasuma?
Dig the suit, man.
But why are you here?
Well, it's a long story.
Good to see all of you.
Hold up... Are you
challenging me or something...?
I'm the mascot here.
Get your own turf!
You're acting crazy again...
K... Karasuma...?
I'm sure he heard what I said!
He'll think I'm a tramp!
Geez, Tenma...
Then why did you say it?
I don't know!
Everyone was telling me
how great I could ski
and I got cocky!
It's okay. Stop crying...
I'll help you smooth everything
over with him, all right?
You really mean it?
All right, this is
what we're gonna do:
we're all gonna jump
at the same time
and spell out
"I love you" to Karasuma.
Tenma goes first,
then me, then Mikoto.
Do you think we're
that coordinated?
Last I checked we weren't
professional skiiers.
Just sayin'.
Don't be so scared.
It's just like that
jump Tenma made earlier...
Let's go! There's Karasuma!
No backing out now!
It's do-or-die time!
Ready... Go!
Karasuma... This... is!
This is how I feel about you!
Futo-sugi.
That means...
"You're too fat" in Japanese.
No, hold on! We got
the kanji all wrong!
No, it's okay...
I ate too much over New Year's.
I need to lose some of it.
Now let me show you how
I feel about your message.
Karasuma, wait!
Bye.
He's so magnificient...
I'm getting cold.
Wanna head back?
Mm-hm.
Good! All of you made it.
Ice skating, huh...?
I'm a little surprised you
wanna learn how to do it.
Hmph.
Still, there's no way we'd
miss your big debut on the ice.
Yeah...
You know... it's
my first time, too.
And it gives me a chance
to get close to Imadori...
Thanks, Lara.
You know... All this
ice brings me back...
It reminds me of the
frozen tundra I saw
when I lived in Alaska.
So tell me... Do I look pretty?
Lara, you might wanna go change!
Is it that bad?
No human should ever
take part in this sport!
Uh... Oh gosh...
Just don't let go
of me, okay, Harry?
Don't worry.
Just relax a little.
Easy...
Hang in there, Satsuki!
You'll get it eventually!
I hope so! Look at you,
you're just like a pro!
Stop, you're embarrassing me!
Hey, something wrong, Lara?
Don't tell me you can't skate.
Is it too hard for
a gorilla like you?
Oye! Imadori...! Teach me how
to skate and I won't kill you!
No problem, baby,
but only if you skate
over to me first, 'kay...
Come on, gorilla girl...
Why you...!
Ice is your weakness, huh?
People say revenge is
a dish best served cold...
All that skating made me hungry!
Hey, you did really well out
there for your first time.
I just wish I could
be as good as you.
I never knew you were such
an accomplished skater.
But I'm not.
I just take Kosuke here a lot
so I get in a lot of practice.
You could have fooled me.
You were the best one out there.
I don't get it.
I usually dominate
any sport I take part in,
but this ice skating...
Hey, guys, did you
get one of these?
The Yagami Cup Figure Skating
Pairs Tournament...? Hey...
Guys, It's actually
being held here today.
Check out the First Prize.
Oh, wow!
What...? "Today's
fabulous First Prize is
a brand new
washer and dryer?"...
I have to enter
this contest right now!
Karen?
Sorry, I got excited...
I need that wa--I mean,
it sounds fun!
Hmph...
We're always rivals,
aren't we...?
We'll compete
against each other!
Are you nuts?
You don't even
know how to skate.
But then again,
there is one surefire way
for you to win this thing and
that's under my firm tutelage
Are you serious?!
Karen, I'm dirty!
Karen, my gym
clothes aren't clean!
Karen, I've got a stain!
Karen!
With a washer and dryer,
I'd be a cleaning machine!
I've gotta hit a
homerun on this one!
Welcome to the Yagami Cup
Figure Skating Pairs Tournament.
Mr. Kobayashi and I will
be your commentators.
All pairs to the rink, please.
Hey? Imadori...
Are you sure your
plan is going to work?
Yeah, don't worry
about it, babe.
I have to try my best to win...
for the family!
Ah, yes. You and I are
going to fire this place up.
Sure you don't want to compete?
It's still not
too late to enter.
Oh, thank you, Harry...
But I can't skate!
I hope you're ready
for the embarrassment
of your life, Queen Kong!
First up is the pair
of Ichijo and Tougou.
Both are students
who attend Yagami High.
Ichijo appears to be at home on
the ice, doesn't she...? Oh?
Hold on, is that a...
Mr. Kobayashi?
Kosuke, I did it!
Yes! Tougou's doing a
rarely-witnessed Alaska Spin!
An impressive move on the part
of Tougou, but it's
against the rules...
He's doing it alone.
You're right.
He's not including his partner,
Ichijo, into his routine.
I think he forgot this
is a "pairs" competition.
Hey, what are you doing?
Unfortunately, we're going to
have to disqualify this pair.
Sorry.
Hmph. You judges
don't appreciate
my rugged individualism, do you?
Kosuke, I'm sorry
I let you down.
Next up is the pair
of Lara and Imadori.
I understand that
Lara hails from Mexico.
It'll be interesting to
see how she fares on the ice.
I'll show you!
I'll show all of you!
There is not a sport
I cannot master!
Looks like we're up.
Let's go do it, Lara...
Let's make an impression
they'll never forget!
Yeah!
Lara...! That's a
speed skating outfit!
That's a mistake only
a novice would make.
Imadori, you tricked me!
There's nothing you can
do about it on the ice,
though, ya big dummy!
Why you!
Ima--I will kill you!
You are dead meat!
Aw, did that hurt?
It sure looked like it.
Uh...
In an amazing twist,
Lara has gone barefoot...
And it appears she's pursuing
her partner across the ice!
Now a perfect finishing move...
Yeah, maybe if this was
pro wrestling... am I right?
Bravo! Bravo! Working a
luchadore move like that
into your routine is
a stroke of pure genius!
Do you think we should...?
Leave? Yes.
Huh...?! What in
the hell?! Aw, dammit!
Don't tell me I fell asleep!
Wait...! How did I get
away from the kotatsu?!
Great! I'm already
catching a cold!
Huh?
Wait, what's goin' on?
It feels like there's
somethin' in there!
But what?!
I... I'm dreaming!
That's the only explanation!
I mean, it's
physically impossible
for a giraffe to fit under a
table that size, right...? Oh!
Man, this is a vivid dream!
Feels like I'm being touched,
but come on, get real.
He's like sixteen feet tall.
There's no way he'd
even fit, no way at all...
A giraffe? In here?
That's crazy talk!!
Pyo-Py-Pyo... Pyotr!
Holy crap! It is you!
You were under the Japanese
style table with a heating unit
under it, which I earlier
referred to as a kotatsu?
She needs help.
Please, my dear friend.
She needs you.
What? Who needs me?
Tenma, in danger...!
Your keen, animal senses
detected it, didn't they?!
Help please.
Argh! What is it?!
Is she trapped under an
avalanche... cold and alone?
Or is some grabby little pervert
chasing her...?! Who cares?!
I gotta move...! Onward beast!
Never fear, sweet lady!
We ride for your salvation!
Hi, Sis...
Yakumo, are you still sick?
Uh-huh.
Here. I made this for you.
A bunny?
Sorta.
Thank you so much, Sis...
It feels so nice and cool.
Really...? I'm so glad!
You're the best.
Tenma's sister!
Hey, you're not
looking so good...
You feel like...
You're burning up!
I better put you to bed, quick!
A little bed rest should
do you some good.
And here I was thinkin'
your sister was in trouble.
I hope you feel better...
Well, I have to go.
Got a deadline to meet.
Another comic.
The spring special...
Iori...
Thanks you so much.
It feels so nice and cool.
Thank you.
♪ ending song ♪
A cruise to the
south islands, huh?
Yeah, sure, I'll go with ya...!
Next time, on School Rumble:
"Southern Rainbow 2-C!
Ya'akumo of the Mysterious
Island! The Seven Seas!"
Oh, yeah, that Four-Eyed bastard
is still on that kite, huh?