This is Ryuhei Suga.
He's in the basketball club and
is good friends with Asou.
In exchange for his family's
famous pickled eggplant recipe,
he gets free ramen at the
Asou family restaurant,
and also tries to score with the
girls who hang around Asou.
Talk about pathetic.
Hey!
Why don't we have the
girls' team over again?
All right.
Here's your pickled eggplant
and rice bran ramen.
Uh... thanks.
Yo! The stewpot's
startin' to boil!
Man, it just doesn't
seem like autumn
without a little
sweet potato stew!
Say...! You're Mikoto's
boyfriend, aren't you?
No-no, just her
basketball coach.
Hi... Good to see
you again, sweetheart...!
Made up your mind
to go out with me yet?
Uh, well...
I'm still enjoying being
single, so I'll have to pass.
Kids...! There's plenty to go
around, so everybody eat up!
The last thing
I need is leftovers!
Yay!
Hey... isn't this your
first time at a Suou
family stew party?
Yes... are you
sure it's all right
for us to drop in like this?
Of course it is!
As long as we bring an
ingredient it's totally fine...!
You brought meat, right?
Huh...? You didn't say
I was supposed to bring it!
Huh?
If you're lookin' for meat,
I got this package.
I thought that you and I, I mean
all of us, could share it.
Great, we got meat, woo-hoo!
Yeah! Pass the stew
and get out the bowl!
I love that chick.
Well, this totally reeks...
I've got no problem
with Ichijou,
but how'd I get stuck at a table
with the jerk who broke my arm
and the girl who
ruined my sneakers?!
Give it a rest, you pansy, you
know I didn't do it on purpose!
Um... you've gotta calm down,
Imadori, you'll
aggravate your injury.
Now then...!
Why don't we take a look
at what kind of ingredients
everybody brought...!
I brought the vegetables!
Just a minute, you guys!
You can't just throw
in stuff on your own!
Lara, wait!
They're leftover
jumbo burgers from work!
The fries are good too.
Oh, no!
This is a real man's ingredient!
The king of spices,
habanero chili peppers!
Too spicy!
I brought some udon noodles.
I guess there's nothing
wrong with udon noodles...
but you can't just go tossing
all that stuff in
willy-nilly like that!
Yoohoo...! Can I try
a bowl of your stew?!
Wowee... it sure looks
kind of dark, doesn't it?
I think there's some kind of
chemical reaction taking place.
Oh, a top secret experiment,
huh? Lemme try some!
Yum!
Huh?!
Delicious!
Okay then, I'll give it a try.
Mmm, it's funny-looking,
but the flavor is really great!
Well, what the heck.
I'm gonna barf.
That stuff is even
too much for me.
What...? You are dumb!
This is the best stew ever!
Yeah, I really like it too!
Thanks you guys!
Let's let Lara finish
off this stewpot...
we'll start again
from the top...
I've got some veggies left.
Okay.
I'll just be hangin'
out over here.
Oh... okay.
I'll start cutting
up the vegetables.
Now, while no one's looking...
Thanks.
It's payback time
for my sneakers!
They didn't notice!
Yakumo... can't we eat yet?
Because I'm starving
to death here!
Come on, Sis, didn't you eat
some of that dark stuff earlier?
This party is like a
delicatessen of stewpot flavors.
It's 'cause there's such
a wide range of ingredients.
Here, Sis, all done!
Hooray...!
Hm, looks like I'm a little
late getting to the party.
Poor Yakumo has
been slaving over
that hot stew pot
this whole time!
Now to show her what
a gentleman I can be!
Here, Yakumo... have some.
Uh, thanks, Hanai, but
you don't have to do...
Come on, no need
to be shy now...
No, it's just that, I... uh...
Oh, forgive me,
is it still too hot?
I-I'll pass, thanks.
It's just about ready...
Now to slip some
to Lara or Tougou.
Darn it! How am I supposed
to get a hold of this...?
I'm really sorry
about your arm...
here, why don't you go
ahead and have the first bite.
Gracias!
Is this batch really that good?
It's the savor of friendship.
It tastes so bitter...
Is there something
the matter, Yakumo?
You don't have to be shy,
just open up and say, "Aah!"
Hanai, I can do it myself.
No, no, it's no
trouble, come on,
let me handle the stewpot now,
you've been at it all day.
Ah...
Please, I'm telling you,
I don't need your help.
Hm?
Napoleon...? Are you hungry too?
That pork miso soup
is so delicious!
Huh?
Now you make sure you eat lots
and grow up to be a
nice big fat pig, Napoleon.
Yeah, there's nothing like
a nice pork miso, is there?
Oh, Harima, I had no idea you
were a fan of pork miso too!
I just love the stuff!
It's so rich and hearty!
There, now...
it's all nice and cool...
and ready for your sweet,
delicate little mouth... ahhh...
A pig?!
Oh, my!
Napoleon!
Puerco?
Mister pig!
Have some more...
I don't want it!
Now it's a party!
Napoleon!
And that was the end
of this year's stew party.
It was a lot of fun.
Make sure to invite us
back next year, Mikoto.
The pork miso was delicious.
Man, yesterday's earthquake
caught me off guard!
Yeah, it turned out to
be a pretty small one.
I know, they said it was
only a magnitude of three.
Aw, geez!
What happened to you?
Yesterday...
Yeah?
Okay... What?
I was...
I was deeply involved
in some personal research
when the earthquake hit.
My first reaction was to secure
my research materials,
which were stacked
on my shelves.
I didn't care about myself!
I had to protect my babies!
That was a little too close!
Hee-hee!
I'm missing it!
One careless moment
was all it took.
Hey, at least you have
your priorities straight!
That's what happens when you
never throw anything away!
Were they really
research materials?
Don't question me!
You couldn't understand
how I feel about my
five hundred volumes!
Not true, I buy ten
volumes a month myself.
Really...? And how do you manage
to store all your treasures,
Miss Librarian?
It's a snap...!
I keep a box on hand
and I put all the books
I've studied inside of it!
Can't fit something in,
I throw it out.
If you like, I can come by
and help you organize.
No, thanks,
that's not necessary.
There are some things
I can't show to girls.
Huh?
Disgusting...! You stay
away from me, you pig!
Okay, you get a box...
keep only the stuff
you can fit inside it...
and toss out the rest.
Finally... It is done.
I think that turned
out pretty good... huh?
Oh, son of a--!!
All right... What's
the big emergency...?
This better be good.
Take your pick.
Huh?
I see... so you've decided
to get rid of them after all.
I gotta say, this
is quite a collection.
But I've got a date...
besides, I don't want
any of this stuff.
Look...
This video is like
from 1984, it's ancient,
it's way older than I am.
I'm very disappointed
in you Sergeant Imadori.
How could you be
so naïve? Here. Watch.
Gee, what do you know?
It's boring.
Patience...
It's coming... There!
Ho...!
One shining moment that
lit the darkness of my soul.
I can't throw it away.
I don't blame you.
My hat's off to your taste.
All right! Sergeant
Imadori returning to base
with relief supplies!
Just be very careful
how you handle those,
they are quite delicate!
Wasn't that Imadori...?
Nishimoto...
What's the big deal, yo?
You've just been to
the school infirmary,
haven't you, Corporal?
Ack...! How the
hell'd you know that?
Elementary, my dear friend...
Your whole body reeks
of medical disinfectant
and Chanel Perfume...
I could tell
with my eyes closed.
Fine... you got me...
I went to see Ms. Tae.
I have something
that's perfect for you.
Are there any naughty
boys out there now?
Uh, Doctor?
Oh, there is, there's a naughty
little patient right here!
Doctor, what are you doing?!
I'm afraid naughty boys need
to be punished very severely.
Dear, sweet god...
the "Infirmary of
Forbidden Secrets" series!
And get a load of her,
that actress looks just
like Ms. Anegasaki!
You... sure about this?
Yes... You've proven
your passion for the skin.
Uh... how's it goin'...?
You know, if these
are in your way,
I'd be glad to take
them all off your hands.
You need more
self-discipline, Trainee Nara.
Only three to a person.
I can't believe
you're just gonna
give me something
that's so totally amazing...!
Is... there some sorta catch?
Just take it before
I change my mind.
Please share your
bounty with us as well!
Feel free to choose
whatever you like.
Sir, you're too
kind for words...!
I should've expected as much
from the world famous
Commander "Buddha" Nishimoto!
If you could spare one for me
I'd gladly sacrifice my life!
Don't give up
your life just yet.
Word on the street is you're
giving away all your treasures!
Think I can score a disk?
No way!
Aw... What's the problem?
I'm not giving one of
my children to a man
who has his own woman!
Come on, man,
don't be like that...
Everyone chooses their own path,
but if you continue
down this one...
A world of carnage will follow.
...yeah, can't wait
'til I get home...
...test these out tonight...
...ninjas...
It's for the best, my lovelies.
It's for the best.
Hey, I heard you were having
some sort of trouble, Nishimoto!
Is that Hanai...? I don't
remember inviting you over!
No need to be embarrassed...
I know the other guys
have already been by!
Right, That's because uh...
Come now, there's
no need to spell it out.
I understand they came over
to help you clean up your room.
As class president,
I'm obligated to help.
So have no fear...
The answer to all of
your problems is here!
Now then, let's get started!
Well, hello there...
This is... This is...! Th-th--
This is filth...!
I'm confiscating these!
No! Wait...! You can't...!
You can't take my
children...! Please...!
Will you let go?!
That guy is some piece of work!
He has no idea the kind
of damage this
could do to the class!
I, Haruki Hanai,
must find a way to dispose
of these properly... huh?
Whoa!
Oh boy!
Unbelievable!
Oh, man, that was close!
I really gotta be more careful!
Yeah, good save, if these things
had scattered all
over the street then I...
Stare...
Oh, hi... there's nothing
wrong here, officer.
Just remember, no matter
what impurities a man carries
with him today,
if he does the right thing
he can still conquer tomorrow!
Hey... is that you, Hanai?
Wait!
It's not what you're thinking!
No, Yakumo, this is just
some trash I'm getting rid of,
it doesn't even belong to me!
Hey, Hanai!
Uh... O... Kay...
I wonder what his problem is...
And what's up with the bag?
Mother Superior...
where's Sister Adiemus?
She's handling the
confessional today.
And so I sent my beloved
children off to foster homes.
Pray... your sins
have been forgiven.
Thank you...
my children have
been saved as well.
Sister... I'd like you
to hear my story next.
Yes... of course...
please, go ahead.
You see, I was carrying
somewhat sinful treasures,
I-I mean, some sinful items,
when a girl
I really like saw me, and
I'm afraid I frightened her.
I should mention,
they were the property
of a very sinful friend...
not mine... and I was just
going to dispose of them,
I wasn't going to
watch them late at night
or anything like that,
so before you, God,
and baby Jesus...
I declare my innocence!
So... then why
did you come here?
Oh. I hadn't thought of that.
Uh... just the same...
Perhaps you should
take this opportunity
to repent towards this
girl you say you like
so much for having
frightened her so badly.
Yes! That's it...! I repent.
God hears your prayers as well.
Thank you, Sister.
No doubt about it,
that was Hanai.
Excuse me, Sister.
Yes? Hello?
My name's Tanaka, and I'm in
the Yagami High Soccer Club.
I like this girl, Toki Nagayama,
who's in the same class as me...
but I don't have
the nerve to tell her.
If we win our
next game, though...
More love troubles, huh?
There's been a
lot of this lately.
So I swear I'll do my best!
Hm?!
Uh...
It wasn't a confession of sin,
but I still hope it goes well.
Um... Please read this.
Please!
Wait. You mean me?!
Yes...!
I'll wait for your answer!
Hey! Hold on!
I confess my love...
Are you for real, or is
this some kind of mind game?
Sorry about that!
I was just saying it
to see what it felt like.
But you do love me.
No, no, no!
You don't have to hide
your feelings, it's natural.
Okay, I do love you
Akira, but not that way.
Tell me, how did it
feel the first time
you told someone you loved them?
I make it a point not to
look back on things like that.
But more importantly,
why would you ask me?
I don't really know.
Interesting...
Are you planning on getting
a boyfriend sometime soon?
Or... other... friend?
Oh, gosh... me with a boyfriend?
I don't think so...!
It's all I can do just
to take care of myself!
It's just that...
when I'm consulted
about matters of the heart...
I have no idea
what advice to give.
I don't think you need to...
Ultimately it's
their own problem.
Yeah, Even so...
It's today... the match.
Oh, they've already started!
Man, I wish I knew who he was...
Oh well... That might be a
breach of confidentiality,
so it's probably
better I don't know.
Get around him!
Finally, some action!
That's it, go!
One down!
Tanaka!
Wow, that's three down!
There's only two left!
Four down!
Five down!
Do iiiiiit!!
Incredible!
So it's all over then?
He's the one.
Was she crying?
I'm the guy who came
in the other day...
We lost the game... I invited
her... to come watch...
She cheered for me like crazy...
but for some reason...
I couldn't even say thank you.
But still... even
though you didn't win
the game like you'd hoped...
you did your best...
Why not... tell her
how you feel anyway?
No... I think I've
had enough for one day.
But you can bet
I'll win the next game!
Then I'll tell her!
So long!
Wait!
Hold on... I, uh...
Good luck!!
Go Tanaka!!
I know you can do it.
Sister Adiemus?
Is that any way to
behave in the sanctuary?
You're awfully chipper today.
Something good happen to you?
That's private.
So... how're you
going to answer him?
Huh...?! You mean the letter?
That's private too.
This is Ryuhei Suga.
Talk about pathetic.
Wow!
Sara, I gotta say,
you're lookin' great today!
You really dress this place up!
That reminds me...
Asou was telling
me the other day
that you really bring
something special to the shop.
Really...?
Asou said that, about me?
And here it is!
Pickled eggplant
and rice bran ramen!
Uh... thanks.
I'm Tenma Tsukamoto!
With great looks,
a perfect figure, and brains,
I'm the campus idol!
Next time on School Rumble:
"Perfect, Forbidden! Entry,
Forbidden! Shorts, Forbidden!"
Hey! Who're you?