Time to take a break.
Damn! She's cute!!!
I have got to
ask that girl out!!
Itoko! If you keep on
showing off like that,
all the guys are gonna
start hitting on you!
Oh, come on.
It happens all the time
when we're at home, Youko.
I can handle that.
But if any more
guys come after you,
you won't have
any time left for me.
Okay, I understand.
I'll play with you tonight,
but for now I need
some time by myself.
Yay!!
That's so cool!
Is that guy a professional?!
Hold on... It can't be--
Why am I so cold?
What the--?!
Tenma...?
I can't find Harima.
Do you know where he is?
No... I have no idea.
I can't believe Harima
had the nerve to try
and sneak into
Yakumo's room last night!
He's just a big,
stupid, hairy ape!
Don't worry, Yakumo...
I'll protect you!
Hi there. Name's Iori, right?
Listen, I could really use
a friend right about now.
Hey! Come back!!
Look! There's an old bum!
Let's see if he's still alive!
Stop it!! Of course
I'm alive! Somebody help me!
Uh, Harima! What on
earth happened to you?
Well... for some reason,
I woke up outside,
tied up in a sleeping bag.
What's weird is I'm sure I fell
asleep in my room last night.
Hey, Tenma!
Do you know anything?
Perhaps you have the
problem of sleepwalking.
Oh, forget it.
I have to hurry up
and finish my pages!
Hey! Do you have any idea
where all my things are?
Oh! You mean that big bag with
all that useless junk in it?
It's in the guest house.
Guest house?
Oh no! My manuscript
could be ruined!
All your clothes
are out there too!
Damn it!
This is where you're
gonna stay from now on!
What? You serious?
Wait. Tenma, what are you doing?
Hey! Let me handle this, Yakumo.
I know you like him a lot.
But, he is still
a high school boy,
and that means he's only
got one thing on his mind.
It says so in "Modern Teen"!
All right! Let's finish this!
You are not allowed to
step foot in this house!
And, stay away from Yakumo!
Ya get me?
What are you talking about?
You know exactly what
I'm talkin' about!
Okay... Not gonna lie.
I have no clue.
So, you're gonna
play dumb, huh?!
You need to stop trying
to act all innocent, Harima...
You're guilty! Just admit it!
What is this about?
What am I guilty of?
Tenma, I don't
know what happened,
but don't you think
you're overdoing it?
Oh, Yakumo. Don't be so naïve.
You had a really close
call yesterday, you know.
We were getting along so well.
Why is she so mad at me now?
Okay.
I just need to calm myself down,
so I can figure this out.
Tenma must be in love with me.
And she actually
wanted me to confess.
But then I went into
Yakumo's room by mistake.
Now she's pissed!
So, she's actin' all crazy, ...
because she thinks I'm in
love with her little sister!
Don't you worry your
pretty little head, Tenma...
I'm gonna straighten
all this out tonight!
To make up for my
"screw up" yesterday,
and win back Tenma's heart,
I have to say somethin' that'll
make her all gooey inside.
I'm willing to die for you?
Uh... Please make me breakfast!
No, that's not right!
I got it! I'll just be honest...
and tell her how I feel!
Seriously!
Harima is so pathetic!
I did tell him off
pretty good though.
I guess I can let it go now.
Tonight my darling,
it's your turn!
You pervert!!
Get out of my house, now!
You couldn't have Yakumo,
so you came after me instead?!
You're a complete maniac!
But Tenma! That's not it all!
Just listen to me!
Son of a...
I really screwed up this time.
Now what the hell
am I supposed to do?
No Tenma... and no place
to finish my manuscript.
I made a reservation
at an awesome restaurant!
Really?!
It'll be ultimate
oral experience.
That could be me and Tenma,
if I hadn't messed things up.
Harima, my love.
Why don't we go to my place?
I'll make you a
fantastic dinner!
Oh, Tenma! You
finally understand!
Harima? What're you
doing over there?
Some punk was
giving me the stinkeye,
so I had to teach him a lesson!
Um, that was a statue.
Aw, I can't believe
you don't have
anywhere to go for Christmas.
You're like a sad little
stray puppy wandering
around in the freezing cold.
That really sucks.
Well, you know if you want to,
you could always come
and stay at my place.
Of course, it's not actually
my house, it's Hanai's dojo.
but, everyone is free to come
and go as they like there.
Yeah thanks,
but I really wouldn't want
to put you out or anything.
Then, where are you gonna go?
Don't worry about it...
I'll figure it out.
Hey man, it's your call.
See you later then.
In any case, I need to find
a way to make some money.
I got tissues. Does anybody
want some tissues?
Here ya go.
So, I had to buy a lot of food
for the Christmas
party at the dojo.
If you don't mind,
I could use your
help carrying these.
This is the living room.
Feel free to use the sofa,
and anything else ya need.
Sorry for imposing.
Don't worry about it.
You're home kinda late.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Something important came up.
So anyway, are
you hungry at all?
I guess I could eat something.
Do you really think
this is all right?
I mean letting me crash
at the dojo like this?
Man, I'm so hungry.
I'll have to grab
something from the kitchen.
She said it would be
okay to go wherever
I want as long as I keep
this worker's outfit on.
Sucks that I can't
wear my shades, though.
Refrigerator... Refrigerator...
Score! That's what
I'm talkin 'bout!
I miss the food
at Tenma's house.
The meals there
were somethin' else.
Hello? Is someone there?
Crap!! Mikoto's family!
What the hell is
Rich Girl doin' here?
Oh. Are you a worker
here or something?
Wait a second.
She doesn't know
who I am. Awesome.
Yes, that's right.
I was about to make
some coffee for Miss Suou.
All right! I gotta sell it!
If she recognizes me,
I'm totally screwed!
You know, I'm heading
up there anyway,
I could bring it to her for you.
I wouldn't dream of
asking you to do that.
This is all just a
part of my job, Miss.
The coffee will
be ready shortly,
no need to trouble yourself.
It's working!
Here is your coffee, miss.
Uh... Thank you!
What the hell is he doing?
I'll leave you alone then, Miss.
Thank you very much.
What the hell is she doing?
Yes!! Perfect!
Is there something wrong?
Oh, no. Just thinking.
Wait, sir, excuse me.
Crap! She couldn't
have figured me out!
My acting was perfect!
Sorry. But, Mikoto wanted
me to give this to you.
Did you drop it?
He just took it
without saying a thing.
What is his deal?
Does he always act like that?
Oh, yeah ...
Come to think of it,
he has always been a
little on the withdrawn side.
Oh...
So, what do ya think? Huh, Eri?
Feelin' a little bit hot
in your nether regions?
What are you talking about?!
Are you outta your mind?!
Although...
From the back at least,
he looked kinda nice...
If you know what I mean...
Oh, really?
Hey! Stop tryin'
to play matchmaker!
Damn it!
If she finds me out, she'll
never let me live it down!
It'll be all over!
I gotta get outta here!
Excuse me, sir?
What the hell'd ya do that for?
You should've seen your face!
I have to say, though, it is
really hard to tell it's you.
Nice disguise!
Yeah, whatever!
Anyway, I have to go out
and run some errands,
so I'm leaving you in charge.
Take care of the
house and be good.
Don't let me down!
What?! You're leaving
me here with her?
We can't very well leave her
here by herself, now, can we?
Don't worry, it'll be all right.
As far as she's concerned,
you're just a dude
who works here.
She's been really stressed...
She won't talk to me about it.
Who knows?
Since she thinks
you're stranger,
she might actually
open up to you.
It's funny.
I never thought I'd be glad
to be in Hanai's dojo...
I messed up again!
It's raining.
The dark clouds,
a perfect mirror of my soul.
It's so depressing.
I should be at Tenma's house
having a warm meal right now.
Rich girl?
Of course.
It would start raining
all of a sudden.
Oh ... Um...
Thank you very much.
No problem.
I'm just doin' my job.
I'll finish for you.
You have to stop
dropping your arm!
Keep practicing. You're
making great progress.
Really impressive
for your first time!
Mikoto. You're amazing!
Well, I've been
at it for a while.
Did you work up a good sweat?
Yeah.
Me too. I'm 'onna
go hit the shower.
Sure.
Oh. Right.
I need to bring
Harima some food.
Thank you.
That was really refreshing.
Sorry I took so long.
Mikoto, are you in here?
Hey, are you there?
You're so quiet.
Did you fall
asleep or something?
Geez, you're creepin' me out.
No!
Ugh, crap. That took
way longer than expected.
I wonder if she's
still even in there.
Mikoto, you're so strong!
You could've gone a
little easier on me though.
My entire body is
covered in bruises.
Why is Eri talking to herself?
When did this become
a co-ed bath?!
What the hell are
those two doing?
I do feel a lot better
though, so thank you.
I'd love to keep learning,
if you don't mind.
Hey, are youou listening
to me over there?
Aw, crap! I'm gonna
get kicked out again!
Just when I found
a safe place to stay!
Damn...! Stupid Rich Girl!
How could you mistake
me for Mikoto?!
Do I look like a girl to you?
It's too late!
There's no way to save
myself! I'm so dead!
Hey, Mikoto.
Have things been going
well between you and Asou?
Who the heck are you
talking about? Asou?
What's wrong with you?
The guy you've been hanging out
with lately from the
basketball team?
Asou!
Oh yeah, him.
You know, I'm not all that sure.
To be honest... I'm not
really interested in guys.
Oh! I didn't know that!
Okay! This is going well!
I'm a better actor
than I thought!
Oh, it's Mikoto! Perfect timing!
Please save me! If you
don't, I'm a dead man!
Okay. Just follow my lead.
Thanks a lot!
I owe you big time!
Hey, are you getting sick?
Your voice sounds
a little strange.
I never knew your
back was so ripped!
You almost seem
like a different person!
Oh! That's normal!
You know how your muscles
tighten after a workout!
Yeah? Well, yours
are like way tight.
And, I think I might
be getting sick.
Yes! Looks like I'll live
to fight another day!
By the way, Eri.
When are you gonna confess
your feelings to Harima?
What the--?!
Have you gone completely insane?
I'm not even
talking to that idiot!
I saw him on the
street yesterday.
I thought he was a homeless man.
Who would wanna be
with a guy like that?
But, you know?
There is a lot of romance in
the air these days, isn't there?
Madoka and Umezu,
Nagayama and Tanaka.
There's even you and Asou.
Help me get outta here!
Hang on a second!
What about you, Eri?
Well, it looks like I'm gonna
have to get married pretty soon.
My parents are making me go
to an engagement meeting...
Damn! You scared me!
I seriously thought you
were saying... Oh, never mind.
If it's just a meeting, then
you can turn it down, right?
Or would that cause
problems with your family?
So what if it does?
I'm gonna reject it,
no matter what it costs me.
I'm coming in, okay?
Damn it! No!!!
She's gonna kill me!
Please do something!
Oh, no! I forgot
he was in there!
I've gotta get out
of here! Fast!
That was way too
frickin' close for comfort.
I had no choice! Cut it out!!
You stupid jerk!!
I used my towel
to make air bubbles!
It wasn't what it looked like!
How the hell is Eri
supposed to know that...?
Do you know what this does
to a girls reputation?
But still, poor Eri...
I mean, an arranged marriage...?
I feel so bad for her,
no wonder she's been
acting so strange lately.
Man... She's still a
high school student.
They expect her to get
married when she's this young?
I'll never understand
the way rich people think.
Eh, there's nothin' I can do.
Might sound selfish...
but I got my hands full
worrying about my own problems.
I understand.
Hey, it's pretty
chilly in the dojo.
You can sleep
here again tonight.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
This frickin' blows!
I've only gotten
ten pages finished!! Damn!
Jerks...! What is it now?!
Hello. Are you Mikoto's father?
Is ... she at home right now?
What do you mean father?
Get outta here jackass.
Scram! Don't make me ask twice!
Seriously!
Can't a person get any
work done around here?
What the hell is it this time?
You better knock
it off, pretty boy!
Please accept my apologies.
I am Nakamura, the
Sawachika family's butler.
I'm looking for the
little Miss. Is she here?
The little Miss? Oh.
You mean the rich girl.
If you're looking
for her, she's...
Hey!!
Stop pushing!
What were you doing out there?
Are you stupid?
We can't just give her away!
Eri needs our help right now.
Looks like Nakamura is here ...
I guess it's time
for me to get going.
But ... you can't.
Don't worry about it.
I already told you, Miko,
I'm gonna turn the guy down.
Well, ... this is it.
Thanks for taking care of me.
You...! You're coming
with me right now!
First of all, I'm not
feeling this outfit...
Second of all, what
the heck are you doing?
Helping you...
and I'll loan
you my worker, too.
Now... Take the motorbike
and get out of here.
It'll at least buy you
some time to think or,
whatever, just do it!
I'm not going anywhere!
I've still got work to do!
You're working for the
Suou family, remember?!!
You'll do what I tell you to do!
I'm counting on you.
You're crazy, woman.
What are you trying to pull?
I don't have time for this BS!
Okay! I'll take
care of the rest!
That was fun...
Now then, what to
do about this guy...
No matter what,
you must find Miss Eri.
That was nice. Feels
so good to be clean again.
The grime of the
past year is gone
and now I'm
gonna start fresh.
Yoshidayama is gonna be
the big man on campus...
Watch out Harima...!
Soon, I'll turn him
into my pet slave.
Then, I'll mock him and
kick him around in front
of his beloved Eri!
Miss Eri. I've found you.
What the hell?
Do I look like a girl to you?
Whoopsy. You're not the Miss.
Damn it! Why should I have
to run around protecting
this rich brat
when I have a comic to finish?!
Next time on School Rumble
Second Semester:
"Eri's Escape, Harima's
Lullaby, The False Bride"!
Rich Girl.
You're actin' strange!