Hey, Yakumo!
I'm coming, Sis.
Hand-making Christmas
presents is so sweet...
Do you need some help?
Heck yeah! But wear a hard hat!
Come on, what are
you mad at me for?
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe because you
didn't bother to tell me
that helpful employee
was actually Whiskers!
Hey... Gimme a break.
You would've never
stayed at my place
if you knew he was
staying there, too...
Plus it's not my fault
you didn't recognize
him in that outfit.
If I'd... known who he was...
I never would've spent
the night with him.
What?! You didn't
tell me about that...!
Oh, my God! How was it?
How was what?
Was it like this?
What?!
Or was it like this?
No!
You perv! Nothing happened!
Oh don't be shy, Eri!
You can tell me,
I'm your best friend!
So, just where did this
rendezvous occur?
Uh, well, we found...
this vacant temple...
And then what happened?
We huddled under a blanket.
Huddled together?
So, the two of you together
under one blanket?
Yeah, that's what I said.
We didn't have a choice!
We were stranded,
it was freezing,
and we only had one blanket!
Mm-hm!
And so I'm supposed
to believe that you two
just platonically
dozed off together?
Neither one of
you tried anything?
Right...
So how 'bout you tell
me the truth now...?
I'm not gonna tell anybody...
I already told you!
Nothing happened!
Nothing!
You're serious?
Screw you...!
Why are you making that face?!
Akira? Yeah it's me.
She says she didn't
do anything with Harima.
Shyeah! I know, right?
Guess you win the bet.
Wait a minute!
You two are betting on me?!
Hold on.
What about a kiss?
You know, like in the
heat of the moment?
Nope. At the rate she's going,
I doubt she's ever gonna reveal
her true feelings to Harima.
It's such a shame.
Why do you suck?
I don't suck! I don't
like the guy! Back off!
Whatever. Let's talk about work.
About work?
Mikoto and her folks have
been letting you stay here.
Don't you think it's
time to pay them back?
Uh... Sure. Of course.
Every year at this time,
Mikoto's parents' company
gets hired for a certain job.
Yeah?
And this year...
you're going to help.
I have to decorate a
giant Christmas tree, huh?
Should be easy enough.
Even if it is the
first job I've ever had.
Okay, people, gather 'round!
We're just about to get started!
Right.
But... Akira's not here yet!
Huh?!
What are you doing here?!
What about you?!
Um, Akira asked me--
Well, Mikoto asked me--
--to come here!
They set me up!
And those two call
themselves my friends!
After everything that
happened at the temple,
this is so embarrassing!
We're goin' to start
with the ornaments in
the back of the truck.
We'll decorate the
top of the tree first
and then work our way down.
Now if this is your
first time with us...
Forget Whiskers.
Listen to what
the foreman's saying.
Focus. Focus... But what
if I do have questions?
Does that mean...?
No! There's no way I'm
gonna ask Whiskers for help.
Hey, is it just me, or does that
blonde girl look like a model?
She does. Why is someone
like her working here?
I think I'll go find out.
Hey wait...! Here,
I can carry that for you.
Huh?
It looks pretty heavy.
Thanks.
First time doing this, huh?
Yeah.
Don't worry. You'll do fine.
I'll show you the ropes, okay?
Cool, that's so nice of you.
All right, everybody!
Time to knock off for lunch!
Man, am I hungry.
Hey...? Can I sit here?
Whatev.
This job turned out
to be fun, huh...?
At first all I wanted to do
was tell Akira and
Mikoto to go to hell,
but I'm actually
enjoying myself today.
What's wrong?
Nah, just forget it.
Hey! If you've got something
to say to me, then spit it out!
Forget it! It's nothing!
I don't wanna talk about it!
Why?! Are you too scared!
Guess I'm not
really one to talk...
If it wasn't for you, I wouldn't
have been able to say no
to my parents and
that arranged marriage.
I should be more grateful,
but you should've told me
who you were. Before we...
Before we...!
Hmph...! You think
I'm too scared?
You're really one to talk.
You almost didn't
tell mommy and daddy
that you didn't
want to get married.
Good thing you did. Still...
I'm sick and tired of
you screwin' up my life...
Get lost, Blondie.
You really suck.
You know that, Whiskers?
Rich Girl, I know in my gut,
I hang out with you any
more you'll do something
to screw up
my chances with Tenma.
Eri, what's up?!
Oh, Tenma!
Are you working here?
No, I'm just meeting somebody.
I knew it!
She's like a parasite
burrowing her blonde little head
deeper into the
arteries of my love.
Wow, it's so weird
to see you working.
Yep... This is my first job.
Like it?
Yeah, kinda... I'm better at
it than I thought, at least.
Good for you.
You always have been
good with your hands.
There's only one
bad thing though...
Whiskers is one
of my co-workers.
What?! Harima?! That scumbag?!
Yeah. That loser.
Talk about bad luck.
So you don't like
him either, huh?
No, what is there to like?
He's violent...
He's coarse...
His feet stink...
And he's always wearing the
same clothes, like, every day.
What did I do to deserve this?!
Then he's all breathe-y
and lusty whenever he
ever gets near a girl...!
I'd watch out if
I were you, Eri.
Huh?
Tenma, I told you it was
all a misunderstanding!
I don't agree with
you on that one.
But I told you I found
him in Yakumo's room...
Did he do anything?
Did you ask him what happened?
Now that I think about it,
he did say something
about it all being a
big misunderstanding...
Harima's a jerk,
he's coarse, he's violent...
But the one thing he's
not is a pervert. Trust me.
What the--?! It can't be!
Rich Girl's actually
stickin' up for me?
See?! I told you!
Did you hear what
Rich Girl said, Tenma?
It was all a big
misunderstanding!
Word up.
It took you long enough!
Please tell Akira that
I'm not talking to her...
She knew that he
was going to be here!
He who?
Don't start!
I got here as quickly
as I could... Hello?
Anybody here?
That's weird...
I'm here. Where are you?
Oh... Another text
message from Akira...
"Good morning, Sara...
By now, you're probably inside
the old school house." Huh?
There's both a challenge
and a present awaiting you
in a classroom on
the second floor.
Solve one, and
you'll get the other.
Maybe this is it.
Well, here goes.
What the--? What is that thing?
I'm alive... Yes!
It's no use. I can't move.
Hello?
Huh?
Yakumo!
Oh my gosh, Sara.
What in the world are
you doing down there?
Are you okay?
No! Stay back!
That's... awkward.
Now we're in the
same predicament.
The wood in this
place is old and rotten.
We've poked through the
ceiling of the first floor.
Yeah, I feel my feet dangling.
It's good we didn't fall
all the way through.
Lemme guess.
You came here because
of Akira's message?
"It's almost Christmas,
and if you'd like a
little holiday challenge,
come quickly to
the old schoolhouse."
What could that mean?
I don't know, but let's send
her a text message and find out.
Takano? Is that you?
Yep.
What are you wearing?
I'm paying homage to
The Emperor Penguin.
It can survive for two months
without eating as it waits
for its mate to return
with food from the sea.
Wait, let me guess.
You bought that
penguin costume, put in on,
and then you fell
through the floor.
Here's an idea.
How 'bout you
stop judging me...?
We need to find a way to
get out of here... A-SAP.
Uh... Oh! It's Tenma...!
Hey Sis, listen...
Hey, Yakumo, where are you?
I'm hungry! Feed me!
Well, Sis, I can't make
you lunch right now...
In fact, I need your help...
You see, I'm on the second
floor of the old schoolhouse
and I'm stuck here
at the moment...
Don't worry! I'll help you
finish what you're doing.
Give me a sec and I'll drop in!
No, Sis! Hold on!
Is she coming here?
Yes.
I think we all know
how that'll turn out.
Hey, that's mean.
Well, maybe she'll see
us here like this and--
Hey, Yakumo!
It's a penguin! Yay!
That plan fell through.
Yep, sure did...
You guys did it, too!
You should have said something!
Is there anyone else who
could help us...? Hey, wait!
Yakumo... you should
try summoning him...!
He'll help if he knows
you're here, definitely!
Summoning?
Wish really hard...
I'm sure he'll hear.
You mean, like, pray?
Just put your mind to it!
I know it'll work!
No luck, huh?
Well, that's strange.
He did say something about
getting new glasses made today.
Oh. That explains why Hanai
didn't come... that's too bad.
You were talking about Hanai?
Yeah. Who else?
Is there anyone
else we can call?
Let's call Eri or Mikoto!
Good luck.
Eri's at a party and Mikoto's
out on a date with Asou.
Oh, no...!
Well, what the heck are
we gonna do you guys...?
We need to come up with a plan.
Otherwise, we'll be
stuck here forever!
Wake up!
You can't go to sleep,
Grandma Yakumo, or you'll die!
Bring it.
I would prefer death to this.
Grandma Sara!
And after that...!
That's stupid!
Why did you get bigger?!
'Cause I'm a penguin, duh!
Speaking of which, aren't
you guys the least bit curious
as to why I'm dressed like
a penguin in the first place?
Well, you wearing funny costumes
has sort of become the norm.
You should know better.
I've got a reason
for wearing this.
You, you mean you
could've gotten out
of that crazy
outfit at any time?!
Yes, that's correct.
But I needed some way to make
you all think I was trapped...
And now I can take
the perfect picture...
For my holiday card. Smile.
Now that's what
I call poetic justice.
Son of a jerk!
There's no one who can help us,
and I'm 'onna starve to death!
We'll miss Christmas and New
Year's, too, if no one shows up!
Oh, no!
Don't panic.
We might get noticed if
someone happens to be doing
something in the
classroom below us.
Oh, come on.
Who would be here
during winter break?
Let's see... I don't know...
Maybe someone who has
an immoveable deadline
to finish one hundred and
twenty-pages of artwork.
However, he was
locked out of his home,
but was able to
stay with a classmate.
He was quickly kicked
out by said classmate
and then had to thwart another
classmate's arranged marriage.
As a result, he hasn't
gotten any work done
and his only refuge is
this old schoolhouse.
Sound like anyone we know?
Not even remotely.
Wait, you don't mean...
Santa Claus?!
What is this?
A gym mat... It broke
our fall and saved us.
But who was that
in the Santa suit?
Consider it a Christmas miracle.
Yeah that's right.
We got rescued.
And we still have
Christmas to look forward to.
And lunch.
Good thing I still had this
ridiculous costume on
from my new job.
Damn! Now I gotta find
another place to work on this!
I'm positive I sensed
Yakumo's presence.
I don't know about you,
but I'm sick of spending
Christmas Eve alone.
So let's meet some chicks
and make something
happen this year!
That's easier said than done.
You're giving up
just like that?!
Come on, Harry! Tell us!
Please?! What are you two
wearing at the party tonight?
Well, well... You two
are gorgeous and curious.
I'm so sorry, ladies,
but that's a surprise.
Aw! Come on now!
Why do you guys always
have to tease us like that?!
Please tell us!
We don't even have a chance...
We're not nearly as
cool as those guys.
We suck at life.
Listen up, dumbass!
Are we mice or are we men...?!
If those guys can get chicks,
there's no reason
why we can't, too!
Well said, boy.
Huh?
Never give up.
Never stop running...
Death awaits those who do...
So you must keep running
furiously... furiously...
Furiously!
Recognizing your weakness
is a step towards manhood...
I, too, have been
down that road.
But are you real men yet?
Well... Let me be
the judge of that.
You must first pass the test
that all real men
before you have...
I'm having a dance party
at my house tonight.
Aside from the lovely ladies,
only those who I deem
real men may attend.
Huh?
Are you saying we can come?
No. Right now you
are only half men.
But if you prove to me you are
real men, you are welcome.
Wait! Hold up!
We're not even gonna try?
Screw him!
That bastard thinks
he's such a big shot!
Real man, my ass!
Excuse me, would you
like to fill out a survey?
Go to hell...
So what if we don't have
girlfriends on Christmas Eve?
Read your palm, sir?
It's not like it's the end
of the world, you know?
The end of the world is coming.
Can I pray for you?
It can't end!
Not 'til I score or get
a girlfriend at least!
But sir, the end is nigh,
and your soul just
seems so parched...
Your face is parched!
That's it!
Let's become real men!
That's the spirit!
Soon, The girls
will want to do us,
and the guys will want to be us!
We'll be real men
with our own style!
You both copied Harry's look?!
What were you thinking?!
Well, um...
You did it too... Hello?
Shut up, Nara! And you.
You really think girls are gonna
be into the whole wig thing?
Damn straight.
Huh... So this is your lame
attempt to be real men?
Your face is lame.
Don't push it!
I'll give you partial
credit for your appearance.
However... It's not enough.
You have to back
it up with actions.
I guess that means
we gotta act cool, too...
You guys got any ideas?
Well, Harry does ride a
motorcycle, doesn't he?
Maybe we should
try to talk like Harry.
Indeed.
That's how you talk, dumbass.
I dunno, he sounded
pretty cool to me.
Damn straight.
You guys are idiots.
These fries are so naughty...
'Cause they're blocking
my view of your beautiful face.
Oh, you're so sweet!
Like Christmas candy, baby.
Whoa...
That's amazing!
We've gotta do that!
Enjoy your Big Was meal!
Hold it, gorgeous!
Can't see your beautiful face
'cause of these naughty fries!
And these naughty burgers!
And this naughty drink!
Give me back my lunch!
You know guys,
I've been thinking...
Maybe we're better off
just being ourselves.
Let's tell Tougou
to cram it. Mmkay?
Bravo!
Tougou!
Only real men would have the
guts to approach Lara like that.
As they say in her country,
you guys have cojones...!
The three of you are
men now! Congratulations!
I'll see you at my
party later, mis amigos!
Huh?!
Is this real? Are we dreaming?
No! It's for real!
We're with the cool guys...!
And the cool guys
always get the hot chicks!
Okay. I'll be right there.
See ya. Sorry, I have to go.
Something's suddenly come up.
No!
But without you
it's not a party!
Now, ladies...
Don't fret. Tougou's
gonna take care of ya.
Yes indeed... Harry may
be exiting the building...
But that... just leaves
more fun for the rest of us!
Uh...
What the--?
What a coincidence...
Everyone else had something
suddenly come up, as well.
Uh... Hey, you guys
tried this food yet?
It's pretty good.
Yeah. Great party, too.
Uh-huh. Yeah... Heh... party...
Yeah.
Hey! Don't tell me
you guys forgot?!
If you recall...
It's a dance party.
So dance!
Uh!
We... did practice...
Just don't step on my feet.
Okay, you guys?
Well, we may not...
have girlfriends...
but it's okay... 'Cause
I have you... and Nishimoto...
and you guys are the
best friends I've ever had.
Nara... You're such a pansy.
♪ ending song ♪
At Christmas, you
get to have curry, huh?
That's right, Karasuma!
Next time, on School Rumble:
"Here, There, and
Everywhere, Christmas!
A Dash for Christmas!
A Shattered Christmas!"
Christmas curry is the best!