This is Yurei and Otama...
Otama is always
there behind Yurei...
The two of them
are always together.
Damn it... after being
adrift for all that time,
I'm way behind on these layouts.
Look, I'm sorry, but
I'm gonna need one more hour!
What's... that for?
Your last comic
was too realistic.
Next time make sure to
draw me one I can publish.
He's such a hard ass!
Well, I at least gave this
one a more exotic location...
That should do it.
Tenma's Sister sure
is takin' her time.
She told me she'd be
here well before six.
I bet that's her now!
You made it just in time...
we've gotta lotta...
Hey, hey!
Ten... T-T-T!
What is Tenma doing here?!
Harima! Yakumo couldn't make
it so I came in her place!
Hey, let me in or
I'll blow your house down!
Check out the snackage...!
So is it okay to come in?
Yes, of course...! Come in!
Thank you, sir!
Itoko's shoes!
Um... What's the matter?
Oh, lately I haven't
been getting much exercise,
so I need to work out!
Okay!
Okay then! Come in, come in!
Wow, Harima... you... sure...
do live in a really
nice apartment!
Yeah... I guess.
Hey, Kenji, you
got company out there?
Is someone else here?
No...! That was... the TV!
The work room is
right down the hall!
But-but...!
Now you just sit tight there
while I put on some tea, okay?!
But-b-but, Harima?!
Oh, man, that was a close one...
I wasn't expecting
Tenma to show up.
You're right, this is a
once in a lifetime chance.
Don't... do that!
Damn you...! You knew
she was here, didn't you?!
Pretty sure I'm in the way here.
So I'm going out for a bit.
Looks like you two
will be all alone here...
Try not to blow it.
Me?
All alone here with Tenma?
Hey I got some, I mean
I made some, I... Tea!
Wow!
You can see
Yagami Harbor from here!
And Yagami Bridge!
It's romantic... isn't it?
Yeah... I s'pose.
Ah, this is so exciting!
Oh, this is so exciting!
After all, this
is the first time
I've been a professional
artist's assistant...!
I'll have to work really hard!
Yeah... right... really hard.
Hey... are these the
layouts...? Lemme see.
No!! Don't look!
But... why not?
Why... why not?
Because they're not ready
to be seen, that's why...!
I have my professional
pride, y'know!
I see...! You're just trying
to be pro...! I get it, homie!
Thanks... Why don't
you just sit down
and have some tea while
I finish polishing these up?
No problem!
That was a close call.
If she'd seen these, the cat
would really be out of the bag.
Hey, uh... your sister...
why wasn't she able to make it?
Good question...
I don't know, she
just said she was busy
and wouldn't be able to come.
I see.
Strange...
Tenma's Sister didn't
say anything about this
on the phone this morning.
She's usually
so conscientious...
I'm surprised she didn't call
me when something came up.
There! My secret's safe!
You know, it surprises me.
What does?
You really can't judge
people by appearances.
I never would've thought you
were the artist type, Harima.
You're not the only one...
I'll tell you, I was
really impressed
with that book you drew before.
You're so talented, it's really
raised my opinion of you!
Let's do this... I'm ready!
Harima, you're so great...
I think I've fallen
in love with you.
I wanna be by
your side always...
that's why I came
here like this.
That's what's going on here!
Right...! So all I have to
do is make my move...! But...
making a direct confession
might be a little awkward...
Maybe I'll try dropping a few
subtle hints first. Yeah...
There!
Okay... the pages are all ready
for you, assistant Tsukamoto!
Let me explain a little
bit of the plot to you...
this is a story about
a man and a woman
who were on a cruise ship that
hit a storm and went adrift.
M-hm, m-hm...
This is the hero...
Mm-hmm!!
And this is the heroine...
Attractive.
Do these two...
look like anyone you know?
Huh...?
Those... those two people...
Yes...! Those two people...?
They appeared in
your last comic book!
This story is a
continuation of that one!
Yeah... good guess.
I forget how dumb she is!
I'll just have to
spell it out for her.
Uh, look...
What's up?
It's like this...
Artists subconsciously
reveal their deepest thoughts
and emotions
through their drawings.
Oh... yeah,
I've heard about that.
Well, that's true of
this comic book too.
It's the expression
of my very soul.
You see...?!
I am the main character!
What's more, I really am
in love with the heroine!
And... to tell the truth...
that... heroine...
Phone call!
Crap, who is it?!
Hey, Kenji How's it goin'?
Have you confessed
to your love Tenma yet?
Mind your own business!
Good grief...
of all the times to call and
check on me, it had to be now!
Way cool...! Harima,
your ring tone is the theme
from "Three for the Kill"
just like mine!
You see, we match!
Whoa! what an
awesome coincidence!
Uh-huh...! Oh, crap!
What is it...? What's wrong?
I forgot there's a "Three for
the Kill" special on today!
Oh, no, look at the time,
it started thirty minutes ago!
We missed the first half hour,
there's no way we'll be able
to follow what's going on!
Wait!
Yakumo could be recording it!
You think?!
Yeah, I'll text
her and find out!
All right... we're in the clear!
Oh, snap!
Yakumo Tsukamoto:
Prepared as usual.
Thank goodness...! I'll lend
it to you later, Harima!
Thank you, thank you!
Have you been having fun, Iori?
I did it...
I sent Sis over
to help Harima out
with the artwork on
his comic book today.
I've been thinking about
doing it for a while... but...
...did Karasuma ever come
to your sister's party?
Oh, yeah... After the
party he came by our house.
I see.
It's like...
I have all this motivation!
I think...
Harima really likes Sis...
But... Sis doesn't
seem to realize it.
I want Sis to
see more of Harima.
Have you been getting
into trouble again?
Look at this...
This is Sis, when
she was in middle school.
No doubt... It's eighty-nine!
"Farewell, Three!
Flowers of Evil Bloom
on the Kamakura Road!"
is without question
the best episode ever!
Oh, yeah...! Mangoku's fight
scenes totally kicked ass!
On the other hand, episode
forty-three is pretty good too!
Yeah...! "Hurry Up,
There's Love Trouble
on Nakasendo Road"
was classic, I was in tears!
And Okiku's guest appearance
was totally awesome,
don't you think?
Artistically, we are as one.
I should've known!
We're a perfect match
for each other!
You know, it's just amazing!
I had no idea you
were a Mangoku fan!
I had no idea you were
a Mangoku fan either!
It's like...
we're perfectly matched!
Oh, wow...
For the last time,
mind your own business!
Uh, Tazawa? This is Mitsui.
I was just checking in...
how's it going?
Fine, just fine...
Great, make sure you bring
it by tomorrow morning...
That gonna be a problem?
No, not at all.
Remember, the big boss
is counting on you,
so make sure you don't
let him down this time...
Hang in there!
Is something wrong?
Oh, they're hounding
me for my story.
When is the manuscript due?
In the morning.
Oh my gosh...! We should hurry!
No, no, it's cool.
It doesn't matter if it's late!
It really doesn't matter...
All I need is for you to
finally know how I feel.
I'm not gonna let
you give up like this!
You've got too much
talent to waste it...!
Besides, I want to see your
story get published in Zinegama!
Really...?
And I'll help you... we'll go
steady down the path to success!
Go steady...
Go steady... Go steady...
You... you say you'll
go steady with me?
Duh...! Of course I will!
Yeah...! Let's get to work!
Whoa, yeah!!
Big Sister Power...
You haven't changed at all.
That picture book...
Once this story is done there'll
be time for everything else.
There's no need to rush things.
We can just take it slow
and spend more and
more time together.
That's what going steady
is all about, right, Tenma?
Um, I was thinkin'...
What?
If we finish up before daybreak,
you think you might wanna take
a ride up the coast on my bike?
Up the coast?
Yeah... when the morning
sun rises out of the water,
it's incredibly beautiful.
Yeah...! Sounds great!
Whoa, you mean it?!
Brush... brush... brush...
Huh?
How... how could she do this?
I'll have to redraw
the whole thing!
I'll never make it in time now!
What...? Is that wrong?
No, not at all...! It's perfect!
Yes! What should I do next?
Uh... For now, how about
just sharpening my pencils?
Okie-doke!
You know...
I know just how your
main character feels...
Unrequited love stinks.
Huh?
And then, just when it
seems like the right moment,
you can't confess how you feel!
Yeah, that's it exactly!
So you think...
if I just spend as much
time with him as possible...
But no... if you don't say
it they just don't get it.
Gotta be brave.
Oh, Tenma, I'm such a pansy...!
Even after you've said
you'd go steady with me,
I still don't have the guts to
declare my feelings to you!
I've gotta flat out declare my
love to Karasuma! Straight up!
Just you wait! I'm gonna
declare my love, straight up!
Tenma!
Huh?
The truth is, I'm...
I'm, uh... hungry.
So am I!
Maybe we should order out.
Hey, why don't
I make something for you?
What...?! No, please don't...
Oh, relax, it's no trouble!
No... that's not
what I'm sayin'...
Where are your spices?
Uh... good question.
Guess I'll have to ask Itoko.
Looks like things
are going pretty well.
The spices are under the sink.
Oh, thank you...
Hey, Tenma... you'll find
the spices under the sink.
Hey...! How'd you
know I was gonna...?
She wouldn't have the
place bugged, would she?
Okay, soup's on!
You shouldn't have.
Ahh...!
I kind of messed it up, huh?
No! It's delicious!
Really delicious.
Maybe we should have a drink.
That's a good idea...
I'll be right back...
Man... how in the
hell can anyone manage
to make something
that tastes so bad...?
It's like she's an artist at it!
However!
The important thing is that
we got through it together...!
Experiences like this are
what going steady is all about!
I made us some coffee...
You want some...? Huh?
Ah...! Here it is!
Yurei and Otama.
Otama was always
there behind Yurei...
The two of them
were always together.
When they were eating...
Yurei would say,
"I don't want any more."
"Yurei, you should
eat all your food."
When they were playing...
Yurei would say,
"I want this one!"
"Yurei, that toy
belongs to her."
And when everyone
went out together...
Yurei said,
"I wanna go this way!"
"But, Yurei, everyone
else is going that way!"
"That's okay,
I wanna go this way...
If you wanna go with everyone
else, Otama, you go ahead."
"Yurei, you want
to be all alone?"
Yurei replied, "Yeah,
I'll be fine all alone."
Otama seemed sad somehow...
However, she
didn't say anything.
"I don't care
what you do, Otama."
Then Yurei started trudging
away, all by herself.
How long is she
planning to sleep...?
Well, at least
I'm getting more work done.
Come to think of it, this has
happened before, hasn't it?
Lookin' back, this
is how it all started.
I love you...
Ever since then,
I've been in love with you.
You disgust me!
Thanks for nothing, Mr. Pervert!
That's when I started
wearing sunglasses,
and grew a beard,
so I could be someone else,
so I could be near you...
A lot has happened... but this
long drama will soon be over.
I know, without any doubt...
you and I will
have a happy ending!
But I can't think about
that now...! Back to work!
Sure, I can still eat
another bowl...! Bring it on!
Man, she's even
hungry in her sleep!
Yeah...
Come on... Harima, dear.
No, no, no!
I'm not that kind of man...!
Think of something else...!
Something else...!
Something else!
Come on... Harima dear.
Not like that!
Ah, son of a...!
Huh?
Doowah!
Now you will have
to face me in battle.
Love you...
Yurei started trudging
away, all by herself...
Step after step she plodded on.
"Oh, look at the flowers!"...
But there was no one behind her.
"Oh, a shooting star!"...
But there was nobody there.
Yurei went home
all by herself...
Once she got home,
there was still nobody there.
When she was eating,
and when she was playing,
and when she was cleaning,
she was all alone.
"Otama... where did you go?"...
Yurei decided to look for Otama.
She asked the
worm on the flower...
"Mr. Worm, Mr. Worm...
where did Otama go?"
"Yurei," said the worm,
"I'm so hungry I can't move."
"Well then,
I'll give you my food."
"Thank you. I saw Otama
looking at some flowers.
"Thank you,
Mr. Worm," said Yurei.
She asked two twins
on the beach...
"Say, you two... do you
know where Otama is?"
"Yurei," said the twins,
"we're sad because we
only have one toy."
"In that case," said Yurei,
"I'll give you mine."
Thank you, Yurei...!
We saw Otama watching a
shooting star over there!"
"Thank you, twins."
Everyone had seen her...
but no matter how far she
walked, Otama was not there.
"Otama," she said,
"where did you go?"
Yurei finally started to cry...
The tears ran down...
one after the other...
and made a puddle...
"Otama... where have you gone?"
Is this really what you want?
Admit it...
...you're in love
with Harima yourself.
♪ ending song ♪
Wow, it sure is hard work
being an artist's assistant!
But you slept through it all!
It takes hard work to
finish drawing a comic book!
It's not finished yet!
Next time on School Rumble!
"A Sesame Seed!"
That's not what it is!
"Period!"