♪ Autumn leaves,
near the dam... ♪
It's been a long time since
we all went out together.
Yeah, I mean, we've been so
busy with the culture festival.
The leaves are
so pretty right now.
Hey, hey, is anyone else hungry?
Yeah, sure... let's open
up those box lunches.
What's keeping the boys?
Why'd you invite them anyway?
They have their uses.
Why do you suppose they brought
all that extra stuff
along just for a picnic?
Even while picnicking
one must always be on guard
Mountain weather can
change at any given moment...
You have to be prepared for
anything... and everything.
Oh, Harima, I'm so glad we had
a chance to be alone like this.
Don't you worry
about a thing, baby...!
I'm gonna keep
you safe and sound.
This is heavy...! Too heavy...!
My precious back muscles
are being compromised.
Ahh! Now this is
what I call living!
You jackass!
What are you doing?!
You didn't expect me to walk
all the way up here, did you?
Out of the bag, freeloader!
Lunch... lunch...
I love lunch...
Ho, ho, ho... behold Yakumo's
extra special picnic lunch!
What the?
Sis... you left the
other dishes at home!
I'm sorry...! I guess
I forgot to pack them...!
I'll make up for it by making
some of my famous rice balls!
I guess we have no choice,
so I'll give you a hand, okay?
No! Just a minute!!
Why not let me cook something?!
Being the amazing
person that I am,
I brought along
some cooking gear.
Ho ho! Good thinking, Harima!
He certainly perked
up in a hurry.
Good! The last thing
I wanted to do was manual labor
I don't know if
there's anything cooler
than a man who
knows how to cook!
You stay out of this,
Four-eyes...!
I'll handle the cooking!
Like hell you will...!
Besides, what does
a delinquent like you
know how to cook anyway?!
I'll show you--! I make
a mean soufflé of pain!
Gentlemen... why
don't you both cook?
We'll have a
men's outdoor cook-off!
That sounds awesome!
Yeah, let's do it!
This is gonna be fun!
I'm in!
Yeah, we'll settle this
thing once and for all!
Oo, oo!
I wanna play too!
What...? The only thing you
ever play with is yourself.
What's the catch?
If I win, Miko has to kiss me!
These are the rules, men.
You are allowed to
cook anything you want,
but you have to supply
your own ingredients.
Okay!
All right, begin!
Tenma, soon you'll know
what my love tastes like!
I am not gonna
lose to that punk!
Miko, don't forget my kiss!
If your lips come near me,
I'm ripping ' em off!
I can show off the skills
I learned at sea as a fisherman!
But ordinary food isn't
gonna be good enough!
It's gotta be something with
more, I don't know, impact!
You... you're huge...! You must
be the king of this river!
All right...!
If I can bag this guy,
I'll have the
ultimate ingredient!
Huh...
I've got the mushrooms
and other wild herbs,
but I still haven't
acquired the meat.
Meat! I hear your primal call.
What a beast...!
He's so beautiful...!
I will rise to the occasion
and put my skills to the test!
Mission one has
been accomplished...
Holy crap! They look like hell.
Right...! Start cooking!
This is starting
to get exciting, huh?
Wait a second...
where's Imadori?
D-cup-a-licious...
Captain Pervo's outta the race.
What a surprise.
All I have to do...
is add my secret
ingredient and it's done!
That's nice...
but guess what...?
It doesn't matter
what you've got...
it's no match for
my secret ingredient... ha!
Finished!
I'm done!
And now it's
time for the tasting.
We'll start with Imadori's dish.
Imadori...?
I thought he was out...?
Having studied
with the great chefs of the
European cruise ships, sampling
spices at port after port,
I finally perfected
this jewel of a curry.
It's... it's... perfect!
The sauce is the best
thing I've ever tasted!
Naturally...! See... I used
the finest flour and beef tallow
and let the roux
simmer for days,
roasting it slowly
for maximum taste.
So you weren't just lying
around doing nothing?
Of course not!
Time is the best
seasoning there is!
This tender, thinly
sliced beef, mingled
with the perfectly steamed rice,
gives it a genuine
western flavor!
I feel like I've
tasted this dish before.
That's because you have!
It's Guruguru Curry...
Primo blend!
No packaged ingredients!
I thought it just
had to taste good!
Loser.
Taking shortcuts... huh?
Too bad... looks like Imadori
fails to collect his kiss.
What? I never offered!
Please, give me
another chance...
Here's a dish
that comes straight
from the depths of my heart!
Miko D-cup curry!
Out of bounds.
Imadori is disqualified.
Next up is Harima's dish.
I'm a man of few words...
My food speaks for itself.
What is this?
What a hearty miso flavor!
Oh, my mouth is like totally
blissing out on this stuff!
That's right! I am a genius!
Eat it...! Gorge yourself on
the delicacy of delicacies,
the Japanese mitten crab!
Yummy... Yummy... Yummy...
My tummy!
It's absolutely delicious...
Tenma!
It's so nice to have a
boyfriend who can cook!
But isn't the
flavor a little sharp?
Say what?!
Now that you mention it,
it is a little salty.
It can't be!
You forgot about the order...
for the seasoning.
Huh?
That's right... You put the
salt in first, didn't you?
Uh... yeah.
What's wrong with that?
Don't you know it's critical
to add seasonings in order,
according to
molecular weight...?
Otherwise you completely throw
off the balance of the flavor.
I didn't know!!
That's a physics
teacher for you!
What a great observation.
Thanks, and it's
actually chemistry.
Well, we're off...
let's go, Youko.
We'll see you!
Dropping by in the middle
of their weekend drive...
those were our guest tasters
Ms. Osakabe and Ms. Sasakura.
And now, Hanai's dish.
My dish is a hot stew pot.
Wow... it looks amazing.
Wild plant stew, right?
Hm...! Not quite,
Miss Tsukamoto!
Behold if you dare, and feast
upon the magic that is my stew!
Incredible...
I can't stop tearing up...
Yakumo... How is it?
It's absolutely delicious.
Ah...! Say it slow!!
It's so nice to have
a husband who can cook!
Yeah but, doesn't it
taste kind of murky?
No! That's impossible!
You forgot to rinse
the mushrooms didn't you?
No, how could I?!!
Your finish was weak.
Huh?
Your mind was filled
with apprehension
and that caused you
to lose your focus.
If you could make your
heart as clear as glass
you would not fall back
into such a deluded state.
I... I'm so sorry!
He's off his guard...
if you want to score with him,
now's your chance,
you sexy little squirrel!
Say what?!!
Grandpa, what are you
doing roaming around outside?
I'm sorry, do I know you?
Oh...! You keep
getting more senile!
Don't get sassy
with me, young lady!
That was our
guest Matakichi Ito.
Now it's time for the results...
who will the goddess
of victory smile upon?
On me!!
No, me!
Here's the chairman
of the tasting panel.
Masaru Suzuki.
Huh?
And now for his special dish,
roast duck with foie grae.
Oh, wow!
Masaru is a
much better cook
than you'd guess
by looking at him.
They ordered these ingredients
all the way from France!
It's absolutely delicious!
I know, you can't get
much more perfect than this.
I guess there's only
so much you can do
with local
ingredients, huh...?
Hmmmm... Well... Hey!
Production assistant, huh?
Anime is based on
comics after all...
could be a good experience.
You probably didn't
know that a lot of
the School Rumble characters
have part-time jobs...
Today, for a change of pace,
we'll take a look
at them at work.
Wow... so that fortress
is Studio Homet?
Well... here goes nothing.
Harima, for instance,
has gone to work as an
animation production assistant.
Sara and Asou work at
a Chinese restaurant run
by Mr. Chen from New Jersey.
Good morning, everybody...! Huh?
Is something wrong, Mister Chen?
Oh, Sara...!
I'm really in a pickle!
The hospital called and
my wife is in labor...!
They said our baby's gonna
be born a whole week early!
Why don't you just go ahead
and close the restaurant.
I can't... I've got
a reservation today!
That's okay!
Asou and I can
handle things here...!
Don't worry about a thing!
Thanks a lot, kids,
I'll see you later, good luck!
This won't work... Let's close.
We should at least take
care of the reservation.
It's more than the
two of us can handle...
I'll just explain
and send them away.
Nihao!
Hey there, Chen looking
good, my friend!
We'll need a table
for eight please!
Uh, I'm sorry, but the
restaurant is closed today...
Cheers!
They're not even listening.
Well, we can't
throw them out, right?
Let's give it a shot!
And so... their battle began...
I've just finished
this new costume.
I'd like you to wear it.
Uh... what is that, exactly?
Yakumo's boss was a cosplay fan.
Tea with Yakumo...!
Puts a song in my heart!
Huh?!
Yeahhhhh...
Holy crap!...!
They're making Yakumo dress up
in one of those
bunny girl costumes?!
Yahoo!
Man... I gotta see that!
No, it's wrong...
Which means that...
I must save her... and be...
A hero!
C... Come on in.
Oh... Hello.
I'll... have an espresso, please
Yes sir, I'll have that
for you in just a moment.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's the espresso you ordered.
The customers all stayed
in the shop 'til closing time...
Their constant staring
wore Yakumo out.
The Nishimoto family
business was a video shop...
several boys from
class had come to help
the popular Nishimoto
with the... remodeling.
There's nothing on the
shelves but the regular stuff.
Where are all the
"naughty" videos?
Yeah, I mean, that's the
whole reason we came here!
Huh?
What have we got here?
What is it?
We should investigate.
Aaand... pull!!
Why would there be a door there?
I see you've found it.
That is the forbidden room.
You mean, that's where
the "naughty" videos are?
Please, chief, you gotta
let us in that room!
We're begging you!
Very well, but know this,
no one who enters
that room comes out
the same man as before.
Now that you've been warned,
do you still have the
courage to proceed?
Though it cost us our lives,
we will dare to enter
the forbidden room!
As you wish.
And so... their
eyes were scorched...
and their souls plucked out.
Welcome to WasBurger!
Karen and Lara
work at WasBurger.
Yo...! Ichijou!
Yes?
Imadori!
What do you want?
I had to stop by.
You see... I couldn't go
anywhere but this restaurant.
Are you saying you...?
Gimme.
Huh...? But that's...
that's the children's super
duper Dozibiron fun meal.
I know... but jeez, give
a classmate a break!
I'm sorry...
Do it!
Come on, Itchy,
what goin' on...?
I thought you and
me were buddies!
The Itchy I know
would hook a guy up...
Dejale stupido!
Ichijou...! Help me...!
Please! Stop! Please!
So the battle between
Imadori and Lara raged on.
Tenma worked part
time at a bakery.
Here we go putting buns in bags,
buns in bags, buns in bags...
Whew, that's that...! Now
I can finally take a breather!
Hey, newbie, we got a
fresh batch of bread here,
so get your buns in
gear and get going!
Oh...! Right!
Finished!
Here's the next batch!
Next batch!
All done!
Not yet!
Here's some more!
And some more!
Man, I'm starting to get loopy!
Hey, I know!
I'll just pretend
these buns are Karasuma!
Ms. Tsukamoto...
put me inside you.
Ah!
Oookay. Moving on, then...
Akira works in a used bookstore.
Why a used bookstore?
Well, not that
many people come in...
and they let me read as much
as I like in my spare time.
Books, huh...?
I gotta admit, they're
not really my thing.
You would get a job that's
all about mental activity.
I have another job
that's more physical.
Since when?
Je comprend.
Je comprend?
If she told you about it,
she'd have to kill you.
Ahh... I'm exhausted.
Thanks for everything
you did today...
It was actually
kinda fun wasn't it?
Fun, huh...?
You are something else.
Well, I'm back.
Oh, my, how'd it go?
How's the baby?
No kid yet.
False alarm.
Huh?
They're gonna kill me!
Animation's no kinda
job for a human being...!
I'll stick to comics you
anime people are freaks!
Mister Nijo, I'd like to
welcome you to Studio Homet!
We think Genroku Defense Force
will be our best anime yet!
That was absolutely
unbefreakinglievable.
To think things
like that exist...
The Swimsuit Sumo series
is the greatest thing
I've ever seen in my life.
Yakumo...
Huh...? Sis!
Are you okay?
No, I don't really think
I'm cut out for manual labor...
I need to get a more creative
job... like saving the whales.
Invincible Robot Dozibiron...
I love you...
Let me fly away with you
and forget all the pain...
Dammit...
Someday I'll be an
original comic book artist,
make it into anime,
and settle down and raise
a happy family with Tenma!
Hm...? Man...
What the hell's
happennin' to this country?
Just hang on, Tenma.
Wait, was that...?
There's no way.
You formed a girls'
basketball team?
Hey, I didn't form it!
There're some cute girls on
that team, aren't there...!
Can I join?
You're not a girl, idiot!
Next time on School Rumble!
Well, the subtitle says it all.
Do it right, will ya?