♪ One... two...
one, two, three! ♪
♪ The library, the library,
it's here at school, ♪
♪ and it's full of books,
yep, full of books... ♪
♪ And when you come here,
it's nice and quiet, ♪
♪ you can concentrate,
and study well... ♪
♪ Study well... ♪
♪ Study... ♪
Tenma... Tenma... Tenma!
Eri?
I'm in big trouble...!
I need a favor and you're the
only one who can help me!
Tenma? Who's that...? Huh?!
Hey...! Hold on! Have
I always been this tall?!
For some reason,
Tenma was a hundred and
sixty-five centimeters tall.
I'm sorry to bother you, Tenma,
but I can't find my textbook,
and without it, I can't study.
I would buy a new one,
but I lost my wallet, too...
And I have to take
big exam tomorrow...
Why do I have to
be such a loser?
Don't worry. I'll give you mine.
Huh?!
But then you won't
be able to study...
No... it's all right, 'cause...
I've already memorized
the entire book.
Thank you so much, Tenma!
It's okay...
You should always help
out when a friend's in need.
Tenma! Help!
Uh! Akira?! Mikoto?!
You shouldn't run in the hall!
This math problem is so hard,
we can't figure it out...!
And we're going to be
held back if we don't!
Help, you genius!
Let's see here.
You're right. It is a doozy...
But if you just do this...
Voila!
Thanks, Tenma...!
We knew that you could do it!
We'll never forget
what you've done for us.
It's all right...
Let's all pass math together!
For some reason, Tenma's IQ was
also a hundred and sixty-five.
Shoot!
For some reason,
Tenma's jump was also
a hundred and
sixty-five centimeters.
Duwa!
For some reason,
Tenma also had a hundred
and sixty-five
wrestling wins in a row.
Thank Heaven, thank heaven,
'cause heaven sent
Tenma to you all...
For some reason,
Tenma also scored
a hundred and
sixty-five points at karaoke.
Hey, guys, look...!
It's Tsukamoto!
Oh my god! It's Tenma!
I love you!
She's so gorgeous!
Seeing her is a great
way to start the day!
Tenma! Look over here!
Hey! Quit pushing!
Tenma, can we
have your autograph?!
Sure thing... But one at a time.
My goodness! Please,
take it easy everybody!
She's as popular as ever, huh?
Yep, but she's different.
She's not stuck-up.
It's nice that
someone as popular
as her hangs out
with people like us.
Um, Tenma...? Will you please
go out on a date with me?
Hey, I was here first...!
Go out with me instead!
Forget you losers!
I'm the only one
who can make her happy!
Oh, wow, thanks,
guys, all of you... But...
Sorry, my heart is already
set on someone else!
For some reason,
Tenma also turned down
a hundred and sixty-five boys.
Dammit! Who the hell is it?!
Yeah! Who's the guy
that Tenma loves so much?!
My reason for living is gone!
Boy, Tenma, you
sure are popular.
Everything you do is perfect.
I wish I could be like you.
Hey, don't talk
like that, Eri...
You're terrific too, girl!
What a pickle.
Everyone seems to really like
me, and that makes me happy.
But what about him?
The boy that I really like?
Miss Tsukamoto...
Who is it? What's the matter?
You look so serious.
Listen, there's something
important I need to tell you.
I love you.
Wait, that can't be true... No!
Harima, I thought you
had feelings for Yakumo--
I don't... Since I met you...
You're the only one I've loved!
Tenma... Go out with me.
It was just a dream?!
Oh, why would
I have one like that?
It was so weird... and silly.
But still...
Tenma... Go out with me.
I was surprised to
hear Harima say that...
Hey, Tsukamoto.
Uh...?
Huh...? What the--...?!
W-what's going on?!
Why's my heart beating so fast?!
You okay? You're red.
What's wrong...?
You got a fever or somethin'?
Um... Hey, Harima...?
Yeah?
Um... We need to talk...
Sure... 'Bout what?
Oh, look, I, I don't
know exactly why, but--
Oh, Harima, I--
Tenma, you gotta say,
"I love you!"
You have to make the alien eat
a snow cone before it rains.
Let's dig in!
Sis, I forgot to ask...
Did your studying go well today?
Nope, I fell asleep...!
There's always tomorrow!
Come on, guys, tomorrow's
my freakin' birthday...!
I wanted to rock out
with my socks out.
Paint the town red, you know...?
But now Yakumo's gotta
go to work even though
it's a school holiday
and we've got the day off...
Yeah, and I've got a
previous commitment tomorrow
and there's no way
I can get out of it.
Sorry, Tenma...
But I already promised I would
help out at the dojo tomorrow...
Besides, we have
exams coming up.
Hm...?! Are you saying
that stupid tests
are more important
than my birthday?!
Look, once this term is over,
we'll throw you a
belated birthday bash.
Oh, really?
I'm tellin' you, girl...
Party of the century!
Wait a minute!
You mean I'm the only person
who's going to be
able to celebrate
with lonely little
Tenma on her birthday?
Happy Birthday.
Harima...
Sorry. I know I'm
probably not the person
you wanted to hear this from...
No, I'm happy...
In fact, I'm happier to
hear it from you, Harima,
than I am from Eri and the
rest of my so-called friends...
Tenma!
Okay!
Now if I just casually work it
in that my birthday
is the day after,
then that can only
lead to one thing!
I wanted to wish you a happy
birthday in person, Harima!
Say, how about the two of us go
celebrate on our own right now?
Okay, what's the
deal with Harima?
He's looks constipated.
Okay, gotta get a plan
together for tomorrow...
First thing's first...
Move out...
Asleep... However...
Just as I thought.
The eagle has been spotted.
Curry? Awesome!
And just as I was
getting hungry, too.
Can't... believe
I fell for that!
After all that
I think I deserve this.
Oh, you silly little boy,
Always chasing
after silly girls,
Hoping that they love you,
Just as much as you love them,
But the thing is that you're
really lame...
Man, she really
went all out, huh?
I have to hand it to her...
Things I saw in there...
were horrifying...
That cat... But none
of that matters now!
With the information
in this magazine
I'll plan the best date ever...!
Nothing can stand in my way.
Gotta make her
think I'm a classy guy,
so I'll start by showing her
the famous sightseeing spots
of Tonarimachi, and then...
Morinoyakata, the western
cuisine restaurant!
That joint's pretty pricy...
but I'll bet anything it'll
really impress Tenma.
I'll just use the thirty
thousand yen
I've been saving up
for a new bike.
I'd be an idiot not
to spend it on her!
Now all I've gotta do is
think of how to invite her...
Yo, Big Brother!
I was thinking, 'cause today
is my birthday an' all...
Whoopty freakin' doo!
You should take me somewhere...
Then again,
it might get kinda boring
if it's just the two of us...
I know...! You should invite
some of your friends!
We could all have
a fun time together!
Like... I don't know.
Maybe that cute
Tsukamoto girl for example!
Shuji!
Oh, yeah...
Yeah...
Hi, Harima!
Sorry to make you wait!
Yo.
Oh, look who's here...
The little sassy boy
from way back when...
Remember, you still owe
me for room and board.
Shut up! I don't remember
you doing anything for me...!
I just wanted Yaku--
He's glad you could make it.
Are you crazy?!
This guy... What a joker.
He asked me to
specifically invite you, Tenma,
to come celebrate
his birthday with us.
Yeah...?! That's so sweet!
Aren't you just precious?
No...!
That Shuji. He's
a regular comedian.
Is that so?
Hey, guys, look!
There's a neat lighthouse
out there, Shuji!
Do you know a lot
about Tonarimachi?
What's the matter?
Does that surprise you...?
Don't let my
appearance fool you.
I am quite the scholar of
scenic and historic sites.
I might teach you
a thing or two today.
This shrine is what I like
to call a solitary beauty.
Ooh! This is gonna
be great, Shuji!
That... That's all there is...?
There's nothing else to see?
How stupid... This is no
"solitary beauty".
It's just some deserted temple.
Hey! Shut your mouth...!
The next place
will be spectacular!
This is the famous
Hasegawa Temple.
Its rear gardens are brimming
with crimson leaves
this time of year...
Plus you can see the ocean.
It's quite a dramatic view.
Wow! I can't wait to see it!
Don't worry, you will.
Just hold your horses.
We've gotta pay
the admission first.
Sorry, we're closed for the day.
So... try coming
back when we're open.
Dramatic view, huh?
Yeah, right. There's
nothin' dramatic about it.
More like traumatic,
if ya ask me.
Nicely put, but just
think how disappointing
this would be if
it were a real date.
Oh yeah, right.
It'd be like going
out with some guy
who just threw a plan
together the night before.
Hey, some guys actually do that,
then think everything'll
work itself out.
Are you serious?
Wow, those guys
have to be really dumb.
Dammit! Just because
they're along for the ride,
they think they can
say anything they want!
This could get bad
if they keep it up.
That was too bad, huh?
Tenma!
She knows I'm a pathetic loser!
It's too bad you're
such a lame-o!
Damn! I can't even
bring a smile to the face
of the girl
I love on her birthday!
Why are we even celebrating?!
Only got one chance: dinner!
Gotta hang in there!
Big Bro? Are we even close to
that restaurant you
were talking about?
Do you know where you're going?
Harima, you're
not lost, are you?
Uh... no... I'm not lost.
It is this way, right?
See... Told ya so.
This is really it...? It looks
expensive if you ask me.
Yeah... So what?
No training wear,
sandals, or shorts allowed.
Interesting...
So... Can you afford a
place that has a dress code?
Can you?
Of course I can
afford it...! Let's go!
Wow...
We still haven't reached
the entrance yet, huh?
Good evening.
Uh... Right.
Whoa...! This is such
a fancy restaurant!
Big brother...?
It's a nice place and all,
but are you sure you
can afford it...? Hello?
Huh?
Uh, yeah, no problem.
I actually come here,
uh, all the time.
Your menu, sir.
Oh, thank you.
Hmm, let's see...
Tens, hundreds, thousands,
tens of thousands!
Tens and tens and tens
and tens of thousands!
So... much... money.
Uh, on second thought...
What a variety!
Even all the names
sound delicious...!
I don't know how
I can possibly choose!
I can't do it!
I can't admit I don't have
enough money in front of Tenma!
Not now! Just look
how happy she is!
Now you, sir...?
What can I get you?
Uh... right... A water...
Hm...? So...
four mineral waters.
Will be you be ordering
anything else this evening?
Uh! Yeah, of course.
Uh, we'll take four of your
Chef's Specials, please.
Very good, sir.
Now please allow us to
show you to your table...
How nice.
Thanks you very much!
Didya see...? They pulled
our chairs out for us!
Routine.
Really...? You think so...?
Wasn't that amazing, Harima?
Uh... yeah sure was.
Wow...! This looks delicious!
Time to masticate.
Big Bro...
It's... delicious...
So delicious.
Are you crying?
No...
I love it...!
I mean, this food...
It's the best I've ever had!
Harima, thank you!
Yeah... of course...
it's no problem.
So you claim.
Oh, man! I'm way over budget!
I can't even afford
whatever the hell it is
we're eating right now!
Another steak!
Huh?!
One more, plea--!
Whoa...! Hold on there!
I'll take another, too!
If that's okay
with you, Harima...
They're delicious!
Yeah, yeah...
Have as much steak as ya like...
All right, then...
Shuji boy, why don't
we have a contest
to see who can eat the most?
You're on...!
I'll kick your ass!
Another! Another! Another!
Another! Another!
I hope you saved
room for dessert.
Oh, wow! Look at all
the different choices!
Which one of them can we get?
Choose whatever you like.
If dessert's here...
Then it's almost over...
Let's see, thirty-four thousand
per person, times four,
that's one hundred
and thirty-six thousand!
I don't have enough!
I'm short by over
a hundred thousand!
The autumn leaves turned a
little late this year.
I agree, but they did look
positively resplendent
around two weeks ago.
Damn! Rich people talk about
the dumbest things, don't they?!
Pardon me...
Are you ready for
the check now, sir?
Oh, crap.
What do I do...?
Uh, maybe if I talk rich,
he'll think I'm rich.
So uh... I really like leaves.
Sir?
I'm just sayin' that
leaves are like positive
and resplendent
sometimes, y'know?
Sorry?
I, uh... I meant
that autumn leaves
sure are pretty, aren't they?
Crap! He's getting suspicious!
Could you show me
where the restroom is?
Right this way, sir.
It's no use.
I'm so sorry, Tenma.
I guess I'm gonna see that
sad look on your face again.
The check...
Huh?
You see... I, uh...
Add this gentleman's
check to mine.
His dinner's on me.
Rich Girl...
Well, well, Miss Sawachika...
And how was your dinner this
evening with Mister Hayashi?
The conversation was boring,
frankly, but the
food was delicious.
Well, I am always
pleased to hear that.
Rich Girl... Why are you here?
You were eating
with Tenma, right...?
Well, you shouldn't keep a
girl waiting on her birthday.
Look, I'm only
doing this for her,
so don't get any ideas...
Now hurry up and
get back to your seat.
Eri! You're here, too?!
Great! Come have
dessert with us!
Oh, Tenma, what a coincidence.
I hope I'm not imposing.
I owe ya.
Thank you, Harima!
Today was so much fun!
Yeah, it was, wasn't it...?
Pretty much perfect!
All right, got her lined up.
No better time than now.
Just tell her tomorrow
is your birthday...
Hey, Tenma, did you
know that tomorrow is my--
To think he did all
of this just for you!
Harima's a nice,
big brother, isn't he?
Yeah!
Yes, indeed.
Moron.
Here it is my birthday,
and I'm all alone.
I can't do anything right.
Ya tryin' to cheer
me up there, Pyotr?
Hey, thanks...
Hey, cut it out.
Yummy Brains...
Ah, well... at least
I got to see Tenma smile.
That's all I needed.
Okay, Pyotr, put me
down. This is weird.
I think I might be sick!
Hey, stop it!
Don't come near me...!
Next time, on School Rumble:
"When I Turned Around,
There He Was.
In Karasuma's Name.x
All Mysteries Revealed!" Say,
I think I've seen him before...