Two hundred years ago...
at a certain tea house
along a country highway...
Here's your food...
Thank you.
Tasty!
Lord Samurai...
you are truly fortunate.
Our dumplings are known as
the best-tasting on the highway.
So I see.
No wonder you're doing so well.
Is something wrong?
The truth is, our sick father
requires expensive medicine,
and we're deeply in debt to the
ruthless Tennoji moneylenders.
If we can't pay back what
we owe them by the deadline,
they're going to take the
teahouse away from us!
Unacceptable!
They've bribed the
local officials to let them
charge outrageous
levels of interest!
That's completely disgraceful!
But have no fear, madam...
I'm not the world's
greatest samurai...
but I swear to stand by
you in your hour of need!
Do you really mean it?
Thank you, noble
warrior, thank you!
I knew we could count
on you, Lord Samurai!
No gratitude need be voiced!
And so, on the day
of the deadline...
It's... awful...!
Looks like this is
the end of the teahouse!
Well... ready to pay us
the money you owe us,
or do we have to get tough?
Oh, please, sir... is there
nothing else we can give you?
Sure, I'll take you as payment.
Uh... but I...
No, wait...! If you
must take someone, take me!
No way... we only
take the pretty ones.
Okay, men... let's move out!
Not so fast!
I am Haruki Yasuboro Hanai,
leader of the Hanai clan...
and I have come to put an end to
this disgraceful injustice...!
Now, release this girl or--
Huh?!
Who are you?!
I can see that
you're no amateur.
You asked for it!
Hey, boss...!
Boss Tennoji we need you!
We're screwed!
Oooh yeah... now would be
a good time for you to leave.
Uhh... maybe I spoke too soon!
Oh, wow...
Could it be, the
samurai of legend...?
It is I.
Hold on!
Harima, why are
you playing Mangoku?!
Miss Tsukamoto...
It's because this
is School Rumble.
Huh?
My name is Kenji Harima.
I'm in love with
Tenma Tsukamoto.
I've tried to tell her
this time and again...
each time,
I've failed miserably.
Meanwhile, to my dismay,
I've discovered that Tenma
is in love with Karasuma,
the absolute biggest
freak in our class...!
What does she see in him?!
In complete despair,
I started drawing comic books.
But then disaster struck again.
The artist I most
admired, Jo Nijo,
turned out to be
that jerk Karasuma!
What's more, my beard was
cut off, I was shaved bald,
and I ended up in
a romantic mix-up
with that blonde rich girl!
Finally, I fled
to the high seas...
where I met the man who taught
me the truth about life...!
I was reborn, and returned
home to draw the comic book
of my heart with the pen
I received from my master...!
I had finally
become a real man...
ready once again to
express my love to Tenma!
Hey Nara!
Huh?
Go get me a cup of coffee.
Uh... sure...
Yoshidayama... you really
shouldn't be sitting there.
Chill, willya...? Harima
hasn't been around for days!
Harima, good to
see you again...!
I was just making sure your
seat was nice and warm for you!
'Preciate it.
I have some bananas here,
maybe you'd like all of them?
Oh, yeah sure...
These things are awesome.
Harima!
How could you even
think of skipping school
this close to
the culture festival?
We're talking
school pride mister!
Shut up.
Oh, Tenma... where are you?
Harima... got a sec?
Huh?
What is it now, Itoko?
Call me Ms. Osakabe when
we're at school, remember.
This postcard came
for you this morning
and I forgot to give it to you
before you left the apartment.
Dan... ko... sha?
Is it something
you've been expecting?
It... it... it can't be!
I did it! The New Face prize!
Now's the time
to declare my love!
Where are you...?!
Where are you... Tenma?!
Tenma is up on the rooftop.
Thank you!!
One order of badass
comin' right up, Tenma!
Okay, sure...
I know love is a
personal matter...
and far be it from me
to butt into your
personal affairs, but still...
How can you tell me you're going
to stay over at Sara's house
and then I find
out you're really up
til all hours with
Harima instead?
Well, I...
Oh, no! Tenma's Sister is in
hot water and it's my fault!
You know, I've never done
anything with Karasuma,
so for you and Harima to- ahem!
I mean, even if you
are seeing each other,
I don't think that sort
of behavior is appropriate.
No! Tenma, you've
got it all wrong!
She was just staying up to help
me meet my comic book deadline!
But that's supposed
to be a secret!
Agh! She's protecting me!
Look... Here is your problem,
you're either too nice
or too agreeable to others,
you understand what I mean?
Boys see that and they think
you're easy to push around.
They think they can get
their own way with you!
That's why you have
to be more careful!
If Harima gets out of hand and
turns into too much of an ape...
Then you've got
to lay down the law
and tell him off good and hard!
I'm so sorry.
Aghhhhh! What are
you apologizing for?!
Now hold on there,
Miss Tsukamoto!
Harima?
What are you doing?
Harima, this is none
of your business.!
It's between me and Yakumo.
You keep your nose out of it.
But it is my business!
Your sister and I were only--
Bananas! Hooray!
Don't think you can
bribe me with these!
We'll worry about the
banana situation later.
Look, I know you're upset.
But there's nothing
to stress about.
I mean, sure, your sister
spent the night at my house,
but that doesn't mean that...
You spent the night
at his house...?!
I thought you were
just out at a restaurant
or riding on his bike
or something like that!
Ah! No, that is, I mean uh...
We were at Itoko, Ms. Osakabe's
place, that's what I meant!
Oh, come on!
Now I know you're lying to me!
Please Miss Tsukamoto!
We haven't done anything
to be ashamed of! Honest!
Look into my eyes...!
Are these the eyes of a liar?!
You're so cute, Tenma...
Aha...! Clammy sweat!!
Oh, no!!
Please believe me...!
Your sister hasn't done anything
dishonorable...! I swear it!
All right then...
I do believe you.
Whoa, seriously?
That wasn't why I was mad.
I was mad because
Yakumo didn't tell me the truth
in the first place,
not because she was out late.
And because
I missed her, you know?
She's my only sister,
she's all I've got.
Thank you, Tenma...
As long as you understand that,
that's all there is to know...
from now on you two can
live happily ever after...
ha, ha, ha!
Yes!! I'll devote my life
to your sister's happiness!
Uh...
Yeahhh, atttaboy, Harima...
I knew I could count on you!
Agh!
How did this happen?!!
Hey, Kenji...
are you sure it's all right
if I keep this video camera?
I can't believe you used my name
to enter some stupid raffle.
Why do you do
these things to me?
Well, I never have any
luck when I use my own name.
I feel kind of bad about it now.
Well, now that I've settled
that matter with Yakumo,
it's time for me to get
my head back in the game!
Word up!
So what do you
think of our costumes?
Karasuma's looking pretty
cool, don't you think?
His moves are really
coming along too!
♪ Tonight has such a
graceful crescent moon ♪
♪ Reborn every day,
every night, shining brighter ♪
You really do
look great, Karasuma.
Yeah!
Oh yeah!
Wa-hoo!!
And from there... who knows?
You mean you're
a music producer?
I heard rumors about an amazing
band, but this is incredible.
Want to make your
professional debut?
No... way... you really mean it?
We did it Karasuma...
We're going to have
our pro debut together!
Uh... sorry we don't need you.
Huh?
You don't sing or
play an instrument, right?
Bumped off by a technicality!
Karasuma...
He's gonna go away on tour, and
there's no telling how long...
Oh... hey, Karasuma...
Where is everyone?
They've gone...
Is something wrong?
I can't sing well... and
I don't play an instrument...
It makes me a
little sad... you know?
Uh, Karasuma?
Please don't feel bad...
I'm sure there's something you
can do well, Miss Tsukamoto,
if you just think
about it for a moment.
Something that
I can do well, really?
Mm-hm.
Turtle.
Turtle?
I don't get it at all!
Why did he say turtle...?
Karasuma, what
are you trying to tell me?
Sis, about that turtle, what...?
I can't give up...!
This is some sort of hint
to find what only I can do!
Let's see, turtle...
gumbo... turtle...
it can't be curry, can it?
Ah ha!
It's word association...!
I know! Turtle... soup!
Are you okay, Sis?
That wasn't it... turtle,
turtle, turtle stew!
Okay, no prob.
Turtle...
Cake!
King Kong!
Curry!
Cacciatore!
Turtle, team, tragedy, piglet,
toothpick, prickly rash.
Turtle, toes, toothpaste,
pasteboard, tiny seed,
mongoose, Mangoku, hot pepper!!
Uh... sis?
Why? Why can't I get anywhere?
What should I do? It's like
I'm under a curse or something!
Wait... a curse... if he's
talking about a curse,
then he must mean
Sleeping Beauty!
I figured it out!!!
The only thing it can
mean is that Karasuma thinks
that I should play
Sleeping Beauty
in the culture
festival this year!
All right then, I'll do it!
I'm not sure I follow you...
but good for you, Sis.
Hey guess what this is!
A turtle.
No, no... this is...
Sleeping Beauty.
Bingo! That's our Akira!
What?
How so?
A turtle creeps...
Sleeping Beauty sleeps.
Oh, yeah! That's how
I figured it out, too... duh.
Yakumo! Are the
box lunches ready?
I tried to make yours just
the way you wanted me to, sis.
Okay, I hate to ask, but can you
deliver it to my class at lunch?
Huh...? But how come?
Never you mind, never mind...
just do this one
little favor for me, okay?
Well... I'm off to
watch Karasuma practice,
so I'll be seeing
you later, sis!
I hope you'll
forgive me, Yakumo...
if I hadn't called over to
your house the other night,
your sister wouldn't have
found out you were staying
at Harima's place
instead of mine.
That's all right...
it's not your fault, Sara,
I shouldn't have lied to her
in the first place,
it was my fault.
But now that it's
all out in the open,
you don't have to hide anymore.
You can be together in
front of everyone if you want.
What...? It's not
like that, Sara...
Good morning.
Um... good morning to you too.
That was weird...
You know, maybe Sawachika really
does like Harima, like I heard.
The festival's nearly here...!
This year I'll be starring
in "Sleeping Beauty"
with Yakumo Tsukamoto
of class 1-D!
He is so sad.
He must be the only
one who doesn't know.
What do you think is gonna
happen when he finds out?
And now, I'm off to see Yakumo!
Shouldn't we stop him
before it's too late?
Guess so.
Hey, Hanai!
Yes, what is it, Mikoto?
The culture festival
programs are put on as a class.
Yakumo's not in ours...!
Just give it up!
Ha, ha ha...!
With my powers as
class representative
I'll have no trouble
overcoming that obstacle!
Okay, that was useless.
Yep. It looks like
it's only a matter of time.
Let the drama ensue.
Still, Eri... he doesn't
give up as easily as you do...
you have to
admit that, at least.
Will you give that
nonsense a rest already...?!
I told you before
that was Tenma's mistake!
Right, after you injured your
ankle at the athletic meet,
Harima bravely took your
place, led 2-C to victory,
and you were so impressed
by his selflessness,
you got carried away and
ended up slow dancing with him.
Yeah, well, as long as
we got that straight.
Oh, of course! We get it!
You know,
She totally wants his bod.
Yeah.
What are talking
about over there?
After six months of planning...
it's been a long journey...
but now my dreams
will come to fruition.
Hey did you hear about
Tsukamoto in class 1-D?
Yeah... I heard she's seeing
that bad boy
Harima from our class.
Eh?
It can't beeeeeee!!!
And... he knows.
So tragic.
You hear that?
I could've sworn
that was Hanai's voice.
Yeah.
I have a bad feeling about this,
but I have to
deliver this lunch.
Hey... did you guys
hear a scream just now?
We did.
But you're just
gonna make it worse
if you go sticking
your nose into it.
Now, that's just mean, Eri!
Hey... I thought you were
having a box lunch today?
As a matter of fact...
It... can't be...
She can't be seeing Harima...
Tsukamoto... how you doin'?
Oh, hey... I'm doin' alright.
It's Yakumo!
I've got a question.
Yaaa... ku... mooooo!!
Did you really stay over at
Harima's place the other night?
Uh... yes... but it... it
wasn't what you think, Miki...
Come on... you know
how shy Yakumo is...
it's such a chore getting
the two of them together.
This is not good.
I have to clear this mess
up somehow...
Harima!!!
What the hell's your problem?
You are... you bastard...
Yeah...? Bring it on,
four-eyes!!
Hey... what are you doing?
Is this for real?
Gee, what's the
matter with Hanai?
Aww... man.
It's serious.
Hey, sis...
Oh, you're here...!
I've been waiting!
Hey killer...? You alright?
Hey, Harima!
Go on, Yakumo... Why don't
you give him his lunch!
His what?!
Uh... okay... here.
Uh, thanks ...
It's packed with
Yakumo's love...! Ta da!!
It's not true...!
It's not truuuuuuue!!
Oh yeah... you're a
lucky guy... Harima!
How fascinating.
Pardon me.
Huh?
Class 2D hereby
formally challenges
Class 2C winner take all.
What do you say we
settle the whole thing
at the upcoming
culture festival?
Say what?!
You're insane!
The culture festival isn't
just for fun and games,
you know... it's war!
Hey, Ichijou... now it's on!!!
I'm glad you could all make it.
For today's meeting I thought
we would turn the spotlight
on our female classmates.
Neophyte Nara...
have you the materials?
Yes sir.
The data has been forwarded
to all your personal computers.
Mmmm... So, who is first?
Megumi Sagano...
This isn't well known,
but in middle school,
she was in the
basketball club...
This may account
for the exceptional
shapeliness of her legs.
Yes.
We overlooked that before!
Neophyte Nara...
your work is improving.
Thank you, sir!
Tsumugi Yuki... The only
bespectacled girl in our class.
Oh yeah, she is...
and a valuable asset
to our class as well!
Mai Otsuka, 2-C's
class representative.
According to
information gathered
from a friend in middle school,
she's actually concealing
an enormous bust.
What...? How the
heck did I miss that?
Tenma Tsuka--...
Okay, keep moving.
Mihara Kozue...
The sharpest dresser in 2-C.
Judging from the contact
she has with other boys,
we believe she is
very experienced.
Just look at how her lightly
tanned skin contrasts
with her tan lines!
Commander, I don't think I can
contain myself very much longer!
Calm yourself...
And go get a tissue...
we still have one more
special report to listen to...
Neophyte Nara?
Sir!
Ms. Itoko Osakabe...
Her figure and
style go without saying.
Her intellect and
worldliness create
a libidinous air not
found in our classmates.
It sure does!
But Commander, this is old news,
we already know all
about Ms. Osakabe.
Yes, but I want you
to consider this.
She's an older woman
and a female teacher...
When you combine
these two elements,
her appeal becomes limitless!
She's totally off the scale!
Sir, you truly are a master!
All of our data is
being attacked by
some kind of a virus!
It's happening to me too!
Somebody make a back up!
All of our precious
data is being ruined!
This sucks.
Hey! One file survived!
Quick, open it up!
He shaves it!
It's the culture festival!
Will we do a play?
A coffee shop? Huh?
You mean we're gonna
decide with a survival game?
Next time on School Rumble
Second Semester:
"Strategies, Battlefields,
Friends!"
My Colt Python is
gonna spit fire!