Charm up, my "Mai" dream!
Remember to always
watch TV with the lights on...
and don't sit too close!
We'd like everybody
to submit story ideas
for the culture festival play.
However...! You're not allowed
to cast yourself in the lead!
We'll take any ideas
that include class
members in key roles.
Mai and I will
assemble the final script.
So we have to accept whatever
casting they come up with?
Wow, we got a lot, didn't we?
Well, at least gives
us a lot to work with.
Huh...? Hey there Mai,
hey there Tsumugi!
Hey, Tenma.
We were just working out a few
ideas for the coffee shop...
Hope you have fun with the play.
Thanks!
Well, let's see what we've got!
Uh...
I never... dreamed we'd ever...
Oh, Hanai, my love...
Yakumo, I can't believe
this day has finally come,
I don't know what to say!
It's not Yakumo, silly.
It's me, Kenji Harima!
I... don't care...
Say what?!
You' are so gorgeous...
so lovely...
Wait a minute! Hold on!
What do you think you're doing?!
I can't hold back!
I can't fight this
feeling any more!
Harima...
Haruki...
Hey you guys,
is there something wrong?
No! Nothing at all!
Nothing at all!
What was that about?!
Don't ask me. I guess it
was someone's idea of a joke.
Ugh, now I can't get
that image out of my head!
Okay. Shake it off.
On to the next one.
Un, deux, trois... Un, deux,
trois... Un, deux, trois...
Un, deux, trois...
Ichijou...! Mihara...!
What was that?!
Do you expect to
become a prima ballerina
with that kind of sloppy work?
No, ma'am!
I'm tired! Don't we get
a break? God(bleep)it!
You want a break
you pu(bleep)sies?
That's just too bad!
So disrespectful!
Wait just a moment!
It's Prima Miko!
They meant no harm...!
Don't be cruel!
Please forgive them!
Fine...
Ah...! Thank yoooooooouuu!
What radiance...! She's like
a jewel, like two jewels...!
D-cup!
I'm sorry, Mikoto...
but with your figure...
And your singing voice...
we'll never be able
to get anywhere!
We have no choice
but to get ghetto!
Intense.
How's it going, you guys?
Huh...? What's the big secret?
Sorry.
We just don't want to
ruin the surprise is all...
ha, ha, ha, ha!
Wow, who do you suppose
came up with that one?
Well, maybe it was Saeko,
she gets carried away.
And she's kind
of dark, you know?
All right, then, moving on...
Can I help you... hm?
Yes... um... one bowl of...
your cheapest soba noodles.
Wait a sec, you were part of the
Sawachika Trust, weren't you?
That seems like
another lifetime ago...
the company went bankrupt...
and now I'm living this
life of abject poverty.
How many lives did
your company destroy
with its evil business
practices? Hm?
You nearly ruined
my business the way
you ruined so many others!
I know you!
Now do you understand what's
it like to be poor and helpless?
There are people out
there who live on nothing
but a bowl of rice
a day and some broth!
I'm sorry! Really I am!
That twist at the end there
reminded me
of the first story...
Do you think Harima wrote this?
Maybe... he probably thinks
if he appears in disguise
for the first part of the
story it means we won't think
he's cast himself as the
main character... pathetic.
That so sounds like
something he would do.
Hmmmm?
I see... so Harima wrote
this little epic, did he?
We're not sure...
Quiet.
Now... now...
it's the culture festival,
I can put my feelings aside.
Mikoto, I have to go take
care of something, okay?
Right... moving
on to the next...
I'm Mai Otsuka!
Usually I'm just an average
first year high schooler!
But the truth is, I have
a secret I can't tell anyone!
Charm up, my "Mai" dream!
I'm a magic girl!
And I have special powers.
You know Mai, you would
be a good magic girl.
Whatever! Shut-up!
Let's think about it over night.
It's gonna be hard
pulling all this together...
there must be someone
who's good at doing this.
Takano, you're still here.
Huh...? Yeah.
Heyyy... Have you noticed that
Takano really likes reading?
Yeah, she'd be perfect
for this. She's so smart!
And she never panics...
she's like, got it all...
"brains and beauty"...!
She's so cool!
What do you think...
should we ask her?
Hm?
Listen, Takano... would
you like to write the script
for the class play?
You can do it!
In fact... you're
the only person who can!
Mm... but I...
Hey, it's a good offer.
You should totally do it.
Easy for you to say...
I'm no good at
dealing with this.
Don't be silly... You're just
letting yourself get tense.
You're usually the
one with that problem.
When'd you become Miss Mellow?
I've always been mellow!
But seriously...
You'd be great...
So just do it, okay.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Wow... I don't think I've
ever seen you smile before.
It's weird... it makes you look
like you're up to something.
It does not.
I'm not kidding...
it's really creepy.
This is what we collected
today and yesterday.
All you have to do is write
a script based on
the stories you like.
All right.
Hmm... What's this?
Once upon a time
there was a girl
who was very anti-social.
Her grades were good but
she was a mischief maker...
she was rebellious and
a tease... however...
she had some
extraordinary talents.
She liked to read and
loved to write stories...
she even wrote a
play for her class
to perform at the
culture festival.
Her classmates were
grateful for her talents
and she lived
happily ever after.
Must be Eri...
Good friend,
but horrible writer.
Hey, Harima!
Huh?
Uh, soba noodles?
Please forgive me
for not understanding
what it's like to be
poor and helpless!
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about!
You do too!
You're staying over
at school tomorrow?
Yeah... our class
is way behind
on getting ready for
the culture festival.
Oh, are you worried
about Harima?
It's all right, don't worry,
just leave it to your sister!
Huh...? What are
you talking about?
Thanks for dinner!
What did she mean by that?
Huhhh?!
It's simple really...
you just ask Harima what sort
of things he likes and what his
favorite type of girl is
and all that sort of stuff...
If I did it, he'd know
I was up to something,
but it'd sound
natural coming from you!
Are you crazy? No!
You really don't
like Harima, do you?
No, Tenma! Not even remotely!
And what brought this
on all of a sudden?
Mm...! Actually, I'm trying
to find out for Yakumo!
You know, she's so shy...!
But for the invincible
battle ship Eri,
this would be
a piece of cake!
Okay, thanks a lot!
Wait a minute!
Wh... what do I do?
Uh, hey, Whiskers...
Huh?
Uh, yeah, hi,
I'm doing a questionnaire
for the coffee shop
menu and I wonder
if you could take a
minute of your time
to tell me a little
about your preferences.
Huh...? Sure, I guess.
All right... Good job, Eri!
You're... kidding.
Generally speaking,
do you like girls
who know how to cook, yes or no?
What?!
That has nothing to do
with the coffee shop menu!
Eri must be trippin', yo!
No...! As long as there's love,
cold noodles in a
cup would be fine!
I can't believe it.
He actually fell for it.
Good one, Eri...! I sure
picked the right girl, huh?
No comment!
Okay, next question.
Shoot.
Which do you like better,
a girl who's good at
sports or one who isn't?
Either one would be fine...
oh, but it might be cute
if she couldn't swim.
He couldn't mean...?
Uh... next question, Whiskers...
I mean, Harima...
Can you tell me what
kind of hair style
you like a girl to have?
Once again, that has
nothing to do with menu!
That's true, but it's
not like he'll notice.
Wait a minute!
That's Tenma back there...!
So that's it! Now I get it!
She wants to know what
I like...! Heh, heh, heh...!
Silly girl, naturally
I like everything about you!
Hm...! That's a real easy one!
I like girls with
squirrelly lookin' pigtails.
Can you feel my love, Tenma?
Hey... you listening?
Does he mean it...? He said...
he said he wasn't
seeing anyone, so...
So then you must mean...?
Pig tails... I'm a fiend!
Hey, sis...
You forgot your things.
Huh?
Good thinking... Yakumo!
What...? What are
you talking about?
Everybody... we're heading
over to the bath house.
Huh?
Woo-hooo...! It's huge!
There it is.
The girls will be right next
door in the next room, naked.
We may not be able to see them,
but still, this is,
without a doubt...
Paradise!
Oh hey... What?
You surprised to see me?
My family owns this bathhouse.
Come on and strip down everyone.
Relax, I've seen
it all before...
I'm not looking.
If my hair had
been different then...
I wonder... what
he would have said?
Woo--hoo!
Wow... Karen you
look really great!
Uh, thanks, I guess.
Yeah, girl, you
got a rockin' bod.
You... you think?
You know, this is
still embarrassing.
What? Getting naked
in front of everyone?
Yeah, it's a little awkward.
Hey, hey, we should
all go in together!
All right.
Right.
Okay, ready, set... go!!
Ahhh... bathhouses
are the greatest.
They sure are.
Is that a girl over there?
Uh...
can I borrow some
shampoo, Yoshidayama?
Carolyn!
Shall I soap your back?
Yeah...! That'd
be great, thank you!
Hey, you too, Mikoto!
Huh? All right!
This is so relaxing...
nothing matters
when I feel like this.
Hey there Sawachika.
What's up...?
So now that we're
all casual like this,
I wanted to ask you...
what 's the story,
are you seeing Harima?
What? Harima?
Hey, yeah!
I've been wondering about
that for a while too now
and it's been driving me crazy!
Yeah, come on, you can tell us!
I'm sorry... have you
been waiting all this time?
Ohh... it's all right.
Now come on...
let's head home...
to our cozy flat.
Sorry it's so small...
When I earn more money...
we'll get a bigger
place, I promise.
You silly girl...
your hair got so cold while
you were waiting for me...
Here, let me warm you up.
I love you.
Harima, what is your deal?
Those boys are so noisy!
Okay, if you want my opinion,
I think you two would
be great together!
Yeah, I totally agree,
you guys look so natural
when you're talking
to each other!
So what's the scoop?
Are you guys an item?
Wow, I never knew...
is that how Whiskers and
I look to everyone else?
It's true...
when I talk to him
there isn't any pretense...
or fake smiles...
to be honest...
I'm surprised by it myself.
To tell the truth...
I think Harima is...
What kind of loser blonde
puts their hair in
friggin' pigtails?!
What are you talking about?
I don't get you!
A disgusting pig.
You're so right!
Hey, Eri...!
Where are you going?
You're not Eri.
Whoa. How'd it get so late?
Man, I'm starving...
Is there anything to eat?
Hey, girls, why don't we
all make some rice balls?
Yeah! Good idea!
Hey, Nara!
We finally got the Swimsuit Sumo
wrestling things ready to go!
Rice ball time!
Man, look at this!
That is quite a
variety of balls.
That's right!
The dishes are
separated according to
the girl who made them!
After you eat them,
you have to guess
which girl made
which set of rice balls!
How am I supposed
to handle this?
Sawachika's balls are mine.
Good luck, Karasuma!
Hey...! That's tasty!
Do you really like it?
'Cause I made that one!
No wonder it's so good, then!
Okay... I have to
find Tenma's rice balls
and say that
they're delicious...
I wonder, could this be it...?
Yeah! No question!
Naturally, I'd be the
one who could tell!
Now, how does it taste?
Okay, I can do this.
Oh, it's even
worse than I imagined!
But if that's Tenma's...
then I'm happy!
Good job!
Huh...? Hm...? Hmmm... Hm. Huh?
I got through to her!
Good for you, Tenma!
Oh, crap!!
I have to get this
taste out of my mouth!
The shape is kind of weird,
but what the heck,
beggars can't be choosers!
No waaaaaaaaaaay!
Impossible! It can't be!
How the hell could anyone
make something like that?
I can't believe
someone could top Tenma
in the awful taste department!
But then...
that means that Tenma
isn't the worst cook here.
Thank goodness!
Hey, uh, Whiskers...
Huh?
I just wanted to
say thanks for earlier.
Uh... What do you mean?
Would you mind eating these...?
We have to clean up.
You're kidding, you mean none of
these gluttons will eat them...?
No problem.
Ack...! That taste...!
Don't tell me the
first one I ate was...
Okay then, well try
not to work so hard!
I don't even know
I'm doing anymore.
G-got it down...
consciousness... fading...
must get taste out of mouth...
Hey, Harima!
It's Tenma!
Take a break, why don't
you, I've brought you
some refreshments
for all your hard work!
Oh nice timing...!
That's my Tenma!
Here!
Sweet death come to me.
Yummyyyyyy!
You mean it...? I'm so glad...
you can have them all!
Tenma... you win... you're
the worst cook... ever...
Jab! Jab jab! Jab!
Good work today.
Oh, thank you...
Your hard work did
not go unnoticed.
So are you feeling better...?
Now that you've cleared
everything up with Harima?
Yakumo's not going
out with him...
it was all a rather silly
misunderstanding.
Well... then give
it your best shot.
By the way... how are you doing?
Oh, romantically?
I would... say not that great
I see.
Well, you know, these things
can change in a single day.
So just try to be patient.
How 'bout you mind
your own business.
Well then, it looks
like we'll have to have
a race to see
who pairs off first.
Hey, it's not like
we're in a hurry!
Once I get the prize
for my comic book,
I'm definitely going to
declare my love to Tenma!
Hey everybody, look over here!
Perfect!
Cheese!
The culture festival
will be here tomorrow!
This is it, ladies and
gentlemen, the culture festival!
We of 2-C must
now unite to... What?
The tea club is also
doing a coffee shop?
Next time on School Rumble:
"Hostesses Are Culture,
Comics are Culture,
Cake is Also Culture!"
Where's Yakumo?