I've been flying for two weeks.
And I still haven't
seen... land.
A tornado! Crap!
Cruise equals happiness!
You know what Eri...?
I can't believe you invited the
whole class to go on a cruise...
That's amazingly cool.
Well, I thought it
would be more fun
if a lot of people came with us.
There's more than
enough room on the ship.
Plus, I really like the idea
of being able to hang out
with everyone before
winter break is over.
And what's better than relaxing
on a cruise? Am I right?
Oh yeah.
Being on vacation
is no excuse to stop
training, right Ichijou?!
Yeah, that's right!
Hey, Tenma.
Why isn't Karasuma here?
Yeah Tenma, how come you
didn't make him come with you?
Well, see...
He said he had to go
visit some of his relatives.
Oh, by the way,
where is Harima...?
Hey, Eri! Have you seen Harima?
He got on the ship
with the rest of us.
Did you hide Harima
away somewhere, Eri?
Why are you asking me that?
How am I supposed
to know where he is?
For all I know about him,
He's probably sulking in
some dark corner somewhere.
I finally get this
rare opportunity to go
on a dream cruise with Tenma...
But, I have to do the
30 page supplement
for the spring special...
and it's frickin' due
the day after tomorrow!
♪ Oh, say can you see? ♪
♪ By the dawn's
early light... ♪
One - Two! One - Two!
Look at this sky.
Reminds me of
my days in California!
Hey. Are you sure we're
going in the right direction?
Hold on. Let me take a look.
Just as I thought.
Right on target!
All right.
Full speed ahead!!
Huh? Aw, crap!!
Let's see. Awesome!
It looks like it's
thawing out just perfectly!
This is too heavy.
Is anybody out there?
I could really use
a hand in here!
Whiskers?
Leave it to me. I can
handle this big tuna.
Damn it!
I spent so much time on
that huge fishing boat,
and all I did was draw comics!
I give up! I give up!
You are such an idiot...!
Masaru? Take care of it, please.
I see.
So, you handled the
challenge well, didn't you?
Good job, Masaru.
Oh, wow! It's a Sashimi platter!
Yayyyy!
I'm going to see how the
children are doing down there.
I need you to take over for me.
All you have to do is
steer straight ahead.
I trust you won't
make a mistake.
I'm just a thug.
I'm no good to anybody.
Hey! Look over there!
That's Tougou and Harry!
What're they doing?
They really did it.
Huh? You mean,
you knew about this?
From what
I understand they wanted
to travel by kayak and
then try to catch up
with us somewhere
in the South Seas.
They were kayaking in
the middle of the ocean...?
Haven't they ever
heard of a typhoon?
Incredible!
They Kayaked all this way?
I can't believe this!
Wow.
That's freakin' amazing.
Huh?
Everybody!
Look over there! It's a reef!
We're gonna hit it!
Huh?
Ahh! We're gonna die!!
I fear no reef!
Indeed, the reef has destroyed
the vessels of many sailors
since the time of yore, and also
dashed their hopes and dreams.
Any ordinary sailor would
give up and try to turn around!
Not I. Please do not
lose heart, my friends.
Would you like to
try a tuna eyeball?
You kidding?
It's one of my favorites.
Masaru! What the
hell are you doing!
What's wrong with you!
We're about to crash into
a bunch of rocks! Turn it!
So, come on!
All you gods of the sea,
give me your worst
and I will overcome it all!
No challenge is too great
for me, for I am Tougou!
Full Speed Ahead!!
It's no use. The engine
is destroyed beyond repair.
This radio is out too.
There's no response.
Isn't there anything we can do?
I can't get a signal
on the cell phone.
Why aren't they working?
We're in an unusual area.
Special waves
interfere with electronics.
Similar to the ones
in the Bermuda Triangle.
Bermuda?
The only option we have
left is to go find another ship
and send it back to rescue you.
Please hurry. and good luck.
We'll be here waiting.
There was so much that
I wanted to say to you.
I'm alive.
You're here!
Yakumo! What is this place?
Wait... You're not Yakumo.
Who are you?
What am I doing here?
Ya'akamo!
Hold on!
Where am I? I've never
seen this place before.
But somehow...
it's very familiar.
Don't look at them!
They aren't who
you think they are!
Hey, you! Just what do
you think you're doing here?!
Sorry...! Uh... We've met?
Have we not?
What...?
But that's impossible...
I guess you're right.
My name is La'ara.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry... You look very
much like someone I knew
a long time ago,
from my travels abroad.
You must want to get back home
so you can see your friends.
You should talk to the queen.
Maybe she can help.
Oh! Da eri da! Hide fus e!
Takabisha! Takabisha!
That is our queen, E'eri.
I should've known.
Ya'akamo! Ja masuruna!
Shu'uga hitta Teyo!
There's a strange
feeling in the atmosphere.
I know. It's because
they are preparing
for this year's sacrifice.
Saso! Tuua Ruki!
She's the one they've chosen.
What?!!!!
Hanai to the rescue!
I don't know
what's going on here.
But I won't stand back and watch
you sacrifice an innocent girl!
Hey! What are you doing?!
It's the modern age
and you're stupid enough
to believe in this
prehistoric ritual?!
Meow.
You have just caused
us great catastrophe!
Because of you our
village will be destroyed
by the evil beast, Deviltusk!
Fine then!
I, Haruki Hanai, swear on
my life that I will defeat
your bloodthirsty,
demon god Deviltusk!
Well, if you want
to save Ya'akamo,
then you must do
exactly as I say.
On the night of the full moon,
go to the forest of Kutapanda
and kill Deviltusk for us.
This is Kutapanda's forest.
He sleeps inside that statue.
He is our village's
guardian deity.
It is said that if our
village is ever threatened,
he will once again
awaken and defend us.
Is that true?
It's not been tested.
And this forest is now
the lair of deviltusk.
I see.
This is bad!
Deviltusk is headed this way!
It's about time!
What exactly is
this monster anyway?
You don't have to do this.
D-D-D-D-Don't worry!
I p-p-p-promise
I'll take care of you!
Damn!!
I will not let you touch
her, you foul beast!
Look Hanai!
Kuta panda! Kuta panda!
Hold on!
Don't believe in fake gods!
Trust me instead!
Those eyes.
They're telling me something...
Could it be?
That this is the key
to awakening their god?
Kuta panda has awakened!
Hanai has given our
village hope for the future.
We thank you.
Don't mention it.
Um...
Hanai, father said
I'm to marry you. So...
What?!
So that, we'll
be together forever.
But Yakumo! It's so sudden!
What are you doing?
You're amazing, Ya'akumo.
Farewell!! Everyone!
Takabisha!
I will miss you... Hanai.
I just had a really weird dream
where Yakumo was Ya'akamo.
Huh?! That's insane!!
I dreamed the exact
same thing just now!
Wait! And I was
the queen, wasn't I?!
Yeah! You were!
Tell me why the hell both of
us had a dream about Hanai?
Yeah, seriously.
Ahoy!!!
What?! Is... i-is that Hanai?!
Hey!! Hey!!
You're right! It is him!
What is it? Whoa!!! It's Hanai!!
He's been flying ever
since the episode before last.
I wonder if he's
here to save us.
Of course! He brought
Kuta panda back to life.
Hey!!! Hanai!!!
This is weird!
What are all of you
guys doing out here?
You're the one who just
flew here on a kite, remember?
Good point...
I was just trying
to get back home...
But, I ran into some trouble
with the kite along the way.
So in other words, you're
stranded too, aren't you?
That is correct!
On my journey, I found
this strange little village...
awakened a sleeping deity,
and defeated the
demon Deviltusk.
But, I'm sure you don't
wanna hear about that anyway.
So, what the heck
are you doing out here
in the middle of the ocean?
It doesn't seem like this
ship has moved much
since I landed on it.
Oh, I see! You must be stranded!
I'm just kidding!
Oh, sh--!
I can't believe all the
food got tossed overboard.
I'm so hungry.
We're all gonna starve
to death, aren't we?
Don't do this, Imadori.
Come on, don't give up.
Hey, why don't we make up
a fun song or something?
A fun song or something?
♪ A-one, and-a-two, and-a! ♪
♪ Once upon a time there
was a number called three. ♪
♪ It fell over on its side,
and then it said to me: ♪
♪ "Whoopee! Look at me! ♪
♪ Now I look like
a couple of D's!" ♪
D-cups, that is...
Huh?! Oh crap!
Go to hell!
You stinkin' pervert!
What's wrong with you guys?!
What are you all
so depressed for?
Don't worry! Be happy!!
Shut up you idiot.
I can't even think.
I haven't had anything
to eat for an entire day.
I wish there was something
I could do to help Tenma.
Hey. Doesn't it seem like it's
gotten a bit chillier lately?
Yeah. It really does.
Don't worry about
a thing, Yakumo.
I'll try to keep you
as warm as I can.
Even if we don't survive this.
I'm glad I'm here
with my sister.
I'm trying to be strong.
But all I can
think about is food.
Oh, look!
No way! Karasuma?!
Naw, can't be!
But still, even if it is an
illusion, I'm happy to see him!
What? Are you trying
to tell me something?
Oh, I... I get it.
You're trying to tell
me not to give up, huh?
I think I understand.
I won't lose heart!
What's going on?
That's right. None of
us should lose heart!
'Cause we are the
world... and so on.
You guys!
Karasuma! Thank you so much!
All right!!
I'm gonna go take
a look at the engine.
I'll come too!
You wanna go catch some fish?
Abso-freakin-lutely!
Ichijou, we must find some
oars and paddle to freedom!
Huh?!
What was that?!
What the hell?!
It's a whale!!
Ahh...! It's a whale!
It's coming!
It'll kill us!!
Everybody duck!
What are you doing?! Get down!
We're dead!
Huh? What's happening?
Who'da thought a
whale would fall in love
with Tenma's sister
at first sight like that?
Well, I guess
it worked out for the best,
seeing as how
we're getting rescued...
Whale power!
It's the wave of the future.
Get it? "Wave"?
'Cause he's like, you know...
You're awesome,
Mr. Whale...! Thank you!
Not really that funny.
All right! Homeward
bound! Let's go!!
Yeah!!! All right!
Who's up for shuffleboard?
♪ ending song ♪
Miss Eri?
Da reeda ome'e?
All alone... with an old book...
and a sister
who's never changed.
Is this really what you want?
All alone? All alone.