Come on... faster...!
I can beat him!
The Black Phantom!
Hmph. Nice try, Junior.
You can run on
home to mommy, now.
You're not man enough to
take on the G-1 Phantom yet!
Well, well,
what do we have here?
Another contender, eh?
Very well, crimson lady.
If you wanna tango, let's dance!
You're hard to catch.
Gotta admit, I'm impressed.
Looks like you're quite
a little filly, aren't ya?
I get the feeling
this is gonna be
a New Year's Eve that
neither of us'll forget!
What the--?
You've gotta be kidding me!
No one's ever beat the Phantom!
What?! You're
actually accelerating?!
Here, on the Yagami Sidewinder?
Are you nuts, baby?!
You're on a bad stretch of road
whose curves have chewed up
and spit out even the
toughest street racers!
Your skills are inhuman!
Wait! Maybe you're not human.
Maybe you're the Grim Reaper.
Red is the color of death.
So I guess you've
finally come for me, huh?
Fine!
I'll race you to the
gates of Hell itself!
You're yielding?!
No... You shifted!
Guess your ride can't hold up
to the ocean winds, can it?!
Looks like that underweighted
chassis has turned against you!
Time for a... Phantom Turn!
Ugh! The sun!
You knew it.
You knew the exact time
the sun would be rising
and figured that
into your strategy.
Didn't think there'd be
anyone that good around here...
And after seeing you,
I don't know
if I ever wanna get
behind the wheel again.
Hey, you know the rules...!
No smoking!
Yeah, sorry about that.
I forgot, I was just
tryin' to calm down...
And cut out the backseat
commentary, will ya?
Get your own license if
you wanna yap like that!
First sunrise of the
New Year... We made it!
Great view.
That looks great on you, Tenma.
Thank you, Yakumo!
Isn't it perfect?!
Oh, I wish Karasuma
could see it...!
I wonder if he's going to visit
the shrine for New Year's.
K-Karasuma, there's
something I need to tell you...
and that's Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, Ms. Tsukamoto...
By the way, I love you
in that kimono.
Really?!
Yes. I didn't
recognize you at first.
I never realized
how beautiful you are.
Come on silly, cut it out.
Quit joking around like that.
It's true.
Tenma... Close your eyes.
Karasuma...
Uh, Tenma? Can you hear me?!
Hey, snap out of it!
Sis! Knock it off!
Harima... Harima!
What the heck? Where am I...?
And how did I get up here?
Harima!
Tenma!
Harima...! Oh, at last!
My love, I've been
looking for you!
For me...?
Now we can finally be
together forever, Harima.
Wait, so that means...
You... love me
the way I love you?!
Oh, finally...!
It's like... It's like...
Like... a dream... Dammit!
Why'd it have to be a dream?!
Why couldn't it have been real?!
Wait! Don't people
say the first dream
you have in a new
year always comes true?
All right! Better go pray
at the shrine to be safe!
Hang on, God, I'm on my way!
Uh-oh!
Looks like we've had our
first wardrobe malfunction,
and what a view!
That young lady just won
Swimsuit Sumo Wrestling's
first "booby prize" of the year!
Hey, no "Happy New Year?"
Oh right, sorry...
Happy New Year, Youko.
Why, thank you...
Happy New Year to you, too.
Thank you. I gotta run. See ya.
He's such a loser.
Oh my gosh, I didn't know
there'd be so many people!
In a crowd like this,
I don't know how I'm
supposed to find Mikoto!
Are you all right,
Miss Tsukamoto?
Karasuma!
Be careful.
It's difficult to
move around in a kimono.
Boy, you're telling me!
It's pretty but it's like
wearing a straitjacket!
So, did you come
to visit the shrine?
I did.
Since we're both here,
why don't we go see it together?
What the hell?!
Is this a joke...? Come on, God.
Gimme a break, would ya?!
I thought my dream was
supposed to come true!
Oh, right now?
I can't. I'm sorry.
My parents' company
is sponsoring this thing
at the New Year's festival
and I can't get away.
Wait. On second thought...
Lots of people here,
aren't there?
Yeah... I'd watch your step.
I wouldn't want you to fall...
What?
Oh. Thank you, Karasuma.
He's concerned about me!
And I'm spending New Year's
with him, just like I hoped!
Oh, Karasuma, you're the best!
Your fate is now
sealed, Karasuma...!
You're gonna pay for this!
Oh, yeah you're going down!
Hello, Harima...
I'm so glad I found you.
The Suou Group is
putting on this thing today,
but something came up
and I have to leave...
You don't mind
filling in, do you?
Yeah right! Now why
the hell would I do that?!
Hey... remember how
you were all homeless
and starving and I gave
you a place to live?
Thanks. I knew you'd understand.
Oh! Happy New Year!
Hey! Wait!
Thanks for the
guilt trip, Mikoto.
Happy New Year. Right.
It's anything but that!
That's it? How adorable.
Well, better not keep
the other guy waiting.
Hey dude... I hope you haven't
been sittin' here too long.
What the hell...?
Why are you here?!
I was about to ask you
the same thing, Rich Girl!
Oh great... Looks
like Mikoto's at it again.
If I knew you were
going to be here,
I would've never
said yes to this!
That makes two of us...!
I gotta get Tenma
away from Karasuma!
That's so awesome!
Oh wow! Sweet!
Didja see it move?!
It's so cool!
I've never seen one!
So, you guys came
to see the Lion Dance, huh?
Yeah!
Mom told us to get bitten.
It's good luck.
Well... you heard those kids...
I'll help until
Mikoto gets back.
Fine. But you gotta be the ass.
The dancing lion talks, too?
I guess so.
He said the a-word!
Wow, you're actually
pretty good at this.
Hmph... shut your mouth.
Wow. These people really dig us.
A Lion Dance, that's cool.
I guess it's not
New Year's without one.
Well, what are you
waiting for, Kosuke?
Go let it bite you.
No, that's okay!
Wait! That thing
eats people...?!
So you fight lions
in this country...!
Oh, I could get used to that!
I'm borrowing these!
Uh... No, wait!
I won't miss this time!
Lara, no!
It's not real!
It's just two performers
in a costume!
It's a New Year's tradition!
You for real?
Why does it bite people?
There's a legend that
says if you get bitten
by a Dancing Lion on New Year's,
you'll have good luck.
You must've been bitten
by a lion once, Sis.
You're lucky 'cause Blue's here
and you want him
to be your boyfriend.
Kosuke, I'm gonna kill you!
Ah...! Oh no Blue,
you have to save me!
I don't know what he's
talking about, honest!
Damn...! Here I am
getting; attacked
by the Queen of the Beasts
when I should be with
Tenma right now! This sucks!
And it was such a nice dream...
Wanna do that with me,
Karasuma?! That's crazy!
Oh, crap!
Tenma, whatever
it is, don't do it!
I've gotta get her out of
Karasuma's slimy little mitts,
but if I try anything
here, everyone's gonna
think I'm a jealous,
two-bit thug!
Wow! Hey, Karasuma, look!
It's a Dancing Lion!
Oh, hello, Mr. Lion!
Happy New Year,
you cuddly beast!
Tenma... you are an
angel of the New Year...
Wait! If I bite her,
and she sees inside,
that'll give me
a chance to say...
...I love you.
Harima...
That's it! I have to
give her a love bite!
Yeah!
I got bitten! Yes!
That's great!
That means you're gonna
have good luck this year!
What the--? Harima...?
Oh no! I-I-Imadori!
Are you okay?!
Viva, leon! With all the
bites you're giving him,
he's going to have a great year!
Oh, no! They're leaving!
We gotta follow 'em!
Rich Girl...
Huh?
So these Lion Dances?
They go parading through
the streets sometimes, right?
Well, what do ya say we go
spread a little New Year's
cheer to the masses, huh?
Well, I guess so.
But do you think
that's a good idea?
Yeah! It'll be great!
It's for the children, y'know?
Mama... Look!
Kenny, no! Don't touch it!
Is it just me, or are
we freaking people out
instead of cheering them up?
It's just you.
So, what can I... get
for you today, "Sir?"
Oh, I'll take a melon soda.
Wow, Karasuma,
that's incredible!
Your order, "Sir."
Hey, be honest.
What're we really doing here?
You stalking some girl?
How do you Heimlich a lion?!
I love the view from here...
This is where we all watched
the fireworks last year.
Karasuma, you slimy bastard!
So this is where you're
gonna seal the deal, huh?!
Miss Tsukamoto?
Yes, what is it, Karasuma?
Close your eyes.
Oh, Karasuma...
Oh, no, you don't!
I'll feast on
your bones for this!
You can open them now.
Here you go.
I bought this earlier.
I thought it would
complement your kimono.
You look... so lovely.
Why thank you, Karasuma.
Oh, and Happy New Year.
You too.
Hey, I'm pretty much done here.
Great. Come help me on this one.
All right, all right,
I'm comin'.
You know, this kite
is frickin' huge.
Is it for one of your
diabolical schemes?
You'll see.
Rich girl...
I'm sorry about this.
You make me be the lion's butt,
drag me around town,
drop me off a cliff,
and that's all you can say?
Look, if there was anything
else I could say, I'd say it.
Yeah. Whatever.
Hey. Whiskers?
Yeah?
For what it's worth...
Happy New Year.
Thanks.
Wow! These New Year's
kites are amazing!
No kidding!
They're really high up there!
And look at all
the different styles!
Hey, Hanai. I'm about
to launch my kite.
Care to give a girl a hand?
Uh... But can't you
just do it by yourself?
It's a special kind of
kite that takes two people.
But since you don't seem to
want to help, forget about it.
I'm sure Tougou from
2-D will help me...
Togou?! No-no-no! I insist!
Hey, Kenji, come here.
Now way. I'm not
about to help you.
Oh? Maybe I should
tell you the same
since you haven't gotten around
to paying this month's rent.
Hey, Mikoto?
Is that samurai-looking
one a kite, too?
Yep, sure is. It's called
a "yakko-dako" kite.
Hey, what do you
call those kites?
What the hell are they doing?
Looks like there's
gonna be a good,
old-fashioned kite
fight if ya ask me!
Bring it. One of my
New Year's resolutions
was to finally settle
my score with you.
Come on! They're
manipulating us...!
And you're too
boneheaded to realize it!
Huh?
Good one!
You jerk! If you want
a war, pal, it's on!
I didn't do that, Akira did!
That shut him up!
Ooh, that's gotta hurt!
That's it, douche!
Come and get it, Four Eyes!
What style! What skill!
What grace!
What idiots.
Got that right.
Dammit man, would you
just give it up already?!
And concede to the likes
of a delinquent like you?!
Don't make me laugh!
Akira! It's time for
operation danger hawk!
Uh... I'm on it.
Harima...
Can you withstand
an attack from above?!
Guess we'll have to see!
First I spin like a cyclone...
Then move in for the kill!
Hyakunin Isshu is a
game where someone reads
a verse of poetry,
and the players have
to pick up the card
with the next verse.
So... just pick them up?
Okay, I got it.
"Just like a boatman,
crossing the straits
of Yura without a rudder..."
"Love leads down a path
to destinations unknown."
Found it!
Imadori!
Did I do it wrong?
No... You didn't break the
rules, just Imadori's fingers.
Hanetsuki?
Yep. It's a
New Year's tradition.
You hit the birdie
with the paddle,
but whoever drops it first
gets ink scribbled
all over their face.
When I'm done, your
face'll be full of ink!
Hmm. We'll see about that.
I've run out of places to draw.
Wah! I wanna switch players!
Yakumo, avenge me!
Hm... This should
be interesting.
No offense...
But you suck at sports.
Let's go.
What, you're serious?
All right, your funeral...
What the--?!
Oh! Watch out, we got
a pro on our hands!
Hold on a second! Crap!
Um, I'm gonna
switch players, too.
Harima has volunteered
to fill in for me.
Huh?
What?! Me?!
Why in the hell would
I do somethin' like that?!
Oh, so you forgot
the lion's butt,
the fall off the cliff,
and ruining my New Year's?
You owe me, buddy!
Now go take your medicine.
Hey! Harima says to
draw all over his face!
Yeah. What she said,
just get it over with.
But I can't!
Okay, seriously, that laugh is
putting me into a hate pocket.
I'm done.
Nice job, Yakumo!
One more game!
Geez, Eri!
What's gotten into you?
Nothing!
Whiskers fills in if I lose!
What?! No freakin' way!
I'm done with this stuff!
I wanna draw on him next!
Uh... I mean, we can
keep goin'... Yeah.
It's tradition...!
♪ ending song ♪
This is definitely my favorite
New Year's tradition.
Are there really gonna
be lots of girls here?
Aw, hell yeah!
Lots of wardrobe
malfunctions, too!
They're here...! Huh?!
Tougou?!
Hmph...
I was expecting
a bigger crowd...
But it touches me that
the competitive spirit
beats within you three...
Well, men, what say we make this
a New Year's Day that
none of us will ever forget!
Please allow me to
introduce my teammates...!
Come, brothers!
Tennoji!
Kuta!
Let us compete!
This is a New Year's tradition
I think I could get used to.
Huh?
What the--?
Ichijo! Skating!
Let's go skating!
All right then.
I guess I'll come with you.
Why are you here?!
Next time, on School Rumble:
"Dream Jumbo. Dream Jump.
Dream, uh, Press."
You tricked me!