The breathtaking culture
festival starts today!
And today is Karasuma's
breathtaking birthday!
So what about
this birthday party...?
Does Karasuma know about it?
No way, it's a surprise.
Fuyuki and the others said they
were going to keep it secret
and spring it on him
later at the launch party.
I've been practicing
baking birthday cakes over
and over again just for this
day... Oh, I hope he likes it.
Hey, Tenma... do you
want me to hang on
to that cake until it's time?
Good idea... knowing
me I'll probably drop it
by accident or something.
I can't wait,
I can't wait... can't wait!
Ahh, very nice... very nice.
There is nothing I like
better than a festival.
Hm... sounds like
things are booming in here.
It's good to see 2-C
finally pulling together...!
I guess my little talk really
straightened them out!
Huh?
What the?!
Hey, Teach, good to
see you, come on in!
What's going on in this shop?
You're in luck, our
number one girl is available.
Wait a minute!
Here's how it works, you get to
choose your drink and your girl.
Huh?!
I've brought your coffee.
My name's Saeko...
It's nice to meet you.
What are talking about?
I'm your teacher
we've already met before!
Oh really...? What do
you mean we've met before?
Are you trying to hit on me?
What?! I'm your
teacher! Hellooo!
There you go again...
you're not going to trick me.
I hope you enjoy
your coffee, big boy.
Saeko the Hammer strikes
again... another quick kill.
Yeah, the poor guy
didn't have a chance.
♪ Tonight, has such a
graceful crescent moon ♪
♪ Reborn every day, every
night, shining brighter ♪
♪ She is like something
in the heart of the moon ♪
♪ Reborn every day,
every night... ♪
Oh, what a cute screen saver!
Yeah...? Give me your email
address and I'll send it to ya.
Great... I would just love
to have it on my phone!
Madoka, this is all
part of the act, right?
Hey... am I unattractive?
Huh?
I just feel like...
I'm no good at this.
Relax, you just haven't
hit your stride yet.
That's right...
It's getting so crazy out there
you're letting the
stress get to you.
Mm.
Hey, Tenma...
Mama wants to see you.
Oh, right!
Tsukamoto... I understand you're
feeling a little depressed
over not getting any orders.
Yes... I don't think
I'm right for this job.
You're just like I was
in my younger days.
Huh...? But we're the same...
Shh, Don't question it...
Like you I was
once very introverted
and didn't believe
in myself at all.
But remember this, Tenma...
You have a special type of
charm that's your very own.
Never give up.
I'll be waiting for the time
when you're the brightest
star in the whole shop.
Mama...! I'll never say
I'm going to quit again!
Hey, we could use some help
back here in the real world.
Everyone!
We've finally reached
our morning quota...!
Please keep up the
good work this afternoon!
Yes, ma'am!
They're all on board!
Well done! This is amazing!
If we can keep this up,
we're gonna be number one in
sales for the whole festival!
Hey! Bad news!
Huh?!
All of a sudden our customers
have stopped coming!
Say what?!
Everybody's going over
to the tea club's café!
What?! The tea club's café?!
Gee, this place looks
pretty intimidating...
No! I swore!
For the sake of my
fellow brothers-in-arms...
I will go in and face the enemy!
It's so good to see
you again, master.
I hope that you had a safe
and pleasant journey.
He's late!
Something's gone wrong!
Do you think maybe he could've
blown his cover somehow?
Maybe we should send
someone else to check.
I will go.
What?!
But first let me say this!
Yakumo is in the tea club
so I'm pretty sure
I won't be coming back!
What good is that gonna do?
There are battlefields
a man must face...
even if he knows
he is going to die...
So for the class
and for myself...
Time for tea!
I'm ready for duty, Inspector.
Officer Yakumo...
let's get to that stakeout.
Yes, Inspector.
And remember, Officer,
brace yourself for the worst!
Yes, Inspector!
Master?
Say it again!
Welcome home, dear.
Would you like dinner?
Would you like a bath?
Duwa!
Duwa...! Duwa...! Duwa...!
Duwa...! Duwa...!
Daddy...! Can we sit
over at the cool table
next with Dozibiron Pink?!
Tell me young girl...
why would you take
up such a profession?
A woman like you is not
meant for this type of work.
It's because of my father.
You see, he ran up
too many gambling debts...
and I was sold
here because of it.
You don't have to worry.
I'm getting you
out of this place!
Really?
Not so fast!
Now... I don't
suppose you're talking
about buying her
freedom, are you?
Not exactly...
But I'm more than
happy to kill all-... huh?!
How 'bout we play a new game.
Huh?
Hey, there's some mistake,
I ordered the episode 102
of Three for the Kill fantasy.
Oh, yes, I know...
but, see, I just like
having you tied up.
Damn that Itoko!
Making me wash dishes just
because I don't have any money!
I wonder what's
taking so long...?
The New Face Award
notice should have arrived
from the magazine by now...
Maybe they
rejected me after all.
Hey there, lady cop!
How about you
give me your address?
Uh, that's
privileged information.
Aw come on babe,
what's the harm?
Excuse me, weary traveler.
Welcome to our church,
may you find the peace you seek.
Have you come to
have your cursed lifted?
You've been cursed
with the inability to
find a girlfriend, right?
For seventeen years!
How in the world did you know?
I'll take care of this guy...
Here, you take this.
Be of good cheer.
Let us offer up a prayer
that your curse be lifted...
Is this the...?
Hey... dishwasher.
Huh...? What d'you
want... you jerk face!
Your teacher is waiting
for you in the back room.
Huh?
What's the big idea?
I thought she was
the teacher here!
Tokiha Apartment?
Come in.
Uh, hello, I...
You're running
a little bit late,
aren't you,
assistant artist Harima?
I can't believe it?!
This is the holiest place...
...in all of comic book history!
I'm sorry I'm late,
Master Tezuka!
Don't worry about it,
go ahead and start
inking the beta layouts.
Yes sir!
Harima, was it?
Yes sir.
Tell me, Harima...
How long has it been since you
started drawing comic books?
About three months...
I haven't drawn
anything lately, though.
Why not?
Huh?
What made you decide to
stop drawing all of a sudden?
I guess you could say
that whatever was burning
so hot inside of me
just turned to ashes.
Can I ask you...
How in the world do
you find the motivation
to keep on drawing so much?
Well... I, uh...
I try...
I try to think of all the
people who have read my work,
or will read my work, and about
the joy it might bring them.
Your pen name is
Hario Harima, right...?
Why did you choose that name...?
You thought people
would find it amusing
and remember it, didn't you?
Don't give up now...
keep on trying.
Where's Yakumo?!
I can't see anything...! I want
the lady cop course again!
Sir! Please calm down!
You had better go.
Huh...? But you...
I'll be fine.
Oh... okay...
I'll be right back.
Okay, I've had just about
enough out of you, mister!
Yakumoooooo!!
The new Sumo Swimsuit
Wrestling champ is Yoshidayama!
I rule!
Harima... Hang in there.
Yyyellow?
Hey, Tazawa! Where are you?
The New Face Awards ceremony
is happening right now!
Some butler is
here in your place.
Huh?
Congratulations, you
got honorable mention!
Gotta go, the ceremony's ending!
It's finally here...!
The day that Kenji Harima
is recognized as
both artist and man!
I better call
Yakumo and tell her.
This sucks
All of our waitresses
have been stolen away
from us by that damn tea club.
You just can't trust
that Akira Takano.
Snap out of it, men!
Let's show the tea club
we don't need them!
We can do it on our own!
And just how exactly
do you propose we do that?
Obviously, there's
only one answer!
Huh?
The boys are just going to
have to wait on the customers!
But we...
No buts!
It is time for the men to shine!
Hell yeah!
That didn't work at all.
I can't believe we managed
to lose Imadori and Asou
to the tea club.
Me either...
For a minute there
I really thought
we could pull this thing off.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Huh?
We stopped off and bought
some snacks and stuff
with the first
half of the proceeds.
Let's all celebrate
the end of the first day!
Aw, thank you guys...
No more sad panda faces...
cheer up and let's party!
Yakumo! I'm here for the cake!
Ha-ri-ma?
Uh... okay, about this, Harima
had some good news today...
and it turns out the
tea club had an extra cake...
Don't explain...
that's just fine.
N-no, it's not what you think...
Okay, don't worry about it,
I'll take both cakes to
the party... See you later.
Okey-dokey, here we go,
I'll just put the
cakes down right here...
I have to make sure not to
mix mine up with Yakumo's...
Tenma...! This is my
chance to confess my love!
Ten... maaa!
Wait for meee!
Oh man, what the heck was that?!
Hm...?
Oh crap!...! That's the
cake Tenma set down
just a second ago!
Wait those letters
"M-A" couldn't mean...
The "ma" in Harima?!
Of course!
Yakumo must have told
Tenma about my award,
and she went and made
a cake to celebrate...!
That's so sweet...! But...
I took the cake Tenma
poured her heart into and...
Ah, crap!!!
Only one option...
Good job, everybody!
Good job!
Yeah, good job , woo-hoo.
Listen up, everyone!
Huh?
There are still more
congratulations in order!
Tenma is such a blabbermouth...!
Well, it won't be so bad having
everyone celebrate with us.
Today is also... our own
Oji Karasuma's birthday!!
Say what?
Say what??
Alright! Then let's party!
It's Karasuma's birthday?!
Thanks a lot, everybody.
Okay, that's enough
with the speeches,
it's time for some cake!
Oh no! If the Harima cake
shows up now, I'm in trouble!
Hope everyone's hungry!
That's it...! I only
have one chance left!
Whoopsie!!
Oh no! I'm just so clumsy!
I'm sorry, Tenma...
this was the only way.
Harima, how could you?!
Huh?
That was my Swimsuit Sumo
wrestling victory cake!
That was uncalled for!
Yeah, even if it
was Yoshidayama,
that was going too far!
Sorry...
I thought it was my cake
and I got excited.
Really, Harima,
I know you're worked up,
but show some restraint!
Don't worry, I have
yours is right here.
Huh?
I heard you had something good
happen to you... here you go.
You are the golden light
of cosmic awesome!
Delicious!
This is beyond delicious!
Kenji Harima is now
one wickedly happy dude!
Oh, sorry about before...
Here, have some of mine.
Aw, look at that.
Yakumo's gonna be so happy.
Now...
We're ready...
for the main event...
the extra special cake I made
myself for Karasuma's birthday!
Voila...! Hm?
What happened?!
It's impossible!
How did Karasuma's cake
turn into Harima's cake?
Tenma, what's taking so long?
Everyone's waiting for you!
I'll be right there,
just hang on for a second!
Okay, but hurry up!
That's it...! I have
only one chance left!
Karasuma!
Happy birthday,
and here's your cake!
What... is she doing?
I see.
Why do things like this
always seem to happen to me?
I bet he never talks to me
again as long as I live...
I bet he hates me.
Hey there.
Oh, Karasuma!
What's this...? A photograph...
Uh...
Well, it's just that before
when we were talking
you said you had trouble
expressing your feelings
sometimes, remember?!
And I wanted to
show you this picture
because I thought it showed
that you had a lot of feeling.
Thanks for what you did today.
Want to walk home together?
Yeah.
Stop tagging along, Mio.
I'm not tagging along,
it's just my brother's class
is this direction too...
Besides, why are you so eager
to be by yourself anyway?
You don't know anything.
I'll betcha I know why.
You're going to meet this
Tsukamoto person, right?
What...? How do
you know about that?
Don't you remember?
You told everyone at school
you had a crush on someone
named Tsukamoto at Yagami High.
So there.
Shut-up...! That's not it!
I'm just going to see
my brother, that's all!
He ran off...
High schoolers...
I wonder if I'll
ever be like them...?
It seems like it's such
a long time from now...
I bet that Tsukamoto girl Shuji
likes is really grown-up...
I wish I could be like her.
Hey, Tsukamoto!
Duwa?!
What should we eat today?
Good question.
Duwa, duwa!
How about dumplings?
Duwa!
That's the Tsukamoto
that Shuji likes?!
No fair...!
I'll never be like that!
I might as well go home.
That hurts!!
Oh, no, my sweater...! I just
got it and it's torn already!
Man, this is totally lame.
Are you lost?
How old are you?
What's your name?
What's your address?
Any previous criminal record?
Captain... Juvenile Division
can take over from here...
You should get back on patrol.
Hm... maybe...
Wait, there's a suspicious
looking person over there!
What...? Freeze, punk!
There... all fixed.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
She's so pretty...
If I were as pretty as her...
I bet Shuji would...
Hey, Miss?
Have you... have you
ever been all mixed up
over a boy you liked?
See, I... really
like this one boy...
but he... he never really
seems to notice me, and...
And uh... I...
Don't cry.
I don't know the whole story...
but I think if you start crying,
you might end up
upsetting this boy too.
I don't have anyone
in particular I like yet...
But once I do find
that special someone...
I think that I'd want to
be able to smile for him.
I wonder if he left and
went home without me.
I finally found you...
Shuji!
You idiot...!
Where'd you run off to?
Were you really
that worried about me?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
If you'd been
kidnapped or something,
I wouldn't have
been able to sleep!
Come on... let's go!
Hey... when are you
going to introduce me
to your brother?
Aw, you're not
missing anything...
When are you going to introduce
me to your big brother, Tennoji?
Well... I don't know...
Okay, you two losers...
You're going to work off
every last penny you owe.
Yes, ma'am.
What's this? 2-C's class play?
Wow, what inspired casting!
And talk about
an interesting plot!
Very nice, 2-C.
Next time on School Rumble:
"Sleeping Beast!
Kiss Impossible! Finale!"
Bravoooo!!!