It's no use, Captain!
The helm isn't responding!
Spineless wimps!
I don't wanna hear
any whining until
after we get this
ship back to harbor!
Yes... sir!
Captain, I did it, the
engine is running again!
Son of a bastard!
Look at the size of that thing!
We're all doomed, there's
no way we can survive this!
I told you before, men
of the sea don't whine...!
Do you know what men
do before danger?
Real men just laugh.
Yeah... yeah, you're right.
Now let's do this like real men!
Right!
Full speed ahead!
Laugh Dammit!
Kid...
have you found your
dream on shore yet?
Captain...
Hey, are you still alive...?
Time to get you movin'.
I tell ya, finding
Santa Claus at the side
of the road on
Christmas is pathetic.
I finished it.
Hold on...! You shouldn't
be gettin' up so fast!
My manuscript.
I finally finished it.
It ended up being
twenty pages too long.
What're you planning to do
with it now that it's finished?
You'll see.
Tenma... so much has
happened between us...
You... you'll be the
first one to see it.
It's bright today.
Okay, sweetheart,
it's time to open the kiln!
I hope the firing went
well...! I'm so excited!
Hey, Akira, what did you make?
Just a little something
to decorate my room.
As it cools, cracks
will form in the glaze,
creating a delicate,
artistic pattern
that's exquisite to behold...
not unlike the fine ceramics
they create in the city of Soma.
Oh, hurray, at last
it's finally finished!
Very impressive.
Tenma, is that it...?
Yep...! That's my
Christmas present!
Yello.
Ah, Tazawa...! How's the
manuscript?
Good... I finished it.
Thank goodness...! You need
to get it here right away!
Wait... But I was gonna
show it to someone first!
What are you talking about?
There's no time for that!
It's the end of the year,
the printers are really busy,
and we're on a deadline!
I promise... this
won't take very long...
No, no, y'can't,
if that manuscript is late
you're gonna get dropped!
The Editor in Chief
really likes you,
so whatever you do,
don't let him down!
I'm not exaggerating when
I say your whole future
depends on getting
that manuscript in!
Mitsui, the printers called.
They said to hurry it up
with those manuscripts!
Okay, okay...!
Bring those pages in right now!
I'm counting on you!
My future... he said...
I never even
thought about that...
Do I have a future...? Me?
Why am I even drawing
comics in the first place?
I was such a loser.
Take this, douche!
There were those smart guys,
who everyone knew would
get into a good college...
And guys who
studied art and music...
And me, the guy no
one gave a damn about.
The kid who was
sure to waste away.
I... have a future?
Tenma can read it as much
as she likes later, right...?
If I'm gonna seize my chance,
it has to be right now!
I'm sorry...
Please forgive me...
The snow is expected to
continue well past midnight...
Some areas may receive
locally heavier snowfall,
so please be careful.
In other news...
Hey, I'm home!
Do it! For the curry!
For a minute there I didn't
think I was gonna make it...
but I just beat the storm!
It turned out a little big...
I hope Karasuma likes it.
Huh?
I'm sorry... I've just...
I've got to do this.
Miss... Miss Tsukamoto...
What do you want now?
You know this house
is off-limits to you!
You took advantage
of my kindness.
You lied to me.
I can't believe you'd
have the nerve
to show your face here again!
It's... it's useless.
There's no way she'll understand
how I feel by reading
this comic now.
It's hopeless...
If I'm not careful, there'll be
another misunderstanding...
But so what...? Why should
I be afraid of that...?
Compared to the crap I lived
through before this comic,
and before I met her,
this is nothing...!
Besides... when ya
come right down to it,
I got nothing left
to lose...! Do I?
Tenma... the... the truth is...
I've been drawing a comic book.
Go ahead! Judge me!
Liar.
Huh?
You're lying, Harima...!
No way you would
do something like that!
No, honest,
it's true! Here! Look!
Even if it is true,
why are you telling me?
It's got nothing to do with me!
But it does!
I mean, this is what I've been
doing with your little sister!
With Yakumo?
Just read the
manuscript... okay?
You mean it's true?
It... it was kinda
interesting... I guess.
All right!!
At long last it's
springtime in my heart...!
Now all I have to do is
deliver this to Dankosha!
They're going to publish his
story in Weekly Shonen Zinegama.
You're kidding...! Wow!!!
I can't wait to see this
thing in print, Harima!
And thanks to record-breaking
snowfall, we're seeing
major delays on all metro
railroads and on major highways.
Did you hear that? Come on!
We've just received word of a
winter storm warning for Yagami.
We now go to one of our
reporters live on the scene.
Hey...! Iori...! Get your
paws off that remote!
Gimme that remote! Gimme it!!!
As you can see, the snow
is really coming down here.
Despite several
minor accidents--
Come on...! I've got to make
it on time... for Tenma!!
Geez! So many obstacles!
Turn...! Turn, damn you!
I love you, Tenma!!
Hurry...! Hurry...! For the
sake of the one you love!
Ride on Harima, ride on!
Was that...?
Well, that was fun, wasn't it?
Oh yeah, nothin' like a
ski trip to take the edge off.
I could've sworn
that was Harima!
What does that
idiot think he's doing?
Itoko here.
I've got the tea ready...
will you have some?
Why didn't he just tell me
about his comic from the start?
I must look like a fool
for hating him the way I did.
I think the reason
you were so upset is
because you cared about him,
and you hated the things
you thought he was doing.
What do you want now?
You know this house
is off-limits to you!
You took advantage
of my kindness.
You lied to me.
I can't believe
you'd have the nerve
to show your face here again!
Anyone else would have said...
I don't care;
you're still worthless.
Most people are
very unforgiving.
Any slight disturbance in their
relationship and it's over.
No questions asked.
However...
Tenma is not most people.
She may not understand much.
Let's face it,
the girl's pretty clueless,
but she does understand
friendship and forgiveness.
Sis... I think that's
what it is about you...
that Harima likes so much.
Hello...? Oh, Mikoto...
W-whoa, why are you
so excited...? Harima?
Harima was riding
my curry dish?!
Yeah, I was surprised too...!
I got a call from Akira.
She said she'd
take care of it...
What do you think she'll do?
Sis!
Ms. Osakabe?!
Come on... get your sister.
I heard most of
what's happened...
I apologize in
advance for the driving.
Girls don't let her scare you,
she just likes giving
me a hard time.
Uh, uh-thank you to our
beloved company president
for that inspiring
holiday message.
Uh... we're glad
you could all be here
for the Dankosha
year-end celebration.
Geez, what the hell is
taking Tazawa so long?
The party has already started!
What's that?!
Why is Santa riding in a dish?
Don't tell me this
is the entertainment?
Somebody call security!
Mr. Gotou...
Here...
Is that a manuscript?
That Santa broke up the party...
The chief is gonna kill him!
Looks like he's done reading it.
There's no way
I can publish this.
Take it and leave, now.
How could you do this to me?!
Huh...? Karasuma?
Back off...! Let go of me!
Takano told me...
what happened...
Calm down.
Look, they're here.
Hey... What're you doin' here?
Merry... Merry Christmas...
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you.
Sis, wait!
Wait a minute, you mean
that thing I rode here on...
was Tenma's...?
She made it herself.
Listen, chief...
that manuscript...
I'm sorry, there's
no way I can run this.
This story is far too intimate.
There's only one person
in the whole world
who should read this.
Although, it is a great story.
Oh, Tenma... please
forgive me... please...
I'm sorry... I'm so sorry...
All I wanted was to
see her smiling face...
Tenma's beautiful smiling
face... that's all...
Harima...
And instead...
Forgive me... Tenma...
Hey...! You okay?!
Um... I... I'm sorry
about the dish... honest...
I'm sorry too...
for what I thought before...
and what I said.
Still friends?
Yeah.
♪ ending song ♪
Hm!
No matter how rough the storm,
the sun always shines
afterwards... amazing isn't it?
Merry Christmas, kid.
Arise and unite! Dozibiron!
Let's go, Pink!
Right!
Next time on Invincible
Robot Dozibiron:
"More than Friends...
Less Than Lovers...
Up Until Then."
You know, Itchy, I'm surprised
your mom is so... A-hem...