Whenever you watch television,
you should always
keep the lights on
and watch from a safe distance.
What's the matter, gentlemen...?
You appear to be a bit confused.
Very well... as a reward,
I'll explain myself to you.
I was on the
outer wall of the school.
I grabbed onto the window
frame and hid myself outside...
a good soldier should always
know the lay of the land...
I trust this has
been educational.
So you're some kind of
cross-dressing soldier?
I think not...
I am merely a humble
butler who was passing by.
Sadly, now that you
have seen me like this...
you must disappear.
I know I've got to be
missing something here,
but I'm guessing this means
he's working for the Play Team.
If that's true...
doesn't matter who he is.
Let me give you boys a
little piece of advice...
Some times when
fighting indoors,
sidearms can be
very effective...
By not carrying one...
you've lost.
Hasta la vista.
Sniper...! Somewhere outside!
Tch!
I'm not sure what happened,
but did we just luck out?
I guess he just let us go...
Or more likely... decided we
weren't worth worrying about.
Okay, so, you got any idea
what the heck was
up with that dress?
I don't know, and believe
me I don't wanna know.
Where'd he go?
She's deliberately
exposing her position.
Is she trying to distract me?
So beautiful...
A flower blooming
on the battlefield.
So out of respect
for your beauty...
We've already lost so many...
Do you have enough
bullets to go on?
I don't know. I just
used up my last clip.
Then it's over...
Looks like...
You know...
if we manage to get out
of this mess in one piece...
How about a date?
Sure.
I wonder if I'm the only
one who managed to survive?
Oh my god! This is
the whole Play team!
Doesn't make sense.
If they're down... who
have we been fighting...?
And are they still out there?
There's no escape
for you now... Miss Suou.
Impressive...
You still remain calm.
Come out!
Coward! Face me!
Leaving you for last was
definitely the right call...
You're really
dangerous, aren't you?
I know you...
You're Tsumugi Yuki...
but why are you here?
I thought you had band practice.
We got permission from Akira.
There's nothing in
the rules against it.
It's time for you to say
good-bye... Miss Suou.
Are you injured
in any way, Mikoto?
No... But, man, am
I glad to see you!
Hanai.
So it's Yuki, huh?
I never expected...
Not so fast... Yoshidayama!
There is no way I'm
doing cleanup detail...!
Get outta my way!
Are you okay?
We better clean this
glass up to make sure
no one sustains an injury.
Oh... okay.
Wow, what's with this guy...?
Is he like, obsessive
compulsive or something...?
I mean, this is
the 21st century,
but he's treating me
like a damsel in distress.
You can't ride
without your glasses...
Come... I, Haruki Hanai,
will escort you home!
No, it's okay!
I'm sorry madam,
but it is my duty.
But before we embark,
how much do you weigh exactly?
Well, there goes the whole
knight in shining armor image.
I'm sorry to be such a bother.
Not at all.
Don't worry about it.
These hills are pretty steep...
Isn't the ride to school hard?
Well, it's a bit far...
but I don't like buses...
Besides, I enjoy the view...
You get a good feel for
the seasons this way...
I like the view from the
top of this hill best of all.
Mmm, it's no use...
I can't see a thing
without my glasses.
Do you... have a moment?
Huh?
You see this view
every day, don't you...?
You should see it today too.
What? No, you really
don't have to stop.
I'm telling you, it's no use.
I'm blind as a bat
without my glasses.
Don't worry.
Believe me, you're
going to wanna see this.
There...
It's beautiful isn't it?
It's amazing.
Now aren't you glad that
I talked you into stopping?
This guy... I just
don't get him...
Well, it's two against one.
One of you will get me,
so go ahead and shoot.
But just know,
it doesn't matter,
because you guys
are gonna lose anyway.
Wait... what do you mean?
The Band Team is already on
its way to take your flags...
Karasuma, Fuyuki...
Ichijou... and Sagano...
If you want to stop them,
you'll have to go through me.
No, I can't do it...!
You weren't supposed to
be our enemy, not the band!
Then you're a coward!
No, Tsumugi!
Don't fall apart
on me, Hanai...!
Please, just stay strong!
We've got to tell the others!
Let's go.
I'm sorry, Yuki.
What...? The Band Team?
Yeah, and we have to stop them
before they can take our flag!
No sweat, we have
nothing to worry about.
We still have the upper hand
when it comes to military force!
What happened?!
Is this the work
of the Band Team?
This is terrible.
Ishiyama?!
Alright, you made it!
What... what was that
sound...? Asou...? Suga!
Please come in!
Do you read me...?! Guys?
It can't be...
Don't you fall apart on me now.
I won't. Let's kick some ass.
Targets sighted.
Hanai and Mikoto.
Now let's pen them in,
just like we planned.
Cool, copy that.
I guess nobody's coming.
Sh! Be quiet!
Remember we're the
last line of defense
against any enemy who
tries to get near the flag!
I'll be back in
just a minute, Tenma.
Huh...? Wait...
Wait a minute,
where are you going...
Don't leave me alone!
I think someone
might be out there...
I'm gonna go check
it out... Sit tight...
What just happened?
Eri...? You okay...?
Eri?
Don't move!
Hello, Miss Tsukamoto,
the moon sure is
lovely tonight, isn't it?
It's strange, you know, I
managed to make it all this way,
but at the very end,
I guess I slipped up
and dropped my guard.
What is this...?
Why are you here,
Karasuma, and not at practice?
It's over, now give it up.
I can't shoot without
hitting Megumi!
And poor Megumi
can't hit me this close.
Maybe, but the same
thing goes for you, duh!
Mikoto!
I'm really sorry
about this, Ichijou.
Well... it looks like we're
both safe for the moment, Hanai.
Harima!
No bullets!
Finish it.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
It's not quite the right moment.
No, don't...! Harimaaaa!
You're too late, four eyes.
Mikoto!!
I wonder if it's all over yet...
whether Hanai's group or
Harima'a group survived...
we're not the ones
who were meant to win.
Then... why did you
shoot Eri, Karasuma?
I was desperate...
But I guess that's
no excuse, is it?
I'm sorry...
Since we missed
out on the drawing
and couldn't appear on the
culture festival main stage,
our only other option was
to enter the survival game
and win so we could
play inside the classroom.
I guess that was
pretty selfish of us
when you come right down to it.
But we practiced so hard,
we couldn't give up
without doing something.
You guys really have
worked hard, haven't you...?
Tsumugi and Carolyn and
Fuyuki and... especially you.
Give us a good
performance, okay?
No, why did you stop me?
Thank you Miss Tsukamoto...
but... I think I should
be the one to concede.
Looks like it's just you
and me now, isn't it?
You bastard...! How dare you
treat Mikoto like that...?
I will never... never
forgive you for that, Harima!!
I don't want your forgiveness...
Just shut-up and fight!
This battle will
decide everything!
Damn it...
I think Harima's still
got plenty of ammo...
But I'm almost out...
Alright... Where are you?
There's no way you've
already given up...
You stealthy bastard!
Coward!
Get out here!
Don't you know there's no use
in hiding from death himself!
It won't do any good
to challenge me, Harima...
I just want to
ask you one thing...
and I want an honest answer...
Just give it to
me straight, alright,
are you really in
love with Yakumo?
Huh?
I've heard some
things about you two...
and I want to know...
I need to know...
do you truly love her?
That's... all I ask.
What kind of idiot are you...?
Why should I have to
answer that question at all...?
If you want to know,
then ask me by force!
So it's a quick draw, then!
Y'know, I was hoping
you'd say something like that.
All right, Harima,
you asked for it,
I'll get your answer
out of you by force.
Heh, right, sure you will,
four-eyes, just make sure
you haven't disappeared
when I turn back around.
One... two...
Three... four...
Five... six... seven... eight...
Nine...
Ten!
I was almost out of ammo.
Why'd you do it?
If we'd kept on fighting like
before you would've won...
It's because I truly understand
how much you're
in love with her...
As someone who
hasn't confessed his love...
I know how much it can hurt.
Wait, are you telling me
it's not Yakumo
you're in love with
but someone else...?
Tell me... who is it?
That's kind of a
personal question, isn't it?
Harimaaaaaaaa!!!
Have to admit, you made
a pretty good movie.
Everyone was a lot more intense
than I thought they'd be...
Starting about halfway through,
it was mostly adlibbed.
I wish those two could keep on
like this instead of fighting.
Oh well, at least this
gave them a chance
to blow off some of their
hostility toward each other.
In all my years teaching,
this is a new one,
students conducting
war games on campus
in the middle of the night!
Now, now, then...
I'm sure they're all very
sorry for the whole thing,
why don't you give them a break?
Do you hear that...!
You people are lucky that
Ms. Osakabe found you...
I'm gonna give you a break
for her sake, so be thankful!
However...
This whole thing was
caused by your argument
over your culture
festival event, right...?
So stop arguing and do
the play and the cafe...!
Got me?
Huh?!
You gotta believe me!
This... old guy with a mustache
was dressed like Sawachika!
Ah, you were seeing things,
Sawachika was over on guard
at the Play
Team's flag all night.
Hey, Eri, you saw him,
right, that mustached pervert?
Can't say I did.
So what the heck are we supposed
to do for the culture festival?
Do we have time to do both
the play and the coffee shop?
No way is there time to do both.
Not to worry!
I, Haruki Hanai, will
take care of everything...!
I'll negotiate at once with the
culture festival committee...
so we can find a way to do both
the play and the coffee shop!
I don't know if it's possible,
but I say we move forward
with both the
coffee shop and the play!
And the band.
Wow! Hanai sure knows
how to take charge!
Hanai, you bastard!
How dare you get
Tenma's attention?
Mikoto!
Oh snap! I totally heard that!
Are you kidding,
the whole school heard it!
Mikoto... heh!
It's not like that!
Pretty quick with
the denial, Mikoto!
What is the matter
with you people?!
Come on you two!
You know you love each other!
Hey...! shut uuuuuuup!!
Oh, uh, Karasuma!
What a coincidence...
you want to walk home together?
Sure.
The culture festival
is almost here, huh?
Uh-huh.
I'm really looking
forward to it...
You know...
I've never seen
you get all exited
over something
like that before.
I really am excited
on the inside...
but I guess it just doesn't
show on the outside.
Well, why don't you just
shout, "I'm having fun"?
Mm... I guess I could.
Oh, don't worry about it...
I mean, I know that you're
really having fun
on the inside...
so cheer up!
If I'm being honest...
the truth is...
I don't know what I should do.
Miss Tsukamoto, even though
I can talk to you like this...
I guess I still don't know
how I really feel inside.
Say, Karasuma...
You like festivals,
don't you...?
Then let's just
have a good time!
All of us!
You're the perv who snuck into
the survival game, aren't you?
Ah...
Whatever do you mean, Mistress?
Look, just give me
my uniform back, okay?
I must offer
my deepest apologies
for making such a grave mistake.
When I first heard the
mistress would be entering
the battlefield, my concern
for her safety led me
to steal in as well.
But I couldn't keep
my old habits under control.
Despite how I appear now,
I was once in the
armed forces long ago.
Yes...
it was a special mission in a
small south American country,
where we put down a coup d'etat,
and rescued the president.
We did it!
We rescued the President!
The mission's successful!
Wait! There's still
a child in there!
A child?!
Stop! Our orders
are to fall back!
It's all right.
No... it's not ...
Go away, there's
no way to save me.
Do you have any
dreams for the future?
Huh?
What do you want to do...?
Is there anyone you look up to?
Is this your mother...? I see...
She must have been a
very good mother to you.
Live, for her sake.
Live and live for
as long as you can...
so you can grow up
to be a good person,
just like your mother was.
So... where is this child now?
Ah... the child
was taken in by me,
and now works as
a maid on this estate.
I've brought some more tea.
I thought you might
be running a bit low.
We were just talking about you.
Come in and say hello.
This is Masaru Suzuki.
He's very shy for a boy...
Ms. Osakabe,
where are you going?
What... the hell.
You guys haven't
decided what play to put on
for the culture festival!
Give me some proposals!
Mai, you're over-reacting.
Next on School Rumble:
"Wild Ideas about the Play!
Wild Ideas at the Bathhouse!
Wild Ideas about Rice Balls!"
Chill out, Mai.
Chill out your face!
Hey...