All right, attention everybody!
Does everyone have a glass?
Okay, let's hear it
for the birthday girl!
One...! Two!
Happy birthday, Tenma!
Cheers!
Thanks a lot, everybody!
Listen up, you guys!
Today, Tenma gets
to be queen all day...!
Give us your orders,
your majesty!
Oh, really...? Okay, first
up is my good friend Eri!
I order you to eat sticky beans!
No way, absolutely no way
am I gonna touch that stuff!
Now, now...
you shouldn't be so
picky about what you eat,
especially when it's
so good for you...
Here, you're going to love it!
Hey, you guys, what do
you think you're doing...?
At least let me get psyched to
eat that crap...! Wait a second!
Well done, my faithful subject,
we are most pleased.
You may step down
now if you wish.
I'm not going to
forget this, Tenma.
Highness... who's up next?
Oh...! Let's see... how about...
Akira!
Smile.
Tenma...
Walk with me.
Wow! Akira, that's adorable!
What do you think she
looks when she smiles?
I'd like to know myself.
Gosh, who's next,
I guess it's Mikoto's turn!
Hey now, remember that I'm
the nice friend, okay Tenma?
So don't do anything too crazy.
I have something special
in mind for you.
I challenge you to a Pocky game!
I'm not playing a kissing game!
We'll use a grid of four boys,
with Akira
thrown in for spice...
so what number do you choose?
Tenma, do you ever listen
to anyone?! Dear god!!
Okay, number one.
You can't just pick for me!
I can't believe
I'm gonna get to see this!
Lame, it broke!
Too bad!
Don't ever do
that to me again...!
Aw, so close too.
If you'd gotten number two,
it would've been Asou.
Carolyn, you get to...
Do this! Isn't this
great! Huh? Isn't it?
You know you love it!
Wow, when it comes
to being a queen
and giving orders,
Tenma's a natural...!
I knew she would
have fun with this!
Uh...
Okay, Mikoto, let's have
you take a second turn!
Hey, remember how I said I
didn't ever wanna do that again?
Yeah. I was serious.
Um... Hey, Harima...
Hey...! You havin' fun?
I happened to remember
about your birthday being...
well, you know, about it
being the day after Tenma's...
So here. Happy Birthday.
Tenma, will you knock it off?!
Don't worry, Yakumo.
This guy doesn't really
need any presents.
But, Eri, I just...
I don't mean to intrude,
but you've celebrated plenty
already, right, Whiskers?
It's okay, Tenma's Sister.
Rich Girl here is right.
I've gotten plenty.
Seeing Tenma smile like
that is enough for me...
And I've decided...
after the party...
I'm gonna give her this bouquet
of flowers and tell her...
I'll finally tell
her how I feel.
Funny... I think
Sis is having fun...
But she seems... lonesome.
She's right.
It's because he's not here...
Hey, Tsukamoto!
Harima asked me to
give you a message.
Oh? What is it, Suga?
He said he had
something for you,
and wants you to
meet him outside.
Whoa, Asou,
gettin' a little fresh
there with Suou, aren't ya?
Hi, Harima, what's up?
Oh! Uh, hi, Tsukamoto.
Suga said you had
something for me.
Uh, yeah, you see, about that...
actually it was
Karasuma's idea...
He asked me to... to...
uh... deliver these to you.
Wow, really?
Idiot! Idiot! God it hurts!
What's this?
He... he said to tell you...
happy birthday.
Harima... the Queen
has an order for you.
I want you to tell
me the truth now,
who was it who
really wrote this note?
I'm sorry... it was me.
What the heck are you two doing
alone out here in the dark?
No! It's not what ya think!
Come on, Tenma!
We can't have a
party without our star!
Well... bye...
And thank you.
Uh... sure...
"Was I able to cheer
her up some?" he wondered...
Remembering Tenma's smile
and her words of thanks...
Harima gazed up
into the night sky.
Hello, Tazawa?
We desperately need an
assistant artist right away.
Are you free tonight?
Wait... you mean right now?
Yeah, we have an
artist who doesn't usually
use an assistant, and we're
kind of in a tight spot here.
Oh... yeah, okay...
Hell, I got nothin' else to do.
Terrific! I'll be waiting for
you at the office.
Well, that was perfect timing...
But I wonder who's calling me
in out of the blue like this?
Man, this is some party, huh?
It's the end of the term.
I think everyone was ready to
let their collective hair down.
Hey, that reminds me, where's
Karasuma been lately...?
I don't think he ever
even showed up
for final exams, did he?
He could have some trouble
passing, couldn't he...?
I mean, I'm not one to talk,
but I'm just sayin'...
I know... you're right...
as the official
class representative...
I've been wondering
about him as well...
I conferred with
Mr. Tani about it.
And apparently he goes
to America every month.
America? Why is he goin' there?
Who knows...?
Mr. Tani's never
actually asked him why.
It seems... he covers
for the classes he's missed
with make-up lessons later.
Karasuma has always
been kind of mysterious...
Maybe this has something to do
with that transfer
he was talking about.
Maybe...
But it's his business...
it's probably best
just to leave it alone.
Hey! Listen up...!
I'm gonna chug this thing!
Where in god's name
did you get that jug?
Suga! Suga! Suga! Suga!
Hey, Megumi.
Tell me...
What in the world do you suppose
Tenma sees in Karasuma anyway?
I mean, I guess he's
pretty good looking,
but he's kinda weird,
don't you think?
I'm sure he has some
hidden good points
that only Tenma knows about.
You know... it must be
kinda lonesome for her...
Not having the guy
she loves at her party.
♪ Oh, say can you see... ♪
Oh... I've been
expecting you, Harima.
Well, I'll leave you guys to it,
work him as hard
as you want, Nijo!
Ka... Ka...
Karasuma!
You heartless jerk,
how can you sit here
when Tenma is having
her... I'm sorry...
I'm here to assist you
Mister Nijo, so put me to work.
Mmm... all right.
This is too weird...
here I am with a professional
gig, just like I wanted,
and I'm working for
Jo Nijo of all people!
This story...
it's a love comedy?
But I remember his comic
being a period drama...
Why would he change it?
And why such a weak premise to
set up one big gag...? Unless...
Could it be?
He's using his comic to
tell Tenma how he feels!
That sneaky bastard...!
I have to stop him,
whatever it takes...!
But how exactly can I do that?
Oh, crap! How could I let
ink drip onto the layout?!
Uh... whoops...
He laughed!
He definitely laughed
at me just now!
He's gonna pay for that!
Okay, get a grip...!
I gotta fix that layout...
There. A perfect recovery,
if I do say so myself.
Wait... it's gonna look strange
if he only has
sunglasses in one panel.
Karasuma... I mean, Mr. Nijo...
They're having a birthday party
for Tenma over at
El Cado tonight...
Maybe you didn't hear about it,
but everyone is already there...
I'm sure no one would mind if
you just, y'know, dropped in.
If you want to...
as one of her fellow
classmates, I mean.
Uh... sorry to intrude...
I just saw Tazawa leave.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
Well, okay...
keep up the good work,
tell me if you need anything.
Mm-hm.
Hmph! I'm such a candy pants...
showing kindness
to my enemy like that!
Well, guess what...
it's gonna cost him!
I'm gonna re-draw this
to make me the star!
Take that, Karasuma!
Good for you... Tenma...
Tsukamoto residence...
uh, hello, Harima... what?
You want me to come right away?
Hello, Harima...
sorry I'm late... what
is it you needed me for?
Hey...
Um... what are you doing?
So you spilled the ink and
decided you had no choice
but to escape out the window...?
Then you remembered
this was the 26th floor
and had no idea what to do next.
Okay, first off,
where are the layouts?
You've gotta help me,
please, Tenma's Sister!
Uh... do you remember the story?
Not a word...
I don't even remember the title,
and I can't very
well ask the editor.
There's no choice...
I'll have to write my own.
But, Harima,
how could you possibly...?
The cruel hand of
fate has spoken...!
I may not look it,
but under this tough guy
exterior I'm a professional...!
After all, I did win the New
Face Honorable Mention!
So you'll continue the
love comedy idea...?
You'll have to
get him to declare--
No, that's a horrible idea!
Uh... uh... that is...
I've gotta stop Karasuma's plan
to declare his love
dead in its tracks!
No, see...
if I do something similar,
someone will realize
it's a fake, right?
So instead...
Koshien Stadium!
What do you think?
Well, I have to admit
that it takes the plot
in an unexpected direction.
Just what I was going for!
O-kay, then
I guess next we'll have
to show him practicing
as hard as he can.
No way! Try to keep
up with me, baby.
At the critical moment,
he'll get mad,
and his strength will
increase sevenfold!
It happens all
the time in comics!
Right. Then what happens?
Leave it to me...!
I've got it all worked out!
Huh...? What's this?
Next there's a battle!
Don't worry... It's traditional
in boys' comics.
At Koshien Stadium they
can have a tournament!
It's perfect!
Uh...
It's classic, there's
always a tournament
when the plot gets stuck!
So then the pitcher
builds up his ki...
Ki?
Yeah, or his aura, or
whatever you want to call it.
We'll need to think of
some way to set that up.
Get this! The umpire
will be a demon king!
Unexpected, huh?
And the other team
is controlled by him,
and they're trying to
wipe out all life on earth!
Uh... why do they wanna do that?
I don't know...!
What do you think?
Why don't you tell me
what happens next?
Well, naturally
it's time for...
...a little romantic action.
It's not my strong point, but
it's bound to be very popular.
I just don't know
how to approach this.
You got any ideas,
Tenma's Sister?
Um... you could...
What? What is it?!
You could maybe
make them... kiss.
Wait...?! Wouldn't that
be going a little too far?
No...! I have to take
this story to the limit!
Way to go, Tenma's Sister!
Oh... you really think so?
Yeah, I'll draw it up right now!
O-okay...
It's still not right.
Wait a minute...! I remember
a bit I saw in another comic!
The main character
stumbles and falls,
and somehow manages to
knock the other person down.
Something like this!
It could work! I just know it!
But... are you sure
you can pull it off?
If I act it out first to check
the composition, I'll be okay.
Huh?
Would you mind, um...
...you know, doing it with me?
For research!
Um... well...
I guess...
All right! You're on top!
Uh... now what?
I'm sure it was
something like this.
All right, you're up...
now you fall all over me, kay?
Okay.
"Ah!" First say, "Ah!"
and then you fall down.
If you say so.
Ah!
I love you.
This still isn't right!
Help me out...
...what do you think?
Uh... I don't really know
much about this whole thing.
But can love...
really develop from
something like this?
You're right...
there's no way
this crap'll work.
I guess I should only draw
things from my own experience.
I was wrong to try to
borrow ideas from others.
Yeah...
All right, I'm gonna
draw something great!
There's no time for us
to lose, Tenma's Sister!
Uh... right!
Okay, here are the betas!
Right!
These are the beta roughs!
Right! What number should I use?
61, please!
We finished it!
Hell yes!
Okay, boss man,
the layouts are done!
What's this...? What happened
to Mr. Nijo's storyline?
Uh...
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
Nah, don't be.
It's not your fault...
I'm the idiot who
spilled the ink, right?
It's kinda funny, though,
I completely forgot what
my original objective was.
Huh?
Which reminds me...
did Karasuma ever come
to your sister's party?
Oh... Yeah... After the
party he came by our house.
I see.
So... Harima... you know...
I still have that
birthday present
I didn't give to you before...
if you want it.
No...! I mean after all
you've done for me already,
I couldn't...
Take it... and Happy Birthday.
Thanks, Tenma's Sister.
What the hell... let's run it.
Game time, everybody!
All right!
I will accept any challenge...
...offered me!
Hey, stop it...!
Those are my lines!
So... what's the game?
Hey, listen to me
when I'm talking!
Well, first we select a topic...
And once you give your answer,
you pass this to
the next person.
When it blows up, the person
holding it plays a penalty game!
Blows up?!
Isn't that dangerous?!
It's all right
Lara, don't worry about it.
It sounds dangerous.
Oh, yeah...
whenever men play games,
it's no fun unless
their lives are at risk...
Don't you agree, partner?
Please stop calling me that.
Very well, let's begin
this competition!
I, Tougou
Masakazu, once feared
as the Tiger of Manhattan,
will take you all on!
Right. So anyway.
Let's get started...! When
you're handed the bomb,
you have to say a
famous tongue twister
and then pass it to
the next player... Go!
Peter Piper picked a
peck of pickled peppers.
Let's see...
Friendly Frank flipped
fine flapjacks, your turn.
Try "Rubber baby buggy bumpers".
No way! I could never say that.
Come on, Lara! You can do it!
Rubber baggy bubby bunkers!
She said it wrong...!
And Ichijou whispered
it to her, I call foul!
Lara, please, take it easy!
Uh, no... I was just
holding it, I wasn't playing.
It's penalty time!
Wow that's
disturbingly attractive.
Okay... on to round two, there's
lots more costumes to wear!
All right, I'll start
this round off.
Everyone name one of the
United States... California!
Dakota. South side.
Hey, come on, hurry up,
what are you waiting for,
are you tryin' to stick me
with it at the last second?!
She wanted to wear that.
All right, here we go...
everyone name some
common flowers. Daffodil--
What's the big idea,
did you set me up?!
No, it's totally random,
don't blame me!
Now, now, rules are rules...
Besides, this
getup isn't so bad.
Right... move
that fin or lose it.
Tell me the truth, Suga.
Do you have it
in for me or what?
Okay, my turn...
the name of a person you
respect above all others...
Stephen Hawking,
the physicist... here!
Interesting...
Dr. Hawking,
world famous researcher
on black hole theory...
You made a very
profound choice, wow.
Never mind the
smooth talk, get on with it!
I'm sorry, how rude of me.
The person I most respect
is... my dead father.
Way to make it awkward.
It's my turn now,
right...? Well, then...
The lovely Monaka Azuki.
Who's that?
The gifted star of
"Infirmary of Secrets."
You foul-minded fat pervert,
do you carry that thing
around with you everywhere?
You're absolutely disgusting!
When are you gonna
grow up, you pig?!
Those two are
pretty close, aren't they?
They've been arguing
since preschool!
Speaking of preschoolers,
where's Tenma...?
She was just here.
If you're looking for Tsukamoto,
I believe she stepped
outside for a little while.
I guess I better
go check on her.
I'll come with you.
Nah, it's cool.
It's not like she
could've gone too far.
This is very uncomfortable.
Duh! It's a penalty costume!
Even with that mask on,
our merciful Nishimoto
retains his poise...! Amazing.
What are you doing stupid?!
The mask is too small for him!
Is he breathing?!
Is he gonna be okay?
This way, Nishimoto!
Follow the light!
We're waiting for you!
Come to us!
We can't wait for you a
minute longer! We want you!
I'm coming for you,
my darlings! Here I am!
Wake up, perv!
I saw a vision of heaven.
Hey, Eri, what
happened to your head?!
Harima?
Are you going to Dankosha again?
What? Me too?
Next time on School Rumble
Second Semester:
"A Man Shut Out, A Man
Left Out, A Man Tested Out!"
It really is winter now, huh?