Before tonight, something inside
me had already given up...
But now, that's all changed...
Am I doing the right thing?
I don't know anymore...
Well, it appears
that I'm a bit too late.
No matter, I'll put
Masaru on the case.
Yakumo, I think I feel like
having sushi tonight.
But... I was planning
on making stew.
All right... Sushi it is.
Just let me put this up.
Thank you! You're the
best sister in the world!
Okay... what kind--
Sis? Where are you?
This is nuts. I should
be working on my comic.
I got a deadline
breathing down my neck
but here I am ferrying
Rich Girl around.
Um, excuse me.
Do you know where we're going?
Well, not really,
just driving right now!
Sorry Mikoto made you do this.
I know you're her
employee, but I feel bad.
Damn right ya should.
So, if I heard right, you're
running away from a marriage?
Not exactly...
I'm supposed to go to an
engagement meeting tomorrow.
My parents arranged it...
They're forcing me,
even though they know
I don't wanna
go through with it.
Sounds like you don't
wanna do it, Rich Girl.
You could say no...
Couldn't you?
Before tonight, something inside
me had already given up...
But now that's all changed...
Am I doing the right thing?
I don't know anymore...
I'm so lost, but looking at the
road in front of me I wonder...
Huh?!
What the hell was that?!
That was Tenma!
But, but what is she doing
with my family's maid?!
Something's up.
I've got to text her!
It's so nice to finally get to
meet you in person, Asou.
Yes, we've heard
so much about you.
You've done so much for Miko.
Thank you, ma'am, you're kind,
but I really haven't
done much at all.
You haven't done anything!
That's my little
spitfire, all right!
Don't be rude.
Asou, I gotta say
you act and look a
lot more mature than
I thought you would. Whoa...
You were saying you stopped by
because you're concerned
about a missing friend?
That's very considerate.
Most kids your age
are not, Asou. That's--
All right! Enough!
This guy isn't even Asou!
That was painful.
Now that I've gotten
a look at your temper,
I can better understand
why you've had problems
finding a boyfriend.
The only problem
I've got right now is you!
On the bright side,
I've heard that things
are blossoming
between you and Asou.
I understand the two of you
had a moment at the arcade?
Argh! Stop talking about my
love life, would you...?! Geez!
How screwed up is it
that even Eri's butler
knows about my dates?!
I hate it!!
I apologize, it's just that Miss
Eri speaks so fondly of you.
Huh?
It's true...
and quite frequently.
I've heard all the stories,
how you enchant the boys
and then pretend like
you're not interested.
How did Miss Eri put it again?
Ah, yes. She said
"OMG she's such a tease."
Dammit Eri, I'm gonna kill you!
Catchin' a cold?
Oh no, I'm fine... It's Tenma
Your maid grabbed me
and put me in your limo.
She sure has big hands,
and a big Adam's apple!
Anyway, she said we're
going to a meeting
and she even called me
"Miss Eri." What a joker!
See ya!
Don't tell me that
idiot mistook her for me!
Somethin' wrong?
My idiotic maid mistook
my friend Tenma for me
and now they're on their
way to my engagement meeting.
Other than that,
everything's great!
We gotta stop 'em, now!
Let's go, Miss...!
I'm gonna make sure neither
one of you has to get engaged!
I don't get it.
Why is he trying so hard?
Hurry! Get on!
All right, if he wants to play
the knight in shining
armor, then so be it.
I'm coming Tenma!
No way in hell you're
getting engaged!
Oh... stop...
I told you, I'm not Eri,
my name's Tenma.
Huh? Menma?
Oh. Miko's texting me...
Eri...? Meeting for
an arranged marriage?
Oh no!
Is that why Eri's maid is
taking me to this meeting?!
That's it!
She must think I'm Eri!
From the looks of her,
she's not too bright,
or very feminine
for that matter.
I've gotta help Eri!
I'll play along and
scare off her suitor!
Um, I need text my sister.
She's probably
worried sick by now.
We have to break
up this engagement!
Dammit! Of all the
times to get a flat!
We don't have
time to be stranded,
we gotta stop that meeting!
Wait, calm down.
Tenma wouldn't marry
some guy she just met.
But she's so cute,
any guy would propose
like mad to her until
he wears her down!
Crap!
It's freezing in here.
I can't believe he gave me
the only blanket we had.
I wonder how
he's gonna stay warm.
I guess the polite thing to do
would be to share the
blanket with him...
Ah! But then we'd
practically be cuddling.
Oh god, I don't want
him to get any ideas.
But if I don't, Mr.
Worker Man here
is probably
gonna catch a cold.
What do I do?
Huh? What's up with her?
She looks worried... Oh, man!
Don't tell me she
thinks I'm gonna try
and put the moves on her!
She does! Dammit!
Rich Girl's even more
conceited than I thought!
Wait, why am I surprised?
I've seen how she acts.
She thinks she's
the hottest girl in school
and that any guy
would go ga-ga over her.
Well, guess what?
Your wily charms
won't work on me.
Maybe I should start
with some small talk
and then offer him the blanket.
Um, Mr. Worker Man? So tell me.
How long have you been
working for the Suous exactly?
Uh... Um... A day...
No! I mean... a year.
You look young.
Working your way
through college, huh?
Do you have a girlfriend?
Huh...? No, I don't.
Really...?! You're kidding!
What a waste!
Wait, is that a flirty giggle?
Yes! It is! She never
acts this way with me.
It has to be a trap.
She's tryin' to set me up!
Oh gosh, I'm sorry.
That was probably a
little forward, wasn't it?
I hope I didn't embarrass you.
No, it's okay.
Since we're stuck here,
why don't you tell
me about yourself?
What do you wanna
do once you graduate?
Do you have any plans?
Uh!
Damn. Can't tell her
I wanna draw comics
and hope to marry Tenma...
I think I'll work for the Suous
for a while, save some money,
then branch out and try
to start my own business.
You know,
be my own person.
That's my real dream.
Hah! Checkmate, Rich Girl!
Wow, seems like you've
got it all worked out.
What kind of business
do you wanna start?
Uh, that's top secret.
So tell me, how do
you deal with people
who get in the
way of your dreams?
Has there ever been
anyone like that in your life?
You have no idea...
Huh?
Uh , I mean...
I can't let things beat me down.
I have to take a
stand against anything
that would try to destroy
my hopes and dreams.
So be strong?
Yeah, that's it, exactly.
This guy is so
different from me.
Why can't I be more like him?
But how do I become strong?
Should I act more masculine?
More grown-up?
I just don't think I have
what it takes to make
a stand for myself.
Sometimes...
Sometimes there are
things that get me down...
They can be hard to deal with...
But I try not to worry too much
about the things
that I can't change...
So I just accept them...
I figure if I can't beat 'em,
I'll laugh 'em off.
Wait! Why the hell am
I telling Rich Girl all this?!
Move over!
Uh! What the--?!
I, uh, didn't want
you to catch a cold.
She's worried
about someone else?!
That's not like her!
This is freaking me out!
She's up to something!
I'll move... I mean, if
this makes you uncomfortable.
No, it's okay.
I'll be honest.
I've been pretty depressed
for the last couple of days.
But hearing you talk
about your dreams,
well things are finally
starting to make sense.
And now I feel like I have
the courage to say
what I need to say.
What?
I know it's a lot to ask,
but would you come
with me to my
engagement meeting?
Uhh...
No, no, it's not like that!
I mean, it would just be
for pretend, of course!
You would be there to
help me break it off.
Uh, no?
I know... I should really
take care of this by myself.
I'm sorry...
But I can't...
I'm not strong enough.
Rich Girl...
All right. I'll do it.
Thank you.
What did I get myself into?
What? She's asleep
already? Hmph.
Poor little rich
girl all tuckered out
from finally speaking
her mind for once.
Honestly, though, I never
thought you had it in you.
For a second there
you made me think:
Hey, maybe she's not a
totally selfish, shallow, crazy,
spoiled, manipulative,
insensitive, egocentric girl.
But it was only for a second.
It's weird. You actually
look kinda cute right now.
Too bad I'm not even
remotely interested.
Mikoto, what are
you talking about?
Whiskers totally sucks at life.
Moment is over.
Back to being mortal enemies.
Oh? He's not here yet?
Good. We're in luck...
Here's what we're gonna do...
Yeah?
Pretend to be
the guy I'm meeting.
My parents have
never even seen him.
Clean yourself up a bit, and
they won't know the difference.
We'll meet. Then you
break off the engagement.
And that's it... So, tell me,
what do you think?
Okay.
Can't believe she actually
convinced me to do this.
This it?
Well, let's get
this over with...
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Eri Sawachika.
I'm pleased to meet you.
Let us discuss our
future, shall we?
Don't worry.
You've got him to back you up.
Everything will go smoothly.
Oh, look at you!
Eri, you look stunning!
Mother!
What are you doing here?
I wanted... to talk.
Please, dear.
It'll be brief, I promise.
I almost forgot...!
Tenma was already here.
All right then.
I'll just have to work my
magic before Rich Girl shows up.
So, um...
What are your interests?
I draw comics.
I draw pictures, poo!
What the--?!
Is she making fun of me?!
Does she think
comics are stupid?!
Was that too rude?
No, you can't let
this guy take Eri away!
Show no mercy!
Coming here wasn't
easy for you, was it?
I'm so sorry.
Mother, please, it's okay!
This isn't your fault.
Yes, it is, at least partially.
Mother! Just stop it!
Please forgive me.
Uh, what are your interests?
Rubik's cube. Love it.
I've been engaged lotsa times,
but every one of them
has been called off.
I wonder why?
That should scare him off!
What do you say to that,
Mr. Soon-To-Be-Ex-fiancée?
Please marry me!
Eri, honestly, if you don't
wanna go through
with this, it's okay.
Mother, don't worry about it.
I'm fine. I promise.
Very well.
Should I tell your father that
you're going through with it?
I guess, since I don't
have the guts to say no.
Did you hear the good news?
We're all in Class 2-C.
Including you.
Nothin' like kickin'
it with the girlfriends!
We need a new pitcher.
When you think about it...
Miko isn't that pretty.
Guess what?
Got myself dumped.
Any guy who'd
dump you is an idiot.
Please deliver this for me.
I can't believe you guys!
You should've told me none
of you knew how to swim!
You stupid jerks!
We have to beat 2-D!
Take that!
Tenma! Cut it out! That's cold!
Hey! You are so
totally asking for it!
Wait! There's something
I need to say!
If you don't scare him off,
Eri's getting married!
You've gotta resort to Plan B!
Woo-woo!
You know what gets me
goin' on a day like this?
What's that?!
Bumpin' techno beats.
What the--?!
I knew this would stop him!
He's into it?!
Sawachika...
Eri!
Eri.
Finally.
Mother... Listen...
I... I don't wanna do this...
And that's my final decision.
Eri, hold on a minute!
Finally. I stood up for myself.
I'm my own person.
How clumsy of me!
I'm sorry, my hand slipped!
It's okay. Accidents
do happen, after all.
This guy's tough!
He wants Eri more than Harima
wants Yakumo...! Hey, wait...
C'mere a minute!
What are you doing?! No!
Hold still!
Mr. Worker Man, it's okay!
You don't have to--
So... The engagement is off.
Understood.
Iori, where's all the tuna?
♪ ending song ♪
Looks like Kuta's not drawing
the crowds like he used to.
Well, he's been
actin' up so much lately,
I think people
are scared of him.
Kuta, would you knock it off?!
Mikoto invited me over to spar.
What do you mean
she's "occupied?"
The truth is...
An engagement meeting?!
No! Are you sure?!
That's terrible!
That's correct.
Miss Tsukamoto and Miss Eri are
both on their way as we speak.
What?! Hanai went after them?!
Please. They're hundreds
of kilometers away.
He'd have to be a lunatic.
Trust me, Nakamura,
you have no idea.
It's Harima, isn't it?!
The rumors are true!
I'm sure you're
being forced into this!
Don't you worry about a thing,
Yakumo! I'll save you!
I don't know how much longer
I can keep on pedaling.
Maybe I can rest up there.
It's a good thing
I packed some food.
I'll have a little dinner
and then hit the hay...
And hopefully not
freeze to death up here.
But I can't...
I'm not strong enough.
Huh?
All right. I'll do it
Somebody there?
Thank you.
Hey what is this thing?
Some kinda blanket?
Oh! It is! It's a big,
warm, comfy one at that!
Somebody in here?
Yes! Over here! Help!
Guess not.
If I don't put an end to
this pandemonium and quick,
I'm going to end up its dinner!
Standard attack strategy
for a big opponent
is to sweep their legs
and topple them!
But that only works for
opponents with two legs!
Damn...! My best attack
strategy will only work
if it stands up like a human!
Thank you!
Down, beast!
Time to finish you!
Oh! Too cute!
Is it morning already?
Can you fix it?
Yeah. I managed to swipe some
tools from that bike over there.
What's wrong?
Nothing! Everything's great!
Are you hungry?
You want some breakfast?
Sure.
I found some food.
I guess it was too
dark to see last night,
but it was right next to us.
Wow. First I find these
tools and then you find food.
This temple's been
good to us, hasn't it?
After escaping last night,
Kuta the Red Panda is safely
back home at the Yagami Zoo.
With his new glasses,
this popular panda is
more precious than ever!
Aw! How cute!
Yakumo, Sara, today we're
cleaning the old schoolhouse.
Come as quickly as you can...
Next time, on School Rumble:
"The Sweet Trap of Work;
The Sweet Trap of the Classroom;
The Sweet Trap of Celebrity."
Penguins, such sad creatures...