Tenma Tsukamoto...
Half human, half machine.
Sis! Hey Sis!
Today's the Dozibiron
off line party...!
You haven't forgotten, have you?
Huh...? A party?
Oh, I did forget.
Sorry, Sis is tired
out from work,
so could you let me sleep today?
All right then...
suit yourself...
I'll just play with
my Internet friend.
Wait, you mean he's
actually coming over?
I'm the chat room moderator...
They all want a
piece of this, yo!
Grade school kids are really
something these days.
I don't want none,
I don't want none...
Wah! Boom!
I'm surprised you'd get together
with someone you only
know from the net...
what if some weirdo comes over?
But this is Dozibiron Blue,
the kid I chat with
all the freakin' time.
Oh, that's right, the
boy you like so much...
How old is this guy?
His spelling is pretty bad,
my guess is he's a
little younger than me.
Well... okay then...
But try to play quietly.
Okay, we will.
I'm going to sleep now.
All right.
Yes?
I... Imadori?
Hey, Itchy... would you like
to go out on a date with me?
Oh... oh my...
so many... feelings ...
are you sure you'd
settle for a girl like me?
Itchy...
I mean... Karen... it looks
like I've given in to you.
Huh?!
Not bad... take this!
Whoa, nice one!
Now let me see...
what should I try next...?
Too late, Blue,
you lost this one!
It figures that's
what I'd dream about.
But I have to say
it was a nice one.
No way! You're
such a sore loser!
My gosh, those two are
making a lot of noise!
Hey...! Turn it down!
Could you use
your inside voices?
Ten four!
Hey Sis, did you sleep well?
Hm...? your sister?
What the heck is he doing here?!
That's...
That's Ima, Ima, Ima...
Dude what's up
with the drama...?
I mean, This is
just Dozibiron Blue.
So Imadori's the...?!
You said he was
younger than you!
Wait a minute...!
How do you know his name?
How do I... he's in
my class, that's how!
What...?! Someone as
fun as this guy...?
That is so... awesome
Oh, never mind that now!
Okay?
I-I have to hurry
and go do something!
Like what, Sis?
Oh, it doesn't matter, I just
have to do something, anything!
Aw...
Ah! The laundry is
all over the place!
So what...? It's just laundry!
Look, give me a hand,
will you, Kosuke?
Hurry and fold them, come on!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Hey, Itchy, where's this go?
Oh, that... that goes
down in the bottom drawer.
Wait a minute, what do you
think you're doing, Imadori?!
Oh, I just thought I'd go
ahead and make myself useful.
Hey, Itchy, I gotta say,
I'm surprised you
own something this big.
That belongs to my mom!
Ho-ho! Give my
congratulations to your mother!
I found somebody's jammies!
Ah...! Give me those
back right now!
Itchy, do you really
work out with these things?
They must weigh a ton!
They're just five kilos each,
that's hardly anything!
Trying to diet down
to under 40 kilos, huh?
Looks like you've almost
made it, hang in there!
Oh, stop it...!
Stop being such a big meanie!
Poor thing...
Little Itchy thinks
Imadori's a big meanie.
I can't take it anymore!
Come on, Sis,
forget all that crap
and play
Dozibiron with us...!
Then you can be Dozibiron Pink
just like you always are!
Yeah, I bet your sister really
rocks as the Pink Ranger!
Hey...
I just realized...
I've been a total jerk to you.
Just relax and be
yourself from now on, okay?
You really mean it?
Okay, I'll play
for a little bit.
All right!!
Arise!!
And unite!!
Dozibiron!!
Episode forty-three, "The
Pressure Point Pushing Monster
Ryusan's Hidden Trap During
the Weekend School Trip...
Part Four!"
Yeah!!
Episode forty-three?
I'm impressed!
That one's a classic!
Great choice!
There's nothing as relaxing
as a massage after a hot bath!
Oh, no! Can't move!
Come on, Crewman Kosuke,
you've got to snap out of it!
No good... all of
my body's pressure points
have become paralyzed!
It's your turn next,
Pink Ranger!
Yeah...! Now this is
where Ryusan attacks!
Soon you'll be as helpless
as your crewmate!
I'll rub you down!!
What are you gonna do, Karen?!
No, you don't!
Take this...! Invincible Hammer!
Not bad, Dozibiron!
Not bad yourself, Ryusan!
Hey Dozibiron Blue!
I bet if you sang
the theme song...
Dozibiron Pink would
show you her bra!
Impressive! But I'm
not showing you my bra!
I'm really sorry if I made
too much of a fuss today.
But... if you can maybe give
me a little advance notice...
next time I can have everything
ready when you come over.
Come back soon, Blue!
Hey... you can count
on it, Kosuke...!
Now don't give your sister
a hard time, all right?
Whatev!
Whaddaya think, Sis...?
Maybe you and Blue
should hook it up...! Ah!
Just kidding...! Huh?
Hey, look...
Isn't this the mask that
Blue brought over with him?
Huh...? I could've
sworn I saw him
put that thing in
his pocket earlier.
There, that takes care of
the exposure and the angle...
The settings are all finished.
All you have to do is
point the camera and click.
Thanks a lot...
for coming in on
the break and all.
Hey, it's no big deal,
anything to help out
a fellow band member, right?
Wow, it's getting chilly...
you should head back
inside, Tsumugi.
I don't really mind...
I mean, this is my only chance
to relax and just
look at the stars.
Just think, next year
we're gonna be juniors...
are you planning on sticking
with your astronomy studies?
I'm not really sure...
I'm taking liberal arts.
I see.
Wow, it's cold!
You guys must be freezing...
I brought some food at least.
Oh, wasn't expecting
you to be here, Fuyuki.
I asked him to stop by
and give us a hand.
Okay.
Come on, everyone, let's eat!
Generous as always, Megumi!
It's one of the perks
of having a family
in the restaurant biz... Ta-da!
Okay, now that
we're all warmed up...
Let's talk about all
this year's love gossip!
Oh, come on, what do
we have to do that for?
Oh, please... we're three
teenage girls, we're together,
it's the end of the school year,
what else would we talk about?
Hey, there's a guy
here too ya know...
They're not listening.
Well, you go first.
What have you got?
Oh good... 'bout time you
weren't so awkward about it.
As it turns out, this year there
were ten couples that got
together... A new record!
I can't believe you
remembered all of them.
Gosh you never change.
That makes us even,
you never change either!
I'm as boring as ever.
Oh, you're right.
I mean, a whole year has gone by
and I haven't done anything!
OMG I was so JKing...!
I think you accomplished
a lot this year!
I mean...
you sang in front of
Imadori, you invited him
to your house,
that's like totally huge!
I didn't invite him over, it was
my little brother, he did it!
The point is, you did a lot
this year, so take it easy
So how did your year go, Yuki?
Hm?
Oh, my year...
was nothing special.
Between stargazing...
and watching
Karen here blossom...
I've managed to
keep pretty busy.
Okay, I'm starting
to get cold again...
tell you what, I'll get some
coffee... you wanna come?
Freeze, boy!
Why not let Karen
and me get the coffee?
You two stay here, okay...?
Just enjoy the snow.
Couple number eleven
coming right up!
Looks like they've got
the wrong idea about us.
Really...? It doesn't seem
like too bad an idea to me.
Mm-mm... no thanks.
No? Why not?
I don't go for guys
who are overconfident.
Okay, maybe
I am a little forward,
but inside I'm just
a delicate flower.
Most guys who act
overconfident are.
You're loud and obnoxious,
begging for attention,
but as soon as someone figures
you out you get all awkward.
Awkward...?
I'm so not awkward...
I mean, really, don't you
think that's kinda harsh?
Sorry but I'm
tired of being seen
as the quiet girl who
never speaks her mind.
Something's different
about you today.
What? What're you talking about?
You're in love aren't you?
That's why you
look so beautiful.
Shut up. Don't try to feed
me one of your stupid lines.
I'm not falling for it.
No. I'm serious!
Women in love have a
certain radiance about them.
Sometimes I think I'm
the only one who sees it.
Is that why you're
a photographer?
I wish I could
capture it on film...
but somehow it always
seems to escape me.
Still, I'm pretty lucky...
I get to see a
whole world of beauty
that most ordinary people don't
even realize is out there.
Like you, today...
I can see it in your eyes.
It's like they're
on fire with passion.
Word of advice...
Don't ever try to become a poet.
Would you stop it?!
Oh, come on,
you know you want some!
Here, try it!
Hey!
Hey... there's the first star.
Um... pretty sure
those are clouds.
Hey... so what do you think
of the new guy they
made division chief?
Oh... um... well, I...
Pretty good looking, I'd say.
Beats the old pervert
we had before.
He smelled like soup and death.
Needs a little work in the
wardrobe department, though.
He wears nothing but black.
Yeah, it's weird.
Think maybe it's some
kind of political statement?
What? You guys have
a problem with black?
Ah-ha...
What is it?
Nothing.
Tenma...! Could this
be love at first sight?
No! Don't listen, she lies!
Filling out forms
sure is thirsty work.
I'm gonna go make
some tea! See ya!
Wow. Bipolar much?
I don't like that girl.
Why?
She's got a lot of
nerve for a new kid...
I mean, kissing up
to the boss like that?
How 'bout we welcome her
to Cybo-Div - Old School style.
I'm Tenma Tsukamoto,
the new girl
in Cyber Division,
or "Cybo-Div"...
They still don't let me
do much more than make tea,
but with this high-priced
gourmet, organically grown tea,
I'm gonna win
Chief Karasuma's heart!
Hot stuff coming through!
The truth is...
I don't have any memories
before six months ago.
I have what they call amnesia.
When I was down and out,
and all alone with
no one to turn to,
it was Big Sister Yakumo who
held out a helping hand to me.
I call her "Big Sister" because
she's so mature and beautiful...
she must be older than me.
This is the stuck
up princess, Eri...
And Mikoto.
She's got a great rack...
And the boyishly handsome Akira,
I'd so do her in that uniform.
We work hard, and they're
a great team to be on!
Who's this again?
Hey there, Chief... how
would you like to join me
for a private candlelight
dinner and hotel tonight?
I spilled the tea!
Huh...! Looks like you'd
better make more, honey...
And bring me a cup too.
Yes, Miss Eri...
Just because she's
got a little money
she thinks she
can lord it over me?
Wait! What in the
world came over me?
Never mind...!
This time the chief
will drink my special
tea of love for sure!
Chief Karasuma,
Miss Eri... your tea is ready!
Excuse me, Chief... how do
I fill out this big long form?
She thinks she's all that
'cause she's got boobs
big enough to have
their own address!
Take... that...! and that!
Not again...! What's the deal?
Could something in my
mysterious past be causing this?
Nah, that's crazy talk!
Now to get out there
and serve that tea!
All right, everyone...
ready to have your
mind blown by my tea?
Big Sister Yakumo!
You too? I trusted you!
Sorry, but it's tradition...
I don't want to,
but I have to do it.
See, this is sort of a
rookie welcoming party.
What...? Welcoming party...
Wait...! Tenma!
This must be that famous
Cybo-Div rookie hazing
I've heard about!
Wow... Tenma's tea is so... hot.
Do you want one?
Huh?
A Cybo-Div welcoming party?
What are you talkin' about?
I'm your superior officer!
You're members
of Cyborg Division,
not some college sorority!
Act like it!
You don't have to yell...
Ichijou!
You made her cry!!
You bastard!
You gotta lotta nerve pickin'
on my beloved Tenma...!
No way are you gonna
get away with that!
I wasn't lookin'
at you, Blondie!
Lara, for heaven's sake,
let him go he's starting
to foam at the mouth!
What's wrong?
Akira.
Hey there.
I see... so that's the problem.
I'm just a stupid, clumsy ox!
Hey now, come on, that doesn't
sound like the Tenma I know.
The Tenma I know is always
cheerful and positive...
and always brightens a
room by leaving a little bit
of that cheer with
everyone she meets.
I wish... it's all just an act.
Act or not, the fact
is you really do make
everyone feel a little bit
better for having known you.
Ya see?
Big Sister Yakumo... Hey, girls!
Oh, Tenma, we're so sorry.
Yeah, we only meant
it as a little joke...
We feel really bad...
Come on, Eri, you too.
It's... Whatever...
I'm... I'm like sorry n'stuff.
Oh, gosh... look at me...
I'm gonna get all weepy,
I just know it...
Yes... up until then...
things were peaceful...
but I had something
important I had to tell her...
even if it meant destroying
this time of happiness.
Miss Tsukamoto.
Chief Karasuma!
There's something
important I have to tell you.
Why, that lousy creep!
I could... I could kill that
jerk...! What's he sayin'?!
Chief Harima...!
Mind your own business
and get back to work!
Shut up...! I'm sick
of your bullsh--!
What the hell is going on?
Network security
has been compromised!
System crash is
like so imminent!
All right... let's hit it!
Cyber!!!
Hold on, pal...!
That's my division!
Sound off.
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
One more time.
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
And six!
Seven!
There is an unprecedented
danger approaching us...
you are the only ones with
any hope of saving us...
now move out!
Cyber!!
I keep telling you
this is my division!
We meet again, Cybo-Div!
Doctor Hanai!
You are all doomed...!
Today I delete you...!
Attack...! Go forth,
precious drones!
Hey...! Getcher
stinger outta there!!
This whole "bees with grabby
hands" thing is getting awkward!
Please, make it stop!
Bring it on!
No...! You guys...
Cadet Tsukamoto...
Avenge our deaths...
Don't let this be in vain...
Don't give up...
We all... really liked you,
please believe that...
Tenma!!
I will carry on the
fight for all of you...
Our enemies will
be shown no mercy.
Just a moment, Miss Tsukamoto!
There's one thing
I have to tell you...
before the battle.
Is this some dark secret
from my forgotten past?
You're wearing mismatched socks.
Oh, no...! How long
has it been like that?!
Then what could've happened
in her past that...?
Don't tell me it
was the time that...
I wanna go home...! Doowah!
Come on...! You're a
scientifically modified
and enhanced human being...!
Stop being childish!
She's scientifically hot...
Oh yeah!
I wonder if that could
be what caused her amnesia!
You got it!
And... due to my
genius modifications,
she was unharmed by the bus!
Of course, she did go
missing after that...
You're gonna pay.
Uh... What's that?
I said you're gonna pay!
You'll be sorry you did this...!
You've violated the
purity of a maiden's heart!
Tenma's internal maiden
circuits are activated
which means we're
f@#!ed, and the thing
in the basement
is like, coming out.
It's happened...
the time has come.
You're up, big guy.
♪ ending song ♪
Oh, come on!
You can't have
more shopping to do!
Sorry, but that's
just how it goes!
Aw, somebody lost their toy.
What is that thing?
I don't know... But I
kinda feel sorry for it.
There. All right!
One more store to hit!
You could carry some
of this, you know!
Let's eat some noodles...
I don't want none...
Yakumo! Aren't the
soba noodles done yet?
The "Three for the
Kill" big year end special
is about to start!
Here! They're all done, Sis!
This is why I love
New Year's Eve.
Soba noodles! Soba noodles!
Come on, Yakumo!
Soba noodles!
Soba noodles! Soba noodles!