For many years, I have
sought this enchanted land!
Has my quest finally
come to an end?
Within that sheer, soaring
tower lies the princess!
Master, I beg you...
don't do this...!
No one who has ever entered
that mystic tower has
returned to tell the tales!
Silence...!
It's my destiny to go on!
Inside that tower the princess,
placed under a curse
by an evil witch, has lain
in enchanted slumber
for a hundred years!
Now... to the tower!
You see, it's an epic love story
and a sweeping
fantasy all in one...!
What do you think?
You know...
I had so much energy after
seeing your sister yesterday...
I stayed up the
whole night drawing
this one hundred and
twenty page masterpiece!
I hate to spring
it on you like this,
but could you read it
and give me your feedback?
Man, I'm beat.
I need some shut-eye, like whoa.
Have you heard?
2-C's play is supposed
to be incredible!
Yeah, I heard the casting
was, like, phenomenal!
It figures...
I mean, Takano has always been,
like, so creative, you know?
Yeah, I wonder
who's playing what role!
I'm so excited I can't stand it!
Now that's what
I'm talkin' about!
Yeah! That is one hot poster!
Know what I mean? Low five.
Wow, the place
is really filling up!
It looks like we
got a full house, guys!
Imagine having all these people
turn out to see our little play!
Sawachika's a knockout!
You look great, Eri!
No doubt about it, all
eyes are gonna be on her!
Okay, so seriously...
You're rockin' that
outfit to the max!
Well, I don't feel
rockin'... I'm shaking!
Don't sweat it... We've
rehearsed this thing to death!
I guess so.
Once upon a time,
in a far off land,
there was a beautiful
princess who was placed
under a curse by an evil witch.
For a hundred years she lay deep
in an enchanted sleep
in a soaring tower.
But now, six brave heroes
have gathered together
in order to rescue the princess!
Six heroes give their call...
all for one and one for all!
The six brave heroes...
traveled across six valleys
and climbed six mountains
until they finally arrived
at a mighty forest of thorns
at the base of the tower.
Halt...! Who gave you permission
to enter this forbidden land?
Stand aside now, unless you
wish to be cut down on the spot!
Brave talk, traveler,
but first you must defeat
the three swimsuit
sumo musketeers
if you wish to proceed
on your journey!
Prepare... to face the awesome
power of Ganji the mighty!
Can we get by?
Oh, yes, absolutely!
Our goal is within sight...!
There lies the princess!
Now, that's the cue...!
Get going!
What can we do...? Those
thorns are protecting the gate!
They grow back as
fast as we cut them!
What's this...?
The thorns just moved!
Oh... oh, no!
The thorns must be under
some sort of curse as well!
I call on the spirits of good,
to dispel this evil magic!
You rock, Eri!
My princess... I swear
I will soon be at your side!
Yeah, Sawachika!
Hey...!It's just about
time for the bed scene!
Okay! Come on,
guys, give me a hand!
Right!
Uh-oh.
I have to wake up Harima!
Harima!
You've got to get up!
Here goes!
One, two...
At last the six
reached the topmost room
of the tower and
beheld the princess...
She laid before them
unchanged for a century,
resting in her
enchanted slumber,
her beauty undimmed
by the passage of years.
What is Harima doing up there?
Suou was supposed
to be the princess!
Hey... we've been ripped off!
You guys just
don't understand art.
Say what?
It's traditional to
have a woman play
a male role in these plays...
but to turn it around like this
and then not even put the
guy in a female costume...
...well, you don't even see that
kind of avant garde technique
in a Broadway play...
right... partner?
Don't call me partner.
Impressive, 2-C...
looks like we're really going
to have to stay on our toes.
Right, Lara?
Hey, what the heck
happened to Mikoto?!
It's true, we're putting
on a class play today
and I'm Sleeping Beauty!
Right... trying to
trick me again, eh...?
What is it this time, some kinda
fantasy princess coffeehouse?
Huh...? Now what should we do?
You're kidding!
Hey... the director says
to just keep it moving along!
Hmm... The show must go on...
We have no choice!
But... but if we keep going,
that means I'll... have to...
Good luck, prince!
Everybody's watching...
What... do we...
what do we do to waken the
princess from her slumber?
The first thing you must
do is defeat the evil witch
who placed the
princess under this spell!
Wait! Who are you?
We're the spirits of the sword!
No witch in the world
can withstand the power
of this magic sword!
But before we can
give it to you,
you must prove yourselves worthy
of bearing this mighty weapon!
You must pass
the test of wisdom!
A test?
This is your question...
Tell me now, hero, what
has four legs in the morning,
two legs in the afternoon,
and three legs... at night?
I know!
That's such an easy one!
The answer is... a monster!
Uh, no, that's wrong, so I guess
I can't give you the sword.
Well... let's keep on going...!
We can't rely on
that sword anyway!
Heh... I totally didn't see that
twist in the story coming...!
Most excellent...! Bravo!
Who's making all that noise?
Oh, crap! I must've
fallen asleep on the set!
Should I get up, or just...?
No, I've got to!
I'll just tell the
truth and apologize.
Princess...! We have
come here to rescue you!
Okay... I'll keep it
going for you, Tenma!
Here!
And so, in order
to save the princess
from her prison of sleep,
the six brave heroes found
themselves face to face
in pitched battle with
the evil witch's minions!
Look out, I'm coming
to get you! Rawr!
I have been slain!
Prince Tenma!
Get back you, foul beast!
Charge!
Prince Karen, no!
Hurry!
Pumpkin attack!
We must avenge the
loss of Prince Karen!
Right!
Prince Madoka! Prince Ayano!
Her soldiers are
tougher than I expected!
And so the princes fell,
one after another,
until at last only one remained.
Now what...? What happens next?
I have finally come for you...
My beautiful lady,
even in my dreams
I have been in love
with you forever.
I, Prince Eri am
here to rescue you.
Princess... with my kiss,
may your hundred years of
slumber finally come to an...
Uh... I... Prince Eri have
come to rescue you...
With my kiss, may
your hundred years
of slumber finally
come to an end...
Not feelin' it!
You got faced!
Better luck next
time, she-prince!
Come on, Whiskers...! It's not
like I want to do this either!
Princess!
Will you just wake up?!
Sorry...
What are you doing in there?!
Well, I, uh...
I hope you're happy...
Because of you
the play is ruined...
Have fun trying to
get us out of this one.
Someone got out of
the princess's bed!
Oh snap!
Yakumo...?! But how'd she...?
I... that is, I'm...
the evil witch of the tower.
And I just happen to know...
that this person is
extremely tired right now...
I think you should
just let her rest quietly
for the time being...
I'm sorry, but I'm
not going to let anyone
disturb this princess's
slumber, not even you,
Prince Eri,
so just leave her alone.
I'm not following everything,
but I think that
the witch has a point!
Yeah, she makes sense to me,
and she's really cute, too!
What is she doing?
Trying to make
me the villain...?
She's got a lot of nerve!
Enough...! I'm going to
wake up the princess...!
Now stand aside!
Do you think we should let
this go on, Akira...? Huh?
Guess I'm a little late.
You know, I've gotta say, their
acting is really convincing.
The prince or the witch...? Who
will claim the princess's lips?
Okay, how long are
you gonna keep this up?
You know, in the
script the prince
is the one who's
left at the end!
Yes... but I...
All right, that's it!
You're finished now, witch...!
Taste my cold steel
and suffer my wrath...
En garde!
Whoa... looks like that witch
is really in a
lotta trouble now!
This is the end!
She got him that time!
Nice counter!
Oh, that had to hurt!
Uh... are you all right?
Wow! He's coming back
at her even stronger!
Answer me, witch...!
Why do you stand between
me and the princess,
why do you wish to thwart me?
It's because the
princess and I...
have been together
for a hundred years
before you came along,
and I feel I must protect her...
Do you swear to me on your
honor you're telling the truth?
I give you my word,
Prince Eri...
Eri, what are you doing...?
I believe you.
I understand
your point of view...
and I won't
interfere any longer.
But though you've
driven me off for now...
there are still things
to be settled between us...
and I will not soon forget.
Farewell witch!
Uh... But I!
Wait... The prince
gave up...! So what's next?
I don't get it,
did the witch win,
or does something
else happen now?
So is the witch supposed
to kiss the princess?
She has to...! That's what
we came to see, after all!
Kiss her...! Kiss her...!
Kiss her...!
That's what she gets...
It isn't my fault.
Oh no... what should I do?
Wow... Poor girl!
What's Tsukamoto's
little sister gonna do?
What do you think...?
She's gotta give the
people what they want!
But... I can't just...
You're our only hope now...
Please, you must hurry and
wake the princess with a kiss...
Tenma-...! I mean,
uh, Prince Tenma!
Oh no, what are you doing...?!
Now I'll really have
to go through with it!
Okay, Tenma's Sister,
don't do anything hasty!
It's just...
Pretend... Okay, Harima?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, what do
you think you're doing...?
Story or no story,
this is too much!
I'll hide it... with my hat.
Mwah.
Wow... Akira's so bold...
What a smooch!
That was the
real deal...! Scandal!
The beautiful princess
at last was awakened
from a hundred
years of slumber...
And... uh... it says
here she went on to live...
happily ever after
with the lady spy...
All's well that
ends well, I suppose.
Come on, Yakumo...
it's our curtain call!
Go, go, go!
Bravo...! That was
absolutely inspiring...!
The greatest play
I've ever seen in my life!
Hey!
Just because you're
Tenma's little sister
and we all know you,
do you think you can get away
with doing anything you want?
No, I'm sorry...!
I... I was only... trying...
trying to help.
Now, now there... both of
you just take it easy...
That kiss was on the nose,
so it's not like
it really counts.
Whiskers can go screw himself
for all I care, Akira...
That's not even
what this is about.
In any event, you
both did a great job
covering for Mikoto...
okay, girls...?
So let's just...
drop this for now.
That's fine with me...
but this is about her
being too disrespectful...
I just think she needs
to have someone remind her
to stay in her place
every now and again.
You don't understand...
Closing ceremonies might
get a little tense, huh...?
Sucks to be you.
Oh... Harima's kiss...
Do you want it back now?
Uh... no thanks... there's
really no need for that...
Okay...
The school cultural
festival has come
to its conclusion
without incident...
and now we come to
the closing festivities...
Oh, man...
he won't shut up... ah...!
I already got a text message
from that hottie I met...
Hi, Imadori!
Huh?
Oh, Ichijou... Aren't these
closing festivities lame?
Oh... they, uh, might
start to get interesting.
Watch the stage, okay?
Good job, girl, you go!
Uhh... and furthermore...
Huh...? My mic...
Hey, everybody...!
Let's skip the boring speeches
and throw ourselves a
real party tonight...!
The band that stopped the show
at this year's festival
has come by to play!
Are you ready to rock?
Hey...! Look there!
Wow...! A stage jacking!
Heeyy...! Wait a minute!
Here we go!
♪ Tonight has such a
graceful crescent moon, ♪
Man... she's incredible!
Yeah, they're really great!
...every night,
shining brighter
She is like something in
the heart of the moon
So, uh... you
wanna dance with me?
♪ ...in shades of blue ♪
♪ Do you know when
we'll be like a cat, ♪
♪ a wildcat, in a cage? ♪
♪ We cannot miss our time,
so let's find a getaway! ♪
Wow... I never knew she could
look that good... impressive.
Hey...! Sorry...
I was held up...
Oh, right... sorry...
I guess I'm not really
in the mood anymore.
Huh...? What do you mean?
Everyone's really getting
into it, aren't they?
Yeah, it's true.
Just look at all those
bodies writhing around.
Hey, Mikoto!
I suppose you're
looking for Yakumo?
No... I... wanted to say...
sorry about the play.
I don't mind really...
The class and the
audience both had a blast.
Yeah, that's true.
Although... I was looking
forward to playing the princess.
Well then...
let's continue the play.
Huh...? What are you... ah!
Asou...
I suppose Hanai
must've put you up to this.
It's cool...
don't force yourself...
And what makes you think
I need to force anything?
As long as we're
both all dressed up...
how about we just dance?
♪ Do you remember
what you said to me? ♪
Oh, man... check out
the prince and princess!
They look incredible together.
Yakumo!
Hey, Sis...
About the play... sorry...
Don't worry about it,
I'm cool with it.
You might want to say something
to Eri, though... okay?
She'll forget the whole
thing if you apologize.
Excuse me, Eri?
I'm sorry... about what happened
with the play and all.
Oh, that's okay...
I mean what's done is done.
I'm totally over it, so you
don't have to worry about it.
Have to admit... I owe you...
if it hadn't been for you
I would've had to go through
with that whole kissing
scene with Whiskers.
So... wanna dance?
I hate just standing
around like this.
Sure... I'd love
to dance with you.
Hey guys, get a load of that!
Aw... good...!
Looks like they made up!
Hey... I've been
wanting to ask you...
Is it really true
that you and Whiskers
have been seeing each other?
Oh, no... not really...
it's not like that...
Harima asked me...
to help him out on a project
he was working on, that's all...
I'm not seeing him, I swear it.
Hmm... I get it now.
Y'know, I have to say...
you really are a
very good dancer.
I guess... I used to dance a
lot when we lived overseas...
I'm going to speed things
up a bit... Can you keep up?
Uh... sure...
Then here goes!
You're pretty good yourself...
You know you really do
make me feel like a girl.
Somebody... please let me down.
Geez, how can you forget to
bring lunches to a picnic? Huh?
The boys are gonna
make the lunch?
Are you sure about this?
Next time on School Rumble:
"Fight, Hunter! Fight, Eater!
Fight, Part Time Worker!"
Maybe I should make the lunch...