Guess it's my turn now, huh?
Well, I'm sure you guys
probably won't believe me...
But I'm telling the truth.
I saw him once.
Saw who?
Wait, you don't mean...!
Yeah... Him.
The flunk out phantom!
Ryu Nenji...
Yagami High teacher,
now deceased.
Legend has it his ghost
still haunts the campus,
and appears to failing students
to offer them a warning.
Woe to those who do not heed,
for they will surely
be held back,
hence he is known as:
The Flunk Out Phantom!
Hey, did you hear?
Yeah. Who hasn't?
Some guy in 2-C saw him, right?
Poor bastard.
Must really suck being
told you might flunk out.
Until now, I never thought
the Phantom really existed.
Be careful, man. He's real.
Phantom, Schmantom!
I've had perfect
attendance this semester,
and it's all thanks
to you, Tenma!
Comin' to class
every day to see you
has kept me from
skippin' school,
so I've got nothin'
to worry about!
Do I?
No way!
Wait! Where'd you go, old man?!
This has gotta be
a mistake, right?!
Oh... Morning, Harima.
What's going on?
Uh! Yoshida! Good morning!
Looking for something?
Uh, yeah.
An old guy with
white hair and a crew cut.
Did you see him?
Nope, just you and that pole.
And by the way, the
name's Yoshidayama.
Hey, wait...! Old guy?
Crew cut? You saw him,
didn't you...? You did!
The Flunk Out Phan--!
Shut the flunk up!
Why would I see him?!
I've got perfect
attendance, numb nuts!
Sorry! I was just joking!
Geez!
I must be seein' things...
But... Why would
I see somethin' like that?
Screw you, ghost man!
I got perfect attendance!
So back the hell off!
Wait. I forgot!
You can get held back
if you have low test scores.
Man, I am so flunked...
Unless I buckle down
and study harder!
I can't fail no matter what!
I gave up a whole night
of sleep to study,
but if it'll keep the Flunk Out
Phantom away from me,
it was worth it.
Harima! Pass it here!
Oh, hey!
Imadori! Speak to me!
Are you okay?!
You jerk! He has
a sensitive face!
I don't get it...
I studied so hard...
Screw it. You barely slept
and your brain's fried.
Eat something...
you'll feel better.
On second thought...
Maybe I'll skip lunch today.
Hey, are you all right, Harima?
Uh, I'm fine...
Here, you can have
my lunch if you like.
What's the matter?
You look like you just saw a
ghost or something.
Stay back! Get the flunk away
from me!
Ow!
Hey, watch where you're going,
Whiskers!
Moron.
Aw crap! One ghost!
Two ghost! Three ghosts!
What the heck is
his freaking problem?
Beats me, but at
the rate he's running,
I'd say Hershey squirts...
Itoko! Open up! Please!
The Phantom's gonna
flunk me if I stay out here!
What the--?
Harima...? Hold on...
Oh, no...! What if the
Phantom got Itoko, too?!
I'll have to take her out!
Begone...! You spawn of hell!
Don't be rude...
I'm no spawn from hell, idiot...
And remember, at school
you call me Miss Itoko.
Please! You've
gotta help me, Itoko!
Miss Itoko, boy.
Hmm... There may be a
way to ward off Ryu Nenji...
"T"... "E"... Done.
Okay now, keep doing it...
Keep writing vocab
words all over your body,
and the spectre of that old
teacher should stay away...
You must ingrain them on your
body and your mind as well.
There's no more room
left to write on my body.
Wait, there's still
my ears... and my ass.
All right, everybody.
Clear your desks, please.
Time for the exam.
It must've worked!
That flunking Phantom hasn't
reared his ugly head today...!
No way I'll fail!
Harima... Go wash
that off. Right now.
You can either do that or
I'll flunk you for cheating.
No, I'm not cheating,
Mr. Tani, I swear!
Don't make me take
this off, please!
Crap! I'm really gonna fail now.
I'm sorry, Tenma.
Well... Let's get
this over with then.
Hey, wait!
I know the answer to this one!
And this one!
That one, too! Now I get it!
I learned the answers
by writing them on my body!
You knew all along
that I'd learn them
that way, didn't you...?
Itoko... Thank you.
I'll cap your ass.
Yakumo! I'm home!
I'm in here, Sis.
Okay, next...
Who were the Five
Great Emperors of Rome?
Nerva, Trajanus, Hadrianus,
Antoninus Pius, and um...
oh... what's his name...?
That would be Marcus Aurelius.
You know, they say mankind
was at its happiest
during his reign.
But what sucks is when his son
Emperor Commodus came to power,
Rome fell into an
age of internal strife.
You know so much!
You're like so amazing, Tanaka!
No I'm not, I just
like history, that's all.
Damn that Tanaka
and his big brain.
Just 'cause he's so smart, it's
easy for him to get chicks...
Tanaka and Nagayama, huh...?
Have they always
been that close?
They have ever since the culture
festival survival game...
In fact, those two are trying
to get into the same college...
You are planning on applying
to the same private
college that I am, right?
Hey, wait, I thought we
agreed on a state university!
Yeah, we did, but that was
before I was offered
a track scholarship.
What...?! When?!
Why didn't you tell me!
Please don't go off to
college without me, Madoka!
I'm begging you!
Woah, Shigeo!
You're freakin' me out!
The corpses of failed
students shall be my walkway
to the world of passing.
Hey, check it out.
Whoa. Looks like he's
possessed or something.
He's white as a ghost, too.
I wonder what's eating him?
Heh. Harima, you douche.
Looking pretty scared
there, unlike me...
Know why?
'Cause I'm not gonna flunk!
I've got a surefire way
to pass all my exams
and I didn't have to cram
at the last minute like you!
With you held back, the position
of number one senior
badass will be filled by me!
Ryu Nenji! Please!
I'm trying my best!
Everybody's getting so worn out.
Like delicate flowers,
slowly withering away.
Especially Tenma.
How long has she been
all zombiefied like that?
About an hour.
Think she'll snap out of it?
I flunked.
Huh?!
I flunked...
I'm 'onna have to repeat
this year. I just know it.
Oh, But that's not
even the worst part...!
Now, Karasuma will sail onto
the next grade without me!
Why am I just now
realizing this?!
Why do I have to
be such a ding-dong?!
Hey, Tenma,
just take it easy, okay?
I think we've only
got one solution...
An all-night cram
session at Tenma's house.
Good idea, and
it'll give us a chance
to get some
last-minute studying in.
Oh, thank you!
All of you! You're the best!
Hey, hey! Don't cry.
We're all gonna pass
this grade together, 'kay?
Let's do this!
All right, let's start
by getting a feel
for how much you do
know about certain subjects.
Tomorrow's tests are on
Japanese History and Physics...
I'll ask you a few
questions about both of 'em
and you answer, okay?
Oh yeah! Sock 'em to me!
We'll start with
Japanese history,
so what year was the Kamakura
Shogunate first established?
Let's see... I know!
In 1129, they made a big
hunk-a meat that was so fine!
Right?
Maybe we should
try physics first.
The three points of a mechanical
lever are what, what, and what?
Ball point, knife point,
and needle point!
Enjoy being held back.
No, wait! Don't leave! Please!
Tenma,...
I thought you were gonna
study all day yesterday.
What happened?
Well, in the morning, I woke up.
Then I headed right to the
library, ready to study...
But I ended up falling asleep.
Well rested, I went home
and started studying
Japanese history.
But all that talk about shoguns
and samurais reminded me
that the "Three For The Kill!"
Mangoku special
was about to come on.
After watching it, I got
serious about studying...
But before I knew it,
I'd fallen asleep again.
To be honest, I don't know
if I actually did study...
Do you guys know if I did?
No, don't! Wait a second!
You're my best friends!
You can't abandon
me in my time of need!
Please! I need your help!
Somehow the three of us managed
to study without anyone's help.
Why can't you?
I get distracted!
Look, even if you put
your nose to the grindstone,
how are we supposed
to help you learn two
whole courses in one night?
Yeah... That's impossible.
Don't say that!
You've gotta help me!
I think we should
put history off for now
and just focus on physics.
Really? I think she has
a slightly better chance
to squeak by on
history than physics.
Yeah, but we should get the
science in while she's fresh.
What are your thoughts, Akira?
History is a little
easier to cram for...
So it's best we
focus on physics early.
Well, ready to give
it a whirl, Tenma?
Newton's first law:
An object at rest tends...
Guess that pretty much
covers physics, huh?
Dear god, I hope so.
See what can happen
when you apply yourself?
Nice job!
Is she all right?!
She's going into
super cram session shock!
Hurry! We can't let
her swallow her tongue!
Everybody calm down.
Well, it does look
like she's doing better.
Too bad I can't say
the same thing about us.
Shake it off. We still
have history to tackle.
That would be nice, but...
if we cram anything else
in there, she might pop.
That's true.
Wait...
Huh?
I know it's gonna sound a little
crazy, but I know a way...
A method so Tenma can
memorize anything perfectly.
Yeah? What is it?
Come on! Tell us!
She must...
Must what?
She must associate
all the names, dates,
and events to someone she loves!
Then she won't forget!
Oh really?
No, no, no, no, wait!
I'm not sayin' that
I use that technique myself!
I'm just sayin' that--shut up!
Quit looking at me like that!
This is why I can't
tell you two anything!
Mikoto...
All of you... Listen to me...
Thanks to what the three of
you have done for me tonight...
I'm gonna pass my tests! I will!
Atta girl, Tenma!
That's the spirit!
Guess we'd better get
started on history, then.
We're gonna pull an all-nighter!
Put on a pot of coffee, Yakumo!
Sis, you've finally
gotten motivated!
Question one!
Warring States period,
who won the five battles
of Kawanakajima...?
A: Shingen...? Or B: Kenshin?
Goodbye.
I can't have
either Karasuma die!
It's C...! A draw! Huh?
I did it! I'm the master!
Please, be quiet...!
This is a classroom!
At the rate I'm going,
I'll be done in no time!
Huh? Tenma's breezing
through this test.
My surefire way to pass
all my exams is copying off
of smart kids,
so you're it, Tenma.
This is like shooting
fish in a barrel!
Third semester, here I come!
Your test, Yoshidayama.
Right.
Zero points.
What?!
How did this happen?!
Why?! Why?!
One hundred points!
See ya soon, Karasuma!
Ninety-nine. One more left.
Okay... Then I get
to tell the last one.
This happened
three nights ago...
I'd accidentally forgotten
some of my photos in my locker,
so I snuck back into school.
It was as quiet as a mausoleum.
I was halfway to the front
doors when I heard it...
I thought I was
imagining things, but then...
It was dark that night,
but I know what I saw.
It was... It was Yassie.
Hey... You're putting us on.
The Lake Yagami Beast?
Yeah right!
Oh, come on!
Even if there was such a thing,
there's no way it'd be
swimming in our pool!
You think so?
Let's go see, then... Right now.
Just like I thought.
There's nothing here...
Yeah. Gotta admit it was
a good last story, though.
I was actually a
little scared to come.
Me, too.
I guess we should
be getting back, huh?
Uh-huh.
Well, I think we've finally got
that chlorine smell out
of your coat, Pyotr.
I know you wanted to see Yakumo,
but you can't run away
from the zoo like that.
'Kay...! Ya hear?!
Really? That must have
been pretty awkward.
It did freak me out a little.
I was watching the
"Three For The Kill" special,
and all of a sudden, there's
this giraffe sitting next to me!
A giraffe...? Awesome.
Too bad he's not here now...
He could join our pajama party.
I'm so glad exams are over.
Now we can finally sleep.
None of us are
sleeping tonight...
At least, not until Mikoto
finally tells us what happened
What? What do you mean?
Don't play dumb
with us. You know.
The date you made
with Asou during the
basketball sendoff party.
We want all the details,
so don't you dare
leave anything out.
We went shopping.
That's it. End of story.
Uh-uh! That's not
going to work this time!
So spill it!
If you ask me, Miko,
Asou iss totally into you!
Oh yeah!
This conversation is over!
Don't you think
he's a little shy
when it comes to girls, though?
Yeah, but I get the
feeling all it would take
to get Asou out of his shell
would be a girl like Mikoto.
Well, talk!
We want the details!
Kay. The truth is...
The two of us really
did go shopping.
Yeah?! Well, what happened?!
That sucks, they're closed.
Guess I shoulda
called first, huh?
Man, this bites.
I really wanted
to get those shoes.
Why don't we try another store?
Can't. This is the only place
that carries the
brand I wanted...
Oh well, I suppose
I'll just have to come back
another time when
they're open... But hey...
As long as we're out,
why don't we go grab
a burger or something?
Uh... I'm, uh...
not really hungry,
but I could go for some tea.
Lies!
What?!
"Not hungry?" You can normally
put away two Was Burgers.
Oh please...! It's more
like four and a half!
And then there's
always the apple pie.
Well, well...
Asou's not the only
shy person we know...
So what happened next?
We sat down...
Hey, um, do you have
any plans after this?
After this?
No, I mean, not really,
why do you ask?
There's this place
I'd like to swing by
if that's okay with you.
Uh, sure.
That's it.
So you read
about basketball, too?
Yeah. What kinda
stuff do you read about?
Huh?! Me? I, um... I'm into...
Romantic stuff, like true love.
All lies!
No! You didn't actually
tell him that, did you?!
Well, yeah?
True love?!
All you ever read
about is combat sports!
If you read anything else,
you fall asleep in ten minutes.
I do not!
I just like to... rest my eyes.
What happened next?
Where did you lovebirds go?
Not that it's any
of your business...
We went and did karaoke!
Whoa. I never knew
Asou liked to sing.
All right. Your turn, Suou.
Huh?
Uh... Yeah, about that,
I think I only know
like one of these songs.
Which one?
"Butterfly?", huh...?
Never heard of it.
Is it an import?
Uh, yeah! That's it!
Oh, so you like to listen
to international music? Cool.
Yeah, every now and then,
spice things up...
Full of lies!
Hold on.
That's not international!
That's Hiro Chosuke's
entrance music!
The pro wrestler.
I remember I just didn't want
him to know I liked wrestling.
Well, did you sing it
in front of him at least?
No, I couldn't do that, either.
Why must you be so full of lies?
I mean, you sing
like a rock star
when you do
karaoke with us.
Yeah, you even taught me
all those killer dance moves!
Oh, I gotta doo-wah! All night!
If you were in
front of some guy,
you couldn't do
it either, jerk face!
Okay, we're sorry, Miko...
We were just hoping that
you'd have a love connection...
What happened next?
We ended up going to the arcade.
Really? Did you go
in the photo booth?
Hey, let's go over there.
Sure, but why?
They have better
games over there!
What?
You actually pulled him away...?
Why would you do that?
Yeah, especially since you
have the high score on it.
Didn't you say that the next
time you were at the arcade,
you wanted to
beat your own record?
Guys, will you give me a break?
Fine, so then what happened?
Um, let's see...
Asou saw a racing game
he wanted to play.
Wow.
I never knew you
liked videogames.
Surprised, huh?
Yeah, I thought the only thing
you were into was basketball.
There's more to me than that.
Like right now...
I'd much rather
be hanging out here
with you than
playing basketball.
You should've kept your
eyes on the road, you dork.
Can you do better,
Miss Backseat Driver?
Well, you're about to
find out, future loser.
I was thinking that maybe
after graduation, I'd buy a car.
Really?
Yeah.
That way I could travel around
whenever I wanted, y'know?
Go see places
I've never seen before.
You're about to see
another wreck happen
if you don't pay more attention.
Come on... Gimme a break,
Mikoto. It's just...
Huh?
It's just weird that graduation
is a little more than
a year from now...
You and me... Everybody else.
What's going to happen to us?
And...?!
Yeah, what happened next?
Did you lose on purpose so Asou
wouldn't know how good you are?
Uh, well actually...
I beat him. And I set
a new speed record.
All right!
I'm sorry, sir, but could
you leave? We're closing.
Cheers, Tenma! Happy Birthday!
Your loyal subjects await
your orders, Queen Tenma!
Next time, on School Rumble
Second Semester:
"At Elcado, In America,
With America!" Oh, me?
I'm emceeing this event.