Yo, Karasuma!
I hope you enjoyed
Tenma's party...
Heard it was a real
jamboree. But anyway...
Don't worry.
I was able to take care of
the comic all by my lonesome.
No need to thank me... See ya!
And by take care of it I mean...
I just turned in
my own drawings.
God, I hope this turns out okay!
What...?! It...
it isn't possible!
Remember how I messed
up Karasuma's pages
and switched 'em with mine?
Take a look.
For some reason they went
ahead and ran my pages...
but put my penname
on it instead!
Wow! You're going to
Taiwan for winter break?!
You suck! I'll be playing
bingo with my Grandma.
Hey... did you see
this new comic...?
Weak art but... the story...
Lemme see, lemme see...
Oh, I read that!
It's sort of a-typical
for a comic, huh?
Hario Harima, right?
I read that too.
The author is standing
right next to ya...!
And what do you mean
"weak art", Suou?
I don't know...
I think the whole
story is kinda stupid.
He totally oversimplifies love.
Everybody's a critic!
Yeah, but... I like
that it's so simple...
I can't follow those
complicated epics.
Mmhm-mmhm...
clearly, Suou is a connoisseur.
When I'm famous
I'll give you my autograph.
Gimme a break, a boy and a girl
don't just suddenly fall in love
and move in together
like that! Please!
They think just because
it's a comic book
they can get away
with anything...!
I mean seriously,
it's so insulting!
Rich Girl, you
empty shell of a woman.
Don't you know what
love is?! I pity you.
And what's your opinion, Tenma?
Whoa! That's a good question!
Takano, when I'm famous
I'll give you two autographs!
You wanna know what I think?
Yeah.
Okay... I'm ready...
I can handle this...
Plunge the blade of
criticism into my heart!
I guess it was okay...
I thought it was kind
of neat that it was
so dreamy and romantic.
It makes me wish something
like that would happen to me!
Yes!! I'm so lucky to be
the author...! I knew it!
I knew you'd love it, Tenma!
All right!!!
Congratulations!
That was a very entertaining
story, Tazawa...!
The feedback we've gotten
from the readers has
been really positive...!
Yes...! I'll work even harder...
and make Tenma even happier!
Hey!
Who's that girl behind you?
I'm his assistant, sir.
Yakumo Tsukamoto.
She helped with the layout,
so I brought her along...
is that okay?
I guess...
Hey, Chief... this is Tazawa.
Actually, my... my... my name--
Never mind, it's cool...
Wait! Hold on...!
What're you doing?
Don't get too close!
So... you're the head editor?
Do you enjoy scaring
new comic book artists,
or is that just
part of your job?
Is she out of her mind?
She'll get herself killed!
You're the first
person I've ever seen
who didn't fall to
the ground in terror.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, miss.
It's a pleasure to meet you too.
That's the first time the
boss has smiled in 20 years!
No, thirty!
So, I understand
you know the captain
of The Cry of the
Demon... don't you?
Um... while I... was...
I was on that ship...
And the captain gave me
this pen--don't hurt me!
Draw me a hundred and
twenty pages by next week.
This is bad! This is really bad!
A hundred and twenty pages?!
So much for enjoying
my winter break!
I'll have to lock myself up in
my room and work the whole time!
Hey, Itoko, I'm home!
Sheesh...! Well, at least
I'll be able to work in peace,
so that's all right.
You're kidding, she locked
the door when she left!
Calm down, Harima, all you
have to do is use your key.
Don't have it.
What?
I'm sorry, Sis.
Just for a while,
during the break.
I told Harima it would be all
right if he stayed here with us.
I'm really sorry, Sis...
it's just for a while,
during the winter break.
I told Harima it would be
all right if he stayed here.
Rowf!
Talk about a weird dream!
All of a sudden
I'm staying at Tenma's house?
I knew it was too good
to be true! Dammit!
But when did the dream
start...? Itoko's trip...?
The editor in chief?
What if I just dreamed that they
published my comic
instead of Karasuma's?
Where am I?
Hey, Harima...! Are you up yet?
It's not a dream!
Oh, Harima...?
Is this enough, or would
you like a bigger bowl?
You're so lucky, Yakumo's
cooking is the best ever!
Better dig in
before I eat it all!
Aw yeah! Me so
hungry for miso soup!
C'mon, Harima!
What's wrong? Dig in!
Okay...
Nope. It's no dream, it's real.
Tenma and me,
under the same roof.
Even better, at the same table!
Uh, let's see, soy sauce ...
Here.
This one's the soy sauce.
The little round headed guy.
Oh.
Don't forget, if there's
anything you need
or want, you just ask, okay?
I never thought
I could be this happy!
The road to the top is truly
paved in the sweetness of life!
Hey, can I lend a hand?
Sure, if you want...
Would you mind putting
those dry dishes up
on the first shelf of
the cupboard for me?
No, not at all.
Uh, is this where
they're supposed to go?
Yes, thank you, that's perfect!
It's sure handy to have
a nice tall guy around
to reach the high places.
Yeah... I'm good at bein' tall.
Holy crap...!
It's almost like we're newlyweds
in our first house together!
Tenma, I swear, as of today...
no, as of this moment
I am your servant!!
Hey... Harima?
Huh?
Laundry's up next?
Don't worry about it,
I'll do it.
It's awfully nice
of you to offer,
but what about your manuscript?
...but what about
your manuscript?
...but what about your
manuscript?
Crap, I forgot all about it!
I've got a hundred
and twenty pages
of heartbreaking
genius to create!!
Little Kuta continues to grow,
and is currently
three meters tall.
Whoa...! Holy snap!
That's Panda Power.
I can't believe he grew so much.
Hm? Is everything okay, Harima?
Oh, yeah, I was just, you know,
lookin' for somethin' to drink.
Oh...! I'm sorry, how
thoughtless of me!
No, it's cool! I can get it
if you tell me where it is.
Don't be silly!
You're our honored guest, aren't
you...? Is coffee all right?
Uh... okay.
If you'd like another
cup, just say so!
Uh... sure... thanks!
Good luck in there, Harima...
though I don't really
know what you're doing.
I have to admit...
I was a little surprised
when you brought
Harima here yesterday.
I'm really sorry
for the trouble, Sis.
Well, what could you do?
Besides, Yakumo, you hardly
ever ask me for anything.
If you wanna have a
guest stay over here...
then your Big Sister
is no problemo!
Thanks, Tenma.
Stupid. Stupid! Stupid!!
That's so lame.
Did Harima really say
he was gonna skip lunch?
Yeah... He said he needed
to stay focused right now.
Wait a minute, focused?
Oh, right, on that whole project
thing I know nothing about.
Harima's not even gonna
have a snack with us?
I'd better go see
how he's doing.
Way to go, future housewife!
Come on, Sis,
it's not like that!
Still it does feel
a little strange...
Right... Iori?
Hello, Harima?
I'm coming in now, all right?
You okay...? Is the
manuscript going well?
He looks like Dad...
Would you like to take a
little break for a while?
I can't!!
The genius... It won't flow!
I know... the scene
I wanna draw...
but for some reason I just
can't get the composition right!
Uh, if you like,
I could pose for you,
if you think that would help.
You mean it...? You'd do that?
Yeah... of course.
It's estimated that
Little Kuta grows as much as
ten centimeters every day.
That's too much...
I need to start getting
dinner ready soon...
but I think I'm really helping
Harima make some progress...
so... maybe just
a little longer.
We've been told by his
keeper that little Kuta
ate a bucket of
seventy-seven fish today...
Let's just hope his taste
for flesh doesn't
cross over into humans.
That's right, eat some more...
Hey! Whatsit?!
Thanks a lot, Tenma's Sister...!
Uh, oh... no ink.
Would you like me
to go buy some?
Are you sure it's no trouble?
No, I have to go out anyway.
If it's no big deal,
then, thanks.
Of course.
Oh, man, I'm so hungry I think
my freakin' stomach's
eating itself... what the...?
Yakumo, you tryin' to starve me?
Sorry, Sis... I'm a little
late with dinner tonight.
Oh, that's okay!
I know how it is with you
newlyweds! All lovey-dovey!
I told you it's not like that!
So cold... what a chilly
night... it's really winter now.
I'm back!
I know I'm awfully late...
You're kidding! Really?
You're so funny, Harima...!
Why don't you
just join our family?
Really?!
You could be our little brother!
Or distant cousin!
Or, whatever...
But just remember, the remote
control is mine pretty much
whenever I want, got it, Kenji?
She called me Kenji!
He looks so happy...
Hey, Yakumo, you're back!
Well then...
I'll get out of your way
so you can get back to it...
Of course I still
don't have any idea
what it is that you're doing...
Um... here's your ink.
Oh...! Uh, thanks a lot!
That's all right,
it's no big deal...
Man, I feel great!
It's like... I have
all this motivation...!
I'll draw a hundred and
twenty pages, no sweat!
Hell, I'll draw a
hundred and fifty!
To the fields of glory!!
Excuse me, Miss.
I was wondering if you'd
made your decision yet.
Are you kidding?
It's not like it's really
my decision, now, is it?
Mother wants me to do this.
I have no choice.
Not that it matters.
No one will even
notice I'm gone.
I wish there was some other way
I could help Harima,
if only just a little.
Iori, what are you
playing with...? A flyer?
Comic book editors' school?
Thank you very much for
coming here today, everybody.
Here we go...
Allow me to introduce
today's speaker...
a former fisherman and
currently editor in chief
for Weekly Shonen
Zinegama... Mr. Gotou!!
You must draw every
moment of the day!
I don't care if
you're hospitalized
or if your life is
falling apart! Draw!!
So you're back again, are ya?
Whadda ya say?
Once you get out of school,
how about joining
our editorial staff?
I can't believe it.
He gave me a
certification badge.
But I didn't really
understand his lecture...
Harima and Yakumo
are so cute together
it just makes me wanna
punch somebody in the face!
Oh, man, love is the
greatest thing ever!
Maybe I ought to do a
little bit of research
to make sure he's
good enough for her!
With my help, Yakumo's
love life is gonna shine!
Okay.
Since my love life's a
little less than perfect,
I'll ask everyone else what
they think makes a good man.
All right, that's sent off.
Now!
I can't trust that
he'll be honest,
not if he knows that it's me.
I need a disguise!
Whoa, that was quick!
Another one?
Man, I'm blowin' up over here!
Excuse me, Harima?
C'mon, Sis, it's not like that!
Yes! Perfect!
Iori, come here!
Are you feeling okay, Tenma?
No, no, no...!
Hmph. I'm Yakumo.
Huh?!
I'll start with Eri's text.
A man should be able
to see the subtle changes
in a woman... or else forget it!
Roger!
Hey Harima!
I mean, excuse me,
but can I ask you a question?
Uh... sure, I suppose...
Do you think there's anything
different about me today?
Uh, yeah, I'll say...
What's with the hair
and the clothes?
Yes! First checkpoint clear!
Okay, what's next?
Lemme see...
I guess I'd be happy if he ate
whatever I prepared for him
without complaining about it.
Have I mentioned how
uncomfortable these things are?
I can believe that.
Probably give
you a backache too.
Okay! Here's Yakumo's curry...
Oww! Let's spice it up!
We'll see if he can stand this!
Here you go, Harima!
Now I wanna see
you clean your plate!
Tenma's cooking!
This could be intense,
but I'll do it!
Wait... that's pretty good!
Oh, my gosh!
The spiciness doesn't
bother him...! He loves it!
And he ate the whole thing!
Second checkpoint, clear!
And next...
Gosh... this question
is so sudden...
I guess what I'd
like most is a man
who'd be able to protect me
in a pinch... yeah, that's it!
That's a good one...
You're a genius, Carolyn!
Now... what to do...
What the heck is up
with Tenma today?
Could it be?
Now that I think of it, I've
been so wrapped up in my work,
the only person I've spoken
to is her little sister!
So Tenma dressed up like Yakumo
so I'd pay attention to her!
How could I let
it come to this?!
Okay, from now on my whole body
and soul are focused on her!
Ahh! Harima!
What is it?!
I'm here for you, baby!
Tell me what to do!!
There's a cockroach, get it!
Don't worry, I'm all over it...
No, I just can't
hit the nice kitty...
Oh, no!
Has Harima failed
the third checkpoint?
Wait a sec, Carolyn's email
has another part to it!
On the other hand, I don't
think I'd want someone
who solved all his
problems with brute force...
I'd like someone who was
kind as well as strong.
It's a complete turnabout...!
Third checkpoint clear!
Okay, it's time
for Megumi's text!
If he looks hot,
that's all that matters.
Oh, Harima!
Oh, god, what is it this time?
Gimmie!
Oh, wow! You're actually--
Hold on.
There's something strangely
familiar about your face.
Give those back!
Hey now, come on!
Lemme have another look!
Sorry, it's too bright
in here, I need my shades!
Man, that was close!
If she remembered who I was
she'd never speak to me again!
Well, if he never
takes his sunglasses off,
it doesn't really matter!
We'll just call that one a pass!
Moving on to Akira!
Money.
Lend me some money!
Sure!
Take it all!
Twelve yen?
It's more than I have... Pass!
You're the perfect man!
The one I've been waiting for!
At last!
You and I can finally...
You and Yakumo will
live happily ever after!
Her big sister is satisfied!
Now make sure you
don't take things too fast
when you're dating!
Shaka-boom!
Hello? Anyone home?
Welcome back, you lucky girl!
Oh no... Tenma still thinks
I'm seeing her little sister...
I've gotta stop this...!
I've gotta spell things out for
her or we'll never get together!
Tonight... I'll tell
her everything!
There's no mistakin' that hair.
Listen... I'm sorry to
bother you so late...
I wanted to do this sooner,
but I wasn't brave enough...
So tonight I'm just
gonna plunge right in...
I... I've always
wanted to tell you, I...
I love you my darling!!!
Iori...?! Then this must
be Tenma's Sister's room!
Little Kuta has
eaten a lot today, too,
and it looks like
he's still growing!
I forbid you to go near Yakumo!
Next time on School Rumble!
"I Don't Want to
Be Tied to Anyone;
I Don't Want to Go to
School or Home Anymore;
Under the Dark Veil of Night."
Harima, you're just
still an ape, aren't you?