Okay... quiet!!
We're the only class
that hasn't decided
on a culture festival program!
Come on, we have to
make our decision by today,
but you guys are
such slackers...!
How did I get stuck
having to handle you
big bunch of idiots
all by myself?
Please, Mai... take it easy.
Obviously, we have to do a play.
I mean, come on, what else would
you do for a culture festival?
Whoa, Imadori is serious!
Yes, yes, yes! Sleeping Beauty!
It just so happens
I've written a script.
What?
Let me see that!
Lame!
You know nothing about art!
I don't know, I think the coffee
shop would be a good idea.
I really like the maid
outfits... they're cool.
Yeah... I'd look
great in one of those!
What are you all
looking at me for?
I would never wear
a maid costume.
If it were left up to me...
I'd say we should all do a play.
No, the coffee shop's better!
Oh, yeah...
I'm totally into the idea
of the girls in maid outfits.
Maid outfits?
The coffee shop has my vote too!
Coffee shop... Maid outfits...
So what do you think,
you guys into it?
Oh hell yeah! You got my vote!
I'm good either way.
Coffee shop!
Coffee shop all the way!
I want Sleeping Beauty!
Yay! Yay!
Dude, the coffee shop is better!
Maid outfits! Hello!
Nurse uniforms
would be good too.
But dude Sawachika would
be smokin' as the
princess in the play!
Instead of a guy,
have Mikoto be prince. Hot!
Come on, guys, let's
think about this seriously!
How can I clear up this
misunderstanding with Tenma?
There's nothing between
her sister and me!
Aww, for the love of Mike!
Enough yakking,
we'll decide between the play
and the shop by majority vote!
Not so fast!
We don't want the
play or the coffee shop!
The three of us want
swimsuit sumo wrestling!
Huh...? But I didn't say...
The girls of 2-C all change
into swimsuits and battle!
School swimsuits
would be fine...
But bikinis or thongs
would be totally... sweet!
You know, guys, I really didn't
want to in the first place.
Great, so now we have a tie...!
And what's more,
not everyone voted!
Okay, at this rate
it's gonna take,
like, forever to settle this.
It would help if our
class coordinator
would snap out of it.
Why, why, why, why, why,
why, why, why, why, why...
I think I know
how to revive them.
For real...? Do you have a plan?
Of course, don't I always?
Hey, Harima...
Do you mind?
I've written a play.
I'd like your opinion.
Looks great...
Look closer.
Kenji Harima...
three votes for the play!
Now there's a three vote margin!
That settles it!
No fair!
Amazing! I didn't know
Harima had three votes!
If the coffee shop wins,
the tea club will offer its
full cooperation, naturally.
And that includes Yakumo.
Haruki Hanai...
five votes for the coffee shop!
He said five?
How is that even possible!
It's another surprise reversal!
Akira, that's amazing...
You know, you really have a
talent for this sort of stuff.
It's whatev.
What the hell?
Since when do you get
five votes, you bastard?
Are you trying to make
a joke out of democracy?
What does a delinquent like
you know about democracy?
I know plenty.
You know nothing! Nothing I say!
But it's still a tie,
you guys...!
You each only get one vote!
I don't think they're listening.
If you have a moment...?
I have a pretty awesome idea.
It's all yours... anything...!
Let's settle it with a game.
Game? You're nuts.
It's gonna take a
lot more than a game
to settle things
between the two of us!
Why don't you go play
with your tea set, girlie?
A survival game.
What's she talking about?
A survival game?
Oh man, that's totally hot.
Sleeping Beauty!
One, two!
Three, four!
I don't care if I get paid!
I don't care if I get paid!!
Give me figures,
a nurse and a maid!
a nurse and a maid!!
I don't care what you assume!
I don't care what you assume!!
I like a girl in a hot costume!
I like a girl in a hot costume!!
Okay guys, let's do
this for the coffee shop.
Takano here...
Everything is ready...
Neither the Coffee Shop Team
or the Play Team are
missing any players...
I congratulate everyone
for having the courage
to participate,
even at such a late hour.
Sir! Yes, sir!
The rules are as
laid out earlier...
Until one team
takes the other's flag,
you are to continue
fighting each other
until the bitter end...
No areas are off-limits...
You may set up any
barricades you want...
Ten minutes from now...
I will sound the
chime to begin battle...
Good luck... all of you.
Sir! Yes, sir!
Attention, everybody...!
Here's our strategy!
Harima and Sawachika are,
without a doubt, the
play team's main force.
We're on the fourth floor,
in classroom 3-F...
and the play team's
on the second floor,
in classroom 1-A...
I don't know where the enemy's
main force will move...
...but we'll concentrate most
of our efforts to defense,
stationed near the staircases...
Our offensive force will consist
only of our most
skilled warriors.
What's the deal with the stairs?
It's much easier to for us
to attack vertically, that way.
They're narrow, difficult for
the enemy to maneuver in,
and simpler to defend.
The horizontal plane
presents much more
of a challenge since it
allows more people through.
Now, the girls will be
in charge of defense...
while the men will be
in charge of offense...
Hey, Madoka!
Shigeo!
Isn't coming here
against the rules?
Why did you go over to
the coffee shop side...?
I thought you were
all for the play!
I don't have to be with
you on everything, Shigeo.
But... Madoka...
I'm sorry but...
Listen... the
next time I see you
I won't hesitate to shoot you.
What? Hey...
Bye-bye!
We'll engage the
enemy on the fourth floor
and advance swiftly,
taking control
of the east stairwell
as quickly as possible!
Oh... I get it.
Hey, that's not a bad strategy.
Right then, let's move out.
Yeah!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Got 'em pretty
stirred up, haven't you?
Move it, we have to get
control of the east stairwell
before the play team can
establish a position there!
All right, it looks like
we're the first ones here!
We have it occupied!
Good work, team, we...
Someone's there...?!
They're fast...
I have to keep
my aim... Harima?!
Dodge...!
But there's no time...!
Jump!
You okay?
Quick, we'll take
cover in the classroom!
Just what the hell is going on
here...?
It seems like the
entire play team
is coming down
on us all of a sudden!
Where are our guys?
Probably safe...
I saw them take cover
in the other classrooms.
That means it's just
you and me soldier...
all alone on the front
lines... This'll be tough.
They're sure laying down...
a lotta fire...
that seems weird.
Wait a minute...
It could be... a trap.
Huh?
While they've got
us pinned down here,
their main force could be moving
this way classroom by classroom,
which means we might be screwed.
Look like it's
all clear... let's go.
They'll never guess
there's a third force
about to move against them...
The element of surprise gives
us the edge in this battle...
The Swimsuit Sumo Wrestling Team
is sure to emerge victorious!
Are you really positive?
Let's roll...
Hey... Nishimoto...
I think I'm stuck.
Hurry it up...
We have to be as stealthy
as ninjas, so be quiet!
Yup. Definitely stuck.
Screw him... Let's go...
Uh... 'kay.
What's that?
Harima...! It looks
like he showed up!
It's a good thing we decided
to take cover in the
back of the classroom!
My eyes...! I can't see!
We're through!
Not on my watch!
Hanai...! You saved us...!
You made it through that
hail of bullets to get here!
Nice sunglasses, by the way.
We must fall back!
We're giving up
this ground? Why?
Because of the enemy's strategy.
I believe they're
trying to distract us...
and keep us occupied
here on the 4th floor.
What are you saying?
At first it seems like
they're attacking in earnest,
but they withdraw too easily,
just like Harima did.
It's a fake...
it's just a diversion...
they're attacking the
2nd floor right now...
No casualties... not yet anyway.
So why don't we
counterattack instead?
If we did... our position
would be compromised.
Retreat, quickly...!
Asou and the other guy, move it!
What do you mean,
"the other guy"?
Kenji Harima... it has
to be me who takes you on.
We don't have to worry,
Asou and the other guy
should be here
any minute now, 'kay!
That's great...!
But they better hurry!
No kidding, we're out of ammo!
We've gotta hang on
until they get here!
I'm sorry...
My last club meeting
ran a little late!
Oh, that's okay!
At last our
songbird has arrived!
How were things going
at the main building...?
Aren't they playing that...
game thingy?
Oh, right... beats me, I didn't
go to the main building.
Well... who cares about them...
Are you ready
to start practicing?
♪ Tonight, has such a
graceful crescent moon ♪
♪ Reborn every day, every
night, shining brighter ♪
♪ She is like something
in the heart of the moon ♪
♪ Reborn every day, every
night, in shades of blue ♪
♪ Do you know when
we'll be like a cat, ♪
♪ a wildcat, in a cage? ♪
♪ We cannot miss our time,
so let's find a getaway... ♪
♪ Do you remember
what you said to me? ♪
♪ It's been ringing
in my heart. ♪
♪ You should have known that
what your words can do to me ♪
We're here to lend
you guys a hand!
Oh, hey there, Asou...!
Other guy.
Hey, what's with this
other guy business?
You're gonna be alright...
Just leave it to us.
Thanks, Asou.
♪ Oh, I have to
say you're beautiful ♪
Sure is quiet on
the 3rd floor...
Hold it right there!
Madoka, hey.
Oh, hello.
Man, am I glad to
see that it's you...
You know you really
need to be more careful...
if my teammates find you,
they're gonna let you have it!
You're on the play team too.
Are you gonna let me
have it...? Are you?
What are you talking about...?
There's no way that
would I shoot you!
You're just gonna let me go?
Of course... What's
the point of us fighting?
We're in love, right?
Then thank you... Shigeo.
You better get going...
let's grab a bite
later on, okay?
Ma... Madoka?
I'm sorry, but I...
I have to try on that maid
outfit, no matter what.
♪ Oh, I have to
say you're beautiful ♪
♪ It's hard to deny it. ♪
♪ Your smile ♪
Shigeo...
♪ You know you made
me feel like a girl ♪
♪ You know I've
never felt like a girl ♪
♪ You know you've shown
me a different way to be ♪
♪ So now it seems
like I'm falling... ♪
This is why...
This is why I said we should
decide by majority vote!
Why...? Why did it
have to go this far?
What...? We can't appear
at the culture festival?
What are you talking about?
That's so lame!
Why not?
It says our teacher didn't draw
the right number for the stage.
Damn...
Well, it looks like
there's nothing
we can do
about it now...
This sucks, royally.
Oh, man... and after we worked
our tails off and like
everything!
But... there's nowhere
else we can perform.
Looks like we'll
just have to give it up.
Not if we join in the
survival game, we won't.
If we win the game,
we'll get the classroom...
We'll just jump in
the middle of the fight
and take them all out.
Asou and the other guys helping
really turned this
situation around!
If Hanai can get
control of the 4th floor,
we might have a chance
of winning this thing.
Mina!
Asou...! Enemy to the
rear...! We've lost two!
What the...?
Do something quick or we're
gonna be ambushed by the enemy!
How the hell did the
enemy get behind us?
Hey... there... what was that?!
I know that hairstyle!
Sawachika!
Stop her...!
She's after our flag!
What have we here?
Now that seems unfair...
The balance of power
is shifting too much.
I really shouldn't get involved
in a children's quarrel,
but on the other hand...
Suga! Get back here fast!
They're attacking like crazy!
We can't hold them
off by ourselves!
I managed to get a
transmitter on Sawachika!
You've got to use your computer
to track her location for us!
We'll come back for you
after we've finished her off!
Uh... there she is...!
She's running past 1-F!
Copy that!
Man... this is
looking pretty bad...
they just seem
to keep on coming!
I'm sure Hanai
will be here soon...
Just hang on!
If we could just move the
barricade forward a little,
we might be able to
hold them off long enough
for Hanai to get here...
Make the coffee shop a good one.
Huh?
Misawa!!
Nice one, Misawa!
Misawa...! No...
Please, just get up!
Noooooooo!!!
That Sawachika is
pretty hardcore, huh?
Oh no...! Why?!
Now we've got her...
We should be able to
run her down pretty quick.
That's strange...
She's showing
herself too much...
I wonder...
Could this be a trap?
She's gone into 2-C!
Right... we end it here.
You fell for the
dummy, sweetheart!
Now here's a taste of
the real deal, Sawachika!
Huh...? What?
Nagayama...! You said
room 2-C, didn't you?
What the hell is going on?
Something's not right, check
her location for us again!
Look, I already checked it!
I'm telling you, she's in 2-C!
And I'm telling you we're
in 2-C and she's not here.
Are you sure she hasn't
changed position?
Yes I'm sure!
She's there,
I'm looking at it right now!
For amateurs...
you did very well.
And now allow me
to give you... your reward.
Gross.
Did you enjoy watching
Miss Eri's adventures?
Next time I believe her exploits
will be even more exciting.
What? Don't be silly.
I'm just a humble butler.
I couldn't possibly do that.