Next!
Right!
What in the world is happening?
Our peaceful neighborhood
is being taken over
by a basketball gang!
Next!
Right!
Is she gonna be okay?
Don't worry, you're
going to be just fine.
Oh wow, they helped her!
Would ya look at that?
They're friendly!
Uh... supper is
ready, everyone...
so, uh, help yourselves!
Yes!
Another bowl!
Uh... right...
Looks like Tawaraya's
still off her game, huh?
The harder she tries,
the worse her swing gets.
Hey, Asou...
can you do
something to help her?
I don't want to make
things any worse...
Wait... did you say "swing"?
We're running out of time,
you've got to do
something with her.
Try changing up the angle
on your hands each time,
'til you get your
feel for it back.
Uh, yeah okay.
Hey, relax your shoulders
a little, you're too tense.
Okay!
Uh, Ms. Tae... you know she's...
Relax, I've got this covered.
Honestly, I don't know much
about injuries or illness...
...but when it comes
to love, the doctor is in,
and the prescription in
this case is shock therapy!
Yeah, are you sure
that's gonna work?
Totally!
Hey, they've stopped practicing!
I'm sorry... I'm totally
worthless at this.
No... it's my fault,
I'm a bad coach--
No, don't say that, you're
the best coach I've ever had...
It's my fault, I don't
have what it takes anymore!
'S not true...
The boys can't
even keep up with her!
Incredible...
She's taken everything
Asou has taught her
and put it into practice!
Satsuki! Wait!
Satsuki...! It's not
lunch time yet!
Yeah, your little prescription
is sooo not working
Oh, dear... I don't understand.
Hey, Asou...
you should go after her.
No... she wouldn't
want to see me...
It's better if you go.
Wow, can we say "clueless?"
Eat!
Lara!
It's from my lunch,
just try it... it's good!
No thanks...
I'm not really all that
hungry at the moment, sorry.
You're kidding? Not hungry?!
So what's eating you then?
Everything okay with your dad?
Yeah, things with
Dad are cool...
I'm living with him right now...
but I've got something more
important on my mind.
More important than
food or your family?
How is that possible?
Are you gonna die?
Come on, just tell me!
If there's anything you need,
you can count on me!
Hello?
Uh, Tawaraya...? This is Asou...
Could you come to
the gym right away?
We, uh... We need to talk.
Look... this has really
been bothering me...
I think we need to
get it out in the open
or things'll just
get more tense.
I want you to be
totally honest with me.
I need to know
how you feel about me.
What do you mean...?
Are you... you don't... what?!
If you don't like me, I
completely understand how you...
It's not like that at all!
You see...
I, uh... I love you,
Asou, I love you!
Huh?
Oh...! Uh... actually, I was
asking how you felt about me
as a coach... not... that.
Stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid, stupiiid!
Uh... hey!
Looks like Satsuki's not coming.
I can't believe it, she's
never missed practice before.
Asou... you called her
after practice yesterday,
did anything happen?
Nothing.
Come on, Satsuki, you've got
to pull yourself out of this!
They say a lioness
raises her cubs
by throwing them
into a bottomless pit.
They fall down... and down...
and then they grow
strong by climbing out!
All right, people,
don't just stand around!
We have a practice game against
the first year boys today!
Right!
First point's up!
Okay, what's up with the
random guy on the court?!
Damn... he's fast!!
That's cool and all,
but who the hell are you?
Pretty shabby defense,
I guess you haven't learned
that you should never drop
your guard even for a moment.
What a douche bag!
What are you doing
here all of a sudden?
Hey, clear the court, you guys,
we have a practice game with...
The first years?
If you're talking about
this collection of losers,
I'm afraid they're
all played out!
Those has-beens didn't even
make a good warm up for us!
Whoa... You got
uniforms and everything!
So, what do you guys want?
We're here to
find out if you have
what it takes to
play basketball...
to see if you have
the will to fight!
Basketball is about strength.
If you're gonna be all
pansy-core about it,
then you don't even
deserve to be on the court.
The time has now
come to find out
which team will reign supreme!
Now, are you ready
to take us on...
to face us like
the men we all are?
This is girl's basketball,
you idiot.
Ms. Tae, would you please
say something to them?
Oh, I'll say something to them.
We... accept your
challenge... Outlaws...!
Now come on, let's fight
them... with all we've got!
Where'd that staff come from?
Why are you on
their team, Tenma?
I thought we were friends!
Sorry, Mikoto, but I'm afraid
we're enemies right now.
Okay then...
if they want a fight,
let's give 'em a fight!
Come on, Lara, use your head,
don't let them provoke you!
What have we been practicing
for all this time anyway...?
For status...? For the
fame...? Of course not!
It's so we can win, right?!
Hey, that's true!
Yeah, like, duh,
let's freakin' do this!
Why not...?
Let's give it a shot!
Aaaalright, let's go...!
Are you guys ready?
It's mine!
Look out, little ladies,
here I come!
Wow, he's really fast!
Way to go, Imadori!
I am a basketball god! And
it's all thanks to the shoes!
I can do anything when
I'm wearing these babies!
I'm borrowing these!
Hey, they fit perfectly!
Let's just stay cool!
We'll take it back!
You need to pace yourself...!
Be careful, Miko!
Sagano!
Woo hoo, Harima,
that was totally awesome!
Oh no... What in the
world am I gonna do?
This way... pass it to me, sis!
Take it!
Don't worry, I've got it
covered, Tenma's Sister!
I-I'm sorry, Sis, he was
open and you were covered!
Oh, now I understand,
you were faking them out...!
Baby sister, you
are simply brilliant!
Gotcha!
Since when did Imadori
get good at basketball?
And Harima?
That came outta nowhere!
Without Satsuki, we can't
get our hands on the ball!
This is so lame.
We need her now more than ever!
Where the heck is she?
Lara... you're not wearing
my shoes out... are you?
Calmate!
I can't take it anymore!
I have to go!
Wait a minute, Lara,
where do you think
you're going, come back!
Great, Now what do we do... huh?
Looks like it's my turn
to step in, doesn't it?
Uhhhh...
Ichijou, you're
doing it again...!
Suou, you're telegraphing every
time you come in from the right!
What's the deal, everyone is
like, sucking hardcore today!
The deal is, we need you.
Lara, what are you doing!
Listen Satsuki... we're
a bunch of amateurs.
Having a pro
like you on our side
is what made a team out of us.
But I...
I know.
You've got love trouble... so
you can't focus on basketball...
I am right, no?
Yes. It is tough...
But there is an old saying
I think you need to remember.
Old saying?
Just listen to me right now!
It's "that is that...
but this is this!"
This is something that
you have to do now...!
Everyone is waiting for you!
Also...
I'm waiting for you
and I believe in you...!
Don't you dare forget that!
You can do it, Satsuki!
Substitution!
'Bout time girl!
I was startin' to sweat!
Thank goodness!
I'm sorry.
I did the best I could.
But Suga says I have
five personal balls
and I'm out for the game,
and that I was a traveler too,
or something like that.
Uh... personal fouls...
Okay, girls, let's do this...!
We're gonna win this
game no matter what!
Yeah!!
Oh, Satsuki...
you've taken another
big step toward adulthood...
It's so beautiful!
Another three
pointer from Tawaraya!
That's her seventh one!
How'd you get her to come back?
Just a little girl
to girl chat...
Now let's worry about
winning this game...
Satsuki is back, and also...
I have these kick-ass shoes!
You're back on your game!
Thanks...! Now...
Let's show these
jerks we're hardcore!
Heads up, Lara!
Ugh... what are you
doing to my shoes?!
Oh...! Foiled again!
Hey...! This is
where you get off!
Sorry for the slip-up!
No sweat,
don't worry about it...!
You and I are homies, right?
Wow, you're so nice!
Is everyone in
Class 2-D like you?
Yeah! There not all
as cool as me, though.
Wow! Maybe I should move to 2-D!
Hey! I'm cool too!
Time out, Regulars!
There's only one way
to turn this around.
We have to feed the
ball to our best player.
Tawaraya...
Can... can you do it?
Yeah...! Bring it on!
O... okay...
Then give it your best shot.
This is bad. We can't
break their momentum.
Well, what do you think
we should do, partner?
Shut up...!
We just gotta hit 'em harder
and don't call me "partner"!
Hey! You guys!
I think it's time for us to
try out my special technique!
You've got to be
really careful, Sis...
That shot's a pretty tricky one!
Yeah, I know it's risky...
but we have to take action!
What does she think she's doing?
It's Bam Star Basketball Gang!
Attack!
Don't worry,
I've already calculated how
to counter their moves!
I'll take care of
these guys. It'll be fun!
Creepy!
And that's enough out of you!
Hey, take it easy, Imadori!
Aagh! That does it...!
Go, fighting spirit!
Eel explosiooooon!
Galactic... bomberrrrrrrr!
You... you did it!
Way to go!
I sure did...! I couldn't
have done it without you!
But come on, you guys, our fight
here is just getting started!
Traveling.
It's okay, Sis,
you tried really hard.
Two minute warning!
You've gotta be kidding!
Ho ho! Doowah!
Tenma's on Lara?
What the heck are they thinking?
Doowah!
Move! Stop mocking me!
Offensive foul!
That's five fouls!
Lara has fouled out!
What are you talking about?
I barely laid a hand on her!
Are you blind or
are you just crazy?
The whole thing was just
a trick to foul out Lara!
We're out of players,
Now what do we do!
Looks to me like we need
to call in our secret weapon!
All right, Tenma, are you ready?
Your time has come!
Are you out of your mind,
Tsukamoto's on our team!
I'm back, everyone...!
Sorry I'm so late!
Tenma... why?
What's happening?
Huh...! Well, aren't
you just the
unpredicatable little kitten!
But hey, that's basketball
for ya...! Let's do it!
You idiot, not only are
you not making any sense,
but now we're one player short!
How about letting me join?
Asou...? You sure?
Oh, yeah... Sorry... I kind
of want to take you guys on.
That's hot...
Bring it.
We've got fifteen seconds
to turn this game around.
We're gonna have to draw a
foul on this shot to tie it up.
You cross over and
I'll take the right, okay!
You got it! Just leave
Harima to me, baby!
Tawaraya is on fire today!
But Suou is nearly exhausted...
there's no way she
can keep this up.
She won't pass!
If I cut in on her drive,
we've got them beat!
Yeah! I was right!
Huh? She passed?
In 'yo face!
Damn! Harima, it's up to you!
Defense... defense...
Someone stop Suou!
A double clutch?!
Incredible! I've never
seen anything like it!
Way to go, Mikoto, you did it!
That was an amazing pass!
Look at that.
I really didn't think
you'd do this well.
A one point difference,
who'd have guessed?
But one point is one point.
Starting tomorrow,
the court belongs to us!
Ah, I'm so over this.
Uhm, Ten--I mean,
Miss Tsukamoto,
can I be on your team instead?
It's getting late.
I have to go get dinner ready.
I don't understand
this country...
Oops, my bad!
Sorry, they wore out!
What am I supposed to
do with a pair of laces?
Hey, Satsuki, is it true we got
a lot of new recruits recently?
Yeah, a lot of people
who came to watch the game
wound up sticking around
and joining the team!
So much for our five
person basketball club!
Oh, well, that's all right,
at least it was fun
while it lasted!
Lara, it was really nice the
way you helped out Satsuki.
What are you
talking about "nice?"
I just wanted to win the game.
So how 'bout it?
Are you gonna keep
playing basketball with us?
Oh, I don't think so,
I mean, it was fun and all,
playing on the
team with you guys,
but I just felt like an
amateur out there.
What, you have got
to be kidding me...
You were great and you
improved more than anybody!
Whatever, you're
just saying that,
besides, I've still
got my dojo duties...
No, I think Megumi's right.
You've got serious talent, Suou.
If you drop out now,
it'd really suck for the team.
I've gone up against you
and I'm not joking around,
you've got what it takes.
Um...
I... I agree with Asou.
You're sharp, you're tall,
and you're always looking out
for your fellow teammates.
You definitely have
a talent for basketball
and it'd be a shame
if you quit now...
I mean I'm just
throwin' that out there.
Uh, thank you...
Wow, Satsuki...
Well, well, if it isn't
my fickle little
heroine of the hoops...
How fortuitous that
I should run into you.
Huh?
Did you mean what you said about
transferring into Class 2-D?
How 'bout it...?
You'd be a utility player...
I'll keep a seat warm for you.
Why that smooth talking
pony tailed S.O.B.,
he's got a lot of nerve
making moves on my Tenma!
Come on, Miko,
just one kiss to show
there's no hard feelings
about the game...
Will you get off me, you idiot?
Oh, Miko, I love it when
you kick me like that.
It makes me hurt so good.
Leave him to me, Mikoto!
Thanks, Lara!
Wow! Everyone sure ate a lot!
Hey, Satsuki.
This may be over...
but what about that?
Remember... I am here for you.
So, Tawaraya...
think you can get by
coaching the team
on your own now?
What do you mean?
Are you going back
to boys' basketball?
It's not really about that...
I'm just afraid that
I might make things worse
for you by coaching you myself.
That's not true.
Listen, you're a really
good coach, Asou...
You and Mikoto are going
to work great together.
Huh?
Well, I'll let you two finish
cleaning up by yourselves!
Hey!
Huh... the weather's
great tonight...
I'm sorry you got stuck
helping with the dishes.
Hey, don't worry about it.
But seriously...
Will you keep on
playing basketball?
Because I wasn't kidding
about what I said before,
I really do think you're great.
Well, thank you...
I guess I'll have
to do some thinking.
If you do play...
I'd be happy to help
you pick out shoes...
You promise?
Hey there, Mikoto...!
I understand that Yakumo
is playing basketball now!
So what do you say, am I in
time for the next practice?
Tenma! Have you put
on weight recently?
You're eating too much! Huh?
On me it's all muscle...
so not the same.
Next time on School Rumble!
"Hee! Hee Hee! Hee Hee Hee!"
Hey! That's not
muscle there, so watch it!