Stop! We can't take anymore!
You're the only one left!
We'll finish this right now!
Guys...
This is the end for you!
Please stop this!
My next move will finish you!
Not so fast!
Wha... who's that?
Just leave this to us!
Dentaku...! Budo...! Nihil!
You guys don't know
when to quit...! Get them!
Don't worry, I've
already calculated how
to counter their moves!
That's enough out of you!
Thanks, you guys!
Fools! It's no use!
You have no choice
but to give up!
The heck we do...! All that
matters is our fighting spirit!
And that's what we're
gonna hit you with!
I'll knock it right back at ya!
Roaring Burst!
Galactic Bomber!
You... you did it!
And I have you guys to thank!
Our fight is just
getting started!
Basketball...
It so rocks my socks!
Now, sis... that's not real.
Huh... Huh-huh...!
Da, da, da, da... da-dah!
Duwa!
Okay, I'm up for some
basketball...! Yeah!
So when did Tenma
become a basketball freak?
Man, Sagano really kicks ass!
I'll say!
She's amazing, huh?
She was in basketball
club in middle school.
She was one of the
regulars, starting first year.
How cool...!
She's got ninja reflexes!
So why doesn't she play now
that she's in high school?
There's no girls'
basketball team...
it's really too bad you know?
Yeah that sucks.
All right, the boys'
game is about to start!
Asou!
Suga, you gotta
D-up man, he's quick!
Dude, not cool!
There's chicks watching!
Oh, yeah...! That's so cool!
I'll bet you anything Asou
makes captain next term.
Go, Asou!
Rock steady cause they
ain't even ready! Yeah!
Wow...! That was bad ass!
Where the heck
did that come from?!
Uh, a little help
here...? I'm stuck.
Basketball rules...!
I want to get out there
pull a Galactic Bomber
on those fools! Yup, yup!
What's a Galactic Bomber?
You don't know?
No idea.
Roaring Burst!!
What?
Really?
You'll serve as
the faculty advisor
for a girls' basketball club?
Sure, since one of my
favorite students asked me to.
If you really think you want me,
I'll be glad to give it a shot.
Then I'll put together
a team right away!
I'd like to be ready for this
month's district tournament,
if that's possible!
Oh, hey...
Mr. Tani, you're the advisor
for the boys' basketball
club, aren't you?
Yes... that's right.
Well, can you recommend
anyone who could help us out?
Huuuh...? Mr. Tani said
I have to give you guys a hand?
Yep...! He said that when
it comes to basketball,
you were the go to guy!
Well, what can I say?
If he's just gonna
spring this on me, okay...
I guess first I should
discuss this with Sagano.
Thank you so much!
What...? A girls'
basketball club...?
Count me in...! I'm with you!
Satsuki Tawaraya,
is it...? Hey, girl!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
You know I...
I used to watch you play
all the time in
middle school,...
I have to say you were
incredible out there!
Oh, now you're embarrassing me!
But way to go, starting
a girls' basketball club!
Oh my gosh!
It's gonna be so much fun...
What have I gotten myself into?
Sorry... I really wish
I could help you guys out...
but it's not my game... huh?
Oh... maybe you should
ask Mikoto over there.
Huh...? But I've got dojo duty.
Come on...!
Can't you get out of it?
Of course she can.
I'll cover for you...
It's a good idea to try
something new now and then.
He's right, Mikoto!
Let's give it a shot!
Let's play! Let's play!
They're not asking you, Tenma.
Okay, you can count me in.
Ah, sweet!
Now that we've
finally got a team,
we're really ready to rock!
How's that...? I have won, no?
When she heard
Ichijou was playing...
...she insisted we
teach her basketball.
She's in intensive training.
Very... at least now
she aims for the goal.
Well, have fun...
she's all yours, man.
Thanks.
That was incredible!
We can use a player like you!
As manager, I'm putting
you on the team!
Talent like yours comes
along once in a lifetime!
Ms. Anegasaki, do you
know the rules of basketball?
Of course I do.
You aim for that little square
on the home plate
thingie, right?
Uh... never mind...
Okay, there's one month
before the tournament!
The first thing you guys need to
work on is building team work!
So right off, I'm going to give
all of you team nicknames!
Huh?
You, first year...
We're gonna call
you Rookie, got it?
Right...! Rookie
reporting for duty!
We'll call you Hostess!
You mean because my family
runs a restaurant, right?
You're Itchy!
Okay... I guess...
Tits McGee...! I mean, Mickey!
Wait... What was the
first part of that again?!
And Gori...! It couldn't
be anything else!
Gracias, Senorita Tae...!
I really like the
sound of that name!
It makes me want
to smash things!
By the way, Ichijou,
what does, uh, "Gori" mean?
Uh, well, it's short
for something
very big and strong and smart...
Si! That name is perfect
for me! I am Gori!
And kind of hairy...
Ichijou! You tricked me!
Once you get the ball...
twist your hips sideways
and fake with your
head and shoulders...!
Protect the ball...!
This is where Ichijou
makes her move!
Nice shot, girl.
Wow... I can't believe it.
We don't completely suck!
It's all 'cause Satsuki
is such a good coach!
Great job...! You know, you're
really starting to get this!
Aren't you going to practice?
All you've done is coach.
Oh, I'll train, too...
I promise, kay...?
We're doing individual
drills next... Oh!
Don't push yourself too hard.
You're the backbone
of the team, you know.
Right...! Thank you
very much, Asou!
You know, this is
a good opportunity
for you to get closer to Asou.
Know your enemy
and know yourself,
and you will be safe
even in a hundred battles!
A girl named Sonko wrote that
in an essay a long time ago...
so don't give up!
I don't know what you mean...
Asou is just another student.
Another student you love!
Heed the words of Sonko...!
And they'll serve you well!
Yeah, now that
I've actually tried it,
I'm starting to really
get into basketball...
but morning practice
is kinda lame.
You've been doing
it a week, right...?
You guys have really
been going at it hard.
So, what is it that made
you get serious about it?
I guess...
It's from watching Satsuki...
She works so hard it's
kind of inspiring, you know?
Oh, That first year girl...?
Yeah, she's pretty
intense about it.
Still, her height puts her
at quite a disadvantage.
I hear that no matter
how much she eats,
and she eats a lot, she just
can't seem to grow any.
How d'you know?
Well, she's one of
Yakumo's classmates.
Oh, that's right.
And I know something
else about Satsuki...
What are you laughing about?
Just 'tween us...
apparently she's got it
and got it bad for Asou!
Now that you mention it,
it does seem like she's
standing right next to him,
like all the time.
You see, you see...?
Teen romance strikes again!
That's great and all,
but are you ever gonna make
it to a morning practice?
Well, I did get up once,
but the charms of my mattress
kind of lured me back in.
"Once"?
So you haven't made it to any
of the morning sessions yet?
Ah, uh, no...
All right, now turn!
Now shoot!
Ahh, so close!
You're awesome... Seriously...
It's really cool of you to
coach me one on one like this.
Hey, it's no big deal...
you're really good at this...
Plus, you've got the height.
Ah, it's whatev.
Hey, Mikoto... you want to play
a little one on one with me?
Sure, why not? It'll be fun!
Damn, she's good!
That what's known
as a quick turn...
Still got a lot to learn,
haven't you?
Roaring Burst!
Galactic Bomberrrrrr!
I'm totally starving...!
Let's get something to eat!
Iiiiii love food!
I know...! Asou, your place
is a Chinese restaurant, right?
Uh...? Yeah... it sure is.
All right then!
Let's have dinner
at Asou's place!
To the feast!
Okay...! Now that
you've gotten that settled
you can leave
everything to me, ladies!
What the hell, man...?
Where'd you even come from?!
Muchas gracias!
I'll see you guys later.
Wait a minute... you're
not gonna eat with us?
Oh... I'm afraid
I have something I have
to take care of right
now... so I can't come.
Best food ever!
Let's hear it for Asou!
Yaaay!
I wonder what Satsuki's
big errand was?
Welcome to... huh?
Tawaraya?
I'd like one Koraku
full belly dinner!
What...? You can stop staring,
it's not like
I followed you here,
I've been planning
on eating dinner here
all day so you
can just ignore me
and go on about your business.
One Koraku full belly dinner.
I gotta say, you look
pretty natural back there.
I live and work in
Chinese restaurants...
I should look natural.
Excuse me, Asou?
What is it...?
Can I get you anything else?
I'd like another one of these
full belly dinners, please.
Oh... sure...
You already finished?
Here you go, another
full belly dinner.
Now that you mention it...
where do you work?
At Muo Li's, by the station.
Oh, yeah, I've seen that place.
Yeah, Suga and the
guys go there a lot.
Excuse me, Asou?
What's up?
I'd like one more of
these full belly dinners.
Wow... Can we
say eating disorder?
Excuse me, Asou?
I'd like... to give...
...compliments to the chef.
Hey!
Don't worry about it...
I'm going that way anyway...
I'll just drop her off.
Thanks, Suou.
You know, you're pretty
cute when you're asleep.
It's admirable, the way
she dedicates herself
one hundred
percent to everything...
It's like she doesn't care about
making a fool of herself...
be it for love, or for sports...
How many people
can say they do that?
She's got guts...
I could learn from her.
Twenty full belly dinners with
extra rice comes to 18,000 yen.
No!
Wait, sis!
Here's your boxed lunch...!
You're going to be getting a
real workout, so I packed extra!
That's my little sister! Thanks!
Now I'll be able to
keep up my energy...
and do slam dunks like the pros!
Good morning...!
Everyone ready to practice?
Come on people!
Let's focus...! You guys are
all over the place out there,
it's supposed to
be about team work!
Right!
Hey! Isn't there
one too many girls?
Tenma!
Ms. Tae! What
position should I play?
Yeah, we need to have a
serious talk about that.
Thank goodness...!
I'm the only one who
doesn't have a nickname yet,
so I was really getting worried!
See, Tenma... the thing is...
and I only found
this out yesterday...
it turns out that
basket ball is played
with only five
players, not six...
So until one of the
other girls gets tired
and decides to drop out,
I'm putting you on
a special program.
Say what?
Uh, Tenma?
Are you done
practicing already...?
I was coming to cheer
you on... or am I too late?
Not at all...!
I'm still practicing!
They said I need my own program!
Ya see... I'm a slow starter!
Really...? Well,
hang in there, sis.
Right...! Go! Team! Go! Team!
Go! Team! Go! Team!
It won't go in!
Oh, Lara, please calm down!
Come on, Lara, take
your shooting position.
Like this?
No, you're using way
too much force in here.
Your left arm should be
mostly used for support, see?
Like this?
Wow...! It went in!
Muchisimas gracias, Satsuki!
Okay, now you join in!
Free throws for everyone!
Are you sure?
Si! Por su puesto
Does that mean yes?
Oh wow, they're already
doing one on one...?
Mikoto is really
coming along, isn't she?
Yeah... I know...
She's a regular Tiger Woods.
Now! To the right!
I can't shake this guy!
Oh, don't tell me
that's all you got.
Get away from me...
Captain Pervo!
Right now why don't
you just call me Coach.
Now let's try it again...
Lemme show you how it's done--
Okay, what do think
you're doing here, doofus?
All right, just watch it
with that doofus stuff,
wiener breath!
I came here to coach!
Believe it or not,
I'm walkin' on air!
Check it!
Just watch and
see how it's done!
Way to go boobs for brains...
Imadori, if you're
just gonna screw around...
No, it's not like that!
Ichijou, come on,
help me out here, will you?
Imadori, I appreciate
the sentiment, honestly,
but... you should go.
Try keeping your arms
closer... ease up a little.
I know...! Tawaraya...!
Could you show Suou here...?
You've got the best form
of anyone on the team.
Of course!
What the heck...?
Try again... maybe you
just tense or something.
Why...? Why?!
Don't give up, Satsuki!
Remember the old saying, "the
NBA is a dream within a dream!"
I don't think that's
quite right, Lara.
Go team, go...
Hey, sis! It's about
time for morning practice!
Uh... Yakumo...
I thought I'd maybe take
a little time off from...
Here's your lunch!
Kinda big, isn't it?
I thought you might want to
share it with the other players.
It seems like it's
been a long time...
since you were so
excited about something...
This is my way of
showing I support you.
I'm behind you... Sis.
All right! I'll do my best!
Tenma didn't show up
for practice again today...
I wonder what's wrong?
I'm sorry... Tenma...
for putting you in
this difficult position...
but it should only be
a little while longer...
Sooner or later, someone
will get tired and quit...
and then you'll be our...
oh, what is that term...?
Oh, right! Our ball buster!
Lara...! The basket's there!
Huh...? Ay, no entiendo!
Holy crap.
That's a pretty scary
team you've got there.
I have to admit,
your girls have managed
to re-ignite the burning
passion for basketball
I thought I had lost
when I left America.
You... sure you're
passion's for basketball?
Come on, ladies, just say it...
you're still missing
something special, aren't you?
Are you ready to take
on Tougou Masakazu,
the guy the Americans used
to call the Big Bull of Texas?
The winner gets to take
the loser out on a date.
No, thanks.
Humph... I see...
You guys aren't ready for
the Big Bull challenge yet.
Forget it then. Your loss.
Harry... I'm leaving
Lara in your hands.
Great... I'll do what I can.
Adios!
Okay... let's finish up
with some shuttle runs!
Right!
Man, I don't know what it is,
but I feel like we have the
power to... to just kick ass!
Come on, Sis...!
Time for practice!
Listen, Yakumo...
about basketball practice...
Here you go!
Plenty for everyone!
You think I overdid it?
No, no, it's fine...! After
practice everyone is starving!
If it wasn't for your lunches,
we wouldn't have the strength
to rock out on the court!
Really...? I'm so glad!
In fact, today I think
I'll have enough extra energy
to score a double dribble!
That sounds amazing, Sis!
Tenma, we need to talk.
I think you have a problem.
She's like a mindless
eating machine.
What happened?
Beats me.
Hey, Sis, have you
been gaining some weight?
I've been going overboard
on those lunches, haven't I?
No, no, not at all,
not at all...!
I've been putting on weight
for our body-checking
defense strategy!
Oh, good...
You're really serious
about this, huh, Sis?
Absolutely...! It wouldn't
be practice for anyone
if I wasn't there
doing my thing!
Mentirosa!
When will I get
back on the team...?
When can I start
my special program?
They say that when a tiger dies,
it leaves behind no hide.
Tougou?
Trust me, you're not the only
one who's been treated badly...
Lift up your head and
take a look around you.
Huh...? Imadori...? and Harima?
Quite a coincidence, huh...?
It turns out I've been
getting into basketball too.
It comes down to
just two things...
the ball and the goal...
...when you've got those,
and get your best team
mates around you,
then you've got basketball!
All of us became outlaws
before we even knew
it was happening!
Let's show those guys
just what we're made of!
Right! As of now,
you're all in special training!
Yeah!
There's a cold wind a brewin'...
Hey! I'm Drive!
Next time on Bam Star Basketball
Gang: "Pass! Dribble! Shoot!"
Roaring Burst...!
Galactic Boooommmberrrrr!
Bam! Bam!
Bam Star Basketball Gang! Yeah!