[HINAMI] The CCG's white
reaper, Kisho Arima.
I'm going to die here.
Hold on, Arima.
She's not fighting.
So, if it's okay,
would you allow me
to take her into custody?
[AKIRA]
November 11th.
On this day,
the CCG planned and successfully
carried out two missions.
The auction raid,
and the quinque steel
transport escort mission.
[AKIRA] We received a tip
that Aogiri Tree
was plotting to hijack
a shipment of quinque steel.
So we used it as bait
and ambushed them.
The mission was carried
out by the S3 Squad,
with Special Investigator
Marude presiding.
After the auction raid
mission commenced,
Aogiri Tree ghouls attacked
our transports, as we expected.
The S3 Squad dispatched
them with relative ease.
Their initial mission completed,
the S3 Squad rushed
to the auction house.
[UTA]
It's time we left.
Fine.
[MIZA]
Scatter and retreat! Now!
[AYATO]
No! Hinami's still in there!
We're outnumbered.
There's nothing we can do!
[NAKI]
We have to run!
[TORSO]
Toru...
Matsumae.
We'll have to seek out a proper
meal through other means.
Right, Master Mirumo.
[SEIDO panting]
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
Takizawa?
[SEIDO laughs]
Mado.
[AKIRA] The Quinx Squad
determined the time and location
of the auction,
then infiltrated it,
slew the S-rated
ghoul, Nutcracker,
and supported Suzuya Squad
in eliminating Big Madam.
Quinx Squad played a key
role in this mission.
And their reputation has
greatly improved, as a result.
A number of Aogiri Tree
members were killed
by an unknown party
as they fled the scene.
Many of the bodies found
were partially consumed.
[AKIRA] If Takizawa really
is alive, then perhaps...
No. That's expecting too much.
[AKIRA gasps]
[AKIRA]
Expecting. Could they have--?
Ginshi Shirazu.
Saiko Yonebayashi.
I appoint you second
class investigators.
Miyuki Mikage. Mizuro Tamaki.
Hanbei Abara. Kuki Urie.
Takeomi Kuroiwa.
And Toru Mutsuki.
I appoint you first
class investigators.
[INVESTIGATOR A] That guy
got promoted two whole ranks.
[YOSHITOKI]
Kuramoto Ito. Keiji Nakarai.
Naoto Hayashimura.
And Haise Sasaki.
I appoint you
senior investigators.
Senior Investigator Akira Mado.
I appoint you associate
special investigator.
Juzo Suzuya. Matsuri Washu.
I appoint you
special investigators.
[SHIRAZU] So you and Urie
are first class now.
That's the same rank Mr. Sass
was not too long ago.
To be honest, it hasn't
quite sunk in for me yet.
[TAKEOMI]
Urie, congratulations.
Yeah.
[URIE] So you killed a ghoul
with your bare hands.
Think I'm impressed?
Just stay out of my sight.
[KUROIWA]
Takeomi.
[TAKEOMI]
Special Investigator Kuroiwa.
Good work. You, too, Urie.
[AKIRA]
Outstanding work.
You've already made
senior investigator.
[HAISE]
Thank you very much,
Associate Special Investigator.
Stop that. You'll make me blush.
By the way,
any word on Fueguchi?
She's still undergoing
questioning for the time being.
She'll certainly prove to be
a valuable source
of information.
But do mind the
appropriate custody period.
[HAISE] I heard that
Fueguchi was involved
in the death of Akira's father.
And I effectively
saved her life.
Could Akira be okay with that?
Or is it like I've poured
fuel onto a smoldering fire?
[KANEKI]
I am me. And you are you.
We're just living
inside the same body.
Please, Haise.
Make sure this time.
--[KANEKI] I don't disappear.
--[KANEKI] That you disappear.
[SATOMI]
Senior Investigator.
As of today, I've been assigned
to the Shimoguchi Squad.
I'm First Class
Investigator Shiori Satomi.
As have I.
First Class, Miho Toga.
It's an honor to be--
Save it for the brass.
Nothing good is
gonna come to you
from becoming part of my squad.
[SATOMI]
We know, sir.
Suit yourselves, then.
Your "Nutcracker."
will be completed
in just a moment.
You should be
looking forward to it.
She's going to make you
an excellent quinque.
[URIE grunting]
[URIE]
More... More!
I can't let Kuroiwa beat me!
[JUZO] You want two going up
while the third one falls.
Catch it and cut.
And if you throw 'em
all up at once,
you'll have time to grab more!
[MUTSUKI]
Not sure I can do all that.
Honestly, I think two
might be my limit.
[JUZO] Aw, are you sure?
From everything I've seen,
you're really good
at fighting with knives.
Hey, Suzuya.
Do you ever get worried
that you'll hurt yourself
with your own knife?
That's never crossed my mind.
Me and pain don't really talk.
Is that what you're
scared of, Toru?
[JUZO]
In battle,
it's those who have tamed
their weaknesses that win.
[MUTSUKI]
"Tamed their weaknesses."
I like that expression.
I didn't come up with it.
I stole it from my teacher.
[STUDENTS]
Thank you, sir!
[HAISE]
Sure. Thank you!
[TOKAGE]
Investigator Sasaki.
[HAISE]
Instructor Tokage?
Thanks for coming by.
Having an active-duty
investigator come and lecture
always goes a long way
to motivate the students.
Well, feel free to
call on me anytime.
[TOKAGE] So their stupidity
hasn't worn you down yet?
Not at all.
I thought they were
pleasant and cheerful.
[TOKAGE] A few of them already
have criminal records.
Which reminds me,
how has young
Mutsuki been doing?
He was always a problem student.
Was he really?
Well, he's earnest
and hardworking now.
Special investigator Suzuya's
been coaching him lately.
Ah, Suzuya.
Well, I'll see you around.
[MUTSUKI]
Shirazu!
[SHIRAZU]
Huh?
I get that, but custody
of a ghoul always
goes to the investigator who
defeated it, and that's you.
And I bet that Nutcracker
will make a strong quinque.
[MUTSUKI]
With a more powerful weapon,
you'll be able to stand up
against more powerful ghouls.
[SHIRAZU]
Yeah. Guess you're right.
[HAISE]
Welcome home, you two!
Did you have a good day?
Was it fun?
You're not hurt, are you?
[SHIRAZU]
No, we're fine.
Good.
Then come along, hurry up,
wash your hands and change!
I've invited some very special
guests to come over tonight.
So let's try to impress 'em!
You sure are enjoying
yourself, Teach.
[HAISE] Of course I am,
it's a celebratory dinner party!
Come back and help me
when you're done, okay?
Sure thing!
Ugh. All right, I'll do it.
[SHIRAZU, MUTSUKI, SAIKO]
Ooh...
[SHIRAZU yelping]
[HAISE]
Shirazu, be careful!
Saiko, it's burning!
[SAIKO]
That's why they call it flambé!
[MUTSUKI]
Urie. What'cha doin'?
Gonna go work out.
[URIE]
I won't let Kuroiwa beat me.
[MUTSUKI] You can't!
We've got guests coming.
You can count me out.
[MUTSUKI firmly]
Urie.
You're helping us.
Get this stuff.
[thud]
[URIE panting]
[HAISE] Urie, I'm so sorry.
That must've been heavy.
[URIE]
No.
By the way, someone
sent you a package.
Wonder who?
[SHIRAZU] I told you to cut it
out with the flambé, Saiko!
[SAIKO]
I've got it this time!
[SHIRAZU]
No. No! Gimme that bottle!
[MUTSUKI]
Hey, Teach?
Coming!
[SHIRAZU, MUTSUKI, URIE]
Ooh!
Thanks, guys.
You were all a huge
help with this.
[doorbell rings]
Whatever you've made,
it smells delicious.
Hope we're not too early.
Hello, welcome home!
Or, I should say,
welcome to our home.
I'm glad you two
could make it tonight.
--[SHIRAZU] Oh! Yum!
--[MUTSUKI] This is delicious!
[SAIKO]
Amazing.
The food is even better
than usual tonight.
[HAISE]
Akira, we made spicy curry, too.
[AKIRA]
Oh, thank you.
I've never made it
quite like this,
so let me know what you think.
It's an exact reproduction
of the Mado family recipe!
Ah. Delicious.
It reminds me of home.
You don't mind if
I sneak a bite--
[ARIMA]
Wait.
I suggest that you refrain.
The Mado family
spicy curry is SS-rated.
Are you okay?
He doesn't look it.
Hang in there, man!
--[AKIRA] He can take it.
--[MUTSUKI] Give him some water!
--Or do we have any milk?
--[SAIKO] I think he's dead.
[SHIRAZU]
Did you really beat a ghoul
with an umbrella once?
[ARIMA] Well, I didn't have
my quinque close at hand.
And this umbrella
was quite durable.
[AKIRA] Yeah, I've heard
more stories like that
about Arima than I can count.
[HAISE]
Juzo told me one that I always
wanted to ask you about.
Didn't you fight in
your sleep once?
[SHIRAZU]
Uh! You're kidding me!
[MUTSUKI]
No way is that one true.
[ARIMA]
I was sleepy...
[SHIRAZU]
Like how sleepy?
[MUTSUKI]
Were your eyes closed?
[SHIRAZU]
Whew. Man, that was good.
[MUTSUKI]
I'm completely stuffed.
[SAIKO]
There's always room for dessert.
[URIE]
How do you do it?
I brought coffee,
and I also got some
presents for all of you.
[SHIRAZU, MUTSUKI]
Huh?
[SAIKO]
Uh...
[SHIRAZU]
Really?
Yeah. To celebrate
your promotion.
Whoa. Thank you, I love it!
[gasps]
Nice. Thanks.
[HAISE] This one's for you,
Akira. You got promoted, too.
Thanks, I appreciate it, Haise.
[QUINX SQUAD chattering]
You are truly like
a father to them.
You really think so?
This isn't much, but here.
But I wasn't promoted.
It's to thank you
for helping me out.
From my name. Thank you.
[HAISE]
That takes care of that.
Hey, Urie. What's up?
Got training to do.
Seems kinda late for that.
Well, don't overdo it, okay?
[URIE]
Who are you, my mom?
Now that I've been
promoted and all,
I expect the ghouls
I get pitted against
will be a lot more powerful.
I need to be prepared for that.
Well, I can't argue
with you on that point.
But try to remember that you
aren't alone in this, okay?
There's a reason
why we're a team.
It's so that we can cover
each other's weak points.
[URIE]
Right.
How pretentious.
[URIE]
Although... He has a point.
[HAISE]
A mask.
Was this the eyepatch ghoul's?
Ken Kaneki. I wonder
how that's written.
If I knew the
characters, I could--
[HAISE]
Sen Takatsuki.
"To Ken Kaneki."
[HAISE] A novel by Sen
Takatsuki, and a mask.
Who could've sent them?
There's no way that they
were sent to me by accident.
The package had
a return address.
It must've come from
someone who knew Kaneki.
Maybe I should try to find them.
Oh. Thanks a lot.
[HAISE] This aroma.
Why's it so familiar?
[sighs]
[OROCHI]
Hey, gimme a refill.
[TOUKA]
Brew it yourself, ya bum.
Uta.
Tell me, do the clowns see
him as a problem or what?
Do you have any idea
what they plan to do?
No. The boss has yet to
let me in on her thinking.
[YOMO]
Hm.
[UTA]
What about all of you?
Still waiting for Kaneki?
--Or perhaps you--
--[TOUKA] Uta.
Huh?
For my part,
I'll just keep doing what
I made up my mind to.
[OROCHI]
Hm.
Right. Thank you for the coffee.
Yours really is
the best to be had.
[UTA] And Touka. Even after
all that's happened,
Ken is still a special
customer to me.
[door bell chimes]
[SHIBA] Hm. Well, your
levels seem to be stable.
[URIE]
Is that right?
I was told you lost
control on a mission.
[URIE]
Who the hell ratted me out?
[SHIBA]
How'd you manage to recover?
I focused my attention,
just like I was trained to.
So that was enough.
Hey, Doctor? About Mutsuki.
What is it?
I can't discuss any
personal information.
It's fine. Forget about it.
[URIE]
There's no way he doesn't know.
Please excuse me.
[URIE]
Shirazu?
[SHIRAZU]
Guess what, Haru?
Your big bro's been promoted.
I'm a second class
investigator now.
They even raised my pay a bit.
So hang tight.
I'm gonna be rakin'
it in before long,
then we'll get ya fixed up.
And don't worry.
I'm not in over
my head or anything.
If I do run into trouble,
I've got my friends.
They're all super awesome.
Urie and Toru just became
first class investigators.
Yeah. They're all great people.
I'll introduce ya
to them someday.
Everything's goin' good.
You look pretty,
you know that, Haru?
[HAISE] The CCG didn't
have much material
on Ken Kaneki,
which strikes me as odd.
There was an article saying
he got hit by a steel beam
at a construction site.
And then there was his
missing person's report.
He went to Kamii University
and he had no family.
I wonder if he had any friends.
This place...
[MEN panting]
[BOTH yelp]
[MEN scream]
[KANAE]
Master Shu.
[TSUKIYAMA]
It hurts. I'm so very hungry.
Isn't there something?
Anything I can eat?
[KANAE] Master Shu.
This is heartbreaking.
So heartbreaking.
[clock ticking]
[TATARA]
Impossible.
[UI] I'm Kori Ui, captain
of the S1. Greetings.
[CHIE]
Not at all.
[YORIKO] Always wanted
to work at a coffee shop...
[MATSURI] I'd like to use
everything I learned in Germany
to take down..
[CHIE]
That's most of it.
[MATSUMAE]
A trap?
[TSUKIYAMA]
I am a gourmet.
[camera shutter click]