[gasps]
[MUTSUKI grunts]
Where am I?
[MUTSUKI] The last thing
I remember is getting
into Nutcracker's car
with Investigator Juzo.
[gasps]
[gasps] Is anyone there?
Mutsuki reporting.
Do you read me?
[MUTSUKI]
It's no use.
[rumbling]
[gasps]
Take it away.
[applause]
Hi! Yay!
Ah!
[laughter]
[AUDIENCE laughs]
[laughing]
[ROMA yelps]
[UTA] Good evening,
Ladies and gentlemen.
I would like to thank you
for your patience.
The moment you've all
been waiting for,
the auction, is about to begin.
[UTA] We'll need
a master of ceremonies
and auctioneers for this event.
Who better to do
the job than us?
The Clowns!
Sit back, relax, and enjoy
to your heart's content!
[applause]
[UTA]
And now, allow me to present
the first item of the night.
An actor who was very popular
in his time, Mr. Yoshiki Okura!
Stop! Don't do this!
[UTA] Let's begin the
bidding at 10,000,000.
[BIDDER 4A]
Ten million!
[BIDDER 4B]
Eleven, no, 12,000,000!
I don't understand why
they'd start the bidding
so high for a washed-up actor.
They know their
audience is willing
to pay more because
of his celebrity status.
I couldn't care less
about his "status,"
it's in poor taste.
[BIDDER B]
Twenty-one million!
[BIDDER E]
Twenty-two million!
[BIDDER I] Twenty-three!
Twenty-three million!
[BIDDER A]
Twenty-four million!
[BIDDER C]
Twenty-five million!
Thirty million yen.
[UTA]
Well, well.
It appears we have
a one-on-one battle
between bidders 33 and one.
Thirty-one million yen!
I'll bid 32,000,000.
Thirty-two-point-five
million on the actor!
Make it 35,000,000.
[BIG MADAM growls]
[UTA] And the winner
is bidder number 33!
Congratulations!
[applause]
[TORSO]
Who is that man?
[AYATO]
They call him "Croque Monsieur."
He's in a different
conglomerate than Big Madam,
but he's another
billionaire ghoul.
[TORSO]
Is this normal?
I mean, are humans always
sold at such high prices?
[AYATO] No, the price varies
depending on the human.
But deep down, they must think
their lives are worthless.
That's why they're able
to put prices on them.
[TORSO]
If I had that kind of money...
[bang]
[TORSO]
Toru?
[UTA] We'll start the bidding
at 1,000,000 yen.
Excuse me, I stand corrected.
[UTA]
This item's special.
It has quite an unusual scent.
[AUDIENCE gasps]
[BIDDER F]
Wait, is that--?
No, it can't be! Can it?
[UTA]
I present, a one-eyed ghoul!
[BIG MADAM]
Hm...
I must have it!
It's the only thing that might
help invigorate Master Shu!
[AYATO]
A one-eyed ghoul?
[TORSO]
I need to bid!
Please, Ayato, tell me
how to join the auction!
That's Toru!
I have to bid until I win!
[AYATO] What the hell
are you blabbering about?
[TORSO]
Toru.
[UTA] This is a rarity,
ladies and gentlemen.
It's far too precious for
a measly 1,000,000 yen.
Let's start the
bidding at 10,000,000!
[BIDDER A]
Ten million!
[BIDDER B]
Twelve million!
[BIDDER C]
Fifteen million!
[BIDDER E]
Seventeen million!
[MUTSUKI]
What now?
Someone tell me what to do.
How do I handle this?
I'm scared.
I don't have a strategy.
Do I stand up and fight?
Or is this where I...?
Save me, Teach!
[BIDDER B]
Sixty million!
[UTA whispering] Your plan
failed. Help isn't coming.
[gasps]
[BIDDER D]
Sixty-five million!
[BIDDER H]
Seventy million yen!
[BIDDER D]
Eighty million!
[KANAE]
One hundred million!
[AUDIENCE]
Ooh!
Don't even think about it.
I'm not gonna let something
this rare slip away from me.
One-hundred-and-twenty million!
[UTA]
Big Madam isn't backing down!
One-hundred-and-forty million!
[UTA]
However, neither is bidder 110!
One-hundred-and-fifty million!
[KANAE]
One-hundred-eighty million!
[AUDIENCE gasps, murmurs]
[BIG MADAM cackles]
Two-hundred million!
[KANAE gasps]
[AUDIENCE gasps, cheers]
[UTA] The winner is bidder
number one: Big Madam!
No. Master.
[UTA] Your merchandise
will be delivered
after the auction.
Amazing! Two hundred million!
Ah!
You deserve a kiss!
[NUTCRACKER]
Two-hundred million!
I can't believe it!
[UTA] Now, ladies and gentlemen,
let's keep the excitement
going by introducing our
next item up for auction.
Presenting another exceptionally
beautiful young lady,
who I suspect will fetch
an equally high price.
[BIDDER G]
Oh! Look at that fair skin
and those big eyes!
She almost looks like
a porcelain doll!
That one's perfect, Madam!
If you had a girl like
that, then you could--
[AIDE A]
Madam?
[UTA] All right, folks,
our starting bid will--
[JUZO]
You don't need one.
[AUDIENCE screams]
[AYATO] It's Suzuya!
The doves are out to get us!
[BIDDERS scream]
[BIDDERS groan]
[AUDIENCE screaming]
[BIG MADAM]
Oh, wow...
[AIDE B]
Let's get out of here, Madam!
What is Juzo doing here?
[MADAM A]
It's the doves.
[MATSURI]
Move in.
Attention, all personnel.
Mission 1 is to exterminate
the ghouls in the building.
Big Madam, in particular,
must be eliminated at any cost.
We anticipate intervention
from Aogiri Tree.
But we can't let this
opportunity pass us by.
Hear that, Mado Squad?
[MATSURI]
Mission 2 is search and rescue.
May I remind you that
your top priority
is the safety of the
abducted civilians.
[MATSURI] I don't want to
mislead them, at the same time,
I don't want any trouble later.
Civilian lives may
be top priority,
but the whole purpose
of this mission
is to get Big Madam.
[NAKI] Hm. Okay, that's
the enemy down there.
Ya see 'em, Gagi and Guge?
[GAGI]
Gagi.
[GUGE]
Guge.
There are a lot of them.
I'll contact my gang--
Would you quit
runnin' your mouth
for once, old lady?
Those who strike first...
...get the last laugh!
Hope you're watchin', Boss!
Wherever you are right now!
What in the world
is wrong with you?
[INVESTIGATOR A]
We have engagement at the front!
It's one of the White Suits!
Naki from Aogiri!
Requesting backup
immediately-- [screams]
Tateshima and Isai Squad,
come with me!
We'll keep the
White Suits at bay!
[BOTH]
Roger that!
[AYATO]
How does it look outside?
[HINAMI] They've got
teams assembled not only
at the front of the building
but on the sides as well.
[AYATO]
They've got us surrounded.
Tell Naki and Miza
they need to open a hole
in the dove's cordon.
Meanwhile, I'm gonna
protect Big Madam.
I'll send them the order.
[TORSO] Wha-What should
I do? Ayato, wait!
You need to come
with me, Mr. Saeki.
It really is you, Juzo.
Mama--
[KANAE]
The one-eyed ghoul.
I could take advantage
of this confusion.
Matsumae.
You can go on ahead.
There's something
I need to take care of.
And I can handle it alone.
Quinx Squad. Arriving
at the entrance.
Aogiri sighted. Engaging now!
[HAISE grunts]
How ya like that?
I'm comin'!
I'm guessin' that's
Haise Sasaki?
[ATO] Yeah, he fights
like Investigator Arima.
Enemy has been cleared
from the entrance. Proceed to--
We s'posed to be scared
of this twitchy skinhead?
Well, he does have big kokakus.
[INVESTIGATORS grunt]
[MATSURI]
Keep advancing, Sasaki.
[HAISE]
But, sir.
Go on, we'll handle him.
You sure about that, Ato?
[HAISE]
C'mon, guys. Let's go!
--[SHIRAZU] Right!
--[URIE] Right.
Those with Ukakus, back me up,
but don't hit your allies.
Roger that!
[NUTCRACKER] ♪ Two-hundred
million, and all for me! ♪
[TORSO]
Toru.
[AUCTION-GOER 4H]
We can't go out the front!
Oh, no! What's going on?
[BOTH grunt]
[NUTCRACKER yelps]
[grunts]
[footsteps]
[NUTCRACKER]
My 200,000,000!
[JUZO]
This rabbit's pretty strong
but I've gotta take him down.
It'll be tough without Jason.
[MUTSUKI panting]
[UTA whispering] Your plan
failed. Help isn't coming.
[MUTSUKI]
Why would he lie to me?
Not only that, but how'd
he know about the operation
in the first place?
Guten abend !
What are you doing down here.
Mein kleines katzchen ?
[INVESTIGATOR I]
That's Naki. He's a tough one.
[INVESTIGATOR J]
How many men have we lost?
[INVESTIGATOR K]
Too many to count!
[NUMA]
I'll get him!
[yells]
[INVESTIGATOR J]
No! Numa!
[INVESTIGATOR I]
Wait, is that--?
The S-rated Three Blades!
Glad you could
finally make it, Miza!
[MIZA]
Don't use my name, you bonehead!
[MIZA cackles]
[NAKI, MIZA grunting, yelling]
Seems we're outmatched.
Yeah, if this keeps up...
[cackles]
I've got ya!
[NAKI] I know I've
seen your face before.
But I'll be damned if
I can remember your name.
Stand back, men.
I'll handle this monster.
Don't go too far ahead!
Come back, Shibashi!
[SHIBASHI] You old-timers
have had the spotlight
long enough,
subordinate-killer Shimoguchi.
Now it's my turn.
[ROMA gasps]
[SHIBASHI] The next
generation's about to create
a new age. One where
we're in power.
[groans]
[SHIBASHI]
Hmph.
[ROMA]
Please...
I'm begging you.
Please spare my life.
[laughs]
[groans]
[ROMA]
Delicious!
Dammit, Shibashi!
I tried to warn you!
[ROMA]
Uh-oh!
You won't get away!
[gasps]
[ROMA giggles]
[UTA]
Hello there, Mr. Hirako.
[VOICE A] The doves are
already in the grand hall.
[VOICE D] Multiple Aogiri
soldiers are unreachable!
[VOICE B]
Get Big Madam to the basement
under the stage.
[VOICE C] There's a spine-user
at Naki's location.
[HINAMI]
A spine-user?
[AOGIRI SOLDIER A]
Miss Yotsume.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Have the Aogiri members
in the grand hall
pull out and head to the roof.
We'll regroup there and
then assist Naki and Miza.
Rabbit, on the other hand,
won't need assistance.
The remaining guard detail
is ordered to protect.
And find Saeki.
Where could he have gone?
[grunts]
[KANAE]
Uberraschung !
Master Shu...
This will bring you back to me.
I've finally found it!
Oh, glorreicher tag !
[KANAE groans]
[TORSO screams]
[TORSO grunting]
I'm so glad you're okay.
[gasping]
[TORSO]
No, Toru!
Wait! It's me, Torso!
You can't run!
[TORSO]
What have you done?
[screams]
You lowly trash!
You dare to defy me?
Who do you think you are?
[KANAE]
Scheisse ! Damn you!
Why did you have to go
and get in my way?
If I don't catch her,
I'll be back to kill you.
Might as well just
lie there and wait.
[TORSO]
Toru. My Toru!
[KANOU] Hm. It would appear the
battle is in full swing now.
I wonder what'll happen
if we drop the Owl
into the mix.
What do you think, Eto?
Good idea.
Time to go. Ready, Takizawa?
I'm so hungry.
[INVESTIGATOR O groans]
Whoa, thanks for the save,
Investigator Ato, sir!
You've got my back,
I've got yours.
[ATO] The fact that
Sasaki and his squad
were ordered to go ahead.
Means that their combat
rating is higher than ours.
Honestly, it's a
hard pill to swallow.
[ATO] There's no denying
they're amazing.
Their potential is limitless.
All of their newfangled
techniques and abilities
are leaving old fogies
like me in the dust.
Have you completely
lost your mind, Marude?
You can't do this--
he's just a child!
I'm not crazy.
This boy's different.
[ATO] It doesn't matter whether
you're religious or not,
everyone comes into
contact with God.
It's the moment when
you come face-to-face
with overwhelming talent.
I know, because...
I have seen God.
I have seen the
unfairness of God.
[ATO]
I may be an ordinary man,
ignored by both gods and devils.
But with enough experience.
I can still amount
to something decent!
Damn you!
Kinda reminds me of a
freshly-picked pineapple.
[clock ticking]
[KANAE]
Your wound is already healed?
[SEIDO]
Ahhh...
[gasps]
A delicious human nugget. Hehe.
Like jam.
[screams]
[SEIDO]
Oh wow! Nice block!
[HAISE]
I can't hold him!
[silence]
[static]