[INVESTIGATOR A]
The Lunar Eclipse building
is almost completely
secured, sir.
Most of the remaining
ghouls are relegated
to the top few floors now.
[MATSURI] As the chief
coordinating officer,
I'll get the lion's
share of the credit.
Didn't even have to
stick my neck out.
[gasps]
[MATSURI grunts]
Damn it all.
That must be...
...the One-Eyed Owl.
[HAISE grunts]
[HAISE groans]
[ETO]
Kaneki!
Haise!
[ETO laughs]
That was just a love tap.
Kisho Arima would've
dodged it easily.
But not this Sasaki fellow.
Apparently, he's a real
glutton for pain. Right?
[HAISE gasping]
Hey. Wake up, little piddler.
I want you to dance for me now.
Dance so hard that your
bladder shakes loose.
Get up, and quickly.
You have so little time.
You are about to die, after all.
You know Master Shu is watching.
[HAISE groaning]
[KANAE yells]
[HAISE screams]
[groans]
[gagging]
[ETO laughs]
[ETO]
Very good.
[KANAE]
I am loved, I am loved.
I am loved. I am loved.
I am loved.
I am loved!
I am loved! I am loved!
I am lo--!
Hey, I thought you were
gonna save me, Haise.
[crunch]
Just shut up...
--[KANEKI] My salvation.
--[HAISE] ...and die, Kaneki.
[KANEKI]
My death.
I never really wanted
to find happiness.
[HAISE]
Die...
[KANEKI]
I don't mind disappearing.
I wish I'd died a long time ago.
So kill me, Haise.
[HAISE]
Die! Die!
It's for the best,
you son of a bitch.
[HAISE gasps]
[KANEKI]
Hey, don't you remember?
[KANEKI] I used to get
beaten all the time...
...by someone I loved.
For childishly pestering her.
[KANEKI]
I'm sorry, Mom. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
That's... my mom?
[KANEKI]
Please don't hit me. I'm sorry!
[KANEKI] I loved Mom more
than anything, you know?
So when it happened...
I was happy.
I thought I'd get to see
the underground flower
garden, and the reaper.
I was gonna get to be like Mom.
Like a worm.
[KANEKI]
But, then... I didn't die.
You mean, you wanted to die?
Yep. I sure did.
That's why this time,
before I die,
I wanna do something
really special,
to make everybody love me.
And then go out with a bang!
[HAISE]
So you think
that this could be
your salvation?
[KANEKI]
Mm-hm.
[HAISE] His salvation is nothing
but sleep and sweet dreams.
I'm the sweet dream.
He'll wake up
and cry for a moment,
and I'll be gone.
It was a mistake,
to think I could want
something for myself.
Can you do it?
[HAISE]
Mm.
[KANEKI]
Night night, Haise.
I'm done.
No more dreaming.
[slice]
[screams]
So, you're awake.
[KANEKI]
Yeah, that's right.
Now would you shut the hell up?
[footsteps]
[INVESTIGATOR B]
We have to stop the bleeding.
[INVESTIGATOR C]
Right.
[INVESTIGATOR D]
Know who this one was?
There's not enough
face left to ID him.
[IHEI]
Oh, hey, Mister Kori.
You've got to try
this melon bread!
[IHEI laughs]
[UI whimpering]
[INVESTIGATOR E]
Special Investigator!
We found more wounded.
[UI]
I'm coming.
I... couldn't save him.
[gasps]
What happened here?
[FURUTA sobbing]
[FURUTA]
Investigator Kijima...
[sobbing]
[laughing]
[KANAE screams]
[gasps]
[KANAE gags]
[footsteps]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Kaneki, is that you?
Yeah.
Hey, Tsukiyama.
[TSUKIYAMA whimpers]
[gasps]
[retches]
[KANEKI]
It's all right.
[ETO] Thanks for the
cold-blooded reveille drama.
Though I still wonder...
...who's stronger between
you and Kisho Arima.
I'd say you're the
cold-blooded one.
Go to hell.
[SHIRAZU] Wonder how
Mister Sass is holding up.
On our end,
Urie's pretty beat up.
Mutsuki and Saiko are all right.
And beyond that?
I don't really know.
I gotta do what I can,
or everyone will die!
[SHIRAZU]
Kuramoto, Kuroiwa,
Urie, Mutsuki, and Saiko.
And me, too.
[SHIRAZU] I can't die
and leave Haru alone.
[SHIRAZU]
More...
More.
[SHIRAZU]
More!
More, more!
More, more, more, more, more,
more, more, more, more!
I need more!
[SHIRAZU yells]
Shirazu!
[SHIRAZU]
Die, you ugly freak!
Urie!
You think that was enough?!
[SHIRAZU]
If you can recover from that,
then I never stood a chance.
[yelling]
[URIE]
Shirazu!
[yelling]
[NORO]
Kuzen. Are you sure?
[KUZEN]
Yes.
Her name's Eto.
It means "sustained by love."
[NORO]
Nice to meet you, Eto.
My name's Noro.
I'll be going on ahead, Eto.
[URIE gasping]
[URIE]
Shirazu!
[URIE] Shirazu! C'mon,
man! Hang in there.
Shirazu!
[SHIRAZU] Bagged myself
a big one this time, huh?
[URIE] His guts are destroyed.
Can he heal from that?
[SHIRAZU]
Where's Mr. Sass?
I wanna see him. Where is he?
The senior investigator's
on his way. Just relax.
And breathe.
Shirazu, we need to
get you to a hospital.
[URIE] Given our
recuperative abilities,
this wound is no big deal.
With proper treatment
and plenty of rest,
you'll be as good
as new in no time.
Don't worry.
What if... I end up
dying from this?
Then who will--?
Don't even talk like that!
You'll be just fine.
[URIE] Look, you're healing
already, just... hang on!
[URIE]
Shit! Where are the damn medics?
[SHIRAZU]
Red-bean soup...
[URIE]
Hm? Say what?
When I gave you
that red bean soup,
I knew you hated the flavor.
[SHIRAZU chuckles]
I'm gonna get you back for that.
Now stop wasting
your breath, buzz cut.
Haru...
Your sister?
That's right.
Your sister needs you.
She's waiting for you.
[SHIRAZU]
Urie... Saiko...
Mutsuki...
You here?
Why aren't any of you
saying anything?
[inaudible]
We're here. We--
[SHIRAZU]
Guys, where'd you go?
C'mon, say something.
[URIE]
Shirazu!
Are you there?
Where is everyone? It's...
[MUTSUKI]
You're not alone, Shirazu!
We're right here!
[SHIRAZU]
It's gotten so quiet...
Don't die!
[SHIRAZU]
So, this is what dying's like.
Shirazu!
[SHIRAZU]
I'm scared.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Don't be afraid.
We're all right here.
Yonebayashi, and Mutsuki,
and me. We're with you!
[SHIRAZU]
Haru...
[gasps]
Who's gonna take care of her?
[inaudible]
[URIE]
Yeah, think about her.
You have to keep raising money
to get her cured, don't you?
So what's the point
of checking out now?
You just put down an SS-rated.
I bet that bounty'll
be more than 10--
No, more like 20 mil!
And the credit--
The credit's all yours, Shirazu!
So, please!
[URIE]
Shirazu...?
No, don't go!
[wails]
[URIE] You son of a bitch,
you can't die!
Why did you come here?
To impede? Destroy?
To kill time?
[ETO]
The last one, I suppose.
I was curious about who would
kill whom between Tsukiyama,
Kanae, and the ghoul
that once went by "Kaneki."
I wanted to see in person.
[KANEKI]
Yoshimura.
Kuzen, your father.
He told me about you.
He wanted me to try
and save you.
[ETO laughs] What made him
think I need saving?
Perhaps you're not so
cold-blooded after all, Kaneki.
Is that pity I see in your eyes?
[KANEKI grunts]
I missed her.
You punk.
[KANEKI] I'll admit that
I liked the old man.
But, that's hardly enough
of a reason to save you.
You're really just
a piece of trash.
That was so rude!
You're a prideful little
idiot, you know that?!
I'll devour you!
[ETO]
Everything is swirling...
Once I get like this,
there's no stopping me!
[ETO growls]
[ETO grunting]
Kaneki!
[ETO] Hey! Come back and I'll
raise you as my own!
[ETO]
Hey!
Why are you running from me?
[ETO]
Uh?
[ETO yells]
[ETO yelps]
[ETO] You know, I've come
to really like you.
We are birds of a
feather, after all.
[ETO laughs]
How thrilling.
[laughs]
I love you, Ken Kaneki.
What an honor,
Miss Takatsuki.
[INVESTIGATOR F]
Can we even call this a win?
[INVESTIGATOR G]
Dunno.
[footsteps]
[INVESTIGATOR F]
Special Investigator Washu,
why are you on the front line?
[MATSURI]
If there's anyone among you
still capable of fighting,
then come with me to the roof.
The One-Eyed Owl's here.
Takeomi Kuroiwa.
Also,
Kuki Urie.
Can you fight?
[MATSURI]
Urie, did you hear me?
[URIE]
You don't feel a thing, do you?
About what?
[URIE]
The dead men lying at your feet.
Do they not mean
anything to you?!
No. It's always surprising
to see who cracks in battle.
First Class Urie,
I actually thought you
showed some promise.
Wait a second.
I hear a ghoul feeding.
[UI]
S-Senior Investigator Sasaki?
Is that you?
[KANEKI]
Excuse me.
I took a lot of hits while
I was fighting the Owl.
I needed to replenish.
Wait, so--
Are you saying, you dispatched
the Owl by yourself?
Not quite.
I came pretty close,
but then it ran away.
It's probably still alive.
I see.
[KANEKI] Looks like Rose and
Aogiri Tree were connected.
Just as we suspected.
[KANEKI] The wounded you
see are Tsukiyama's men.
I didn't have time
to finish them.
Until now.
[TSUKIYAMA groans]
Should I go ahead
and dispatch him?
Yeah, and I'll dispose
of the other one.
[TSUKIYAMA] Kaneki, is this
truly the path you're choosing?
No...
Shu...
Master...
[KANAE grunts]
[gasps]
[KANAE]
Master Shu!
This is farewell, Tsukiyama.
[KANAE]
Master Shu.
Let me go, Kanae.
I want you to live.
I'm afraid I can't do that, sir.
This body of mine is broken.
I'll die soon.
But, I will still protect you.
You are everything to me.
But, if... I could just
ask one indulgence...
Here, at the end.
I wish only to hear my name,
my true name, from your lips.
Master Shu.
How I have dreamed
that one day I might hold
you to my bosom like this.
Father, Mutter,
Nathanael and Arnold.
I beg your forgiveness.
I beg for yours
as well, Master Shu.
I've shamed you.
I fell in love with you,
and I never had the right.
It's not shameful.
And no one will
chasten you for it...
...Karren.
[KANAE whimpers]
[KANAE]
This life is cruel.
For I was unable
to live as myself.
This life is wondrous.
For I was able to die as myself.
Ah. Is it fair
for me to be this happy?
[SAIKO cries]
[URIE]
Now you show.
Shirazu asked for you,
but you weren't here.
Where were you?
You weren't here,
and now he's dead!
So, this is my fault?
[gasps]
His life wasn't mine
to defend in this fight.
It was yours.
"All the detriment in this world
stems from a lack of
individual ability."
Don't blame me.
Blame your own incompetence.
[URIE cries]
[cries]
[crying continues]
[INVESTIGATORS scream]
[KANEKI]
Arima, are you angry?
Or are you just... sad?
[KANEKI]
Right up to the end,
I never understood you.