[TSUKIYAMA]
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go!
--[screams]
--Master Shu!
[screaming]
[crash]
[MAIDS gasp]
[MAID A]
Master Shu!
Where do you think you're
going in your state?
[TSUKIYAMA sobs]
Isn't it obvious?
I have to go... see Kaneki.
I have to see him!
[KANAE] When Ken Kaneki
lost his memories,
he was given the
name Haise Sasaki.
He is not the man
you knew before.
Master.
I'm begging you, please,
don't forget that.
He may look like the man
you once called a friend,
but he's currently a
ghoul investigator.
He's a threat to our kind,
therefore you must--
[TSUKIYAMA]
Kaneki!
[KANAE]
Master Shu! Come back!
[TSUKIYAMA]
You need to relax, Kanae.
I assure you,
this will go as planned.
There's no way my sweet Kaneki
could ever forget me!
We'll spend the day together
catching up, Kaneki, dear.
--It's been too long.
--[KANAE] Master Shu!
Let's make up for lost time!
[TSUKIYAMA groans]
[PEDESTRIANS murmur]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Ka... neki...
[HAISE gasping]
Uh... Are you all right, sir?
I like your crazy suit.
Excuse us.
Are you sure he's okay?
My heart has been broken.
How could he forget?
[KANAE] He risked exposing
himself to the doves.
He's not in his right mind.
[UTA]
Welcome, everyone.
[footsteps]
That guy's a ghoul, right?
Sure looks like one.
Shh!
[HAISE]
Okay guys, Mr. Uta's
gonna be making
masks for us today.
[MUTSUKI]
Masks?
[SHIRAZU]
What kinda masks?
You mean like the
ones ghouls wear?
[HAISE] Mm-hm. I want
us to go undercover.
[SHIRAZU] First, you made us
dress like chicks, and now this?
We already have
abilities like theirs,
but with these masks
we can wear their uniforms.
He can even make it look like
both our eyes are kakugans.
[SHIRAZU]
What good is that gonna do us?
It'll help us infiltrate
their world.
I like your jagged teeth,
man, they look cool.
You got a girlfriend?
Well no, not at the moment.
But you like girls, right?
Is there anyone that you're
interested in?
Uh. That's kinda personal.
That scowl tells me
you're a very serious guy.
Is it cool if I make your
mask really weird?
Why would you wanna do that?
Because I think it'd be funny.
[URIE]
What the hell?
This guy sure looks
like a ghoul to me.
We should've run a check
on him before we came here.
Y'know, you remind me of
a mischievous little elf.
I get that a lot.
The name's Saiko.
So, what're your
favorite things?
[SAIKO]
I'm really into food,
video games, sleeping,
candy, manga, and anime.
Love the eyepatch,
looks good on you.
You like it?
Um, I guess so. Kinda.
You have such a lovely face.
A little full, but you've got
excellent bone structure...
[MUTSUKI]
That voice.
I've heard it somewhere before.
Listen, Mr. Sass.
I get what you're tryin' to do,
but have you gotten the brass's
approval for this mission?
Not yet, that's the next step.
[UI]
Absolutely not.
You want to go masquerading
as a ghoul of all things?
This makes me question
your character
as an investigator, Sasaki.
[HAISE]
But, sir.
Tell me. Where would
your allegiance lie
if you lost control
in that situation?
I understand, sir.
Please excuse me.
[door clicks]
[FURA] Personally, I thought his
mask plan was a good idea.
That's not the image
we want to convey--
we're champions of justice.
[FURA]
I don't know if I'd go that far.
Give me one of those.
[UI]
You sure, Investigator Fura?
If your wife finds out,
she'll be pissed.
That's why I only smoke
'em at the office.
[FURA] Tell me something, do you
really think it's a bad idea?
Or are you just determined
to keep Sasaki from
earning any merit?
The man's a loose cannon.
He's dangerous.
[IHEI]
Arima! What's with Haise?
[HAISE yells]
[UI] He exceeded his
kagune usage limit.
That idiot.
Kori. I'll handle this.
At his core,
he's a ghoul.
[DOG barking]
[MIRUMO]
I heard that Shu
actually left the
house this afternoon.
I'm glad he's feeling better.
[KANAE]
There's no choice.
This is for the best.
Master Shu's appetite is finally
starting to straighten out.
[MIRUMO] It's awfully quiet
tonight. Where is he?
[KANAE] In his room, apparently
researching something.
[TSUKIYAMA]
He doesn't remember anything.
I won't stand for it.
There must be a way
to jog his memory.
Perhaps a game of squash
would do the trick.
Heh. Ah, those were the days.
[SERVANT A]
Master Mirumo!
A message on the CCG website?
To Rose?
[KIJIMA]
Hey there, Rose!
I had a formal greeting prepared
but for convenience's sake,
we're just going to
call you "Rose." Okay?
As you know, we captured
your colleague the other day,
and I thought you might like a
report on his current condition.
We roughed him up a bit,
but he's still alive, for now.
We've attempted to interrogate
him numerous times,
but he doesn't seem
to wanna talk to us.
I can't imagine why.
Since he wouldn't talk,
I figured he didn't need
his tongue anymore.
[KIJIMA]
The thing is, once I cut it out,
I realized he had other body
parts he doesn't need.
I'll be getting rid
of those, too.
I'm the only person who knows
where your buddy's
being held captive.
For the record,
I'm Shiki Kijima.
And now that you've
seen my face,
I'm certain you'll
never forget me. Heh.
You probably wanna kill me, huh?
Come by anytime and try.
I'll be waiting for you, Rose.
[UI] What do you think
you're doing, Kijima?
The general public has
access to the CCG site.
You do realize that video is now
being viewed by civilians.
Yes, sir!
It's quite popular. The number
of views has been climbing.
When they see you torturing
their man, Rose will retaliate.
What were you thinking,
egging them on like that?
Do you have any idea of the
danger you've put yourself in?
I'm well aware I've
jeopardized my safety.
The thing is,
I'm not afraid of dying,
so I honestly
couldn't care less.
You're violating the
anti-ghoul act, Kijima.
Yeah.
Anyway, I have a meeting with
the board of inquiry in a bit.
So, if you'll excuse me,
I must be going.
I'll see you later, unless I end
up getting kicked off the team.
Crazy bastard.
[SHIRAZU]
Mr. Sass.
Have you seen the video?
Yeah, it was hard to watch.
I don't care who he is,
that's too cruel.
It's just...
There has to be some other way.
Maybe...
But in the end,
they'll still be killed.
What?
[SHIRAZU]
It's nothin'.
[TSUKIYAMA] I feel as though I'm
responsible for Yuma's capture.
I can tell that Aliza is
pretty broken up about it.
You've been working so hard.
Diligently harvesting
day after day,
simply to procure
sustenance for me.
Master. Please forgive
me if I'm out of line,
but you didn't force
us to do so,
we did it of our own volition.
The only reason that
Yuma was captured
is because we botched
the mission.
By no means should you feel
responsible, Master Shu.
Matsumae. Mairo.
I need your help.
There must be a way for us
to get Aliza's smile back.
[KANAE] You've come up
with a rescue plan?
Yes. And the key man
will be Ken Kaneki.
I haven't quite worked out
all of the details as of yet.
However, we can use
his investigator status
to our favor.
I don't know, Master.
Are you sure he'll listen
to what you have to say?
What if he refuses to help?
[TSUKIYAMA]
If it were anyone else,
it would be difficult
to convince them.
But with Kaneki,
it'll be pas de problème .
I've no doubt he
will gladly accept
my request for assistance.
As long as we can get his
memories back, all is well.
Tout va bien !
My dearest Kaneki.
He probably doesn't even want
to be a ghoul investigator.
[KANAE] I'm glad to see
Master Shu so optimistic.
Nevertheless, it worries me.
[CHIE] Oh, I see. Yeah, I
figured that might happen.
Okay, then.
Here's what I'm gonna
need you to do,
go ahead and give him
the second photograph.
All right, then.
[KANAE] I don't need that little
mauschen barking orders at me.
Master Shu always come first.
His wish is my gebot .
We'll be together,
until the end.
Glorreich .
[footsteps]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Hello there.
Huh?
[HAISE]
Oh. Feeling better?
Yes, I am, thanks for asking.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Ah, my sweet Kaneki.
[HAISE] You look much
healthier than before.
I am. May I?
[HAISE]
Sure, be my guest.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Oh, Kaneki.
I can't believe you
don't remember me.
After everything we've
been through.
Do you enjoy reading?
[HAISE]
Uh, yeah.
That's usually how I
spend my free time,
with my nose in a book.
[TSUKIYAMA]
That's it!
I enjoy reading, as well.
Have you ever read any
of Sen Takatsuki's works?
I think you'd enjoy them.
[HAISE]
Yeah.
[TSUKIYAMA]
My dearest Kaneki...
I know you better than you
even know yourself right now.
I've read her work.
She's a talented author,
but her books aren't for me.
Really?
I get attached to
characters when I read,
but in her novels, she'll kill
off anyone, even the main.
It's just too painful.
Oh. Is that so?
[TSUKIYAMA]
Now, now.
No need to get upset.
Calmez-vous .
[TSUKIYAMA] As you've seen,
I'm rather frail.
My condition makes it difficult
for me to make friends
with anyone around my age.
I would love to talk books
with you again sometime.
[SAIKO]
Maman!
[BOTH gasp]
[TSUKIYAMA] The investigator
brats. Such a nuisance.
Guess that's my cue.
Time for me to get back to work.
Glad you're feeling better.
Take care of yourself.
Wait!
[KANAE]
Master Shu.
It's okay. No need to worry.
There'll be other opportunities.
[gasps]
[SHIRAZU panting]
[HAISE] Hurry, Shirazu!
We're late for the meeting!
[MUTSUKI]
Hey, Teach!
[TSUKIYAMA] Those stupid
kids are in the way.
I'll never be alone with Kaneki.
[KANAE]
Look at this, Master Shu.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Kaneki!
Hori?
Of course!
She is such a good friend.
I dare say she understands me
more than anyone
else in the world.
[TSUKIYAMA] Hori, would
you tell me something?
What is a "Gourmet" anyway?
[CHIE] I dunno. You'll have
to figure it out yourself.
Here's a question for you.
Would you ever die for your
ingredients, Tsukiyama?
[laughs] After all this time,
I'd like nothing more than to
chat up that little mouse.
I can't help but wonder
what happened to the others.
The Anteiku folks.
Little Hinami and the rest.
It's been so long.
They probably don't even know
Kaneki's alive and well.
And...
I'm sure they would
love to see him.
[KANAE]
Master Shu.
I will see to it that you have
your time alone with him.
[KANAE]
Are you with Aogiri Tree?
If so, I have a job for you.
[URIE] Do you think the other
squads are making any progress?
Without any leads? I doubt it.
They're being cautious.
The video's got 'em on edge.
I guess we'll just have to
wait for crazy old Kijima
to be attacked.
[HAISE]
Don't be rude.
[URIE]
Huh? Is that...
...the guy from the auction?
[HAISE]
Where are you guys going?!
[HOGURO]
Mr. fancy-pants is on the move.
[GRAVE ROBBER] I suppose we
should get going, too.
[footsteps]
There's no gettin' away from us!
[URIE] This is my chance
to test my skills.
[KANAE] You never should've
left your babysitter.
Stirb jetzt !
[HAISE]
Shirazu! Urie!
[gasps]
[HOGURO]
Are they the ones we're after?
Look at 'em, Shosei!
They're nothin'
but a bunch of kids.
It's the White Suits.
What're Aogiri
ghouls doin' here?
[HOGURO]
Man, what a letdown.
If I'd known, I never woulda
brought all these men.
[SHOSEI]
Hoguro.
This is an incredibly
important job for us.
In this case, it's better
to be safe than sorry.
[HOGURO] True. We'll get
this job done in no time.
And we'll do it for Boss Naki!
Teach! I've got you covered!
I'm fine. Go help
Shirazu and Urie.
[MUTSUKI]
Roger that!
You're comin' with me, Saiko!
Okay!
[HOGURO]
Hang on.
I can't remember
whether this guy
was even in the photo or not.
[SHOSEI]
I dunno. He may have been.
[HOGURO]
You've got our attention.
So, what's the job?
[KANAE] I need you to get rid of
some investigators for me.
Your targets are in this photo.
Can you do that?
You want us to off four doves?
[KANAE]
I'll pay you upfront.
[ALL gasp]
And for each one of
them that you kill,
I'll pay you double that amount.
[SHOSEI]
Hm...
[HOGURO]
Screw it! I can't remember.
Let's just go ahead
and kill him, too!
Poor Maman.
Don't worry, Saiko,
he's gonna be fine.
Shirazu and Urie need our
help more than he does.
[TORSO]
Toru!
Uh!
[TORSO]
It's really you!
[MUTSUKI]
Torso...
[TORSO]
Oh, wow!
Did you change your hair?
It looks lovely!
That style really suits you...
This guy's trouble.
Find someplace to hide
and stay there!
[MUTSUKI grunts]
[TORSO groans]
[MUTSUKI yells]
[TORSO] You were strong before,
but now you're even stronger!
Ah, you're so incredible!
My beloved Toru
really is the greatest!
I'm going to make you mine, even
if I have to sacrifice it all!
Are we forming a connection
through your blades?
Maybe it's just me, but I find
this terribly exciting!
Yes, that's it, Toru!
Connect with me some more!
Stab me, stab me, stab me,
stab me, stab me, stab me,
stab me, stab me, stab me!
[TORSO yelps]
[grunts]
[GRAVE ROBBER]
Are you all right, Torso?
[TORSO]
Toru.
T-Toru.
Toru...
[GRAVE ROBBER]
Jeez, you're useless.
[TORSO]
T-Tor...
[TORSO groaning]
[MUTSUKI yells]
[MUTSUKI]
That's not a kagune.
It can't be...
Is that a quinque?
[KANAE grunts]
[SHIRAZU groans]
[SHIRAZU]
My kakuho! Crap!
Now I can't produce my kagune!
What're you waiting for, idiot?
Use your quinque!
[SHIRAZU]
That's right. My quinque!
[NUTCRACKER screams]
[SHIRAZU gasping]
[retches]
There goes our fearless captain.
[URIE]
I can take care of him
all by myself!
[gasps]
[KANAE]
Damn! He got me!
[yells]
[KANAE]
What happened?
He's so much stronger
than he was before!
[KANAE gasps]
[gasping]
I could snap your neck!
[KANAE groaning]
Bastard.
[URIE]
He got away.
But that's fine for now.
As long as I've had
the sensation.
[footsteps]
[URIE]
C'mon, let's go.
This is a trap.
She's fast! [gasps]
I'll give it one last push!
[MUTSUKI]
I've got you!
[GRAVE ROBBER]
Interesting.
We're both bikakus.
Whaddya say we see
who's stronger?
Allow me to introduce myself,
my name is Grave Robber.
And I'm about to take you
quinque from you!
[MUTSUKI grunting]
[MUTSUKI]
Oh, crap!
[GRAVE ROBBER grunts]
[URIE]
Stand back! Let me handle this!
Now, Shirazu!
[URIE]
Get to work, dumbass!
[growls]
You're goin' down, bitch!
[GRAVE ROBBER grunting]
They have an ukaku, too?
Time for me to get out of here.
Hey Toru, are you okay?
[MUTSUKI]
Y-Yeah.
Let's head back.
[SAIKO] Mutsie told me to
find someplace to hide,
so I did, but, how
am I supposed to know
when it's safe for me
to come out again?
I never should've left,
I should be fighting beside him.
[gasps]
Wow. You sure are a cutie.
[whimpers]
You're like a plump
little manju bun.
[SHIKORAE]
I bet you're nice and spongy.
Oh yeah, nice and spongy.
I've got you now.
Ya better not move,
or I'll snap it!
Someone help me.
[gasps]
[URIE]
What the hell happened here?
[HOGURO]
This mission is hopeless.
We've gotta retreat!
[HOGURO, SHOSEI grunt]
[MUTSUKI]
Teach!
[HAISE] Hey, guys!
Is everyone all right?
Yeah. More or less.
Any idea why they came after us?
Afraid not.
But now,
I think Aogiri Tree and Rose
may be connected somehow.
[gasps] Where's Saiko?
[SHIKORAE]
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
So nice and spongy.
Nice and spongy!
[laughs]
Can't wait anymore. Hungry!
[SHIKORAE]
Ouch!
[SAIKO]
Uh.
Thank you, Mister.
Uh...
[HAISE]
Saiko!
Thank goodness!
You okay?
[SAIKO]
Maman.
That big man in black saved me.
Uh...?
[clock ticking]
[ETO] Why, hello there.
It's Kanae, right?
[MIRUMO] Please allow us to
do so until the very end.
[KIJIMA] I must admit.
This is quite touching to see.
[SHIRAZU] Investigator
Sasaki said that, too.
[ASADA] We all came
as quickly as we could.
[TSUNEYOSHI] You are hereby
commanded to carry out
"Operation
Dispatch Tsukiyama."
[UI]
Don't move.
[static]