[TOUKA]
Hey, Ken.
Huh?
Good morning. Coffee?
[SHIO] S, A, A, S, S
plus, SS, S plus, and S!
I could make special
investigator in no time.
[YUSA] Stop tallying up
their potential credit.
[HOGURO]
Whoa, what is this?
What the hell are
these doves doing here?
We're here to protect Kaneki,
not to start a fight.
We won't make trouble.
We came to fulfill
Kisho's dying wish.
They aren't our enemies.
[NAKI]
They might not be yours.
[KURONA]
What kind of meeting is this?
What business does the
staff of a coffee shop have
with the remnants
of Aogiri Tree?
Whatever.
As long as I get to kill
Dr. Kanou, I'll help you.
Look, Kaneki.
When Rushima fell, your people
came and they saved my life.
[MIZU]
So, I'll hear you out, at least.
What is it you're after?
My goal is aligned
with the wishes
of the last One-Eyed King.
I want ghouls and humans
to come to an understanding.
[laughs]
I expected something foolish,
yet I'm still surprised.
So, how do you plan
to bring about peace
between humans and ghouls?
We'll talk it out.
[KURONA]
Are you out of your mind?
The reason that
we've been killing
each other for so long
is because no one's
tried to compromise.
Our peoples can coexist.
As a ghoul who was once
human, I'm living proof.
The key is that
we start a dialogue.
But I doubt they'll come
to the table just like that.
So we'll force them
into a situation
where they have to negotiate.
Right here, I declare the
founding of an organization.
One dedicated to this cause.
As for this group's name,
I'll call it Goat.
Tch!
Ridiculous.
Take Hirako,
I fought your boss.
He killed my sister.
She's Touka and Ayato's mom.
They loved her as I did.
I'm being told now that
he was sympathetic to ghouls.
Yet if he were
standing in front of me,
I'm sure I would
still want to kill him.
[HIRAKO] Everyone around
that guy worked their butts off
in the hopes that he might toss
a callous compliment their way.
That happens to be
the reason I'm here now.
I've wanted him to
acknowledge me for a long time.
Kisho Arima is dead.
You're free to hold
onto your grudge,
but you'll never get
another chance to act on it,
and doing so wouldn't bring
your sister back, Renji Yomo.
We believe in the successor
Kisho chose for himself.
And you believe in a
person called Ken Kaneki.
Isn't that enough for now?
Remember the goal here,
we can reach an understanding
without having to agree.
Not on everything.
Well in that case,
it's doable.
Take!
Turn on the TV!
[NEWSCASTER] This is live
footage from the 22nd Ward.
The local CCG headquarters
is billowing with smoke,
after reports of an attack
from an unknown group.
Similar reports are coming in
from neighboring wards, as well!
Will it look like we did it?
[HIRAKO]
First they killed the Washus,
now they're after the bureaus.
It looks like they aim to clean
out the whole organization
in conjunction with the
appearance of the One-Eyed King.
I see.
So this is how our enemy works.
[NISHIO]
She has a hell of a fever.
Wound might get infected.
No. I just...
And she's barely been conscious.
If this keeps up, she'll--
There has to be some
way you can help her!
Well, I can't help at all
if you choke me to death!
[NICO]
Oh hi, Banjo.
You look well.
Long time, huh?
[BANJO]
Nico? How'd you get here?
[chuckles]
[NICO]
When imprisoning a clown,
you need to shut everything up
just as tight as you can.
Roma sent out a little
SOS and I picked it up.
Check it out.
A kagune worm.
Did you come here to save Roma?
Oh, I'm sure
she'll be all right.
I just thought I would stop by
and make eyes at your new king.
[BANJO]
All right.
[NICO]
So about this woman,
do you want her to die, or...?
Are you implying that you
could help us fix her up?
[NICO]
Not a chance.
That said, I do know of a way.
[NISHIO]
A way?
Yeah, and it's very simple!
You should take
her to see a doctor.
[KANEKI]
Hi, Naki.
Hey, Naki! Cut it out!
[NAKI]
Aw, shut up!
I have to make this bastard pay.
You see I just found out
that you're the one
who murdered Boss Yamori!
I'll avenge him. Right here!
So I take it that
you're not interested
in becoming part of Goat then?
[NAKI]
You think we'd team up
with the shitsack
that killed our boss?
Sorry to disappoint,
but that ain't our style!
Naki.
What will it take
for you to follow me?
The way we do it in
the 13th Ward is simple.
Whoever's strongest,
is at the top.
Give me your best shot.
Interfering would be
an insult to the boss.
Just watch.
You're not even in the
same league as Yamori.
Of course not, he was a god!
You won't get away from me!
Doesn't it hurt
when you do that?
It does.
[NAKI]
That's the boss' Kagune.
Would you like to continue?
[NAKI]
As promised,
from this day forward, you're
the leader of the White Suits.
[KANEKI]
Naki.
The White Suits are strong
because of your leadership.
I don't want them without you.
Fight for me, and I'll
fight for your sakes too.
[NAKI] Keeping our word once
it's given, that is our style.
[NISHIO]
The Great Wheel Act.
Word is, they're an
underground human outfit
that supports ghouls.
When pigs fly, right?
I don't think it's
that inconceivable.
Huh?
Seems your flying pigs
have arrived.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Ogura,
I'm part of the Great Wheel Act.
Mr. Ogura, what's the
Great Wheel Act really?
It was originally comprised
of a large group
of student activists.
So it all started
at a college, I guess?
[OGURA]
Yes.
The bulk of the group's
first leaders were students
from Kamii University.
But the faculty clamped down
on them and forced many to quit.
In terms of the
group's membership,
it's undergone drastic changes,
but the principles it was
founded on still remain.
What principles?
The first is that no one
chooses to be born as they are.
That premise naturally
applies to humans and ghouls.
As the world stands,
one's fate as citizen or pariah,
predator or prey,
is decided from birth.
But if we can
dispel that standard,
perhaps both sides will
realize they have a choice.
Such a paradigm shift is
our group's objective.
These ideas were first put
forth by a medical student.
One who's since turned
her attention towards
the treatment of ghouls.
From what I've been told,
this woman was once
in love with a ghoul.
[gasps]
Huh?
[OGURA]
We will continue to assist
what ghouls we can in secret.
Just as we'll continue
to hope that ghoul's rights
are established in this society.
So count us as allies of
Goat and of the One-Eyed King.
I don't wanna pry,
but is their group's
founder who it sounds like?
I want some coffee.
Catch you, later.
Huh?
Where am I?
I'm so glad you're okay!
And who in the hell are you?
[AKIRA]
So I was asleep without a care
while all of this was
going on around me?
You were wounded.
Huh?
[AKIRA] Sorry, but could
you leave me alone for now?
[AMON]
Have time to talk?
Yeah.
[AMON]
It's a strange thing.
All these people who've
been trying their damnedest
to kill each other are
now standing as allies.
That's true for most of us.
But when it comes
to you at least,
I never felt like you
wanted me dead.
What you did really
came as a shock to me.
I was completely at your mercy,
and you spared my life.
[AMON]
Eyepatch.
This world has an
understanding of ghouls.
They eat humans,
so they're monsters.
To most people,
it's as simple as that.
That's exactly
what I want to change.
And while I have
the strength to fight,
I will.
You were once human yourself,
so why would you go to such
lengths to protect ghouls?
[KANEKI]
Cause I'm like them.
Always have been.
Isolated from society.
Limited in what we could enjoy.
Well, not completely.
There were some people
dear to me who were human.
But when it came
to most people I met,
I could take them or leave them.
I'm not interested in fighting
for some faceless stranger.
I wanna help the
people I'm close to.
And it just so happens that
in my case, most are ghouls.
It's a pretty selfish
motivation, huh?
Maybe, but it's
one I can relate to.
[KANEKI]
So, Amon,
what do you plan
to do after this?
[AMON]
I don't know,
but some part of me will
always be an investigator.
I'll do whatever
I judge to be right.
[KANEKI]
Akira's regained consciousness.
Why don't you come
down and say hello?
[AMON]
Tell me,
If a friend or an acquaintance,
who you thought you'd lost,
were to suddenly
come back in your life,
how do you think you would feel?
[KANEKI]
If it were me,
I think I'd be scared.
Scared of what?
I'd be scared that
they might go away again.
Actually,
you might have a point.
[door opens]
[meowing]
Huh?
Hey.
It's been a while.
[AKIRA]
You brought my cat?
Yeah, it has been a while.
So how'd you get
in my apartment?
Didn't give you a key.
Through the window.
[AKIRA]
So, breaking and entering?
How far you've fallen.
To think that an
upright investigator--
Wait, that's former for us both.
Akira.
First off,
please allow me to apologize.
I couldn't tell you.
[AKIRA] Thanks for
bringing Maris Stella.
It's been years.
I was finally coming to terms
with the fact that
you were dead.
So what am I supposed
to say at this point?
I don't need your apologies.
I'm not happy with you,
but I'm not upset either.
What I am, is very confused.
Sorry, Former Investigator Amon.
Don't be. It's fine.
I'll be staying here
for a while, at least.
If you need anything, just ask.
[AMON]
I'll be waiting.
[AKIRA]
He didn't lie to me,
and he wouldn't.
[AKIRA]
But I doubt he was telling me
the whole truth, either.
How can I face him,
after all that's happened?
[knock, knock]
[door opens]
Akira Mado, right?
Are you feeling better?
Think we should talk.
Before we go on,
I think you should know.
I killed your father.
[gasps]
[AKIRA] That's a hell of
a thing to get someone up
from their sickbed to tell them.
[AKIRA] I'm glad you're
such a tactless bitch.
I'll be able to
despise you openly.
That's fair.
Come on.
[AKIRA]
What is she playing at?
[GIRL]
Let's take a break.
Who's gonna go now?
[AKIRA]
Children.
[TOUKA]
They're ghouls.
Children that have been
staying with Aogiri tree.
[TOUKA]
One's who've lost their families
and have had to grow up alone.
[HINAMI]
Hey, Touka.
[TOUKA]
Hinami.
[HINAMI]
Glad you came by.
[TOUKA] They've been nagging
me to come out for a while.
[HINAMI]
I see.
[BOY A]
Hey, is that Hinami up there?
[GIRL]
Hurry on down here! You're late!
'Kay, I'm coming!
I only fought your father
because he was trying
to go after Hinami.
She's in the same boat
as those three children.
She lost her parents,
so now we're her family.
That's one way to put it.
Nice and delicate.
But why not say what you mean?
Eh, Rabbit?
Her parents were
killed by my dad, right?
That they were.
[AKIRA] What'd you think
you'd gain by showing me this?
Did'ja think I'd
get all sympathetic?
I don't need any
sympathy from you.
But I do have some
sympathy for you.
Is that so?
My dad was very kind.
That was especially true
when it came to how
he treated his children.
He was always smiling.
Endlessly patient.
But he also killed
a lot of people
in cold blood
behind our backs.
Not for eating either,
he did it to avenge our mother.
Now, he's gone,
and if you ask me,
he was a perfect idiot!
I thought my father was
a useless waste of a parent,
for turning his
kids into orphans
over something as
pointless as that!
And I also felt worthless.
'Cause my brother and I couldn't
make living worth it for him.
If he'd just
let us see his pain,
maybe I'd have realized
that it was him who took
her death the hardest.
If I could,
I'd go back in time
and scream his head off.
Then I'd hug him.
And tell him how
we could've lived.
[BOY B]
Hey, Touka!
You okay up there?
Yeah, I'll be down in a second.
You coming?
[AKIRA]
Huh?
[TOUKA]
Just do it.
[AKIRA]
Whoa. Wait!
[TOUKA]
Last thing I'll say,
I've known Hinami
for a long time now,
and she has never held any kind
of grudge against your father.
It's true.
Come here,
you little devils.
[BOY B]
Get her!
[BOY A]
Hi, Touka!
[GIRL]
Where were you?
[BOY B]
You smell like coffee!
Hey listen, kids.
Why don't'cha give this lady
here a big squeeze too?
Yeah, sure.
Do you mind?
Knock yourselves out.
[BOY B]
She smells good.
[BOY A]
Mm-hmm!
[GIRL]
Hey, do you wanna play, too?
[TOUKA]
Hinami.
Huh?
[AKIRA]
She's so warm.
[AKIRA] Who was
I supposed to hate again?
Who am I supposed to hate?