[MATSURI] Request an intercept
helicopter immediately.
We've got some extra
trash to take out.
That's one more down!
[KIJIMA]
Oh, Furuta?
Do mind that you don't
slip in the blood.
[FURUTA]
Right, sir.
Bless my soul. Master Mirumo!
I'll take the ones in front.
You flank 'em from the left.
Right.
[grunts]
[SHIRAZU]
Saiko, get down!
[GHOULS yelp]
[HAISE] At this point, they'd
each distinguish themselves
in any squad. They're
all developing so well.
Well done. Let's
push upstairs now.
[URIE, MUTSUKI, SHIRAZU]
Roger!
[SAIKO]
Aye aye!
[door clicks]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Mairo!
Master Shu. I'm
glad you're safe.
Matsumae.
The CCG has taken
the lower levels.
Lead by the woman
from that ambush.
Understood.
Master Shu, a helicopter is
on its way to collect you.
Please wait for it on the roof.
Matsumae.
Why aren't you
wearing your mask?
Swear to me that
you'll come back.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Will you promise me that?
Would you come back early today?
Yes.
Promise me.
Fine.
That is a promise...
...I cannot make.
[gasps] Matsumae.
Master Shu.
You must go on living.
While I have enjoyed this life,
it has always belonged to you.
Please do not let
this be for nothing.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Your words...
...are so unfair, Matsumae.
Sasaki. They're trying
to keep us from the roof.
Head there now and
search for enemies.
Understood.
Hey, Shirazu.
You're in charge.
Right.
Kickass.
The CCG's ninja warrior.
[HAISE]
There's no one here.
This was a major company.
It sure did come
to a sudden end.
[MATSUMAE]
Master Shu. Please.
Continue to grow stronger.
There's a forest of
thorns before you,
but you can make it through.
Of that, I have no doubt.
[MATSUMAE] Shu. I realize
how disrespectful this is,
but I would ask that you forgive
me for the feelings I hold.
Because I love you.
The same as if you
were my own brother.
[TSUKIYAMA]
What a ridiculous farce.
[UI]
Investigator Sasaki.
What's the status on the roof?
[UI]
Sasaki!
[HAISE] It's clear.
No one's arrived yet.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Do you mean to be merciful?
Would you please surrender?
If you do, you might
not have to die.
I can recommend that
we take you into custo--
Surrender, you say.
[HAISE groans]
[TSUKIYAMA]
I will not surrender.
My father and many others
staked their lives on the
chance that I might live.
So my life is theirs
as much as my own now.
Mister Sasaki. I have
no idea who you are.
Hold it!
[SHIMOGUCHI] An unknown.
We'll dispatch him together.
Don't get careless.
[SHIMOGUCHI] Don't know
who this bastard is, but...
[KANAE growls]
[SHIMOGUCHI screams]
Shimoguchi, no!
No, you idiots. Run!
No, sir!
[SHIMOGUCHI]
Retreat, that's an order!
Stop being stubborn!
Do you wanna die?
Given the circumstances,
I can finally say
I hate you both.
You're always in the way.
You're useless to me.
Now get the hell outta here!
[TOGA] Too bad, 'cause
we rather liked you,
Senior Investigator, sir.
We'll buy you some
time, sir. Fall back!
[INVESTIGATOR A] We've lost
contact with Shimoguchi Squad.
Looks like we have a new player.
I copy that.
Quinx Squad and
Ito Squad, go assist them.
Understood.
I have a really bad
feeling about this.
[MATSUMAE]
She's fast and strong.
[IHEI] It's time I
brought an end to this.
[MATSUMAE] If this keeps up,
she'll beat me.
No matter what, I'm done for.
Master Shu.
[MATSUMAE]
That's right. My only chance.
My final weapon...
[MATSUMAE]
...is this feeling.
[gasps]
I shall run you through!
[sputters]
There's our target.
Prepare to engage.
[KURAMOTO]
Watch out!
Umeno!
No! Nezu!
[KURAMOTO]
Yonebayashi!
[TAKEOMI grunts]
[SAIKO yelps]
[TAKEOMI]
You all right, Yonebayashi?
Yeah.
You saved me.
[MUTSUKI]
Urie!
[URIE]
Shirazu!
Hold him in place, Mutsuki!
You got it!
[SHIRAZU]
Saiko!
[screams]
Is... Is he dead?
[gasps]
No way.
[KURAMOTO]
You're kidding,
It's like he's straight
out of a monster movie.
How do we--?
Mister Ito!
[sputters]
[KURAMOTO]
My ribs.
Ah, man. He got me good.
I got impaled.
I-Investigator Ihei?
[IHEI]
Okahira. Your quinque.
[OKAHIRA]
Huh?
Give me your quinque right now!
Throw it here!
[OKAHIRA]
Right!
Perish.
Hurry up and die,
you damn ghoul!
Right now!
[MATSUMAE] Will my shield
hold against this?
[IHEI giggles]
[MATSUMAE grunting]
[MAIRO]
Matsumae!
[MATSUMAE]
Mairo!
Look after Master Shu!
Nice!
You missed the half...
that matters!
[gasps]
Investigator Ihei!
[KIJIMA]
Well, well.
A shame that Miss Hairu
had to meet with
such an early end.
Farewell, sweet beauty.
Fear not, for I'll avenge you.
I think I'll give you
a taste of this as well.
This tool of mine,
which carved Yuma
and the talkative
Aliza to mincemeat.
[yelps]
[KIJIMA]
Huh?
[MAIRO] Don't underestimate
the tenacity...
...of a loyal butler.
Kijima, look out!
[KIJIMA yelps]
[MATSUMAE]
Fanculo !
[KIJIMA groans]
[screams]
Mr. Kijima.
[KIJIMA]
Cheese! I want some cheese!
[screams]
[MATSUMAE]
Yuma. Aliza. Mairo.
You have been avenged.
[MATSUMAE] Master Shu.
I'll rejoin you soon.
I'll take point now.
You stand by at
the rear, Furuta.
[FURUTA]
Sure.
What just happened?
[INVESTIGATOR B]
Investigator Furuta!
What have you done?
What do you mean?
I was standing by at the rear.
You'd use one of
your own as a shield?
Shameful. Have you
no honor at all?
Pardon? You're confused.
It wasn't I who killed him.
That was clearly your doing.
[MATSUMAE]
My eyes.
[FURUTA] Interesting that you
think you're in a place
to cast judgement.
Considering that you're
all murderous man-eaters.
[FURUTA] I mean, that's fine.
To each their own.
But perhaps you shouldn't...
be quite so proud.
Oh, that isn't where I am, dear.
Sorry about this.
[HAISE]
There's no point in resisting.
How do you think you're gonna
get out of this net by yourself?
Choosing to fight...
...is suicide!
That's not for you to ponder.
It's your duty to stop me.
And it is mine to
defeat you and escape!
[HAISE]
Right. A left feint.
A kick as he waits
for an opening.
Then, with his kagune
coiled, a thrust!
I've more or less
got him pegged.
Next, a lateral slice.
[TSUKIYAMA] Strange. You still
know Kaneki's moves.
[panting]
[chuckles] You're quite
strong. Even now.
What's wrong, Haise Sasaki?
Just kill me.
[KANEKI]
Don't do this.
[HAISE screams]
[KANAE] Stop your squealing,
Du dreckschwein .
Kanae? Is that you?
[KANAE]
Ja.
[MICHIBATA] You'll be fine,
Kuramoto. Just hang in there!
[URIE grunts]
Damn it!
No matter how much we cut him,
he just grows back.
Unless we stop
that regeneration,
we're done for.
But none of us has a
strong enough quinque.
[SHIRAZU]
No. I have one.
Take this!
Just stay the hell
down this time.
I'm begging you.
[MICHIBATA screams]
[KANAE] Do you know why
roses are beautiful?
It's simple. You pick
them before they wither.
[KANAE] May you become
a beautiful memory
for Master Shu, in death.
[ARIMA]
Haise. Once again.
[HAISE]
No. I can't. Please, Arima.
On your feet, at once.
Do your job, Haise.
Kill. Like I do.
You are my quinque now.
That is, unless...
you'd prefer to die again.
[HAISE gasps]
[KANAE] I blacked out for
a moment. What was that?
[HAISE]
No, no! It isn't for you.
It's my body, it belongs to me!
So get the hell away
from it, don't touch me!
[KANAE] I won't have the
likes of you near my master!
Master Shu. You are my pride.
You are my light. You are my--
[KANAE'S FATHER]
Emma, see to the children.
[EMMA]
Right.
[KANAE'S FATHER]
Nathanael. Arnold. Karren.
Please, do not let the
Rosewald name die here.
[KANAE] Soon after leaving
the house, we lost Mutter.
Arnold gave his life
to protect us,
and then Nathanael
gave his to save me.
When I reached
the Tsukiyama family.
I conducted myself so as
to take my brother's place.
To fulfill my father's wish.
I called myself his son.
[KANAE]
Could we train more tomorrow?
[MATSUMAE]
Sure.
[KANAE groans]
[MATSUMAE]
Kanae!
I'll be fine. It's the usual.
How long will you
keep it a secret?
You may be fine now,
but your physique will change.
[KANAE] I know that.
Regardless. There's no choice.
This is to honor my late family.
If I just keep training...
[MATSUMAE]
The servants have all caught on.
About the only person
who hasn't is Master Shu.
[KANAE]
Master Shu.
My heart is trapped
in that forest of roses.
Even now.
[ETO]
Table.
[KANAE]
A great banquet.
[ETO]
The sea.
[KANAE]
Warnemunde . I'm tired.
[ETO]
Illness.
[KANAE]
Mutter.
[ETO]
Pride.
[KANAE]
Master Shu.
[ETO]
Death.
[KANAE]
Inevitable.
[ETO]
Contempt.
[KANAE]
Humans.
[ETO]
Sleep.
[KANAE]
A soft bed. Please let me sleep.
[ETO]
Flower.
[KANAE]
Rose.
[ETO]
Time's passage.
[KANAE]
Cruelty.
[ETO]
Lies.
[KANAE]
Liars.
[ETO]
Female.
[KANAE]
[ETO]
Did you want to be loved?
[panting]
[KANAE]
What kind of question is that?
Of course I wanted to be loved.
Kanae.
Shu... Master.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Get away from him.
[HAISE] I was seized by
such sadness, but then,
I remembered a familiar phrase.
[HAISE]
"Lost one, whom I hold dear.
This isn't your fault.
It's your parents who failed
to raise you."
[clock ticking]
[SHIRAZU]
Urie! You think that was enough?
[TSUKIYAMA panting]
[TSUKIYAMA] No one will
ever chasten you for it.