[KANAE]
Master Shu. Here.
Tell me.
Can you smell anything, Master?
[sniffs]
[TSUKIYAMA]
No, I can't.
[gasps]
[TSUKIYAMA]
However...
There's something
familiar about them.
At any rate, I'm very
fond of the design.
[gasps]
[KANAE]
Master Shu...
This is heartbreaking.
[URIE]
I'm not sure what to expect.
I don't feel any
different. Not yet.
Sir, I have a request.
I'd like to raise
my Frame level.
And may I ask why?
Are you hoping you can
avenge your father's death?
[URIE] Would you quit
prying and just give me
your approval already?
[knocking]
[URIE]
Huh. Kisho Arima?
Kisho.
Urie here says he
would like to undergo
Frame release surgery.
Your opinion?
[URIE]
Why the hell is he asking Arima?
Tell me.
Do you understand the risk
involved with this procedure?
[URIE]
Yes, sir.
And you have your
mentor's consent?
[URIE]
Yes, sir.
[ARIMA]
Hm. Well, in that case,
I have no problem with it.
[ARIMA]
I'm confident Urie can handle
the increase in power.
[URIE]
Kisho Arima acknowledged me.
I'm the only one
who can do this.
I won't lose
control like Sasaki.
[door opens]
[SHIRAZU]
Ah! Look who's here!
Glad to see ya back
from the hospital.
[URIE]
I'm not 100 percent yet.
So, I've gotta relax and
take it easy for a while.
[SHIRAZU]
Those doctor's orders?
Or are you tryin' to get
outta workin' with me
'cause you're pissed
I'm captain?
--C'mon, no hard feelin's, man.
--[URIE] You're not funny.
--[laughs]
--Now get your hands off of me.
Huh?
[yelps]
So, what'll we do?
I dunno.
I have no clue how
we should proceed.
What's wrong, Third Class?
Seems like the squad
we're gonna be workin' with
has pinpointed
Nutcracker's location.
I've got a feelin' that things
are gonna get hairy, ya know?
We're supposed to
start a joint operation
with Suzuya Squad tomorrow.
It'll be dangerous,
so we need everyone's help,
including you-know-who upstairs.
[URIE]
Juzo Suzuya's squad?
Then let's go have
a chat with Saiko.
What? Uh, you think
she'll open the door?
[SAIKO] Woohoo! I finally
got the new lion head.
Oh, wow, and it's made
of titanium, too. Awesome!
Somebody's coming this way.
Two of them.
No. Three of 'em.
--[knocking]
--[SHIRAZU] Open up, Saiko!
We know you're in there!
Open the door...!
[SAIKO]
I'm a crustacean.
A mussel hiding in its shell.
[MUTSUKI sighs]
It's no use.
Then we don't have a choice.
No, I guess not.
[URIE]
Let's go.
[gasps]
[SAIKO] Wha--?! You used Kagunes
to break down my door?!
Don't tell me that
you guys are Quinxes!
[SHIRAZU]
You are, too!
[yelps]
[SHIRAZU grumbles] Look,
we've got a mission, okay?
You gonna help or not?
Nah. I don't really wanna.
Captain Urie gets to me.
[SHIRAZU]
I'm the captain now.
Wha--? They finally fired Urie?
Bet he did something
indecent, didn't he?
[URIE]
Shut up, you troll.
Can we get back on topic?
You're workin' with us
on this investigation.
Captain's orders.
Why? Come on!
What kinda horrible
human being would force me
to give up my slacker lifestyle?
[SHIRAZU]
You're cool with bein'
a good-for-nothin'
couch potato?
I'm goin' back to my cocoon!
Come out and face the music,
ya little bagworm!
[SAIKO]
Stop it! Don't skin me!
Bagworms are precious!
Everyone likes silk!
Yonebayashi.
[SAIKO]
Yeah, what's up?
You haven't heard the news?
Rumor has it that the higher ups
are currently discussing
whether to fire you.
Whoa, for real?
[URIE] Did you think
they wouldn't notice?
The CCG is well aware that
you've been collecting a salary
while living a life of leisure.
They're examining spending
and attempting to cut waste,
which puts you at risk.
It'd be difficult for you
to get by in regular society,
what with your "physical
condition" and all.
Oh, yeah. That would
suck, all right.
[URIE] Idiot. Read your
consent form again.
As a precaution, Quinxes are
guaranteed financial support,
even after they retire.
So, how do I save my job?
Go to work and
carry out your duties.
You might impress them before
they decide to fire you.
That's your only hope.
Go to work. Carry out duties.
Impress them.
I'll take this
damn thing, and--!
[SAIKO]
And log out of it for a while.
'Kay, Captain Shirazu!
Saiko Yonebayashi is
ready to get to work!
Seriously? Good to hear.
It took ya long enough.
We're gonna be heading out
bright and early
tomorrow at 7:30 am.
--Don't oversleep, okay?
--[SAIKO] Aye, aye, sir!
In that case, I'm gonna
go to bed right now!
I'll see you gentlemen
in the morning!
[SHIRAZU]
Urie.
I just wanna thank you
for convincing her to help.
You may get on my nerves,
but I guess you're
not such a bad guy.
That was impressive.
Yeah, I wasn't
expecting that tactic.
But, I've got one
question for ya.
Where was that motivation
when you were the captain?
I've had some time to
think about what I've done.
[URIE] And I've learned there's
a better way to go about it.
We've waited long enough
for the others to arrive.
Shall we get started?
[URIE] Just as I suspected,
threatening Saiko
didn't change a thing.
Her time management skills
are completely lacking.
She's a gear that simply
doesn't mesh with our machine.
[JUZO]
Whoop-oop-oop!
[URIE] If we try to force her
to do her job, and do it well,
"Shirazu Squad" will
implode from within.
And if that happens,
then the captain's
position will be--
Sorry I'm late, everybody!
[SUZUYA SQUAD]
Investigator Suzuya!
Good morning to you, sir!
Morning!
Good to see ya, Juzo!
[JUZO]
Haise!
[JUZO] Oh! You always
come through for me!
[SHIRAZU]
Hey! We're here!
Sorry we're late!
[panting]
[HAISE]
Shirazu! And Saiko?
Sorry, Mr. Sass!
I tried so hard to be on time!
It's perfectly fine.
I know Saiko can be a handful,
so thanks for bringing
her along with you.
[HANBEI] Now, if you'll
please refer to the handout.
What you see before you is a
list of orders for "ingredients"
that were confiscated
from Nutcracker's home.
These are ingredients?
[HANBEI] Yes, we believe
Nutcracker is abducting people
to fulfill these orders.
She's gathering them as
goods to be auctioned off.
So, like human trafficking?
Yes, exactly, but they're
being sold to ghouls.
Whoa, wait, does that mean
the highest bidder eats them?
Yeah.
Sometimes they choose
to keep them, like pets.
Well, that's disturbing.
I ask that you approach
this mission with caution.
The SS-rated ghoul,
Big Madam, may be involved.
As a result, there's a
possibility that this
will become a joint
operation with Division II.
[SHIRAZU]
Holy crap.
This investigation's even
bigger than I expected.
No kidding. I was shocked
when he said we might
be working with Division II.
[URIE]
Excuse me, Sasaki?
That's right, you have
a checkup today.
Best of luck to you.
[URIE]
I'll see you later.
Aw, man.
Do you think he's
gonna be all right?
Yeah, he says his
Rc levels are unstable.
[SHIRAZU] Guess he's more
delicate than I thought.
[DONATO]
So, Torso got away from you.
Yes, but your insight
helped immensely.
So, thank you for that.
No problem.
I couldn't care less
what happens to him.
It makes no difference to me.
Anyway.
What'd you wanna talk about?
[DONATO]
Well, Haise.
I wanted to ask you how you
feel about your memories,
or lack thereof.
I can tell that
you're being tormented
by conflicting thoughts.
One moment you think
"I don't miss my memories,"
and the next you can't help
but wonder who you truly are.
Let me ask you something.
What would you do
if there was a way
to get them back?
Would you choose to
regain your memories?
[OROCHI]
Doesn't matter how hard you try,
you're irredeemable.
What brought this on?
Why're you asking me about this?
Why now? Well.
There's another ghoul who
has a personal interest.
[HAISE]
Another ghoul? Really?
That's right.
If you decide you want
to unlock your memories,
he holds one of the keys
that will help you do so.
His name is...
[HAISE]
All right, guys.
For this mission,
we become women!
[SHIRAZU]
Hm?
[KANAE] Master Shu says that
he doesn't smell anything.
Really? Nothing?
'Fraid not.
We've no need for these
dingy shorts anymore.
Get rid of them.
Are you sure?
Hartnackig ! Roses do not lie!
Incidentally, may I
ask who those
undergarments belong to, Chie?
[CHIE]
A ghoul investigator.
What's his name?
[CHIE]
Haise Sasaki.
[KANAE]
The Guinea pig!
I know you were a
schoolmate of Master Shu,
but that means nothing to me.
You're just a lowly human.
Better tread carefully,
because I can kill
you at any time.
[CHIE] Shu Tsukiyama, huh?
He seems interesting.
I would like to invite you
to dinner and a show
tomorrow night.
[TSUKIYAMA]
I won't ask again!
I demand that you answer me.
What do I see in your eyes?
Dear Hori. You won't
believe this.
I've stumbled upon an
incredibly rare ingredient.
Once I've tasted it,
I'll give you my thoughts,
even if it takes
all night to explain.
[TSUKIYAMA] Hori, would you
tell me something?
What is a "Gourmet," anyway?
[CHIE] Life is boring
without you, Tsukiyama.
So get well soon.
[SHIRAZU]
Whoa. You kiddin' me?
No way. I ain't dancin', brah!
You're off your nut!
Now watch your language, Shi!
That wasn't ladylike.
[SHIRAZU] How can I be
a better lady, Mr. Sass?
Just try to be more feminine.
[SHIRAZU]
Same for you, Toru!
Uh, yeah, well.
[SHIRAZU]
And, Saiko... Never mind.
Hey!
I know this seems strange,
but you saw the Nutcracker's
ingredients list yourself.
Apparently she's on
the hunt for young women.
We had no choice
but to go undercover.
[SHIRAZU] Ugh, there's
gotta be another way.
Look. Against the wall.
Yeah, that's her, all right.
[SAIKO]
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
[SHIRAZU]
Hey, big boy. You're a cutie.
You wanna dance with me?
I suck at this.
[laughs]
I need to try and
catch Nutcracker's eye.
But how do I do that?
[gasps]
[MUTSUKI]
Don't look at me.
Don't look, don't look,
don't look, don't look.
Don't look, don't
look, don't look--
[gasps]
[MUTSUKI]
Oh, hey, Teach.
Calm down, Toru.
You look fantastic.
Uh. Thanks a lot.
[MUTSUKI] That's not what
has me worried, though.
I've gotta find a way
to calm my nerves.
[SAIKO]
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Whoa! Down girl!
[chuckles]
[NICO]
Look, Roma.
There's a familiar
face in the crowd.
You're right, I see him, Nico!
Is that the "Haise" we've
heard so much about?
It's kinda hard to tell
since he's dressed
like a woman right now,
but he sure does look
like Kaneki, doesn't he?
Definitely.
[ROMA]
I don't know about you,
but just looking at
him pisses me off.
I mean, why's he
smiling like that?
[NICO]
Maybe he's happy?
[ROMA] Yeah, that's the
problem! I don't like it.
I wanna see him writhing
around in agony!
Kaneki's most beautiful
when he's drowning
in a swamp of tragedy!
Jeez.
You really are all about
yourself, aren't you?
I want the old Kaneki back.
He was such a handsome,
angsty, tortured soul.
But...
I guess this Haise guy
would have to die first.
Indeed, Roma.
Ever watched someone
spill a glass of wine?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
[DONATO] What would you do
if there was a way
to get them back?
Would you choose to
regain your memories?
[HAISE] If I was given
the choice. I guess...
[SHIRAZU]
Mr. Sass.
[HAISE gasps]
Uh, I dunno, lady.
That sounds kind of
sketch to me.
[NUTCRACKER]
There'll be some top-notch VIP's
at this party. You could
make a lot of money.
Yeah?
[MUTSUKI laughing]
Check it out! We match!
Mine's an eyepatch,
but that's close...
[SHIRAZU] What the hell
does he think he's doing?
I overheard you offer
that chick a job.
[SAIKO]
Maman!
I think that Mutsie might've
had a little too much
to drink tonight.
[gasps]
[MUTSUKI]
Hey, Teach!
Believe it or not,
the Nutcracker just
offered me a job.
Thanks to me, our undercover
investigation is go!
Awesome! Way to go, Toru!
[MUTSUKI] Oh man, I'm feelin'
so good right now!
I'm gonna go do a victory dance!
[SAIKO] Hang on, Mutsie,
I'm comin' with ya!
[SHIRAZU] Hey, what about me?
I wanna dance, too!
[HAISE]
Good grief.
[HAISE] If I ever get
my memories back,
and suddenly I'm not
Haise Sasaki anymore,
my only hope is that
I'll still remember you.
[HAISE] Associate Special
Investigator Matsuri Washu,
the brains of S2.
He's a rationalist,
through-and-through,
who'll do whatever
it takes to win,
even sacrifice his own men.
It's widely known that he's
not fond of the Quinx project.
[MATSURI]
When is this auction being held?
[gasps] The 11th
of November, sir.
Then let's have
Investigator Mutsuki go in.
On his own.
You want him
to infiltrate alone?
Do you have a
problem with that?
We can't risk taking quinques in
because they might
do a pat-down.
Therefore, it's the
perfect job for a Quinx.
But, sir. Mutsuki's
never been on a--
[MATSURI] That's enough!
I don't want your excuses.
I've given you an order.
[JUZO]
Excuse me, I've got a question!
Do you, think I could maybe
infiltrate the auction, too?
[HAISE] Are you sure
you wanna do that?
If we're gonna go in
there and stir things up,
it'd be best to have
at least one more person
working on the inside.
[MATSURI sighs]
Very well.
I promise you won't
regret it, sir.
[knocking]
Yes, come in.
[MATSURI] For this mission,
the S2 and Suzuya Squads
will be working alongside
Investigators Hirako,
Mado, and Shimoguchi.
Each of whom will be heading
up their own squadron.
Now, allow me to brief you
about the Auction
Search-and-Destroy Operation.
[HAISE]
Investigator Shimoguchi!
It's good to see you out of
the hospital. Feeling better?
[SHIMOGUCHI]
I don't need your sarcasm.
Let him be, Haise.
It's the most considerate
thing you can do right now.
In this line of work,
everyone will lose
a superior or subordinate
at some point.
The CCG's an assemblage of
those who've lost others.
Build strength and kill ghouls.
That should be your focus--
do you understand?
It's those who have
the least to lose
that're the ones who
wield the most power.
[HAISE] I have to take from
others or they'll take from me.
Like it or not, that's just
the way the world works.
[ETO] You like looking down
from above, don't you?
[AYATO]
Eto?
[ETO] I have a message
for you from Tatara, Ayato.
He wants you to be
Big Madam's bodyguard
during the upcoming auction.
[AYATO]
What's the breakdown?
[ETO] Like, I said, your job
is to protect Big Madam.
You can bring Naki
and Miza, if you like.
Consider it done.
[ETO]
Thank you.
[AYATO] Saeki. You're
coming along with us.
[TORSO]
Hm?
You need all of the experience
you can get right now.
From here on out, the job's
only gonna get riskier.
Uh. If you say so.
I'll do what I can.
[TORSO]
Toru. Toru.
How I long for your
cold body. Toru.
[MUTSUKI grunts]
Don't just stand there,
cover your squad mates!
Damn it!
[HAISE]
Don't let go of your weapon!
Talk about pathetic!
Remember, the ghouls aren't
gonna hold back in battle!
Let's try again!
[yawns]
[HAISE]
Mutsuki. Juzo. Please stay safe.
[MATSURI]
Commence the operation.
[clock ticking]
[UTA] Who better to do
the job than us, the Clowns?
[CROWD murmurs]
[CROWD gasps]
[UTA] Sit back, relax, and
enjoy to your heart's content!
[ROMA]
Uh-oh!
[NAKI] Okay, that's
the enemy down there.
You see 'em,
Gagi and Guge?
[AKIRA]
I'll handle this monster.
[static]