[INVESTIGATOR A]
Chief!
Cochlea's under attack.
How much of Rushima's
been cleared?
[INVESTIGATOR B]
About 56 percent, sir.
[YOSHITOKI]
Hmm...
This information stays here.
Do not inform the assault teams.
[INVESTIGATOR A]
Yes, sir.
[HOGI pants]
[TORSO giggles]
[TAKIZAWA chuckles]
[HACHIKAWA]
Ugh... This isn't like me.
Sorry Hachikawa, you missed!
[SHIKORAE]
Roundhouse kick!
Skewer!
[HOGI gasps]
[HACHIKAWA] You think your
freckles are ugly, huh?
That why you wear
your hair like a mop?
To cover up your face?
Look at mine.
[gasps]
You might not like
those freckles you got,
but I would rather have
shit smeared on my face
than look like this.
[HOGI]
Hachi...
[HACHIKAWA]
This isn't like me.
Ya think we should eat him now?
Why not?
Where's Saeki?
[TAKIZAWA]
Oh...
I take it no one's injured?
[URIE] These low-level ghouls
won't be nearly enough.
I need way more credit to
become a Special Investigator.
[beeping]
[INVESTIGATOR A]
Hachikawa Squad has gone quiet.
Huh?
[INVESTIGATOR A]
Last we heard,
they'd encountered
the SS-rated Owl.
Hachikawa...?
But Mutsie's with them!
[URIE]
I know.
But exterminating
Aogiri is our top priority.
Let's go.
[URIE]
Just be okay, Mutsuki.
[TORSO]
Toru...
[MITSUSHITA]
Were you hurt?
[MIZA]
I'll be all right.
Have to say.
That Suzuya kid
is a real monster.
[MITSUSHITA grunts]
Huh?
[MITSUSHITA moans]
Your death will
bring my squad pride.
For Suzuya!
[MIZA]
They already found us?
[HANBEI]
It's stuck in the wall.
Come on.
Silver Skull!
I'd expected no less from you.
You almost finished
me off, Three Blades.
Huh?
Excuse me, but are you
one of Suzuya's men?
[HOJI] In the fight to
dispatch his older brother,
we suffered more than
a hundred casualties.
And from what we've seen,
the younger brother poses
an even greater threat.
Listen, Mado.
I want you to go into this
battle under the assumption
that I am going to be killed.
[HANBEI]
She's got me on the defensive.
I have no chance
of winning like this.
[KURONA]
Nice reflexes.
Your technique's good, too.
You know, back in the day.
[KURONA] We counted
skill with the quinque
as our greatest asset.
Huh?
Let's play a game.
[HANBEI]
I must be fearless!
I'm outmatched.
She'll overpower me with ease!
[KURONA chuckles]
[HANBEI]
Come on, Abara.
You can't let this be the end!
Can't even brace myself.
[screams]
[KURONA]
I don't follow.
Why are you so loyal to Suzuya?
[HANBEI]
My leg.
[KURONA]
You must know that
he doesn't give a
damn about your life.
I mean, he did
abandon you, after all.
[HANBEI] I will correct
you on three points.
First off, it is only right
that I should be loyal
to my superior investigator.
Second: Putting duty aside,
Special Investigator Suzuya
has earned my undying loyalty.
And third, the leader of my
squad, does not abandon his men!
You know, I was hoping
I'd run into you, Rei.
You get a little more monstrous
every time I see you.
Eh, Kurona?
Got time for one
last class reunion?
[TATARA]
I'm glad you made it, Hoji.
We have a lot to work through.
My sorrow for my brother.
My resentment towards you.
And towards Aogiri Tree.
[HOJI]
Yes.
It'll all be settled.
Because you're going
to die here and now.
[TATARA] I despise you
with every fiber of my being.
[AKIRA]
A kakuja.
[HOJI] You remind me
of your brother, Tatara.
Huh?
More of your squad?
[KURONA]
This is delightful.
I'll kill them in front of you
and show your agonized
expression to Shiro.
[JUZO]
Shiro?
You mean she actually
recovered from those wounds?
Huuuh? Of course Shiro's alive.
She's here with me!
You're just ignoring her!
Oh, that's seriously nasty.
[KURONA]
All this time.
I've kept Shiro
alive within my body.
But soon, I'm gonna
have Papa fix her up right.
[JUZO]
I doubt that's possible.
[KURONA]
I don't want to hear it.
Shut your mouth, Suzuya!
[TATARA]
Burn!
[screaming]
[HOJI] The fuel that
stokes that flame...
...is your hatred for me.
[HOJI]
Huh?
[grunts]
[groans]
[TATARA]
It's over.
Hi.
We're going to finish
what Juzo started.
[JUZO]
Excellent coordination, team!
[KURONA]
He's dead.
I killed him.
I killed Rei.
Did you see, Shiro?
[KURONA laughs]
You're jumping the
gun a bit, aren't you?
[KURONA]
Huh?
But I... I thought
you were dead.
[JUZO] I hope you
won't think ill of me for this.
[KURONA]
Huh?
[screams]
[JUZO]
Wow.
You dodged that?
Is it okay to let her go?
[JUZO]
Yeah.
If you have to run from
the same opponent twice,
you'll never beat them.
[gasps]
Takizawa.
Remember when
you hurt me, Tatara?
I've decided it's my turn.
I'm gonna kill you.
[TATARA]
Back off.
[TAKIZAWA shrieks]
Hot! Hot!
Hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot!
But! But!
But, but, but, but, but,
but, but... I'm not done.
That was toasty!
[TAKIZAWA] You know,
it hurt back then, too.
Tryin' to remember
just how much.
Oh yeah.
This much!
[TATARA]
E... To.
[TAKIZAWA]
Is something wrong?
I took down the bad guy see?
Aren't you proud?
[TAKIZAWA]
Hoji, I... I missed you--
All troops,
the SS-rated Owl is here.
Prepare to dispatch it.
[TAKIZAWA]
Why? Why? Why? Why?
I'm still alive?
But I... I was done for.
I'm sure of it.
[door sliding open]
Huh?
Investigator Takizawa,
I trust you're feeling well?
[TAKIZAWA]
Yeah, but...
Who are you?
And how the heck
am I alive right now?
[KANOU]
First things first.
Take a look at your new body.
[TAKIZAWA shrieks]
I worked on 63
wounded investigators
after the battle in
the twentieth ward.
Only you survived the procedure.
What've you done?
You're familiar with creatures
that can regrow lost body parts,
aren't you?
Takizawa, I have
successfully made you a ghoul.
[TAKIZAWA barfs]
Oh look.
Your stomach is now rejecting
what it once considered edible.
That's a good sign.
[TAKIZAWA screams]
No more!
Just make it stop!
I can't take any more.
[KANOU]
But I can't stop just yet.
I have to find a surefire
way to make a Kaneki, first.
[TAKIZAWA]
Please! Stop it!
Don't do this!
[wails]
[TAKIZAWA]
I used my power to kill Tatara.
I saved the CCG.
Or I was going to save them.
I wanted to.
That's all I wanted.
I especially wanted to save you.
Do you know why?
Because even when I envied you.
I wanted you to see me.
To take notice.
Was that so much to ask?
I'm sorry, Takizawa.
That wasn't very nice...
Amon.
[KANOU]
Hey.
Good to have you back, Kuro.
Good to be here, Papa.
You've grown up a
little bit, haven't you?
What brings you here?
It's my sister.
I want you to help Shiro.
[KANOU] Not even
I can bring back the dead.
[KURONA]
Shiro is alive!
She still breathes
and eats sometimes.
She even tries to speak!
[KANOU]
Really?
[moaning]
My, that is perplexing.
Though I think I know the cause.
That sound is gas.
Huh?
[KANOU]
Yes.
Gas is trapped in the
fissures on your abdomen,
the sound comes when it escapes.
So what will you do now?
It's a fact that your
sister's deceased.
If you can't help,
then I'll see to it
that you die here.
[KANOU]
Very well, then.
This is my latest Quinx.
I'm excited to find out which
of my creations is superior.
[TAKIZAWA] Interesting
that you didn't turn up
until Mado was in trouble.
Did you really just sit there
and watch me murder Hoji?
And now, it looks like
you're about to join him.
Is something the matter, Amon?
Come and kill me.
[AMON]
Takizawa.
I'm not here to fight.
I came to try to save you.
Well, that's certainly
sweet of you,
even if it's also
a bit condescending.
[TAKIZAWA]
How are you going to save me?
All you ever do is slink
about in the shadows.
That's not to say
you shouldn't try.
Because I'd love to see
you try, Kotaro Amon.
We're ghouls now, Amon.
So come on.
Let's act like it!
[TAKIZAWA]
You're just too weak.
You're a failed experiment.
Every bit as useless
as Kanou said you were.
[AMON] So this is how you manage
to keep deceiving yourself?
I see your weakness.
I know it's the
same as your strength.
[AMON]
Takizawa.
You're not really a ghoul.
No. You'll be an
investigator until you die!
You hear me?
Shut up!
What the hell would
you have me do?
[gasps]
[URIE]
You should withdraw, Mado.
The SS-rated Owl
is too powerful.
Leave him to the Quinx Squad.
Now fan out.
Isn't that guy...?
[URIE]
Mutsuki, where are you?
[OKAHIRA]
That steam!
It's hot!
[KANOU]
Right.
Let's proceed.
Hey, Naki.
What's wrong?
You asleep?
Huh?!
[MIZA]
Na...
[MIZA sobs]
Naki.
[UI]
Greetings, Three Blades.
Regardless of how well you
fight back, you will die here.
So kill yourself.
[MIZA]
Not a chance, bob cut.
Until my last breath has
been torn from my throat,
I will fight proudly!
How are you standing?
I thought you were dead!
I'm fine.
I just needed to
take a quick breaker.
[SHOSEI]
Hey Boss.
Huh?
I'm pretty sure the word you're
looking for is "breather."
[NAKI] As the leader
of the White Suits.
I want to meet death in a way
that my boss can be proud of.
[KURONA]
There's too many.
[OKAHIRA]
No hard feelings.
I don't have a choice.
Dr. Kanou!
[KURONA]
You're not right.
You're touched in the head.
You turned us into
monsters without a thought!
Bastard!
You'll pay!
[KANOU laughs]
Do you really
believe I care what y--
Girl makes a decent point.
[SHOSEI]
Damn.
There's no end to these guys.
[HOGURO]
More and more keep showing up.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Bonjour à tous!
Would you like some help?
[ALL 4]
Huh?
Who are you?
[laughs]
[YOSHITOKI]
What's the meaning of this?
[AMON]
You're not getting through!
I didn't know.