My poor Shu.
[KANAE] Master Mirumo,
I have news.
Master Shu has begun
eating indiscriminately,
and he has lost control
of his kagune.
If this goes on, I fear that...
[MIRUMO]
That he'll come apart?
Yes, sir.
[MIRUMO yells]
[KANAE]
Master Mirumo?
Please forgive me.
I lost my composure
for a moment there.
Master Shu.
[KANAE sniffling]
[TSUKIYAMA] Hello. You're
Kanae von Rosewald, yes?
I'm Shu Tsukiyama.
I heard that we'd
taken on a new servant.
Welcome to the family.
Have you settled in?
Uh... Yeah.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Rosewald.
It means "rose forest,"
correct? Come, young man.
I can show you
a forest of roses.
Look there. The duftwolke .
A noble German rose.
Kanae, we are distant brothers,
bound by blood.
So you need not cry alone.
Instead, live proudly
and beautifully.
Such that you rival this rose.
That is the duty of all
members of our family.
[ALIZA]
Kanae!
Um. You should see this.
[TSUKIYAMA groaning, yelling]
Master Shu!
[gasps]
[growls]
Forgive me.
I have no choice.
Damn you.
What do you worthless
fools take me for?
I am a gourmet.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Bring me my epicurean delights.
Let my tongue and teeth
wrestle with their quarry!
[TSUKIYAMA yells]
Use the inhibitor!
[SERVANTS gasp]
[SERVANT A]
I'm sorry, sir.
[screams]
[TSUKIYAMA] Kanae. What
are you doing in here?
I was tidying up
your room, Master.
Apologies if I
disturbed your sleep.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Not at all.
Thank you.
[TSUKIYAMA] I'm so sorry you
have to see me like this.
[gasps]
[KANAE]
No. It's not your fault.
[TSUKIYAMA]
You will watch over
the Tsukiyama family
for me. Won't you?
[KANAE]
Yes.
[KANAE sobbing]
[KANAE]
Hass ! Hass ! Hass ! Hass !
[KANAE] Hass ! Hass ! Hass !
Hass ! Hass ! Hass !
[KANAE] Right now, I even
hate... my own loyalty.
[CHIE]
Hey.
[NUTCRACKER]
I want to be pre... tty.
I want to be pretty.
I want to be pretty. I want--
[screams]
[TATARA] Impossible.
Cochlea will not fall again.
How many times must you ask?
Hinami's abilities are
indispensable to Aogiri.
[TATARA] Since when were you
one of my advisors, Ayato?
I'll judge who's
dispensable for myself.
[SEIDO cackles]
[AYATO]
Something funny, Takizawa?
Oh, I just think the way
ghouls care about each other
is kinda kooky,
and kooky kinda sounds
like cookie, and cookies
are good, don't'cha think?
--I sure love me a cookie.
--[AYATO] What did you say?
[TATARA]
Don't.
You and Fueguchi knew the risks
when you decided to act alone.
We'll simply recruit
a replacement for her.
Tatara...
...Yamori, the Bin brothers,
and all the other dead.
What is Aogiri to you?
Just a bunch of interchangeable
pawns in your game?
[TATARA] That's right.
And you are just a stray dog.
So know your place.
[SHIRAZU]
So that's it.
[CHIGYO]
Congratulations!
Completely natural chimera
quinque's are very rare.
You hit the jackpot!
Shirazu? What's the matter?
Go ahead and open it.
[NUTCRACKER]
I want to be pretty.
[SHIRAZU gasps]
[grunts]
[HAISE]
Shirazu!
Hey, you're not sick, are you?
It's all right.
It happens all the time.
This might help.
[HAISE] Lots of people get sick
when they first see a quinque.
Especially when it's from
a ghoul they killed.
That's... not...
I'm all right.
So, hey.
The bounty I got for
taking out the Nutcracker.
It was 1.7 million.
You think that's a lot?
[HAISE]
I don't really know.
[AYATO] If you're gonna
blubber about it, then quit!
I'm sick of watchin' you cry.
[HINAMI chuckles]
You think this is funny?
A little bit. I'm sorry.
It's just that,
when you get angry,
you look and act
exactly like Touka.
[HINAMI]
It calms me down.
[AYATO]
Hinami.
[HAISE]
Thank you for the tip.
Not at all.
Here. For you.
You're always so kind, Kaneki.
[KANEKI]
I am me. And you are you.
[HINAMI]
Whenever I was feeling down,
you'd always bring me books,
same as you are now.
It's strange.
I have no idea how I'm
supposed to treat you.
But I guess a lot of us
are feeling that way now.
You had friends.
You know that, right?
Everyone really liked you.
I'm sorry, but I am not
the person you knew.
I'll come back soon.
[HAISE] Why am I pretending
I'm on this ghoul's side?
When the time comes, she'll be--
Do I want to save her?
[HAISE]
What am I thinking? Who am I?
Oh! How's it going?
I, uh, definitely wasn't
trying to hide or anything.
[KIJIMA] I was wondering where
you'd run off to. Furuta.
Oh, why hello there.
I'm Kijima, nice to meet you.
And you as well. I'm Sasaki.
[KIJIMA]
Yes, I'm well aware.
[gasps]
I believe this Rose
case will find us
working closely together.
When the time comes,
I hope you'll take it easy
on me so I don't fall behind.
Well, I'm afraid
we must be going.
Do come along, Furuta.
It was nice to meet you.
[KANAE]
Tell me, Mauschen.
What exactly is it
that makes you feel
so partial to Master Shu?
Huh.
Well, he's fun to be around.
Wouldn't you agree?
That's most of it.
[KANAE gasps]
[KANAE]
You say you can help him.
If that's truly the case,
then tell me how, Mauschen.
[CHIE]
Here!
[INVESTIGATOR A]
Are you Chie Hori?
[gasps]
You're suspected of
assisting in ghoul predation.
We'd like to ask you
a few questions.
[INVESTIGATORS]
Uh--
[BOTH gasp]
[INVESTIGATOR B]
Hold it!
[CHIE]
I try to act brave, Tsukiyama,
but the idea of dying
really terrifies me.
So if I can't avoid it,
at the very least,
I don't want it to happen
until I feel like I've really
lived. And because of that,
I'd like to spend as much time
as I can enjoying my life.
[SHIRAZU]
Hey, Saiko. Wake up, will ya?
[SAIKO]
First you forced me out of bed,
then you made me skip breakfast.
[SHIRAZU] That's what
happens when you sleep
until the last minute!
--[stomach growls]
--[SAIKO groans]
[SHIRAZU]
Oh, boy.
I'm Kori Ui, captain
of S1. Greetings.
My squad will take the
lead in this operation.
We look forward
to working with you.
[UI] These are largely
mass abductions,
and there's been no sign
of predation at the scene.
This leads us to believe
that Rose consists of
organized and
well-trained ghouls.
Since they leave very
little evidence behind,
we'll need to pull
on a lot of threads
if we're to track them down.
That means coming up
with effective methods
of investigating outside
the box. And quickly.
[SHIRAZU] So he wants us to
think outside the box, huh?
[MUTSUKI]
And with practically no leads...
[IHEI]
Excuse me.
You're the members of the
Quinx Squad, is that right?
Uh. Yeah, that's right.
I'm the squad captain.
What's up?
Hey, Captain.
You seem a little tense.
Shut up, I'm totally relaxed!
He's the captain of love.
Well, uh. Hello there.
My name is Hairu Ihei,
and I'm Special Investigator
Ui's partner.
As it turns out, I'm pretty sure
I'm the same age as all of you.
Seeing as we were all
part of the same class,
I was just hoping that
we might become friends.
We're the same age?
[URIE]
Strange.
How did someone from our
class advance so quickly?
We're leaving.
Senior Investigator Ihei.
Ah. Yes, sir!
She's that high ranked?
She used to be part
of Arima's Squad.
And she took part in the
Owl Extermination Mission.
[URIE] She fought on the
frontline of that battle?
This dimwitted girl?
[TAKEOMI] Investigator Ihei
joined during Term 74.
So, in a sense, she's
three years ahead of us.
[SHIRAZU] Huh. No wonder
I haven't seen her before.
[thud]
[stomach growls]
[SAIKO] Captain, please.
Don't let me starve.
I've heard there's a
delicious bakery over there.
Let's try it out.
[SHIRAZU] Huh? C'mon,
we were just about to start
canvassing the area.
[whines]
All right. Fine.
You did skip
breakfast, after all.
Kuroiwa. Wanna join us?
Ah!
[SAIKO]
Ooh! It smells like heaven.
[SHIRAZU]
Whoa, those sure look tasty.
[YORIKO]
Hello, welcome to--
Hey, Kuroiwa. How ya been?
A friend of yours?
Kosaka.
[YORIKO]
Here. Hope you enjoy.
[SHIRAZU] I know I will.
Man, this bread is just amazing.
Thank you very much.
So, Kuroiwa,
you're a ghoul investigator now?
That's right.
[YORIKO]
Guess you wanted to follow
in your father's footsteps?
[TAKEOMI]
Yeah.
I wonder, has Kuroiwa always
been the serious type?
Oh, yeah. He never
says that much,
but he still has a
really strong presence.
And he's always been
an outstanding athlete.
And what about you?
Like your job?
Yeah. Always wanted
to work at a coffee shop,
but a bakery with
coffee is just fine.
Oh, I feel that.
Uh-oh, we should
prob'ly get goin' now.
Not that we have anything
to report to our bosses, heh.
I plan to report that
we located the whereabouts
of a delicious bakery.
[TAKEOMI] Kosaka. Thanks.
It was great bread.
Uh...
Sure! No problem. Come anytime.
[FURUTA] Stupid boss.
Who does he think he is?
[FURUTA] He can take his synergy
'n blow it out his ear.
[GROUP gasps]
[KIJIMA]
Well done, Furuta,
it's like you were destined
to play ghoul bait.
I'm not at all pleased
to hear that, sir.
[chuckles] They may not
leave any traces,
but we can still predict where
they're likely to strike.
So this was a trap?
[FURA]
A wall?
The detachable kind.
[MATSUMAE]
We should leave.
Oh, I disagree.
[knocking]
[door opens]
Good evening, sir.
Is the shop open right now?
Of course. Come on in.
[HAISE]
Amazing.
[UTA] Anything special
you were looking for?
Uh. Yeah, there, is.
[HAISE]
I'm here about this.
It was delivered to my place.
And it said it came
from your shop, so...
I see. Well, I remember
sending it out.
How strange. Perhaps I
got the address wrong.
Oh, I guess that
would explain it.
By the way.
Did you happen to send
this book along with it?
Afraid not. Just the mask.
That sure is strange.
Well, thanks for your time.
Say, if you don't
mind my asking.
Your eyes.
Oh, yes. These are just tattoos.
Ink is injected into
the sclera via needle.
It does fade every
few years, though.
Oh... yeah?
[HAISE]
That sounds painful.
Oh. I guess I should return
your mask to you, huh?
[UTA] No, that's
all right. You keep it.
Uh?
After all, it was
fate that you and I
should meet in this way.
[HAISE] Um, well then,
thank you for the gift.
Hey.
[UTA]
Yes?
You don't just buy
and sell masks, do you?
You create them.
I do.
[MATSUMAE]
That was quite the performance.
Well, in that case.
Ah! Heh. More tricks?
[IHEI giggles] I've dealt with
ghouls like you before.
My hands should be nice
and warmed up now.
[MATSUMAE]
Who the hell is this girl?
[MATSUMAE] She can even
dodge at this range?
[grunts]
Gotta be quick.
Are you all right?!
Yuma!
[KIJIMA] Excellent work
diverting their focus.
I'm quite impressed,
Investigator Ihei.
Huh?
Aw...
[MARUDE]
So, S One is on the Rose case?
[MATSURI] Yes. Apparently,
they've already caught one.
You don't say.
[MATSURI] I'm a special
investigator too, now.
[MATSURI] I'd like to use
everything I learned in Germany
to take down Aogiri Tree.
[MATSURI]
Under our current chief,
we won't be able to beat them.
Not under our current chief.
[MARUDE]
What you learned in Germany
was how to send good
men to their deaths.
It seems I have failed you
utterly, Master Mirumo.
Please forgive my incompetence.
It's fine. You did
nothing wrong.
I'm just glad you're safe.
[sighs]
[ALIZA]
Yes. But where is Yuma?
[MATSUMAE]
Aliza...
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[KANAE] We can be sure
that the CCG has caught on
to what we're doing.
Any future harvest attempts
are going to be
extremely difficult.
But if we stop,
then Master Shu will...
[MATSUMAE grunts]
[gasps] Does it hurt?
It's not that bad. A bit
of rest, and I'll be fine.
Please don't let me keep
you from your work, Kanae.
[gasps]
[CHIE] I put some
pictures in this envelope.
I'm pretty sure he'd
want to see them.
If you really wanna see
Tsukiyama get better,
then you have to help
him get what he wants.
[metal leg tapping]
[KIJIMA] I can tell
just by looking at you.
You won't talk.
No matter how creative
this interrogation may get,
you will be silent as a lamb.
With that in mind,
I think instead, I'd like to
offer your friends a gift.
Tell me. What part
should I give them first?
[CHIE] I need you to make
me a promise, okay?
Promise that you'll
honor Tsukiyama's wishes
above everything else.
If you think you can do that,
then let him see
the first photo.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Kanae. This...
[gasps]
...is heartbreaking.
[clock ticking]
[HOGURO]
Are they the ones we're after?
[TSUKIYAMA] There's no way my
sweet Kaneki could ever forge...
[GRAVE ROBBER]
Are you all right, Torso?
[KIJIMA] As you know,
we captured your colleague...
[SHIKORAE] You're like
a plump, little manju bun.
[CHIE] Okay, then. Here's what
I'm gonna need you to do.
[URIE] This guy sure
looks like a ghoul to me.
[SHIKORAE]
Can't wait anymore... Hungry!
[HOGURO] Let's just
go ahead and kill him, too!
[static]