[cheering]
Hey! Let's have another!
They look so happy!
Bottom's up, my friends.
Here's to ya!
Cheers!
[chatter]
[YOMO] Make way for
the king and queen!
[GHOUL B]
Go home; you're drunk!
[laughter]
[KANEKI gasps]
Oh hi, Teach.
[URIE]
Special Investigator Kuroiwa.
[KUROIWA]
Mm.
[URIE] What made you agree
to help me with this?
[KUROIWA]
I heard you were a friend.
[URIE]
A friend?
[KUROIWA]
My boy would always say to me.
"Urie's a good rival,
and a good friend, too."
Furthermore, you
remind me of your father,
and I had a lot
of respect for Mikito.
Is this some sort of inquest?
This is becoming an
especially busy day for me.
You're free to
decline this inquest,
but if you choose to do so,
that fact will be recorded.
[FURUTA] So what exactly is
it that you want me to prove?
Is it the clarity of my mind
or just my loyalty?
[URIE]
Cram it.
[FURUTA] I have one
other question for you.
Huh?
For me to prove
myself beyond dispute.
What do you think
would be required?
Huh?
[FURUTA]
I'll tell you.
[laughing]
We'd need to have
some witnesses.
[screaming]
Get them out.
I'll find you after the fight.
Kaneki!
Careful.
Get up, kid.
Run for your life.
Let's hold them here
while the others escape.
Oui, Monsieur Yomo.
[NISHIO gasps]
Huh?
Touka!
I need you to get the
children out of here, Hinami.
--But you'll--
--[TOUKA] Just get going!
[gasps]
Hello again.
You're gonna die here,
you ugly bitch.
Can you break their
skin without a quinque?
There's a trick to it.
It's so much fun
to fight at the CCG!
Hi!
Don't worry!
I'm coming, Shiko!
[KUROIWA screams]
Ahh! Eggplant!
[ROMA]
Please. Don't hurt me.
I surrender.
Let me... live!
[URIE]
Same trick you pulled
to kill Shibashi
in the auction raid.
Good thing I read the report.
You're a one-trick pony.
[SHIKORAE]
He, she, he, she, he, she...
So you are in league
with the ghouls.
Let's see you talk your
way out of this one, Furuta.
Behind you.
Huh?
[ROMA]
Say, kid.
What do you think
is the one enemy
that ghouls and humans
have in common?
I would say its boredom.
See, this world is a circus.
We all just want some
senseless pleasure.
Dear God.
Icky.
Dispatch the traitors.
Shio and Rei cover the left.
Yusa, go right.
[NAKARAI]
These guys are strong.
Foes or not,
they're commendable.
Kuroi... wa... run.
[screams]
[ROMA giggles]
[URIE] What are you doing,
you maimed old man?
Just leave me and run, damn it!
[ROMA laughs]
Superfluous side note.
I've been mullin' over the old
chicken or the egg debate
all day and I've figured it out!
I can say for sure that
the chicken came first!
Huh. I blacked out.
[ROMA]
You busy, Chief?
No. Did you finish
all your chores?
[ROMA]
Yeah, I'm ready for supper!
[FURUTA] How about a nice big
bowl of Special Investigator?
[ROMA]
Oooh, that sounds amazing!
Yes!
[laughs]
[KANEKI]
They all have Rize's Kagune.
Just like me.
And given how fast they healed.
Could they be...?
[JUZO]
Sorry 'bout that.
Could you stand back a bit?
I always liked you, Haise.
but I'll kill you the
same as anyone else.
You're still on
Arima's orders, aren't you?
Why did he entrust his last
mission to you, but not to me?
[HIRAKO] If you're
questioning his faith in you,
it never faltered.
Arima believed in us both
till the day he drew
his final breath.
He had faith that I'd fight
for his sake no matter what.
And he had faith that
no matter the circumstance,
you would fight
for what was right.
That's why I was
the one he chose for the job.
I don't understand what
you mean, and I don't care to!
[pants]
[NAKARAI]
Why would you let me live?
I do as my king bids.
[gasps]
[groans]
[ROMA]
My infamous body.
[chuckles]
Hamburgoo!
[ROMA]
Nice dodge!
Let's make some meatballs!
[pants]
Night-night!
Did we get him?
Probably.
[ROMA]
A shield?
[SHIKORAE]
Huh?
Ohhh! Well,
isn't that interesting?
[SHIKORAE]
Wings!
He got Shiko!
[ROMA shrieks]
Brother!
Sayonara.
[URIE]
Kuroiwa!
You're okay.
[KUROIWA]
You know.
I've always wanted
to apologize to you.
I wasn't able to
protect your father.
If only I had been stronger.
He might've survived.
I'm truly sorry, Urie.
It's my fault your father died.
No, it's not!
Not yours or anyone else's.
He chose.
It's all on him.
[URIE]
I've been blaming myself too.
For doing nothing,
when there was nothing
that I could've done.
I was too small to help him
or to take the hit when
I found out he was gone.
I couldn't just accept
that he was dead,
not without blaming someone.
[KUROIWA] You really are the
spitting image of your father,
you know that?
[URIE]
Kuroiwa!
My! This blade
sure has a fine edge.
You piece of shit!
[FURUTA]
Don't be so dramatic.
If you liked him so much,
then why'd you let him die?
[URIE]
Special Investigator Marude.
[MARUDE]
You look like hell, Iwa.
Marude.
You're not alone.
I'm right beside you.
And I'm not going
anywhere, understand?
I'm with you to the end.
[URIE]
Special Investigator.
You mind explaining
what the hell's going on?
Huh?
Hmm?
Who's your friend?
Touka didn't escape?
[KANEKI]
Touka...
Get away from Touka.
Kaneki!
Ken Kaneki.
He's the one.
Leave her alone.
Ken Kaneki.
Head of the beast.
You have to die.
He must die!
Can't let him live.
Tear him apart.
Kill him now!
You have to die!
No, stop. What are you doing?
Kaneki.
Don't you die on me!
[KANEKI]
Touka.
I'm here, Touka.
[KANEKI]
Touka. Touka.
Touka.
[KANEKI]
I'm completely powerless.
But your head's
still attached, right?
Can you still breathe?
Yeah.
Do you still have the
strength to bite someone?
Uh-huh.
And the strength to crawl?
Yeah.
Then nothing's changed.
We should keep doing
what we've always done.
We move forward.
No matter what.
Just like a centipede.
Touka.
Touka. Touka. Touka!
[gasps]
[KANEKI]
Touka. Touka. Touka.
Touka. Touka!
Touka!
I'm right here, Kaneki!
[MUTSUKI]
Why's it just her?
Why's she the one
you care about?
Why aren't you
calling out my name, too?
[KANEKI]
Touka! Touka!
Touka!
Teach, I... I just...
Kaneki.
[KANEKI]
Touka. Touka. Touka.
[FURUTA]
Huh?
[laughs]
Sounds like I win!
I want you to clean
your plate like a good boy.
Okay, Kaneki?
Your daddy is so very proud
of you, my adorable dragon!
[clock ticking]
Let me apologize.
[gasps]
[FURUTA] Does no one want
him to find happiness but me?