Who is that kid?
[YOSHITOKI] He's from the
Furuta branch of the family.
Their youngest. Intrigued?
Just thinking he has good form.
[YOSHITOKI]
Tsuneyoshi seems to favor him.
Among the illegitimate
children, at least.
But that can only
take him so far.
His place is at
the foot of our table.
Nimura dash and slash!
[laughs]
What's the matter?
Ah-ha!
Got you!
So that didn't quite do it.
Oh well.
How about this?
I'm not done yet!
I must confess.
For the sake of
a beautiful duel,
I was rather hoping
you'd have a sword.
Oh, now we're talking!
Wait a second.
This all you've got?
Cut me already.
Let's carve each other--
[FURUTA shrieks]
Ahh, that was painful.
And the chill in
your eyes cut, too.
[giggles]
But this is more
like it, I think.
You and I have to put
our very lives on the line.
Or else the game
isn't any fun, you see.
The best things in
life are dangerous.
That's especially
true for games.
And when you think about it,
we're all just pawns
on a great board.
Now...
[FURUTA] ...I think I'd like
to play a game of house.
Come on.
Let's play.
[MARUDE]
Ugh!
How many of these
bastards are out there?
[FURUTA] This is exhilarating,
don't you think?
Die!
I said to die.
You trash.
[KANEKI]
You really are strong, Furuta.
You know.
I'm not half as graceful as you.
I'm not smart either.
Or powerful.
Against you.
I couldn't protect the world.
I couldn't even protect
my own tiny little part of it.
Up to now,
all I've done is lose.
You're better.
But this time I'll come through.
I'll beat you
and protect the others.
Humans and ghouls.
Huh?
[FURUTA]
Damn it!
Come on, Special Investigator.
You really think you have
the right to play the hero?
To pretend that you
meant well all along?
I don't buy it!
It was a screwed-up world
we lived in before,
but you've made it even worse!
Don't you remember
what you did to Tokyo?
What of that?
What of the countless
innocent lives you've crushed
beneath your boots?
Not just humans, either.
Exactly how many ghouls
do you think you've eaten?
I would wager that you
lost count quite a long time
before you finally stopped.
And largely thanks
to your myriad of failures,
I've had a wonderful time of it.
You tried to fight against
an incarnation of brutality,
but practically
became one yourself.
That little coffee shop
you tried to protect.
Where is it now?
And how's the false family
you tried so desperately
to hold together, back
when your name was Haise?
Even after that,
you had the blind gall
to name yourself king.
To let a whole people
put their trust in you.
But you failed.
Yeah.
At everything you've tried!
Hey.
At least you put
on a show for me.
Your failures reassured me
that no matter what we do,
some things can't be changed!
It's true!
You'll make a mess of
things today as well.
Soon enough, it will all
be flushed down the drain!
[giggles]
Is that what you want?
Why do you have
that look in your eyes?
Don't tell me you think that I'm
the one at a disadvantage here.
You're an honest to goodness
riot, you know that?
It's just not enough.
I wiped the Washu clan
from the face of the earth.
I took the reins of the
CCG and drove it to ruin.
I unleashed the dragon
that ravaged the earth
and claimed countless
thousands of lives.
But it's still not enough!
I want more.
I need more.
So much more!
Give me everything!
[FURUTA]
More!
Give me everything!
[TSUKIYAMA]
Monsieur Naki!
Let's give 'em hell, boys.
Go crazy!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Don't go too crazy.
We're still healing.
[FURUTA]
♪ Kagome... Kagome... ♪
♪ The bird in the cage. ♪
♪ Bird in the cage. ♪
♪ When, oh when,
will it come out? ♪
Tell me Haise.
Don't you ever feel like
all of this is just pointless?
Living and dying.
Creating and consuming.
There's no value in it.
There's no reason for it.
None of it's worth the trouble.
[FURUTA]
We're all just children,
and the world, a box of toys.
We play for as long
as we're allowed.
And when our time is up,
there's nothing we can do.
The box is closed to us.
Never to be opened again.
I feel sorry for you,
Associate Special Investigator.
You keep clawing
forward through the muck
of this worthless earth.
And you've made it all this way,
through sheer effort.
If you didn't happen to cross
paths with Rize when you did.
You never would've had to
take on all that responsibility,
not to mention your suffering.
Right?
[KANEKI]
Furuta.
Look.
I was a nobody, with nothing
to set me apart from the crowd.
Not a thing.
But that changed
after I met Rize.
We talked about books and then--
Well that's when I started
to become who I am.
It's when I learned
what true pain was.
How to fight for my life.
I've lost a lot since then.
I've failed a lot.
[KANEKI] But... I also
found a place for myself.
I found teachers and friends.
I found allies.
Comrades.
I found love.
And after all the
mistakes I've made.
After being hurt
as badly as I have.
I could never believe
that it was all for nothing.
Wait. I know you.
You're Matsuri Washu!
[KANEKI]
So yeah.
Even if I'd known everything
I would have to go
through because of it,
I'd do it again.
I still would've
gone to see Rize.
I'd keep it the same, cause it
all helped get me where I am.
And one more thing.
I know this world can be harsh.
But I don't think it's
screwed up, it just, is.
And even supposing that someday,
everything does
go down the drain.
I'll keep on struggling,
just like I did today.
You're one of the only
people I've come across
I just don't get.
Oh well.
I'll be dead in a moment anyway.
How fucked is that?
It's seriously fucked.
Just like everything else
in this god-forsaken world.
Tell me, Investigator.
If I said that
all I really wanted
was to live a normal life,
you would laugh, wouldn't you?
Huh?
[KANEKI]
No.
[FURUTA laughs]
Ready or not!
[RIZE]
Not! I'm not!
Hey, Rize.
[RIZE]
Hmm?
Don't change.
I hope that when I'm an old man
and you're an old woman,
we'll still be the same.
[RIZE]
That's sweet, Nimura.
But I don't really wanna
become an old woman, you know?
[FURUTA]
Oh, you don't?
Well, I do.
I think it'll be fun.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sure it would've been.
[MARUDE]
Attention all personnel.
The fighting is over.
We've won.
Now attend to the wounded.
Repeat.
The fighting is over.
We've won.
Now attend to the wounded.
[KIMI]
Kaneki.
You've almost made it.
The core should be
right above you now.
Please hurry.
[HIDE]
Good luck.
Make sure you come back.
[KANEKI]
We lose.
We take.
We catch and get caught.
We conform and
we make others conform.
We do nothing but cycle
between those roles.
Take what we can and fight not
to lose more than we must.
But as hard as we fight,
we will lose it all.
The people we loved
and were loved by will die.
No matter what.
Someday we'll be forgotten.
To live is to be unhappy.
It's futile.
Even so,
small and grotesque as I am.
Short and cruel
as this life may be.
I still claw forward.
I still search for beauty.
Because...
...it's worth it.
To keep choosing.
To keep being chosen.
[KANEKI]
Farewell, Rize.
Thank you.
[RIZE]
Hey.
Kaneki.
You know.
[RIZE] I've been watching
you for a long time.
[NISHIO]
Kaneki!
[HINAMI]
Big Brother!
[URIE]
Sasaki!
[TSUKIYAMA]
Kaneki!
[AKIRA]
Haise!
[YOMO]
Ken!
[BANJO]
Kaneki!
[AYATO]
Kaneki.
[SHIRAZU]
Mr. Sass!
[SAIKO]
Maman!
[MUTSUKI]
Teach!
[ARIMA]
Haise.
[HIDE]
Kaneki.
[TOUKA]
♪ Standing here again, ♪
♪ fading out the quiet hum... ♪
[URIE] The oviducts that carried
the RC toxin were destroyed.
And the majority of Tokyo's
populace remained human.
But the city was
forever changed.
[URIE] A new regenerative
treatment was developed
using cells from
the dragon's spawn.
[URIE] In time, it'll have saved
more lives than it took.
[sobs]
[URIE] A vast number of bodies
were found on Rushima,
including one with
Quinx surgical scars.
It was determined that
the body was that of Shirazu.
♪ ...memories we shared,
I won't forget you again. ♪
♪ I realize the
two halves of me ♪
♪ though I walk the
same path as before, ♪
♪ and I know that my
being remains unchanged. ♪
♪ I step through the
same door once again, ♪
♪ and my soul is yearning
for the same end, ♪
♪ my one desire. ♪
♪ The same voice calls out to
me and yet, I can't answer. ♪
♪ The "me" I was before today
is still sleeping inside. ♪
♪ I look up to the stars,
and it overwhelms me now. ♪
♪ Though it may conquer me,
I won't let go. ♪
[giggles]
[KANEKI]
Sure is a nice day.