[BANJO gasps]
Huh?!
Thanks, Ayato!
[AYATO]
I'll draw the doves' attention.
You go and get those cells open.
[GHOULS]
Right!
[BANJO] Why'd the
entrance just open for us?
[AYATO]
Not sure.
But I'm guessing
he must've done it.
The half-ass.
Banjo, you're up.
[BANJO]
Right.
Sorry about the wait.
[HINAMI]
Why?
I'm so happy...
Why did you come here?
Even more though,
I'm sad, because...
You're an
investigator now, right?
He's doing the
same thing, all over.
[KANEKI]
Not anymore.
This'll be my last job.
Once I've rescued Hinami,
I'll fight Arima
and die...
[AYATO]
Kisho Arima.
Why? Why can't I hit you?
[AYATO]
No. Not here.
You?!
Arima.
[HIKARI]
Renji!
Her name's Touka.
She's just as cute
as her mom, right?
Touka.
[ARATA]
Up you go!
[AYATO]
I wanna try it!
Lift me, mom!
[HIKARI]
Not right now, Ayato.
[TOUKA laughs]
Do it again! Do it again!
[ARATA]
All right. One more time.
[ARATA cries]
I couldn't protect her.
I was too weak.
Now she's gone forever.
Because I...
Does that make it easier?
Taking all the blame, yourself?
It should've been you.
You should've died
to save your family!
Wait, it looks like...
...this guy's eating
another ghoul.
[screaming]
Huh?
[YOMO] Kirishima would
never have left my sister,
except to protect
Touka and Ayato.
I knew that,
but blaming him actually
did make things easier.
Least for me.
And now,
I've let their father
be taken from them too.
[YOSHIMURA]
There are few things
as difficult as
protecting someone else.
It's far more typical for us
to try to protect someone
and lose them regardless.
[YOSHIMURA]
That said,
there is still something
you can do to help Kirishima.
You can honor his desire to
keep his precious children safe.
[YOMO]
While I live...
...they are safe.
This has to be a joke.
It's a joke.
You're joking.
So? What's the punchline?
Stay back.
[FURUTA]
I hate to be a bother.
But as you know,
I can't just let you pass.
Why're you here?
Why do you think?
We wanna rescue Hinami,
just like you do.
I think you got taller.
Huh?
Stop worrying about me.
Go and look after Hinami.
[AYATO]
Whatever, dumbass.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Don't 'cha burn out
on me now, Uncle.
[YOMO]
Touka.
Ayato.
[FURUTA] You're tearing me
apart, you know that?
What a sad thing it is.
To think that I've seen
the sweet, smiling face
of Investigator Sasaki
for the last time!
It's heartbreaking!
Oh well!
[FURUTA]
Stay still, would you?
Sic him, Kijimaa!
Thumb attack!
Let's go.
[TOUKA grunts]
[AYATO]
Ahh...!
[YOMO]
No.
Not them, too.
[YOMO] Do you plan to take
everything from me, Arima?
Including my sister and my hope?
[YOMO] I'm sick of this endless
cycle of taking and losing.
[YOMO] My only wish
is to leave something.
I want to believe that
the choices I made,
that my time in this world...
...had meaning.
[YOMO]
I've fallen short so many times.
But this time...
...I'll protect them!
Argh!
[TOUKA]
Yomo!
I've got this.
Right.
Hey, Kaneki.
I'll see you soon.
[KANEKI]
That stings, Touka.
You'll "see me soon"?
[AYATO]
Hinami!
Hey, Ayato.
Let's go.
So, um...
You're such a screw-up.
Sorry, Touka.
[KANEKI]
I don't sense any reluctance
or hesitation from you.
Arima.
We were friends.
I don't want to fight you.
[KANEKI]
Is it just me?
[KANEKI] We fought countless
times when you trained me.
But not in earnest.
Not like this.
It's subtle, but.
[KANEKI]
You tend towards the defensive.
You attack from the left...
...because of your eye!
[KANEKI]
And with the time I just bought.
I should be able to--
[ARIMA]
Fight like you mean it.
[ICHIMI]
Whoa.
[JIRO] This place
friggin' reeks of blood.
[BANJO] I've activated
the emergency shut down.
We can slip out through here.
Are you sure?
About leaving without Kaneki?
[TOUKA]
If we tried to help,
he'd just have to
fight and protect us.
He'll be fine.
I'm sure.
[motor whirring]
Huh?
Who turned this thing off?
[ARIMA]
Make a choice.
Will you die yet again?
Six hundred and forty-five.
That's the number of times
I could've struck a fatal blow.
Which means,
that it's also the number
of times I let you live.
[ARIMA]
Tell me:
What have you chosen?
I can't win,
but I can keep you occupied
while my friends escape.
[ARIMA]
Enough.
It would appear all the time
I spent on you was wasted.
I'll see you soon.
[ARIMA] You finally
got some fight in you.
Send me the quinque.
I'm in the basement.
[ARIMA] This quinque
was made from the Owl.
You'll be the first enemy
I use it against.
Here I come, Kaneki.
Oh my goodness.
You're really putting it out
there, aren't you, young man?
Well, if you're
making all that effort,
I might as well pitch in.
For sweet little
Hina's sake, too.
Soo gross!
Although, for me at least,
it's also extremely amusing.
Are we enjoying
the show, gentlemen?
[FURUTA shrieks]
[ETO]
Thanks for the paté.
It was delectable.
How the hell
did Eto get down here?
Keep moving!
[KANEKI]
From below?
I wonder.
Did Touka and
the others get away?
Yeah.
They must've.
[KANEKI]
It's fine then.
[HIDE]
Hey!
Hang on a minute.
[KANEKI]
Hide?
[HIDE]
So...
You think you managed
to buy them enough time,
which means
it's okay to give up.
Man, you really
haven't changed much.
[KANEKI]
But I can't...
[HIDE]
You can't beat him?
I say you can.
You really think so?
Yeah, of course I do.
Hide.
Yeah, what's up?
[KANEKI]
I... I...
It's been kinda hard
not having you around.
You better not
die of loneliness.
Look.
You haven't found
your purpose in life yet.
[HIDE]
But you will before too long.
'Kay? Now go.
You barely escaped
with your life.
Don't waste it.
Oh, and Kaneki.
[HIDE] Given the circumstances,
I don't regret what I did.
Not a bit.
But still,
I wanted to live at your side.
I won't shut up
till you hear me.
Even if you're a mess...
...live.
[KANEKI] My head keeps
playing reruns of past mistakes
with the same words on repeat.
Dorky.
Lame.
Worthless.
Indecisive.
Weak.
But still,
that's just... who I am!
[FURUTA screams]
You wiped out V's
most elite troops with ease!
Say, why don't we
just talk this out?
I think you may
be a bit confused
about where
the prison's exit is.
Why don't I point you
in the right way,
and we'll call it even?
[ETO]
No, I'm good.
Diplomacy failed!
Shrug off the past!
It's Nimura dash time!
[ETO]
Don't you wanna play?
No, I'm fine!
[FURUTA]
It's a dead end.
[ETO laughs]
I'll say it is.
[FURUTA]
I really dislike conflict, okay?
As such...
I'd like to end this peacefully.
What do you say?
[KANEKI] Beating you
will be no easy task.
[KANEKI]
Which means...
I win!
[FURUTA]
Aw...
Looks like you ate
your old friend for nothing.
[FURUTA]
I feel great!
Thank you, Dr. Kanou!
You changed my life!
That kagune... Is it Rize's?
[FURUTA]
Yes.
Kaneki and I have a matched set.
It's rather beautiful,
don't you agree?
Well, it is from her.
[ETO]
Nimura Furuta.
You don't seem to care
about your family or V,
so what is it you want?
I want super-peace.
Is that so much to ask for?
No! It's not!
Please feel free to kick the
bucket at your leisure, okay?
Duh-die! Duh-Die!
What the hell's with him?
[KANEKI]
It's over.
Your weapon's destroyed.
The fight goes on,
until you have dispatched
your opponent.
[KANEKI]
Of course you'd say that.
[gasps]
[KANEKI]
This fight is already over.
Keeping this up,
would be meaningless.
[ARIMA]
Then...
You have no
intention of killing me?
No.
[ARIMA]
So this is defeat.
I've been fighting ghouls and
killing them for 18 years.
But this is the first time
that I've faced an opponent.
And run out of options.
[ARIMA] I'll ask you
one last time, Kaneki.
Is it truly your intention
to leave me alive?
[KANEKI]
That's the choice I've made.
So be it.
[TAKIZAWA]
Hey, Amon.
I really, really...
[HOJI]
You remind me of your brother.
[HANBEI]
I won't abandon my men!
You can take that
resentment to your grave.
This is where you
will meet your end.