[FURUTA]
I'm grateful to you, Mutsuki.
[FURUTA] Under your leadership,
the Oggais were able to provide
the nourishment needed
to make Kaneki like this.
Allow me to thank you
for finding your way to him,
just as I knew you would.
[laughs]
Isn't love amazing?
So tell me, how does it feel?
Knowing your beloved
is a monster now,
and it's all because of you.
[gasps]
[FURUTA giggles]
Is it a boy?
Is it a girl?
No! It's a monster!
[MAN]
Hey. What the--?
[screaming]
As we've all just witnessed.
The monster has already
inflicted tremendous damage
and catastrophic casualties.
Its body stretches
throughout the city.
You found me
faster than expected.
[KANOU] Hoped I'd have time
for a quiet gravesite visit.
It would appear Furuta's made
a fine account of himself.
Information about ghouls once
suppressed by the Washu clan
will finally see
the light of day.
[KANOU] Ghoul research
will at last move forward.
Modern medicine will now
advance by leaps and bounds.
If only it had come sooner.
[hisses]
You think that can placate me?
Make amends by dying.
I'm not interested
in making amends.
Seeing as I've no regrets.
I envy you, though.
I'm not so good-natured
that I can nurse a hatred.
Kurona.
Let me apologize.
[gasps]
[gunshot]
[KANOU]
So this is death.
How fascinating.
[MARUDE]
We've located Kanou.
Or, his corpse, I should say.
[MABUCHI] He was the
last source of decent intel
we could've hoped to get.
So I would've thought,
but I'm told we have a backup.
[MABUCHI] Hold on,
what're you talking about?
[MARUDE]
Don't know.
Ask Nagachika.
[door opens]
Huh?
[MARUDE]
Who are you?
I was Dr. Kanou's assistant.
My name is Nishino.
[HIDE]
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Cool. It's working.
[AMON]
So, you can speak again?
[HIDE]
Yeah.
Thanks to Dr. Chigyo.
What were you doing
in that weird outfit?
[HIDE]
I was sizing things up.
Looking for people who might
be willing to help Kaneki.
If I had played
my cards a little better.
Kaneki might not
have ended up like this.
I failed him,
but I won't fail him again.
For me to pull this off,
I'm gonna need some help.
[AMON] You're asking for our
help as former investigators,
I take it.
[HIDE]
Yes.
I can guess what you need.
Damn it all.
Bet my father's turning
in his grave already.
[HIDE chuckles] Your instincts
are as sharp as ever.
[AMON]
Nagachika.
Why would you go this far
to rescue Ken Kaneki?
[HIDE]
Why?
Well,
I guess it's
'cause I like the guy.
Do I need more reason than that?
[AMON]
No.
Let's go.
You'll give your kid a cold.
Wish this would let up.
The rain, too.
[ITORI]
Hi, Touka!
[TOUKA]
Itori, hey.
Look at you.
You're a woman now.
What's the plan for Uta's group?
[ITORI]
Nothing's changed.
They plan to clown around,
as they always have.
I thought I'd ask the same thing
about your little flock here.
It might be best if
you made a run for it.
[TOUKA]
No, we...
[ITORI] You're resistant
to that, are you?
Then why not see him through?
[TOUKA]
How do you mean?
You know.
Kaneki only got this way
because he was trying
to help you, right?
A lot of people died...
Don't listen.
[ITORI]
...or were killed, I should say.
Kaneki crushed the
kind and the wicked alike.
Because all were complicit in
the persecution of ghouls.
Seems to me that
he did this for your sakes.
[MALE GHOUL A]
She's right.
The king did it for us.
[FEMALE GHOUL A] They needed
to suffer like we did.
[MALE GHOUL B]
He killed them like the doves
killed my brothers.
[FEMALE GHOUL B]
They killed my baby.
[MALE GHOUL A] The king saw
our pain and took his vengeance!
[FEMALE GHOUL A]
Yes.
He avenged our fallen.
[MALE GHOUL B]
Yeah!
And now it's our duty
to see him through!
That's not true!
So shut up.
He was always thinking
about humans.
Helping them.
Ghouls too.
It was all he ever did!
You want to "see him through"?
You think that's what's best?
Well, I think you're wrong.
Does no one want him
to find happiness but me?
He can't read books
like he loves to.
Or enjoy a cup of coffee.
Or chat with his friends,
and the people he loves.
He'll never even get
to hold his own child!
I don't want to see
him through like this.
I want to get him back
the way he was!
I want to watch him as
he leads us into the future.
And then!
With any luck I'll take
a bite of them both!
A father and child set!
Easy.
I've still got some old
gripes to bring up to him.
I just want a chance
to fully earn his trust.
I feel like
I never really thanked
him for saving me.
[TOUKA]
I need him to name our child.
My language skills are lacking.
[TSUKIYAMA]
That's beautiful!
I'll be thinking of names too,
so just let me know
if you want suggestions.
[TOUKA]
Nah, I'm good.
[NISHIO] So... what do
you think we should do now?
[HIDE]
Touka! How goes it?
[TOUKA]
Hide?
[KIMI] When the monster
becomes active again,
it'll go on a feeding frenzy in
order to replenish its strength.
[MARUDE]
How do we fight it?
That monster is a kakuja,
which means it was
formed by a ghoul.
That ghoul's body
is somewhere inside.
If we can remove it,
the rest should disintegrate.
Good luck though.
It's like a needle in a
haystack in a burning barn.
[MARUDE]
Is that our only chance,
or do we have
some kind of fallback?
We could always
just let it die on its own.
And how long do you
think that would take?
If I had to guess,
two hundred years.
Damn.
We'll just have to
find the real body then.
[MABUCHI]
You should see this, sir!
Huh?
What's all of this
commotion about?
[gasps]
Nagachika?
And Investigator Mado?
Amon, you're alive?
Wait.
What the hell is this?
[HIDE] I thought we
could use some backup.
Huh?
[HIDE] Our only chance is to
dig out the main body, right?
But humans alone
can only do so much.
We're gonna need
some mobility to pull this off.
You can't be serious.
Come on.
Are you suggesting that we
work side-by-side with ghouls?
[HIDE]
Yeah.
[MARUDE]
Are you joking?
[HIDE] These ghouls
could've run away easily,
but they're willing to help
you destroy that monster.
Because Ken Kaneki's inside it.
Ken Kaneki?
[MALE INVESTIGATOR A]
So the One-Eyed King,
turned into that thing?
Maman?
[MALE INVESTIGATOR C]
How could this have happened?
Where the hell's
the chief right now?
What does he have
to say about all this?
[UI] The chief has resigned,
in a sense.
The creation of that monster
was his true objective
from the beginning.
He played every person in the
CCG for a fool and succeeded.
You there.
Do you really believe that
investigators and ghouls
can work together?
Why don't you take a good
look at the faces of everyone
in front of you,
and think again.
Leave now, or you
will be dispatched.
[AMON]
Investigator Ui.
As an investigator, what is
your first and foremost duty?
It's to hunt down and
fight against ghouls.
[AMON]
You're wrong.
Yes, it's our duty to fight.
But it's peace we fight for.
You should fight for it now.
Even with ghouls at your side.
[SAIKO]
I'll fight!
I'll fight at their side!
These ghouls may have
been our enemy in the past,
but that isn't what
matters right now!
[MALE INVESTIGATOR A]
I won't do it!
It goes against
all that we stand for!
[MALE INVESTIGATOR C]
They're the real enemy here!
[FEMALE INVESTIGATOR A]
The CCG still has its pride!
Your so-called pride...
[gasps]
...can kiss my ass.
[MARUDE]
Huh...?
Damn.
I gotta hand it to them.
[FEMALE INVESTIGATOR B]
Look over there.
[FEMALE INVESTIGATOR C]
It's Suzuya Squad.
All right, Suzuya.
You make the call.
Huh?
Okay, then let's take
this thing on together.
It oughtta be a
piece of cake that way.
Ah...
Guess I'll have to suck it up.
I hope that you're
right about this.
[MARUDE] The CCG accepts
your offer of assistance.
[KIMI] We need a definitive
way to locate the main body.
If we could distinguish
some separate substance
within or around it.
[NISHIO]
Hey, beautiful.
I don't mean to
bother you, but...
Well...
I looked all over for you.
Why'd you run off
with Dr. Kanou?
Because I needed
to gain his knowledge.
And what were you
hoping to do with it?
[KIMI]
Make my dream come true.
Create a world where a human
could live free and openly...
...together with
a ghoul like you.
Nishiki.
Kimi.
[HIDE]
Guess he's takin' a nap.
How long have you
been in love with him?
Huh?
[HIDE]
C'mon, you can tell me.
[TOUKA]
Hmm...
I had gone off the rails and
fought the doves alone.
Then Kaneki told me he would've
been crushed if I had died.
And that was all it took.
[HIDE]
So that was it?
Well, it does sound
like something
that screwball would say.
[TOUKA] He's always so ready
to sacrifice himself to help me.
Hope I can help him this time.
[HIDE]
Let's try.
So... How'd the wedding go?
[TOUKA]
Uh... It was fine.
[HIDE]
What?
Come on, spill the beans!
Did you have time
for a honeymoon?
Ooh, did he give you a ring?
[TOUKA]
Yeah, well...
Actually, I gave him one.
[gasps]
That's how we can find him.
[HIDE]
Hmm?
Come with me!
[MARUDE]
A ring, you say?
[TOUKA]
Yes.
He'll be wearing a ring exactly
like the one I'm holding.
So with metal detectors--
Good plan.
As long as we get
enough metal detectors,
we can focus on
searching for the ring.
Which'll mean
finding Kaneki himself.
Still, that kakuja's
beyond massive,
and it's spread
throughout the city.
Which means we won't
have nearly enough detectors.
[MIRUMO]
Evening, Shu.
Doing well?
How can I help?
Hmm...
All right.
Hello, sir.
How are you?
[MARUDE] You got this many
of them, and in so little time?
How is that possible?
I asked the
prime minister for help.
If the media found out
they'd have a field day.
I'll leave the rest
to you, gentlemen.
You have our thanks.
Ghoul or not,
we're all Japanese.
It's becoming active again.
Commander!
We need to evacuate at once!
Please continue operations.
If he's allowed to
become fully active again,
his body will grow dozens
of times its current size
in a matter of days.
Tch!
Pardon, sir.
What now?
[MALE INVESTIGATOR H]
It's... It's spawning something.
Mabuchi.
How do the numbers look?
I'd estimate that
we're outnumbered
a hundred to one, sir.
[MARUDE]
In that case,
we can take these things.
Attention all personnel!
Continue the operation!
Office staff, deal with
those periodontal bastards!
Retreat is not an option!
Ghouls and Quinxes,
continue the search
and be quick about it!
[URIE]
Mutsuki!
You think he's okay?
[URIE]
Don't do this, Mutsuki.
What's going on with you?
There's no reason for us
to be fighting, is there?
Yonebayashi!
[MUTSUKI]
This is all my fault.
I... I'm the one who
turned Teach into a monster.
Look, that doesn't matter.
Huh?!
[gasps]
[SAIKO]
Mutsie.
The captain and the
rest of us at the chateau
have all been worried
sick about you.
I'm glad you're alive,
but I don't get it.
What do you want right now?
Just tell us how
so we can help you.
Mutsie.
We're ready
to talk when you are.
[MUTSUKI]
He knew.
From the moment I first met him,
he knew I was a woman.
[gasps]
Anyone else would've asked
what my problem was, but...
He pretended with me.
He protected my lie
as if it was his own.
Because all he cared
about was protecting me.
And how did I repay him?
[MUTSUKI]
By turning him into that thing!
I'm done!
If you want to stop me,
then kill me!
[shrieks]
Uri!
Not a chance.
[MUTSUKI]
Take all the hits you want.
I won't change my mind.
I've made my choice,
just accept it!
Mutsie, if this is
really how you want it to end.
Then why do you look
like you're hurting so bad?
[MUTSUKI] I... I wish
I'd just died before.
When Torso took me to the cave.
Or when I underwent
the Quinx surgery.
Or when I first
picked up a knife.
It's just...
Life at the chateau helped to
hold me together for a while.
It was the first place
I ever felt safe in my life.
[MUTSUKI]
I just wanted that back.
Oh well.
Doesn't matter now.
[MUTSUKI] I don't want
to hurt you two anymore.
And it's time I stopped
fooling myself.
I should've died
a long time ago.
I'm sorry about all the trouble.
[gasps]
[SAIKO] You really
think you should've died?
To hell with that!
What about...
What about me?
Did you ever stop to think
how I would feel if you died?
I love you, you jerk.
[URIE]
She's not the only one.
I feel the same,
and so did... Shirazu.
[gasps]
I know it hurts,
but stay alive for us.
If you still plan to die,
I want you to know that
we will stop you every time.
There's still
a lot of things to do...
[URIE] ...and I need
your help to do them.
Urie, I... I'm...
[SAIKO sobs]
Mutsie!
[MUTSUKI]
Sorry, Saiko.
[URIE]
You left some big shoes to fill,
but I'm getting' there, right?
Captain Shirazu.
[clock ticking]
[RIZE laughs]
What's you hurry, kiiler?
Stay for a while.
Oh.