[KANEKI]
Do it. Accept me as part of you.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon--
[HAISE]
I won't let you swallow me up.
[BOTH gasp]
[HAISE yells]
He destroyed Orochi's kagune!
[URIE] Don't get your
hopes up. It'll be back.
[HAISE]
You're stronger than I expected.
--[gasps]
--[OROCHI] Why, thank you.
So awesome!
He's using his kagune
and his quinque!
[OROCHI]
That's cheating!
How ya like this?
[groans]
Mr. Sass!
[HAISE] What'll I do?
I can't regenerate in time.
[KANEKI]
Haise.
Haise!
[HAISE gasps]
You okay?
Stand down.
But, Teach.
You heard the order. Follow it.
[MUTSUKI]
What's with him?
It's like he's
a different person.
You're not getting
past me, Orochi.
[OROCHI]
Oh, really?
You're a lot tougher
than those delinquents
I've been fighting.
What's your story?
[laughs] I should warn you,
you're much better off
not knowing anything about me.
[OROCHI]
This guy... He reminds me of--
[OROCHI groans, sputters]
[grunting, groaning]
Now it's payback time!
[OROCHI] If you keep this up,
you're gonna kill me.
Jeez. What is it with you?
Doesn't matter how hard you
try, you're irredeemable.
Kaneki.
It was you. Nishiki.
[HAISE grunts]
[HAISE]
What's going on?
Who the hell is Nishiki?
I can't think straight!
What am I saying?
[groaning]
[screams]
[OROCHI] Sorry,
old friend. But time's up.
I realize we came here
in pursuit of Orochi.
But now we've got an
SS-rated ghoul on our hands.
Prepare to restrain Haise.
[screams]
[MUTSUKI]
An SS-rated ghoul?
Kuramoto. Takeomi.
Yes, sir!
Ready!
[URIE]
Kuroiwa.
[groans]
Akira.
Yeah. He's in in my sights.
Time for a little nap, Haise.
So, our attempt to secure
Torso and Orochi failed.
I see.
[AKIRA]
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
No matter.
Now, tell me what
happened to Sasaki.
[AKIRA] He lost control
while fighting Orochi.
Thanks to Senior
Investigator Hirako,
we were able to restrain
him successfully.
I suppose it's possible
that contact with Orochi
triggered his breakdown.
Well, good work,
Senior Investigator Mado.
Please continue to look
after the Quinx Squad
and First Class Sasaki.
Yes, sir.
[AKIRA] The Quinx project
is Chief Washu's doing.
He initiated the
project himself.
And he's the one who selected
a half-ghoul, Haise Sasaki,
to act as the
Quinx Squad's mentor.
The question is: What
are his true motives?
[KIJIMA]
Investigator Mado.
Is something the matter, dear?
You have such a serious
look on your face.
[AKIRA]
I'm fine, Investigator Kijima.
Heard your last
mission was eventful.
Trouble with Sasaki?
Yes.
Luckily, we were able
to get him under control
without incident.
I find the Quinx Squad
utterly fascinating.
The half-ghoul--
First Class Sasaki--
and his team of investigators
with built-in quinques,
scouring the streets
for top-rated ghouls.
I would love to talk more,
but I must hurry along.
I have a guest coming
in from Germany
and must prepare
for their arrival.
It was a pleasure
to run into you.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Let's get going, Furuta.
[AKIRA]
Item.
Haise Sasaki is to be
treated as a human.
However, if he loses control,
investigators are required
to treat him as a ghoul
and he must be... exterminated.
[AKIRA] What a cruel
set of instructions.
[SAIKO]
O-Ooh! Ha, ha...
As an investigator,
if a foe threatens your life,
you run!
Does that really justify
a slap in the face?
[HAISE]
You're the captain!
You never should've
exposed them to danger.
Isn't it even more dangerous
to turn your back on the enemy?
If I hadn't shown up when I did,
you would all be dead.
Do you understand
the finality of death?
As long as you're breathing,
you've still got another chance.
But once you're gone,
there's no bringing you back.
Urie. I can't risk
this happening again.
You're relieved
as squad captain.
[BOTH gasp]
[URIE]
I find that hard to accept.
[HAISE]
Superior's orders.
You're just a ghoul to me.
[HAISE gasps]
[SHIRAZU]
Urie!
Mr. Sass risked his
life to save us,
you ungrateful bastard!
You're much worse than
any ghoul I've come across.
I should kill you right here
while I've got the chance!
I'd like to see you try.
[MUTSUKI] Urie. Don't
do this. Just apologize
[URIE]
Good for nothing hypocrites.
[HAISE]
C'mon, let him go, Shirazu.
Urie can say whatever he wants--
it's not going
to change my mind.
Besides, I've already
decided on a replacement.
Quinx Squad's new captain
is Investigator Ginshi Shirazu.
Huh?
[gasps]
[SHIRAZU]
Who, me?
Uh. But... I...
Hang on, are you sure, Mr. Sass?
That's a job for
someone with smarts.
I ain't got the chops!
You may not be the
sharpest tool in the shed,
but you'll look out for
the team. I trust you.
If you get too defiant,
I'll have no choice.
I'll devour you.
Y'know, since I'm
just a ghoul and all.
Hey, listen, Urie.
[SAIKO shrieks]
[bang]
[SAIKO whines]
Stupid score cap!
[ARIMA]
You chose Ginshi Shirazu?
[HAISE]
Yes.
Appearances notwithstanding,
he is considerate
of those around him.
There's no doubt that Urie
is outstanding, but...
[ARIMA] An interesting choice
of direction, Haise.
It's just like you.
I only hope that Urie...
sees this as an...
...opportunity to work
on his attitude.
You sound like a parent.
You care about them, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
They're like my high-maintenance
children, y'know?
Okay, I surrender.
You're getting
stronger. Not bad.
Arima. Mind if we talk?
Let me guess,
it's the voice again?
Yes, sir.
I tried to fight him off, but
he kept whispering in my ear.
Somehow, I just know
that's my former self.
I don't remember anything
about the first 20
years of my life.
It was hard. Realizing
that I'd lost so much.
But it doesn't matter.
I'm happy where I am.
If my former self resurfaces
and takes control.
I risk losing everything
I've worked so hard
to build over the last two
years, and that frightens me.
I understand, but what
about the friends and family
from your past that
you left behind?
I'm not concerned with them.
I have a family.
I'll be sure to stop by
the Chateau sometime soon.
I would like to
borrow another book.
[HAISE] You don't have
to go to all that trouble.
I can always just
bring it to you.
That's okay.
It'd be nice to see
my "grandkids," too.
[gasps]
[HAISE] If there comes a time
that I lose control,
and I can't go back to normal...
I hope Arima knows.
I'm sure he does.
[OROCHI]
You're irredeemable.
[HAISE] You're wrong.
I've been redeemed.
The only reason
I'm here is 'cause...
[HAISE]
I've found my place.
Even though it's
not a real family.
[SHIMOGUCHI grunting]
[SHIMOGUCHI]
Calling CCG HQ.
While Shimoguchi Squad
was investigating Torso...
We were attacked by
a ghoul from Aogiri.
[SHIMOGUCHI] Rabbit has left
my squadron incapacitated.
I repeat.
We were attacked
by the SS-rated ghoul
Rabbit.
[TAKEOMI]
Urie.
[URIE]
Yes, Kuroiwa?
How's Investigator Sasaki doing?
There's no need to worry.
Our squad's mentor is
tougher than you'd think.
[TAKEOMI]
Apparently. Well, good.
[URIE] No, it's not.
Nothing is "good," Kuroiwa.
You're the spawn of
that despicable man
who left my father to die.
There's no excuse.
Why didn't he fight
alongside him?
[URIE]
You don't know how it feels.
The pain of knowing that what
little remains of your dad
is lying inside a coffin.
You've still got your father.
You're a lucky bastard,
Takeomi Kuroiwa.
[TAKEOMI]
Well, let me know
when it'd be a good
time to stop by.
Take care of yourself.
[URIE] You, too. Don't work
yourself too hard.
[URIE] I hope he
works himself to death.
[AKIRA]
Thank you for seeing us.
I'm sorry to hear about
your men, Investigator.
I know it's hard,
but I need you to tell us
what happened that day.
You're telling me you want
your kagune beefed-up?
[URIE]
Yes, sir.
And you think doing
that will make you
more like Sasaki?
[SHIBA] You don't seem to
understand how this works.
I'll go over the science
with you one more time.
The idea to create
Quinxes, like you,
came about thanks to Sasaki's
unique half-ghoul state.
A kakuho was taken from a ghoul
and implanted within your body.
Then five stages of
Frames were set up.
You started at Frame 1,
but you've already
increased to Frame 2.
Your kakuho's currently
operating at 40% capacity.
[URIE]
I get it.
So, if I wanna use
a stronger kagune,
all we have to do is
raise my Frame level
and I'll be good
to go, right, Doc?
[SHIBA] Yes, but I
wouldn't recommend it.
[URIE]
Too late--my mind's made up.
[URIE] I wanna go through
with it, Dr. Shiba.
[SHIBA sighs]
[SHIBA] I'll need you
to get both the chief
and your mentor's
permission, please.
[URIE] Don't go playing
the moralist now, old man.
[HAISE]
The attacker goes by "Rabbit"?
Yeah.
The same ghoul who
teamed up with Fueguchi
to kill my father.
The infamous Kureo Mado.
Arima's told me all about him.
He said he was an
excellent investigator.
He also said
he learned how to handle
a quinque thanks to him.
I suspect Torso is
affiliated with Aogiri.
If that's true, it's a matter
of time before we lose the case.
HQ will want it taken over
by someone in S1 through S3.
[HAISE] Do you think
Shimoguchi's gonna be okay?
[AKIRA] I hope so, but he
was the only one to survive.
And that's a bitter pill.
Huh?
It's painful to lose
those who you've spent
so much of your time with.
[AYATO]
Know that, once you join Aogiri,
it won't be easy
for you to leave.
Think long and hard
before you make a decision.
[TORSO]
I don't have any choice,
I've got nowhere else to go.
But Aogiri?
How did it come to this?
[TORSO]
Hang on.
[TORSO] If I make use
of Aogiri, then maybe...
[AYATO]
Hey, Saeki.
Yeah? And you are?
[AYATO]
The name's Ayato.
What'd you wanna ask me?
[AYATO]
Rumor has it you went up against
the Quinx Squad.
Was there a guy named
Haise Sasaki among them?
This sucks!
We worked our tails off,
and for nothin'!
[URIE]
I'm back, what's up?
We just found out
that HQ decided
to pull us off the
Torso investigation.
Ugh. I'm more than
a little pissed off,
but they're sayin' they
have reason to believe
he's a member of Aogiri Tree.
Then there's nothing we can do.
S1 through S3 are in charge
of Aogiri matters, remember?
Yeah, but it blows
'cause I feel like
we almost had him, y'know?
I know how you feel,
but we can't get
mixed up with them.
Do you have any idea how
many casualties there were
in the war against
Aogiri Tree two years ago?
Well? Do you?
I dunno.
[door opens]
[SHIRAZU]
What're you doin', Saiko?
[SAIKO sighs]
[SHIRAZU] No way.
Don't even think about it.
You seriously gonna eat
that whole ham by yourself?
[yells]
[SAIKO]
It's so crispy and juicy!
[door slams]
[sighs]
Anyway. What's next?
Do we have orders yet?
[SHIRAZU] Uh-huh. They
want us to track down
a ghoul called "Nutcracker."
[NUTCRACKER humming]
[CLIENT]
Hurry up. Just do it!
Is this for real?
I'm so excited!
[NUTCRACKER] Then I won't
keep you waiting, big boy.
[chuckles]
[CLIENT screams]
[SHIRAZU]
Okay, Mr. Sass.
As leader of the "Shirazu
Squad" I've gotta ask.
Got any tips on how we go about
finding our next target?
Ah! Hey, what'd
you do that for?
I was just tryin'
to look the part!
[HAISE]
She's called "Nutcracker."
She operates in the
red-light district.
Her rating's still under review.
What's with the
name "Nutcracker"?
Seems weird to me.
[HAISE]
Apparently, she's got a thing
for smashing the testicles
of her victims.
[SHIRAZU]
Ew...
[MUTSUKI]
That sounds... painful.
[HAISE]
Oh, by the way, Captain Shirazu.
May I ask why Urie and
Saiko aren't joining us?
I saw Urie this morning,
but he wasn't feeling good.
He said he was going
to see Dr. Shiba.
He seemed to think there
was something off
with his Frame.
Said he might have to stay in
the hospital for a few days.
Hm?
[HAISE]
You should've reported to me
as soon as you found out.
Sorry 'bout that.
[HAISE]
What about Saiko?
We tried to wake
her up this morning,
but there was no answer.
Couldn't get into her room
'cause the door was locked.
I really hope she didn't
die of ham poisoning.
Ham what?
[sniffs]
Well, well, what do you know?
I have a feeling it's
gonna be a great day.
And why's that?
Oh, no reason.
Do you mind if we
stop in really quick?
[MUTSUKI]
":re"?
[door bell chimes]
[gasps]
What an aroma!
I guarantee you this café serves
a delicious cup of coffee.
Trust me, my "nasal kagune"
hasn't let me down yet.
[SHIRAZU] Mr. Sass sure is
stoked about this place.
[MUTSUKI] He told me trying
different coffee shops
around town is
sort of his hobby.
[SHIRAZU]
Hm...
[TOUKA]
Aw, c'mon, Yomo,
how many times do we
have to go over this?
When customers come in, it's
your job to greet them and--
[gasps]
♪ ...and think of you. ♪
♪ Am I imagining you here,
right next to me? ♪
♪ Your eyes catch my own, ♪
♪ I look back fleetingly, ♪
♪ before I realize
you're really there. ♪
♪ I dreamed you'd
be beside me, ♪
♪ that we would meet again. ♪
♪ Your eyes glisten,
your tears are falling. ♪
♪ I know you have not
forgotten the past that ♪
♪ we shared as I quietly watch
you wipe your tears away. ♪
It tastes... so familiar to me.
♪ Although I've found you, ♪
♪ I know this meeting
will not last. ♪
♪ I have to let go... ♪
[HAISE]
She stood there, smiling.
Like she was at a loss.
Or maybe feeling a little sad.
♪ It's time to wake
from this dream. ♪
[HAISE]
And I...
[HAISE] I asked myself,
how could anyone...
[HAISE]
...be as pretty as her?
[clock ticking]
[KANAE]
Master Shu.
[SAIKO]
No. Three of 'em.
[KANAE]
Can you smell anything, Master?
[DONATO] I couldn't care
less what happens to him...
[HAISE] For this mission,
we become women!
[SAIKO] Don't tell me
that you guys are Quinxes!
[HAISE]
Now watch your language, Shi!
[SHIRAZU]
Brah, you're off your nut!
[SAIKO]
I don't really wanna.
[HAISE]
The 11th of November, sir.
[MATSURI]
...their own squadron.
[static]