[KIMI] The dragon's vitals are
starting to become active again.
[HIDE]
And those creatures it spawns
are still turning
humans into ghouls.
[NISHIO]
We dug Kaneki out of it,
shouldn't it have at least
slowed down by now?
[KIMI] That was my theory,
but look at this.
It has another core.
[HIDE]
It has more than one?
We've got our work
cut out for us, then.
Then we should get to it.
Let's send a few scouts,
get an idea of what--
[KIMI]
We don't have time for that.
[HIDE]
How much do we have?
[KIMI] Based on the limited
analysis I've been able to do,
I'd have to say
twelve hours at best.
[HIDE] And if the monster
does become active again.
[NISHIO] Every human in
Tokyo will become a ghoul.
[TSUKIYAMA] Then we'll
just have to charge in blind.
[KIMI] But the underground
route to the core is dense
with the same gases produced
by the dragon's spawn.
That wouldn't be a problem
for a ghoul, right?
It's less of one,
but you still have a limit.
Exceed a certain threshold, and
it'll affect your RC cell count.
Then I should
be the one to go in.
[gasps]
With my RC count,
I doubt the gas'll affect me.
[KIMI]
Fair point.
Your RC levels
are abnormally high,
but not much higher
than they were before.
It's risky though.
Can't catch a break.
There are quite a few of them.
Guess they plan
to put us down for good.
[KANEKI]
We need to move.
I'll head to the core right now.
Kimi, I'm counting
on your support.
As for you, please stay
here and help the CCG.
I'll go too.
[KANEKI]
Ayato?
Where have you been?
I've been out
scouting underground,
watching that monster grow.
[TOUKA]
Ayato, Kaneki.
You two be sure to make it back.
Till then.
[MARUDE]
Attention all personnel.
Beat them.
That's an order.
[ITORI] Looks like they still
have some fight in them.
[UTA]
More than expected, I'd say.
We need to buy some time.
[DONATO]
You are quite correct.
Let's bring it out.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Die! Die, die, die!
Kaneki can't, so je vais
couper vous in his stead!
What'll it take to shut him up?
[chuckles]
Good luck, Teach.
[whistling sound]
Can't be sure, but I think
that was the last of them.
[URIE]
Something's off.
The numbers don't add up.
But I didn't see
them retreat, so...
[whistling sound]
Huh?
That sound.
You know what's causing it?
Couldn't say.
Huh? What's that?
[gasps]
Where the hell
did that thing come from?
Another Owl?
How?
[KAIKO]
You're Kisho's man.
I consider this quite fitting.
Since I never got to exact
my revenge on that traitor,
it's only fair that the
first human I taste
should be his
most faithful acolyte.
You let those
monsters infect you?
[KAIKO]
Infect?
Oh, no.
This is a blessing.
I was once a
wretched half-breed,
but the dragon gave me
new life as a ghoul.
I've never felt such perfect
harmony with my body.
The dragon that you cower
in fear of, is the ark of life.
Damn it all!
Ukaku squad!
You give me a constant barrage!
Don't stop shooting!
You're up, Suzuya!
Nicely done, Suzuya.
Now!
My turn!
Did it work?
Got it.
[HIDE]
Not yet.
It survived.
Not bad.
Feels like I was born with it.
[JUZO]
Oh, wow.
I don't know how
to kill this one.
[KIMI] There's a huge group of
those creatures straight ahead.
It looks like this must be
where they incubate.
Regardless, you're closing
in on the second core.
It's further down.
[KANEKI]
Strange.
I can't get her out of my head.
[crackling sounds]
[KANEKI]
Huh?
[AYATO]
Bastards are hatching.
Get down!
[AYATO]
More coming out every second.
Kaneki!
Go on ahead.
I'll stop them.
There's no one who can
take your place, Kaneki.
You need to save your
strength for the real fight.
So go!
[AYATO]
Best of luck,
ya damn in-law.
[MARUDE]
That monster isn't letting up.
How many of us can still move?
[INTEL]
Checking that now, sir.
[NISHIO]
Nagachika, you read me?
[HIDE]
Uh. Yeah!
There was a weird noise
right before this thing showed.
It was like a whistling sound.
Do you think there
could be a connection?
[HIDE]
It's possible.
[gasps]
Put on the map please.
The Owl's headless.
What if it's being
controlled remotely?
[HIDE]
Hinami!
Probe to the south, please.
About seven o'clock.
I'm on it.
[HINAMI]
The rumble of engines, close.
Shouting, further off.
Hurried footsteps.
The last breaths of a dying man.
Vibrations in the air,
displaced by the Owl.
But beyond that, even further.
I can just make out
something else.
I found them!
They're on the roof of
a building three blocks
to the south.
[ITORI] Oh my, it sounds
like they're onto us.
[DONATO]
Then we should relocate.
Go on ahead.
[UTA]
Good luck, Crown.
It's been a good while,
hasn't it, Kotaro?
[DONATO]
That was a fine attempt.
You're strong.
However.
It looks like
experience will triumph.
[UTA] I can't tell you
how long I've dreamt
this moment would come.
Or how I've imagined the
sweet warmth of your blood,
as I grasp at
your beating heart.
Let's have some fun.
[YOMO]
This isn't fun for me, Uta.
It's painful, and I don't
mean the hole in my stomach.
Even now, you're a friend.
Huh?
[YOMO]
I won't kill you.
And I won't have
you killing me, either.
[laughs]
I'm so glad to have
you as my friend.
Renji dear.
Always the straight-shooter.
Not a bit of guile in you.
Even with the world as it is,
you, I can always trust.
[laughs]
Don't you see?
I have always wanted to eat you.
[UTA] Make me feel
like I'm alive, Renji.
[UTA]
Now you're all mine.
[UTA] Come on, Renji, how
can this not be fun for you?
[pants]
[YOMO]
Uta.
We grew up a long time ago.
We can't keep playing
games forever.
[UTA] We would have such fun,
playing together.
Why'd you stop?
[UTA]
Hey.
You remember that fight?
The one we came out of without
a working leg between us?
And Itori took us
home on her back.
No matter what was destroyed,
or how much blood
the two of us spilled.
In those days,
none of it mattered.
But that's over now, isn't it?
[UTA]
The world changed around us.
You adapted,
while I stayed the same.
[YOMO] If you want
to eat me, then try again.
[gasps]
I mean, that's not
to say I'll let you,
but I wouldn't mind you
causing me trouble.
After all, we're friends.
[UTA]
I see.
That's quite mature.
Hold on.
You can't carry me like this.
[YOMO]
Watch me.
[MUTSUKI]
Huh?
[AMON]
In all these years,
I never harbored any
feeling but hatred for you.
But some part of me knew.
A truth that refused to be
ignored or pushed aside.
[AMON] This world
can be terribly cruel.
And you made it worse.
[AMON]
You're as twisted as they come.
But so am I.
[AMON]
Because...
...I loved you.
[DONATO chuckles]
Here lies Donato Porpora,
who was every bit the
villain you knew him to be.
I'm sure this looks like the
carnage of the apocalypse.
But man is cunning.
All shall be renewed.
I've but helped
to till the field.
[chuckles]
This is a fitting death,
I think.
After all the reaping I've done,
it's only fair that I should
miss the harvest to come.
And it's also fitting that
a paragon of justice like you
should be the one to--
[AMON] You used to make us
donuts for breakfast, by hand.
When we got cold at night,
you'd bring us extra blankets.
When the dog we used
to keep passed away,
you dug it a grave
in the mountains.
When you say "we,"
you speak of yourself
and the children I dined
on in the shadows.
Are those days
still nostalgic for you?
[AMON]
Yes, they are.
As much as
I've tried to hate you.
As hard as I've tried to forget.
I can't do it.
I can't help but treasure
every moment I spent
at that orphanage.
Is it so wrong for a son
to love his father?
[laughs]
After everything,
you call me father.
[laughs]
Looks like this is round two.
[FURUTA]
What are you doing here?
Oh goodness.
Don't tell me you
wanna do something crazy.
Like bringing all of
this to a premature end.
Well, if that's
how it has to be.
Then do your worst.
I should warn you,
I'm surprisingly strong.
[clock ticking]
[KANEKI]
Thank you.