[AMON]
Akira.
Huh?
[AKIRA]
Amon.
Hey.
All that time we spent.
I feel like I was
wasting it, now.
[AMON]
Where'll you go?
[AKIRA]
That's a damn good question.
All I had left
to drive me was hate.
And now I'm out of that.
So where can I go?
[AMON]
You can go anywhere you want.
Huh?
Our lives...
They aren't over.
Alive is all I am now.
I'm nothing.
[AMON] Emotions are
what guide us forward.
Emptiness is one of them.
[AKIRA]
So just let myself feel it?
Yeah.
I'm scared.
[AMON]
I'm here.
For as long as you'll have me.
[AKIRA]
Don't block me this time.
[TSUKIYAMA] According to
information from our people
in the third hideout,
there's a ghoul community
near this waterfront.
And the doves are
planning to attack it.
We need to hurry.
[NISHIO]
I understand how you feel,
but you can't save us all,
my king.
[NISHIO]
This is ugly.
[TSUKIYAMA]
We've always been targeted,
but not like this.
The world above-ground
is no longer safe.
Are you a virgin?
[TV] We can expect
increasingly cloudy skies today.
Huh?
You heard.
Answer the question.
[KANEKI]
Wait.
Where's this
question coming from?
Uh. I just figured you were.
Y'know, I'd be willing
to help you with that.
Wait. Are you saying
what I think?
[FURUTA]
Feast your eyes!
We have dispatched yet
another den of ghouls.
We'll suffer their presence
among us no more.
There is no place for ghouls
in a perfect world.
It's the third hideout.
We need to move
to the 24th Ward fast.
Huh?
Touka?
What's up?
[TOUKA] Ayato is already
on his way there.
Yeah, but the other
hideouts, they need my help.
Stop trying to take
everything on yourself.
[gasps]
Tsukiyama's here.
So are Nishiki and Yomo.
And the Aogiri Tree people, too.
You need to rely
on your friends more.
Each time this stuff comes up.
I try to figure out how
to stop you from going.
It's not hard to see that
you're okay with dying,
but you're still needed.
Think I get it now.
So that's why you said
what you said earlier?
That was part of it.
Back when you were a dove,
you'd come to this
shop alone sometimes.
You'd steal glances.
Use your book for cover.
The look in your eyes.
I recognized it.
I'd seen you make
the same eyes at Rize.
[KANEKI]
I feel like such an idiot.
[TOUKA] Surprised you never
caught me making them back.
[door opens]
[gasps]
[MUTSUKI]
Teach.
[KANEKI]
Mutsuki.
I knew I'd find you someday.
Teach, please.
I need you.
We all do.
Come back to us.
I'll do anything you ask.
I'm sorry.
But I can't do that.
[gasps]
This shop.
It's rank with
the stench of ghouls.
So you've really
turned against us.
Against the Quinxes, the CCG,
and me as well.
[MUTSUKI]
Did we ever mean a thing to you?
Of course.
[MUTSUKI] You aren't
yourself right now, Teach.
What's holding you back from me?
Tell me, so I can destroy it.
Mutsuki! Stop this!
Aw! That voice.
It's good to hear it again.
[KANEKI] Blade's coated
with RC inhibitors.
Kaneki!
Buy a damn drink.
Or get out!
Just die.
You thieving tramp!
It's you.
It's your fault!
[MUTSUKI]
Bitch.
This is why I hate women.
Huh?
After them!
Scary.
I'll gut that bitch.
I'll kill her.
I'll kill her!
[URIE]
Special Investigator.
The chief is looking for you.
[JUZO]
And I'm blowing him off.
Don't suppose
you'd care to join.
Sounds good to me.
[JUZO]
That smell in the air.
It takes me back.
[URIE]
To the battle for the 20th Ward?
Yeah.
It's the scent of blood
in the streets.
[JUZO] What do you think
peace really looks like?
People fight ghouls.
So if one or the other
were to disappear,
could you call that peace?
I would've been happy if things
had stayed the way they were.
[door opens]
[URIE]
Kuroiwa, what's up?
[gasps]
Wait.
No.
You're getting married?
You know what?
That's what peace looks like.
♪ I dreamed you
were beside me, ♪
♪ you were there once again,
as if you had never left, ♪
♪ and I remember
wanting to say, ♪
♪ asking you not to go, ♪
♪ but I know that
was impossible then... ♪
♪ You say "I can't stay here"
as my damp eyes open. ♪
♪ The sunshines on
the bleak horizon. ♪
♪ It's just another day.  ♪
♪ I look out at the dimly lit
buildings and think of you. ♪
♪ Am I imagining you here,
right next to me? ♪
♪ Your eyes catch my own, ♪
♪ I look back fleetingly, ♪
♪ before I realize
you're really there. ♪
♪ I dreamed you'd
be beside me, ♪
♪ that we would meet again. ♪
♪ Your eyes glisten,
your tears are falling. ♪
♪ I know you have not
forgotten the past that ♪
♪ we shared as I quietly watch
you wipe your tears away. ♪
♪ Although I've found you, ♪
♪ I know this meeting
will not last. ♪
♪ I have to let go
continue finding your way, ♪
♪ though I will miss you. ♪
♪ It's time to wake
from this dream. ♪
[cheering, applause]
[SAIKO]
Get it, boi!
This belonged to my parents.
[TOUKA]
It's something I treasure.
So I want you to have it.
Thank you.
It's a good gift.
I'll think of you
every time I see it.
[KANEKI] Guess we should go
back to the 24th Ward now.
They'll be waiting.
[TOUKA]
Yeah.
[UTA]
Itori, what have you found out?
Anything good?
[ITORI]
But of course.
What do you take me for?
Goat has moved to the 24th Ward.
[UTA]
They're underground?
[ITORI]
Yes.
The way things are going,
they're doomed.
[ITORI]
They may be.
But that said,
I wouldn't mind witnessing
their final moments for myself.
Why not watch the curtains
fall on them together?
From the premium seats.
Sounds good to me.
[door opens]
Huh?
[NICO] You've outdone
yourself, "Chief."
Can't let you give
me too much credit.
The true Washu's had
been slacking off is all.
But soon enough
I'll stop with these skirmishes
and bring this game
to a proper end.
And I take it
you've selected the piece
you'll need to checkmate them?
[FURUTA]
I need someone merciless.
Someone with the strength
to make these pacifists
wet themselves and flee.
They'll be the final boss.
[UTA]
Do you mean to use them on Goat?
Or will they strike the CCG?
[FURUTA] All that matters
is that they're on my side.
I am preparing the
mightiest of enemies.
One strong enough
to slay Kisho Arima
or Eto Yoshimura with one blow.
A veritable dragon.
Chief,
you called for me?
[FURUTA]
Takeomi Kuroiwa, was it?
I called you here
because I have something
I'd like to ask you about.
Sir?
Before that,
would you mind
jogging my memory?
What does it say in
Paragraph 1, Article 88
of the Anti-Ghoul act?
[TAKEOMI] The passage
states that it's illegal
to harbor a ghoul
or enable its escape.
A crime which can sometimes
be punished by death.
[TAKEOMI]
Yes, sir.
Well then,
with that little fact in mind,
I'd like you to come with me.
Huh?
[TAKEOMI]
Urie.
What's going on here?
Yoriko's high school
best friend was a ghoul.
A fact which just came to light.
She was arrested?
Yoriko says she
didn't know at the time.
Trouble is, that kind of
thing's impossible to prove.
[NISHIO]
Kaneki.
[KANEKI]
Huh?
Have you heard any
news from the CCG?
[NISHIO] They're still
hell-bent on finding our king.
Looks like they plan to kill
this group by crushing its head.
[KANEKI]
Sound thinking.
As a matter of fact, we might
try to do the same thing.
[sighs]
Don't you think you should be
a little more careful
with your life now?
Your kid's gonna need a dad.
Huh?
Uh...
Huh? My kid?
[NISHIO]
My bad.
Forget I said a thing. Later.
[KANEKI pants]
Touka!
Hey, Touka!
Yeah? What?
How are you?
Y'wanna?
Huh?! Oh no!
It isn't that. I-I mean...
Not that I don't want to!
It's just...
Well I thought I'd ask, how
you've been feeling lately.
Now that you mention it.
My foot's sore.
And what else?
I'm sleepy.
My hair's getting kinda dry.
And what else?
Hey, what's this all about?
[KANEKI]
Nothing, really.
Also,
I think I'm pregnant.
I'm not sure if
I'll actually deliver.
I had planned to tell
you once I felt more sure.
Prob'ly should'a
told you sooner.
Sorry.
So, uh, when's it due?
This December.
Okay.
Touka, I'm glad.
[gasps]
Really?
Yeah.
[KANEKI]
So, um...
Do ghouls have their
own way of getting married?
Uh.
We don't have to--
I'm just curious.
If we did wanna get married,
what would we do first?
Well, for us, there's no need.
I mean, it's already
been done in a way.
And it's a little bit
awkward to talk about.
How come?
[TOUKA]
To get married.
We would mark each other.
[KANEKI]
Like how?
[TOUKA]
On our bodies, with a bite.
As hard as we can.
So the mark will never fade.
Even in death.
[SAIKO]
I wanna save her.
Yoriko is Takeomi's wife,
and she's also a friend.
She makes yummy bread
and she shares it with me.
[URIE]
Let it go.
The chief made his decision.
We have to accept it.
[SAIKO gasps]
Don't you care at
least a little bit?
[URIE] Doesn't matter if I care,
the verdict's final.
You pigheaded jerk!
That training
you guys do all day
really did screw up your heads.
You're all certifiable!
[URIE] This doesn't
sit right with me either,
but we can't stop it.
[SAIKO]
I'm done with this crap.
I'll become a NEET.
No.
I'll become a terrorist!
[URIE]
Yonebayashi.
[SAIKO]
The CCG isn't good anymore.
It's just a bunch
of murderers now.
And I don't want any part of it!
[URIE]
Saiko.
I know there's nothing
we can do to save Yoriko.
Uri.
I'm sorry.
It's true that the
CCG's been perverted.
We've lost sight of
what we used to fight for.
We've grown numb to it,
but years from now,
people might look
at what we're doing.
And see us as criminals.
Unless we raise our voices
and make it stop.
How are we gonna do it?
We'll have to find a way.
[SAIKO]
And what if we can't?
If we can't...
...then we'll both
become terrorists.
[CROWD]
Congratulations!
[cheering]
[YOMO]
Let's dance till morning, Nishi!
[NISHIO]
Hey! Gimme back my drink!
[TOUKA]
Pretty amazing.
I never thought they'd do
a whole reception for us.
Tsukiyama said it
would be good for morale.
I think he just wanted
to throw a party.
The man does know
how to plan a celebration.
I'll give him that.
So tell me.
Is this what you wanted?
[clock ticking]
Kaneki.
[JUZO]
I always liked you, Haise.
But I'll kill you the
same as anyone else.
[ROMA laughs]
[static]