[KANAE panting]
[KANAE]
Beady-eyed scheizkerl.
If I ever see him again...
...I'll kill him.
[ETO giggles]
[gasps]
Why, hello there.
It's Kanae, right?
[KANAE]
Who are you? A ghoul?
No, the scent's off.
Which is she?
[ETO]
Funny smell, isn't it?
Have you decided if
I'm a fellow ghoul
or a human being yet?
Tell you what.
Guess right, and I'll
give you this apple.
Just who are you?
[ETO]
Oh, hey.
You're the last surviving
Rosewald, aren't you?
[KANAE]
How does she know so much?
[KANAE] I'm not in the
mood to be jerked around.
I'll fill my stomach with you!
[ETO laughs]
[ETO giggles]
Where'd you go?
[KANAE grunts]
You want me to
fill your stomach?
I doubt you could finish me.
[KANAE]
One eye?
[ETO]
Yes, that's correct!
[KANAE grunts]
[sputters]
[ETO]
Are you full yet?
Remember the tree of knowledge?
Why did God put it
in the garden of Eden?
Strange, right?
It's almost like he was
telling them to eat from it.
The God that I've
always imagined
is not some benevolent,
all-knowing father.
But a careless child
with tremendous power.
[KANAE]
What are you talking about?
[ETO]
Look, I'm just saying,
this world is far too full
of defective items.
Like you, for example.
[KANAE gasps]
No matter how
desperately you tried
to restore poor
Tsukiyama's sanity,
you couldn't do it.
But that remnant of a man
called Haise Sasaki
brought him back.
And all it took was one look.
[KANAE gasps]
[ETO] In truth, you'd like
to kill Haise. Right?
[ETO] You never really wanted
your master to get better,
now did you?
That's not true!
I wish for Master Shu's
health above all else!
You must realize that
he doesn't love you.
Stop talking.
[ETO] And there's no reason
to go on loving someone
when you know full well
they're never gonna
love you back.
Shut up!
Shut your mouth.
Shut up, shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up!
Now you see.
My loyalty to Master Shu was--
[ETO]
Mere possessiveness.
[KANAE]
I-I...
[ETO] You need the
fruit of the garden.
Knowledge, in exchange
for your life.
From this moment on,
you will know me as your god.
[SHIRAZU]
Hey! Wait up, Urie.
I told you to stop
trying to work alone.
If you won't pick up
your new quinque,
and all you have to fight with
is that half-baked Kagune,
then you have no right
to tell me anything.
[SHIRAZU gasps]
[URIE] If you can't fight,
then quit. Idiot.
[BOY A]
Hey, pass the ball!
[BOY B] You slowpokes
couldn't catch an old lady!
[HARU]
Big Brother? My eye's itchy.
Lemme look.
Oh. There's somethin'
growin' there.
[HARU groans]
It'll be okay.
We'll get a doctor
to check it out.
'Kay!
[SHIRAZU]
Haru.
[HARU]
Brother. I want to...
...to be pretty.
Pretty like... a princess.
♪ Pretty like a princess. ♪
[SHIRAZU]
Money. I need money.
I have to get it somehow.
I don't have to
like killing ghouls.
I just have to keep doing it.
To keep on making money.
[FURA] You're from
Sasaki's group, right?
[SHIRAZU]
Huh? First Class Fura.
That's me.
So you can't use your quinque?
[BOY C laughs]
Well. You're in
fairly decent company.
It's common with new guys.
Mr. Sass--I-Investigator
Sasaki said that, too.
[FURA]
Honestly,
I couldn't use the quinque I got
from my first kill, for a while.
[SHIRAZU] Huh? So then,
how did you get over it?
You're not gonna
just wake up one day
and "be over it."
You'll feel guilt and regret.
See the bleeding faces
of your victims.
Smear yourself with layer
after putrid layer of doubt.
But then, eventually,
an answer comes along
that lets you come to terms
with what you've done.
I don't have the most
rational disposition.
So for me, that answer
was a long time coming.
[FURA]
Look, Shirazu. If you ask me,
the people who pull their
hair out over every kill
are in a better place mentally
than the ones who don't.
It's not a noble
profession we've chosen.
We're butchers. What we
take from them is life.
[SHIRAZU] What we take
from them... is life.
You can take it from here.
Shirazu, how goes it?
You try out your nut yet?
Otherwise, I'll use it.
[SHIRAZU]
Hayashimura.
[HAYASHIMURA]
Hm?
I need you to do me a favor.
What is it?
So. Shirazu, uh. What's new?
[HAISE] You didn't get yourself
into trouble, did you?
I won't get mad if
you did. Just tell me.
[SHIRAZU]
I'm sorry, guys.
I know I've been dragging
you all down lately.
From now on,
I'm gonna be the squad
captain you deserve.
And I wanna thank you, Urie.
For putting things
into perspective.
Sure.
[URIE]
When did I do that?
[UI] Although we've
yet to confirm this.
It seems Rose and Aogiri Tree
have formed an alliance.
If I might speculate, sir.
Given its timing,
this move could be
in response to the video.
Well, well.
It would seem that
my little provocation
has born unexpected fruit.
What fruit?
This development is
quite clearly a setback.
[KIJIMA] Are you sure?
I see an opportunity here.
If Rose and Aogiri Tree
have opted to work together,
then any information
we obtain about one
could also teach us
about the other.
If I may, sir.
I think investigator
Kijima may be right.
As long as we can beat them,
I don't really see a problem.
Excuse me?
My apologies sir.
Without proper knowledge
of the enemy's strength,
expanding the scope
of this investigation
would be a fool's gambit.
Then finding out should
be our first priority.
Special Investigator Ui.
Would you reconsider the
mission I proposed before?
[UI sighs]
[UI] Very well.
Please fill in the others.
Yes, sir.
[SHIRAZU] You really look
the part, Mister Sass.
[HAISE] Oh, yeah?
So, we get any useful intel?
[SHIRAZU] Yeah. We went
undercover in the 18th ward.
Apparently, it's run
by someone called
"Three Blades Miza."
If our luck holds up,
then I think
we might be able to find
a member of Aogiri tree.
[HAISE]
You don't say.
Urie? How 'bout you?
We carried out our investigation
in the sixth ward.
All the ghouls we came
in contact with there
had their guards up.
Further investigation
may be needed.
They're probably acting
a bit warier these days
on account of what's
happened with Rose.
[HAISE] I can see how
that would make them
more cautious around outsiders.
[HAISE sighs]
[SHIRAZU] So how'd it go
for you, Mister Sass?
[HAISE]
O-Oh.
[GHOULS gasp]
[GHOUL B]
Oh, no, it's Eyepatch!
[GHOULS pant, yelp]
[HAISE]
This mask.
It seems that it's
known amongst ghouls.
[HAISE] I need to learn more
about the Eyepatch Ghoul.
[HAISE] Kotaro Amon was killed
in the line of duty.
Strange, it doesn't
give any details.
[HAISE] Is that information
being concealed?
Maybe it's the same
with the Eyepatch ghoul.
But why?
[grunts]
[KANEKI]
It... It was me.
[gasps]
[KANEKI]
He's dead because...
Because I...
I killed him.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Aliza.
[gasps] Master Shu.
I'm so sorry.
Yuma was captured because of me.
[ALIZA] That's all right.
Don't blame yourself.
[ALIZA]
I just wanna see him again.
[TSUKIYAMA]
I give you my word.
I'll do everything in my
power to bring him back.
[TSUKIYAMA] Bon jour.
I'd hoped I might run into you.
Actually, I wanted
to see you, too.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Then this is doubly fortunate.
Sorry. But are you a ghoul?
[TSUKIYAMA gasps]
Let me rephrase that.
Are you someone
who knew Ken Kaneki?
[TSUKIYAMA] Can I tell him
the truth? I don't know.
Before now, I tried
to avoid my past,
to bury my former self.
But... I need to
find out who he was.
So that I can become
his redemption.
First, tell me this.
Does it bother you
that, in doing so,
you may be forsaking that self?
[inhales]
That's fine.
[TSUKIYAMA gasps]
[HAISE] I want to be human,
even with this body.
Kaneki was someone
who was dreaded
even by his fellow ghouls.
That isn't who I want to be.
I want my life to stay
like it is forever.
But someday, I know that
I'll have to remember.
I guess, it's something
like my destiny.
So I'm asking.
Please, if you know
anything about me,
then say it.
I'm sorry, but I
no longer know...
[TSUKIYAMA] ...what it is
I should say to you.
Would you ever die for
your ingredients, Tsukiyama?
[TSUKIYAMA]
Hori. You knew, didn't you?
That I couldn't
allow myself to die.
There are too many people
I hold precious in this world,
for me to leave it.
[TSUKIYAMA] But, I certainly
did enjoy those days.
When I could simply
gaze upon my delicacies.
Truly. It's something
I shall miss.
[ALIZA whimpering]
[KIJIMA] You must've known
that I only let word
of my whereabouts spread
because I was hoping
that someone would
come after me.
I must admit, this is
quite touching to see.
You attacked me all by yourself
in the hopes of
saving your friend.
He's already dead of course,
but the thought was there.
[KIJIMA] Ah, what a tug
on the heartstrings.
However, I must admit
that I'm concerned
about how loose those
lips of yours are.
Everybody knows
that a good servant
should always be discreet.
[KIJIMA] You truly were
a brave young woman.
May all your comrades
be the same.
[UI] The Tsukiyama group
has been influential
for more than 100 years.
Their company has assets in
a wide variety of industries
with over 20 subsidiaries.
If the truth were
to become public,
we'd surely face pressure
from all quarters,
which would hinder
our investigation.
Please request an
information blackout
and a full investigation into
the Tsukiyama company
and its affiliates.
Very well.
Captain of the S1 Squad,
Senior Investigator Kori Ui.
You are hereby
commanded to carry out
"Operation Dispatch Tsukiyama."
Yes, sir!
[UI] Special Investigator
Washuu. Need something?
[MATSURI]
S2 will be supporting you.
This is a courtesy call.
I'll be presiding
over this mission,
and I'm glad to
have you onboard.
And I look forward
to seeing you in action.
[UI] That damn hyena's just
hoping he can claim more credit.
[MATSURI] He's just
a punk from Arima's cult.
[AKIRA]
Someone's hard at work.
[HAISE]
Akira.
So what are you
snooping around in?
I was just... just
reading some old files.
[AKIRA]
Reading up on Kotaro Amon?
Yes.
Well then, you're in luck.
I knew him personally.
He died in battle, during the
Owl Extermination Mission.
Was there anything else
you wanted to know?
[HAISE]
About the Eyepatch Ghoul.
That's a name you should forget.
[HAISE]
Sorry, I can't do that!
[gasps]
Why don't you want me
to know that name?
Is it because I'm
the Eyepatch Ghoul?
Is it because I'm the
one who... murdered Amon?
You don't get it.
The terror of waking up each day
and not knowing anything.
I'm trying my best to trust
in what I've been told,
but it just isn't enough.
Uh...
[HAISE sobs]
Where...
Where did I come from? Who am I?
Hais--
My name isn't Haise!
I... I...
Haise. You're you.
Regardless of your
name. You're you.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Yuma. Kaneki. Kanae.
Could I have--?
[knocking]
[MIRUMO]
Hello, Shu.
Huh? Papa.
I brewed a cup
of coffee for you.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Thank you.
It's unhealthy to dwell
on things for too long.
Leave it to your coffee, Papa.
It's woken me back... up...
[MIRUMO]
Matsumae.
[MATSUMAE]
Sir?
Please take my son to safety.
[UI]
Mirumo Tsukiyama?
[MIRUMO]
Oui.
[UI]
Don't move.
I have no intention of fighting
or attempting to run from you.
This is a house of gentlemen.
[UI] This ghoul's trying
to play for sympathy.
My servants are all
in their rooms.
They are ghouls, the same as I.
But up to now, we have
lived as humans would.
Please allow us to do so
until the very end.
[INVESTIGATOR A] Mirumo
Tsukiyama has been secured.
Repeat! Tsukiyama
has been secured!
[SAIKO]
Sweet, let's go home.
[URIE] The mission's
already accomplished?
Screw that, Rose.
Put up a fight.
Let me increase my kill count.
[HAISE] Something about
this doesn't smell right.
[MATSURI]
It's a distraction.
Whose escape would the master
secure by giving himself up?
A wife or child maybe?
We've set up a perimeter
around the estate.
He should know that
they won't get far.
Give me a list of
all buildings owned
by the Tsukiyama family.
[INVESTIGATOR B]
Yes, sir.
[MATSURI]
Crafty little worms.
[MATSUMAE]
Master Shu. You're awake.
Matsumae, where--?
Where are we? What's going on?
[MATSUMAE]
We're out for a drive.
Look me in the eye when
you answer this question.
Papa. Where is he?
Master Mirumo chose
to remain at his estate.
The other servants
are with him as well.
As of seven PM today,
the Tsukiyama family's social
privilege no longer exists.
[gasps] Hold on.
Are you saying that--?
[MATSUMAE] The family
secret has been exposed.
The CCG is closing
their net as we speak.
Master Mirumo has elected
to allow them to capture him.
So that we... will have a
better chance of escaping.
It's happening again.
Matsumae! You have
to take me back!
[MATSUMAE]
I can't do that.
[TSUKIYAMA] Please,
I have to save my father!
[MATSUMAE]
You can't.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Matsumae!
It's over now.
Due to my failure, the annals
of the Tsukiyama family
have come to a close.
But, Master Shu.
While you survive,
your bloodline and
history can continue
in another form.
You're saying that I must
take all their lives
upon myself now.
[MATSUMAE]
It's the duty of a family head.
[TSUKIYAMA]
So that's what this feeling is.
No wonder I can't stop it.
[TSUKIYAMA]
All right.
[MATSUMAE]
Time is running short.
I have to speed up a bit.
[MATSUMAE]
Master.
These are all ghouls
of the Tsukiyama group.
[ASADA] When we heard
you were in trouble,
we all came as
quickly as we could.
[KUREI] It'll be some time
before the helicopter arrives.
Until you're able
to make your escape,
it will be our honor
to defend you.
[TSUKIYAMA] So many people
answered his call.
I'm impressed anew by
my father's greatness.
Yes.
This is what your family
built for our kind.
[ASADA] Wow, I hadn't seen
Master Shu since he was a kid.
He's grown into
a real looker, huh?
That he has.
I'm glad we got
the chance to see.
Yeah. He should've done
some modeling for us.
I bet that look would've
been a real hit.
Our very own ghoul poster boy.
Would've been great.
[ASADA] We owe everything
we have to Master Mirumo.
To his family.
Yes, I know.
Now we can repay that
debt with our lives.
I suppose we'd better make
these doves earn their pay.
[KUREI] We don't even have
time to get sentimental.
Commence the extermination.
[KANAE wheezing]
[ETO]
Kanae.
If you want to be
treasured by someone,
you must first remove the
one they treasure already.
I'm going to share
another bone with you now.
It'll be okay.
You'll be loved
for sure this time.
I mean,
just look how adorable you are.
[clock ticking]
[HAISE panting]
[KIJIMA]
That's one more down!
[MATSUMAE]
Fanculo !
Give me your quinque right now!
[TSUKIYAMA]
I will not surrender.