[panting]
[grunting]
You don't have to do this!
Please stop!
[SEISA]
Don't do it!
Forgive me for calling
you out here like this.
I--I just couldn't hold it in.
Yuriko...
I can't hide my feelings,
and I refuse to try!
[ERUNA] Okay, but we
shouldn't do this now.
Not right here.
[YURIKO gasps]
[ERUNA] So let's go
to the nurse's office
where there's
no one around!
[BOTH giggling]
[ERUNA giggling]
[ERUNA'S MOM]
Eruna! Eruna! Eruna!
What, Ma?
We're doing a special
vision test with a love letter
in the nurse's office right now,
so come back later,
'kay, thanks!
[ERUNA'S MOM]
Fantasizing again, are we?
Well, your future is real!
Apply to a high school already!
Do you even know
how long it's been
since the holiday started?
[ERUNA] That's right,
it's Golden Week!
I still gotta be Golden Week!
Come on, Eruna, you can
do anything if you just try!
[ERUNA'S MOM] Do not use
nonsense to avoid this,
young lady!
I don't get it.
How can someone
be so unconcerned
about eventually
living in a gutter?
That's not a compliment!
Right.
You know I'm a week that
likes to be complimented!
[ERUNA'S MOM]
You are not Golden W
Now knock that crap off!
Apply to a school,
and when you get accepted
I promise not to bug you
about it anymore.
Okay? Okay?
[ERUNA]
'Kay.
[bell chiming]
So have you decided where
you want to go yet, Eruna?
[ERUNA]
Nope, not at all.
What about that school
just out of town?
[ERUNA]
Uniforms aren't cute enough.
That's really your reason?
Uniforms are important!
I mean, if I have to wear
something ugly,
I might as well live in a
freakin' gutter!
Seems kinda dramatic.
Look, I want
to have a career
where I get
to watch TV all day.
Why should I have to go to
school for that?
[FRIENDS] Eruna,
watching TV isn't a career.
[ERUNA groans]
This is lame.
Why aren't there
any fun jobs out there?
[gasps]
[YURIKO]
Eruna! Oh, Eruna!
Are you all right?
Yuriko?
Oh no!
We must be the only people
left alive in the whole world.
[ERUNA]
Everything will be fine.
We can make it together.
Just us two.
But first... I have an idea.
[YURIKO gasps]
[ERUNA] Let's go
to the nurse's office!
[BOTH laughing]
[laughing creepily]
[SHIGURE] You know,
whenever I find you,
you're always behind that thing.
[ERUNA] Shigure,
how come you're here?
I got permission
from my dorm to come here.
All I had to do was tell them
I had to go see
the cutie known as you.
Don't make a face like that!
I'm your cousin,
not your brother,
so we could totally have
normal kids together, probably!
[ERUNA groans]
So many levels of gross.
[SHIGURE yells]
[ERUNA] Well, spit it out.
What do you want?
[SHIGURE] You know,
your mom is spreading a rumor
that you have yet to decide what
school you're gonna apply to.
[ERUNA]
Hmph!
[SHIGURE] If that's true,
what about this one?
It's my school,
Mikagura Academy.
Let me see here...
Their uniforms are cute,
so that's a plus.
Cool! Everyone lives in dorms?
Gotta love all the
cultural clubs, too.
And not like you're gonna find
another school like it, either.
Oh, and by the way...
I'm Manga Research Club Prez.
[SHIGURE]
Hey, don't ignore me!
I mean, yeah, I get it,
but just a heads up,
a little bit of interest this
direction wouldn't hurt you any.
[sighs]
Eruna, you're
kinda drooling there.
[yells]
[SHIGURE yells]
An angel!
She's the real deal!
I can't believe a girl this
perfect really exists!
Wait a sec, aren't
Photoshopped models
used for this sort of stuff?
It's like the difference
between pictures
of a fast food burger
and the mushy reality.
Yeah, good call.
I'd like a burger.
But if we do fast food,
I'm getting a double.
[ERUNA]
Pay attention!
[SHIGURE] If you're curious,
the girl in the photo
is Seisa Mikagura.
She's the granddaughter
of the principal.
Hey, you know what?
Go ahead and get
yourself a burger.
Grab me some nuggets
while you're a--huh?
Wait, don't go anywhere!
Repeat what you just said!
What, that I'd like a burger?
Not that part!
Wait, you mean,
"Oh, and by the way,
I'm Manga Research Club Prez"?
Too far back!
[SHIGURE] "The girl in the photo
is Seisa Mikagura.
She's the granddaughter
of the principal"?
[gasps]
God, thank you!
[SHIGURE]
Um, Eruna?
Yep. She's the one.
[SHIGURE]
You can't marry a chick.
At least not right now.
Not that!
This is it.
I'm gonna apply for this school!
They're entrance exams,
that's all.
I can do it.
I mean, everything I needed to
do to get ready for today...
...I came really close
to actually doing,
so I bet I'll be just fine.
You are most kind for waiting.
[squeals]
Do you know how
delicate you look?
I don't suppose you'd mind
if I took your picture
real quick, would ya?
Huh?
Aw, nuts, I forgot my camera.
I'm so stupid.
Everything is in order
if you'd like
to follow me this way,
Miss Ichinomiya.
She knows my name!
Super pretty
and totally cute.
I think I'm gonna keep you
and call you Kurumi.
So what's the dealio?
Have you worked here
very long, Kurumi?
Are you seeing anyone right now?
Can I put myself in the running?
[laughs] Just kidding!
You will take the written
portion of the entrance exam
in this room.
Oh, right.
[ERUNA] Why do these
not seem hard?
[ERUNA]
She's sleeping?!
What's the catch?
Is this a trap?
Do I need to
hold it up to the light?
Maybe this has invisible ink.
I got it!
[yawns] What an idiot.
[ERUNA yelps, groans]
Next up will be the interview.
I can do this,
because everything I needed
to do to get ready for today...
[yells]
Go in as soon
as you're ready.
[ERUNA gasps]
Is anybody even here?
[VOICE]
Yeah. I don't know...
She doesn't look like she has
what it takes to me, ryui.
[VOICE] A direct descendant of
the main Ichinomiya family.
We even gave you special
treatment on the test,
which was also unfortunate.
[sighs] Wow. Poor thing.
Not often we get to see someone
as unlucky as you, ryui.
You should have a crap
luck cut off switch, ryui.
[screams]
Mine eyes, mine eyes!
Ah, the strange cat's eyes
are its weakness, I see.
Don't "I see" me, ryui!
To commit that kind
of ocular assault
upon such a cute and
lovable me can only mean
you are a cruel,
vicious child, ryui!
Right, a talking cat
with wings.
[gasps]
Is this another delusion?!
Crud!
Yeah, as if you
could dream me up.
Pinch yourself to check, though.
What's the point of pinching me?
I'm the one interviewing you,
so you know!
What?
Yep, I'm from
Mikagura Private Academy.
Think I'm gonna keep
you, too, and call you Bimii.
[BIMII] You don't get
to name me, ryui!
Also, what's up with ending
your sentences in "ryui"?
Don't you think it's
kind of like awkward?
Oh.
Well, then what about "fluffy"?
Would it be better if I said
"fluffy, fluffy"?
[ERUNA] No. I'm thinking
you should go for "ug."
That seems very unique, "ug."
No way, kid!
You chose that because
it's short for ugly,
didn't you, ug?
[ERUNA] I'm bored.
Is this the interview?
Oh. That's right, ryui.
We already have the
interview result in, ryui.
What?
But we haven't
done anything yet.
[gasps]
You mean...
...I failed?
[ERUNA]
No!
If this pointless conversation
was the interview,
then I've gotta be out.
And if the outs are
piling up with each inning,
then to continue
this baseball analogy,
it's the bottom of
the ninth with two outs
and the bases are loaded.
But I don't get baseball!
Which means I still got
a chance to turn things around!
[BIMII]
Well, your optimism confuses me.
What?
Does that mean
I didn't get in, then?
Don't worry, ryui.
You totally passed.
But how?
Well, first of all,
just being able to see me
means you're approved.
[ERUNA]
Okay. It's real.
[BIMII] I told you,
this isn't a dream, so stop--
If you're lying to me,
I'm so gonna make you pay!
[BIMII]
Why would I be lying?!
[ERUNA] I dunno, my delusions
are usually honest,
but they're not
usually cats, either!
[BIMII]
I'm not a delusion!
[ERUNA] Which is exactly
what a delusion would say!
[ERUNA]
What?
Say what?
[ERUNA]
What is going on?!
This is a party to
welcome the new students.
One of the distinguishing
features of this academy
is that every student
in attendance is required
to be a member
of some sort of club.
Seriously? Those're clubs?
Might as well tell ya
what really makes
Mikagura such a special school.
We have to join clubs because we
all compete with each other
in these battles.
And why would you do that?
Because winning is
the only way a club
can earn a higher rank.
Since everyone wants the best
perks,
battles occur pretty regularly.
Basically, the clubs that win
more battles have a higher rank,
which means they get
preferential treatment.
Better and bigger dorm rooms,
he best food.
Stuff like that, ryui.
Oh!
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Fun, it's like a party!
I'm in!
[STUDENTS chatting]
[ERUNA] Wow, there's
a lot of clubs here.
I didn't know people could
have this much culture.
[BIMII] Oh, yeah,
speaking of which,
I forgot to give this
to you, ryui.
[BIMII] It's a device
original to this school
that's given to
all the students, ryui.
Pretty cool, huh?
That thing collects
and keeps track
of all the points
you earn, ryui.
The more club battles you win,
the more points
you'll have, ryui.
You can even shop with it, ryui.
[ERUNA] So what you're saying
is my dreams have come true!
[BIMII] This is the girls' dorm,
where you will be sleeping
every day from now on, ryui.
[ERUNA]
It's all girls?!
[ERUNA] Yuriko,
I'm turning off the light.
[YURIKO]
Not just yet.
[ERUNA] I can take your
clothes off if you want.
[YURIKO] I would do it myself,
but I'm feeling so exhausted.
[breathing heavily]
[HIMI]
Hello there!
Hah! What's the deal, Teach?
Why'd you come
to the girls' dorm?
Don't tell me you're
one of those guys
who doesn't wanna
go home after work
because he's "lonely"?
[yells]
[ERUNA]
You're so tiny and adorable!
Do you want to live together,
like under the same roof?
C'mon! I'll feed you
carrots every day!
I'm not a rabbit,
and I hate carrots!
I'm not tiny, either!
Now put me back down!
[BIMII]
This is Himi Yasaka.
She's the president of the
calligraphy club, ryui.
Hello!
It's nice to meet you!
Wanna be my new best friend?
Ohmygah, what if
we became so close
people started getting
the wrong idea about us?
Doesn't that sound awesome?
So anyway,
Eruna's been assigned
to this dorm,
so I was just
showing her around.
Cool!
Well, in that case, I don't mind
taking you to your room!
[HIMI]
Ta-da, this is your room!
Uhh... You sure?
Because that looks like
a sleeping bag to me.
If you're not in a club,
then you don't get to have
your own room, ryui.
[gasps]
There's no need
to worry, though.
Sleeping bags are supposed
to be like really warm.
My brain
understands your words,
but my heart's
convinced I'll freeze.
Look, I can see another
not-a-room over there
that already has something
shivering to death inside!
[GIRL crying]
I want to go home!
Oh, mommy, I want to go home!
[HIMI]
Yoo-hoo, hello in there!
Hey!
I'm in the calligraphy club if
you wanna join.
You'll get to have a large,
private room
and delicious food if you do!
[GIRL gasps]
Um...
I'd like to, but I've just
started doing calligraphy,
so I didn't think you'd take me.
Are you guys okay
having beginners?
[ERUNA]
Excuse me!
I want to join the
calligraphy club, too!
Hmm... Let me think.
I know!
Write something down for me
so I can check out
what you can do!
[HIMI] It's not a big deal
if you're a beginner!
Calligraphy isn't about
technique, it's about soul!
[ERUNA yelling]
[HIMI]
Are you finished?
--[ERUNA] Yep!
--[GIRL] Yes!
Your strokes are really nice!
You can totally join the club!
What? Oh, really?
Thank you so much!
I decided to write my name!
Katai is a flower and a bag!
I won't let you down.
I'm gonna rock
at drawing letters!
Yay, calligraphy!
Himi! Don't forget
to look at mine!
I don't know what this is.
Nothing personal, but do you
have darkness inside your soul?
Maybe!
Sorry, Eruna, but this
is called a F. A. I. L.
[ERUNA]
A fail?!
[KATAI] If it helps at all,
the sleeping bag I was in
is nice and warmed up,
so please feel free
to go ahead and use it!
[ERUNA] As a matter of fact,
that doesn't help at all!
Come on, Katai, let's go!
Okay, Himi, I'm so
excited about life now!
[BIMII] It's probably time for
me to head to my room, ryui.
[ERUNA yells]
[BIMII] Aw, chill out.
I'll be back, ryui.
Wait! Don't leave me!
[stomach growling]
[ERUNA] I'm so hungry,
and I wanna take a shower.
But soon,
I feel like things are
gonna get more fun.
[KURUMI]
Good morning, class.
I'm your homeroom teacher,
Kurumi Narumi.
I don't want to be called Miss
Narumi because that's weird,
so go with Miss Kurumi.
No way! Kurumi?
Remember me? I totally
guessed your name right!
Why don't we start
with introducing yourselves.
First up, student number one,
Eruna Ichinomiya.
Here! Uh... Aqui?
I wrote that for you
to read in class, ryui.
Uh, you're welcome by the way.
[ERUNA]
Thank you, Bimii!
Ahem!
I'm Eruna Ichinomiya,
a trick star surprise
from the far outside.
Here to keep battles fresh.
At least that's my goal!
I'm not just number one
on the attendance sheet, either.
So if you want the chance to
have a sip of sweet liqueur,
then invite me
to join your club.
In your face!
[ERUNA]
Yay me?
What?! Shoot me now.
This can't be all I get
to eat for lunch!
Yep, if you don't
belong to a club,
this is your meal, ryui.
Huh?
[BIMII]
Whoops, forgot to tell you
that if you're not in a club,
you only get five minutes
in there, ryui.
But it's better for water
conservation, ryui.
[ERUNA]
I don't care about conservation!
It's not better for me!
Hello!
Teenage girl with raging
hormones in here!
[BIMII] You should just join any
club for the time being, Eruna.
[ERUNA groans]
Okay, fine.
What club is this girl in?
Seisa Mikagura's in
the going-home club.
That's real?
A going-home club?
Yes, it's very real,
gets special treatment,
and hasn't accepted new members
for a while now, ryui.
[BIMII] As a matter of fact,
Seisa just stays in her mansion
and hardly ever
even comes to school.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[stomach growling]
PS, I'm starving.
[BIMII] Which is why
you need to join a club.
If there's one you like, you can
sign up for a trial period.
[BOY yelling]
[BOY] I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to! I'm sorry!
Dude, why are
you cowering there
like you're about
to start crying?
Knock it off or everyone's gonna
think I'm bullying you.
[ASUHI] Oh. I'm sorry.
That's not what
I'm trying to do.
That guy is Kuzuryu
from the art club.
And the one on the ground
is Asuhi Imizu
from the astronomy club.
Jeez, thanks a lot.
Now the whole school will be
talking about this.
Look, man, you need to stop
acting like a noob.
Oh. I, um...
I didn't mean to make a scene,
and I'm really sorry
for bumping into you.
[SEISA] Why don't we
leave it at that, guys?
[SEISA] Kuzuryu,
this isn't the kind of thing
to get that upset about, is it?
Me upset?
Whatever. We're just
having a conversation.
Are you all right?
I'm good!
I can't thank you enough!
You saved me!
I realize he has a
tendency to scare people
because of how he looks,
but he's misunderstood,
that's all.
I hope you won't
hold that against him.
[breathing heavily]
Let me guess...
She's the one you decided
to go after this time?
Was that to me?
Did the goddess just say
real words to me?
I still can't say
for sure, ryui.
I'm thinking about it, yes.
But if so, she might
have possibilities
of a different vector
from you, ryui.
I see.
Welcome.
If you haven't decided on which
club you wanted to join yet,
think you might join
the going-home club
for a trial period?
Of course, that's only if you
feel so inclined.
I'm inclined!
I feel so inclined.
Yeah, I'm like totally
inclined right now.
In fact, I was born inclined!
I feel so inclined
with my body and soul!
Then it's decided.
[STUDENTS gasp, whisper]
[SEISA]
Oh, yes.
It completely slipped my mind.
There's a small
club battle next week.
Unfortunately, I've been
planning on being indisposed
that particular day.
If you could enter as
the going-home club rep,
that'd be great.
[ERUNA] My goddess invited me
to join the going-home club.
I don't think it's my
imagination, either.
Oh, please be
real life this time!
Booyah!
[ERUNA] This feels like
the start of a story!
[ERUNA]
And it's gonna be awesome!
[SHIGURE] And now,
my lovey-dovey school life
with Eruna finally begins!
Our love can
overcome everything,
for it is pure and true!
That's why we're
gonna get married!
Will the kids at school give us
their blessing?! They better!
Find out next time on
"Romantic Honeymoon"!
[ERUNA] Why're you making up
a fake preview, Shigure?
[SHIGURE]
What? It's not fake!
[ERUNA]
Uh-huh!
Next time it's about the
gorgeous and hella mysterious
Seisa Mikagura,
aka the principal's
beloved granddaughter.
I'm assuming she loves
her because, well whatever.
Seisa leads me into
the forbidden girls' dorm
so we can have forbidden
dorm experiences,
like college, but not!
Next time, "Secret Flower
Garden Escalation!"
[BIMII] Eruna, you're making
that preview up too, ryui!
[ERUNA]
Uh, don't be weird, Bimii.
[BIMII]
You don't be weird, ryui!
Can we do the preview
for real, already? Gah!
Eruna's ability
finally awakens, ryui!
Next time,
"After-School Stride."