[CRITIC 6A]
Simply wonderful!
[CRITIC 6B] He's still immature,
but he has a rare talent!
[CRITIC 6C]
That one has a bright future!
[overlapping voices]
[KUZURYU]
What did I just paint?
Trash. Complete trash.
It's just like me.
[party poppers popping]
[SHIGURE]
Congrats, Eruna!
You're the best
in the whole world
and don't you
forget I know it!
Yeah!
[SHIGURE (rapping)]
Yo, yo, Eruna.
You won round two-una.
Let's celebrate.
Just me and you-una.
Just kidding.
Or not, whatever you need.
As long as it doesn't
involve making me bleed.
[ERUNA yells]
Okay! I get it already,
so will you stop trying
to rap at me, please?
Well, you're
very welcome, Eruna.
I'm glad you liked the song
I made especially for you.
Do you even try to listen?
Surprise!
My sick rhymes aren't
your only present, either.
[ASUHI]
It's almost time, guys.
Are you ready?
The go word will be "go," okay?
[HIMI] I wanna give
the "go," though, okay?
Should we use something else
in case I just
accidentally gave the "go"?
[MINATOGAWA]
I want to say it, as well.
I've never been entrusted
with "go" before,
so I think it would be fun.
[YUTO] Minatogawa, if we go
after you say "go"
all emotionless,
we won't be very
energetic when we go.
--I got this.
--[KATAI] Hush!
Keep it down, everyone,
or else she'll hear us!
Uh, heads up,
she already heard you.
[BIMII] And it's pretty obvious
who's there, too, ryui.
[ASUHI]
But "go" was my idea!
[HIMI]
I called "go" first!
[HIMI, ASUHI arguing]
Don't mind us.
How am I
supposed to do that?!
Shut up! I'm
officially calling go!
Ready, set, go!
[ALL]
Surprise, Eruna!
[overlapping congratulations]
[ERUNA]
Quit talking all at once!
I can't understand
what you're saying!
[ERUNA whining]
I'm here.
Is that like
really weird, though?
I mean, since I lost,
I wasn't sure if I should come.
No way!
You're not weird at all!
We can still support each other!
Who wins doesn't matter.
[KATAI]
Eruna, what's wrong?
Nothing!
Nothing at all. I'm fine!
[YUTO]
Hey, Eruna.
If you're feeling worried
about Usamaru, don't be.
Tonkyun is, let's say,
"more than eager"
to avenge him in battle.
Didn't you hear?
If Tonkyun wins
his next two matches,
he'll get the chance to face
that psychopath Azumi Sagara.
Are you serious?
[YUTO] Yep. Besides,
it's not that bad for Usamaru.
A lot of drama kids
have lost by now.
No biggie.
Just look on the bright side,
we've got an
awesome upperclassman
that'll take
good care of 'em.
An upperclassman
that'll take good care of 'em?
[FIRST YEARS]
Thank you, Nyamirin!
[NYAMIRIN] I know
you all tried so hard!
[ERUNA] I'm gonna go to the
drama club's party instead.
[BIMII] You can't ditch
your own pep rally, ryui!
I won't let you!
Turn a blind eye!
She's waiting.
But more importantly,
boing, boing...
...they're waiting!
[grunts]
[SHIGURE] All right. Let the
official Eruna pep rally begin!
Cheers!
[ALL]
[ALL chattering]
That was so much fun!
It might've been my
favorite present like ever.
[SHIGURE]
I'm glad you had a good time.
I asked Seisa to come,
but she said it was
past her bedtime,
so she couldn't make it.
This is why I
hate these club battles.
[ERUNA]
Oh.
[SHIGURE] Kuzuryu asked
who else was coming,
which made me hopeful,
but then he said he was afraid
he'd ruin the mood if he showed.
Oh come on,
like Enoyan needs to worry
about ruining the mood.
He should have realized that
the mood would already be ruined
with you being here.
Eruna, how can you say that?
It's as if you don't even care
when you're breaking my heart!
Oh, hey.
What was the rookie battle like
when you were a first year,
Creep Master?
Don't tell me you won.
[SHIGURE]
No, I didn't win.
Actually, I wasn't a student
at this academy yet
when I was a freshman.
Where'd you go?
[SHIGURE] Mikagura has
a sister school of sorts
that acts as our rival.
I attended that
academy for a year
before transferring
over as a sophomore.
Oh, Kuzuryu went there
his first year, too.
[SHIGURE]
It's pretty far west of us.
You know how we only have
cultural clubs at Mikagura?
Well, they're basically
the complete opposite
in that respect.
They battle and
have matches like we do,
but they only have sports clubs.
I was practically obsessed
with kendo back then,
so I enrolled ready
to throw myself into it.
But in the end,
I had a hard time dealing
with how everything
was win-or-lose there.
[SHIGURE]
That's where I met Kuzuryu.
Seemed like a
cool enough guy to me.
[SHIGURE] Let me get this
straight. You're a ringer,
so you're not technically
a member of judo club?
[KUZURYU] Yep.
I've got basketball tomorrow
and track and field
the next day.
You're good at
everything, then, right?
Why not pick just
one club and own it?
I was gonna go with kendo,
but looks like
that wouldn't work out.
You're there,
and your Hero Time...
No one can beat you.
[BOTH laughing]
[SHIGURE] Kuzuryu wasn't
a member of a single club.
He helped out a lot
of different clubs
acting as what's
called a ringer.
However, as his
reputations spread,
kids started getting
jealous and bitter.
They resented him.
And then...
One day,
he accidentally overheard
one of his closest friends
talking about him
behind his back.
Let's just say what was said
didn't sit well with him.
[SHIGURE] After that,
he felt like he couldn't trust
the people around him anymore.
[SHIGURE]
Kuzuryu, what's wrong?
[KUZURYU] Don't act
like you care, Hero Time.
You're just like everyone else.
You don't really like me.
And you don't want
me here either, do you?
[SHIGURE]
What?
[SHIGURE] That was the last time
I saw him at that school.
He transferred out.
Poor Enoyan...
Oh, he suffered so much.
[blows nose loudly]
That was gross.
Anyway, it turned out I couldn't
adjust to their style either,
so immediately after
I won their rookie battle,
I transferred here
to Mikagura Academy.
[SHIGURE]
It kinda sucks, though.
I mean, we're nice to
each other and everything,
but we've never been as
close as we were back then.
Still, at least neither one
of us is at that awful school.
You guys both
did the right thing!
Well of course you came
to Mikagura Academy!
That was the smartest
move you could've made!
In case you missed it,
let me reiterate that I won
the rookie battle that year.
I almost lost a bunch of times.
Seriously, I barely
squeaked out the win.
but I do wonder
what would've happened
if Kuzuryu had
participated, too.
[ERUNA] I don't understand
why if you were in
the kendo club before,
you decided to go with
the manga research club
once you got here.
And why did Enoyan
choose the art club?
[SHIGURE] To be honest,
that is a pretty long story.
And we should save it
for another time.
[ERUNA]
Tension max... let's go!
[DEVICE]
Winner. Eruna Ichinomiya.
[ERUNA]
Yeah! Tension max, go!
[DEVICE]
Winner. Eruna Ichinomiya.
[ERUNA]
This is awesome!
The world's my freakin' mollusk!
[BIMII]
Oyster.
You know you'll be
in the quarterfinals
if you win
your next battle!
Uh...
[pounding on door]
[ERUNA]
Enoyan!
Your favorite and most adorable
underclassman has come to visit!
Hey!
You've been
completely surrounded!
Imagine how much you're
making your mother cry.
You should
surrender immediately!
[clears throat]
Milk!
I got some nice, cool,
yummy milk for you!
Okay, where's the milk?
It's, uh, at the store.
I'll go get some right now.
You love me!
[KUZURYU]
It's fine.
You don't have to
go buy anything.
[ERUNA gasps, laughs]
[ERUNA]
Wow!
So this is like your
fortress of solitude?
[KUZURYU] You don't have
to make it sound dramatic.
Heads up.
[ERUNA]
Cool! I can drink this!
Did you get it just for me?
No, stop being be ridiculous.
[ERUNA]
Groovy!
There are so many
certificates and trophies!
[ERUNA]
"Innocence"?
How cool, this says
it's the Grand Prize!
That's amazing!
[KUZURYU]
It doesn't mean anything.
[ERUNA]
What? Yes it does!
And I bet the person
named Innocence agrees.
That's not a name, stupid.
It's the title
of a damn painting!
Okay, well I wanna see it, then!
Where is this Innocence?
[KUZURYU]
Who knows?
[ERUNA] Why won't you
show it to me?
[KUZURYU]
Just kidding.
Stop looking at that junk.
[ERUNA]
Junk?
The guy who came up
with a title like "Innocence"
without a shred of
irony or embarrassment?
Yeah, well that kid
isn't here anymore.
[ERUNA]
Oh! By Kyoma Kuzuryu!
[KUZURYU]
What did you want?
[ERUNA]
That's rude.
Why would you assume
I would come see you
because I wanted something?
Funny story...
I just decided
I wanted something.
I have a favor to ask!
[KUZURYU]
I refuse.
[ERUNA] I didn't say
what it is yet!
[ERUNA]
Come on, Enoyan.
Will you draw me, please?
I want you to
draw me how you see me!
And if you want me to...
I'll do it.
As long as it's
for the art, of course.
I don't mind taking
it all off for this!
Turn me down if you want,
but you know I'll
just come back tomorrow.
Well that's fine with me.
I'll just turn
you down tomorrow.
[ERUNA]
Crap, it's late!
Hey, you should come
watch my next match!
It'll be fun.
You can cheer for me!
[KUZURYU]
Why should I?
Isn't it obvious?
Because I asked you to!
[KUZURYU]
Yeah, we'll see.
Sounds like a promise to me!
What was that about?
I have no idea what
she's thinking, as usual.
[USAMARU]
Hurry, Eruna! Over here!
[ERUNA]
I'm running!
[USAMARU] Of course she's
as high as she can get.
Big surprise.
[STUDENTS laughing]
Alrighty, you got any idea
why he's riding a panda?
You know, one would've figured
he'd have gone with a pig.
[SAGARA] Is my opponent today
another supporting character
from the drama club?
The rabbit loses,
so they send in a pig?
Nothing like a little
smoked pork, am I right?
[laughs]
[TONKYUN] It's true I'm
a supporting character
from the drama club.
However, even us lowly
supporting characters
have very different
ways of fighting.
[DEVICE]
Begin the match.
[SAGARA] I'll make mincemeat
out of you in no time.
Let's do this.
Yeah. Molto Accento!
[loud cacophony]
Oh, I get it now!
She can't increase the gravity
of a wide space all at once.
He just has to
approach her like that
without her
locking on to him.
[SAGARA] You know you're
third-rate, right?
I bet you wish you were
as smart as a pig, huh?
If you were, you might not have
assumed a top performer like me
wouldn't have seen
through your lame plan.
[TONKYUN] All you are is talk,
you know that?
[TONKYUN] If you think you
can beat me, go ahead and try.
What, are you scared
of a moving pig?
You scared of me?
[yelling]
[SAGARA]
You swine!
How dare you think you can
talk to your better like that!
One little piggy!
Two little piggies!
You better watch out or
all the piggies are gonna die!
Last little piggy's turn!
You're finished!
[TONKYUN]
Top-Performer, huh?
You don't really seem
that special to me.
[SAGARA]
So what?
Think about it.
How are you going to break
my crystals in that state?
All you can really do is
wait until time runs out.
[TONKYUN] Seems like you would
be the one more concerned
with how much time is left.
[TONKYUN]
The end is upon us.
[TONKYUN] Unfortunately, your
performance has come to an end.
You jerk! You were
planning this from the start.
I discovered your handicap
while watching your
match with Usamaru.
Your ability is impressive.
But it cannot be
used continuously.
After you perform
for a certain amount of time,
you appear to require a rest.
And then there's a lag time
before you can activate your
ability again, isn't there?
In yesterday's match,
after your performance ended,
you just stood for a while
on top of the pipe organ.
Once your ability has stopped
and you can't float
in the air anymore,
all you can do is
hide safely out of reach.
In general, the right move.
But if you had fought
fair and square,
there's no way you'd've
been able to beat Usamaru.
Shut up, you disgusting pig!
Remember you lost
to a supporting character.
Ad Lib Role!
[DEVICE]
Winner, Tonkyun.
[CROWD cheering]
That's my boy!
Tonkyun, you did it!
[ERUNA]
What are those?
[USAMARU]
He's wearing bunny ears!
That's too passionate!
Oh, I think I'm gonna cry!
Eruna.
I thought you'd be a
little more excited than this.
Huh?
Haven't you put it together?
Next round's the fifth.
You and Tonkyun facing
each other in battle
is finally gonna be a reality.
Huh? What?!
[BIMII] This match is
about to start, ryui!
Whoever wins
this battle will be
in the quarterfinals, ryui!
Exciting stuff!
Are you two ready, ryui?
I'm not gonna lose, Tonkyun!
I'm fighting for
something important,
and that will give me
the strength I need to win.
[TONKYUN] I'm fighting
for something, too.
For the drama club...
...and for myself.
[STUDENTS laughing]
[KUZURYU] "Taking applications
for club members.
Beautiful girls welcome
with the potential to rise
immediately to
management positions.
Lolis will receive
a snack allowance.
Interested girls should contact
first-year Eruna Ichinomiya.
Don't tell me this is why
she came by earlier.
I can't blame her
for trying, though.
[BIMII]
Eruna!
I did say that the rookie battle
would help promote your club,
but that's not
what I meant, ryui.
Besides, your descriptions of
the types of members you want
is too sketchy, ryui.
[ERUNA]
What are you talking about?
Katai wrote it all cute for me.
There's nothing
sketchy about cute!
[DEVICE]
Begin the match.
Before he activates
his power, I'll get one!
I had a feeling
you would try that.
What about this?
[ERUNA]
Now! Sudden tension max...
...go!
All right, no reason
to hold back, is there?
Ad Lib Role!
[ERUNA yells]
[ERUNA]
Oh, no!
Is it gonna work
if I'm this far away?
[TONKYUN]
How ironic.
The bullet is obviously slower
than the person who fired it,
which is why I can
see it almost too well.
What? No way!
[TONKYUN] Even if I'm the
one who wins this round,
it won't change
the fact that a member
of the After-School Six
is moving up, so...
Get ready, and cheer for me
during the next match.
[ERUNA]
I told you.
There is a reason
I have to win this.
[ERUNA] This is the first time
I'm revealing my secret weapon.
I was stupidly thinking I could
save it for when I fought Asuhi.
Sorry I underestimated you!
[TONKYUN] That was an unexpected
and wonderful secret weapon.
However, you only have
one blade, while I have two.
I will challenge you
with twice the swordsmanship.
Please don't let that
make you hate me, okay?
No worries.
It's weird. I can't shake this
sensation that I won't lose!
It's like I feel
different inside.
It's almost as if I
can feel it in my blood.
Would you like me to
deal the final blow, Eruna?
I will show you that light
can be extinguished with flame!
[ERUNA]
Heck yeah!
[TONKYUN] Her speed is
increasing as she fights.
Is she improving?
It shouldn't matter because
I still have two swords.
[ERUNA]
Good point.
But this weapon isn't just
your everyday
sword of light, Tonkyun.
Look closer!
--It's a bayonet!
--You're kidding me.
[yelling]
[DEVICE]
Winner, Eruna Ichinomiya.
[CROWD cheering]
[TONKYUN]
Nicely done.
That was an
impressive fight, Eruna.
I guess I'll make sure to cheer
for you during the next match.
[KUZURYU]
What do you mean you lost?
I know, right?
I didn't do too hot
in the quarterfinal.
Haruka Toishi from the broadcast
club beat me pretty easily.
Your abilities were
completely analyzed, ryui.
And there was that difference
in your strengths, too.
[KUZURYU]
What the heck?
And to think I was
gonna give you this
as a present when you won.
You wanted me
to draw a picture of you,
so I did it, okay?
[ERUNA] Wait...
Is this the picture you drew?
That's supposed to be me?!
You're very welcome.
It's called
"Innocent Full Throttle."
Before you go, you wanted to see
the other painting of mine,
"Innocence," right?
Where did I
put that sucker again?
[ERUNA] It's fine. I can
imagine what it looks like.
Look, my touch is back.
Thank you. Really!
Want another one?
For real, you can have
as many as you like!
Nope, it's appreciated,
but no thanks!
Eruna! Hurry, up, ryui!
The finals are
about to start, ryui!
[CROWD muttering]
[ERUNA]
Oh no...
Poor Asuhi...
He lost?
[DEVICE]
Winner, Otone Fujishiro.
[ERUNA] Enoyan,
that picture you painted
was ah-mazing-sauce-pants!
[KUZURYU] It's because
I drink milk every day.
You should drink some,
as well. It's fresh.
[ERUNA] Fresh? You mean,
like, you personally milk a cow
every morning?!
[KUZURYU] I'll leave that
to your imagination.
[ERUNA] Okay give me a minute.
I'm going to visualize it.
Okay, you're milking...
Whoa, you're a
furious milker, man!
Hello, underhanded, too?!
I did not see that coming.
Must be those painter hands that
make you so talented with teats!
[giggles]
[KUZURYU]
Of course your mind went there.
[ERUNA]
Oh!
[KUZURYU]
What's wrong?
[ERUNA] Don't look, but
Seisa is standing next to us!
[KUZURYU] Maybe she wants
to do a preview, too.
[SEISA] No I don't.
Not especially, at least.
[ERUNA] Yay, a preview
together with Seisa!
It can be a trailer
for our happy wedding!
Like an opening prelude.
[SEISA]
You don't make sense.
[ERUNA] Then do a preview
you understand!
Please show me how it's done!
Teach me something, senpai!
[SEISA]
If you insist...
Next time on this show,
"Izayoi Seeing."
Something wonderful might happen
beneath the star-filled sky.
[ERUNA]
That's how you say it?!
I don't think I've ever
said Izayoi out loud before!
See, I did learn something!
Thanks, Seisa!
[SEISA]
You're welcome...?