[camera shutter clicks]
[SEISA giggles]
[SENPAI]
Is it already time?
I guess we should stop here
for today, then.
We've got the
club battle tomorrow.
And a tough one at that,
considering we're
fighting each other.
You realize
I won't hold back.
You better not.
Plus, fair fights
are more fun anyway.
I couldn't be more excited.
How 'bout you?
[CROWD muttering]
The finals are over,
which means it's time for me!
[SHIGURE]
What a great season!
But this year's
rookie battle is over!
And the winner has been decided!
[CROWD cheers]
[SHIGURE]
So now, the hero interview
you've been waiting for
will be conducted by moi!
The manga research club rep,
Shigure Ninomiya!
[GIRL 7A]
We love you, Ninomiya!
[GIRL 7B] Did you see?
He took off his glasses!
Your winner, Otone Fujishiro.
Believe it or not,
this talented fighter
isn't actually a
member of any club!
If Miss Fujishiro's
still not part of a club,
then I'm willing to bet
she's in the same situation
that you're in, ryui.
I know. Makes me wonder.
It's weird she doesn't look
happy even though she won.
And now, it's time
for the hero interview!
[microphone feedback]
You think Fuji's a hero?
Don't know why.
That was really more
like a standard warm-up.
Au revoir, the interview's over.
[SHIGURE]
Hey! Where are you going?
You can't leave in
the middle of my interview!
Sorry about that, folks.
Now...
What a twerp.
I didn't realize
he was that blind
without his glasses on, ryui.
[SHIGURE] Let's try
this again, shall we?
This year's
hero interview, take two.
First, tell us how you're
feeling in this moment.
Conflicted, maybe.
It's not easy to narrow down
my emotions to one word.
Whoopsie!
I'm accidentally
interviewing the wrong person!
Otone, where did you go?
I've heard of
the emotional biting
on a handkerchief
thing before,
but I never thought
it would look so icky.
[sniffing]
[SHIGURE]
Eruna, yes!
I'm so glad you're here!
How did he know?
He can't see me!
[BIMII] Fairly certain
he sniffed you out, ryui.
[ERUNA]
Hey, wait. Shigure?
Well, since we've
got some extra time,
here's a surprise interview!
This student left a great
impression at the rookie battle
and made it all the way
to the quarterfinals!
But that's not all!
She's also planning to have
brilliant and adorable babies
with me in the future!
Meet my cousin--
[SHIGURE yelling]
[giggling]
I wonder what kind
of girl that Otone is.
I'd really like to talk to her.
What do you
wanna talk about, ryui?
Oh, nothing in particular.
I'm just kinda curious
what she's all about.
[crying]
[BIMII]
From what I understand,
Minatogawa takes care of most of
the flowerbeds over there, ryui.
[crying]
It's her! Ohmigah, look!
She's sitting in the most
adorable ladylike position
I've ever seen!
I can't handle the cute!
I have to go talk to her
before I explode!
Here goes nothing.
Move it or lose it, girl!
[BIMII]
Hold up!
It sounds like she's muttering
something to herself, ryui.
[OTONE]
I went and did it again.
C'mon, don't
worry about it, Otone!
You can sit in that position
anytime and anywhere.
Do what you want!
Oh great, I've lost you,
haven't I, ryui?
I didn't even mean
what I said this time.
À quoi bon. I'm lost.
It's like there's a devil
living in my head
that makes me a lunatic.
Bimii! Did you hear her?
She speaks in fancy lingo,
like from another country
and stuff.
Do you think she's
a world traveler, maybe?
Oh, I bet she is!
I can't take this.
It's so cool!
I wish I could figure out
how to stop being
so dang shy!
I can't help it, though.
When I get nervous,
my mind blanks out on me.
Then, mean hateful words
just jump out of my mouth
like little sabotaging bastards!
[sobs loudly]
Otone, you don't have
to worry about that crapola
ever again!
I will hold you tight
and keep you safe!
I'll be your savior.
Demon!
Oh no!
Mama told Fuji over
and over about the beast
that would prey on pretty girls
when they were alone,
but stupid Fuji
didn't believe her!
Wait, that means Fujishiro
must have been pretty.
And that's why you showed up!
Mama, did you see this?
Fujishiro is pretty!
[BIMII] It's not just that
she's not a member of a club.
This chick appears to be
just as crazy as you are, ryui.
[OTONE]
Huh?
Fuji swears that she's seen
you around somewhere before.
Hey, you're that
girl with panache
who impressed us until
the quarterfinal melee'
but then screwed
the pooch and lost
to what's-her-name from the
broadcasting club, right?
My name's Eruna Ichinomiya!
I'll stay right by your side
until you can
stop being so timid!
Fuji, shy?
what are you talking about?
And she is not even
sure what timid means!
Is it just me, or did nothing
about what she just said
make any sense, ryui?
Ah! Mr. Bimii!
Thank you so much for
your hard work at school!
And just so you know,
Fujishiro is an A+
super-duper star student!
Mr. Bimii should write
that down in the student record.
Write that Fujishiro
is a star student.
Write it down.
You need to understand
that whispering in my ear
won't brainwash me
into doing anything, ryui.
You know, I don't
think Bimii has the power
to write in any student records.
What?
Well, this is a waste of time.
[BIMII shrieks]
So, basically even
though you're a teacher,
you can still be pretty
low on the totem pole.
That must be a really
embarrassing dynamic for you.
Must be hard being so ugly, too.
Why did she get so
mean all of a sudden, ryui?
Is it Dark Otone,
or Light Otone?
I can't choose!
I just love both
of them so dang much!
This rudeness of yours
is not appreciated!
Fujishiro is always
light, obviously.
[ERUNA]
Shameless!
Man, that girl is truly,
truly outrageous.
I dig it!
[ERUNA]
What do you say?
You know you do.
You wanna sit in that
ladylike position, right?
[SEISA]
Is it like this?
Yes, yes it is!
That looks perfect!
It's the foolproof sitting
position with no openings
no matter what angle
you're looking from!
You're so talented, Seisa!
That might be the most
modest way of sitting,
but it still evokes
unexpected beauty.
One that lies
in our anticipation.
We see the perfection
yet nonetheless wait
for accidental openings
to present themselves to us.
[ERUNA]
Whoa!
A surprise ladylike position
from Miss Kurumi!
Wow!
On top of that is a waft of a
slightly dangerous fragrance,
skirting the edges of foul play,
and the collaboration
with Seisa's modesty
also brings an
exquisite synergy!
[ERUNA grunts]
[KURUMI] You can imagine
whatever you want,
but I'd really
rather you not drag me
into your bizarre delusions.
Yes, ma'am.
So this special girl who has
the oh-so-wonderful
ladylike sitting position
is Otone Fujishiro,
winner of the rookie battle?
Yep!
She's just really talented,
I guess.
Oh, and like me,
she's not a member
of any club yet,
but not like me, she's a
complete nutty nutball.
From what I've heard,
Asuhi's loss to her
was pretty terrible.
Yeah, but in his
interview after Otone left,
Asuhi seemed kinda
positive about it.
[ASUHI] The winner, Otone
Fujishiro, was extremely strong.
I honestly don't even
compare to her right now.
But after this great
learning experience,
I think I'm going to try to
fight Miss Fujishiro again
in the next club battle.
I'd like to fight her
as much as possible.
Hopefully, I'll win
more matches than I lose.
Then...
I can prove to you
that I'm a winner!
Asuhi actually inspired me!
I'm gonna work hard
making my new club,
and next time,
I'll pass quarterfinals!
I'll win the whole
shebang and own that stage!
[ERUNA]
Seisa, help!
I need to know what kind of club
you think I should make!
I thought you wanted
something along the lines of
"The Surrounding
Eruna Ichinomiya
with Fawning
Pretty Girls Club."
I say go for it.
What about "The
Surrounding Eruna Ichinomiya
with Kicking Girls Who Like to
Kick Eruna Ichinomiya Club"?
I know I'd join it.
[ERUNA gasps]
I didn't think about that one!
But I'm not opposed to it.
You should be.
I dunno, why don't you
just call it the "Idiot Club"
and call it a day?
Well I'm not
opposed to that, either!
It doesn't matter, though.
The problem I have right now
is getting the
three people I need
to officially
form a club together.
But Seisa, once I
finally do form my club,
will you please fight me
again as representative
of the going-home club?
Well, you realize
I won't hold back.
Duh!
Fair fights are more fun anyway!
I couldn't be more excited!
How 'bout you?
Is everything all right?
Yes. Don't worry. I'm fine.
[NYAMIRIN]
Oh look, it's Asuhi!
Congrats on
coming in second, man!
Well, thank you,
drama clubbers.
[TONKYUN]
Is something wrong?
Early predictions pegged Asuhi
as a first-magnitude star,
but he was actually
a six-magnitude
and didn't shine much.
So not nice!
Why would anyone
write that crap?
No, it's okay.
They're just telling the truth:
I wasn't strong enough.
It turned out I couldn't live up
to everybody's expectations.
I let them all down.
You are much
too hard on yourself.
I watched the match,
and I have to be honest, mister.
You seemed a lot stronger than
when you practiced with Yuto.
She's right, and remember
we all know you rock!
Wow. That's really
nice of you to say.
Thank you.
And you know,
I guess even the
dimmest star in the sky
is sending light out somewhere.
I'm not too happy
that my faint light
was made fun of publicly.
It's not just embarrassing--
It makes me sad.
But I'll get over it.
A party so we can
cheer up Asuhi?
That's right!
Yuto's great at coming up
with party ideas.
Well... It's just...
No one should ever feel that bad
about coming in second place.
I was curious
what your take on it was.
I say why not?
Let's do it!
If you want my two cents,
you probably oughta
steer away from calling it
a "cheer up party,"yui.
We should shoot for something
more fun than "cheer up."
I know, guys!
We should make it
a surprise party, roar!
[ERUNA]
Good call, Kumano!
If that's the
direction we're going,
I think we should
have it in Yuto's room.
What?
Why is it always my room?
Hey, who all
should we invite?
Himi, Katai, Minatogawa
will all show up,
I'm pretty sure.
I wonder if Seisa and
Enoyan will come this time.
Oh, that would be so rad!
Oh! Let's invite Otone, too!
No way, you're joking, right?
You're talking about the girl
that Asuhi lost to, roar!
[TONKYUN] Think it'd be
okay to invite her?
Well, yeah!
I don't know if she'll come,
but Light Otone
would at least
be a nice addition.
And then, let's see here.
You can't forget about me!
Go away!
[SHIGURE screams]
Great.
Since we all seem to be
down for the party,
the drama club can
take care of planning it.
Eruna, do you mind being
in charge of inviting people?
Not at all!
--[BIMII] Ow! Ryui!
--[ERUNA] C'mon! Let's go!
[HIMI]
A party? I'll be there!
What should I wear?
Is this okay?
That's fine, but you would
look good in anything!
If I had to choose though,
I'd say to come in
your birthday suit!
How fun!
I'll be sure to
cover myself in blood
and grab an umbilical cord!
I don't think that's
what you meant, ryui.
[ERUNA]
Sounds perfect to me!
[BIMII]
No, ma'am!
We don't want to
freak Asuhi out, ryui!
[MINATOGAWA] I'll go if you
want, but you can't have him.
[ERUNA]
Uh good, I don't want him.
I don't know.
I'm afraid if I show,
I'd end up ruining the mood.
Unless you're okay with it
being ruined a little bit.
Don't worry!
If that happens,
I'll just make Bimii fix it!
But how?
And why me? Ryui.
Why would Fujishiro
want to go to some lame party?
It's weird to even ask her.
Fujishiro doesn't
get this idea at all.
You'd have so much fun,
Light Otone!
[OTONE]
Fuji doubts that.
Or more like
you don't doubt that!
Right?
A party?
Okay, I'll at least
think about it.
After you think about it,
you should go!
Oh poo.
This is getting heavy.
Now what kind of theme
do we think it should be?
Themes are cool!
Normal parties are boring!
[TONKYUN] Since Asuhi
likes astronomy so much,
maybe we should go
with "under the stars."
The roof at night
would be cool, roar!
Yeah! That's a brilliant idea!
Okay, then I say
the location of the party
should be changed
from my room to the roof.
[USAMARU] Any thoughts
on what we should tell Asuhi?
Well, we definitely want
it to be a surprise, so...
Maybe we give him this invite
without telling him
what it's for.
I'm exhausted, ryui.
Oh, hey, Mr. Bimii!
Talk about some
perfect timing, roar!
Did you invite everybody?
I don't think so.
I was too busy following
Eruna around as she bought food
to pay too much attention,
but she thinks
they'll all make it, ryui.
It's sweet of you
to help, Mr. Bimii!
Now, we just need Eruna to
let all the people she talked to
know the location
has changed to the roof.
Also, while you're at it,
do you mind dropping by and
giving this invitation to Asuhi?
Ryui...
I'm starting to think these kids
are trying to work
me to death, ryui.
Oh, it's Mr. Bimii.
Hello, sir!
[BIMII] Hi, Asuhi.
I've been looking for you.
I'm supposed to give you this
message from the drama club.
It's that the location
has been changed
to the roof of the dorm, ryui.
[BIMII] I'm sure
I'll see you later, ryui.
She's not back yet, ryui?
What are you gonna do?
[ERUNA]
What's this?
Fancy!
Looks like it's
a challenge offer!
I bet it's from someone
who wanted to learn
from this amazing
rookie battle quarterfinalist!
If I accept this challenge and
am super cool while I beat them,
the whole school
will be talking about me!
And that would be
awesome for my new
yet-to-be-named
and-formed club!
Yeah!
Eruna's not here. Huh...
No, and Seisa
hasn't shown up, either.
I'm just assuming
Otone won't make it.
What happens if Asuhi
gets here before them?
I dunno, but we
should hide pretty soon.
Jeez, you guys
sure like surprises
for a group of people
who aren't surprising.
[footsteps]
It's him.
Look, she's here!
Crazy.
Maybe I came too early.
I knew I should have shown up
here fashionably late.
Shoot, I missed the chance to
have an awesome entrance!
It seems like Eruna might
be a little confused again.
Hello, Eruna.
Minatoga-what?
That's so
unbelievably flattering.
I never would've guessed
you were the one
who challenged me to a match!
I'm in, man!
Challenge accepted!
Uh, okay...
Don't mind if I do.
[ALL gasp]
Excuse me?
What? Asuhi, you're here?
Yeah, I heard that
the location had changed,
but I never found out what
was the location was for.
[ALL laughing]
Looks like our
surprise bombed, huh?
Yeah, guess so. Move out.
[SHIGURE]
Jump!
Stick it.
And now, we'll start the
surprise party of the year
with everyone's favorite emcee,
me, Shigure Ninomiya!
[ERUNA gasps]
[NYAMIRIN]
We love you, Asuhi!
[ALL]
Congratulations!
We're all proud of you
for winning second place
in the tournament!
Huh?
That's right!
The big star of today's party
is you, Asuhi Imizu!
Now, let's--
[screams]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL yelling]
[ASUHI]
Wow, really?
You guys planned a party for me?
Thank you,
that's very kind!
You don't have to be
so proper about it.
For real.
It's no big deal, roar!
Aw, man!
I blame Bimii for
screwing up this whole day!
No, even if he
didn't screw up,
rain is still rain.
[TONKYUN] We were defeated
because we didn't check
the weather forecast.
Do you wanna
go somewhere else?
Doesn't the drama clubroom
have lots of space?
What?
You don't want to
wait a little longer?
Yeah, the rain
might stop, roar!
I hope it does!
It'd be so cool to have
the party under the stars!
Me too!
I mean, we are having
this thing for Asuhi!
Wow, guys.
You all really are the best.
Did I ever tell you
what happened to me
when I was younger?
There's a story behind me
loving stars so much, you know.
Oh, really?
Well, what is it?
Y'see, I was
bullied as a kid.
I can't even remember
when it started.
The other boys
would pick on me.
Apparently, I wasn't tough
or manly enough for them,
or something.
At some point, I heard
that if you made a wish
three times on a falling star,
your wish would come true.
So then one day, I made a wish.
I wished with all my heart
that I could become strong.
I might've just
convinced myself of it.
But either way
because of that wish,
for the first time ever,
I stood up to my enemies.
For the first time ever,
I stood up for myself!
After that,
all those boys
stopped bullying me completely.
So that one wish
is why you love stars?
It is. They saved me.
[chuckles]
Well I guess he doesn't
actually smile all the time,
and go figure,
he's not perfect.
Sorry, it's nothing.
Killing Art.
[ERUNA]
Wow! Look at the sky!
[ALL exclaiming]
Right there's Arcturus.
It's a star near Spica
that's also known
as the star of happiness!
Whoa!
You know, Asuhi...
You may not realize it,
but you always manage
to shine just as bright
as that star up there does.
For what it's worth,
that's how I see it.
Cool.
[OTONE] Fujishiro saw
what you did for them.
[OTONE]
How fun!
Fuji witnessed the power
of Killing Art, didn't she?
[ASUHI] Confess!
What would you wish for
on a falling star, Eruna?
[ERUNA giggles]
Can I really say it?
[ASUHI]
Of course you can.
[ERUNA] Really? Well, don't
look at me if things get crazy,
because I'm gonna say it!
I might even say it three times!
I've got a list so long
I had to cram it all
into 158 journals!
[ASUHI]
The sun would rise again
before you could
say that three times.
[ERUNA]
And it's Asuhi with the retort!
Nice one. I approve!
You know what,
you're good as the funny man,
but still, you can be
a great straight man, too.
[ASUHI]
Thank you...?
So what would you
wish for, Fujishiro?
[OTONE] Fujishiro would
only wish for one thing:
World conquest, naturally.
I'm not joking, either.
Earlier, Fujishiro was working
out a dreadful, wicked plan
with the big four who serve
and love me unconditionally.
[ERUNA]
What?! The big four?
Oh yeah, the Cantopop boy band
from Hong Kong! Yes, please!
[ASUHI] I think she's talking
about four accounting firms.
[OTONE]
No, not those!
These big four are a
much more dreadful big four
than either of those fours!
They're so scary,
they'll make you wet yourself.
[ASUHI] Next time,
"Unidentified Treasure."
I'm going to defeat
the dreadful big four,
and then I'll
get to be number one!
[ERUNA]
Wait! They'll be here?!
[ASUHI]
Uh, no. Probably not.