[ERUNA]
Hey, Seisa!
Guess what, girl!
Took long enough, but the
school has finally recognized
my legendary new club!
They even gave us a sweet
room to use and everything!
And that's why Eruna Ichinomiya
will vacate your mansion!
Here, take my sleeping bag!
She's been soaked
with a ton of memories,
so please take care of her.
I'll come back and visit
you soon, sleeping bag.
I swear it.
Remember me with her!
Gross.
The only thing that bag's
been "soaked" with
is your sweat and stench,
so why don't you go ahead
and take it with you
on your way out.
[screams]
[grunts]
Oh, just you wait, Seisa,
my club is gonna be super fun!
Thank you for everything!
[giggles]
[BIMII sighs]
[BIMII]
Ugh...
[BIMII screams]
[sighs]
[BIMII sighs]
I hate this, ryui.
I bet.
I mean, the human thing
was weird enough,
but that was way more intense
than I thought it would be.
Maybe it's just Fuji,
but she has a feeling
we're getting a peek into
something creepy here,
like Mikagura has a
secret côté obscur.
If this wasn't real life,
I'd be afraid they wouldn't
let us return home alive.
Everything hurts.
Why do I always
forget how hard it is
to go back to this form, ryui?
Go back?
What? Bimii, are you telling
us you used to be human?
[BIMII sighs]
Yes, ryui.
It's a long, fascinating story.
To start with, what you just saw
isn't the way I'm
supposed to transform.
In fact...
[BIMII]
Hey! Where are you going?
Don't you want to listen
to my origin story?
[BIMII screams]
[BIMII]
Right behind you, ryui.
Yay!
Our room's starting to
look officially official!
About time.
But... I dunno... It just...
Does it look a little, um,
well, a lot dreary to you?
Well, obviously.
Don't worry, though.
We've got help!
Speak of the cute devils!
[KATAI sighs]
Congratulations
on your new club!
I bet you're both excited!
You said you were
looking for something
to decorate your new
room with, right?
Here, a hanging scroll
from the calligraphy club.
Our gift!
Cool! We got a scroll thingie!
[HIMI] Like a newborn butterfly
that is still a caterpillar,
your new club will shine
and fly out into a future
where no one touches its wings.
I wrote this scroll
in that spirit.
[ERUNA]
Perverted transformation?
[OTONE]
Metamorphose.
Ta-da! Do you love it?
Uh... Sure, why not?
My turn.
--[ERUNA gasps]
--How'd you do that?
He's a ninja!
Truth.
I brought you a
present from my club.
Nice!
Flowers are blooming
on the pervert part!
[pants]
Eruna, darling.
My present for you
is this double bed.
Naturally, we'll be
sleeping on it together!
[gasps] Eruna? Wh-What's wrong?!
Was it something I said?
Please don't...
Don't lock me away.
It's so cold out
here in the hall.
[YUTO]
Well, look at you, Eruna!
Yeah, congrats!
I guess everyone
beat us here, huh?
Congratulations!
You should be proud of yourself!
Thanks a bunch. You're so sweet!
Is that to make the room yummy?
It is. I hope you enjoy it.
--I thought it smelled nice.
--[SHIGURE] Are you refusing to
accept my present?! How can you
--do this to me, Eruna?
--[GROUP laugh]
Oh, dear, um. Hey there, Otone?
--[GROUP] Huh?
--Congrats to you, as well!
Wow! You have very good manners,
taking the time to greet
Fujishiro, as well.
At this point,
you seem promising,
so perhaps Fuji will be a little
convivial to you hereafter.
Eruna, you might wanna go ahead
and translate that for him.
[ERUNA chuckles]
Thank you! I'm so happy!
Please be friends
with me from now on!
Kiss and heart, XO forever!
Wrong!
Quit taking liberties
with what I said.
Fuji never mentioned XO.
Yeah, but kiss and
heart were there?
Well either way, I'd
like for us to be friends.
[OTONE]
Uh...
[door clicks, creaks]
Hey...
I didn't expect you to show.
Aren't you gonna go inside?
[KUZURYU]
Hmph.
Naw, you know I'm not
the best with crowds.
Later, man.
[MILK MACHINE]
Moo...
--[chattering]
--[ERUNA] Uhh...
What was Enoyan thinking
just leaving this creepy guy
at the door without taking
two seconds to come say hi?
Very much his style,
though, ryui.
It's weird that Seisa
hasn't swung by, yet, huh?
Now that you mention it,
I expected her to have made
an appearance by now, ryui.
You don't think she's
not happy for me, do you?
Because that would suck.
--[knocking]
--[gasps]
Do you mind if I come in?
[ERUNA]
Rumina!
Look, you need to
give it up already.
I'm not gonna let you
steal this room from us!
--That's not it.
--Huh?
Oh, well, in that case, did you
come to celebrate with us?
No, that's not it, either.
[ERUNA]
Ooh.
"What is the 'ghost' that
lives in the school?"
Yeah! I've heard
about that before.
[TONKYUN]
Me too.
People have been telling stories
about a ghost for a while, now.
Correct, and all of us
at the newspaper club
are ready to take down
this so-called ghost.
Sounds cool.
So? What do you need from me?
If you're going to confess,
you should do it now.
This is your only chance.
You know the identity
of this ghost.
It's you, is it not?
[ERUNA]
Huh?
[RUMINA] Can you blame
me for accusing you
after your previous lies?
[RUMINA]
You knew at the time
you were making a fool
out of the newspaper club.
Now we have to fight to
get our good name back,
and it's completely your fault.
Yeah... About that, I've
been meaning to say...
Thanks so much,
you really helped us get
that third member we needed.
[RUMINA] And where is this
so-called third member?
[ERUNA gasps]
Uh....
Just admit it.
You guys are the ones behind
this ghost nonsense, aren't you?
No, we're not!
For real! It's not
them, so back off.
Honestly, I don't know what this
ghost thing is about, either.
Fine.
Then, we've a mystery.
Who in the world could this
reported spirit really be?
[TONKYUN] Any chance it
could be, like, a real ghost?
What?! As in supernatural?
[BOTH yelp]
So? I'm not scared
at all, are you?
Not even a little!
--[bones rattling]
--Yeah. I'm not afraid either.
'Cause, otherwise, I'd be
all shaking like a leaf,
which I'm not. Nope.
I don't care at all.
Of course, that fake story
was an embarrassment,
but we can make
this an opportunity
to reclaim our good name.
So we're gonna find out
the truth no matter what.
I expect your club and friends
to help with the investigation.
You are going to help us with
this investigation, Eruna.
Yeah, duh, totally gonna help
you with all the ghost stuff.
Hey, Eruna?
Are you seriously gonna go
on a ghost hunt for Rumina?
Yeah! Know why?
'Cause ghosts are almost always
sad, needy, and beautiful girls!
[OTONE] I'm not sure if ours
is a beautiful girl or not,
but I guess it's true you don't
normally hear about ghosts
that are just like, overflowing
with joy and self-confidence.
[ERUNA]
See, that's what I'm saying.
So we have to find this
ghost lady and catch her.
Then, we can make her
take sexy pictures!
No way that won't
promote the club
and impress Seisa
at the same time!
Seisa Mikagura?
Why her?
Because she's the reason
Eruna created a new club
in the first place, ryui.
She wanted to prove
herself to Seisa.
[ERUNA]
Uh-huh!
Seisa...
My goal right now is
to make this a club
that will surprise her
with my coolness!
[BIMII] Eruna's what you could
call over-dedicated to this.
Hey! It's not just me, Bimii!
Come on, you transformed and
--turned into a student!
--Everything Eruna does
--A super hot student!
--is all for that Seisa girl.
--What was that
--I wonder...
--all about, huh?
--Does Seisa even know?
[ERUNA] I'm guessing it
wasn't for the yaoi fan girls!
[footsteps]
Here I am!
No way...
Aww, you drama club
nerds are the best!
We're going to help you
find that ghost, Eruna!
Figured it sounded
like fun, so why not?
[TONKYUN]
Unfortunately,
Kumano had something
come up last minute,
so she won't be able to join us.
I wish I had thought of that.
Himi sends her love.
She said she had a stomachache
and wasn't going to make it.
That's a bummer.
But major kudos to you for
deciding to come without her!
--Here you go!
--Huh?
Did you bring that because we're
supposed to "catch" a ghost?
[TONKYUN] Eruna, we're talking
about a supernatural being,
not a butterfly.
Huh? I thought Otone
would be here by now.
She's not?
Expected her to be first.
Strange that she would
be later than me.
Especially since she left
before we did, ryui.
[ring]
[ERUNA]
Uh. It's from Otone!
[BIMII]
What's wrong, ryui?
Otone said there was something
else that she had to do.
[nervous laugh] I had a feeling
that girl was more afraid of
this ghost hunting adventure
than she let on.
Heh.
That sounds pretty
funny coming from a guy
whose whole body is shaking.
[USAMARU]
What?!
No, I'm not shaking with fear;
I'm shaking with rage!
I'm about to kill
this ghost, man!
[YUTO]
All right!
You guys ready to get this
freak show on the road?
[GROUP]
Yeah!
[USAMARU]
Uh... Y-Yeah, let's do it.
[doorbell rings]
[KURUMI gasps]
You're the rookie battle winner.
I'm Otone Fujishiro.
I apologize for
calling so late, ma'am.
I was hoping to speak with
Seisa Mikagura if possible.
Unfortunately, my lady has gone
to bed and is not available.
[SEISA]
It's okay.
[KURUMI gasps]
[ERUNA]
Come out, little ghostie.
You can trust us.
We're not gonna hurt you!
Little ghostie,
are you even real?
[USAMARU groans]
[USAMARU gasps]
[screams]
Over there!
--[USUMARU cries]
--Will you keep it down?!
[NYAMIRIN]
Yes, hush it.
You're going to scare
the ghost away!
But I saw things!
Horrible things!
[USAMARU]
Where'd it go?
[TONKYUN]
What are we looking at?
No way! Did you find the ghost?
[ERUNA]
Usamaru! There's nothing there!
No... It's not a ghost.
What I saw looked like
part of the school
was collapsing in on itself.
[TONKYUN] Nothing appears
to be collapsing to me.
Nope, me either.
Oh...
Maybe I just... imagined it.
[TONKYUN]
According to the data
given to us by the
newspaper club,
the majority of eyewitness
reports about the ghost
are right around this corner.
[ERUNA gasps]
Hey! My old home!
I slept right here.
Oh, nostalgia.
Thanks to not being
a member of a club,
Eruna was forced to
live in this hallway
before she moved into
Seisa's mansion, ryui.
Moments like these
make you think about
what life was like
on the other side.
Not to mention how far
I've come since then!
[KATAI giggles]
It's funny now,
but I remember when Eruna would
hop around in her sleeping bag,
and it would
completely terrify me
until I'd finally
realize it was her.
Oh yeah. I always thought it was
way too much trouble to get out
of the bag, so I'd just jump
to wherever I wanted to
go while I was still inside it!
Every time I saw you,
I thought for a sec you
were a ghost haunting me.
[YUTO]
Hm.
Hold on, you guys.
Hey, you know all those
eyewitness accounts
reporting the ghost to
be right around here?
What did they say exactly?
[TONKYUN]
According to the data we've got:
The ghost was an eerie face
that would appear out of
nowhere in the darkness.
That's what they said.
So you guys are
probably thinking
what I'm thinking, right?
[TONKYUN] You mean that the
ghost must have been Eruna
wandering around
in her sleeping bag?
Eh?
What? Really?
[laughs] No, that's hilarious!
You're so stupid.
Seriously?!
That's kind of a letdown
after we were thinking we were
gonna find a real life ghost!
[TONKYUN]
This is a problem.
You know that, right?
No?
[TONKYUN] When Rumina
asked if you were the ghost,
you denied it.
It'll look like you lied to her.
[ERUNA gasps]
[RUMINA] You knew at
the time you were making
a fool out of the
newspaper club.
Now, we have to fight to
get our good name back,
and it's completely your fault.
--[ERUNA whimpers]
--For real,
she is gonna be
so pissed at you.
[NYAMIRIN]
Unbelievably pissed.
[ERUNA]
Ugh...
[gasps]
Oh, right! Bimii!
Would you do me a favor?
[BIMII]
Eh...
[owl hooting]
[RUMINA gasps, grunts]
Hey! Who are you, and
are you the perpetrator
purportedly pretending
to be a poltergeist?
[RUMINA]
Come back!
[GHOST moans]
Huh-uh.
I didn't just see a
genuine ghost, did I?
[screams]
I have no idea how that
could've fooled anyone, ryui.
[gasps]
[BIMII gasps]
[KUZURYU]
Huh?
[OTONE]
Answer the question, Seisa.
It's not that hard.
Fujishiro wants
to know the truth.
She wants to know why you
refuse to go see Eruna.
[SEISA sighs]
And here I thought your
presence would be interesting.
Eruna formed a new
club for you, Seisa.
You know she did,
so don't deny it.
Are you just égoïste?
[OTONE] Seems you're
selfish because even though
Eruna worked hard to form a club
specifically to make you happy,
doesn't look like you're
too happy for her.
And even though Eruna
has been waiting for you
to show up in support of her,
you don't seem to want
to do that, either.
Is it pride?
Will your precious
pride not allow you to
walk over there
and be kind to her?
Why? Because if Eruna
wants to see you,
she should be the one
making the effort?
Are you so special that
you can't be bothered
to make an effort for
anyone other than yourself?
Who are you?!
Rather, who do
you think you are?
A celebrity?
The Queen of Sheba?
Are you teasing her on purpose
to feel better about yourself?
Having fun leaving her
hanging like this?
You'd think you were
some child star
trying to make a comeback
but afraid everyone
will think you suck,
so you say you've been
spending time in the "theatre"
because you're a "real artist"
when really, you're just
an attention-seeking jerk
who wants to be worshipped!
Well, guess what.
It's not very nice,
and it's an unbelievably
cruel way to treat Eruna.
[SEISA chuckles]
Not that it matters to me,
but you never actually
lived abroad, did you?
[OTONE gasps]
Did you not notice?
You stopped trying to
Frenchify your words
somewhere in the middle of
that darling little speech.
So what?! That has nothing
to do with anything right now!
Let me ask you.
So what if I am all those
things you just called me?
How is my life any
of your business?
Why bother getting angry
about a situation that
in no way involves you?
[OTONE]
Because...
[ERUNA laughs]
Hey, at least we can officially
close that case, amiright?
[USAMARU]
Not so fast!
'Kay.
Eruna, I get that you were the
ghost everyone else saw, but
what the hell was
behind what I saw?
[YUTO]
Are you talking about
when your imagination
got the best of you?
Shut up!
That's not what happened.
The school was collapsing!
It's cool.
Calm down. We get it.
I don't know about you guys,
but I'm still kinda freaked out
that Mr. Bimii was even
able to turn into a human.
[TONKYUN]
His method of transformation
didn't help, either.
Oh yeah, that threw
me for a loop, too.
What was that factory looking
place supposed to be anyway?
[TONKYUN]
Probably smart if we just forget
that whole thing ever happened.
[KATAI] Mr. Bimii sure is
taking a long time catching up.
I bet he's just floating
around being lazy.
Hey! What's up, Enoyan?
Is everything okay?
Oh!
I bet after drinking milk
all by your lonesome self
in the dark of night,
you started to long for
company and came to see me.
Such a sweet heart!
And of course, you can
hang out with us!
That's not it, stupid.
But now that I think about
it, maybe I'm the stupid one
for thinking I needed to
tell you what I just saw.
[ERUNA]
Huh?
[KUZURYU] Has to do with
that girl from your club
with the purple
hair and Seisa.
Best-case scenario:
they're about to fight.
[ERUNA]
Huh?
[ERUNA] Otone and
Seisa are gonna fight?
Your club doesn't have
anything to do with me,
and I don't have
anything to do with it.
Why waste your time
worrying about my actions
when you can do
whatever you want?
[OTONE] Because inside
Eruna, you're always there.
[SEISA gasps]
[OTONE] Because no matter how
much fun we might have together,
she'd have more fun if
you were there, too.
You have to know she's
always thinking about you.
[OTONE] Fuji worries because
no matter how hard she tries,
Eruna keeps you in
a forbidden place
that Fujishiro cannot enter.
Wow.
It's really not
that big of a deal.
I just don't get you.
If I were in your shoes, I--
I would naturally want to stay
as far away from you as I could.
[OTONE] That might
be the smartest move,
but it would be selfish.
Besides Fujishiro isn't
worried about herself.
All I want is for
Eruna to be happy!
She understands me.
She was the first person to give
me a chance and be my friend.
To me, that girl is more
precious and cherished
than you will ever know.
[And what I feel for
her is stronger than
what anyone else might claim.
That includes you, too, Seisa.
Believe it.
[OTONE]
Now you understand why
I will do whatever it
takes to make you listen.
[SEISA]
Hm.
Whatever it takes, my goodness.
What could you do?
Anything?
[OTONE]
Won't know unless I try, will I?
I do hope winning
the rookie battle
didn't make you too
confident, Otone, dear.
You wouldn't want to get hurt.
Anticomplex!
Snake!
[OTONE grunts]
Are you seriously planning
to fight me with pink ribbons?
[OTONE grunts]
Sword!
[SEISA grunts]
[SEISA gasps]
[OTONE grunts]
[ERUNA panting]
I don't get any of this!
Why would they even be together?
[gasps]
Oh no. I'm too late!
[SEISA grunts]
[gasps]
Killing Art, go.
[OTONE grunts]
Rain down.
[SEISA gasps]
Fuji thought you were finally
going to use Killing Art.
[SEISA gasps]
Who's too confident, now?
You shouldn't
underestimate Fuji.
[SEISA grunts]
So do you think you're
too good for this?
Don't wanna waste your
treasured ability
on such a pathetic loser?
Is that how it is, Seisa?
You can't be bothered
to take out the trash?
Or is it so you have
an excuse to use
when you get your ass
kicked by Fujishiro?
You won't escape.
[SEISA yelps]
[grunts]
[OTONE]
Sword.
[OTONE] Even now, you refuse
use your ability on Fuji?
If you'd rather me win than
use Killing Art, then so be it.
When you lose,
remember, no excuses!
[ERUNA]
Otone, don't!
[OTONE gasps]
[ERUNA panting]
[OTONE growls]
What's going on?
One of you tell me!
[HIMI] Hey, hold on! We aren't
far from the last episode,
so why haven't I shown up yet
in a single preview?! How rude!
[ERUNA]
Don't worry, Himi!
I've been saving
this one for you!
Go ahead and preview
to your heart's content!
[HIMI]
Really? Here I go, then!
[KURUMI]
Just a moment, please.
I haven't been included in
a single preview, either.
[ERUNA] Why did I not
think of putting Miss Kurumi
and Himi together before?!
Well, then, ladies, knock
us out with a new preview
that no one has
ever, ever heard!
[BIMII]
Hey, hold on a minute, ladies.
Don't forget that I have
yet to do any previews
in my human form.
[ERUNA]
Bimii!
[HIMI] Meh... Thanks,
but no thanks, Mr. Bimii.
I think I can handle
this preview on my own.
[BIMII]
Negative.
I've got two hundred
and eighty-seven,
nine hundred and
twenty-eight thousand
nationwide fans waiting
for this moment.
I can't give that up, even
for you, darling Himi.
[ERUNA] Then why don't
we do it all at once?
[KURUMI] Because we hardly
need some lame preview
that sounds like a bunch of
pathetic students holding hands,
so they can all cross
the finish line at once.
Everyone can't
always get a medal.
Next time, "Nostalgic Triangle".
[HIMI] Aw! You went and said it!
No fair, Miss Kurumi!
[BIMII] They call that
stealing a march, mecha!
You're a disgrace
as a teacher, mecha!
[ERUNA]
Bimii, calm down!
You're ending your sentences
with "mecha" again!
[KURUMI] Next time, Lady Seisa's
past will finally be revealed.
[ERUNA]
What? Seisa's past, what?!
Now my heart's all a flutter!