[YUTO'S BROTHER]
Yuto! Come on, already!
You know you wanna
play Miracle Man with me!
Oh my gosh,
you won't ever believe this!
Super Miracle Man's uncle
saw his true identity,
and then he decided he was
gonna try and make money off it
by writing a tell-all book!
[YOUNG YUTO]
Holy crap, that guy sucks.
[YUTO]
Back then, I loved hanging out
with my little brother.
He was a cool kid,
innocent and friendly.
Always making friends
wherever he went.
And then there was me.
I was the complete opposite.
If my brother was
the one out in front,
I was the one in the back.
I always knew why
I was left behind.
[YUTO'S BROTHER]
Wait, what about Yuto?
Why doesn't he get
to come with us?
[YUTO'S MOM] Your brother
is going to live with Daddy.
Come on, it's time.
[YUTO'S BROTHER]
But I want to be with Yuto!
[YUTO]
It's my fault.
If I could have just smiled
and been more like him...
But I couldn't.
I wasn't good enough,
so she left without me.
I wasn't the one she wanted.
I wasn't my perfect
little brother.
[YUTO]
See, Mom? I'm smiling.
I know how to act
like the Yuto Akama
that anyone would want now.
If I wanted
to fool everyone else,
I had to start with myself.
Believing you're
someone you're not?
It's harder than you'd think.
So here I am.
The Solitary Coup d'Etat!
[SEISA]
Eruna? Eruna.
Can you help?
I need this unzipped.
Yeah, sure,
whatever you want!
No need to rush.
I'd like you to go slowly.
Cool. On it.
[laughing creepily]
Seisa, I don't know if I
can go much lower than this.
I'm too embarrassed!
[screams]
[groans]
[KURUMI]
My lady. Good morning.
Don't worry about getting up
if you would rather not.
I can just leave breakfast
here in case you get hungry.
Miss Kurumi!
I'd like something to eat, too!
Is this my breakfast?
Hey, I'm not a dog!
Wait...
Does this mean you're actually
recognizing me as Seisa's pet?
Yay! I get to play
fetch with Seisa, aroo!
[groaning]
Oh, by the way,
food and lodging aren't free.
Know that everything is being
deducted from your points.
[ERUNA]
Rude!
Guess what!
I get to start my training for
the rookie battle today, Seisa!
[ERUNA screams]
[ERUNA, HIMI grunting]
[yelling]
Here we go, Toy Gun!
Tension max...!
Ooh, sucks to be you!
No regrets!
See ya next week!
Ugh, what's the deal?
I can't get my special
attack to work at all!
That's because
it's your real ability, see?
You have to learn how to use it
before you can control it, ryui.
[groans]
[YUTO]
What, worn out already?
Must be working hard.
Come on now, don't tell me
the great Eruna's been beat!
She has, but that's
not the issue.
Her problem is that it's
like she's forgotten
how she was supposed
to fight in the first place.
You forgot how to fight?
I thought you were just trying
to take advantage
of the moment and grope me!
I can't win the
rookie battle like this!
I'll never get my own club now!
I'm super depressed!
[ERUNA] Himi, training with you
can make me feel better, though.
Teach me how to be gentle!
[ERUNA, HIMI arguing]
Yuto, what do you think
about holding a class
for club battle beginners so
they can get a little experience
before the tournament?
A class for beginners?
[NYAMIRIN]
That's what I said!
We like Eruna, so why not?
Might as well coach our own
first years from drama club
while we're at it.
Yeah, great idea!
[TONKYUN]
It'll be good motivation.
I'm on board
for that, roar!
Well?
It makes sense.
As long as it's just
until the rookie battle,
I don't see why we can't.
Can I be the
first person to sign up
for the class, please?
Yay! We're teaching a class!
Isn't that nice?
You should thank them!
A big thanks
to both of you!
Just who exactly
are you talking to?!
Eruna, try to keep in mind
that my coaching is brutal.
I'm a relentless bear, roar!
Wow. Almost too cute to handle.
You best get ready, roar!
I haven't mentioned this,
but it's been bothering me.
You realize you're not
actually a bear, right?
[KUMANO gasps]
Also, ending every
thought with a growl
kinda seems like
you're forcing it.
[USAMARU] Stop! You know
not of what you speak!
Nyamirin decided she was a bear,
and since Kumano
has a thing for Nyamirin,
she does everything she can
think of to "be a bear."
This is a passionate
fire you can't put out!
[wailing]
[KUMANO]
You don't have to say it!
I know that's a weird way
to end my sentences!
But this was the only
way I could think of
to show my personality and
stand out in the drama club!
You're not growling,
good for you!
[KUMANO sobbing]
It'll be okay.
Why do drama kids
have to be so loud?
[ASUHI]
Excuse me, um... Yuto?
Come on, Yuto!
[ERUNA]
Asuhi!
I just wanted to apologize
again for yesterday.
I'm still embarrassed about
how bad I lost to you.
Cool.
Well, that's all.
I'll be on my way.
[NYAMIRIN] Okay, I'm gonna
take your measurements.
[ERUNA] You want me to
dress up like an animal, too?
Do I get to be a cute squirrel?
Or la lone wolf, since I'm
all "not in a club" and stuff?
[NYAMIRIN]
I was thinking a gorilla.
[ERUNA whining]
After-School Red,
Yuto Akama!
I'm the Subsection Chief,
Nyamirin!
I'm the After-School
Peace Officer, Kumano,
so no fighting
in the battles, roar!
[TONKYUN] After-School
Second Division, Tonkyun.
Uh, but my real name is--
After-School Private,
passionately Usamaru!
After-School Noodles,
Eruna Ichinomiya!
And this is our
new entrance theme!
[ALL] We are the
After-School Six, so suck it!
Man. I wanna go home.
What?
Oh no, the evil syndicate
Dark Chaos Gang
is running wild
and rampaging the city!
After-School Six,
move out! Now, roar, roar!
Heck yeah!
Here comes my
Passionate Tornado Kick!
Clip-clop, clip-clop.
Let's finish off
the Dark Chaos Gang!
Toy Gun, tension max,
go get 'em!
We know you can
do way better than that.
Let's take it back once more,
and make sure you
get it down this time!
Sir!
Tension max, go!
Go!
Go, tension max go, go!
Go, tension max,
stop being such a jerk!
[yells]
Oh, After-School Noodles!
Are you okay, roar?!
No. I'm sorry,
but it's too late for me.
No, Noodles!
Don't be so stupid!
Without six of us, we can't
be the After-School Six!
You can't just give up.
Not now, not when
you're so close.
The limitless express
train of passionate youth
won't wait for you, Noodles!
Oh, do you mean it,
After-School Private?
[TONKYUN]
Come, Noodles.
We shall fight to the end.
Forever!
Thank you, After-School
Second Division, and scene.
Not bad.
Now stand up and make it great!
Playing the drama is fun!
[ERUNA]
I got it!
If they come at me here, I--Wah!
If it's this way, I--Gah!
Find the opponent's
opening and quick--Ow!
I can't sleep.
Will you quit being so noisy?
Squee! It's a sneak attack
from the side!
What're you reading?
Oh, this brilliance
is the official script
for the After-School Six.
It's actually more like
a strategy guide
for the rookie battle
that Yuto was nice
enough to write for us.
The drama kids have
been helping me a lot.
I'm so much better already!
Feel free to have
high expectations.
I think you're gonna fall
in love with me all over again!
Hey! I was wondering...
Do you mind telling me
what kind of attack
your Killing Art move is?
[ERUNA]
During the practice match,
everything happened so fast
that I couldn't really
see what you did.
Sorry, but I'd really
rather not talk about that.
Huh? Okay.
Then, would you
rather talk about
what color your underwear is?
[SEISA] No. I don't want
to talk about that, either.
Whoa, Seisa's so
enchanting when she acts shy.
[footsteps running]
[door opening]
[KUMANO]
Sorry I'm late, roar!
I wanted to make sure
I got a ton of food
so you guys could keep your
energy up, roar! Go team!
[ALL cheering]
[TONKYUN]
Oh. Hold on.
This is a stamina
pork bowl, isn't it?
[KUMANO] Oh my gah.
I'm so sorry!
Please don't think I want you
to be a cannibal or anything!
[TONKYUN] Just because
Nyamirin gave me a pig costume
doesn't mean I'm an actual pig.
It's not cannibalism.
[KUMANO]
Oh, good.
Pigs are delicious,
regardless, though!
[TONKYUN] Do you mind if
we could all start calling me
by my real name now?
It's actually--
Heck yeah!
Lucky me got a ton
of red pickled ginger
in my awesome pork bowl!
[BIMII]
Ryui. Ryui.
[TONKYUN] I don't eat pork,
so you can have it.
Because cannibalism?
Tonkyun, say it ain't so!
[TONKYUN]
It ain't so.
I just don't dig on swine.
I'll give you
a piece of mine, too,
if you want it, Gorilla!
Gorilla?
[makes gorilla noises]
[ALL laughing]
Man, the After-School Six
is really killing it, you know?
You'd think being the only one
whose power hasn't awakened yet
would bum me out, but I'm good.
[ERUNA] If you could choose it,
what would your attack be?
[USAMARU] I'd want something
that only the lead in a movie
would have.
I'm thinkin' like, uh,
Super Miracle Man's style.
He was the greatest!
Oh! I remember him!
I used to watch that show
when I was a kid!
[KUMANO]
Hey, I did, too, roar!
Yeah, that guy had
like the best catchphrase
of all time!
[ALL] Protect the royalties
from the tell-all book!
Super Miracle Man has arrived!
Hey, bro. What's wrong?
Sorry.
I just remembered
something I had to do.
What is up with him?
[SHIGURE] Thank you so much for
your patience, dear admirers!
The time has finally come to
reveal the tournament brackets
for this year's rookie battle!
The emcee
will naturally be me,
manga research
club president and rep.
I am Shigure Ninomiya!
[cheering]
Those girls need to
hear the real deal pervy intel
on that creeper.
[SHIGURE]
Eruna!
I see you back there!
Look everyone, it's my
gorgeous and talented cousin!
How embarrassing.
I wish there was a big hole
so I could kick him into it.
That's very 300 of you.
[NYAMIRIN]
What's up, our girl Noodles?
Hey, what's up with you,
After-School Six?
Wait, why isn't Yuto here?
[TONKYUN]
Apparently, he is absent today.
Talk about crummy timing, right?
The rookie battle
starts tomorrow,
so today's our
last day together.
Roar.
Oh, right, boo.
[SHIGURE]
Here we go!
The tournament brackets
shall be revealed!
[TONKYUN]
Finally.
[crowd cheering]
It's so far away,
I can't see!
[TONKYUN] Why don't you
just use your device?
[ERUNA]
All right.
Who am I up against first?
Fun! It's Katai!
So cool.
Things just keep getting
more and more interesting!
Like it or not,
this is the end!
After-School Six, let's make
today count like never before!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Yuto. I hope he's okay.
[YUTO]
Hey there, Seisa.
Unusual to see you at school.
Hey there, Yuto.
Unusual to see
you sans followers.
I guess so, just thinking
about a character thing.
What kind of role is it?
A tough role,
harder than any other.
This guy's loved
by everyone he meets.
Needed by them, too.
And that's really what
he wants for himself.
But one day, a girl
shows up out of nowhere
who can see completely
through his façade,
and there's a boy, too,
and they're just
so alike, but...
Every time he looks at the boy,
he realizes that all
he's doing is trying to copy
that exact same nauseatingly
sweet and innocent personality.
It irritates the hell
out of him, and scares him,
but if he loses his mask,
no one will like
or need the guy anymore.
He's had a rough past,
and those memories don't help.
Well, if it were me,
I would let go of that past.
Take away its power.
How would you do that?
Let go of all the people.
The things I went through...
I would block everything out.
[ERUNA]
Yuto!
Hey, I didn't
know you'd still be here!
[ERUNA]
Yep!
Nice work, then.
After today, I guess
the After-School Six
is disbanding to
start something new.
Although, I can't say
I'll be disappointed
to have the drama club
back to normal.
Sorry I was gone.
I'm just, uh, bad at goodbyes.
You know how it is.
[ERUNA]
Don't be silly!
It's not a goodbye because
once I start my brand new club,
I'll bring my
brand new members over!
Then we'll brand
new battle each other!
Can you tell me something?
Because I can't figure it out.
Huh?
When did you realize the
truth about who I really am?
[YUTO]
Why didn't you say anything
even though you knew
this whole thing I do
was just an act?
I just don't understand
why you'd stick around, Eruna.
I guess because...
Because I also
realized something lame
like that shouldn't
mean we can't be friends.
[YUTO]
What?!
[ERUNA]
Uh... It's no big deal.
Besides, I'm pretty sure
everyone else
knew what was up, too.
[USAMARU]
Guess who!
Yuto, my man,
you're here! Great!
[NYAMIRIN]
Well, hello!
Glad you made it!
Welcome back!
We thought that
we needed a party.
It's to honor the end of an era!
We bought so much food,
we're gonna be sick, roar!
[TONKYUN]
Yuto, what would you like?
I wouldn't let them get pork
miso soup this time,
so you know.
[NYAMIRIN]
There's pork bone ramen, though!
[TONKYUN]
Seriously?
[ALL laugh]
[KURUMI]
Excuse me.
Are you looking for something?
I haven't been able
to find the idiot anywhere.
I became concerned
that she might have
snuck into your
room again, my lady.
[phone beeping]
Can you see my face?
I just wanted
to tell you in person
that I'll be spending
the night with
the After-School Six in Yuto's
room instead of at your place!
Get over here, Eruna.
Tonkyun took off his mask!
I've never seen his face!
We should call you
CutieTonks, roar!
So sorry to abandon you
so soon after moving in,
but to make it up to you
and keep you from being lonely,
I'll leave you with
a goodnight Eruna kiss.
[kissing noises]
Seems you will be able
to sleep peacefully
this evening.
Have a wonderful night, my lady.
Okay. Let's see.
Where will I be fighting?
[yells]
Ouchie.
Here.
[ASUHI]
Oh. Thank you!
It's weird.
You're so much like him.
My little brother, I mean.
Well, get to that match
and do your best.
I will!
[BIMII]
Even with all the practice,
your Toy Gun is
still unstable, ryui?
[ERUNA]
Not worried.
I'm feeling confident.
Even if I can't get
my special attack to work,
I still have a lot of
other stuff I can do now
thanks to working with
the After-School Six.
Were you as surprised
about this as me?
I hope you know that
I aspire to be like you,
but at the same time,
I also feel like getting
revenge for Himi's loss.
I wanted to
fight you eventually.
Just never imagined
the opportunity
would present itself so soon.
Let's make it a great fight!
Sure! I can do that!
Seisa, you came all
this way to watch, huh?
Must be curious.
Who, me? Nope, not at all.
[DEVICE]
Begin the match.
[ERUNA yells]
This is like so much fun, right?
Yeah, totally fun!
I wanted to win
without using this,
but oh well, look out!
Here it comes!
Cutie Ink!
Now that's cool!
Heck yeah,
my tension's building up!
[yelling]
[KATAI] By the way,
I won't run out of ammo!
It's almost over!
Man! So intense!
[ERUNA yelling]
I'm ready to go
guns a-blazing if you are!
[ERUNA]
Tension max...
Toy Gun, go!
One more for show!
[DEVICE]
Winner, Eruna Ichinomiya.
[cheering]
I definitely lost, but hey,
at least it was a fun fight!
Go win the tournament now.
You think you can do it?
Duh!
[ERUNA]
I can use Toy Gun again, people!
It's all thanks to those
crazy drama club kids.
The After-School Six are going
to last forever and ever, amen!
I'll keep training,
and next I'll learn
how to use a real gun!
[BIMII]
No real guns for you, ryui!
[ERUNA]
Are fake guns okay, then?
[BIMII] No, you'll still
look like a criminal, ryui!
[YUTO] Would that be like
a "Fake Handgun" ability?
[BIMII]
Let the fake gun go, ryui!
[YUTO]
It'll trick your eyes.
[BIMII]
No tricking anything, ryui!
[ERUNA] What about
the ability "Fake Money"?
[BIMII] Stop it,
this is getting dangerous, ryui!
Can we just do
the preview already?
[YUTO]
Next time, "School Fantasia."
The rookie battle
rushes toward its climax.
Will Usamaru's ability
finally awaken,
and whatever could it be?
[ERUNA]
Ooh, I've got one for him!
It's called "Passionate Sweat,"
and it's where
his sweat smells so bad
it can break crystals!
[BIMII]
Okay. That's disgusting.