[giggles]
[ERUNA]
Who, me?
Just shining bright like a
diamond on "Isle Eruna"!
'Scuse me...
But I really need to get the
interview portion started now.
Thanks again for this.
I'm Rumina Rikyu, the newspaper
club representative.
That was your first battle.
Talk about a
spectacular debut, huh?
Maybe.
So how exactly did you win?
How'd I win?
Um, let's see.
Well, I suppose you could say
I won because of fate.
I was ready to embrace an
opportunity when it arose.
I've been told this
is called an "awakening."
You know,
like something magical.
Interesting perspective.
[ERUNA] Um, what is
that supposed to mean?!
You act like I'm not right!
What is this interview about?
I thought it was to like
make everyone feel guilty
for not believing in me?
[RUMINA] Do you not feel
as if you share this victory
with anyone?
Actually, I do!
That was such a
wonderful fight, Eruna.
It's true.
You are the new hero
of Mikagura Academy.
However...
I wonder if you
would mind being a hero
I could keep all to myself?
Nope! I wouldn't mind at all!
Well, that's it
for the interview.
I'll just be on my way.
Seisa, let's be
together forever!
[ERUNA]
Holy crap, this is so good!
I can't believe I'm getting
to eat such fancy food
for breakfast!
This is thanks
to the points I got
from winning
yesterday's match, isn't it?
[STUDENT] "Here, I didn't
eat all of my sandwich,
so you can have
the rest if you want."
The days of filling my empty
stomach with the rejected crusts
someone gave me are over!
This soliloquy
is depressing, ryui.
[KATAI]
Hey, Eruna!
You were amazing!
Amazing amazing!
I mean I was shocked Himi lost,
but I was so happy for you!
You seem so calm,
but you've gotta be
freaking out on the inside now!
Thank you,
former sleeping-bag bestie!
Your bag is always there if
you want to come back to it.
Thank you, but no.
Oh, don't be shy.
You're so freaking adorable!
[KATAI]
It's the drama club!
Hey, Eruna.
I guess you decided to grace us
with your presence after all!
Why would you say that?
Did ya see the newspaper
club's extra edition?
Check it out.
Let's see.
Talk of the School!
"New Student Eruna
Ichinomiya Lives it up
Starting with Breakfast?"
This has nothing whatsoever
to do with the interview
we had yesterday!
And when the hell
did she take this pic?
[laughs]
Come on, don't get upset.
I think it's cool
that the article shows
who you really are,
behind the scenes.
[ERUNA growls]
[YUTO] Besides,
now the whole school thinks
you're a shoo-in to win
the rookie battle coming up.
Rookie battle?
A tournament where new students
compete with each other.
Since the competition
eventually impacts
the structure of the school,
it's considered an
important event, ryui.
What? No one told me about that!
Yo! My name's Usamaru,
and I'm a
first year here, too!
By the way, you were like
wicked cool in that fight!
Your passion was inspiring!
Don't get
I won't lose to you, but...
--Agh! I love your passion!
--[ERUNA] Calm down.
Maybe we could use
our inside voice?
This is my inside voice!
I can't help it!
I'm just a
passionate guy by nature!
[TONKYUN] I learned
from watching, as well.
[NYAMIRIN]
This pig's a first year, too.
I like to call him Tonkyun.
Tonkyun?
[TONKYUN] Nyamirin, how many
times do I have to tell you?
I'm not a pig, and I'd
rather you not call me that.
Oh, my actual name is--
Growl!
I'm looking forward to
the rookie battle, roar!
Oh! I am Kumano,
a second year student.
Roar!
Wow, cute but crazy.
[YUTO]
I think it's safe to say
you surprised everyone
in the drama club.
I mean, the only
other person at school
who can activate their
power without using an item
is Seisa,
and she's, like, legit.
That's not all that surprising.
We have a mutual love
between us,
so it's safe to say our bodies
and souls are basically one.
Oh, crap!
I didn't tell her
that I won yet!
Damn it!
Later, taters!
I gotta go find her!
[BIMII]
Wait! Eruna! Come back, ryui!
Thank goodness
that wasn't awkward,
right, you guys?
I think it's so cool
how honest she can be
about her life and love
and like, you know.
I'm just gonna shut up now.
[ERUNA]
Yay, I'm back!
And why do you think
she'll let you in this time?
Because, duh,
I've totally prepared
a secret weapon
that's gonna
be a sure thing!
[doorbell rings]
[ERUNA in male voice]
Ding-dong!
Package for Miss Mikagura!
It's an extra-extra
extra-large ham!
[BIMII] I think you meant
to say hamster, ryui.
Whatever. The point is
she won't be able to say no
to Himi's cuteness and
she'll have to open the gate!
No way those gates will open.
[BOTH scream]
Jeez. You tricked me.
But chips help, so...
Sorry not sorry!
You were only allowed inside
because my lady was interested
to hear your thoughts
on the battle yesterday.
[bell rings]
[KURUMI] My lady, I have
brought the idiots at the gate
to see you.
The creature is here, as well.
[BOTH gasp]
[ERUNA] I'm in the room
where my goddess lives!
This is where she probably...!
Yep, it is where
she probably...!
Those have touched her skin!
They smell like Bulgarian roses!
[ERUNA yells]
--[ERUNA] Why the face?
--[BIMII] Stop being creepy!
Hey! Found her! I win!
What? Well, where is she?
[ERUNA squeals]
[ERUNA]
Seisa, I'm here!
[groans]
[crash]
[ERUNA]
Always the face...
My lady, please,
it's time to wake up.
My lady.
Guess what, Seisa!
I fought the good fight
and won the battle!
The honor of the going-home
club has been secured!
Now, feel free to praise me!
I always do better when
people sing my praises!
Go ahead, Seisa.
I'm humble and ready.
Oh, who's a good girl, Eruna?
You're a good girl!
Oh my yay!
This might be the highlight
of my whole entire living life!
[SEISA]
However...
If we're honest...
I think a large part
of your victory
can be attributed to Himi
mistakenly letting
her guard down.
[gasps]
Himi, if you had gone
for the win from the start
like you should have,
it would have been virtually
impossible for Eruna
to get to your crystals
before you broke hers.
Am I wrong?
[HIMI]
No. I guess not.
[ERUNA]
Yes, you are so wrong!
You guys are looking
at a natural chosen hero.
I mean like "from
the school hero" chosen.
Why else would I have
been able to defeat Himi?
And on the first try, at that!
I know my words
don't make sense,
but just trust me on this!
In fact,
I bet I could put up a decent
fight against you, too, Seisa!
How nice.
You seem to be very confident.
Just remember
this was your idea.
Tomorrow after school works.
You and I are going
to have a practice battle.
If you can somehow manage to
break even one of my crystals,
I will allow you to officially
join the going-home club.
On the other hand,
if you can't do it,
then I will revoke your
provisional membership
and you will go back
to being sans club.
[gasps]
[SEISA]
What do you say?
Uh, no way!
No matter how good she is,
she'll still lose.
That's way too hard, ryui.
Yeah! I'm in! Let's do it!
[ERUNA]
If I break even one,
I'll officially be in
the going-home club!
And then, I'mma live in
this phat mansion with you!
[BIMII, HIMI groaning]
[BIMII] She added her own
condition to the deal, ryui!
[STUDENTS whispering]
It's totally her.
She's that new girl
who owned Himi
from the calligraphy club.
I heard she's
having a practice battle
with Seisa today.
This is everything!
I've always wanted to be famous!
But you need to
get it together, now.
If you can't play it cool,
girl, don't play.
Wait for me!
Once I finish my
battle with Seisa,
I'll pretend to be a patient who
sexually harasses the new RNs
by giving them suggestive orders
while you all join me
in the nurse's office!
I can't even imagine
what's going on in your head.
And I really don't
want to, either.
[ERUNA]
Where are we?
[BIMII]
It's a training room, ryui.
You can watch other people's
battles and learn from them.
Really? That's bad a--
[yells]
[ERUNA]
Asuhi, that was awesome!
Hey, Eruna!
I knew you had to be amazing!
So what was that move,
a one hit KO?
No. I wish, but I'm
not that good yet.
Your cuteness is killing me.
[ASUHI]
Um...
I can't tell if that's
a good thing or not.
Hey!
So what are
you doing right now?
Do you wanna like have
a practice match with me?
[YUTO]
No, he should battle me.
I mean, you haven't
seen these battles yet.
You might want to watch
a legit practice match
before you try to fight in one.
Maybe it's just me,
but don't you think
you'd learn more
if you start out
as a spectator first?
Yeah, that is a good point.
You won't be alone.
The first years from my club
want to watch, too.
I vote the two
of you do this thing!
Um... I don't...
There's no way I could beat you.
I don't stand a chance.
That's okay, though.
This'll be the perfect
opportunity to learn
from someone
who's better than me.
Good call. Let's do this.
All right,
I don't mind being the ref.
Come on, Teach.
It's just a fun and easy battle.
We don't need you to
waste your time with us.
As you wish.
But don't do anything
too dangerous, ryui.
[YUTO]
A'ight!
[ERUNA]
Wow!
I didn't expect so many
people to come watch this!
[BIMII] That's because they
don't normally get to see fights
between club representatives
outside official matches, ryui.
[DEVICE]
Fifteen. Fourteen
Twelve. Eleven. Ten.
Nine. Eight. Seven.
Six. Five. Four.
[countdown continues]
Asuhi. You're mine.
'Kay, here we go!
--Shooting... Star!
--Coup d'Etat Faker.
[ASUHI]
Shooting Star! Shooting Star!
Shooting Star!
[YUTO]
You held your own for a second.
You should be proud.
That's not too terrible
for a first year, I guess.
[ERUNA]
Asuhi!
Yuto, my man,
that was incredible!
Um, thank you
very much, Yuto!
And I'm sorry.
I wish I could have
been a better opponent!
Meh.
[NYAMIRIN]
Hey, nice fight!
[TONKYUN]
I think I learned a lot.
Yeah, don't ever let
yourself get schooled!
What was that about?
Uh...
[BIMII]
Eruna! It's almost time!
You need to get ready
for your match, ryui!
What? No!
Are you serious?
You can do it!
We'll come watch, girl!
[ERUNA] So this is
where we're battling today?
[BIMII]
Unlike last time,
there's nowhere
for you to hide, ryui.
True, but still looks like
there's plenty
of space to run!
[RUMINA] Extra! Extra!
Read all about it!
Extra, extra!
Newspapers for everyone!
Hi, Eruna!
Y'know, I think today is gonna
be a wonderful memory for us.
Maybe we should call it
"Eruna Day" from now on
as our own special holiday.
And in celebration,
I get to go on a date
with you every single year!
Sounds great, huh?
[sighs]
[SHIGURE yells]
I'd rather you not
show love with violence.
Thanks, though!
I saved one for you!
[ERUNA] Why did you
choose a bikini pic?!
[ERUNA growls]
It's great. Yeah!
I love how my little
Eruna is growing up!
[SHIGURE yells]
Gross.
[MINATOGAWA]
Let me have it.
A crane.
[ERUNA]
Well, that's awkward.
[MINATOGAWA]
It's about time to fly away.
Flap, flap, flap, flap.
[ERUNA]
Like real awkward.
[DEVICE] One minute
until the match begins.
Fifty-eight.
Fifty-seven. Fifty-six...
Seisa's here.
[counting continues]
How's it going?
Are you about ready
to start the battle?
Am I ready to officially
join the going-home club?
Heck yeah! Duh!
[SEISA]
That's not what I meant.
I was asking if you
are ready to lose.
Lose and not be in a club again.
Unfortunately, I don't prepare
for negativity and bad stuff.
I know that's a lot of
negative words, but still!
[DEVICE]
Five. Four.
Three. Two. One. Zero.
Begin the match.
Hey! Come get me!
[ERUNA yelling]
[ERUNA]
What the hell?! Is she sleeping?
Oh, yeah,
she's definitely sleeping!
She's even got a snot bubble!
Fine, if that's
how you're gonna be...
I got ya!
[ERUNA yells]
Ow! The crap?
Oh no! My crystal!
[ERUNA]
Here! Tension max...
...Go!
What's going on?
I'm sorry, Eruna.
[yelling]
Go, Killing Art.
Nice try, girl.
But what a shame.
And I'm back to
being a clubless loser.
[BIMII] Eruna!
You need to cheer up, ryui!
[ERUNA]
Ow!
Get off, I don't wanna
catch your ugly. Stop!
Look, I know you're
upset about the battle,
but you can't let the
results get you down, ryui.
That's not like you, anyway.
[ERUNA]
Hmph!
Milk?
[KUZURYU]
Hey.
You hiding out here
so you can have a good cry?
[ERUNA]
Kuzuryu!
[KUZURYU] Look, that would've
happened to any new student
in your position.
[ERUNA]
Is the milk, um, for me?
I feel like you're
trying to cheer me up.
Thank you.
But I, um...
I can't drink milk,
so can I maybe exchange this
for something that better
meets my dietary needs?
[KUZURYU, BIMII]
Huh?
Specifically...
I'm into drinks
that cost the most
because who wants to
swallow something ratchet?
Have you lost your mind?!
Milk is good for you!
It's got nutrients!
No one's too good for that!
You need your nutrients!
[ERUNA]
At least he didn't litter.
[BIMII]
That sounded mean,
but if you think about just
the words, it was kinda nice.
Listen, you need to keep in mind
your power is new
and isn't complete yet.
He's has a good point.
You are inexperienced.
Your ability didn't
activate properly
because you haven't
had much practice, ryui.
I get it.
As long as I practice,
I'll get stronger and stronger
until I'm the school hero again.
Once I've perfected
this rare and awesome power,
I'll be able to take
over the whole country
and then maybe I'll
even rule the world!
I love me!
[KUZURYU] Don't you think you're
getting a little carried away?!
Yeah!
All I need to do to get that
experience is join a club,
and then...
Although, I went to visit
a bunch of different clubs,
and there wasn't really one out
there that seemed to fit me.
Aww!
Dang it! This sucks!
If that's the case,
have you ever thought about
creating your own new club
that does fit you, ryui?
You only need three members,
and it has to be
some sort of social club,
but as long as you
meet those standards,
it doesn't really
matter what kind it is.
for it to be accepted, ryui.
Fascinating idea. My own club.
All right! I'm gonna do it!
[ERUNA]
Did you hear that, Universe?
Eruna's makin' a new club!
Not to burst your bubble,
but it'll be hard finding
members this time of year.
You also just
lost a practice match,
which isn't a
great sell, either, ryui.
Boo, and there's
the point system, too.
No one's gonna
want to join a club
started by a student
as weak as me.
Look, if you want
to change peoples' minds,
start by fighting
in the rookie battle.
[ERUNA]
You think so?
[BIMII]
Ryui.
If you get good results there,
you'll get more attention.
The way I see it,
you could get at least two
club members that way.
[ERUNA]
I like it!
But I refuse to settle
for something uninspired
and just good!
I'm gonna get
first place or nothing!
Hey, thanks a lot, Bimii!
Oh, you too,
well-meaning-if-not
scary-as-hell-paint-covered-guy!
[BIMII]
Ryui! Where are you going?
[KUZURYU]
What are you talking about?
I'm not scary at all!
[water splashing]
[ERUNA]
Hey, Seisa!
I wanted to tell you something!
I've decided to
make my very own club!
I know that I like lost
pretty embarrassingly today.
But when I get to
be the representative
of a club that really gets me,
I wanna fight you again.
I hope that you'll give me
another chance to prove myself!
I promise not to lose next time!
I know it won't be easy.
In fact, I've decided
that the best way
for me to get new club members
is to win the rookie battle!
[ERUNA]
So please, will you watch me?
I swear you won't regret it.
You'll be able
to see moves like this, yah!
and that, ha!
And one of these, kazam!
[ERUNA]
That oughta convince her.
I did it!
[giggles]
My new room is ready!
[ERUNA]
What are you doing, Seisa?
What do you think?
I can't let you
spend the night in this.
However, you're staying in the
hallway in your sleeping bag.
[ERUNA]
Thank you!
Success!
[ERUNA]
Seisa's Killing Art was amazing!
But it was so fast,
I couldn't actually tell
what kind of technique it was!
[SHIGURE] Then let's check
using the video I shot
with my high-speed camera!
[ERUNA]
You have one of those?!
I wanna see! I wanna see!
[SHIGURE]
Okay, here we go! Click!
[ERUNA] Oh, look! It's Seisa
moving in super-slow motion!
No, wait. It's you taking
off your clothes, Shigure!
Grody!
[SHIGURE]
Oh no! My bad.
This was the high-speed
footage of something else
that I, uh,
well.. never mind!
[YUTO]
Never mind indeed.
Ichinomiya, is this
really the best way
to do the next episode previews?
Shouldn't you be taking
them more seriously?
[ERUNA]
Akama, you're too laid-back!
How are we gonna get people
to watch the next episode
if they're falling asleep?
[YUTO]
Hey, I'm perfectly normal.
You're the one who's letting
her ADHD take over.
[ERUNA] Um, FYI,
ADHD is where it's at.
Come on, Akama!
Find your inner awesome!
[SHIGURE]
I'll get into it, Eruna!
I'll get so into it,
I'm gonna lose all control!
[YUTO] Next time,
"Apathetic Coup d'Etat."
I dunno.
Maybe I should try getting
a little more hyperactive.