[STUDENTS chattering]
[ERUNA]
Hey, what's up, cutie pie?
You interested in
joining my new club?
If you join now,
you receive bonus perks
like getting to be all,
"heh-heh-heh-Eruna
Ichinomiya-style,"
if you know what I'm sayin'.
Thanks, but...
[BOTH] ...we think
we're gonna have to pass.
Don't miss out on
the best club ever!
If you join up,
you'll get to leave your honor
and reputation at the door!
I don't understand why
no one wants to sign up!
To be honest, ryui,
your pitch is disturbing.
Please seek help.
Bonjour to all you
beautifully blooming blooms.
Hello, have you come by to play,
my little butterfly friend?
[ERUNA]
Otone!
[gasps, screams]
Eruna the honeybee has arrived
to sting your pure heart!
It's your lucky day.
I have a club recommendation!
You sh-- Ah!
[OTONE]
Away with you!
--[ERUNA gasps]
--There's no way in hell.
The last thing I want
to do is join your club.
In fact, I'd rather
sign up with one where
they sit around popping
bubble tape all day long
than be a member of
anything connected to you.
[BIMII] She really
doesn't like you, ryui.
Well, no surprise here! Dark
Otone is in rare form today!
--[phone rings]
--Huh?
[OTONE gasps]
The annual treasure
hunt is coming soon?
Ah!
--Awesome!
--[OTONE gasps]
[ERUNA] Yay! Eruna the hero
obtained an emerald brush!
obtained mystic lipstick!
If I put this on, I'll go up
by two thousand levels!
--[KURUMI] "Stare"
--[ERUNA gasps]
--[clang]
--[ERUNA] Ah!
I'm down.
[KURUMI]
Seriously?
And I thought mice had been
going through the trash.
Nasty.
[SEISA]
What are you doing, Eruna?
[ERUNA] Oh, just training
for tomorrow's treasure hunt.
Ah yes, yet another
annual orienteering event
for all the new students.
Luckily, I've done a
lot of treasure hunts,
so I ain't scared.
Also, if I can get
some good press,
girls will pillow
fight to join my club!
[GIRLS screaming]
[GIRL 8B] Please, let me
join your club, Miss Eruna!
[GIRL 8C]
Step off! I was here first!
[ERUNA laughing]
Oh yeah, it's a treasure hunt,
and I'm up for treasure!
A ticket for a bath
where we get to
wash each other's
backs would be fun.
Or one where we eat pocky
like Lady and the Tramp.
Or like strip twister, maybe?
It really doesn't matter
as long as I get something
that lets me have
my way with you.
[SEISA]
A back massage.
Huh?
I might consider that ticket.
One for a back massage.
Like for real?
Like for real, for real?
[yells]
You can bet your cute butt
I'm gonna finish first tomorrow
and get some sweet
back massage play!
These miracle hands are
gonna rub, rub and tap, tap
until you're begging them
to massage you in places
that you never imagined
needed to be kneaded!
A back massage.
Oh yes, ma'am! Whatever you say!
[SEISA chuckles]
--[CROWD chattering]
--[fireworks]
Hello again, new students!
And welcome to this
year's treasure hunt!
[STUDENTS cheer]
Come on, there's gotta be
someone here besides Shigure
who can emcee all these things.
Maybe, but there's
not someone here
as popular with both
the boys and the girls.
When the newspaper club ranked
upperclassmen on reliability,
he won first place
by a landslide.
All right, first up,
I'll be announcing our
thrilling pairings of fate!
Our what?
You mean you didn't know?
During the treasure hunt,
we all have to go around
to the checkpoints
in teams of two, girl.
Take a look at your device and
find out who your partner is!
[BOTH gasp]
[chuckle]
[TOISHI]
Huh?
Hi, I'm Haruka Toishi,
from the broadcast club.
I bet we'll be
a wonderful team.
[TONKYUN] Yeah, me, too.
I'm with the drama club.
--My name is--
--[USAMARU screams]
I don't understand! Why?!
[whimpers]
[SAGARA]
Usamaru! This should be fun!
Should it?
I want to say that I'm sorry
for what happened, by the way.
I have this tendency to
turn into a different
and kind of nasty person when
I'm fighting in club battles.
But today, I promise
I'll be nice.
[USAMARU screams]
Yeah, that's the spirit
we need, Usamaru!
'Kay. Now, let's see who
they paired me up with.
[gasps] I'm with Otone!
[ERUNA]
Guess what, Otone!
[OTONE gasps]
What? Not like Fuji cares.
Wow, you and me totally get
to be on a team together!
We're partners now.
[OTONE gasps]
Please refrain from touching.
The rules say you can only shake
Fujishiro's hand for one second
and that was if you
purchased ten of her CDs,
--which you haven't done.
--Sounds like a great deal!
I'll buy a hundred
or even a thousand!
Now that everyone is paired
off, it's time to start!
What does the treasure contain:
dreams, hopes, or a
few worldly goods?
So... Go forth, seek, and
you shall find the answer!
Um... That was weird.
Do you think this
means we should start
or is he just having a seizure?
Yeah, it's hard to tell
what he's trying to say
with all that blood
coming out of his mouth.
[TONKYUN] This is too
painful for me to watch.
Let's go.
[HIMI]
Weeoo weeoo!
First-aid Himi to the rescue!
[ERUNA gasps]
I came immediately
after I found out
somebody's poor little
heart was hurting.
Pain, go away! You see, he's all
better, now. Okay, let's see.
Are there any more patients
out there who need me?
Oh boy...
[ERUNA]
Oh no, my heart. It hurts.
It feels like it's been
snapped in two! Owie!
--Oh, please help me, Himi!
--[HIMI] Sure!
Brought a special
shot just for you!
[ERUNA gasps] A needle
won't heal a wounded heart!
[HIMI] Okay, I can give you
two shots if you want.
[ERUNA]
No needles!
The only thing that can
cure me is a hug from you.
Squeeze me as tight as you
can against that tiny body
and those not so
tiny lady lumps!
Well, I can if you want,
but everyone else
has already started.
[ERUNA gasps]
[ERUNA screams]
Otone, wait for me!
Best of luck, Eruna!
[groans]
I wonder if this
is the right way.
Wanna tell me what you think?
Fujishiro thinks she is not
going to work with you.
Fuji's only doing this hunt
because she has to
for her student record.
Well, I, for one, am happy
we're on the same team.
If anything, we'll at least get
the chance to talk some more.
[OTONE gasps]
Ridiculous! Fujishiro has no
interest in the likes of you.
Then, let me re-introduce
myself to re-interest you!
Born in New York and raised in
London, I'm Eruna Ichinomiya!
In sweetness, I'm as fat
as seven Tsugaru apples.
And right now, I'm
shacking up with
Seisa Mikagura from
the going-home club.
[OTONE]
Seisa?
Oh! You mean the girl who has
the ability to reshape space
whenever she feels like it?
I don't understand your words.
Fujishiro saw Seisa do it once.
Remember the other night
when it was raining
like really, really hard
and then, out of the blue,
the sky completely cleared up?
What? You mean that was Seisa?
How sweet! Oh, of course, she
would go out of her way for us.
[leaves rustle]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[ERUNA]
Eyes!
--Wait!
--[OTONE] No way...
That could be the
monster we need!
I'm gonna go catch it so
we can cook it for our dinner!
Yums!
[MECHA BIMII]
I am not a monster!
--[ERUNA yells]
--[mechanical whirring]
It's Bimii!
And yet, it's not Bimii.
I am Mecha Bimii, mecha.
I was sent here to liven
up the treasure hunt
for the new students
who are participating.
Hey, if you want me to,
I can guide you to
the first checkpoint.
Nice, you're already
more reliable than Bimii!
--Huh?
--[OTONE gasps]
[YUTO]
What's up, Eruna?
I welcome you to the
very first checkpoint.
A mental challenge,
are you kidding?
Not at all, and if you
can't pass it, you're out.
Don't expect Fuji to help
you answer anything.
[YUTO] All right, let the
Super Miracle Man Quiz, begin!
[ERUNA]
Huh?
Here we go!
Question One: when Super
Miracle Man transforms,
what does he always eat?
[ding]
Stick candy!
--[bell rings]
--Stick candy is correct!
Question Two:
What enemy did SMM fight
at Mount Fuji's Sea of Trees?
[ding]
That would be See-Through
the Thirty-Eighth!
--[YUTO] Correct!
--[bell rings]
Charisma Colonizers!
--[YUTO] Correct!
--[bell rings]
Because he showed Masami
the diary Okada traded to him!
--[YUTO] Correct!
--[bell rings]
One hundred percent!
Way to go Ichinomiya!
Heck yeah!
Oh! What a brilliant
mind, mecha!
The second checkpoint
will be a test of strength
against yours truly, roar!
All right! Let's get
this party started!
--[ERUNA] Ah-ha!
--[KUMANO screams]
That's no fair, roar!
[NYAMIRIN]
As you can see, hopefully,
the third checkpoint
is a vision test.
Which way is this?
Heh, jiggle up and down, heh.
--[NYAMIRIN] What about this?
--[ERUNA] Heh, heh, left!
--[NYAMIRIN] And this?
--[ERUNA] Right!
--[NYAMIRIN] This?
--[ERUNA] Up!
--[ERUNA] Down!
--[NYAMIRIN] How about this?
--[ERUNA] Left!
Up! Down! Up! Up!
Right! And oh, left!
Good work!
--That was 100% accurate!
--Nice in-motion vision, mecha!
[STUDENTS chattering]
That looks perfect.
I'm so thirsty!
What the...?
I have hot tea right here
if you would like some.
Get your fresh milk, straight
from the cow this morning.
Hey, lanky girl, you should
be drinkin' more milk.
Am I right?
[STUDENTS scream]
Oh yeah, good luck, Eruna!
The treasure chest at the goal
isn't too much
farther from here.
I believe you can do it!
Once you win this hunt, I think
we should have another party.
Just keep at it no
matter what, roar.
Roger that! I, Eruna Ichinomiya,
will find that treasure!
I won't let you down!
[STUDENTS laugh, cheer]
[OTONE]
Hmph.
Huh?
[ERUNA panting]
Wait for me, Otone!
Will you stop it
with the following?!
Fujishiro has had enough, and is
retiring, effective immediately.
[ERUNA gasps]
[ERUNA]
But Otone!
[OTONE]
Anticomplex, go!
--Snake!
--[hiss]
[ERUNA yells]
Okay, that hurt... Huh?
A snake? What?
Snakes? Why did it
have to be snakes?!
[ERUNA]
Please, wait, Otone!
[OTONE] I'm sick of watching
you and all your friends
act chummy right in my face.
I mean, it's kind of the worst.
[ERUNA gasps]
[whimpers]
My neck! I-Is this a
vampire snake?! Agh!
Gosh, I wonder where
Otone ran off to.
--[MECHA BIMII] Oh!
--Huh?
If we go much farther,
we'll be out of bounds
for the treasure hunt.
Really? Then just
a little bit more.
--Okay?
--Okay.
--[ERUNA yelps]
--[MECHA BIMII] Mecha!
[BOTH scream]
[SHIGURE]
It's almost time
to find out which
pair of new students
will manage to obtain this
year's most wonderful treasure!
What's going on? Looks
like Eruna's not moving.
I wonder what could've happened.
[ERUNA]
Again I say ouch.
[MECHA BIMII]
Are you okay, mecha?
Yeah, I'm fine. Just
a little scraped up.
I actually have a hunch that
you might be a little worse
for wear than me, Mecha Bimii.
I am, mecha...?
Wow.
Yeah, but to be fair,
you look like you were
made kinda shoddily.
[MECHA BIMII]
In truth, you flatter me, mecha.
What do we do now, Mecha Bimii?
[MECHA BIMII] Sadly, I cannot
fly all the way up there, mecha.
Aww.
Doesn't help that
I lost my device, too.
I guess all we can do
is wait around here
until help arrives, huh.
[ERUNA sighs]
Oh no, you seem down, mecha.
I've got an idea!
If I dig right here,
we should come out somewhere
close to Buenos Aires, mecha!
How sweet, but I wish
you were actually helpful.
If only some pretty
princess in shining armor
would show up and pull off
a daring rescue.
--[leaves rustle]
--Huh?
A princess? Could it really be?
Oh, it's Otone!
What are you doing here?
Ow, that smarty smarts!
Fuji likes to go for
walks in this région.
But, more importantly, what
are you doing in such a place?
I wasn't paying attention
and fell down from up there.
Managed to hurt my leg, too.
Am I not the most adorable screw
up you've ever met or what?
--[ERUNA laughs]
--[OTONE gasps]
What are you doing?
[OTONE]
Come with me, all right?
[ERUNA]
Huh?
[ERUNA gasps, laughs]
[ERUNA] Cute! I can't take
how cute this house is.
It's right out of a fairy tale!
--Yeah?
--Great show, but this is where
Fujishiro comes to cry.
Or rather, it's where
Fujishiro comes to
plan out her world conquest.
Aha! I get it, now.
Nobody knew who you were or
noticed you were around until
the rookie battle because you
were out here the whole time.
It's a secret, so please
don't say anything.
If word got out, my school
record might suffer.
I am known as
Mecha Bimii, mecha.
[ERUNA] But even if he was the
real Bimii, it wouldn't matter.
Oh yeah. That's right.
--[kettle whistles]
--[OTONE, ERUNA] Huh?
[OTONE]
Hot!
[ERUNA]
Nice move!
You know how to
make pain precious!
I never dreamed there
would be a pretty girl
in the 21st century who
would burn her hand and
then put said hand to her ear
in an act of coy brilliance!
Um... Did you fall on
your head or something?
[gasps] Maybe letting Eruna
in here was a grosse erreur.
[OTONE]
Anyhow, it is l'heure du thé.
[gasps] You can drink from
the faucet outside, though.
Mecha! This is how you
treat me once you find out
I don't have the power to
affect your record, mecha?
If this place is for one person,
why is there two of stuff?
Two cups and two chairs
and two coasters.
Even the pancakes
come in a pair.
Huh?
That's not true at all!
To hear you talk,
you'd think I'd been sad,
spending l'heure du thé
by myself all the time,
as if I was imagining someone
else was here to talk to!
Hey, so, Otone? [giggles]
I don't mind helping you!
Thank you, but no thank you!
Oh, come on, let
me help you out.
--I can get the fish ready!
--No way!
You can't serve fish
at l'heure du thé!
Fine, then I'll
knead the udon dough.
Look, this is l'heure du thé!
And... And it's not like I
want to have l'heure du thé
with you anyway.
Don't be difficult.
Just play along!
[MECHA BIMII]
Gurgle, gurgle, gurgle.
[ERUNA giggles]
--Better drink up!
--[OTONE gasps]
Huh?
[OTONE]
Try it.
What? You wanna add jam?
Doesn't that seem weird?
Are you confusing it with miso?
No, and Fuji thinks
putting miso in there
would be a lot weirder.
[gasps]
That's so good!
It has a milder taste but still
manages full-bodied flavor.
This is the best miso soup
I've had in my entire life!
It's not miso soup, you twit!
It's Russian tea!
Cool, so like KGB alphabet soup!
No, and you owe Russia
a big apology!
The Russian culture is more than
spies, secret missions, and
obsessive sister countries.
Maybe try learning
a thing or two!
This is really good, yo!
Eruna, you are
just unbelievable.
[ERUNA chuckles]
[gasps]
[nervous laugh]
[ERUNA giggles]
[gasps]
Okay then...
Um... Maybe Fujishiro will
try adding a little bit more.
Great idea! I wanna put
some more in mine, too.
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH laugh]
[ERUNA]
You know what?
I think we should give the
treasure hunt another try.
I'm just saying
I'd really like
to find that treasure
with you, Otone.
That's kind of you to say.
I'm sorry, though.
It's not that simple.
[MECHA BIMII]
Mecha!
[BOTH gasp]
[MECHA BIMII speaking gibberish]
[MECHA BIMII roars]
--[roaring continues]
--[BOTH scream]
[BOTH screaming]
[BOTH scream]
[MECHA BIMII roaring]
[screaming]
[BOTH panting]
--[MECHA BIMII] Mecha!
--[BOTH gasp]
[SEISA panting]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[MECHA BIMII roaring]
Eruna!
Now, Killing Art, go!
[OTONE]
Anticomplex, go!
Bridge!
[SEISA gasps]
--[gasps]
--C'mon, let's get across!
[ERUNA yelps]
--[MECHA BIMII roaring]
--[BOTH panting]
[MECHA BIMII roars]
[BOTH gasp]
[ERUNA grunts]
Tension max...
...go!
[MECHA BIMII roars]
Nice work, lady!
[OTONE giggles]
Same to you!
[ERUNA]
Let's go, Otone!
--[OTONE] Sure!
--[footsteps]
--[STUDENTS chattering]
Oh! Look, you guys.
Eruna's finally made it back!
And the final pair has,
at last, made their return.
Welcome back, my Eruna!
Welcome back.
[TONKYUN]
Yeah, good to see ya.
[BIMII]
It took you long enough, ryui.
[ERUNA giggles]
It's real Bimii!
Real hugs, real crud,
and real stinky!
You're awful insulting
for someone who seems
happy to see me, ryui!
--[BIMII yells]
--[ERUNA] Ow!
Okay, so which pair
won the treasure hunt?
[TONKYUN] A team you
would never suspect.
[ERUNA]
Usamaru?!
Is everyone ready to see what
the treasure chest contains?
It's a ticket good for
a manga based on the
two of you, drawn by me!
I'd like an eloquent story
about passionate youth.
I-It'll just turn out to
be psychological horror!
[screams]
[All laugh]
[YUTO]
You did well too, Otone.
[OTONE gasps]
Yeah, I wouldn't have been able
to make it back without Otone!
[gasps]
I've heard a lot about
you from the flowers.
Thank you for always taking
special care of them.
Oh, so you like flowers?
Uh... No...
Fuji, um... I...
That is, it's time for
Fujishiro to go hang out
with the hooligans in town
and cause big trouble
for all the innocent folk.
[whimpers]
[OTONE sobbing]
I don't understand why
I have such a hard time
opening up to other people.
[ERUNA]
Otone!
[OTONE]
What?
Oh, wonderful. It's you again?
[ERUNA] I still haven't gotten
a chance to thank you properly.
Fuji can do without your thanks.
I knew you'd say that,
but thank you anyway.
I had a blast doing the
treasure hunt with you.
Yeah, not that we actually
managed to hunt down
any treasure, though.
--I sure did.
--Huh?
I found a great treasure.
Lucky me, huh?
Otone, whaddaya say
you and I form a new club?
[ERUNA] Honestly, I'm not even
sure about the concept, yet.
But you gotta admit the
two of us could put together
a pretty spectacular
club, right?
Since you insist, yes.
Let's face it, there's really
no reason for me not to join.
[ERUNA giggles]
[ERUNA]
We're finally friends, Otone!
Ooh, lightbulb.
Let's form a new club!
[OTONE] Um, how 'bout
you not flatter yourself
just because you drank
Russian tea with Fujishiro?
[ERUNA laughs]
There she is, Dark Otone!
I love it when you go Dark.
Okay, now try
being... Red Otone!
[OTONE]
There is no such... Fujishiro!
[ERUNA]
Nice! Very hot-blooded!
Next, I'm thinking
you should do Yellow.
[OTONE]
Well, I do like curry...
[ERUNA]
You're really playing along?
Ooh! Then, it's time
for the big one: Pink!
[OTONE] Could you maybe
not get carried away?
[ERUNA]
And we're back to Black.
[MECHA BIMII] Enough of
the idle chatter, you two.
Just do the preview
already, mecha.
[ERUNA]
Mecha Bimii, you survived!
[MECHA BIMII]
Next time, "Derailed Scandal."
Bimii's terrible, sad secret
finally comes to light, mecha.