[OTONE] Even now you refuse
use your ability on Fuji?
If you'd rather me win than
use Killing Art, then so be it.
But when you lose, no excuses.
[ERUNA]
Otone, don't!
[OTONE gasps]
[ERUNA panting]
[OTONE growls]
What's going on?
One of you tell me!
[ERUNA]
Otone, say something!
Um, I--
Fuji is sorry, but she was
just thinking of Eruna.
She just wanted you to be happy!
Come on, don't run away!
I'm not mad. I'm just confused.
Why would you guys fight?
[ERUNA gasps]
[ERUNA]
Seisa! Wait a second!
[ERUNA gasps]
[SEISA]
What is it?
Say what you want to say.
Get it over with.
[ERUNA]
It's just that...
You did make a club
with that girl, right?
Then, you need to stop
worrying about me
and focus on her instead.
Congrats.
Is that good enough?
Of course it is.
But I don't understand.
I said stop
worrying about me!
[gasps]
[SEISA]
Otherwise...
...you'll be next.
Do you want scars like these?
[SEISA]
Let's go.
--[music playing]
--[chattering]
[YUTO] Looks like
something's got you down.
[ERUNA gasps]
Oh, hey, you guys.
And uh, I'm not down,
I'm just lost in my awesome
daydreams per usual.
I was winning the
midterm battles,
and then totally
getting a harem! [laughs]
Hey, where did
your posse go?
We're not used to
seeing you by yourself.
Yeah, isn't Mr. Bimii
always with you?
[ERUNA]
Wait, now that you mention it.
Bimii?
No wonder my
shoulder felt light!
So is he your guardian angel
or your guardian devil?
[BOTH laugh]
I guess we're not the only ones
getting ready for
the midterm battles.
All the teachers
have to prepare, too.
That's true.
[TONKYUN] Has the I'll
Figure It Out Later Club
chosen a representative, yet?
[ERUNA]
No... Not exactly.
Well, let's see.
It'd probably make the most
sense to have Otone do it
since she won the rookie battle.
[USAMARU] Yeah, but you're
not taking into account
how much better
Eruna's gotten lately.
I mean, that
special attack alone
could take out a ton of people.
It's bad ass!
[footsteps]
Hey, Eruna.
Don't be so blue, sunshine!
Cheer up! It's a beautiful day!
Huh?
Fujishiro is always cheerful.
In fact, she is always
cent per cent cheerful.
Especially today, she's
like three times that,
so three hundred
percent cheerful.
Fuji has so much cheer that
it's becoming a problem.
Well, that's fantastic to hear!
So anyway, it's almost time
for the midterm battles;
which means the I'll Figure It
Out Later Club's first match!
And we still have to decide
who's gonna be our
representative.
[OTONE] Fujishiro doesn't
think she wants that position.
You should represent us.
She thinks that would
be better for the club.
I mean, you did form it so you'd
be able to face Seisa again,
but you can't do that
if you're not the rep.
[ERUNA]
Otone...
And I'm sorry about, yesterday.
Fujishiro didn't need to
get into your business.
She was wrong and acted
like a stupid jerk.
Whatever, so over it, girl.
Besides, how can
I be mad at you?
You did it for me!
[OTONE] Yeah, um, that
might have been a lie.
Fuji said she did it for you,
but it might have really been
for herself because Fuji...
She might have been a
little jealous of Seisa.
If you want to know the truth.
Fujishiro wanted to make
sure you would keep smiling.
I admire you the most
whenever you're happy.
And that's why you
should be our club rep!
Fight Seisa like you've wanted,
and make Fujishiro happy
because you're happy!
That was wicked profound.
[OTONE gasps]
Um, oopsie, Fuji might
have just said too much.
On that note, she'll
be on her way now.
She's busy.
Those thugs won't
beat up themselves!
[ERUNA]
Hold on!
You're not allowed to go.
[OTONE gasps]
Okay, fine. I'll be
the representative.
But you're still a member of the
I'll Figure It Out Later Club,
so you can't leave!
I need you, silly.
Help me train!
[OTONE gasps]
[giggles]
Well, I guess I don't
have much of a choice.
Be warned, though.
Fuji's not gonna hold back,
so you better be ready!
[ERUNA giggles]
Anticomplex, go!
Snake attack!
Toy Bayonet, go!
[ERUNA whistles]
[OTONE]
Nice work.
But if you let yourself get
satisfied with this performance,
there's no way you're
ever gonna beat Seisa.
For real?
[OTONE]
For real.
When Fuji fought Seisa,
the only reason she
won was because
Seisa wouldn't
use Killing Art.
If Seisa had used her ability,
Fujishiro would have
most likely lost.
That's so weird.
Why do you figure Seisa
decided to hold back with you?
[HIMI]
Hey, there you are!
Guess what, Eruna!
The tournament brackets have
finally been announced!
I have a feeling this
year's going to be
the wildest year ever!
[chattering]
Looks like if we both
advance like we should,
we'll get our chance, and fight
each other in the third round.
[SHIGURE gasps, chuckles]
[ERUNA] Look for Seisa's
going home club!
[OTONE] Fuji doesn't see
Seisa's club anywhere.
If you're looking for
the going home club,
they withdrew again this term.
[ERUNA, OTONE gasp]
[KATAI]
Talk about a relief.
Can you imagine if
we had to face Seisa?
Even you would've
had a difficult time
beating her, huh, Himi?
No, I would not have.
I'm insanely strong!
Let's say Seisa's as strong as
like, a hundred thousand
African elephants.
Well, I'm that strong,
just more Asian style
with a touch of dwarfism.
[KATAI]
Wow.
[SEISA]
Killing Art, go.
[OTONE gasps, grunts]
[OTONE grunts]
[OTONE gasps]
[SEISA gasps]
[grunts]
[SEISA groans]
[OTONE]
Sword.
[KURUMI]
I wonder, my lady...
Why it is you didn't use Killing
Art when you faced that girl?
[gasps]
[doorbell rings]
[ERUNA]
Seisa please let me in!
I need to talk to you!
--Please! Seisa! Hello!
--Could you please her away?
[ERUNA]
Come on, can't we just talk?
Open the gate! Please,
let me come inside!
Seisa, please!
Oh!
Kurumi, Seisa's home, isn't she?
Just give me one sec!
I really need to talk to her!
My lady said she does not
wish to see you right now,
so please go away.
Can't you do something?
--[KURUMI] No, actually I can't.
--[ERUNA] C'mon, just one look!
[KURUMI]
C'mon, just go home.
That girl is
stubborn to a fault.
She'd probably feel better
if she just fought her here.
Get it over with already.
Of course, all things equal,
I'm hardly one to talk.
[ERUNA]
I'll give you these!
I don't want them.
[ERUNA]
What about this?
Will you just leave already?
[ERUNA] Hold on, I've
got the perfect thing!
I've been saving her.
She's soaked with sweat and
tears-- my sleeping bag!
[KURUMI]
Go away.
[ERUNA screams]
[cheering]
[ERUNA] Even if I can't
fight against Seisa.
I still need to focus on
winning so we can advance.
If I do that,
Seisa's bound to finally
show me some support!
[DEVICE] Midterm battles,
B-block, first round.
I'll Figure It out Later
Club rep, Eruna Ichinomiya
versus broadcast club
rep, Haruka Toishi.
Begin the match.
[ERUNA growls]
Go!
[OTONE]
Congratulations!
Here's to winning round one,
and good luck on all the rest!
[ERUNA sighs]
Well, thank you!
But I only won because
you helped me train!
You can't fool me, Light Otone.
I know you're the
one being so nice.
I wonder if Dark Otone
might want to come play!
You're nuts.
At the very least, you must've
been hit in the head pretty hard
to think getting past
round one matters.
You don't deserve
applaudissements.
For real, you don't even deserve
the C in congratulations.
Yeah, that's perfect!
That's exactly what
I needed to hear!
[OTONE]
Eruna!
For the last time, stop
it with the affection!
[OTONE]
Anyway, it's almost time for
Shigure and Kuzuryu's
match to start.
[ERUNA]
Shigure and Enoyan?!
Let's roll, Dark Otone!
--Woosh!
--[OTONE] Hey!
How many times does
Fujishiro have to tell you
she is pure light, so knock
off that dark business!
[footsteps]
[KURUMI] You're not going
to watch the matches, then?
I expected you to at least
watch the idiot fights.
--Don't you want to know?
--[SEISA] No, I do not.
[KURUMI gasps]
[KURUMI]
Oh, my lady. Is it happening?
[BOTH panting]
[gasps]
Huh?
You got any idea
what's going on?
[BOTH gasp]
[ERUNA]
Huh?
What is this?
Seisa?!
[gasps]
[OTONE]
No way whatever that was,
was just an optical illusion.
[ERUNA]
Yeah.
I wonder if this is what
Usamaru saw the other day.
[ASUHI]
Eruna isn't here yet.
[HIMI]
I wonder what she's doing?
This is the first time
Shigure and Kuzuryu have
ever fought each other.
Gah!
Seriously? How have they managed
to not have to battle until now?
I have no idea.
There have been a ton
of official matches,
and they're both
ridiculously strong.
You would think they
would have, but nope.
This fight is
number one for them.
[MINATOGAWA]
I know why.
Kuzuryu always gave up early.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Yep, it's weird.
In the matches right
before the ones
where he'd have to face Shigure,
he always managed to lose.
[OTONE]
Yeah, this isn't creepy at all.
Uh-oh, don't tell me
you're a big scaredy-cat?
No way. Are you
kidding Fuji, right now?
Because, like, she's
not afraid of anything.
Except for like...
...people who can't
tolerate gluten.
[ERUNA]
The photography club?
[OTONE]
That's kinda strange.
You'd think a photography
club would be a big deal,
but I've never seen it before.
I didn't notice it in the
tournoi brackets, either.
[OTONE]
Wait! You're going in?
Fujishiro isn't mentally
prepared to do that yet!
Eruna!
[OTONE gasps]
[whimpers]
There's nothing to be scared
of. It's just an old room.
Huh?
[ERUNA]
Hm?
[grunts]
These are all of Seisa.
[ERUNA] Look at how many
expressions she's making.
I've never seen her like that.
[ERUNA]
What a beautiful sunset.
Almost like a picture
of a beautiful sunset.
[ERUNA gasps]
[thud]
--[slurping]
--[ERUNA gasps]
--[ERUNA] Bimii?!
--[BIMII gasps]
[OTONE panting]
--Oh no! Oh no!
--[HIMI] Good grief, Otone,
what took you so long?
And where's Eruna?
[OTONE]
Eruna's gone.
She disappeared into the
photography club room.
The door to the room
disappeared, too!
[KUZURYU] Looks like something
happened to Eruna.
Then let's get this over with,
and the sooner the better,
if you ask me.
[cheering]
[DEVICE] Midterm battles,
A-block, third round.
Kyoma Kuzuryu versus
Shigure Ninomiya.
[cheering]
[BIMII] We're currently
in a different dimension
than the Mikagura Academy
you're used to, ryui.
[ERUNA] I figured that's
what was going on.
Why else would the sun never set
no matter how much
time has passed?
[BIMII] Did you know this
clubroom was actually
part of the school at one time?
Seisa used her Killing Art
to seal it away into a
different dimension.
Basically, she
transformed the room
into a space that no longer
exists in reality, ryui.
Why would she do
something like that?
Because she was hurt.
Seisa cared a lot about
someone in the photography club,
and that someone
betrayed her, ryui.
I'm guessing the
betrayer took these?
Yep. They became close
pretty quickly.
It happened during
Seisa's first year.
Everything changed for her the
day before the midterm battles.
[BIMII] Back then, Seisa
was in the art club.
The other girl was
in photography.
Seisa became a model for
her upperclassman friend,
and the two girls
became very close, ryui.
Seisa respected her,
and in return, she loved
Seisa like a little sister.
But when it came
to battle ability,
Seisa was the overwhelmingly
stronger one.
And then, in the midterm
battles that year,
the two girls were scheduled
to face each other in
the first round, ryui.
And a tough one at that,
considering we're
fighting each other.
You realize I won't hold back?
You better not.
Plus, fair fights
are more fun anyway.
I couldn't be more excited.
[BIMII]
Seisa couldn't have cared less
about winning or
losing the battle.
She was just happy
to get the chance
to face someone
she looked up to.
Sounds a lot like
you, doesn't it?
[BIMII] Unfortunately, the other
girl saw things differently.
With the school's point
system at the time,
if you won, you'd get a lot
of points and attention.
But more importantly,
upperclassmen were not
supposed to lose to freshmen.
And she didn't really like the
idea of being crushed by Siesa.
So....
[SENPAI] Hey, Seisa,
I have a favor to ask.
[SEISA gasps]
[SENPAI]
Do you think...
Do you think you could
throw tomorrow's match?
[SEISA gasps]
[BIMII]
Seemed simple enough.
However, if Seisa
agreed, she knew
their entire relationship
would be meaningless.
[BIMII]
Which is why Seisa refused
to throw the match
for her, and then...
[explosion]
[BIMII]
They had an unauthorized battle
the day before
the official match.
Of course, it was
against the rules, ryui.
The upperclassman may not
have meant for it to happen,
but in the end...
[BIMII] Seisa was
seriously injured, ryui.
Her friend dropped out of
school and left the area.
The photography club
was disbanded.
[BIMII] And in order to erase
her memories with the girl,
Seisa used Killing Art
to seal off the ruined school
building and this clubroom.
That's when she created
the going home club,
and shut herself up
in her mansion, ryui.
[ERUNA]
Poor Seisa...
But I don't get it.
Why now?
Why is it showing back up
and disappearing like this?
Most likely because
Seisa's power has
started growing weaker, ryui.
--[ERUNA gasps]
--The bottom line?
The space is becoming unstable.
Yeah, that makes perfect sense.
It wasn't that Seisa
wouldn't use Killing Art
during her fight with Otone,
she couldn't use it!
[SEISA gasps]
[screams] No!
[KURUMI] Even without using
a power like Killing Art,
you still can only throw
things away or burn them.
[KURUMI]
Unless...
you're actually afraid to
get rid of them for good.
[KURUMI] Things may
disappear from this world,
but they remain in
our hearts and minds.
[KURUMI]
That's what memories are,
and they don't always have to be
bad, you know that, don't you?
[banging]
So, you're finally coming
at me like you mean it.
I've been waiting a
long time for this.
[KUZURYU chuckles]
Why do you always try so hard
to sound like an honor student?
Are you wanting
to point out that
the great heroes
of the school can
care about us lowly
delinquents or something?
[SHIGURE]
I'm not an honor student,
and I'm not a hero, either!
The only thing I'm
trying to point out
is that it's about damn
time you and I fought!
It's also about time
you let the past go!
[SHIGURE yells]
[KUZURYU grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[SHIGURE] Back in the day,
you were always better than me.
Did you know I looked up to you?
[KUZURYU]
Great.
I'll make you look
up to me again!
Get ready for some neck pain!
My favorite manga character
fought with his rival
to become as strong as possible,
so no one could ever beat him.
Does that sound familiar
to you, too, rival?
This isn't a manga,
so don't fool yourself
into thinking things are
going to go that smooth!
[SHIGURE]
Hero Time, go!
[KUZURYU]
Palette Barrett, go!
[yells]
[gasps]
[KUZURYU]
Over here, Shigure.
[SHIGURE gasps]
[KUZURYU]
Part one, finished.
[KUZURYU yells]
[cheering]
[DEVICE]
End of the match.
[KUZURYU] It's been a while
since I've had this much fun.
My favorite manga character
shook his opponent's hand
after a particularly epic fight,
and they wound up
becoming friends.
So what do you say?
Although, I guess you and I
have been friends for
a while, haven't we?
[KUZURYU chuckles]
[chuckles]
I already told you,
this isn't a manga, man.
Wait, we gotta go!
What about Eruna?
We don't have
time for this crap!
Uh--
[SHIGURE]
Eruna, my love!
I'm coming to save you!!
[chuckles]
Huh?
Shoot, what now?!
[BIMII] I think this
has to do with Seisa.
She's finally losing her power!
[BOTH scream]
[SHIGURE] Kyoma, you finally
did it. I knew you could.
[KUZURYU] We don't have time
for that... Eruna's in trouble!
[ERUNA]
Actually, I'm totally fine.
[KURZURYU] Not much of a preview
if you tell them how it ends!
You gotta string 'em
along, even it is a lie!
[SHIGURE] Next time, a
trial awaits Eruna and me!
Will we be able to overcome
the numerous difficulties
and have the wedding
of our dreams!
[KUZURYU]
Wrong lie, man!
[ERUNA] Next time,
me and Seisa, and Himi,
and Otone, Katai, Rumina, and
every cute girl in the world
have a wrestling match
and it's in the mud--
[KUZURYU]
Not that lie, either!
[ERUNA]
Fine! Gah!
Next time, Enoyan and Minatogawa
spend a lovely spring day
on the north face of the Eiger,
studying cave cricket ecology.
[KUZURYU] Where are you even
getting this crap from?!
[SHIGURE]
You'll just have to watch,
and see what happens
for yourself!
[KUZURYU] No, you don't get
to be clever about it, now!
[ERUNA] Next time, the big
finale! "Infinite Grand Finale"!
[SHIGURE]
It's the last episode,
but I have a feeling
it's a start!
[ERUNA]
Wait...
Do you mean it like, "Our
fight has only just begun"?!
Because that would really
suck for a last preview.