[SEISA]
I have a question, Eruna.
Care to join me at my mansion?
What? For real?
Yes, for real.
I know you're
just a trial member,
but you're still a part
of the going-home club, right?
Now come home with me,
and let's live together, okay?
Oh, Seisa, yes!
[ERUNA]
Uh... Yuriko?!
[ERUNA yells]
[sighs, groans]
[ERUNA] I thought joining
a club for a trial period
would change something.
[BIMII] Some things
have changed, ryui.
You have a whole minute of
shower time, which is nice.
And look in front of you.
I see an extra side dish!
Right.
Yeah, I can work with this
sticky, gooey bean situation.
I'll just pretend it's a fancy
breakfast in a cushy castle!
Look, a full-course French meal!
I'll start with foie gras
with caviar on top!
Oh. Yeah, yum.
Seems kinda heavy
for breakfast to me, ryui.
[stomach growling]
What was I thinking?
I can't fill my stomach
with my imagination.
Now then.
I'm sure those of you who
came from our middle school
are already well aware of this,
but please understand
that I need to explain
how club battles work
for our new students.
Okay.
Why don't we start with
the idiot over there?
I mean, uh...
Eruna Ichinomiya,
come to the front.
Oh! Yes, ma'am!
[stomach growling]
[ERUNA]
Pink bananas!
[KURUMI]
No, they're not fruit.
These are crystals used
in the club battles.
The competitor that successfully
breaks all three crystals
floating around
their opponent first
within the allotted time
is the winner.
[KURUMI]
As you see...
You can crush them
with your hands like so.
--Now.
--[ERUNA yells]
Biting them is an option,
but if you'd rather not
experience that unpleasantness,
you can release
your own individual powers
and hit them with
your special attacks.
[ERUNA]
Huh? Who what?
[bell ringing]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I am finally here, though!
Now, for the entrance
you've been longing for!
I worked on this for you ladies.
[GIRL 2A] It's Shigure Ninomiya
from the manga club!
[GIRL 2B] Eruna,
have you met this guy yet?
Yeah, he's a pervert
with a major cuz-com.
Cuz-com?
Cousin complex, like, bad.
No shame, cuz.
This complex guy's about
to drop a special attack!
I call it Hero Time!
Huh...? What? Uh...
[SHIGURE]
What am I gonna do?!
I forgot my pen and
left it back in my room!
[screams]
[BIMII] If you want
to release your powers,
you're gonna have
to get yourself
some sort of a
summoning object, ryui.
In the case of
your twisted cousin,
he likes to use
a pen since he's
in the manga
research club, ryui.
I don't really get that.
But are you telling me
I have special powers?
Oh gosh, no.
Unfortunately, power like his
does not live inside you
as of yet.
However, since you
were accepted here,
you're definitely going to.
I got it!
What I should do is
get Seisa to teach me
everything she
knows about this stuff!
Genius!
It'll be after school!
A club activity!
I just know she'll help!
--Seisa, I need you!
--[BIMII] Hey, not so fast!
[doorbell rings]
I'm here to do
club activities, Seisa!
Question, Eruna.
Do you even know what
the going-home club does?
[ERUNA] Nope!
That's why I came over!
Take me by the hand and show me!
In fact, show me all
kinds of things if you want!
[SEISA]
All right.
Lesson one. Turn around.
Okay!
[SEISA] Next, put your
right foot in front.
[ERUNA]
Okay!
[SEISA] Then, put your
left foot in front.
[ERUNA]
Okay!
[SEISA] Repeat that three
hundred and fifty times,
give or take a hundred.
[ERUNA]
Okay! Hey! Wait a minute!
The going-home club's
club activity
is going home, ryui.
[SEISA]
See you later.
I don't wanna go!
[ERUNA]
So, Himi,
all I want is for you to take me
by the hand and show me!
[HIMI] I need more details
than what you're throwing at me,
'cause it seems like you want me
to be Seisa's replacement.
No, that's not how it is.
Think more like
being in the mood
to have dessert
for breakfast.
Dessert?!
Cool, I'm down
for any kind of sundae
as long as there's
a strawberry on top!
That's not what
I meant, either.
I know! Like how the
kind of person you'd marry
is different than the
kind of person you'd date.
Still not
making any sense, ryui.
That's weird.
Why date someone if you don't
like 'em enough to get married?
Either way,
what's important to me
is that I'm with the
kind of person who also saves
the strawberry
on sundaes for last.
[ERUNA]
Hey, I do that!
In that case, Eruna,
let's save our special attacks
for a special day and
keep them a secret until then.
What kind of special day?
[BOTH laughing]
Oh jeez, where did
your mind just go, ryui?
[HIMI]
Seriously though, Eruna,
if you want to learn
about the club battles
and special attacks,
you should go visit the
other clubs and ask them.
[BIMII] The art club shows up
regularly in the top ten, ryui.
Wasn't that scary guy
from this club?
I don't know if
I wanna talk to him.
[BIMII]
Don't worry, ryui.
Kuzuryu might look
hardcore on the outside,
but under that tough exterior
is a pretty good guy.
[ERUNA]
Attention, please!
It's Eruna Ichinomiya!
The last great
new student has arrived!
[KUZURYU]
What?
[ERUNA]
Uh, hey, uh...
What's up?
Okay, he's a good guy.
He's just quiet, ryui.
Not exactly into
the "talking" thing.
[ERUNA]
Well that's no help.
Attention please!
It's Eruna Ichinomiya!
The last great
new student has arrived!
[ERUNA]
Holy crap!
What is this?
The Mikagura school
of making flowers look
stupid awesome together?
[MINATOGAWA] No, it's
the Minatogawa school.
Everything you see
was arranged by me.
Meet Sadamatsu Minatogawa.
He is the president of the
flower arrangement club.
Your flowers kick ass!
[BIMII]
The flower arrangement club
is also a regular
in the top ten,
but they have fewer and
fewer members each year.
That's why this is
now basically a clubroom
just for Minatogawa, ryui.
His power is called
Selfish Flower, ryui.
It allows him to
manipulate plant life.
[MINATOGAWA]
Eruna, do you like flowers?
If they're yummy!
You can't eat flowers, ryui.
Why?
The yellow ones
they always give you
when you order sashimi
are delicious.
You can't eat those, ryui!
To be honest,
I'd rather you not eat
any flowers at all.
They're alive. See?
Right?
[ERUNA] That oughta cover
at least one meal for today!
[BIMII] Eruna, you forgot what
you were trying to do, ryui.
[ERUNA]
That's right!
Attention please!
It's Eruna Ichinomiya!
The last great
new student has arrived!
[BIMII] The drama club is
one of the most popular clubs
in the school.
It ranks high in both
members and points, ryui.
[ERUNA]
No way I'll lose in acting.
You may not realize
you've been socializing
with an actress extraordinaire,
but this particular girl
has been cast in the
pivotal role of "Tree"
every year since kindergarten.
[GIRL]
Oh, yay!
It's the most
adorable teacher ever!
[BIMII] No, let go,
I can't breathe, ryui!
Her chest is huge!
Hey, what'd you say?
You know, something about
being the last student?
[ERUNA] No, I said
the last great student!
[NYAMIRIN] Grate?
Like grating on our nerves?
[ERUNA]
Great like cool!
[NYAMIRIN] You're cold.
That explains the layers!
Okay, I think I'm starting
to get offended here,
unless you're special needs
or something, maybe?
[BOY] What's going on?
It's so loud.
[ERUNA]
Hey!
I saw that guy at the new
student welcoming party thing.
I'm Yuto Akama,
the drama club rep.
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you, too!
[BIMII] Eruna is trying
to find out more
about different special
attacks for the club battles
by going around to everyone
and asking what they do, ryui.
[YUTO]
Oh? Sounds like a good plan.
Have you been to the
astronomy club already?
No, not yet, ryui.
Why, is the
astronomy club awesome?
No.
Well, not when
compared to drama.
[YUTO]
This is my special attack.
Coup d'Etat Faker!
I play tricks on your eyes.
Nice, right?
[KUZURYU] Even though
you're in the going-home club,
you haven't gone home yet?
[SEISA] No. I just
got to school, so...
Eruna Ichinomiya.
A funny girl.
Are you as stressed
about her as it seems you are?
[ERUNA]
Everyone's incredible.
I wish I knew what to do
to be able to use some sort
of sweet power like them.
[BIMII]
There's no use rushing, ryui.
It just takes time.
As long as you train
your mind and your body,
it'll come to you eventually.
[ERUNA] Wow! I've never
seen so many stars!
[BIMII] Are you listening
to anything I say, ryui?
[ASUHI]
Oh, hey!
You're Eruna Ichinomiya,
aren't you?
When Seisa invited
you to join her club,
were you blown away?
[BIMII] Asuhi's here right now
because the astronomy club
is scheduled for
activities tonight, ryui.
[ERUNA]
Astronomy?
Um, isn't that the one Akama
said wasn't all that good?
Shut it!
The astronomy club
is all that good.
It's a top ranking club, ryui!
That's true.
[BIMII] Why aren't the other
astronomy members here?
Oh, I'm just early,
that's all.
This is my first
astronomical observation
since I started
high school, so uh...
I'm... I'm excited.
I thought more
people would come earlier,
but it looks like
I'm the only one.
Confusing!
Is this really a boy?
I'm freaking out.
He's like the epitome of
everything I love in a girl!
[BIMII]
Asuhi may be a new student,
but he's already the
astronomy club rep, ryui.
He's incredibly gifted
for such a young kiddo.
Thank you!
But I still have
so much more to learn!
[ERUNA] Hey, can I see
what that's all about?
[ASUHI]
Oh, sure.
Gimme a minute, first, though.
I'll adjust it some so
it'll be easier for you.
What a sweetie!
[ASUHI]
'Kay, go for it!
Thanks, man!
[ERUNA laughing]
[ASUHI]
Isn't it lovely?
Stars show us
different expressions
depending upon the time of day.
I never get bored, even if
I look at them all the time.
How sweet!
I feel like I could
stare up there forever.
Wait! No, don't push that.
[ERUNA]
This?
[screams]
Oh, shoot.
I'm so sorry, Eruna!
That power is
called My Shooting Star.
The telescope fills up
with energy from the stars
to fire with.
But it's kind of a big flaw.
Anyone who manages to hit
the button can fire it
as long as the bullets
have been loaded.
That is so cool!
How did you get your power,
and how did you learn to use it?
[ASUHI]
Oh. I guess I...
I don't really know.
I like stars, so I grew up
always looking at them.
In fact, I've been
stargazing way earlier
than elementary school.
Before I knew it,
I had this neat power.
[ERUNA] All righty, the keyword
is "before I knew it"
and that's true, "good things
come to those who wait."
[BIMII] Isn't that
more of a key "cliché"?
[ERUNA]
Don't you judge me!
[BIMII] Instead of
getting angry, missy,
you might want to focus on
getting rid of
that sleeping bag, ryui.
[ERUNA]
Oh, hey--
Yeah, what?
[ERUNA] It seems like Seisa
probably doesn't
want me to know,
but, uh, what kind of power
is that girl working with?
Seisa's power is
called Killing Art, ryui.
It's the only power
in the entire school
that can be activated
without an item, ryui.
Yeah, she's kind of
a big deal, as they say.
And the best part about it...
Oh, my goddess!
Screw that
"before I knew it" crap!
I'm going to do
an intensive training
and learn a super sick
attack just like her!
You can practice your
special attack on me, Eruna!
I'll just wait right here.
Oh, dreams do come true.
Imagine me, her first partner.
He is so gross.
But, instead of puking on him,
I just won't hold back.
What's your item, ryui?
Since I'm in
the going-home club,
I thought I'd use this.
Give it a shot.
Eruna! Come to me!
School Bag... Crash!
Unless I'm wrong,
you're just hitting him
with your bag, ryui.
Fine, then I'll use this!
Eruna, come to--
[ERUNA]
Go, Sleeping Beauty!
[BIMII]
Still just hitting him, ryui.
[ERUNA]
Okay, maybe this?
[SHIGURE]
Eruna! Come to me!
Things we don't say out loud!
Here goes!
[yelling]
[ERUNA]
Bimii!
Yes! I did it!
We're spending the night
in the nurse's office! Yay!
[BIMII]
Focus, ryui!
[ERUNA]
In my fantasies,
I can activate techniques
like "this," and "that,"
and "What? Get out!"
But in the lame real world,
things are way harder and suck.
[ERUNA]
Seisa, hey!
I suppose it's
impossible for you after all.
What? No, that's not true!
So you say.
But I don't understand
how you're going to fight.
Don't you worry!
I'll prove that I can do it!
Trust me!
I want to win so I can
become an official part
of the going-home
club with you, Seisa!
[SEISA] The going-home club
just goes home.
It doesn't matter
if I allow you to join or not.
We go home. That's it.
There's nothing
for us to do together.
[ERUNA]
We can go home together!
[SEISA] I live in a mansion
and have a feather bed.
You live in an open room
and have a sleeping bag.
Your solution is not an option.
[ERUNA]
Then what if we go halfway?
We can stop
somewhere on the road,
or go the long route?
Ooh, what if we stop
at an ice cream shop
and stuff our faces
till we get brainfreeze?
We'll get stomachaches and have
to go to the nurse's office.
Come on, how much fun
does that sound, right?
We can do anything!
It'll be on the way home!
[ERUNA] The only reason I
wanted to come to this academy
was because I saw you
in that pamphlet,
which was love
at first sight for me.
I mean, have you seen you?
Who wouldn't want
to go to the same school
with someone that gorgeous?
And then you invited me
to join the going-home club
out of nowhere.
It made me so happy!
Your point?
My point?
My point is
I'm gonna rock this!
[BIMII] We will begin
the match, now, ryui!
I didn't know
I was gonna fight Himi.
[HIMI]
Surprise!
You should be proud of yourself
for already being the going-home
club representative, Eruna.
That's really such a
huge honor for you!
And after I beat you
like I'm about to do,
you can be even more proud!
Yeah, says the
loser from Loserville.
[BIMII] The time limit
is one hour, ryui.
Whoever breaks all three of
their opponent's crystals first
wins the match.
[ERUNA] Uh... where's
my crowd of screaming fans?
[BIMII] Oh, the other
students get to watch
from wherever
they want to, ryui.
The match will be broadcast
to their phones and what-not
from cameras installed
around the school, ryui.
[BIMII]
Ready, now?
If so, let's get this started!
[DEVICE]
Begin the match.
[ERUNA yelling]
I won't let you get away!
[ERUNA]
I could ambush her here!
[HIMI]
Eruna!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
It's time to eat!
Ooh, good news!
There are girls wandering
around the school
in nothing but swimsuits!
You don't wanna
miss this opportunity.
Eruna!
[ERUNA]
Do people think I'm that dumb?
I mean, come on!
Hey, you don't have to
run away from me, newest bestie!
[ERUNA] I'll get the
first one when I jump down,
grab the second
before she turns around,
and then take the third
as she aims for my crystal.
I'm so gonna crush this.
Hi! I've been looking for you!
[ERUNA]
She's a psychic!
Remember, you're in
a battle with Himi.
You're not clever enough
to trick me, silly.
[ERUNA yelling]
[HIMI]
Wait!
[ERUNA]
Huh?
Well, that looks pleasant.
[ERUNA] Okay, what's
the deal with this room?
[SPIRIT GIRL]
Eruna...
You are a descendant
of the chosen line.
Now, you must awaken yourself.
Never forget.
This power has always
been a part of you.
[ERUNA]
Weird.
"Is this real or a fantasy"
moment alert.
Who was she, though?
[HIMI]
I found you!
You're not allowed
to come in here, silly.
Uh hold on! Wait!
Sorry!
I'm kinda starving,
but I can't hit up
snack time until I finish you.
[HIMI]
What's going on here?
Did she awaken?
Aw man, not now!
[ERUNA]
Crazy. My body feels so light!
[HIMI]
Lovely Ink!
[ERUNA]
Pawn?!
Not sure what this is,
but man, do I like it!
Oh, no!
[yells]
[ERUNA]
Shoji?
So this is a battle?
It's crazy fun!
That's check.
[ERUNA]
Why are we playing shoji?!
[SPIRIT GIRL]
Now, you must awaken yourself.
Never forget.
This power has always
been a part of you.
[ERUNA] Aw yeah! No way!
This is my power?!
Tension max! Go!
[yelling]
Seriously?
How did she do that
without having an item?
[ERUNA]
Did I win?
No way.
Ha, sorry I
kicked your butt, Himi!
[SHIGURE]
Eruna's finally awakened.
That's my girl.
[SHIGURE] Congratulations
on your first victory, Eruna!
[ERUNA] The mighty
Eruna Ichinomiya's power
has finally awakened,
and it's called Toy Gun!
But wait, a new assassin
appears before her,
and the villain
is named Modded Himi!
[BIMII] Or nothing
like that happens, ryui!
[ERUNA]
Well not yet!
If I keep believing, though,
someday she'll appear!
Besides, everyone has a
little Modded Himi in them!
[SHIGURE]
I see her!
[BIMII]
Are you serious, ryui?
[ERUNA]
For a Modded Himi,
start by fastening the arms and
legs of a freshly-caught Himi
to an operating table.
Then, you'll want to rub
some seaweed and kelp
into her face. They're full
of nutrients and minerals,
like arginine and stuff.
So while you're making her skin
all smooth and silky soft...
[SHIGURE]
Yes! Do me next, Eruna!
Mod me that way, too!
[BIMII] Next time,
"Not Quite a Heroine"!
Modded Himi not included.