[ASUHI]
I know this might sound crazy.
But I saw a big, hairy
man in those trees.
It had to be bigfoot!
[ERUNA giggles]
Nobody'll know it's me, right?
I'm so scared.
It was Mr. Bimii.
He turned into a chupacabra!
What did I see?
Well, uh...
There was somethin' in the sky?
It was flying over the
old school grounds?
I guess it was some
kinda oofo? Uh, UFO?
What else could it be, right?
Yeah... I'm not usually
one to gossip, but...
There are two people
from a certain club
who've started an all-out war,
vying for the heart
of another member--
[beep]
[CLUB MEMBER 9A]
Wow!
Cryptids, UFOs,
and club scandals.
Things have been so crazy
around here lately,
I don't think we're ever gonna
run out of news to print.
I'm glad there's enough
to keep everyone
in the newspaper club busy.
That's good.
But I doubt that
it's a coincidence.
[NYAMIRIN]
Yuto, please tell me the words
that I've been longing to hear.
Your heart belongs
to me, and only me.
Isn't that right?
Say it, my love.
But Nyamirin--
[KUMANO]
Roar!
Stay away from him,
you giant jezebel!
--[KUMANO pants]
--Calm down, Kumano.
What's gotten into you?
He'd never fall for
a girl who looks like
she's smuggling
midgets in her shirt!
That's the silliest
thing I've heard.
He even said it himself,
"There's nothing
that I love more
than a pair of super
bouncy bazongas."
Uh...
He might've felt that way
before but things change!
He was bound to get sick
of your jumbo jumblies
the way you go and flaunt
'em all over the place.
He's tired of floppy fun bags,
now he's ready to join the
itty bitty titty committee!
That's not true!
In fact, just the other day he
talked about my rocky mountains!
He wanted to take
a hike in them!
That's all you've
got going for you!
Look, I may not be stacked,
but I've got brains and beauty!
You're a space cadet!
I'm smart and hotter
than a hot spring!
You're not gonna come
between me and my man,
got it, Tits McGee?
I-- Uh--
What's it gonna be, Yuto?
Yeah, are you gonna go with
plump pillows or my booblets?
I'm sorry, ladies,
but I can't chose 'cause I love
big breasticles and mini melons.
[BOTH gasp]
Sometimes you want bouncy,
and then sometimes ya don't.
Why, oh why, can't
I have 'em both?
I wanna live in a world with
big cans and bee stings!
Double whammies...
...and titbits!
What's with this script?!
I don't even know what
these stupid words mean!
Great, just what I need.
Another actor
throwing a tantrum.
You're the one who wanted
to join the drama club,
so shut up and act already!
If you play your cards right,
I can make you famous, baby!
Gimme a break.
I don't understand why
we're even doing this
skit in the first place.
Okay fine, I'll explain...
...again.
Otone and I need
to recruit members
to make our new club a reality,
so we've come up
with a master plan!
First, we come up with
a scandalous story,
and we report it to
the newspaper club.
When they come out to cover
the faux news, we're there,
casually holding up
our recruitment signs
in the background.
We get peoples' attention
with a crazy story,
and then we suck 'em in!
Before ya know it,
they'll be all,
"Maybe I should
join that new club."
It's farfetched, but it
could happen, right?
Yeah! That's wicked smart!
Your signs'll have a
"suppository effect" on folks!
You mean a subliminal
effect, ryui.
[ERUNA] The newspaper club
could show up at any time, so...
Let's take it from the top!
Wait a sec, Spielberg.
If the newspaper club's
covering this like a real story,
everyone'll think it's legit.
[ERUNA snickers]
Your script doesn't exactly
portray me in a good light,
everybody's gonna think
I'm a two-timing jerk!
[TONKYUN]
You're right.
Once the news gets out,
everyone in school's gonna think
you're a low-down,
dirty, cheating pig.
--[YUTO gasps]
--[ERUNA growls]
Pot, kettle, Porky.
Well then, I quit!
Aw, c'mon now,
don't do that!
Tell ya what, if you stay,
I'll let you switch
roles with Tonkyun.
Here ya go! Wear this!
[YUTO]
What the...?!
A-Are you kidding me?!
[TONKYUN]
I'm touched.
You needed a monster
and you thought of me?
Mm-hm!
Hey, Eruna!
You and I need to have a
little chat about something.
You've never seen my chest,
so how would you know
I have "titbits"?
Look, I'll have you know
that I'm a solid B cup,
which is a hell of a lot
better than most petite girls
are workin' with, roar.
Am I the only person
here who's having fun?
Look, I hate to break it to ya,
but I seriously doubt you're
gonna get any new members
with this whacky plan of yours.
Nobody's come to me yet,
but I'm sure they will.
Have you been approached
by anyone Otone?
[gasps] I'm afraid not.
But it's still early
in the game, right?
[TONKYUN]
Have you even decided
what kind of club
it's going to be yet?
[sighs] I don't know.
I came up with a bunch
of different ideas,
but nothing solid.
I'm not worried; I'm sure it'll
come to me sooner or later.
Dontcha think you should figure
out the purpose of your club
before you start
recruiting new members?
Nah.
We haven't shifted away
from the basic concept of
surrounding yours truly
with as many cute girls
as we can possibly
squish in a club room
so I think we're
gonna be just fine.
You know, you might wanna
shift away from that
concept altogether, ryui.
If worse comes to worst,
we might have to think about
recruiting people
from other clubs.
I think that sounds
fun, don't you?
You gals wanna be in two clubs?
Maybe, but we're already
so busy, you know?
What she's trying to say is,
"Thank you, but we're
not interested."
[ERUNA]
Hmph.
[TONKYUN] Sorry, but the
drama club needs me
even more than you do.
Help me out here!
Can you at least
share Usamaru with me?
I mean, he's better
than nothing.
Hey, what's that
supposed to mean?!
I'm a lot better than "nothing,"
I'm freakin' awesome!
Sure, if you wanna borrow
him, that's cool.
Yeah, he doesn't do
much here anyway.
What's the matter
with you people?!
I thought you were
supposed to be my friends!
I know I may not be the best
actor here but I'm not that bad.
--[GROUP laughs]
--Am I?
Guess there's no sense
trying to rush things.
We'll find members
when we find 'em.
Well, don't get too
lackadaisical.
"Lacka" wha...?
See, in order to
form a new club,
you've gotta meet
all the credentials
by the time the midterm
battles start, ryui.
[ERUNA] Hold up, dontcha
mean midterm exams?
[BIMII]
Nope, you heard me right.
Here, take a look at this,
and you'll get the general idea.
Basically, the midterm battles
help us evaluate each club
and its members, ryui.
[ERUNA]
Hmm...
It seems like it'd be
easy enough to find
at least one more member
before the battles begin,
but what if we don't?
Hate to break it to ya, but if
you don't meet the deadline,
you can say goodbye to your
dream of starting a club.
Wha--?!
Then we'd better hurry
and find someone
or all our hard work'll
be for nothin'!
I don't even care who joins,
we just need another warm body!
So you'll take anyone?
Why? You know someone?
Maybe.
I have someone in mind,
but I don't know.
Let's see if you can find the
members on your own first, 'kay?
Ryui.
Really? Who?
I'm dying to know, Bimii!
Ahh, I'm the one who's
gonna die if you don't let go!
You're squeezing so
hard, I can't breathe!
I can't tell you right now!
It's a last resort, ryui!
[sighs]
That's much better.
Anyway, let's hurry and find
you girls another member!
That's not gonna be easy.
At this point,
I think I've asked everyone
in the whole school to join.
Wow.
So the idiot's found
someone to join her club.
And to think it's
Otone Fujishiro.
She won the rookie battle.
Oh, that poor girl.
Has anyone warned
her about Eruna?
I doubt she has any idea what
she's gotten herself into.
Now that there are two of them,
all they need is one more member
and their club will
officially be added to
the school's Academy roster.
I imagine you'll be glad
to get her out of your hair.
It'll be much
quieter around here.
That's fine with me.
It's about time she moved on.
What a relief, then.
I was afraid you'd be upset
about her leaving the mansion.
Are you finished eating?
Yeah, I'm going to lie down.
[ERUNA]
Guess what, Seisa?
[SEISA gasps]
I finally convinced
someone to join my club!
I'm one step closer to
makin' the dream a reality!
Looks like all your
hard work paid off.
But... that's not enough.
You still need one more
member in order to apply.
One down, one to go!
I've got this, Seisa!
You just wait! You'll see!
I wish you the best of luck.
[ERUNA]
Thanks!
Welp, back to recruiting!
[SHIGURE] Aw yeah, I've
been waiting for you!
[laughs]
Eh...?
And here you are!
When I heard you were
starting your own club,
I knew you'd come
a knockin'.
It was only a matter of time!
You want me to join, dontcha?
Of course you do, who wouldn't
want a class act like me?
Uh, listen...
So tell me, have you decided
on a name for your club yet?
A name? Not yet.
Well, in that case,
I've got one for ya.
Whaddya say we call it
"Shigure and Eruna's
Club of Eternal Love"?
Our activities can be
writing love letters
and smoochin' all day long.
Woohoo!
♪ Shigure and Eruna's
'Club of Eternal Love', ooh! ♪
♪ Where every single day
is a rendezvous! ♪
♪ It's a special place
for me and you! ♪
♪ In rooster terminology,
cock-a-doodle-doo! ♪
♪ There's magical spell that
goes, "Bippity Boppity Boo!" ♪
♪ Hands off my girl Eruna,
or I will sock it to you! ♪
[CLUB MEMBER 9B] I hate to
interrupt you, Shigure.
[SHIGURE]
Hm?
But she left a while ago.
[SHIGURE]
What the--
[ERUNA]
I can't believe it.
I never thought
I'd stoop so low.
You know I'm
desperate for members
when I have to ask Shigure,
the creep master to join.
[STUDENT 9A] I'm so excited to
meet up with Otone, aren't you?
[STUDENT 9B]
Yeah! I was wondering what
kind of club she's starting.
Knowing her, it'll be awesome.
[STUDENT 9A] Right?
She's so freakin' cool.
Aw, yeah!
It looks like Otone
worked her magic,
and recruited a
couple of cuties!
Oh, hey. You must be
Otone Fujishiro.
Wow, you're so pretty.
[ERUNA snickering]
So are the rumors true that
you and Eruna Ichinomiya
are trying to start
a brand new club?
Would you mind telling us
some more about it?
You girls aren't worthy.
Fuji's not gonna
waste her breath.
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--[ERUNA] Huh?
Let's go, Anticomplex.
Snake!
[STUDENTS scream]
[STUDENT 9A] What do you
think you're doing?!
If you really wanna
be in our club,
then you'll have to beat Fuji.
Just think of it as
an admissions test.
[STUDENT 9B]
You gotta be joking.
Surely you don't think
we're so common,
we'd let anyone who shows
interest join our new club.
We're not gonna settle
for whoever's available.
We only want Mikagura's best.
So if you wanna become
a member of our club,
then you're gonna have to prove
yourself by battling Fuji.
But we can't beat you!
Yeah, we're not strong enough.
You're the winner of the rookie
battle for crying out loud!
Well, this is... bad.
[OTONE] Okay, which one
of you wants to go first?
Uh, not me.
I don't wanna die today.
[BOTH] Thanks but we've
changed our minds!
[ERUNA]
Holy wow, Otone!
This is a side of you
that I've never seen before
and I gotta tell you,
I'm totally a fan.
It's good to see that
you're not sugary sweet
all the time, y'know?
I seriously love this whole
bossy thing you got going on,
but you might've come
on a little too strong
with those girls.
Hey, where are you going?
[OTONE panting]
[ERUNA]
Otone, wait up!
Why're you running away?
Are you disappointed with Fuji?
Huh?
We've both worked really hard
trying to find members
for our club.
We finally get two
potential recruits,
and instead of welcoming
them with a smile...
...Fujishiro went
and scared them away!
Don't be silly,
I'm sure they know you were
just messing with them.
I mean, you're gonna go
after them, aren't ya?
Be all super sweet and ask
if they wanna join us.
That's your plan, right?
Please tell me that's your plan.
No, je suis désolé.
Huh?
Fuji wanted to scare them off.
Oh wait, I get it!
"Jay-Z desortee" means
you're kidding, right?
Fuji's dead serious, Eruna!
Huh?
Fujishiro knows that we
need members and fast.
She would hate for our dreams
of starting an awesome
new club to be ruined.
She feels torn.
She wants for you to be happy,
but deep down she knew
she had no choice,
but to scare the
other girls away!
Seriously?
Mm-hm.
Okay... But why?
'Cause... Fuji is spoiled.
She doesn't want to share you.
You're her favorite person.
She likes having you to herself.
She doesn't want new members
to ruin her friendship.
I would never let that happen!
It doesn't matter how many
people join the club,
you and I are always
gonna be friends, Otone.
[OTONE]
Whatever!
Fuji's scared of losing you!
[ERUNA]
I'm not going anywhere.
[OTONE]
Fujishiro's always been a loner,
but she finally made a friend.
She cares so much
for you, Eruna.
She'd be heartbroken if someone
were to ever come between you.
That's why she scared
all those girls away.
You could never
understand Fuji's pain
'cause you've got
lots of friends.
What do you mean by
"all those girls"?
Just how many
have you scared off?
Too many to count!
Fuji knew that it was wrong,
but she couldn't help herself.
Eruna's the only friend she has.
She can't lose her.
Thank you.
[gasps]
Nobody's ever valued
my friendship
as much as you do, Otone.
It makes me really happy!
Eruna...
You just gave me a great idea!
[OTONE]
Huh?
Here we go!
Ready for awesomeness?
♪ Ba-da-da-da! ♪
Let's call it the
"Otone and Eruna's So Close
That It's Questionable
Friendship Club"!
Ah! Fuji thinks it'll be
hard to recruit new members
with a name like
that, don't you?
[ERUNA giggles]
Maybe so but who cares?
I don't wanna upset you so let's
quit worrying about new members.
It should just be the two of us.
You and me, all alone.
[ERUNA laughing]
Eruna...
You're really creeping
Fuji out right now.
Why do you always
have to be so pervy?!
[OTONE whimpers]
[screams]
[ERUNA] That must've
hurt! Are you okay?
[OTONE]
Yeah.
[ERUNA gasps]
I've never seen
this room before.
Neither has Fuji.
They must not use it
anymore. It's all dusty.
[ERUNA] I bet we could breathe
some life into this place.
Can't you just imagine us
meeting here after class
and hanging out?
We could even bring snacks
and stuff our faces!
[OTONE]
That'd be awesome!
And Fuji could
bring her tea set!
Aah! I wanna sit right
here in front of the window.
Then Fujishiro's gonna
sit next to you.
This could actually work.
We could have everyone
sit in a circle facing us.
Hey, Otone, are you
thinkin' what I'm thinkin'?
No doubt about it.
Fujishiro thinks that
this would be the...
[BOTH]
...perfect clubroom!
[OTONE chuckles]
[ERUNA giggles]
[RUMINA]
Keep dreaming, ladies.
'Cause that's
never gonna happen.
Oh yeah? Why's that, Rumina?
It's not yours, so
you don't have any say.
Oh, but it is mine.
You see, it's
already been decided
that the newspaper club's
going to be taking this room.
[ERUNA gasps]
No way.
That's so unfair, you
guys already have a room!
I know your club's
been busy lately,
but not enough to
need two of 'em!
Don't be silly, we're not
going to use both of them.
We've outgrown our current
clubroom so we're moving here.
Don't worry.
I'm sure that you'll
find a decent one.
I want this one!
If I spit on it,
then it's mine, right?
[OTONE sighs]
Tell you what, if you
really want it that badly,
then what do you say
we fight for it?
You're fighting?
But we don't know anything about
Rumina's strength
or fighting style.
Why don't you let Fuji do this?
There's no need to worry, Otone.
I've so got this.
I'm gonna kick her butt and then
we'll have our perfect clubroom!
Maybe you should let Otone fight
since she's so much
stronger than you.
I mean, she did win the
rookie battles, after all.
But I guess it doesn't
matter because, either way,
you're no match for me.
[DEVICE]
Begin the match.
[ERUNA grunts, pants]
[RUMINA] Charging in head
first is such a rookie move.
It's unsophisticated.
You think you can break
all of my crystals at once?
What's she doing
with that book?
It's gotta be her
summoning object!
[RUMINA inhales]
Hot off the presses!
Eruna Ichinomiya's
bold confession!
At just four years old, Eruna
made a wish on a falling star,
"I wanna be Shigure's
wife when I grow up!"
What the--?!
Who in the heck
told you that?!
[RUMINA]
Here's an exclusive scoop!
When Eruna was
just six years old,
she attempted to make
Valentine's chocolates
for her beloved, but she
failed spectacularly.
When she gave Shigure
the misshapen treats,
he said, "They're ugly but
they still taste good!"
and she was so touched
that she was--
Okay, okay, I think
we've all heard enough!
How did you get this info?
[RUMINA chuckles]
It's really easy when you're a
member of the newspaper club.
People come to us with all
kinds of scandalous stories.
It was Shigure, wasn't it?
I'm gonna strangle that creep
for spilling all my secrets!
[OTONE]
What?!
You're trying to tell Fuji that
everything Rumina said is true?
No, you've got it
all wrong, Otone!
[RUMINA] We interrupt this
convo for a special report!
For her ninth birthday,
Shigure surprised Eruna
with an original rap,
and she was so touched that
she was moved to tears.
Fuji doesn't know
who's creepier,
Shigure for writing you a
rap song for your birthday
or you for crying about it.
Please make it stop!
I don't think I can take
--much more of this!
--Breaking news!
For Shigure's birthday
that same year,
Eruna surprised him
with an original rap,
and he said, "Thanks but don't
give up your day job, kiddo!"
And she was so touched that
she was moved to tears.
[OTONE gasps]
What happened?
Why did Eruna's
crystal just break?
[ERUNA gasps]
She didn't receive
any physical damage.
Wait, was it you?
You see, a funny thing happens
whenever people get
excruciatingly embarrassed.
They don't want
to fight anymore,
they just want to curl
into a little ball and hide.
The stress causes them
to subconsciously destroy
--their own crystals.
--[ERUNA whimpering]
[laughs] Yes.
My enemies drop like flies
thanks to my special power.
I call it, "Secret Memories"!
Watch!
I'm about to finish her off!
--This just in!
--[ERUNA cries]
No! Please stop!
--I can't take it!
--[crystal shatters]
[ERUNA whimpers]
Are you giving up?
Wow, this was almost too easy.
I'm toast...
Aw, c'mon, you still
have one crystal left,
and I haven't even pulled
out the big guns yet.
I've got so much dirt on you
that I could do this for days.
--[RUMINA muffled speaking]
--[gasps]
[ERUNA]
Otone's ribbons!
[OTONE giggles]
No way.
What, all of a sudden,
you wanna fight back?
Okay! Here's a news flash!
When Eruna was twelve
years old, she asked Shigure--
She asked him to go to the--
No... Why isn't it
working anymore?
Take her down, Tension max!
Go!
[RUMINA gasps]
I totally trashed
that bully! [laughs]
And now, the super cool
clubroom is ours!
[OTONE]
Yeah!
Félicitations!
[RUMINA]
Whatever.
It's not like your
win matters anyway.
See, your club needs
at least three members.
And you've got two.
[BOTH gasp]
[RUMINA]
You know what that means.
If you can't come up
with another member,
then your request
will be denied,
and this "super cool clubroom"
will go to the newspaper club.
You wasted all that
energy for nothing.
Oh, and just so we're clear,
I know you've been calling
in fake news stories
in a sad attempt to
publicize your club.
C'mon, Eruna.
Did you seriously think
we would fall for that?
I hope you can forgive Fuji.
There were lots of people
interested in joining.
That's all in the past, Otone.
Well, since you don't
have enough members,
I think it's safe to say
this room belongs to
the newspaper club.
[HANDSOME STUDENT]
Excuse me.
--[RUMINA gasps]
--[OTONE, ERUNA] Huh?
I'm looking for
Eruna Ichinomiya.
I'm interested in
joining her club.
[HANDSOME STUDENT]
Sparkle!
Um, I'm Eruna.
And who are you?
That's impossible!
I don't have any information
on this guy whatsoever!
[HANDSOME STUDENT]
Smile!
[ERUNA]
We did it!
[laughs]
Our club request
has been approved,
and we got the cool clubroom!
[giggles]
You really pulled one
over on us, huh?
--[HANDSOME STUDENT chuckles]
--[ERUNA] For real!
I had no idea you
could do that, Bimii!
[BIMII screams]
It's not easy for me
to take that form,
it's incredibly draining.
So I can't maintain it
for very long, ryui.
Well, I'm afraid
you're gonna have to
'cause now that you're
an official member
of the club, we're gonna
need your help with battles
and activities
and stuff, y'know?
Sometimes I think you're
trying to kill me.
Please hurry and find
some more members, ryui.
Now that we're official,
can you tell us what you
decided to name the club?
[laughs]
I named it...
♪ Ta-da-da ♪
The "I'll Figure It
Out Later Club"!
[OTONE, BIMII scream]
[BIMII]
What kinda name is that?!
You can only put it off
for so long, ryui!
[USAMARU screams]
[ERUNA]
Get it together, Usamaru!
[USUMARU]
But I saw it!
[NYAMIRIN]
What? You saw what? What?
[TONKYUN] Was it Kuzuryu
getting up at five every morning
to milk a cow?
[USAMARU]
No!
[NYAMIRIN] Then was it
Mr. Bimii when he goes "pwoosh"?
[USAMARU]
What are you talking about?!
[KUMANO] Ah-ha! Then
it was the slimy part
in the zipper on
Miracle Man's back, roar!
[USAMARU]
What are you talking about?!
It really worries me that
there'd be a slimy
part of a zipper!
[ERUNA]
Never mind that, Usamaru.
How are things
going with Sagara?
[USAMARU]
Ugh!
Why'd you have to bring up
Sagara's name right now?!
[KUMANO]
Aww! Usamaru's blushing, roarr!
[NYAMIRIN] You're surprisingly
good pair, aren't you?
[USAMARU]
We're not a good pair at all!
[TONKYUN]
Yes, I see.
And I get the feeling
you're kind of lonely.
[ERUNA]
Uh, Tonkyun?!
[KUMANO] Next time,
"Sleeping Bag Haunting."
Usamaru and Tonkyun together
in the same sleeping bag, roar!
[USAMARU]
None of that makes any sense!
I'm telling you, I saw it!
[NYAMIRIN] The nameplate
on Tonkyun's house?
[TONKYUN] My house
doesn't have one of those.
[ERUNA] So, just what was
it then that Usamaru saw?!
[KUMANO]
You'll find out next time! Roar!