All right. Let's do this...
From here we should split up.
Okay.
There are at least three intruders in our facility.
Terada and Koyama have been defeated.
It's time for you, the Awakened, to shine!
You've endured the trials of
rigorous training and came out strong.
Now's your chance to show just how powerful we can be!
Though... none of you stand a chance.
No way!
So all the Scars were sent after the intruders?
That's big. They must be worried.
When are we gonna get in on the action?
I feel like all we do is lame grunt work around here.
Just let it go, man.
'Cause those who don't awaken
will always be stuck at the bottom.
Eventually, we'll end up subordinates of kids like him.
Ain't that the truth. Speaking of...
Did you hear about the kid who
was sent here from HQ as a temp?
From what I understand,
he's an Awakened Child that they created on their own.
A normal kid survived that insane
awakening experiment HQ puts them through?
Lucky!
I wanna be in an experiment for the big-wigs, too.
You wanna die? Don't even think about it.
The destruction of your mind's
just the beginning of that torture.
Really? Gen, you know about HQ?
Just stories, mostly.
Heard the trials are so painful
most people don't make it out alive.
After 20 years as a lackey around
here, I've learned HQ is bad news.
You don't want nothin' to do with those guys.
Wait...
Hang on a sec. What the hell
do you think you guys are doin'?
Should've known it wouldn't be easy.
What happened to your trainers?!
Took them out.
What?! Can't believe they were
beaten by a bunch of snot-nosed kids.
We'll take care of...
Let 'em go!
No way! Are you serious?
I wasn't expecting that... Are you sure?
Yeah. Just go.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
We aren't gonna get stabbed in the back, are we?
What the hell?! Why'd you...?!
Shut your mouths, you youngins!
You don't know anything about how the world works!
An ESP-er and a normal human are like night and day.
The difference in strength is astronomical.
If it's a powerful one, it's like zero versus ten.
There's no way you can win.
Damn it. If only my powers had awakened, I could've...
Give it up.
If you don't awaken the first time
around, there's no hope of it happening.
Ever.
Wait. Seriously?
We're gonna be lackeys forever?!
There's no way you're fine with that, Gen!
I don't think you kids are really grasping the situation.
Claw will definitely rule over this world.
And when they do, all of us lackeys
who supported them will be rewarded.
But for right now, we just need to wait things out.
Until the day the revolution is finally upon us!
Ah-hah. What do we have here?
From the looks of that door, I'd say I
found somewhere or something pretty special.
Must be where they're keeping Ritsu and the others.
Hm?
Uh?
I thought it was one of the intruders at first,
but it's just security.
What are you wanderin' around for?
Oh, so that's where I am! I got a little turned around.
My sense of direction is just terrible.
Just do your damn job, okay?
Right, sorry about that.
Hmm...
What's over here?
I haven't actually been inside this room yet.
Maybe I'll just have a peek as long as I'm down here.
Hold it!
You're lying. You're an impostor.
I'm telling you to let me see the room, small fries.
This guy's one of the intruders!
Everyone, release your powers!
Whoa.
Individually, they're no big deal, but
they're not bad when they work together.
A normal human wouldn't be able to escape from this.
How long do you think you can keep this up, tough guy?!
Hey, nice effort.
But you're still outclassed!
Now. Back to the matter at hand.
Let's see what's goin' on in this room.
Hey, you! Explain this.
Uh. Well, th-this is the awakening experiments room...
These look like a bunch of torture devices.
Yes...
Our organization discovered that experiencing
pain is a catalyst to being awakened.
Hmm... Actually, they're not too far off.
But even after going through that much pain,
all you guys can do is momentarily inconvenience someone.
In the end, the world really does favor the gifted.
You'll never be A-listers. You have a
better chance focusing on body building.
Is that so?
What do we have here?
It's not every day a ghost wanders into our facilities.
How would you like to become my ghost?
I promise I'll take excellent care of you.
So you wanna own me, do you?
Someone dangerous just showed up.
Huh?!
You weren't able to find them in their cage?!
Don't mess with me, punk!
I told you to bring 'em here! So where are they?!
Well, you see, uh,
from the looks of it, they got out on their own.
If you're lying to me, I'll kick your lackey ass!
I'm not lying. I swear!
Okay, then.
Good grief.
I don't like imitating those thugs from the alley,
but it seems to work well on weaklings.
This isn't over.
You're wide open! Ignite!
Ha, ha! With this flame, I'll...!
Can't believe you thought you could fight me.
Those powers are a joke.
It's funny. Everyone in Claw seems a little...
Aw, did you get burned?
What you're seeing is true pyrokinesis.
The ability to wield fire at will.
A Scar...
Are you the brat Koyama was goin' on and on about?
How pathetic.
I'll turn your body to ash.
I know what you're thinking.
"It's okay, my barrier can withstand this!"
The inside of your barrier
turns into an insanely hot sauna.
So much so that your lungs will burn when you breathe.
A stupid mistake amateurs like
you make time and time again.
You're the amateur here.
Big talk, kid.
But in order to fight back,
you'll have to drop your barrier.
And when you do, you'll be burned to a crisp.
And if you keep this up, you'll be steamed.
So that means this fight is over.
Your options are either burn to
death or surrender to me and hope...
Bring it on.
Sure!
Prepare to die!
Now I won't spare you, even if you beg me to!
But given how much heat I'm throwing at you,
your pleading tears would evaporate anyway!
Ow!
When I switched my barrier
over, my clothes got kinda singed.
It's true that you can't defend and
attack at the same time with psychic powers.
So the solution was to put a barrier around my attacker.
Uh? Well, guess you're not listening.
You're causing a racket, so I'll let you out.
Wow, that's surprising.
You can still move around with all those burns?
Who knows? Maybe people with pyrokinesis
have a higher tolerance to heat.
Either way...
Your arrogance and lack of
flexibility led to your downfall.
And with that, I'm the winner.
Whew! Now I'm sweating.
Maybe I was a little scared.
I must say. Well done.
You're much stronger than I was as a child.
However, I possess more strength now
than you will have in your whole lifetime.
It's the end of the road. Just give up.
Exaggerate much, buddy?
Oh, hello. How's it goin' everyone?
So, uh... I'm looking for my younger brother.
Apparently, he's somewhere inside this building.
Yipee!
My dolls found one! They found an intruder!
Hey, Tsucchi. Can I do whatever I want with him?
Yeah, sure. You caught him, so he's your toy now.
Yay!
I'm gonna go have a look!
If I don't hurry, my dolls will break
him before I have a chance to play!
Mukai, the puppet master.
Quite the ability she's got.
She can control all those wooden
dolls remotely and telepathically,
holding an immortal army in her hands.
And just look at her, so excited over finding a new toy.
I wouldn't wanna get on her bad side.
It's all clear now.
Then let's move. We need to find the exit, and quickly.
Ah-ha!
Found you, jail-breakers!
Ha! That was easy!
Sorry, you guys. Guess I picked the wrong route.
No, don't worry. You did just fine.
We'll force our way through.
Ya think so, brat?!
Now! Combination Super Psychokine...
Holy crap!
It looks like their espers aren't really all that strong.
Power-wise, they're all on the same level as Hoshino.
What's that mean?
They're better off punching people.
Not bad!
You're right about them not being strong.
They're useless as real soldiers.
I don't see a scar like the trainers talked about.
He's not a part of the upper echelon.
Who are you?
Who, me? Wonder who I could be.
Perfect. We're dealing with a smartass.
We're all in a bit of a hurry right now.
We can play guessing games some other time.
Now, now, no need to be so mean.
I thought we could all be friends here.
This guy seems dangerous.
Agreed. We're finished.
It's okay. You guys can go on ahead.
Kageyama.
I'll take care of this one myself.
Hang on! I've got a bad feeling about this!
Just give it up. You can't defeat me.
I don't believe that.
Really? Why?
I mean you're not a moron or anything, are you?
Maybe...
Or maybe it's 'cause I know someone stronger than you.
Is that so?
He must be one of the other intruders, I take it?
Then, I suppose I'll just have to use you as bait
and bring him out of the shadows.
Tsucchi!
Oh, Mukai.
You're back from playtime already?
You're as ruthless as ever.
Wood scraps?
Hey, Mukai. What happened to your dolls?
That boy broke them. He broke all my lovely dolls!
Leave this to me.
He's mine now.
Hm?
Hey, you!
Tell me, are you one of the intruders?
He really is just a kid.
How could he possibly...?
Are you the violent-type too, old lady?
You brat! Who are you calling old, huh?!
Tsucchi!
You're not going to stop me with telekinesis like that!
Her ability is hardening qigong,
which she uses to divert all of her qi into
her fists or knees to make them more powerful.
She's a top-class fighter, even among the Scars.
If she manages to lose, you might
actually have to step in, Takeuchi.
And take this intruder seriously.
This could get tricky if I give
him enough time to attack again.
These hits aren't having much of an effect.
Is his qi guard really that thick?
Without any build up?!
Hey! Your damn phone's ringing!
Wait a minute. What the...?
You came this far, so why are you crying?
Because... I really don't wanna have
to beat up a lady during this rescue.
Huh?
What did you say?
My master always told me guys
who go around beating up women
are the biggest losers in the world.
You're quite the gentleman, but that's an insult.
I'm giving you permission to
fight me fair and square, okay?
Give it everything you've got!
Stay away from me!
Tch.
It sure looks like I drew the short straw in this one.
I've never even heard of this power.
This human can make evil spirits his obedient pets.
You're good at running away.
But why don't you leave that body behind?
It'd be easier to move as a spirit.
Huh?
Are you holding that man hostage?
Forget him. He's not worth it.
Crap!
This body won't hold up much longer.
Only third-rate spirits would let
the body they possessed be damaged.
But I have even less of a chance
of beating him in spirit form.
In that case...
What exactly are you trying to do?
I've noticed those things return
to their master after they attack.
Now why would they be trained to do that?
Maybe it's 'cause their master
isn't strong enough to protect himself?
I see right through you!
He's fast!
Here, Cookie! Here, Gum!
Now he can't come any closer.
What?!
Did he fall?
No, wait! He's not...?!
We can fight some other time. See ya, dude!
I'm gonna crush you in the next round!
Go! After that bastard!
Bring him to me! He will be mine!
Fooled ya, dumbass!
Oh, man, you fell for that?
Crap!
Get back here!
Three seconds should be plenty of time.
How about a knuckle sandwich?!
Not so fast...
You're the one who underestimated me.
What makes you think I only have two evil spirits?
You mean... all those around his waist are...?
Crap! There's nowhere to run!
Looks like Tsuchiya was defeated.
Takeuchi, I'm counting on you.
Very well.
No one in the world is a match
for the power of my super qigong.
I'll win, no matter what!
Takeuchi, the super qigong user.
His face changes in battle mode.
Even I can't completely get a read on him.
What do you think?
I was thinking you should all run away from here.
Why is that?
Simple. Because I know Kageyama.
Oh?
Not to mention, it's impossible to
take over the world with psychic powers.
Use this opportunity to wake up from that dream.
You won fighting against Miyagawa.
Why are you wasting your time living among
the normals when you're such a powerful esper?
We are special beings. And that's a fact.
Not a dream.
Long as you keep believing that, you
will never be able to take him down.
I know you were trying to do something, but I'm sorry.
I'm kind of in a hurry.
N-No way...
Is that Ritsu?
What happened?
Oh, he's still breathing. Thank goodness...
But I don't understand.
Why does my little brother have
to be put through all of this?
I just... I don't get it.
It's unforgivable.
Well? What's the situation here, young one?
Hope you haven't already been defeated by others.
I haven't even used my powers yet.
Did you do this to him?
Not hiding your hostility, eh?
In that case,
I'll show you even greater despair, free of charge.
No...
This... isn't real...
Man, that was a close one.
He managed to amplify the illusion
Muto showed him and reversed it.
But was it planned or natural instinct?
Gotta admit, he's pretty interesting.
It was totally worth using his
brother as bait to get him down here.
Not bad you two.
Out of the 11 Scars, 7 have been
defeated during this intrusion.
How should I explain that situation to the boss?
What's going on? Kageyama actually lost?
It can't be.
The guy who carried those two here... did he really...?
Hey, what's up? It's okay, don't be scared!
There's no way he'd lose to someone like that!
Hi, I'm back! What's up?
Seems you captured the others, too.
You look pretty happy.
Yes.
One of the intruders is an evil
spirit who has a very strong ego.
They got Dimple, too?
This poison jar has hundreds
of evil spirits thrown inside it.
The one that survives after viciously attacking
and devouring the others becomes the ultimate pet.
What in the hell is this place?
No, wait! Stop it!
Let's talk about this! W-Wait! You don't wanna eat me!
I have no nutritional value!
Help me, please!
I see it! There's the exit!
Now we can call for help!
Wait! Stop, it's no use.
We've got a problem here.
What's wrong, Hoshino?
Damn! There's no way we can get through that!
Wait a second, they're...!
What the...?
Did someone important show up or something?
That aura...
Holy crap! Even I can feel it.
It's an insanely powerful esper!
No way, it can't be.
There's only one person with those powers.
And that would be their leader.
Claw's boss!
The boss of Claw finally shows himself.
Yes, it's me.
I'm sorry I kept this hidden from you so long, Mob.
No matter what happens from now
on, live your life to the fullest.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100, Episode 11: "Master Leader."
The serious option C? An excellent decision.