Hm? What's that?
At the same time that Ritsu was mistaking
Dimple for some sort of creepy-looking balloon...
...the rumors going around about Mob,
who had bested Hanazawa, shadow leader
of Black Vinegar Middle School,
started to take on a life of their own.
"White T Poison"...
This was the title given to Mob,
whose identity had yet to be revealed.
White T Poison...
I'll be the one to defeat him!
I'm gonna defeat this Poison guy
and make him admit that I'm the best.
So the next target is Salt Middle School.
White T Poison will make excellent prey.
This is my chance to shine.
And so, the rumor mill continued churning out of control.
The fierce battle to see who would take
down White T Poison was about to begin.
Whew! Thanks for the help!
Somehow I managed to make it back
from the particle level all by myself.
But my spiritual energy was way less than it used to be.
So I couldn't get back into the house anymore.
It appears that low-level spirits
can't go anywhere near this place
simply because Shigeo lives here.
What is that?
Some kinda talking jellyfish-looking thing?
I know what needs to be done.
Huh? Wanna shake hands?
I have to exorcise it!
Whoa, wait a second!
Stop kneeing me in the face already!
I'm not a threat! I'm Shigeo's friend!
You're what?
You could even call me his mentor.
I'll let you off the hook this time, because
you were obviously confused and panicked.
But, that aside...
I've got a proposition.
How about you and I team up?
No thanks.
Hey, let's not be so hasty.
Wait a second, just hear me out.
You've only recently awakened your psychic powers, right?
What? I have psychic powers now?
The fact that you can see me is
proof of your newfound abilities.
The name's Dimple.
I'm what most people would call a ghost.
So are my psychic powers only strong
enough to allow me to see ghosts like you?
Well, I see you haven't realized how to use them, yet.
Go ahead.
You should be able to do that now, just like your brother.
I shouldn't get my hopes up.
Hm? What's the matter?
Doing anything like this is way out of my reach.
What's with him?
Does he have a complex or something?
Well, that's understandable,
given who his brother is and all.
It... It's... It's not...
I can't do it!
Dimple!
It's not bending!
Hey, relax, kid.
What the...?
Did I do that?
Join me, little Ritsu...
Join me and I'll help you surpass your brother.
Surpass... my brother?
Is that even possible?
I can be more powerful... than Shige?
Sure you can if you'll let me use your body.
Ritsu's not eating with us?
I guess he's not hungry.
I wonder what could be wrong with him.
Is he upset about something?
No...
In fact, he seems oddly happy.
How do I get to the point
where I can use my powers freely?
It's better to actually try them
out, rather than explain, little Ritsu.
Stop calling me that.
Fine, then. Plain old Ritsu it is.
Now, how 'bout you close your eyes,
and relax your entire body.
Prepare for possession, you fool!
Now your body's mine for the taking!
Heh, heh!
What?!
I've possessed him, but I can't control him?
Hey, Dimple. Where'd you go?
It's because my spiritual powers
have become so weak... Damn it!
I heard the student council took care of the problem.
You mean with the pervy gang leader?
Wow, way to go.
They're the heroes of the school.
Yamazaki, Year 2, Class 4.
I'd like a word with you.
Huh? What do you want?
Your coat. It isn't buttoned.
So what? Buzz off.
I can do it.
Now, I can use psychic powers, Dimple.
That's because I'm helping to regulate their output.
But rest assured, these abilities
have always been there, lying dormant.
And it's my guess that the reason they came out now
is due to some radical change in your emotional state.
Have you endured some
"way-above-average" stress levels lately?
Like pooping your pants in public, or getting
caught peeking into the girls' locker room?
What kind of a question is that?
I'd never do those things.
I was joking, Ritsu.
Don't be so damn serious. Oh...
That's right.
You're an honor student, aren't ya?
Then, what is it? Did you do something bad?
A rumor's going around that you're
stealing the girls' gym clothes.
Huh? The hell are you talkin' about?
The student council did some investigating.
And what'd we find out, Kageyama?
We discovered some of the girl's gym clothes
tucked away and hidden in your bag.
What?! You guys are lyin'!
Deny it if you want,
but that may not go so well for you.
You see, the school's been
very strict with deviants lately.
But I'm here to offer you a way out of this.
Simply admit Onigawara ordered you to do these things.
If you comply, you're merely another victim.
Sound good? Now button up.
Using these and other similar methods,
the whole school was cleaned up,
turning it into the optimal environment for academics.
However, because of the considerably
immoral strategy that was used upon certain
delinquent students to accomplish this outcome,
a deep scar would be forever engraved on their lives.
And the two student council members saddled
with this task had to live with that burden.
So they either became drunk with power,
feeling a delusional sense of accomplishment,
or they suffered greatly.
Whoa!
Ritsu, your power's grown even more!
I see, corruption and guilt...
Those are the things that become fuel for my powers.
Whatever you're doing, it is working!
What's the matter?
Something eating at you?
Dimple, you just won't stop talking.
Oh?
Tell me. If I could control my powers on my own,
would I be able to make you disappear?
Wait, is his personality changing, too?
Whoa! S-Seriously?
Amazing... That's incredible, Kageyama!
Want me to keep going?
If you'd like to see a bigger example,
I could fold your car in half.
What?!
What in the hell's gotten into him??
Excuse me...
May I help you with something?
I heard from Kamuro that you're the one who's
been planting all that false evidence around.
Tell me, are you the one who framed us?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Dimple.
Leave it to me.
Even if I did do such a thing...
Now it's too late.
Why, you little... Who in the hell do ya think we are?!
That does it! Get him!
You're dead meat!
A fight.
Scary!
But isn't that guy's hair, like, totally amazing?
Check it out!
You're right!
Whoa!
Hey, you there.
What's up?
Gah! That's...
I think you've done enough.
If you depend on that, you'll get hurt.
You've got the wrong idea about this.
I know...
You think you're really special.
It's hard looking at someone who
reminds me of the way I used to be.
Consider this a warning.
Don't try to live relying on psychic powers.
Are you another esper like me?
I have no idea who you are...
...but I have no need to take warnings from you.
Don't mess with this guy!
He's not someone you can beat!
I'm sure he's not much different
from the people at the Awakening Lab.
I wanna size up our powers.
Ritsu?! You idiot!
Don't do it!
Why, thank you for the handshake.
I'm Teruki Hanazawa. Pleasure.
Don't try to fight him!
Let go! Now!
Having trouble standing, are you?
You're so young.
Now's your chance! Run for it!
I was surprised at how strong he was, back there.
Maybe it's 'cause his brain's so developed.
Could that coincide with his power level?
No. His brain's not huge... that was a wig.
Though I'm not sure why he was wearing it.
I'm so frustrated.
How could I lose to someone other than my brother?
Dimple. I wanna get even stronger.
So I won't lose to anyone ever again.
Little boy.
Do you have a moment?
Huh?
This is the Vase of Happiness.
A renowned potter put his heart and
soul into making it a one of a kind.
Anyone who buys this item will surely be blessed.
Now it normally goes for about 2.5 million yen,
but I'll make you a deal: 800,000 yen just for you.
I don't have that kind of money.
Then I'll drop the price to 500,000.
Well, I don't have 500,000 yen, either.
Running low on funds?
Just call your mommy and ask her.
I'm pretty sure my mom also wouldn't buy it.
This isn't over yet, kid.
Hey, why don't you touch it?
The grainy texture feels so nice.
Here.
Er, I can't really tell.
That was close.
How did he...?
You should be careful.
Hey, you broke it.
Wait! I-I didn't...!
What? You're going to say it was my fault?
Uh... No, but...
Look, little boy...
Problems that you can solve with money
are better than those that you can't.
Got it?
Oh, what a run of bad luck. Did you break that, sir?
Do you have a phone?
I-I don't...
That rang at the perfect time.
Why don't you answer it?
Now what are you doing, Mob?
Why'd you make me come down here, anyway?
You know I'm taking a meeting soon.
Would you happen to be this boy's guardian, sir?
Oh, I get it.
It's 5,000,000 yen to replace this.
You mean that huge piece of junk?
No way it's worth that.
Wait... What'd you say?
Listen, you don't seem to know how things work.
Maybe I'll teach you a lesson.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
You totally cracked my clavicle.
That's gonna cost you, my friend.
Huh?
The hospital will fix me up for about a million yen.
You can't be serious, you dumbass! That's outrageous!
Verbal abuse causes psychological damage.
So, that's gonna be another million.
Listen, you!
You've got bad breath.
Subjecting me to it's another million.
What the hell?!
Your voice is causing me ear
damage. That'll be another million.
Look. You frayed my shirt.
Then, that's one more million for garment damage.
Now, that's equal to what he owes you for the vase.
I'm no stranger to the kind of
business you guys are running.
Come on, Mob. Let's go.
You're not goin' anywhere.
There's no escape!
This boy's misfortune was decided the
moment he broke the Vase of Happiness.
I'd hate for anything bad to happen to him!
"Misfortune"? "Bad things"?
Before I came here, I was talking to
someone who'd been haunted by an evil spirit.
Apparently, it can be passed along,
and now the spirit's haunting me.
I hear strange noises at night, weird
things keep popping up in pictures,
doors open and shut on their own.
It becomes unbearable.
Who knows? The spirit might have
transferred to you guys by now.
Be careful when you go to bed tonight.
Huh? A haunting?
Doesn't feel too great, does it?
That's pretty much exactly what you guys are doing.
A ghost?
What are you, a little kid? So scary!
That sure shut those two up quick.
And I gotta say...
That last bit was great, Mob.
Huh?
You shook the building to scare them, didn't ya?
Nu-uh.
I thought all that was you sending
the evil spirit after those two.
Wait a second.
Are you saying you couldn't see...?
Come on.
Of course I could see it.
I can't believe them.
Con artists are terrible people.
The worst of the worst.
You said it.
Only the lowest of the low try to take advantage of
someone's weakness and exploit it for their own gain.
What? You as well?
Yes.
He said, "So, you're trash, too?"
And all I was doing was chewing some gum during class.
Kamuro, this school doesn't belong to you.
We still have other pieces of trash to deal with.
Let's keep things moving.
You plan to continue this?
Come on.
You're not going to suggest we stop, are you?
No.
It just that you make me feel sick, that's all.
You get off on this, don't you?
I was correct in choosing you as an accomplice.
If you knew, why did you decide to help me?
Because I was tired.
Just tired of being myself.
Of everything. Maybe I wanted to find
out what it would feel like to be a fool.
There's more to it than that.
In the end, it made us both popular.
You and I have become the heroes of this entire school.
So "looks-too-old-for-school-guy" wanted to be popular?
I, on the other hand, have obtained a much bigger world.
By the way, President,
did you happen to find any telepaths out there?
If I did, I wouldn't be here now, would I?
Inukawa! You can't put a bomb there! That's cheating!
Kurata, would you mind being a little quieter, please?
'Cause I've still got a few
more things I wanna say over here.
Oh. Sorry.
Musashi, that's enough.
No, it's not! Now, man up!
Go to class, Onigawara!
I've got no place there.
I mean, none of my friends will even talk to me anymore.
Oh, a visitor.
The student council president!
I see this place is as rotten as the
rumors led me to believe. More to the point...
What are you doing on campus, Onigawara?
Infiltrating the school when you
haven't been showing up to class?
No!
But I can't stay at home!
If I do, my mom will ask me why I'm not...
Listen to me, President.
Onigawara didn't do what you think he did.
Should I have you all dealt
with for being his accomplices?
'Cause, don't forget, I have the power to do so.
What?!
President...
President, some weird guy just
showed up at the school gates.
What should we do?
It never ends.
The problems pile up one after another.
So who are you guys?
I told the other nerd that I'm here for White T Poison!
"White T Poison"? What on earth is that?
Don't play dumb!
He's the talk of all the thugs right now.
I'll deal with him, President.
That should settle things.
Whoa! You really laid him out!
It was done in self defense.
Not to mention, they were students from
another school, so it shouldn't matter.
Not only is he willing to get into a fight,
he's incredibly strong, too.
Hey...
Are you the guy that knocked out Kenzaki?
Huh?
Who's better known as White T Poison?
Wh-What are you...
I was just watching, I didn't...!
Then who the hell is White T Poison?!
I don't...
That's enough! It's time to stop this!
Man, you look awful.
This is all your fault!
I became a victim because of you!
You taught a gang leader from another school a lesson!
Don't you understand?!
If that's true, then so be it.
He got what was coming to him.
Y-You're kidding me!
No! Not again!
Are you that White T Poison guy?
Oh, it's you, Tokugawa.
Shinji doesn't wanna see anyone right now.
Is that so?
Disgusting.
For someone who wanted to get rid of the
garbage, you should've started with your own room.
H-How did you get in here?
No matter.
Either way, we still have trash to contend with at school.
No way! I'm done with all of that! Get out of here!
It's too late.
We've both done something
unforgivable with our roles in this.
No one's going to save us, understand?
It seems the puppet's been broken.
The school is finally clean.
So now whatcha gonna do?
Ya know thugs from the other
schools are gonna keep showin' up.
With these powers, I can do whatever I want.
Yeah!
You could be a psychic superstar!
Dimple...
You're trying to use me as well, aren't you?
Huh?!
What are you talking about, Ritsu?
We're partners! I'm on your side!
Oh, here they come.
More than usual today.
I came to see what was going on and, of course...
Are you that White T Poison
guy who beat Hanazawa and Kenzaki?
What?! Is he pretending to be Kageyama?
Think things'll finally be
settled once I deal with you guys,
so let's just say you found your man.
It looks like I'm gonna have
to ask him about this, myself.
I found something interesting.
I believe he's the one you were looking for.
I'll apprehend him and head back.
But before that, I should watch
for a bit and see how good he is.
Possession.
All right. Let's get this over with.
Oh! You think it's gonna be that easy?!
Get ready for a pounding!
Don't stop! Go get him, you chickens!
We would...
But, we... can't move!
Hey, Dimple. Let's go all out.
Now's my chance!
Huh?
Your magic tricks won't work on me, White T Pois...
Hey, what's goin' on here?
Is White T Poison doing that?
Maybe, but he can't stop all of us!
Let's charge him!
Don't worry, I won't judge any of you.
I've come to understand something.
When people wander from the right path in
their lives, there usually isn't any reason.
I guess it's always been that way.
I'm facing enemies that have lost the will to
fight, moving forward for the sake of violence.
There's no reason there.
This kind of freedom is strong.
Boundless.
I'm much freer than all of you.
Why, you ask?
I'll tell you. Because I've lost my limits.
I've obtained loss.
It's you What are you doing, Ritsu?
The brothers confront each other in an alley after school.
Suddenly, an adult esper we've
previously seen appears out of nowhere.
Hey, Mob, that guy's really bad news!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100, Episode 8:
"The Older Brother Bows Destructive Intent."
I recommend the convenient option A with the Blu-ray set!