Guess we ran into more trouble than expected.
You mean you did.
Whatever! You only had wimpy-looking ones to deal with.
I'm amazed this one actually managed to hurt you, Koyama.
He might get special treatment.
No, it wasn't him.
Another guy got in my way, and he was freakin' tough.
What? You're saying you encountered another esper?
Yeah.
His psychic abilities were really strong for a kid.
I couldn't match him in power, so I used your spray.
And where is that kid?
He wasn't part of the mission, so I left him.
This is why I didn't wanna pair up with you.
Huh?
What's that?
Though he may not've been your target,
our orders are to make abducting kids
with the strongest psychic powers our top priority!
If the division leader found
out that you messed up like this...
This all sounds very interesting, indeed.
Just fill me in on the situation.
We'll handle it ourselves.
I'll make sure the division
leader never hears a peep about this.
This is the worst person to overhear us.
Pardon me for asking, Terada, but wouldn't
it be better to bring the other Scars here?
No. I'm all that's needed for this one.
Koyama's an idiot, but he is powerful.
As an enemy, that kid'll be a handful.
If he joins us, he'll likely
surpass me, which is not an option.
So I don't consider this a mission.
We're just gonna go nip a little trouble in the bud.
Oh. And this is a secret, by the way.
Let's say we're gonna capture him, got it?
Yes. Understood.
What do you wanna do, Kageyama?
This is a big organization. Well-run too.
If you ask me,
I think you're going to need somebody
pretty special on your side for this.
What do you mean?
Somebody strong and extremely smart.
You know, like somebody right under your nose.
The Body Improvement Club!
Come on. There's no need for you to play the fool here.
I'm talking about me! So let's team up for this one.
Yeah? You sure, Hanazawa?
That came from outta nowhere, didn't it?
Look, I'm going to end up
clashing with Claw again someday.
So I figured I should do it now while I
still have a fighting chance against them.
And by fighting chance, I mean you.
You get serious about this, and there's no way we'd lose.
How can you say that?
We don't even have a clue where to start.
Please! Let me help, too!
If there's anything you need, let me know!
That won't be necessary.
I'm confident that the next attacker
will be here any second.
But that's no good at all! You should hurry and...
Hm?
Well, that was quicker than I thought.
I'm looking for Kageyama.
Now which one of you would that be?
Let's ask him some questions.
Do you think Terada can win against that kid?
Come on, I'm stronger than that guy.
That's not what I'm asking you.
I wanted to know if he could win.
Well, Terada's always been cautious.
As strong as that kid was, he was still only a kid.
If I hadn't let my guard down, I
could've squashed him from the get-go.
Terada will probably be fully prepared.
So if you ask me,
that kid's probably gonna go through some harsh torture.
Hurry up and spit it out.
I let my guard down!
He's tired.
Why don't you let him catch his
breath and relax with a sip of water?
Do you have any idea how cruel that suggestion is?
You don't have to be nice to scum like these clowns.
But either way, it seems like this guy won't talk.
Guess Claw's elite, the Scars, live up to their name.
Despite fighting the boss and ending up with a scar,
their abilities were acknowledged,
and they became part of the upper echelon.
And then this guy Terada heard about the kid who gave
another Scar member, Koyama, some trouble and showed up.
Tough break, man. You ended
up being captured and tortured.
Now, if you feel you're in danger,
tell us what you know, quickly.
I did! I did!
Everything you just said to me is
from the information that I gave you!
True.
We know about their hideout,
the names, as well as the abilities,
of all the other Scar members,
and a few other things on top of that.
Maybe...
But I find it hard to believe
he'd tell us everything so easily.
Come on, kid. Gimme a break.
What's the hold up?
It's past the time for our regular upper echelon
meeting, yet only 7 out of the 11 are even here.
What a joke.
You've gotta wonder about Claw's management system.
Terada knew about this and left anyway.
So he should be fired!
Need I remind you that you two just showed up?
He's right. Makes you about 30 minutes late.
This group is comprised of numerous
people who have never worked well with others.
As long as we do what we need to
do when we need to do it, it's fine.
Ha! Then I guess you're out, Koyama.
Heard you got your ass kicked by a middle-schooler.
I didn't lose. And I completed my mission.
You really are a simpleton, you know that?
I suggest you stop playing
around with these macho games and...
Shut your mouth, fugly!
I'll kill you, you pierced chicken.
What?
Koyama. Go and take a seat. The division leader is here.
Hope you weren't waiting long.
I just got a message from the boss.
He's coming back to Japan next month.
From what I've gathered, he's
going to pick a couple of you
to be the upper echelon back at HQ.
What? Are you serious?
Yes, but it seems doubtful he'd pick you,
considering how badly you messed up today.
That's right!
Basically, our goal is world domination.
A skilled hawk can hide its claws until the last second,
but we're not like that.
We're more like badass hawks who don't hide our claws!
'Cause of that, we'll steal all we
can, stand at the top of the world,
and lead humanity into its rightful and glorious future!
Sound good? Anyone wanna join us?
Any of you guys?
What morons.
Listen up, you cocky Natural brats.
I wouldn't underestimate the power
of your trainers, if I were you.
Remember, you noobs haven't even
been acknowledged as members yet!
It's not a done deal!
Are you the person in charge here?
No one in our group has psychic powers.
This is a big misunderstanding, so please let us go.
Did you all make a secret agreement to act
as though you don't have any psychic powers
in the hopes that you would be freed?
Very well... You, come out here.
The younger Shiratori brother.
You have ten seconds.
Now show me your powers.
Be quick.
Don't do it.
All right. I understand.
Come. Nobody holds out on me.
K-Kaito!
They're gonna try to brainwash us one by one.
Why is this happening?
I just wanna go home!
Daichi, help!
Save me!
Huh? Oh, no! What happened?
No... Kaito...
Wh-What have they done to you?
H-He's dead...
This will happen to all of you.
Take the evening to reconsider your attitudes.
If you value your pathetic lives.
I see it. It's that building, right?
Yes. That's it.
These powers can't be coming from a child.
Okay. We should go the rest of the way on foot.
Terada's getting away.
Should we go after him?
Hmm...
Considering how badly we beat
him, I doubt he'll defy us again.
It'd just be a waste of time, so let's
continue on inside and save your little brother.
Stupid brats.
You'll pay with your lives for
mocking me and trampling my pride!
Telekinetic control.
Air Whips!
With a range of 60 meters, my powers will
display their true potential here among the trees!
Kageyama! Are you all right?!
Yeah, but that startled me.
Where'd these trees come from?
It's that Terada guy.
He said he used telekinetic powers in the shape of whips.
Say your prayers, brats!
Terada!
If I let you escape me and
infiltrate the facility like this,
my reputation will be ruined!
I've got you now, punk!
Well, I guess you aren't so lame after all.
Oh, crap!
My powers are pretty impressive, huh?
How long can you keep this up?
Kageyama!
I have to focus on keeping these trees away from me.
Do something!
I guess there're a lot of ways to use powers.
Apparently, in the face of absolute
power, technique and finesse don't mean much.
You were finished as soon as
Kageyama considered you an enemy.
This battle will only last one night.
Let's escape.
Come on, man!
You saw what happened! If we defy them, we're all dead!
Can't stop thinking about it. Blood everywhere...
Shut up! Just stop it.
If they're gonna torture me, and brainwash me later,
I'd rather risk my life trying to escape.
Maybe, but Shiratori's still grieving over his brother.
It'll take him a while to get over this.
Shiratori, help us escape from this place.
Have a heart, dude!
Sure. I wanna get outta here, too.
Uh?
Apparently, my younger brother is fine.
We're telepaths, remember?
We can communicate with each
other even if one of us is far away.
I was talking to him just now.
He said that he was shown a glimpse of
all of our bodies, bloody and lifeless.
I'm not completely sure how it works, but I think
that guy has hypnotic powers that show us illusions.
Must be how this organization brainwashes people.
Through fear.
Good thing he chose to take my brother.
'Cause together we saw through their tricks.
So he's alive.
Yeah, but that doesn't change the
fact that these people are dangerous.
And that's exactly why we need to get out of here.
Let's make our move tonight.
Those trainers still underestimate
us, and we should take advantage of that.
Wait. Hey, what're you guys talking about over there?
They must be workin' on their escape plan.
Yeah whatever. They're not gonna go anywhere.
Not the best time for this, but...
What's wrong?
Well, before I tell you all of
my plans, I just wanted to know...
Uh...
What're your names again?
For real? Man! You don't even remember
our names? What's wrong with you?!
You always were hard to read
with that gloomy face of yours.
But that is kinda rude.
Now, now...
Let's put that behind us and introduce ourselves again.
My name is Rei Kurosaki.
And my specialty is clairvoyance.
Pleasure to work with you.
Likewise.
Takeshi Hoshino.
I have some super strong telekinetic powers.
Go Asahi.
I'm known as the godsend who's able
to burn down everything in his path.
By whom, exactly?
I look forward to working with you.
My name is Daichi Shiratori.
Kaito's my little brother who got taken away from us.
Let's hurry up and rescue Kaito,
then get the hell outta here.
But do you have any kind of plan? We'll need one.
And don't forget, the trainers are right over there.
I think they already know we're
trying to pull off some sort of escape.
I'm sure there were other kids
who tried to do the same thing.
That would mean they're used
to dealing with escape attempts.
There goes any chance we had of leaving this place.
Not necessarily.
If they're still underestimating
our powers, then we can get outta here.
Really? How?
They probably let their guard down 'cause we're kids.
They didn't check our belongings.
A spoon? So do you just carry that around everywhere?
Ignite!
Now, Hoshino!
All right!
There!
Oh, it opened.
That was easier than I thought.
Well done, brats. What's your next move? Huh?
Can't wait to hear about it.
Crap. Kageyama? What now?
Let me warn you; It's safer in that cell.
Take one step outside of there and you'll regret it.
Kageyama?
You had a plan for all this, didn't you?
Let's use Hoshino's super strong telekinesis
and Asahi's fire power to get outta here.
Uhh...
Isn't that adorable?
Listen, man...
You can't move something as heavy as a
person with telekinesis. It's impossible!
I might be a pyrokinetic genius, but even
I can't set fire to something that's moving.
Really sorry about this.
I'll take care of it, then.
Huh?
Ha, ha. You'll all be held responsible.
If you think we're gonna hold back on
you 'cause you're kids, you're mistaken.
I don't think that.
The three of you are incompetent, disposable lackeys,
so why would I ever expect you to have common sense?
Y-You're gonna be killed, Kageyama.
Oh, I see. Tough guy, huh?
Well, try protecting yourself with that spoon-bending.
Mr. Natural!
Please, powers. Do as I say. I really need you!
Wh-Whoa... That's crazy!
Guess you didn't even need us to open the lock.
No, we needed to show them that
we were limited in our powers.
This is a blind spot for that security camera.
Let's have whoever's watching think we're
being disciplined for a while and go rescue Kaito.
But even with my powers, I don't know where he is.
Kurosaki.
At this point, we're gonna
have to rely on your clairvoyance.
Huh? My powers?
Can we count on you?
I'll-I'll give it my best.
Oh... Give me a break...
There're some tough-lookin' guys by the entrance.
What should we do?
Shigeo, you really need to think about this.
Wanna blow them away?
But we don't know anything about 'em.
Uh. Umm...
Uh, let's focus on rescuing Ritsu.
That figures.
Okay then.
Oh! What's that technique?
It's the Air Whips.
I figured them out.
Sorry 'bout that.
I'm not sure if you knew this, but it's
easier to possess somebody when they're in shock.
You seem used to this, Dimple.
Are you a pretty dangerous evil spirit?
No, of course not. Right, Shigeo?
He's totally dangerous.
We might've been better off if you'd possessed Terada,
'cause then we could've used of his powers.
All espers have their own mental protection.
As such, it makes it harder
for evil spirits to possess them.
That goes for you guys, too.
Not to mention, I'm in a lot weaker
state of being than usual right now.
But normally, I'm able to destroy
people's minds with little effort.
Honestly, you weren't a big deal before, either.
Don't you get it?! I was weakened then, too!
But why is that?
Oh, come on! Because you almost exorcised...
Never mind, forget it.
All right! Let's go!
Good. The coast is clear. We're counting on you, Kurosaki.
We should go this way.
Let's move.
There, let's keep going.
Right.
Huh? Who're you guys?
Easy! Are you trying to kill him?
I guess we both hit him at the same time.
Listen up, Kageyama.
Leave all these lackey-grunts to me, okay?
Now, the first thing we should do is
find out where they're holding your brother.
Oh, okay. Sorry...
He's so laid back. It's really starting to throw me off.
Identify yourselves!
You abducted some kids, didn't you?
Tell us where they are or you're gonna get it.
Okay, okay. The children are in the basement.
He said the basement.
There we go. That wasn't so hard, now was it?
Thank goodness.
You fools. We can hear you over the radio.
We got intruders. Go capture 'em.
Hold up. Let's contact the Scars about this.
You never know, they might be espers.
An emergency, huh?
It's gotta be him.
That means Terada got his ass kicked.
First it was Koyama, and now Terada.
What's goin' on?
Again, I didn't lose to that little twerp, got it?!
Terada just rushed into things without thinking.
I'll take care of him this time.
I'm delighted beyond words to have the
opportunity to face the little runt again so soon.
Are you saying we should leave the intruders to you?
Yes, exactly! Stay outta my way, you bastards!
Don't rush things. There's more
than one intruder to deal with.
What does that matter?
You're gonna lose again.
Is that so?! You wanna die first, Sakurai?
Stop it. You're both Scars.
That plan is fine, Koyama.
Find the intruders.
But you won't get away with
losing to the same person twice.
Yeah, I know.
At this point, we're up against the clock.
Let's split up and look for your brother.
I'll head off to the right.
Kageyama, you take the middle. Uh?
Lucky us. It looks like the mini boss just showed up.
This guy again? Ah, great.
We meet once more.
I beat the crap outta you, and you can already move?
Well, I'm glad you're doin' all right.
I'll kill you this time, for sure.
And the rest of you.
Now let's both hit him together with our full powers!
We don't have time for all that.
Oh, yeah? Is that so?
What, are you tryin' to reserve your stamina or somethin'?
You're gonna have to face me.
Now die!
He's coming! Uh?
What...? What's happening?
I can't move a finger.
Sorry. Didn't think about that being so noisy.
I see.
You meant that you didn't have
time to try to hold back on him.
Didn't expect that from Kageyama.
Koyama's not responding.
We're dealing with someone powerful here.
Ha! How pathetic.
Let's go.
It's time to show these intruders the true terror of Claw.
Mob infiltrates Claw's hideout
along with Teru and all of his hair,
and the body-possessing Dimple.
They end up facing the Scars, who refuse to hold back.
Think you can win this, Mob?
Next time on Mob Psycho 100, Episode
10: "The Heinous Aura Mastermind."
Option C involves Blu-rays, manga volumes, and events!