Shigeo Kageyama, also known as Mob,
second year of middle school.
In one's life, the second year of middle
school kicks off a most sensitive time.
It is commonly known as adolescence.
Some thrive in athletics.
Some work hard on their studies.
Some devote themselves to their hobbies.
Some polish their talents.
Some rebel.
While some fall for the opposite sex, tasting
bittersweet, and sometimes unrequited, love.
All those youthful desires form
the amalgamation that is adolescence.
And, what was Mob doing during this precious time?
Working as an assistant for a psychic at 300 yen an hour.
The reason for your curse is porn sites!
Wait a second. Porn sites?
Yes!
The jinx you carry on your shoulders is a terrible one,
commonly referred to as the One-Click Curse!
A-A one-click curse contracted from web porn?
They use illegal, 18-plus sites to curse your
shoulders while also burdening you with their fees.
Nowadays, even supernatural curses are being digitized.
Get real!
Who in the hell would believe that giant tub of hogwash?
Relax and keep perfectly still.
I'll lift the curse right now.
No, there's no need to go...!
Your right shoulder is stiff.
The curse really has a hold on you.
If you think I'm payin' for this,
you've got another thing coming!
What the...?
It actually feels pretty good!
Sorcery Crush!
Finishing blow!
This is one of Reigen's special moves.
He relieves the stress from physical fatigue,
and gets rid of stiff shoulders and back pain.
I believe that I was able to lift the curse.
Do your shoulders still feel heavy?
No! I'm sorry that I doubted you.
Everything feels so much better!
May I come again for a follow-up?
That'd be no problem!
Let's see...
The fee for a 40-minute massage is 3,800 yen.
Idiot! Don't call it a massage fee!
Call it the "curse-dispelling" fee!
Two hundred yen is your change.
Hey, here you go, Mob.
Feelin' kinda hungry?
Yes. Thanks for the food.
Master Reigen, you're getting much
better at these massages, lately.
Well, yeah.
I've been tryin' different things to
improve, like reading up on some new techniques.
'Course, it's only effective 'cause of my spiritual power.
Hot!
Such a waste!
Master, I...
I've been thinking about something...
Well, this is a rare occasion.
You don't start conversations.
Well...
I can use a little ESP, and
I'm different from other people,
so I came to discuss that with you
and then I ended up becoming your student.
At the time, I didn't have anybody else
to talk to, so I was and am grateful...
Because you teach me things, and pay me on top of it all.
However, I wonder...
Is this really okay?
That's what's been on my mind.
Does he think his pay's too low?
Or did he finally figure out that I'm a fraud?
What do you mean exactly?
How do I put this...
Rather than waste my youth working after school,
I have this sneaking suspicion that there are
other things I should be experiencing in my life.
Huh?!
Ah, so that's what you're talkin' about!
Puberty! An important phase in one's life.
Is there something specific you wanna do right now?
Be in a band? Dance?
Hitchhike across the country?
No, I don't have anything particular in mind.
Okay. Listen, Mob.
I understand what you're going through,
but there's no need to rush into things.
In my opinion, the Going-Home Club is what's best.
You're goofin' off during the period
of your life you can goof off the most,
and that makes you a winner in my book.
So, I say, just keep on bein' a
slacker and make money off me. Ya know?
Now, hold on a second, Takenaka!
I get treated like a weirdo
just for being in this stupid club!
Take it easy!
I can't do it anymore!
This isn't good.
A club's supposed have five or more members, right?
So what should we do now, President?
There's only one thing we can do.
We've gotta find a new member.
And I mean now!
Maybe Takenaka changed his mind and came back.
That's gotta be it! Takenaka!
I just received a submission
of resignation from this club.
It's...
The student council!
This club... is abolished.
Abolished?
Wow! Already?!
Sadly, I'm going to have to ask you to gather your things.
I recently had a brand-new club
request for a room just like this.
Hold on!
We've only been down to four members for a few minutes!
I'm not gonna let you get rid of the Telepathy Club!
The bond we share in this Club's too strong!
The student council's got nothing on us!
You think you're all high and mighty
because of how you part your hair?!
Shut your mouths.
You pissants don't really wanna anger me, do you?
If you're that desperate to
keep this joke of a club going...
...then bring me a brand new member
by the end of the school day on Friday.
B-By Friday? For real?
That only gives us two days.
Impossible.
Quit your whining!
If we ask everyone we see to join,
we'll be able to snag at least one!
But, that's not gonna happen, now.
The recruiting season ended a long time ago.
No! I'm gonna let this go!
We haven't overcome obstacle after obstacle to
be shot down in such a ridiculous way, have we?!
Uh, president?
We haven't done a single thing.
I didn't even know this school had a Telepathy Club.
It's creepy, so forget it.
Nah, I've got a job, guys.
What's the big deal? If it's abolished, it's abolished.
You should be studying. Entrance exams are this year.
Well, are any guys in your club hot?
I wanna leave time for dating.
I'd be worried about the stares,
and it seems too dangerous.
It's creepy, so forget it.
Sorry. It's creepy, so forget it.
Creepy.
Nope.
Forget it.
Uh, no.
Sounds lame. No.
Guess it really is impossible to
find new members this time of year.
Not to mention we keep getting called "creepy."
Now even I wanna quit.
The president's lost it!
You need to calm down, okay?!
The Going-Home Club...
President!
I found him!
He's not in any clubs or committees, and
he doesn't have any friends or girlfriends.
Salt's go-homer and all-round bum,
Shigeo Kageyama of Year 2, Class 1.
Well, I'd say he's basically right.
Well done, Inukawa!
Please allow me introduce you to the other members:
Kijibayashi, and Saruta.
Nice to meet you.
How's it goin'?
And I'm the president of this group,
Tome Kurata, Year 3, Class 5.
You can call me All-The-Way Tome.
She's pulling out all the stops!
Tome, huh? Hey, what a coincidence!
That's my grandmother's name.
Uh... See? The fates have brought us together!
There you have it!
Please join the Telepathy Club!
I can't today.
What?!
Wait just a second, Mob! Are you
serious? You actually have plans?
Mm-hm. I have to head out to my
after-school exorcism job right now.
Exorcism? What is that supposed to mean?
Ah! President!
I just remembered something!
This guy was sort of famous back in grade school!
He could bend spoons and make erasers move.
You know, like telekinesis!
In other words, he's an esper!
Stop being such a weirdo and just join our club.
I mean, the exorcism can wait a little while, right?
Mob. Hey, so how's it goin' with you?
Uh, Master...
I'm being recruited into a club.
Is it okay if I'm a little late?
Just join and leave, what's the big deal.
No, I have to wait until the student council
meeting is over, then go submit my club admission form.
Wait.
So if I told you to come to work immediately,
you'd end up not joining?
Uh, yeah, but...
Shouldn't I try and keep the
promise I made to the others first?
Then, it's not like you actually want to join?
Not really, no.
'Kay, hurry on over.
Time for you to show 'em how things
are done in the Going-Home Club.
He says he needs me right away, so I'll be going now.
P-Put me on for a sec!
Look, I really need Kageyama to
join today no matter what, understand?!
A girl, huh? She must be trying to use Mob.
He's not really the type to play any kind of sports stuff.
Probably isn't a good idea to force him.
We're not some stupid sports club!
We're the Telepathy Club!
Huh? You're kidding me.
It's a club where we train to feel telepathic powers.
Uh, that sounds shady as hell.
"Telepathic," huh?
Don't play dumb with me!
You know exactly what I'm talking about!
I've heard from a reliable source
that Kageyama has telekinesis and ESP!
I bet you're just using him to solve cases
and get more customers 'cause you can't do it
on your own 'cause you're a big phony!
Shut your mouth, amateur!
Don't you dare waste my student's precious time
with your middle-school nonsense!
What?!
Are you saying that you don't
care if they shut down our club?
We'll get kicked out of the room and have nowhere to go!
Master, the club president is crying,
so I think I should join after all.
Don't be fooled! They're crocodile tears!
Huh?
Bonds, memories, and friendship...
It's not like any of those things will
disappear just because a club is abolished.
They're using you!
Trust me, they just don't wanna
lose their room, their budget,
and their pointless after-school time,
judging from what their club sounds like to me.
See through it, Mob!
If that shady club goes down,
it's because it was damn well meant to go down.
If you understand, hurry up and come to work!
I get it. See you soon.
So, it looks like I gotta go.
Sorry about that. I'll catch you guys later.
Uh... Wait a sec!
Please, just hear me out, okay?!
Now listen, the president seriously
believes in telepathy and all that stuff,
but honestly, the rest of us here
just wanna lie around and goof off.
Right now, we're in middle school.
This is the only time we're gonna be
able to do nothing and get away with it!
Play cards with us in this lazy little
paradise we've created! What do ya say?
You're not gonna find a more carefree club than this.
We have until tomorrow to set
things straight, so think it over?
You're our last hope, Kageyama!
Save us!
Mm...
So I assume you turned them down, didn't ya?
Nuh-uh. I figured I'd take a night to think about it.
You shouldn't drag these things out, Mob.
You need to turn down things you don't wanna do.
Right now, the thing I least wanna do...
..is to be dressed up like this.
Oh, there it is.
Saint Highso Girls' Academy.
It's a private all-girls high school.
And, the clients have asked us
both to meet up with them on the roof.
Right.
Stop! What in the world do you think you're doing?
Excuse me?
You heard what I said! Don't play dumb!
Oh, I'm just a student here on my way to class.
Reporting from the front gate.
Suspicious individual here! Requesting backup!
That's kinda mean, isn't it?
Can it, you perverted weirdo!
I knew this wouldn't work.
But I'm glad they saw through our disguises.
I didn't wanna sneak into the school dressed like this.
That was a close one, huh?
Now hurry along and stay away from that freak.
Huh?
Don't you worry. We'll deal with this phony.
Uh...
Huh?
What am I doing?
Won't I get in a lot of trouble if I'm busted?
He said we were supposed to meet
our clients on the roof, but...
Um, hello?
I've come from the consultation office.
So, are you three the clients, or uh...?
Huh? Who in the hell are you?
You don't look familiar. Transfer student, right?
Huh?
Consultation office?
You're here to see if you can "get
through" to us thugs, is that it?
So annoying!
Do you really think we're just gonna sit
here and let some twerp like you lecture us?!
No, I'm just...
Why don't you mind your own damn business, do-gooder?!
If you don't, we're gonna make you regret it!
Sorry about that. My bad.
Ugh. Talk about a downer. Let's get outta here.
Hmph!
Hello?
First thing you do is get picked on by thugs.
Way to go.
We're the clients you're here to meet with.
Isn't that Reigen guy coming?
He got caught up at the front gate.
Also, you both came dressed as girls?
Really?
He couldn't get permission to
come in, so we didn't have a choice.
I see.
We're sorry to make you go through all that.
The school just refuses to take us
seriously about any of this supernatural stuff.
So that's why we called you.
What exactly was it that you told them?
Students' belongings are mysteriously vanishing,
and we've been hearing weird noises.
Like, a poltergeist or something.
We heard things have been spotted
floating through the air, too.
Yeah.
Apparently a bra started
floating around in the locker room.
A bra?
We're sure it's not just kids playing pranks.
It's definitely supernatural.
So we went online, looked around,
then called the cheapest exorcist in
the area and somehow ended up with you.
Looks like you get what you pay for.
Huh?
Can't believe a guy was trembling so much
just from dealing with some high school girls.
You must be quite the reliable gentleman.
Oh... Thank you.
That was sarcasm, duh!
She wasn't complimenting you!
Are you sure we can trust him with this?
I have my doubts. You seem pretty unreliable.
What's up?
Something wrong?
I-It's okay...
I just have to perform an exorcism.
Now, let us know if you feel anything spiritual.
Right.
Well? Do you sense anything?
Maybe a little.
Is he being serious right now?
There. It's nearby.
Are you for real?
Someone help!
What's going on?
Something was here...
Something was just looking in from the top of the door...
The windows are locked tight.
And we would've seen if somebody
tried to leave through the exit.
I'm going to follow the spirit.
Whatcha got? Anything so far?
So, we can trust you, right?
Right.
You still can't find it?
The spirit is angry.
Huh?
And, if we keep pursuing it, it might try something.
Wh-What are we gonna do?
The basketball team is practicing inside.
Let's end this.
I've trapped the spirit.
Found you.
Huh?
It's huge!
What is that?! A ghost?!
Now you've done it, you psychic brat.
How dare you trap me in my own haunting grounds!
Are you going to try to ruin my paradise?
If so, then this is what you'll get!
Crap! I underestimated his psychic abilities!
If I don't take a hostage, he'll erase me!
You! You smell nice.
I choose you!
Now, get back!
Huh?
It's all over now.
Listen to them cheer. Good for you, dude.
Thanks a lot.
You were pretty reliable after all.
Damn it...
How?
How was I defeated by a loser like you?
And I thought I'd finally found happiness.
Honestly, you seem to be similar to me.
Similar?
The way you get nervous around girls.
You're playing the loser role in
youth just as I did, aren't you?
I...
I finally started to have fun after I died.
I was content.
But I guess that's all over now. Isn't it...
So...
Are you living every day to the fullest?
What's wrong?
You seem kinda out of it. Somethin' bothering you?
Huh? No, I'm all right.
Thanks, though.
Sure. Okay then.
Ah! Mob! You actually showed up!
We believed in you, Kageyama! We knew you'd be back!
Now, hurry up and sign this club admission form.
Huh?
You're already here?
That was much faster than I expected, Vice President!
Well, I had to make a little
extra time to show this room...
...to them.
This will become the club room of
the newly formed Body Improvement Club.
And they'd like to get set up as soon as possible.
What? Now, just hold on a minute!
The Telepathy Club won't be taken away!
Kageyama was about to sign all
the paperwork needed to join!
Seriously?
Are you out of your mind?
Uh...
Tell me, what grade are you in?
I'm a second year.
Have any experience in other organizations?
No, I don't.
Do you have a close friend or
love interest in the Telepathy Club?
I have an acquaintance.
Cram school?
I don't attend.
Do you study?
Not particularly.
Any hobbies?
I, uh...
Don't you have anything at all you want to do?
Huh?
If you let these students goad you into
joining while having no interest at all,
what exactly will you gain from it?
Well, uh...
All I wanna do is live every day to the fullest.
Will wasting time after school
with soda, snacks, and video games
help you "live every day to the fullest"?
If you want to join this club
of your own free will, go ahead.
However, you should carefully think this through.
What is it you really want to do with your life?
What I wanna do...
Do I have anything I wanna do?
Does everyone else have something?
Something enjoyable? Something I'm envious of?
What are they enjoying?
Clubs, hobbies, studying?
Now that I think about it,
hanging out with girls might be fun.
I did have a dream!
I wanted to confess my feelings to my first love,
Tsubomi, and hold hands as we walked home.
Take a look, Tsubomi!
When you make frogs float, they start swimming.
Oh, wow! That's so cute.
I can make the bar all squishy, too.
You're amazing, Mob!
Look!
I'm only showing you these things, Tsubomi!
I'm getting bored.
The red team can move!
You're fast, Akira!
That's it...
If I can change anything by joining a club...
...then I'm gonna join!
Thank you for having me, Body Improvement Club!
Wait, what'd you say?
Huh?
Welcome aboard! Good to have ya!
Thank you!
Unable to locate the whereabouts of
the suspicious individual who infiltrated
an all-girls' school by crossdressing,
the whole area is on high alert...
Hot!
Mob joins the Body Improvement Club.
On his way home, in an attempt to be popular,
he goes to the main temple of
an obviously shady-looking cult.
Are you sure about this, Mob?
Next time, on Mob Psycho 100,
Episode 3: "An Invite to a Meeting
Simply Put, I Just Want to be Popular."
Recording it? That's also a wise decision.