What a surprise.
Guess there are other middle-school-aged
espers besides you, Shigeo.
But, looks to me like he's surprised
to discover another one, as well.
Impossible... Are-Are you a natural?
Someone with powers like me?
And what's that creepy-looking ball of energy next to you?
Huh?!
Are you that thing's master?
No, it's haunting me.
Well, whatever.
There are a bunch of questions I wanna ask you,
but first we need to establish something.
How the hierarchy works around here.
The what?
Now remember... be careful, Shigeo.
Even you could get tripped up if you don't take...
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
What?!
Why do you keep trying to attack me?
I haven't done anything to you. Let's be fr...
You've got him worried, pal.
Not that I don't understand how he feels.
So far, I bet he's lived his life
as a big fish in a very small pond.
And for the first time ever, he's meeting
someone who could be his natural enemy.
If he doesn't establish his superiority right away,
there will always be a struggle for power between them.
But all that aside...
What's with those weird movements?
They're kinda like wire stunts.
Telekinesis.
It lets you move objects around and stuff.
So, are you up for doin' that?
Nah, makes me nauseous.
Using telekinesis, I teleport to my opponents
and blow them away with my Psycho Fist.
But, this strategy I use against average people
looks like nothing more than "weird movements" to him.
Damn it!
Shigeo...
You need to teach this kid a lesson here.
Show him that you're not someone to mess around with.
Come on. Look how he's standing.
He's gonna attack again.
You need to retaliate and hit him with something big, too.
No, I can't.
You're not supposed to use psychic
powers against people, remember?
Don't be such an idiot!
Look at who you're talking about!
That kid's putting his abilities to
good use and living a fulfilling life!
On the flipside, look at you.
You live quietly, one boring day after another.
Do you really think there's anything appealing
about you without your psychic powers?
Listen very closely, Mob.
You and I are different.
We were born with special and unique
powers that other people don't have.
Even so we mustn't let it get to our
heads and think we're special or above them.
People who're fast...
People who sing well...
People who're book smart...
People who're good at talking...
People who can use psychic powers...
They're all unique and you can't put one over the other.
Confidence in your powers is fine,
but you mustn't get conceited.
Depending on how we choose to use them,
they can also be deadly weapons.
They're just the same as knives.
And you know what not to do with them, right?
Point them at other people?
Then, you understand perfectly.
Don't ever forget that.
That's the moral code people like us
with special powers need to live by.
That gets ruined once you know Reigen said it.
Anyway, I won't use them in a fight.
Also, I don't wanna live a life
having to rely on psychic powers.
I'm going to find some other
potential within me to nurture.
Not to mention, I started working out.
I'm gonna improve myself.
You say that, but...
Shigeo!
How'd you like that?!
A telekinetic tackle with all my weight behind it!
You've been given psychic powers
but choose not to use them? How stupid!
There's no reason to live your life
stooping to the level of average people!
Bringing out other potentials when
you have these powers is useless!
Working out? Studying?
Ridiculous! Leave that crap to the masses!
Brains, brawn, and even the law
are powerless before a gift like mine!
I'm special... better than others!
And the entire world revolves around me!
Jeez, I guess there's no choice.
Hey, little boy.
How about we just end all this and call it a draw, okay?
No way. Ending in a draw with a guy like that
would be the biggest disgrace of my life.
I understand you feeding your ego, but
I can't have you breaking Shigeo, either.
He's not going to fight back,
so obviously he's going to lose.
And that...
...won't work.
Dimple...
Most of my spiritual power's been erased,
so I'm pretty much just some leftover scraps.
Even so, I shouldn't have any
problem serving up some discipline...
...to a cocky little brat like you.
Shigeo's someone who can become a god.
He's not some second-rate loser like y...
Huh?
Dimple, no!
I erased that thing with my Psycho Wave from the core.
So there shouldn't be a single shred of him left.
Dimple's been... He was exorcised...
Forget about your club.
Work on your psychic powers instead!
That Tsubomi's sure got a nice ass, doesn't she?
Who the hell are you calling a ladybug?!
How 'bout I send your master to the hospital.
Come on! Listen to me! I'll make ya popular.
Hey!
Want me to show you how to use X-ray vision?
Ha! Fooled ya!
I don't know either, ya pervert!
Just for a sec, would you do me a solid
and let me take over your body?
Dimple...
What's wrong?
Does it actually bother you
that your little pet was erased?
No, not really.
Yeah, I guess you wouldn't be.
After all, it was sort of a
pointless existence to begin with.
'Course your existence is as pointless as his.
Compared to someone like me, you're third rate.
Just a small fry.
You can become big, Shigeo!
I guarantee it!
Some idiots get the wrong idea if
everything isn't spelled out for them.
They actually think they can be someone "special"
if they put in a little effort.
Be more confident!
After all, you're the main character!
What's with that look?
Got something to say?
Tell me, why do you have to belittle other people
by calling them things like "average" or "small fry"?
Huh?
I mean, I just realized Dimple
might've been an okay guy, that's all.
Compared to you, anyway.
What did you say?
Bastard...
I'm going to wipe that smug look right off of your face!
I'll make you submit to me with
the power of my psychic abilities!
So, I hope you're ready. Nothing will stand in my way!
That's dangerous.
If it wasn't me, you could hurt someone.
So, stop.
Are you trying to tell me that you won't get hurt?
I'll teach you to underestimate my power!
So...
You just gonna keep defending yourself?
Look, I told you to stop doing that.
Show me these powers of yours!
If you won't let me see them
we'll have to try something else.
I'll know how much you can take
by administering an endurance test.
Ugh, that hurt.
The home ec room.
Knives are sharp and dangerous.
You shouldn't point them at...
Don't try to order me around, runt.
You'll just reduce your lifespan.
I have no intention of killing him.
I just want him to fight back.
Will you stop this?
You'll cause an accident.
Huh?
You did this on purpose didn't you?
It was an accident!
You're dead!
You're gonna pay for this.
I won't forgive you, no matter what you say!
How dare you...
You think I look like some middle-aged
pencil-pusher now, don't you?!
Huh? I didn't say that.
But you thought it.
No. That's fine.
I'll admit it. It's the truth!
I look ridiculous! It's awful!
But now that it's come to this,
I feel I must know your name.
What is it?
My name's Shigeo.
Shigeo Kageyama.
Kageyama...
I'm Teruki. Teruki Hanazawa.
Oh, hi. Nice to meet you, Teruki.
No, it's not nice.
It isn't as if we're friends now or anything.
I just wanted to know the name of
my enemy before I rip you to pieces!
Hey! Stop this already.
If you want me to stop, make me stop!
Come on! What's wrong?
You've gotta start fighting back!
Stop stalling and face me!
I'm popular and the main character of my story!
This entire world and everything in it revolves around me!
I am the chosen one... me, Teruki Hanazawa!
I don't get it.
How are you able to find all
of this confidence in yourself?
What a stupid question!
It's my psychic powers, of course!
I can control the destiny and
movement of everything around me!
And you are my first enemy!
Now, attack me!
Let's have a test of strength!
No way.
Why not?! I told you it's okay!
Come at me!
Because...
I don't wanma hurt you, that's why.
Huh?
Are you kidding? That's absurd!
It's not like I'm some "Average
Joe" you're dealing with here!
I'm on a different level than the rest
of the lowly creatures on this planet!
Just because you're able to use psychic powers,
you're no better than... What'd you say?
Uh, I mean...
You're kinda goin' overboard here.
Think so?
Well, you're the only person who could make that argument.
That's why your very existence pisses me off!
Hold on... That's it!
I think I just realized why you hate me so much.
It's because you and I are the same.
And not because we both have psychic powers.
But the fact that you have no confidence in yourself...
...same way that I don't.
If you take away your abilities, there'll be nothing left.
You'll be empty.
You're scared of that realization.
No friends, no standing out.
Just another loser who won't leave a mark in this world.
That's me.
Don't you see?
Deep down, you're the same as I am.
You just don't wanna admit that you're
nothing without your psychic powers...
No!
Quit dreamin', idiot!
The two of us are completely different, understand me?
We're the same.
From my perspective, you're just an average person.
Shut up!
He's not using his powers.
What am I doing?
How did this happen? Damn it, it's you!
This is all your fault, you bastard!
Everything was perfect.
You got another high score?
Long as I used my powers,
everything went just the way I wanted.
Look at that shot! Amazing!
We're sorry! Please forgive us!
And yet, you took my world...
I-I made some cookies, if you'd like some.
You... Your very existence...
...destroyed that!
Damn it!
Use them! Use your psychic powers!
No... I won't...
I can't... use them...
...against people!
Is this it?!
What the hell was that?
How many times are you gonna reject me?
Kageyama, didn't you say you started working out?
That means, no matter how hard you try,
whatever that was you called a punch is all you've got.
Don't you get it?
People can't change that easily.
Just give it up. Use your psychic powers.
Otherwise, I'm going to...
Hey! Give it back!
Give us back our New Year's money!
Don't get so cocky, kid. I'll kill you.
Ritsu!
You stay out of this, brat!
Brother!
Bro... ther...
It hurts... brother...
I'm going to change.
No, I won't use them.
It's coming... I'm going to change.
Huh? Hey, Kageyama?
Hey! Wake up! Wait!
Don't leave me behind!
Kageyama...
The battle between the two espers,
Shigeo Kageyama and Teruki Hanazawa,
never reached its conclusion.
As a result of rejecting each other's ideals,
there was no victor, and they were only left
to fill the void in their hearts
with a feeling of deep emptiness.
Or so it seemed...
What is that thing?
Do you finally feel like fighting?
Good!
In the end, you couldn't stay true to your ideals, either!
Bring it! Ultimate Barrier!
You used them! Kageyama!
You couldn't stand it anymore
and used your psychic powers!
You broke down and used them against another person!
So how does it feel?
Huh? Is he unconscious?
What is all this?
What the hell is this power?
What...
My powers are being sucked in by Kageyama...
No, that's not all...
All of the energy in the atmosphere...
Are you telling me his vessel is able to handle this much?
Teru sensed something that must never be touched in there.
Something incomparable, its identity unknown.
You're kidding... What is this?!
What in the world did I awaken?
That's enough, I'm sorry!
I won't do it again! Please!
I won't use my psychic powers against other people!
Oh... I guess...
I'm just an average person after all.
It was then that Mob realized:
He failed to change as he had promised himself.
He caused another accident because of his psychic powers.
He didn't know where to direct his emotions.
His powerlessness born from overwhelming contradictions...
...and the feeling he would
never be able to conquer himself...
Sadness.
What had just occurred
was Mob's meager attempt at resisting his inner self.
Hanazawa...
I-I'm sorry about your clothes an...
W-Wait, Kageyama... I'm... I...
What happened? Who won the fight?
Huh? Hey, look! It's Teru!
He's right over there.
Huh? What the hell?
He's been beaten, stripped, and shaved!
I'm not gonna let that happen to my hair!
Those guys...
You saw it, Kageyama.
It's just as you said it was...
Take away our psychic powers,
and we're nothing more than...
Kageyama!
Oh. Hey, guys.
We were worried about you. You're not hurt, are you?
No, I'm fine. Really.
All right, then. Good to hear.
Now let's all go back and do some more squats!
There's nothing I can say.
I completely lost.
Mob searched for about three hours,
but he couldn't find Dimple anywhere.
I'm home.
Shige?
Glad you're back. Don't catch a cold.
Thanks.
You're home late today.
Wanna eat?
Nah. I'm gonna get to bed.
You seem kinda down.
Did somethin' happen?
If you wanna talk about it, I'm here.
Goodnight, then.
Ritsu.
I'm sorry about that one time.
"That one time"?
You mean when you got super carsick
and threw up into the hood of my jacket?
No... Well, sorry about that, too.
I really can't remember what happened...
...with that accident involving my powers.
I've wondered... Back then...
What did I do to you, exactly?
Oh, you mean when those high
school kids picked a fight with us.
Don't worry, you didn't do anything to me.
One of the punks kicked me away and I got hurt.
But you were there to protect me.
Just forget about it, it's no big deal.
Goodnight.
Earlier today, sometime just after 5 PM,
countless people reported seeing a
supernatural phenomenon in the stormy skies
above Seasoning City.
Among the rubble, there were also
reports of what looked like a person
flying up into the air, but we
have not been able to confirm...
Back then...
Ritsu!
You stay out of this, brat!
Brother!
The theory that this was man-made is gaining traction.
That wasn't him. That wasn't my brother.
I have no appetite.
He caught a cold.
His desire for psychic powers
makes Ritsu stray from the right path.
Having no idea that was happening,
Mob goes on a carefree date with Tome.
Come on, Mob. This isn't the time for that!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100,
Episode 6: "Discord To Become One."
First-press limited edition?
That is the absolute best decision.