It looks like there really aren't
many espers out here, are there?
I mean, all of these people have walked
by and not one of them has stood out to you.
Unless, of course, you're just
not saying anything to trick me.
No, there really haven't been any.
Hm...
Hey. So are the two of you on a date?
Whoa. This guy seems pretty unique...
It's Hanazawa.
Sorry, but... something's come up.
Cool if I borrow him for a bit?
Uh... Sure...
Someone's fighting under my name?
Yeah. It's a student from Salt Middle School.
You might even know him.
He's back that way.
You should go and take a look for yourself.
It's you...
What are you doing, Ritsu?
Shige... What are you doing here?
I'd ask you the same thing, Ritsu.
Must be his younger brother.
Who's this kid?
Who are these people piled up on the ground?
Did you do all this?
Ritsu...
Yes. I'm responsible.
Watching two siblings fight isn't
exactly the classiest thing to do.
Really? This is your doing, Ritsu?
It's true.
No way.
Come on, you're just kidding, right?
I mean... seriously? Brother...
Seriously. I did this.
See, I've finally obtained psychic powers.
Huh?
Whoa, Ritsu! What do you think you're doing?!
Not another word, Dimple.
Tch! He's drunk with power.
This is why I hate brats.
I'm not hanging around for a battle I know he'll lose!
Dimple?
Whatever. I don't need him.
I've got the hang of it now.
Listen, Brother.
I've come to realize something very important.
What? What do you mean?
Look, if something's bothering you...
You do have psychic powers...
I missed...
Ritsu... You did it!
You've wanted them for so long!
Do you remember? Back when you were a little kid,
you'd cry your eyes out 'cause you couldn't bend spoons.
Who would've thought that now...
The situation hadn't changed until recently.
Now listen to what I was trying to tell you.
I've always wanted psychic powers.
And because you had them, I'd always admired you, Brother.
Really? You're making me blush.
But that was just a big misunderstanding.
It was?
I couldn't handle my inferiority
complex and fear towards you...
So I was protecting myself by
thinking it was simply admiration.
More than anything, I was scared of you.
I never knew what you might do if you got stressed out.
We could never even have a fight as brothers.
I mean, that would be suicidal, right?
I'd have no way to protect myself from your powers.
So I did my best to stay out of your
way and not cause any trouble between us.
Now that's just a humiliating past.
I tried so hard for so long,
no matter how crazy or frustrated it made me...
And yet...
...you never worked hard in your life, so why?!
But now I've obtained them.
Now I don't have to be scared anymore.
The delusional admiration is gone.
Actually...
...I've lost all interest in our relationship.
So, this buddy-buddy act of ours ends now.
It's over.
Ritsu. I can tell. That's all just a lie.
I want you to face me!
Hit me with the full force of your powers!
But I guess part of what you said is true...
I am your brother.
And that means...
...I have to help take care of you.
I'm terribly sorry that my little brother hurt you.
He lost his temper, that's all.
Please look past this and be friends with him.
Huh?
What'd you say?
You're the older brother of that freak show?
Yes. And I'm very sorry.
You idiot!
Think that's enough to be forgiven, do you?!
You need to grovel down on your knees first!
Oh... Okay...
Stop it.
Why would you do that?
Tch! What do you think you're doing?!
Ritsu... There isn't any use in trying to get rid of me...
I mean, we're brothers.
Hello?
I'd like a status update.
It's been ten minutes since you reported
that you've found the target. What are you doing?
Thought while I was here, I'd observe the...
What are you, an idiot?
Hurry up and bring him here.
All right, fine.
Actually... just in case, send a photo.
It'd be a real pain in the ass if you brought back
the wrong brat.
Yeah, yeah...
Mocking me...
There you go. Sent.
Got it.
That's him... Shigeo Kageyama.
Like I said...
Confirms the "Awakening Lab's" data...
Tch. What a completely exaggerated name.
It's embarrassing to even have to say it.
Now, listen. Don't mess this up.
The more information we leak, the more annoying it'll be.
No fooling around.
I got it, I got it...
Acting all high-and-mighty...
Let's get this wrapped up.
The tables have turned!
White T Poison!
If you don't want us to beat the crap out
of your brother, then get your ass over here.
Ah. Hold it. You shouldn't do that.
Huh?
I was hoping we'd end this. No more hurting people.
There's been enough violence.
Now, just who in the hell do
you think you are, small fry?!
Only the strongest can give out orders like that.
And the strongest will rule. That's the way of the world.
Just how pathetic are these people?
The strongest one here is obviously...
You're exactly right.
Tch! Let go!
Ritsu!
What?!
Who's that?!
Who the hell are you?!
Like you said, the strongest will rule.
It's such an obvious thing that
sometimes, you forget about it.
Let me guess...
You guys figure that if you're strong at
fighting, you can rule your school and turfs, right?
That's cute. Really. Nice job. You should keep it up.
But this guy's on a completely different level.
You punks don't stand a chance in hell of beating him.
So I'm gonna take him from the fighting grounds.
You can keep squabbling with whomever else in peace.
He's comin' with me.
Hold it right there! He's our target! You can't...
Yaugh!
That's our business!
How dare you treat our boss like that?!
Wait, I got a bad feeling.
This guy's too strong... It's not fair...
You thugs are such simple creatures...
Pathetic.
Uh?
My little brother...
Shige...
Did I hit him too hard?
Well, if he dies, I'd say he was just unlucky.
Hey, tall guy.
What's with that angry stare, huh?
It wasn't angry... I was just looking, that's all...
Grovel and apologize to me!
Huh?!
We're reviewing the scene you were playing out earlier.
I know! All of you should grovel! Get on your knees!
Oh, do you need a little added incentive?
If you don't grovel, I'll kill you little punks.
What a sight to behold!
Look at all you pathetic dipshits!
Let this be a lesson for those who think they're badasses.
And I've got one piece of advice
for the rest of your rotten lives.
Try to live by walking on the side of the road,
so you don't cause the strong ones you
can't handle any trouble. See ya, brats.
Damn it!
What was that about?
Look that's...
Ritsu!
You, too, brat? You want some of this?!
Wait... What are you...?
I wasn't told anything about this kid
having a brother with psychic powers...
Let go of my brother... or you'll regret it.
So, you've put up a barrier.
Oooh, I'm shaking!
I'm not supposed to use these powers against others...
But this is different!
Is that all you got, little man?
I remember now!
From before... He's that adult esper I noticed.
Love to stay and play, but I've got other plans.
Luckily, there are ways to deal
with little esper brats like you!
Telekinetic Helix!
He's attacking again.
I don't wanna grow up and become this guy.
Now, cry...
Huh?
You're so light. You fly like a bird!
It hurts... I can't exhale...
Or inhale... My stomach is burning...
You surprised? My powers rip through your
barrier like an excavator through a pile of rubble.
Shige!
Stand up.
You're gonna protect your little brother, right?
Whoa, holy crap!
That is one hell of a beating!
This can't be real...
Seriously?
He's gonna die.
Brother...
Leave him alone...
Stop hurting him! Please!
Stop it, now!
Just take me! It's what you wanted, right?!
Then do it!
That's a wise decision.
But I don't play fair...
What's with that look on your face?
Think I'll take this opportunity to wipe it off!
Look what you've done...
This is the first time this has
happened while I'm still conscious.
Can you feel it? Rage. Burning in me.
He brought my hands to the ground...
A brat like that...
I can't get away!
That guy is finished. It's over.
You who attacked my brother and me unprovoked...
You did this to yourself, and now you're gonna pay for it.
Don't you ever show your face in front of us again.
Telekinetic Helix!
What?! How can it have no effect this time?!
Unbelievable...
Hey, did you see that?
What the hell happened?
What's going on?
You're kidding!
Energy Bomb!
You're actually making me use my trump card...
Shige!
Why won't he fall over?
At this rate, things won't end well.
Oh! I know! Reinforcements!
Damn it! What's with this brat?!
H-He's strong!
If I don't put up my guard,
I'll be knocked out in an instant.
Yeah! Get him!
Can't believe a guy like that exists.
Hey, look at that! It's... It's a white T-shirt!
That's it!
He's not White T Poison's older brother.
He's the shadow leader at Salt Middle School.
White T Poison!
Taking him on in a battle of abilities isn't good.
I don't have a choice. The mission comes first.
Hey, look out! He's got a knife!
Shut up, you stupid punk!
If you're not giving up, I'll end it.
The next move will be the last.
Take this, brat!
Damn it! This barrier's so powerful!
My knife's not even gonna scratch it!
Just kidding!
What happened?!
I don't like using this stuff,
but I don't have time to deal with this crap anymore.
You've all gotten a good look at my face.
So, I'm gonna have to make you disappear.
O-Oh, crap!
Run!
H-Hurry!
You really think I'll let you get
away after everything you've seen?
Impossible! I can't take him on anymore!
You're coming with me!
He left and he didn't kill us?
We did it!
Yeah!
All right!
Amazing! You saved our lives!
What the...?
He's unconscious, but still standing.
I'd stay away, if I were you.
It's still dangerous to be near him.
You're from Black Vinegar Middle School.
I can't believe someone was able to push him
over the edge like that. That's no ordinary guy.
He left and took Ritsu with him.
Dammit! Looks like we're too late!
This is rock salt from the Himalayas.
It goes great with pasta or meat.
It'll also come in handy for our needs in the exorcism.
Your shoulders feel heavy, right?
Yes. A fortuneteller said there was
something dense weighing down on them.
So they just told her that and took the money?
How irresponsible.
I know just what to do.
Uh, why are you...?
Ghosts and spirits are completely powerless against salt.
First, we'll weaken them with the rock salt powder.
And with this scraping noise by your ears...
This'll be really annoying to spirits
that wanna live in a quiet place.
Eventually, they'll grow agitated and leave.
Phase two!
We'll use the hard edges of the rock salt and do a massage
to loosen up your tense muscles
and improve your blood flow.
We'll place a hot towel on your face to cover your eyes.
This shuts out the spirits' visual interferences.
Along with using aroma oils to maximize your relaxation,
we'll light some incense that spirits hate.
Such a wonderful smell!
Aroma Runaway Express!
This is one of Reigen's special moves,
where he sends his clients on a specialized
beauty trip that relaxes the body and soul.
Oh, my goodness! I feel so much younger!
That's an added bonus!
I'm so glad there was no actual spirit to deal with.
This is the first time I can remember
that Mob didn't show up for work.
I'm gonna have to lecture him when I see him, again...
Brother...
If there's anything troubling you, let me know.
I'll be there to listen anytime.
Shige, somethin' bothering you?
You sure everything's okay?
If you're not feelin' right, I'm here to listen.
Oh, it's nothing. Really. I'm fine, Ritsu.
Thanks for asking, though.
Sure.
Ritsu... Ritsu... I see, now...
I'm sorry I didn't realize it sooner.
Good, you're finally awake. I was worried.
Hanazawa... Where are we?
My apartment.
Dimple told me about everything that happened.
Hey! Looking good, Shigeo...
Dimple... What's going on?
Why were you there with Ritsu?
It's a long story.
And he was kidnapped. Dimple...
Oh?
Are you to blame for all this?
It's a misunderstanding!
I don't know who those guys are!
He doesn't, but I do.
Huh?
They've been trying to follow
me around for a few years now.
Huh? Is that why you live by yourself
even though you're in middle school?
Let me give you a little bit of advice.
Stay away from them.
Huh?
But they've got my brother.
You'll die.
It's an organization called Claw,
formed by dangerous espers.
They want a revolution and aim
to turn the world on its head.
Their ability to function as a group is first-rate
and there're over a hundred who're actively involved.
You're kidding, right?
Over a hundred...
There are plenty of facilities across the world
that are researching ways to manufacture psychic powers.
But the only one to succeed
at such an undertaking is Claw.
Apparently, they take child espers who have yet to mature,
brainwash them, and raise them as soldiers.
They aren't as powerful as us Naturals,
but if you underestimate them,
their sheer numbers will crush you.
You know a lot about 'em.
Got most of my info from one of their
guys who tried to kidnap me before.
Luckily though, that time around, I taught him a lesson.
So basically, they're a bunch of
shady espers from a dangerous group.
Hey, Shigeo, you're lucky. You
could've been killed back there!
It doesn't matter...
Ritsu, my little brother, was kidnapped.
I'm gonna go save him.
Huh?
Do you have a death wish?
No, not at all.
Then calm down and think.
I think I can win.
Have it your way.
But how do you think they found
out about your little brother?
I don't really have any idea.
Ah! I just remembered!
There's a research facility where
people like you were gathering.
As a matter of fact, Ritsu was there recently, too.
Are you serious?
So the information must have leaked from there.
Maybe we should check it out.
But I have a bad feeling about this...
I can lead you there.
Ah! This is terrible...
How could they do this to civilians?
It looks like they're unconscious, but not dead.
Wh-Who are you?! Where did he
go?! That guy with the sword!
You need to answer our questions first.
Now tell me, did you sell Ritsu
Kageyama's personal information to Claw?
To Claw? What's that? Ritsu Kageyama?
You must be mistaken.
The one I invited here was a kid named Shigeo Kageyama.
You're wrong. That's me.
It can't be!
This all started with a misunderstanding,
and yet they really managed to awaken Ritsu.
I don't what's going on.
Damn it all!
And we were finally seeing some hope in our research, too.
It looks like this guy really doesn't know anything.
Where are the other kids?
They were kidnapped. Is all of this my fault?
To think there's a group like that...
All right, so what level of power
did the kids who were kidnapped have?
'Cause I'd like to know exactly
what we're up against here.
Hold on a second. Who are you guys, anyw...?
What do you think you're doing, Hanazawa?
Introducing ourselves.
Come on, brats. Hurry and get out.
Quit dawdling. Keep moving. Don't make me smack you.
Now, don't scare them any more than necessary.
They'll be useless.
Tch.
Kageyama.
You look rough, are you okay?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
But listen, we really shouldn't fight back right now.
Trapped in a suspicious research facility,
Ritsu plots an escape with the good-for-nothing espers.
Meanwhile, Mob rises to save Ritsu.
That's right, Mob! That's what you call a man.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100,
Episode 9: "'Claw' 7th Division."
Option B involves buying the Blu-rays and the manga.