[SEIJI]
Is that true?
Those poor girls.
[SEIJI shudders]
So you're saying that SPR5
is fated to disappear,
just like that?
[rattling in hall]
[gasps]
[footsteps departing]
♪
[YUA]
No way. We're being disbanded?
But why?
[line ringing]
[ringing continues, connects]
Yumiko. You all right?
[breathing shakily]
[weakly]
Yeah. You make it?
'Kay.
That's good.
For now, keep moving.
I'll call you again
once I find Kouta.
[line distorts]
[TAKUYA]
Got it. We'll meet up after.
By the way, we found Geek.
-Since we have a truck--
-[line disconnects]
-[line ringing]
-[TAKUYA sighs]
[monitor beeping]
-[rapid beeping]
-[WOMAN screaming in pain]
-[steady beeping]
-[screaming continues]
[mechanical whirring]
[WOMAN gasping in pain]
[high pitched whirring]
-[rapid beeping]
-[screaming continues]
[TAKUYA]
What's wrong? Have a bad dream?
[YUKI]
I'm fine.
It's just hard
to sleep back here.
[TAKUYA]
Try anyway.
Getting sleep'll help you
grow up strong.
Huh? Stop treating me
like I'm a child.
[TAKUYA scoffs]
-[GEEK] Wait.
-[TAKUYA] Huh?
[GEEK]
This is crazy.
It's just like I thought.
-Geek.
-Takuya.
-Oh, hey.
-Listen. Call me crazy,
but I feel like
we're going in circles.
You see that sign?
It was for an SPR5 concert.
[TAKUYA]
Why don't you focus on driving?
[GEEK]
No, you don't get it.
SPR5's been
gone for years.
They were caught
in the Lost.
I didn't realize.
[GEEK]
This is insane.
I don't know what's going on,
but it's not normal.
We might be
in a major bind here.
Yeah, I see that.
[GEEK] What is this?
It doesn't make any sense.
What the hell, man?
No matter what I do,
we end up right back here.
[TAKUYA] We're able to move
some at least.
But we're restricted
to this general area.
[GEEK]
I think I remember this venue.
Pretty sure that SPR5 only ever
did a single concert here.
'Cause three months
after that,
they had a show
at the Martial Arts Hall
and got caught in the Lost.
This doesn't make sense.
[GEEK]
Hmm?
[HOMURA]
Yua, come back.
[GEEK gasps]
-It's really them.
-[HOMURA] What's with you?
[YUA] Look, I'm not
trying to get ahead
of anyone in the group,
I promise.
I'm just saying that we need
to grow our fan base faster.
Hang on, is this about
the meet and greets?
That's already been decided.
We talked with Seiji
and agreed to stop.
-[RENA] Mm-hmm!
-But--
We just need to focus
on performing at our best.
Forget the promotion stuff.
Seiji can handle
all that by himself.
Speak up, Rena.
If you think things are fine
like this too, then say so.
Honestly,
I'm having enough trouble
just keeping my place
in the group.
The popularity polls
have been rough.
That's really SPR5.
Yua's standing right there,
just a few feet away.
Looks like they're having
a disagreement.
[YUA]
Why are you all so stupid?
Do you want us to get disbanded?
[ALL gasp]
Where'd you get this idea from?
Seiji wouldn't do that.
Maybe you're just stressed
from the tour?
[YUA]
No. Why won't you listen to me?!
Just forget it.
Yua!
-[GEEK panting]
-Geek, stop.
I know that this bothers you,
but we need to focus
on getting out of here.
But we--
[TAKUYA] There are routes
we haven't tried yet.
[GEEK sighs]
[GEEK]
All right, fine.
[YUMIKO shuddering]
[gasping in fear]
[YUMIKO]
Kouta?
[heavy breathing]
[flashlight clatters]
[line ringing]
[tires screech]
[ALL gasp]
[HOMURA]
What's with you?
[YUA] Look, I'm not
trying to get ahead
of anyone in the group,
I promise.
Sounds like the exact
same conversation.
We're not just stuck
in this place.
We're stuck in
some weird time loop.
[YUA]
No. Why won't you listen to me?!
-Just forget it.
-[HOMURA] Yua!
[grunting]
[tires screeching]
-[GEEK] Sorry!
-Hey, what're you doing?
Let him.
I wanna follow her too.
[GEEK]
Yua!
♪
[ALL panting]
[GEEK]
Found her!
[GEEK panting]
Um...
Hey, Yua.
Listen.
The concert's starting soon.
If you don't hurry back,
you'll miss it.
[YUA] Sorry, you have
the wrong person.
[GEEK]
Huh?
Yeah. Could have told you
that would happen.
If I remember right,
SPR5 are celebrating
their first year together
with the current roster.
That's what this show's about.
[YUKI]
Yeah, that's true.
It was an anniversary concert.
But Yua didn't go
for some reason.
[GEEK]
Oh, yeah.
There was an announcement
that she wasn't feeling well.
But it was pretty controversial.
A lot of fans didn't think
she was really sick.
[TAKUYA] Fascinating. Now can we
get back to our problems?
[GEEK] You don't get it.
There's more to it than that.
-[TAKUYA] Hmm?
-[YUKI gasps]
There's no doubt
that we're in the past.
-[inaudible]
-[GEEK] I'm not sure how.
My best guess is that
we entered a rip in space-time
because we got
too close to Lost.
If we change the past,
we'll change the future, too.
I have to do this!
[TAKUYA]
Wait.
If there's a way
to save them from the Lost,
then I'm gonna find it!
[TAKUYA]
Hmm.
If we are in the past,
that still doesn't explain
why this loop keeps repeating.
[TAKUYA] I'm worried about
Yumiko and Kouta.
Let's go back.
[HARUKA] Why has Yua
been acting so weird?
[NAMI] Don't know.
It's like a switch flipped.
[HOMURA]
What do we do?
She's so important to the show.
We can't perform without her.
Yeah, but it's too late
for us to cancel.
Oh, Yua, please come back.
-[door opens]
-[GIRLS gasp]
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Atsuko, you're here?
All of you, listen to me.
I have a message
for you from Seiji.
They're what?
But what about Yua's reputation?
[SEIJI]
The doors are open.
The show must go on.
As for Yua,
we'll tell the public
that she got sick.
No way.
[HARUKA sighs]
♪
[GEEK panting]
[GEEK]
I thought you might be here.
-[YUA gasps]
-[GEEK grunting in effort]
[YUA]
How'd you find me?
[GEEK] You mentioned this place
in your blog once.
You wrote that you liked
the ocean view.
I what?
I never wrote about that.
[GEEK]
But you will. Someday.
[gasps]
Look, uh, this might
sound crazy, but your show
at the Martial Arts Hall
in three months,
you need to make sure
that it gets canceled.
[YUA]
Huh? And why would I do that?
[GEEK]
No use. Guess I should've known.
Come on. You can't give up yet.
There's still hope.
Just find a way to convince her.
[GEEK] Look, Yua,
I'm sorry to bring this up,
but I'm just worried about you
because you haven't been
doing well lately.
I mean, you messed up
your choreography
for the very first time
the other day.
I think maybe you need
to take a break.
And that it might be
a good time for it?
[TAKUYA] So you're saying
Yua's a Tama-shi?
[YUKI]
I'm not sure.
But that's what my gut tells me.
This strange pocket in time.
I feel like she might be
the one who created it.
You have any reason
to think that?
These Tama-shi,
are they some kinda ghosts?
I guess they might've
been human once.
The ones
we've come across so far
have acted like
mindless killers.
Could be that they were
being controlled.
Like you did with Akira?
So you might not be the only one
who can call Tama-shi?
I have no idea.
[TAKUYA]
Neither do I.
But on the plus side,
looks like you're figuring out
how your power works.
Just what did the Agency
do to you?
Sorry.
Damn it.
We're right back
where we started again.
[YUA] You're talking about
our last concert, right?
I messed up pretty big there.
Tried to do a move
I hadn't really practiced.
[GEEK] It wasn't really
your fault though.
You took Rena's place
because she wasn't feeling well.
Right?
[YUA]
You have good eyes.
I care, is all.
You know, other fans
misunderstand you,
but you're a kind person.
I've seen how hard you work.
[YUA] Come on, it's no
big secret that I'm devious.
That isn't you!
It's just a persona you use
to attract fans to the group.
[YUA]
He saw right through me.
I hope you know
that you don't have to act like
some kind of
rebellious bad girl.
There's no need.
You could take the top spot
in the popularity polls
just by being yourself.
You don't have to sacrifice
who you are
just to drive up interest
in the group.
You were doing enough
for SPR5 before all this, Yua.
You're an integral part of
the team just the way you are.
You didn't hear
what I heard!
[GEEK]
Huh?
[YUA] I heard that we were
gonna disappear.
[GEEK] Huh?!
I know that it's true,
'cause Seiji said it.
SPR5 is fated to disappear.
[gasps]
Yua? Yua!
-[YUKI] Hey.
-[TAKUYA] Hmm?
If you could revisit
your own past,
is there anything
you would try to change?
[TAKUYA]
Not sure why you're asking.
But I think most people
would probably say yes.
We all have regrets.
[YUKI gasps]
[tires screech]
No use.
No matter where we go,
we end up back here.
[YUA]
Why are you all so stupid?
Do you want us...
[YUKI] Why do we always end up
back in this moment?
[TAKUYA] It's frustrating
hearin' these kids.
Huh?
And why is that?
Because she obviously isn't
telling them everything.
So, then, maybe that's why.
Because she couldn't be honest.
-[GEEK] Takuya!
-[TAKUYA] Geek?
[GEEK panting]
[GEEK]
I talked to Yua.
So SPR5 is
"fated to disappear?"
That's what she heard
the producer say.
And it explains why
she's acting so distraught.
It's his call.
So if he really planned
to disband the group,
why wouldn't he just
tell them as much?
[GEEK]
I'm not sure.
[TAKUYA] That phrasing.
"Fated to disappear."
No way.
What's this producer's name?
I'm pretty sure it was Seiji.
He's in the concert hall, right?
I'm gonna go talk to him.
Hey, Takuya,
hold on a minute, will ya?
We don't even know
what the guy looks like!
Hey, um, Geek?
[GEEK]
Huh?
[YUKI]
Will you take me to Yua?
[footsteps approaching]
You won't change anything
by sitting in place.
-What?
-Come on.
[YUA]
Who are you?
Hold on.
Wait.
[YUKI]
Stay here and you'll regret it.
[YUA gasps]
[YUKI] You don't want
to live with regret.
Take it from me.
[YUA]
Stop, I can't keep up.
[YUKI] You were on
the track team, weren't you?
So run.
[YUKI]
Back then,
I didn't have
the courage to act.
I was experimented on.
Day after day.
But I never tried to run.
I was convinced
that it was pointless.
[YUA]
No, I won't do it!
[YUKI sighs]
[YUKI]
You have to go.
Or else you'll regret it.
That's just how it is.
So I have to take you.
Or else I'll regret it.
[YUA] Hmm.
[BOTH panting]
[indistinct chatter]
[TAKUYA] Shit. Where is this
friggin' producer hiding?
[YUA]
I'm sorry, but I can't go back.
I said such terrible things.
I was only trying
to save the group,
but everything just backfired.
There's no place
for me with them.
Not anymore.
[YUKI inhales sharply]
[YUKI]
You don't know that.
[YUA] Huh.
Huh?
[ALL]
Yua.
We thought we heard
your voice back here.
You had us worried,
you know that?
[YUA crying]
Sorry.
I'm so sorry. I just...
It's okay.
Let's talk this over later.
First things first,
we have a show to put on.
Yeah. We'll need
all our members.
Right.
[footsteps running]
[GIRLS chuckling]
Um...
[YUKI chuckles softly]
Thanks for the help.
[GEEK crying]
[GEEK] Talk about
an emotional roller coaster.
[YUA panting]
I overheard you two earlier
and you really surprised me.
How did you know that Yua
was part of a track team?
That's some pretty
obscure trivia,
even for a crazed fan like me.
Read it online.
I was a fan myself.
[GEEK]
Wait, I'm not alone?
I've met another Yua fan?!
I think Yua should
sound us off today.
[NAMI]
Yeah, agreed.
Huh?
[chuckles softly]
Right, let's have a great show.
The fans are waiting for us.
[ALL] Time to show them
how the Supreme Five do it!
Aw, man!
All that work and we don't even
get to see the show!
-[rumbling]
-[TAKUYA gasps]
[YUKI]
The sky.
[GEEK] Think that means
we left the rip in time?
[TAKUYA]
So it would seem.
[sobbing]
-Wait.
-[tires screech]
I've gotta check and see
if that was really the past.
Just one way to be sure.
[GEEK] Huh?
I don't get it.
Nothing changed.
Yua missed her appearance
at that concert,
and SPR5 was still
caught up in the Lost.
No way.
Then what was
the point of all that?
What did we just go through?
Sorry. You should j-j...
You should just go on ahead.
[TAKUYA]
Got it.
If that wasn't the past,
then what the hell was it?
Feels like we know less now
than we did before.
Actually, thanks to this,
I think I understand now.
-I get what the Tama-shi are.
-[TAKUYA] Hmm?
That day countless people
with love, hope, and regret
were suddenly torn
from this world.
They never got to tell
their crushes how they felt.
Or accomplish their dreams.
Or say goodbye
to their families.
I think that a Tama-shi is
the unfinished will of a person
caught in the Lost, given form.
The last thing Akira did
was try to protect me.
Okay, then what about Yua?
Even months later, she must
have been full of regret.
I think the place
we found ourselves trapped in
was a world
that her Tama-shi created.
[TAKUYA]
Damn. Tough break.
[YUKI]
We couldn't change the past.
But I don't think
it was pointless.
[HOMURA] This next song
was the very first one
that we performed
with all our current members.
No matter what lies ahead,
the five of us
will overcome it together.
This song's theme is our will
to keep that promise.
I tend to drag the group down,
so that works out for me.
Clumsiness is part
of your character.
I'm not a character,
I'm a person.
Oh! So what does
my character do?
-Cause trouble.
-Say what?
We know we're
a little bit different.
So we wanted to say...
[ALL] We're grateful
for your support! Thanks!
Now please enjoy our next song.
[ALL]
"With Your Breath."
[AUDIENCE cheering]
♪
[high-pitched static]
[YUKI groans]
What's wrong?
[YUKI]
Something's nearby.
[TAKUYA]
A Tama-shi?
Leave it to me.
If you buy some time, then I can
find out what it's thinking.
Speak to me.
State your will.
[TAKUYA gasps]
-[TAKUYA grunts]
-[YUKI screams]
[groans]
♪
[YUKI]
Takuya!
[SOUMA]
My "will?"
Gee, sis.
What are you going on about?
[YUKI]
Souma?
[TAKUYA groans]
[SOUMA]
Been a while, Yuki.
I missed you.
Hold on.
What did you do?
[SOUMA]
What did I do?
Same thing you did.
Come on, let's go home.
[gasps]
[SOUMA] What's the matter?
You just found out I'm alive.
Aren't you glad?
[YUKI] Stop this.
[SOUMA]
Huh?
[YUKI]
Open your eyes, Souma!
My eyes are wide open,
you're the one
who's having trouble seeing.
I get it.
He's the problem.
Not for long.
[TAKUYA groaning sharply]
Takuya!
[gasps] Stop this,
you're gonna kill him!
[SOUMA] You should come with me,
I mean it.
After all,
the two of us are family.
And seeing as
our dad is gone,
we really need to
support each other.
-[TAKUYA groaning]
-[bones cracking]
Please just let him go!
[explosion]
[gasps]
[wind whistling]
-[rumbling]
-What the hell's going on here?
These waves.
♪
[inaudible]
[TAKUYA]
Next Episode, "Suspicion."