[keyboard keys clacking]
♪
[sighs]
[GEEK] Scariest thing
in the world. People.
♪
[knock on door]
[door opens]
[KEIGO]
There's no work for you here.
[KIKYO]
What do we do now?
Well, it looks like this is
home sweet home for a while.
I guess this is
what we deserve.
I had a thought.
Maybe we should tell
the two of them the truth.
[sighs]
I agree, we should.
It's for the best.
[TAKUYA]
You have to eat.
I know you might not have
much of an appetite, but...
Geek is giving my bike
a little check-up.
It'll take some time
to get fixed.
You should try
to rest till then.
-[YUKI] Takuya.
-[TAKUYA] Hmm?
I'm so sorry.
No need to apologize.
Just say thanks.
[groans softly]
Seriously, I can't believe
you made it out of there.
Did you know
that would happen?
No way.
Believe me,
I'm as shocked as you are.
[KOUTA sighs]
[KOUTA]
In the moment,
I just thought, "Oh, wow.
So, this is the part
where I die."
My vision went dark, but then...
[footsteps approaching]
[groaning weakly]
[TAKUYA]
Impossible.
There's no way
he'd save you or Yumiko.
You went against the Agency.
No, you're wrong.
You're really misjudging
Mr. Kaibara.
Is that right?
Then why'd he stop
my investigation?
If we'd just exposed
the academy,
then we could've saved
all those children.
But, no.
He sided with the Agency.
I understand
how you could see it that way.
It's just, I dug deeper
into it after everything.
[YUMIKO]
Kouta.
Please let me tell him, okay?
Truth is, we had no choice
at the time.
Believe it or not,
Mr. Kaibara actually saved you.
[gasps]
He was under heavy threats
from the Agency.
If he didn't comply,
then they would've killed
everyone in the firm.
The only reason
he went against his values
in the first place
was to save our lives.
You think you're frustrated?
Imagine how he feels.
[TAKUYA]
Shit.
[KIKYO]
Here, for you.
Some undies and other basics.
That stuff isn't Takuya's forte.
Thanks a lot.
[sighs]
Yuki, listen.
I know it's probably cruel
for me to tell you this now,
but the Lost isn't over.
[gasps]
[YUKI]
What do you mean?
[KIKYO] Quite simply, the Lost
is expanding as we speak.
[keyboard keys clack]
Considering the energy
used to trigger the event,
it should have expanded
to about this size.
That's unreal.
[KIKYO]
Except it isn't.
So the Lost will continue
to grow until completion,
and I'm afraid
that's just a fact of life now.
Of course it's a problem
that the entire world
will need to face.
The earliest danger
is decades from now.
So at least we can be thankful
it isn't imminent.
[TSUKI] If that hole
had properly connected,
then the Noah Project
would've been complete.
You think this could
really be all Daichi's doing?
[TAIYO]
It must be,
that's the only thing
that makes sense.
He's obviously using some method
to stop the expansion.
[TSUKI] But I can't imagine
he's still alive in there.
[SUZUNA] We've tried to send
messages into Lost,
always to no avail.
[TAIYO] But don't forget
that once there was a message
that originated from Lost.
And you think
it was from him?
Yes.
There's only one reason
Yuki would heading to Lost.
She had to have received
a message from her father.
Let Yuki run free
and have her awaken,
or alternately,
have Souma go berserk.
I was convinced
that either would be enough
to substitute
for the portal device.
But it was actually
simpler than I thought.
As long as we eliminate Daichi,
the portal will
reach completion.
You okay?
I know you said the danger
is still decades away,
but the hole will eventually
swallow everything, right?
I have to go
and do something about it.
My father's calling for me.
Even that message might've
been a trap set by the enemy.
[YUKI] Are you saying
that should stop me from going?
Because if there's even
the smallest chance,
then I have to go.
[gasps]
Okay, then listen to me.
I need to tell you about
the true dangers of Lost.
-[TAKUYA] Dissolve the contract?
-[EIJI] Yeah.
Even after everything
that's happened?
I thought the objective
was to deliver Yuki to Lost.
Well, there's something
I haven't actually told you.
What do you mean,
we have to eliminate Daichi?
How would we do that?
[TAIYO] I've decided I'll be
heading to Lost myself.
Are you serious?
You know those surge particles
are dangerous.
You can't honestly
be considering that.
[TAIYO] All of our experiments
up until now have been conducted
in order to become unaffected
by such a thing.
[TSUKI]
But the medicine is incomplete.
If a normal person
were to walk into Lost...
[TAKUYA]
Okay, sure, I'll bite.
What are surge particles?
An unknown particle
that permeates all of Lost.
It's not good news.
It has devastating effects
on the nervous systems
of living creatures.
If you are exposed to it
for long periods of time,
it erodes the hippocampus
and causes memory loss.
At worst,
it can cause abnormalities
in your mental state.
-After that, you may die.
-[YUKI gasps]
[KIKYO] I'm sure that's why
there have been no survivors
from any of the survey teams.
Not a single one.
-So...
-[inhales sharply]
[TAKUYA] You were sending
Yuki and me to Lost
even though you already knew
all of that, right?
Yeah.
And I'm sorry,
but we can't put the two of you
in any more danger.
You may think
I'm a selfish prick
but this is how I really feel.
The director of Lacuna, Taiyo,
has started to move.
Taiyo?
That creepy guy?
It seems he's trying
to communicate
with something in Lost.
If Yuki moves, he'll eliminate
her without hesitation.
He is a dangerous man.
[groans softly]
Please, I'm begging you.
Don't go.
[sighs]
[rattling]
[GEEK]
There! See what I mean?
Yua's sweet moves just now.
Did you see that?
-[music playing on laptop]
-No?
[GEEK] Come on, you have
to pay attention.
Right there. See?
She fell one beat behind,
but Yua made it through
with some ad-libbing
like the freakin' champ she is.
Cool.
Isn't that amazing?
I mean, she gets some flack
for being devious,
but she works harder
than anyone else, for sure.
She really pays attention
to her surroundings, you know?
I see, yeah.
Oh, if you're hungry,
help yourself to some rice balls
and potato chips.
[TAKUYA] Why do you always eat
those two things together?
[GEEK]
Because it tastes like magic!
Here, try this.
Come on, open up.
'Kay, now for
the rice ball chaser.
Is this what you mean
by "together"?
Just do it.
There it is.
Tell me your mouth
isn't in heaven right now.
You can't,
because crunchy-juicy-tastic!
Oh, time for Yua's solo.
Listen to these lyrics,
they're so good, man.
-[music playing on laptop]
-[GEEK humming]
-[TAKUYA sighs]
-[GEEK] Hmm?
-Hey. Wait.
-[brakes squeal]
Hold on. Be right back.
Thought you might
wanna borrow it.
[TAKUYA] Didn't I just
watch that with you?
[GEEK] Yeah, but it only
gets better with each viewing.
[TAKUYA]
Hmm.
[GEEK]
You have to return it, though.
It's my one treasure.
[TAKUYA]
Sure.
Look at that.
What a great view.
Yeah.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Yuki.
What's the first thing
you wanna do
when life goes back to normal?
Huh?
[TAKUYA]
Well?
Normal life? What is that?
I haven't even thought about it.
Too many things have happened.
Well, unfortunately,
the scooter's not ready yet.
Think you can wait
a little bit longer?
Oh, yeah.
Of course.
[door opens]
-[YUKI sighs]
-[door closes]
[GEEK]
What did you say?!
So, Takuya was an experiment
for you from the beginning?!
[KOUTA]
Would you calm down?
[GEEK]
If that's the case,
then you guys are no different
from the Agency!
-[YUMIKO] True.
-[KOUTA and GEEK] Huh?
Pushing them forward,
holding them back.
You're master manipulators.
Yeah, you're right.
Jerking them
around like that.
It only makes it more painful
for those two.
♪
[keyboard keys clacking]
[machine powering on]
As I thought,
this line is the limit.
[TSUKI]
The ingredients are balanced
for surge particle blocking.
The theory checks out,
so this doesn't make sense.
Which means that we must be
missing an essential factor.
Prepare more test subjects.
But, wait, if we do more...
[TAIYO]
As long as the portal connects,
the Agency will
no longer matter.
-Hurry.
-Right.
[TSUKI groans softly]
[indistinct chatter]
[SHOPKEEPER]
Now, didn't you see that story
last night about cabbage?
[WOMAN]
That it's good for the skin?
Right. Not that you would
need anything like that.
[WOMAN] Oh, you charmer.
I'll take one.
[SHOPKEEPER]
Good choice.
How do you think you did?
Well, I know I bombed English.
Yeah, same here.
World history, math,
and Japanese, too.
[STUDENT]
Oh, that sucks.
[BOY] That's no fair,
I'm telling Mom!
I want to learn piano, too.
[GIRL] You don't have
a good ear, so you can't.
Well, you're ugly, so you can't.
[GIRL]
Mom, did you hear him?
He's being such a brat.
Huh? Wait, Why me?
Why do I have to do it?
If it's so important,
then you tell him yourself.
Huh? Why tomatoes?
[MAN]
Shh.
Ugh! Wait, can you hear me now?
Ugh! Jeez, this is so not fun.
[cell phone rings]
[TAKUYA]
What's up?
[KOUTA over phone]
Hey, what you doin'?
You're free right now,
aren't you? Right?
Would you mind picking up
some tomatoes?
Huh?
[KOUTA]
Yeah.
Yumiko wants to make
some pescatora,
so she needs tomatoes.
She says the right ingredients
are important.
Wait, which tomato
did she ask for, again?
Well, anyway,
apparently she has to have
a certain type of tomato.
[TAKUYA]
I've never seen her cook before.
This is a first.
[KOUTA] Cool, I'll text you
the place, okay?
Thanks for taking care of that.
[TAKUYA]
Hey.
[sighs]
What the hell, man?
I've been thinking
about the lab lately.
About what it was like
back then.
Those were the days.
We were so proud
of being at the forefront
of scientific research,
remember?
It was fulfilling.
Yeah for me, too.
I mean, a scientist couldn't ask
for a better situation
than that.
After all, we got to work
alongside Daichi's genius.
He was a pretty strange guy,
but he sure loved his family.
Every time he spoke,
it was about Yuki or Souma.
Hmm. That's called
a doting parent.
[KIKYO chuckles]
[EIJI]
Just...
Sometimes I find
myself wondering
what Daichi really thought
of his own research.
Remember, science can be
poison or medicine
depending on how it's used.
[EIJI] We are partially
responsible for the Lost,
and that's just a fact.
We have to face
that responsibility, now.
[KIKYO grunts softly]
Easy enough to say,
but will you follow through?
Yeah.
I wanna put being human before
being a scientist for once.
So no matter what happens,
it's our duty to
fully support their decision.
That's the least we can do.
[chuckles softly]
Hmm.
[YUMIKO] You haven't had a treat
for a while, huh?
An occasional break is healthy.
[YUKI scoffs]
[sighs]
Hey. Want some tomatoes?
♪
So, is that enough water?
Wouldn't think so, right?
At first I watered them
a ridiculous amount.
But they didn't end up
tasting great.
Unfortunately, what I'd done
was zap those
tomatoes' will to live.
This is just the right amount
to grow them hardy.
[twig snaps]
Here, try one.
Takuya knew
about surge particles.
That's what
you're telling me, right?
[YUMIKO]
Yes.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
[YUMIKO]
You've decided, haven't you?
[YUKI gasps, sighs]
I say we order another.
Huh?
Just one, we'll split.
[chuckles]
[YUKI chuckles softly]
Hmm.
You've got plenty there.
She'll be able to make it
even if she messes up.
I appreciate this.
[engine revving]
[KAIBARA]
Takuya.
It's your life, you know.
Go live it however you want.
[motor scooter engine revving]
[TSUKI groans softly]
[TSUKI]
We have to stop this, Taiyo.
[TAIYO] No. We're sure
of the balance of ingredients
for the inhibitor drug.
We just need the missing piece.
Something from
a parallel universe, not here.
Since we're from there,
originally,
does that mean
we should be able to enter again
without losing
any of our memories?
We don't have enough
evidence to support that.
Daichi retained his memories
once inside Lost,
that's one piece of proof.
If only we can get
that hypothesis confirmed.
I'll do it.
I'll be the test subject.
[TAIYO]
Huh?
You're sure?
It'll be fine.
I know there's no way
that I could ever forget you.
Tsuki.
Go ahead.
-[keyboard keys clacking]
-[whirring]
♪
-[keyboard keys clacking]
-[whirring]
[beeps]
Huh?
Taiyo?
[gasps] You see?
It's true.
I knew I would remember
you perfectly.
[TAIYO]
Very encouraging results.
However, just in case,
what do you say
we test the upper limits?
[gasps]
Wait, what? Why?
[steady beeping]
Let me out of here! Please!
Why are you doing this to me?
Taiyo!
The hypothesis
has been confirmed.
[rustles]
How is the bike?
Well, it's all fixed up.
Oh.
-Hey.
-[TAKUYA] Hmm?
[YUKI] What's your idea of
a normal life, Takuya?
[TAKUYA] Having a place to stay,
a place to work,
and some friends to be with.
[YUKI]
That sounds nice.
[TAKUYA] Normal is the best kind
of happiness.
I agree, it sounds great.
Once everything is over,
I hope I'll be able
to have that.
I wonder
what's the best place to live.
I'd like a place
with a cool view.
A house beside the sea.
I think I'd like a cat, too.
[TAKUYA]
A big window would be good.
The cat would love it.
Wonder what color
the curtains should be.
Blue's nice.
[YUKI]
What?
Come on, a blue sea
behind blue curtains?
[TAKUYA]
Oh, good point.
Green, then.
[YUKI]
Yeah.
I like the sound of that.
And I guess the furniture
should match.
[TAKUYA] I'll come visit
from time to time.
[YUKI]
Yes, and I'll make dinner.
[TAKUYA] Nothing fancy,
just coffee and toast.
[YUKI] No way,
what're you talking about?
It has to be white rice
and miso soup.
[TAKUYA]
Ah, a traditionalist.
[YUKI] It must be wonderful,
living a normal life.
[TAKUYA]
Yeah.
[YUKI]
I'm determined not to forget.
[TAKUYA]
Same.
No matter what happens
after this,
let's try to remember,
that's where we're headed.
♪
[YUKI]
Delicious.
[TAKUYA]
Right?
[motor scooter engine revving]
[footsteps approaching]
Hang on tight back there, okay?
Yeah.
[TAKUYA]
Let's go.
♪
[YUKI]
Next episode, "Trust."