[drumroll]
-[YOSHIAKI] Three, two, one!
-[AUDIENCE] Three, two, one!
[cheering]
[applause]
[cheering continues
over monitor]
It's finally time.
The thing
we've all been waiting for.
Tonight, Yoshiaki is
going to make
an entire building disappear
right before our eyes.
Are you ready?
[audience cheering]
[YOSHIAKI]
First, a target must be chosen.
Even I don't know
what the target might be.
It could be Parliament,
or the residence
of the Prime Minister.
You can never tell.
It could even be your own house.
Is this cool?
Did we get clearance to do this?
Who cares? We'll figure it out.
This is pure gold.
Go for it, man. Make it happen.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[hatch opens]
This one!
[cheering continues
over monitor]
[HOST] Looks like
the place has been chosen,
ladies and gentlemen.
Now, the question
on everyone's mind is.
where could it be?
My friends, this'll be
the last target of the night.
The Lacuna Chemical Laboratory!
♪
So we'd infiltrate
from our side?
We'll hunt down the principal
they're protecting.
Make him confess.
It's a once in a lifetime chance
to bring down the Agency.
You know, it might turn into
a battle against Tama-shi.
Yeah, I know.
But we don't have
much of a choice.
-[YUKI] I...
-[gasps]
I agree.
I wanna go, too.
[TAKUYA]
Wait, are you sure?
Shouldn't you stay here
with your little brother?
Thanks for that, but, no.
Souma is stable now
and doesn't need me.
[EIJI]
Understood.
I'll notify you
if anything happens.
[YOSHIAKI]
I will now make the entire
Lacuna Chemical
building disappear.
If you live nearby,
please feel free
to come watch live, in person.
Did he just say Lacuna Chemical?
That's really close by.
Hey, Mom,
we should go check it out.
[REPORTER 1] Think the Prime
Minister's lover's really here?
[REPORTER 2]
You got that tip, too, huh?
Yeah, but it sounds bogus.
[REPORTER 2] I'm right there
with you, buddy.
[cell phones ringing]
Hey, something's up.
Across town at Lacuna Chemical.
[REPORTER 1]
Let's check it out.
[REPORTER 2]
Sure.
This tip seems
like a bust, anyway.
Okay, they're on the move.
[overlapping chatter]
♪
-What's going on?
-Go put in a report.
Wait, is Yoshiaki even here?
[MAN]
He's already inside, isn't he?
Dude, look at
all the TV stations.
Take a look behind me.
Tell us, do you plan
to let reporters inside?
Come on, don't be stupid.
As if we could do that.
[REPORTER] Excuse us.
Out of the way.
[helicopter blades whirring]
♪
It has just begun.
[scoffs]
[door opens]
Long day, am I right?
Hey, you guys online,
are you seeing this?
That's right, I'm in.
This time,
I've infiltrated this place
to help Yoshiaki
with his special show.
I'm inside
the Lacuna Chemical Laboratory.
There are actually some pretty
crazy rumors out there
about this institution.
I'm hoping
I might get a chance
to look into those
while I'm here, too.
Hmm?
[indistinct conversations]
[YOSHIAKI]
Right now, there's a live stream
coming from inside
the Lacuna Chemical Laboratory.
[audience murmuring]
That means you'll all be able
to see the truth,
with your own eyes.
Everyone here now,
and everyone watching live,
look for yourselves.
Confirm it with your own senses.
What the hell
is he talking about?
Wait. Keep filming,
this is good content.
But, like, he can't really make
the building disappear, right?
[helicopter blades whirring]
♪
[YUKI screaming in pain]
[rapid beeping]
[gasps]
[machine powering on]
[GEEK]
Holy crap.
Look at this over here, guys.
I mean, there it is,
this thing was obviously made
to hold down human beings.
Check it out.
Headgear and restraints?
This a pharmaceutical company,
right?
Why the heck
would they ever need this stuff?
[over cell phones]
This means the rumors are true,
they're doing
human experimentation!
What? That's nuts.
Is that really true?
I guess so.
-Wait. Did he just say Lacuna?
-Yeah, that's right.
I've already gotten
an informal offer from there.
Hey, Yoshiaki's saying
something now.
I lost my parents
at a very young age.
My brother and I, we were
sent to a children's home...
I'm not responsible for this.
You get it, though, right?
This feeling?
Broadcasting should
always be like this.
It's freakin' incredible.
[YOSHIAKI on monitor]
Unfortunately,
the children who lived there
were used as subjects
for human experimentation,
and the company behind it was...
Lacuna Chemical.
Well, it certainly
doesn't look staged.
This is gonna be
one hell of a lawsuit.
[CROWD murmuring]
Is there any truth
to the allegations?
Was there human experimentation?
Sir, you have to go.
[overlapping chatter]
[RESEARCHER 1]
Hurry up, throw this away.
[RESEARCHER 2]
You, too. Follow this list.
[RESEARCHER 3]
Yeah, that goes.
[RESEARCHER 2]
This, too.
To think, they actually have
the gall to come and attack us.
Stupid pests.
What are you doing, anyway?
Hurry up, would you?
[RESEARCHER]
Right. I'm sorry, sir.
-[door opens]
-[gasps]
You're looking well, Principal.
So, it's you.
What are you doing here?
[GEEK]
Oh, that's simple.
We just happened to hear
that you were
the overseeing director
of this place now, right?
From principal of Light of Hope
to a managing director.
That's quite the promotion
for a guy like you.
Care to take this time
to explain yourself
to the world, sir?
We're listening.
No, I have nothing
to say to you.
The least you can do is
speak the truth.
Tell us, how long
were you involved?
You don't understand.
I've done nothing.
I'm a victim, like the rest.
I don't even get how you live
with yourself, old man.
Think about all the children
who were sacrificed.
[GEEK/YUKI gasp]
[TAKUYA groans]
Shit!
[STUDENT]
Oh, it dropped.
Who were the guys in black?
-Scary.
-Whoa.
Yoshiaki's followers
have increased
by, like, 200,000.
♪
[YOSHIAKI]
Hey, what's going on?
How are things
progressing for them?
It's going great.
You did really well.
Hmm.
Put your trust
in the public now.
[YUJI]
As the records here prove,
Lacuna had been sending
large sums of money
to the academy.
That principal was
definitely hired by Lacuna.
So it seems abundantly clear
that they're both involved
with the human trafficking
we've uncovered.
I have a sworn statement from
that magician with me, as well.
This is our chance to bring
Negishi a little peace.
If we don't move now,
then when will we?
[YOSHIAKI]
Right now, there's a live stream
coming from inside
the Lacuna Chemical Laboratory.
That means you'll all be able
to see the truth,
with your own eyes.
Everyone here, now...
[MEN groaning]
[TAKUYA] Well, that sucked.
What a pain.
This is the end for you guys.
[PRINCIPAL]
It couldn't be helped, though.
We had to have money
to keep the academy open.
What was I supposed to do?
I couldn't just let the children
end up homeless on the streets.
It wasn't my fault.
I had no choice.
[gasps]
Please.
I really was thinking
only of the children.
You have to believe me,
I'm begging you.
[NEWSCASTER] The president
and vice president
of Lacuna Chemical
have both been requested
to volunteer themselves
for questioning.
First Investigating Division.
Kakizaki.
Sorry, but we'd like
the responsible parties
to come with us.
My, you seem awfully
well prepared for this.
So did you bring a warrant?
It's voluntary.
You're free to refuse.
It's your choice.
-[TAIYO] Well, let's go.
-[TSUKI gasps]
A wise decision.
[scoffs]
I'm happy to say you won't get
to look that smug for long.
We'll have warrants soon.
[OFFICER] Yeah, there's
a mountain of charges.
It's almost time.
[overlapping chatter]
Yuki, you have to go back.
-[YUKI] Huh?
-What's wrong?
Souma's condition
has changed again.
[gasps]
-[door opens]
-Hmm?
[YUJI gasps]
Commissioner.
Thanks for your work,
you're free to go.
Uh... But, sir--
[COMMISSIONER]
Did you not hear what I said?
[grunts]
[door closes]
[COMMISSIONER]
My sincerest apologies.
Please, leave the rest to me.
[rumbling]
[TAKUYA]
What's going on?
[static]
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
What happened?
[KIKYO]
I don't understand.
There's a distortion
in gravitational waves
emitting from Souma.
Huh?
But that's crazy.
Takuya, listen.
This is the same as the Lost.
[grunts]
The Lost is happening again?
[ALL gasp]
♪
[KIKYO gasps]
[groaning]
[EIJI]
It's bad.
We have to get out of here.
But you have to save Souma!
[SOUMA groans sharply]
[EIJI]
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid we've already
passed that point.
[gasping]
[EIJI] Kikyo, send out
an anonymous evacuation warning
for the area.
You know, I don't remember
hearing that this was the plan.
It was simply the best way to
make use of the useless Souma.
[TSUKI]
I can't argue with that.
He was very unstable.
The boy can't even seem
to control himself
without an artifact,
which is pathetic.
A failed creation.
Although, when Tsuki's Tears
was destroyed,
Souma was able
to hold it together.
[TAIYO] That's because
she was close to him.
-[SUZUNA] It can't be.
-[TSUKI gasps]
His big sister
acted as an artifact.
It's true.
This time, he was triggered
because his sister
wasn't around.
That energy cannot
be compared to the Lost
that occurred
three years ago.
♪
-[WOMAN gasps]
-[overlapping chatter]
They actually meant to drag us
out into the open, didn't they?
Pitiable.
Fun bit of entertainment.
No matter what happens now,
the Lost is going to occur.
-[horn blaring]
-[TAKUYA] You all right?
[KIKYO] Yes.
[EIJI]
Takuya, this place is dangerous.
We have no choice
but to evacuate.
[grunts]
[panting]
[TAKUYA]
Okay, how can we stop Souma?
Listen, that kid is
a ticking bomb right now.
The only saving grace
at this point
is that he's a living organism.
And by that, you mean...
I mean if Souma's vital activity
were to shut down,
well, then...
[YUMIKO]
No way.
[YUKI]
That's it. I'm going.
[ALL gasp]
[TAKUYA]
You can't do this.
[YUKI]
I have to try to take him on.
[TAKUYA]
That's crazy, it's impossible.
[YUKI]
You don't know that!
Weren't you the one
who told me...
I won't know till I try?
[groans softly]
Hmm...
Hang on tight!
♪
[BOTH scream]
[groans]
Yuki.
♪
Akira.
[TAKUYA, weakly]
Where is she?
[KOUTA]
You really don't have the time
to worry about anyone else.
Not now.
[gasps]
Kouta.
[SOUMA MONSTER]
Don't come.
I hate you.
All of you.
♪
Go away!
[YUKI groans, screams]
Souma.
[SOUMA]
Don't...
Don't look.
Don't come.
Go away.
I hate you.
[groaning]
Little brother.
♪
I'm sorry.
[SOUMA MONSTER groans]
[gasps]
♪
[sobbing]
[SOUMA MONSTER]
Stop this.
Don't look.
Go away.
[thumping]
[SOUMA] I'm scared.
I don't want this.
-[YUKI gasps]
-[SOUMA] Sis, I don't wanna die.
[gasps]
Souma!
Please help me.
Please, Yuki, will you?
Stop, sis. You have to.
[SOUMA MONSTER]
Sis, stop.
[TAIYO] You're saying
it didn't occur. Why?
[SUZUNA]
Even with my power,
I wasn't able to see
this possibility.
[grunts in frustration]
Daichi.
Just how much do you plan
to get in my way?
♪
[inaudible]
[YUKI]
Next Episode, "Fate."