[indistinct conversations]
[TAKUYA]
It's true.
My friend here
touched her thigh.
But, come on. 100,000 yen
for a single bottle of beer?
Sorry, man,
but those are the rules.
See this?
To be fair,
that's really fine print.
'Kay, you win.
-I'll pay the 140K.
-Seriously?
In exchange, he gets 150K.
For medical bills and glasses.
You think you're
pretty hilarious, huh?
[door opens]
[KAIBARA] All right, all right,
that's enough.
Do me a favor
and take the hit this time.
[MAN 1]
Who the hell are you?
[MAN 2 sighs] Sorry,
we can't do that, Mr. Kaibara.
We've got rules in this place
for a reason.
I heard you guys
are expecting a pretty big deal
to go down real soon.
I'd be happy to keep that
from the police, though.
Yeah, I'd appreciate that.
Get back to work.
[scoffs]
Who are you?
You up for some ramen?
[YOSHIAKI] Lacuna is
a major organization, though.
I never would've thought
they'd be connected
to that little facility.
But it's true. So the police
can't do anything.
We'll need to find some really
solid evidence to crush them.
[KEIGO] The problem is
that the academy
is in the lock-down district,
so that's tricky.
It's gonna be helpful
having you two
since you know
what it's like inside.
[TAKUYA]
Is that what you really believe?
You honestly think
that's the only way to live?
Wow. You digging
a new flower bed?
[GEEK]
It's an underground shelter.
Who knows what's next,
you know what I mean?
Better to prepare.
Oh, the anemone. Beautiful.
[EIJI]
Yeah, they've grown well.
Did something happen?
Though very small, there was
a change of gravitational waves.
[EIJI]
Hmm.
Just as I thought.
[YUMIKO]
Here.
Thank you.
Hey, Yumiko?
Didn't Takuya come from the same
detective agency as you?
[YUMIKO]
Yes, until the Lost.
[YUKI] So, has he always
been like this?
[YUMIKO] I bet you're curious
about his past.
I'd be happy
to tell you what I know.
He has a very good reason
for being a lone courier,
now, that's for sure.
He has his reasons
for being more than
a little hung up
on contracts, too.
We're a pretty small agency.
But it makes us close,
like family.
Yumiko, Takuya,
take care of him, would you?
[YUMIKO]
Sure.
[KAIBARA] Well, have fun
but don't overdo it.
Take that last part
with a grain of salt.
This work requires dedication.
It's a dangerous job,
and sometimes we have
to operate outside the law.
[groaning softly]
Give me 50 more.
I don't know whether
it was sheer perseverance
or innate talent,
but Takuya's skills
got stronger and stronger.
Before anyone knew it,
he was the ace of our agency.
[KAIBARA] She's got some mileage
on her, but she runs great.
Take care of her.
You want me to ride a scooter?
Detectives and scooters
go together. Here.
Don't worry, I'll take care
of things here. Cool?
Sorry, we can't, Mr. Kakizaki.
Come on, help me out.
Let's go on patrol.
We can only give you an hour.
[YUJI]
Got it. Thanks.
[KAIBARA]
An undercover investigation.
The Ministry of Health,
Labor, and Welfare
wants to investigate
a possible case of abuse
at a certain orphanage.
Poor children.
Well, I'm obviously perfect
for this gig.
I'm great with people
and kids freaking love me,
you have no idea.
Nope, not this time. Takuya.
Will you take it?
Yes.
[KAIBARA]
You'll be infiltrating
the Light of Hope Academy
for Disabled Children.
[YOSHIAKI]
Look how run down it is.
[KEIGO] It's been three years
since the Lost.
The whole lock-down district
looks exactly like this.
I hope there's still
some evidence left in there.
Let's go.
-[high-pitched static]
-Huh?
[groaning]
[breathing heavily]
[TAKAHIKO]
Take this!
Continuous Fire Attack.
Takahiko?
Wait, where did
this kid come from?
Hey, where did you go?
You didn't clean
the rabbit hutch again.
I'm gonna tell
Mama Hinako on you.
[gasps in fear]
A noisy girl has appeared.
Block it out.
Karin.
Big Brother Takuya.
Did you buy us
some more bananas?
Naoya.
[HINAKO]
Takuya.
I'm glad you're back.
[TAKUYA]
Ayano. Hinako.
Everyone, the baby chicks
have finally hatched,
if you'd like to see.
Oh, they have? Yay!
[TAKAHIKO]
Can we play with them?
No, they were just born,
so we can't touch them
quite yet.
Would you like
to join us, Takuya?
[TAKAHIKO] She means
she's real lonely without you,
Big Brother Takuya.
I don't...
We'll go on ahead inside.
So, then, are all of 'em...
That's right. Tama-shi.
Both her and the kids.
They'd all gone to see
the circus together.
And they got caught in the Lost.
...disturb them too much.
Light of Hope Academy
for Disabled Children.
Turns out they actually have
a connection with you.
The things that were happening
to them were similar.
Huh. You're talking about
the suspected child abuse,
aren't you?
It was Takuya's mission
to find the truth,
and he took that mission
very seriously.
[TAKAHIKO] Are there really
chicks up there?
Oh, look.
They're peeking out now.
-[chirping]
-[NAOYA] Aw, they're so cute!
-Shh. Stop being so loud.
-[NAOYA] Right.
[KEIGO] It's an entire world
made by Tama-shi.
Sheesh. Anyone know
how to get out of here?
As far I know, the only way out
is for the Tama-shi
who made it to be released
from their regret somehow.
[YOSHIAKI]
So in order to leave,
first, we need to figure out
who created
this world and why,
do I have that right?
It's me.
[TAKUYA]
Listen to that chirping.
They're just like all of you.
[NAOYA] Hey, that's not
what we sound like.
Yeah, there is no way
we're that noisy.
That's not what I meant.
I'm saying that soon,
you'll fly away from the nest
to wherever you want.
You really think so?
[TAKUYA]
Sure. Once you're all adults.
You'll have hopes and dreams,
and you'll make 'em come true.
-[TAKAHIKO] Really?
-[TAKUYA] Yeah.
I'm positive.
Ayano?
Then, I wanna be
a famous soccer player.
I've always wanted
to be a veterinarian.
What about you?
Huh? Well, I...
I do love math,
so if I have to choose,
I'd be a math teacher.
But the principal and
Mama Hinako both told us
we aren't supposed
to think like that, so...
Why is that?
It's the academy's philosophy.
One must be of use to people.
More than what one wants.
We teach them
how to live for others.
A noble existence,
rather than only
looking out for yourself.
Well, the principal always
told me the same thing.
I just realized.
That Hinako girl was
at the academy when I was here.
[TAKUYA] So she's a product
of this place herself.
[YOSHIAKI]
All the way to the end.
So what that really means,
is that this school
was her entire world.
[KEIGO] The academy was
not doing well financially.
If Lacuna was giving them
monetary support,
we can assume there should be
some hidden record books
somewhere.
We'll search
with a fine-toothed comb.
[gasps]
-Hey, kiddo.
-For you.
I made it from the anemones
in the garden.
Beautiful.
Your dream was to own
a flower shop, right?
♪
Thank you.
Looks like they buy you as you.
Well, that's good to know.
At least we can be sure
we've got that option.
But let's avoid contact.
Come on.
[VOICEMAIL] The number
you have dialed is unavailable,
or currently in an area
that cannot be reached
from your location.
Why does it keep doing this?
We're about to run
out of time here, guys.
♪
[TAKAHIKO]
I'll take that one.
Cool. I'll have seconds, too.
[YOSHIAKI]
Looks like it's snack time.
Same as when I was here.
Interesting.
I was always sent out
to buy dinner supplies
at this time.
Is everyone finished
with your snacks?
Then you know
what comes next.
[ALL]
'Kay!
[sighs]
I've noticed that your grades
have been slipping a bit, Ayano.
Why don't you take
two more of the red ones?
[AYANO]
All right.
Hey, do you know what
the Japanese anemone symbolizes?
No.
Patience.
[shudders]
Man, that's messed up.
It was just a part of daily life
for everyone here, though.
[YOSHIAKI]
Takuya.
[TAKUYA]
Shit!
Why didn't I figure out
what was going on?
It's not your fault.
[ZENSHIRO]
Their future dreams?
Who put them up
to writing this rubbish?
[HINAKO]
Oh, um...
It's the principal.
It was Takuya, right?
So unnecessary.
I'm afraid he doesn't seem
to fit in very well with us.
I certainly hope you haven't
been influenced by that man.
[gasps]
Of course not.
[ZENSHIRO] Do not disappoint me,
understand?
Never, sir.
After all, you were the only one
who would take me in.
I was an unchosen failure
of no use,
and still, you gave me
a place to live.
Good, I feel like
we're on the same page.
♪
[YUMIKO]
At the academy,
there was this special,
gifted class offered,
but only some kids
were picked to go there.
It was considered
an honor to be chosen.
[bus engine revving]
[TAKUYA]
So, Naoya was chosen today?
Where do the chosen children go
every week, anyway?
[HINAKO] They're taken to meet
potential foster parents.
I think I might like
to go with them next time.
I doubt the principal
will give you permission.
[TAKUYA]
Why not?
Everything's above the board,
isn't it?
Both my brother and I
were chosen to go.
That was when my brother's
power manifested.
I bet that's why he left.
So he wouldn't be used
by the agency.
[TAKUYA]
Tell me, Hinako,
all I want is
these kids' happiness.
[HINAKO] They are happy.
How could they not be?
[TAKUYA]
Huh?
HINAKO[] Those children
have been tossed aside.
By everyone.
Even their own parents decided
that they didn't want them.
And now, don't you see?
They actually get to be
of real use to someone.
Is there any greater happiness?
[TAKUYA]
Is that what you really believe?
You honestly think
that's the only way to live?
Yes, I do.
[TAKUYA]
Hmm.
[gasps]
[TAKUYA grunts]
Why?
Why didn't I face
her down over this?
You didn't know.
Remember,
this is all in the past.
Think of what we can do now.
Okay?
Human experiments?
So it was the same thing
that was being done to me.
[YUMIKO] Takuya had already
started figuring out the truth.
He was so close,
he really was.
But then...
[TAKUYA] What do you mean,
"the investigation's closed"?
Just exactly what I said.
It's no longer necessary
to have you at the academy.
[TAKUYA]
Why not?
[KAIBARA]
It's already been decided.
[TAKUYA]
I can't accept this.
Not when I'm so close
to the truth.
[KAIBARA]
Remember something, Takuya.
We aren't the police, okay?
We're no heroes of justice.
Mr. Kaibara, wait!
[grunts in frustration]
Why so suddenly?
Honestly, I've never
understood that,
Mr. Kaibara's change of heart.
Regardless, though, orders from
above are always absolute.
Particularly with
dangerous missions like this.
That's the deal.
I can't imagine
Takuya taking orders obediently.
That's certainly true
of the Takuya we know now.
[YOSHIAKI] So detectives
do the same thing
as thieves, sometimes.
Please shut up.
I can't hear.
[gasps]
Wait, why is Mr. Kaibara here?
Where are you going?
Stop, I said I can't hear.
[KAIBARA] He's hot-blooded,
there's no doubt.
But I know him, and I think
it must've been something
really worth looking into.
[ZENSHIRO]
You've got to be kidding me.
Look around.
There's nothing to find here.
[KAIBARA] So, what's going
to happen to the children?
[ZENSHIRO] That's not for me
to decide. It's out of my hands.
Bullshit.
[KARIN] Aren't they pretty?
This one is my favorite.
Aw!
♪
You okay?
It shouldn't have mattered
that our agency pulled out.
I should've kept
investigating this anyway.
Look at what we got.
Someone gave
the school circus tickets.
Would you like to come with us?
That was the day.
What do you mean?
What day? The Lost?
Sorry, I won't be able
to go with you.
Huh?
I'm submitting my resignation.
Today will be my last day here.
So the superiors
said something.
That's too bad.
I was really hoping
you'd be able to join us.
Now that I think of it, we've
never gone anywhere together
in the entire time
you've been here, have we?
[TAKUYA]
Sorry.
[TAKAHIKO]
Hey!
Come on, let's go already!
Well, I guess this is goodbye.
Our time seemed so short.
♪
[TAKUYA sighs]
[groans]
[TAKUYA]
Wait!
You can't go.
-Ooh!
-He likes her.
[KARIN]
Are you gonna get married?
Sorry. I'm, uh...
Forgive me.
[HINAKO]
Why are you apologizing?
[gasps]
You weirdo.
Know what?
I've finally decided something.
Huh?
Once we get back
from the circus,
I'm going to tell the children
the truth about everything.
I want them to know...
their life is theirs,
with unlimited possibilities.
So...
You should know
it's thanks to you.
By the way...
please clean out the birdhouse
before you go, would you?
Goodbye, Hinako.
♪
[YOSHIAKI]
Well, looks like we're back.
[TAKUYA groans]
Are you okay?
[TAKUYA sobbing]
[YUMIKO]
After that, Takuya was out.
He quit the agency.
[engine starts]
But even after everything,
he still rides that scooter.
I think somewhere,
deep in his heart,
he still wants to believe
in Mr. Kaibara.
What exactly does it mean
that we're back?
Was Miss Hinako
freed from her regret?
Is that what happened?
[grunts]
The documents in the safe were
nothing but a bunch of trash.
This was a total waste of time.
[HINAKO]
By the way...
[gasps]
[HINAKO] ...please clean out
the birdhouse
before you go, would you?
♪
What are you doing with that?
Holy crap!
It's the cash book
she kept a record of.
These are deposits
from Lacuna.
[YOSHIAKI] That means
we have solid evidence
that the academy
and Lacuna were connected.
We can attack
the Agency with this.
Now all we really need
is a living witness.
I'll do that.
I can take on that role.
Think about it,
it makes sense.
The public will listen to me
because they know me.
Yoshiaki, are you sure?
I mean, you might lose
everything you have.
No, I know what I need to do.
And this is it.
Also, I think this is what
my brother would want.
You got it. Thank you.
Huh?
[KEIGO]
Takuya?
♪
[gasps]
Look who’s back.
[TAKUYA]
Yep.
Yuki, I'm sorry, but there's
something I need to do
before we head to Lost.
Guess it can't be helped.
[TAKUYA]
Huh?
It's fine, I'm sure
you'll explain it all later.
Hmm.
Sorry.
You don't have to apologize,
just say "thank you." Jeez.
Right.
Hmm?
What's wrong?
[YUKI] I'm sure I've seen
this person before.
At the research facility,
multiple times.
Wait, what did you say?
I thought the Agency
disposed of him.
They sheltered him instead?
Takuya.
[grunting]
♪
[YUKI]
Next episode, "Choice."