[soft clicking]
[CROWD cheering]
[HOMURA] Everybody feeling
good out there?
So much love!
You guys are amazing!
We hope you're having
the time of your lives tonight.
'Cause we're gonna keep singing
our hearts out for you!
Are you ready for the next one?
Here we go!
♪
[YUKI]
Those unending ordinary days.
The existence
known as life itself.
‐[AKIRA] Miss Yuki!
‐[YUKI gasps]
[people screaming]
[YUKI]
If suddenly, one day,
without any warning,
it were all to disappear...
[YUA]
Everyone, run!
[screaming continues]
[YUKI]
The spirit of those people,
their unique memories
and experiences...
Miss Yuki!
Akira!
[YUKI]
Where would they all end up?
Yuki.
Souma.
[explosion]
‐[door opens]
‐[alarm blaring]
[footsteps approaching]
[BLACK COAT A]
Get up.
[YUKI whimpers softly]
Hurry up, there's no time to‐‐
‐[choking]
‐[BLACK COAT B yells]
‐[BLACK COAT A screams]
[panting]
[YUKI shudders]
Come on.
[alarm blaring continues]
[inhales sharply]
Well, shit.
[TAKUYA grunting]
‐[explosion]
‐[glass shattering]
[YUKI gasps]
[TAKUYA grunts]
Look, I'm just
the courier, okay?
As soon as I can deliver you,
my contract ends.
Just keep quiet
till then, got it?
‐[helicopter blades whirring]
‐[YUKI gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Are you kidding me?
♪
[TAKUYA sighs]
Guess we're doing this.
[gasps, whimpers]
[gasps]
♪
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
[TAKUYA grunting]
[grunting]
[YUKI gasps]
[YUKI whimpers]
[energy humming]
Huh?
[MONK grunts]
[groaning]
[tires screeching]
[CITIZEN #1]
Stupid bastard!
What the hell are you doing?!
‐[CITIZEN #2] That was crazy!
‐[panting]
The hell?
[horns honking]
‐You okay?
‐[YUKI panting]
[honking continues]
♪
[indistinct yelling]
Come on. Shit.
♪
‐[gasps]
‐[grunts]
Come on!
Hurry!
[TAKUYA grunts]
‐[beeping]
‐[inhales sharply]
How?
[BLACK COAT on radio] Find them!
They should still be nearby.
[beeping]
[steady beep]
[EIJI] She's within
normal values for now.
Hey, man, who the hell
were those guys?
I was aware
the Agency was dangerous,
but no one told me something
like that would happen.
[EIJI]
Check her brain waves.
She's still in
a state of confusion.
We should really
let her rest now.
[EIJI]
No need.
Besides, I've got to figure out
what was done to her
at that facility.
Yeah, that's
a real good question.
What do you know?
♪
[keyboard keys clacking]
[EIJI]
The Tama‐shi.
[TAKUYA]
Hmm?
‐And what is that?
‐[YUKI gasps]
[EIJI] It seems they are
the victims of the Lost.
Three years ago.
[TAKUYA scoffs]
So, what are you saying?
I was attacked
by some kinda ghost?
No. To begin with, no one's
ever found the victims' bodies.
We've only ever
called them Tama‐shi
for the sake of convenience.
[gasps]
[EIJI]
That girl?
Is the only
known survivor of Lost.
That's why she's important.
[gasps]
[EIJI]
She's a valuable sample.
One we're lucky to get back.
Your bedside manner
needs some work.
Yuki, we met before.
Do you remember?
[EIJI] Probably not,
she was pretty young.
Fascinating stuff.
Either way, my job here's done.
I don't want to get
caught up in anything.
Don't forget
to transfer the funds over.
[EIJI]
Wait.
I know you just got back
and the timing sucks.
But there's another job
for you if you want it.
[TAKUYA]
Huh?
[EIJI] I need you to go
to the missing city, Lost.
[TAKUYA scoffs]
Are you kidding?
That whole area's been
quarantined by the government.
[EIJI] Yes. They've been
secretly investigating it
since the disaster.
But there's been no progress
for the past three years.
No human has ever returned
from that spot alive.
But robots can't be used
for the investigations.
Rumor is, all forms of
communication within the area
have been completely blocked.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I thought that place
was just a big void
of nothingness now.
[KIKYO]
That's not quite accurate.
The state of nothingness
exists there.
[TAKUYA]
How's that different?
Here, take a look at this.
It's a message.
In quantum encryption.
[TAKUYA]
"Yuki, I'm waiting at Lost."
[YUKI gasps]
What the hell is that?
[EIJI]
This is from Yuki's father.
[YUKI inhales sharply]
My father's alive?
Are you sure?
[EIJI]
We haven't confirmed it yet.
As you know, three years ago,
he tried to stop the occurrence
of Lost and got caught up in it.
And now,
seemingly out of the blue,
we get this message.
[YUKI sobbing]
[EIJI] Either way,
going to Lost should
bring you some answers.
Huh? So, the job, is it her?
Yes, that's right.
I want you to deliver
Yuki to Lost.
[TAKUYA sighs]
[EIJI]
Sorry, Takuya.
You're the only one I can ask.
[TAKUYA] You'd better make it
worth my while.
[YUKI]
Hmm?
[EIJI]
Don't worry, it will be.
♪
[pop music playing]
[MAN humming along]
Wonder where I should
hold the RL meeting
since it'll just be me
again this year.
[chuckles]
‐[vehicle approaching]
‐Hmm?
‐[screams]
‐[tires screeching]
‐Geek, what's up?
‐[GEEK] Takuya!
Jeez. You almost gave me
a freakin' heart attack!
[TAKUYA] You're beautiful when
you're angry, you know that?
[GEEK]
Would you shut up?
Can you look at her for me?
[GEEK]
Yeah, no prob.
Hmm?
Are you kidding me?
What's with the girl?
Have you seriously resorted
to kidnapping?
[TAKUYA]
Well, something like that.
[GEEK] I should have her
fixed up in about 30 minutes.
There's some food over there
if you're hungry.
[TAKUYA]
Thanks, I'll pass.
[GEEK] So, where are you off to
with that cutie in tow, anyway?
Is it a date?
I'm so jealous I could puke.
Ugh, long story.
The short of it is,
I'm headin' to Lost.
‐[GEEK gasps]
‐[tool clangs]
[GEEK whispering]
Are you nuts?
Come outside.
We need to talk in private.
Dude, that's insane.
You're really serious?
She's the lone survivor of Lost?
It sounds crazy, but, yeah.
Listen, man, I know
you've never been the type
to get blinded
by a big paycheck or anything,
so I don't know
why you're doing this,
but it's too dangerous.
Besides, you're already
injured as it is.
[TAKUYA]
Just part of the job.
[GEEK]
I get it, but this is...
[TAKUYA] I follow through
on my contracts.
Sort of a personal policy.
No matter what they might be,
my packages get delivered.
[GEEK]
I know. I respect that.
But "personal policies"
be damned,
you're walking
into your own grave.
Tell me why!
Why would you go
that far for some girl?
She's a stranger, right?
Look, stranger or not,
she's just a package.
[footsteps receding]
[BOTH gasp]
Damn it.
♪
[YUKI]
Oh, Father. Souma.
Akira.
It's been three years.
Tonight, demonstrations
are being held
to honor the victims of Lost.
We head there now.
[PROTESTER]
The government should announce
the truth to the public!
[PROTESTERS]
Tell the public the truth!
[WOMAN]
I can see it.
The alignment of your stars.
The fate that you bear upon
your shoulders is a heavy one.
[cell phone ringing]
Takuya, looks like
the Agency's expanded
their search to this area.
We're on the move now,
just to be safe.
Find a route to Lost and head
that way as soon as possible.
Well, yeah, I'd love to do that.
But now the girl is gone.
[BOTH gasp]
[EIJI]
What?!
‐[keys clacking]
‐[rapid beeping]
[GEEK] Crap, where the heck
did she go?!
What did I do? Did I say
something I shouldn't have?
[TAKUYA] An acquaintance of mine
is looking for her.
I'll head to Lost
as soon as she's found.
[water spritzing]
[cell phone ringing]
Hmm.
Hey.
[YUMIKO]
It's been a long time, Takuya.
[TAKUYA]
Yeah, sorry, but I was hoping
you'd check
something out for me.
Oh, yeah, what's that?
I need you to tell me
the best way to get into Lost.
[YUMIKO]
What? Why are you going there?
What in the world are you even‐‐
Please, Yumiko.
[sighs]
[YUMIKO]
Of course.
I know I have data
from a previous search.
I'll send it over.
[TAKUYA]
Thanks. I owe you one.
[beeps]
That jerk.
He really hasn't changed at all.
♪
It's a dangerous path you're on.
You should turn back.
If not...
I can't turn back, though.
Nowhere to go.
Did you really think
you could do this on your own?
Get on.
Come on, hurry up.
You're going, right?
You're gonna go find your dad?
Look, you don't have
to believe in me, okay?
But you saw your dad's message.
At the very least,
believe in him.
[YUKI inhales sharply]
Hmm!
[engine idling]
‐[helicopter blades whirring]
‐[YUKI gasps]
Well, well.
Looks like they consider
you pretty valuable.
[grunts]
‐It's fine.
‐[YUKI] Huh?
We can just lose 'em again.
[gunfire]
[YUKI screaming]
You kidding me?
[yells]
[grunts]
[PILOT screams]
[explosion]
[YUKI screaming]
[TAKUYA grunts, sighs]
[YUKI gasping]
[TAKUYA]
Shit!
[grunting]
[YUKI gasps]
[YUKI]
Enough!
Don't do this.
It has nothing to do with you.
Even if I do get to Lost...
♪
...everybody is dead, anyway.
Even my father!
[TAKUYA]
Don't give up.
Did you see it
with your own eyes?
You won't know for sure
till you go.
[YUKI]
But it all disappeared.
Everything!
[TAKUYA]
Go back. Be sure.
[YUKI] At this rate,
we'll never make it.
[TAKUYA groans]
♪
‐[energy humming]
‐[energy blasting]
[tires screeching]
♪
Akira?!
[gunfire]
[gasps]
Did you call him here somehow?
[grunts]
‐[AKIRA groaning]
‐[YUKI screaming]
Yuki!
[YUKI grunts]
[AKIRA grunts]
[rapid gunfire]
[MONK groaning]
[explosion]
♪
We should be out
of their range now.
[TAKUYA grunts]
[energy hums]
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
Sorry.
Didn't mean
to cause any trouble.
Just make sure
you collect her properly.
Once you've done that,
you can kill the guy.
[SUZUNA]
Will do.
‐[SOUMA] By the way...
‐[SUZUNA] Hmm?
[SOUMA]
Tell me, Suzuna,
why didn't you
report the situation sooner?
What, did you think
you could get ahead of me?
♪
[KIKYO] I wonder, was this
the best course of action?
What are you implying, huh?
[KIKYO]
Come on.
You know very well how dangerous
it is to approach Lost.
For starters, the fact that
nobody's ever reached it,
that's a lot.
[EIJI]
Well, at the very least,
we can rest assure
that the Agency won't kill her.
Not as long as she still
holds some value to them.
[KIKYO]
But what about him?
[EIJI] Either way it goes,
he'll be a useful sample.
Beyond that,
the Observer will decide.
♪
He's down, but still breathing.
I can do this myself.
[gunshot]
♪
[YUKI]
Next episode, "Sacrifice."