♪
[TAKUYA]
Taiyo.
[YUKI]
Father?!
No! Stop it!
♪
[grunts]
You made it, bodies intact.
[TAKUYA grunts]
You bastard.
♪
[BOTH gasp]
[panting]
[YUKI groaning]
[weakly]
Akira.
[panting]
[groaning]
The strength... of your will
is everything in this place,
Miss Yuki.
Don't give up, okay?
[panting]
[TAIYO] You know very well
you can't escape, Daichi.
There's no time.
I've come because the Lost
must be completed.
Are you kidding me?
Monster.
Thousands of lives
have been sacrificed.
-Isn't that enough?
-No, I don't think so.
Not nearly enough.
[YUKI panting]
[TAIYO]
Daichi, get out here.
You really want to stop
the Lost that badly, do you?
We're trying to save
our world, remember?
Don't be selfish.
Think for a moment
of all our comrades out there
who are suffering.
What's giving you doubts
about this now?
[panting]
That thing?
The result of a dumb mistake?
Easy fix.
I'll erase it,
along with your doubt.
[TAKUYA grunts]
[grunting]
[YUKI gasps]
How did you do that?
[gasps]
No, the medicine
should still be working.
[gasps]
Taiyo?
You see? It's true.
I knew I would
remember you perfectly.
So through continual
mutual confirmation,
you've maintained an existence.
[scoffs]
How very heroic.
However, compared to what
I've had to shoulder,
my old friend,
it's almost embarrassingly weak.
[gasps]
I'm here now, Dad.
[sobbing quietly]
Please, sir.
Why did you ask Yuki
to come to Lost?
Tell us.
What's the point?
She's suffering here,
can't you see?
♪
[BOTH gasp]
[inaudible]
[gasps]
What does that mean?
That she can choose for herself?
[groans softly]
♪
[YUKI]
But what does that mean?
[YUKI sobs quietly]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[MIFUYU] Hey, Souma,
did you grab your lunch box?
Yeah, I've got it.
[MIFUYU]
Yuki.
How long do you plan
on messing with your hair?
You're gonna be late.
[YUKI]
Almost done.
[chuckles]
I guess she's finally
reached that age.
I'm off.
[MIFUYU] On their way.
Thanks, Akira.
Take care of my babies, okay?
It's my pleasure, ma'am.
[SOUMA]
Man, tests are the worst.
Well, that attitude
isn't gonna help.
If you paid attention in class,
you should be just fine.
Miss Yuki always seems
to do well in class.
What are you trying
to say, you jerk,
that I'm stupid
compared to her?
[AKIRA] Of course that's not
what I'm saying.
[SOUMA] I just haven't gotten
serious yet, that's all.
[YUKI]
Well, then, get serious.
[SOUMA scoffs]
Maybe someday.
Any moment now, the car
carrying the president
of Lacuna Chemical
will drive by.
Here they are.
If you're just joining us,
the president and vice president
of Lacuna Chemical
have been charged
with using children
from an orphanage
for cruel human experimentation.
Unfortunately, we aren't able
to see much since they're...
You should be very proud.
Great work.
[REPORTER] ...are simply
stunning and unlike...
[TAKUYA]
Thank you, sir.
[REPORTER] ...the children
were allegedly...
Poor kids had
nowhere else to go.
-It's terrible.
-[REPORTER] The video...
[SOUMA] I told you I didn't want
any peas, Mom.
[MIFUYU]
Try not to be so picky.
[SOUMA]
What about Dad? That's not fair.
-[knock on door]
-[YOSHIAKI] Come in.
[MAN]
It's almost time.
[YOSHIAKI]
Right, yeah.
[exhales]
[MAN]
What's wrong? Are you nervous?
[gasps]
[TSUBASA]
I mean, aren't you a magician?
Gotta keep your cool
at all times.
[YOSHIAKI gasps]
Tsubasa! Where have you been?
[HOMURA] Now, thanks
to every single one of you,
we're finally able
to stand up here, all together.
[NAMI]
It's been crazy getting here,
but we got through it
because of each other.
And now that
we've come this far,
I can't imagine anything
holding us back.
[HARUKA] We're gonna continue
pushing forward at top speed
with all we've got.
So, try to keep up, okay?
We don't wanna leave you behind.
[kisses]
[RENA] Salty Haruka blew
an actual kiss?
What's even happening?
I've decided to
challenge myself this year.
And how about you, Rena?
I don't know.
Oh! It'd be cool
not to be known as clumsy.
I hope you'll stay
just the way you are.
Yeah? Then Yua gets to keep
being the devious one.
-Hey, now, watch it.
-[GIRLS giggling]
Look, I know
that's what everyone says,
though there are times
when even I wake up
with a wet pillow
in the morning.
But during good times and bad,
you were here for us.
Because of all of you,
I felt like as long as
we didn't give up,
everything would be okay.
Thank you so much,
from our hearts!
[AUDIENCE cheering]
Yes, Yua!
[cries]
♪
[CHIEF] I want to
congratulate you once again
on the
police commissioner award.
Excellent work.
[NEGISHI]
Well, it's thanks to all of you.
[RYOKO] Congratulations, Dad,
er, Officer Negishi.
[YUJI] I can't believe
you took down Lacuna. Unreal.
[KEIGO] I know you chased
that case for a long time.
How about a drink?
[NEGISHI] There are still crimes
being committed.
It's about to get busier
from here on out.
[RYOKO, YUJI and KEIGO]
Yes sir.
Hey, I'm home.
Huh? What?
[ALL singing]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Yuki ♪
[YUKI sobbing quietly]
[YUKI]
I won't...
I won't do it.
I can't choose.
Of course.
I think it would've been better
if the Lost had never happened.
But it happened,
and most of us had to continue
to live in this world.
These last three years,
people have desperately
pressed on.
Even though their loved ones
suddenly disappeared,
they never gave up on life.
They didn't know how
or why things went wrong,
but they chose
to keep moving forward.
And what about those
who were born after the Lost?
If I choose one universe,
it means I reject
the existence of the other.
I can't do something like that.
I can't, Dad.
♪
[sniffles]
The truth is, so many things
have happened to lead us here.
They've been difficult
and painful,
but it's about more than that.
We pulled together
and depended on each other.
We discovered
how strong we were.
[TAKUYA] No matter what happens,
that won't change.
We'll fight and grow.
The past is done,
but the future...
that's still there
waiting for us.
♪
[YUKI]
The Lost happened.
I can't and won't forget.
I have to stay here.
So, Dad, thanks so much.
But you know, I'm not a quitter.
That's not who you
raised me to be.
[BOTH gasp]
[YUKI screaming]
♪
[GEEK grunts]
-Okay, what was that?
-I'm not quite sure.
There's a huge burst of
gravitational waves near Lost.
[KIKYO]
What's happening inside?
[gasps]
Takuya!
[JACK]
It's coming from Lost.
[SUMIRE] But we can't
get any closer.
[JACK]
Shit!
[TAIYO]
Daichi.
Enough of your boastful drivel.
I will simply
eliminate you entirely,
and then I'll finally
complete the Lost.
I will succeed.
Millions of people's
futures depend upon it.
Stop this, now!
[grunts]
[roars]
[gasps]
♪
[TAIYO growls]
[groans sharply]
Yuki.
[TAIYO roars]
[TAIYO]
This is the end.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[bullet thumps]
[groans]
[TAIYO]
Did you actually believe
I wouldn't be able
to see this coming?
♪
[TAIYO groans sharply]
[grunting]
[TAIYO]
Damn Suzuna.
She predicted it
up to this point.
♪
[AKIRA]
Yuki. Yuki.
This is your chance.
Use that against Taiyo.
[YUKI]
Takuya.
[TAIYO grunting]
[roars]
[growling]
[groaning]
♪
[DAICHI] Get on the scooter.
Do it. Now!
[groans]
[motor scooter engine starts]
[DAICHI]
Yuki...
you've grown up so much.
[GEEK]
Jack, did you hear?
Yeah.
-Huh?
-[gasps]
-[JACK] That's... It's her.
[car doors open]
Hey, wake up. Come on!
Where is he?
Yuki!
Takuya!
♪
[YOSHIAKI] I'd hate to make
a tree disappear.
I don't think anyone
would appreciate that.
So today I'll focus
on this bottle.
-One, two, three.
-[WOMAN 1] Will it work? Wow.
-[cheering]
-[WOMAN 2] Wow!
Did you see what he did?
Thank you very much.
Really appreciate it.
Sure. We can do that.
Investigating your husband's
cheating habits
will run you right around
100,000 yen a day.
-Huh? Uh... Hey. W... Hey!
-[cell phone beeps]
I don't wanna chase
cheating husbands.
I wanna do jobs that matter.
[KEIGO]
Beggars can't be choosers.
Just go back
to the police force.
[YUJI ]
Believe me, if I could've,
I'd be there already.
[EIJI] In other words,
the problem of Lost
is one that belongs
to everyone on Earth.
Its effects unfortunately
reach all of mankind.
So, in response to that,
our foundation is creating
a project team.
Recruiting talent,
no matter where from.
If you can help
with this difficult problem,
we ask you to reach out
and join us.
[camera shutters clicking]
[chalk scribbling]
[cell phone vibrates]
Huh?
[GEEK] How's Yuki
doing these days?
[EIJI sighs]
She seems to have slowly
acclimated to her daily life.
Her complaints are normal.
"Studying is hard," etcetera.
What about the issue
with her memory?
Well, she's having trouble
remembering a certain courier,
if you believe that.
[EIJI] She made it out,
but she was exposed
to the surge particles
for too long.
-Hey, Yuki.
-Huh?
I'm headed this way, too.
[YUKI]
Oh, cool.
Have you been
keeping up in class?
[YUKI]
Hmm.
I mean, barely, I guess.
Make sure and ask me
if you hit any problems.
I'll lend you my notes.
[YUKI]
Great. Thank you.
[gasps softly]
Something wrong?
[YUKI]
It's nothing.
[KOUTA]
This is hard.
[KAIBARA] That's pretty pathetic
from someone so young.
[sighs]
I didn't think it'd be
this much manual labor.
[KAIBARA]
So...
anything new?
Any leads on where he is?
No, sorry.
[YUMIKO]
Thanks for the treat.
I still say we should
brand this tomato, you know.
Let's find a way
to distribute them.
What do you say?
[KAIBARA]
No, no.
I've only ever wanted
to do this as a hobby.
[KOUTA]
Well, I need to head out soon.
[YUMIKO] Don't you still have
work to do here, though?
[KOUTA]
What? No. Shut up.
[door opens, closes]
[motor scooter engine revving]
[motor scooter receding]
[wind howling]
♪