[helicopter whirring]
We're reporting live from
the explosion site
in the south eastern area
of Tokyo.
Our question is, could this be
a repeat of the Lost?
At the present moment, no
casualties have been reported.
For your safety, we advise
the public to stay indoors
unless it's absolutely
necessary.
-We will remain on the scene...
-[SYUNPEI] Whoa, look at that.
At least it's in
the lock-down district.
I guess we should
all be grateful.
The officers in that precinct
will need backup.
I need more men down there
to get a handle on it.
[door opens]
[RYOKO]
Good luck out there, guys!
[CHIEF]
What're you doing here?
Aren't you off today?
Oh, I just need
to borrow Syunpei for a bit.
-[SYUNPEI] Huh? For what?
-[CHIEF] Negishi!
[door closes]
Hey! Takuya!
♪
[monitor beeping]
Takuya.
[GEEK] You two were the ones
who told him to go to Lost
in the first place!
This is all your fault!
What the hell are
the Tama-Shi, anyway?
You knew this would happen,
didn't you?
The whole time, you knew
that Takuya might die!
You better take responsibility!
[YUMIKO]
Listen, Geek.
You need to go into hiding
until things cool off.
Huh? What did I do?
[YUMIKO] You infiltrated
the lock-down district, too.
The police will know by now.
If you stick around here,
they'll track you down
and start asking questions.
Do you really think
I'd leave him behind?
[EIJI] Then come stay
with me at my place.
Look, I'm not trying
to redeem myself or anything.
But at least I know
you'll be safe there.
You should come with us, too.
[KIKYO]
Ready to go?
[YUMIKO]
Make up your own mind, Yuki.
After all...
this is the result
of your actions.
[footsteps fading]
[car door closes]
-[RYOKO] Excuse us.
-[EIJI] Hmm?
I'm Ryoko Negishi.
An investigator.
I'm Aoyama.
Can we help you?
Did you have anything to do
with the second Lost
that transpired this morning?
What makes you think
she's involved with it?
And I believe
this morning's phenomenon
is a bit different
from the Lost.
[SYUNPEI] Maybe so, but that's
what the media's calling it.
[RYOKO] This image was captured
near the time of the event
by a surveillance camera
within the lock-down district.
Young lady,
there's no mistaking
that you're the one
in this picture.
As for the man...
He's in intensive care.
No visitors allowed.
At the risk of sounding callous,
he should have known
how dangerous that area is.
Just what were the two
of you doing over
in the lock-down district?
A mistake.
They were out on a date
and accidentally wound up
where they shouldn't have been.
I assume you're in high school,
aren't ya?
You got student ID?
What school are you enrolled in?
This poor girl.
Her whole family vanished
three years ago
during the Lost.
The trauma made it hard
for her to attend school,
so she's stayed home
ever since.
Of course, we've kept her
on top of her studies.
But I guess dates aren't
too traumatic for you, huh?
Hey, back off.
She's not allowed
to have any fun?
Have you been eating all right?
You look so frail.
Seriously?
You're gonna let 'em go,
just like that?
I bet the ladies love you.
[SYUNPEI]
What's that supposed to mean?
[keyboards clacking]
[YUKI]
I don't understand.
Why can't we just
tell them the truth?
The Agency's everywhere.
We can't trust anyone.
They've infiltrated every part
of the government.
The police are no exception.
[GEEK]
Huh? Are you kidding?
You live here?
[EIJI] I guess it's kinda big
for a single guy.
Well, come in.
[RYOKO] Presenting
my special mirin rice!
There's plenty to go around,
so please help yourselves!
Man, something about this rice
is addictive as hell.
Oh, yeah, it's great.
[YUJI] I don't know what secret
project you guys are working on.
But you could learn a thing
or two from her.
She may be young,
but there's a reason
-she was promoted to lieutenant.
-Here!
And her old man was
a legendary police officer,
so it makes sense.
♪
[shuddering breaths]
[gasps]
♪
[YUKI]
Souma.
♪
[inaudible dialogue]
[SUZUNA]
How admirable of you.
[YUMIKO]
Suzuna!
How did you find us?
I assume you've come here
to finish us off, then?
I can erase you whenever I want.
The same goes for him.
[YUMIKO gasps]
[YUMIKO] Last time, you said
something strange to me.
That you shouldn't overwrite
things any further.
What does that mean?
Well, since you asked,
there is something
you might like to know.
[YOSHIAKI]
And now,
I'm going to make this car
completely disappear!
[AUDIENCE applauding
and cheering]
[YOSHIAKI]
Ready?
One!
Two.
Three!
[MALE HOST]
Unbelievable!
Let's give it up
for the renowned magician
Mr. Yoshiaki!
Wow, what a performance!
I saw a magician make
a tiger disappear once.
[YOSHIAKI gasps]
[turning pages]
-[slurps]
-[YOSHIAKI] Excuse me.
-But who are you?
-Shit! That's hot!
Hidaka Detective Agency.
Keigo Hidaka.
What's this?
Sorry to bother ya,
but I've been investigating
a certain children's institution
for a few years now.
The Light of Hope Academy
for Disabled Children.
I got confirmation
that you attended there.
So we can skip over that part.
Yeah, so what?
Gonna sell that info
to a tabloid?
-Be my guest.
-No, no, no.
I'm not trying
to get some kinda payoff.
Actually, I am here
to help you out.
Mr. Yoshiaki, tell me this.
Are you still searching for that
long-lost big brother of yours?
You both grew up
in the same institution.
His name was Tsubasa, right?
I bet if you called out
to him publicly on TV,
you'd get a lot of responses.
Not to mention
an increase in viewers.
But if you did that,
it just might hurt ya
more than help ya, wouldn't it?
Because of who
your big brother is.
You certainly did your homework,
didn't you, Detective?
[KEIGO]
My price is 500,000 yen.
I thought you weren't
interested in money.
Yeah, but a man's
gotta earn something.
Don't give up on me yet,
hear what I'm offerin' first.
[screams in pain]
You wouldn't be racketeering
again, now would you, Keigo?
You've got the wrong idea!
Please let me go!
[KEIGO]
You're a civil servant.
You don't know how tough it is
striking out on your own.
I thought being a civil servant
was too confining
and self-employment
gave you freedom.
[KEIGO] So, has there been
some kind of development?
Is that why you
were lookin' for me?
I'm still not entirely certain
if the Agency
is involved or not.
But I'd like you
to check into this man.
He's a freelance courier,
but it seems he used to be
in the same profession as you.
[KEIGO]
Hmm. Hmm?
I think I've met him before.
[RYOKO]
Perfect!
So can you do
a little digging for me?
[KEIGO] As if I could ever
say no to you.
But, Ryoko,
don't be reckless with this.
[RYOKO]
Same to you, Keigo.
[door opens, closes]
Good grief.
That girl is gonna work me
to death one of these days.
[chuckles]
But she is a chip
off the ol' block.
[groaning]
You're awake!
[TAKUYA]
Where is he?
Kouta?
[YUMIKO]
I searched the whole area,
but I couldn't find him.
After that, the second
Lost event happened.
Where's Yuki?
[YUMIKO]
She's fine.
We took her somewhere safe.
That's a relief.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
I meant to ask you, if you know
a producer named Seiji?
[YUMIKO gasps]
What?
How would you
have heard about him?
♪
They just announced it
a minute ago.
He fell asleep at the wheel.
No way.
I finally find
a freakin' clue to Lost,
and he suddenly
turns up dead?
[YUMIKO]
Listen to me.
Please don't go back to Lost.
Stay away from there.
I couldn't take it.
I don't want to see you
get hurt again.
You might not even come out
of there alive next time.
I understand.
Really.
But I'm not backing out
of the contract.
[RYOKO] My apologies
for barging in like this.
But I brought you some lunch.
Well, you hungry?
I give humble thanks
for this food.
Mmm.
Not too shabby.
I like to add mirin to the rice,
but I ran out.
It's normally
a lot tastier than this.
I read up on your father, Yuki.
He seemed like
a really amazing man.
[YUKI]
You think so, huh?
The premier authority
on applied physics.
The director of Japan's
research institute.
It's all impressive.
I studied the arts, so I'm
clueless about that stuff.
You know, my father
was also caught in the Lost.
Day after day,
work, work, work.
Of course, I knew that being
a police officer meant
he'd be busy
most of the time.
But I missed him,
and I was lonely.
-[YOUNG YUKI] Have a safe trip!
-[DAICHI] Sure thing.
Be back soon.
So anyway...
[door closes]
[SOUMA] We were supposed to ride
roller coasters tomorrow.
He keeps breaking his promises.
It hurts my feelings.
Souma, Dad's gotta work
extra hard
because everybody
is counting on him.
Try to be patient, okay?
[RYOKO] I wish he'd had
more time for us.
But still, I admired
his dedication.
I wanted to be just like him.
To be respected like he was.
And so,
after my father got
caught up in the Lost,
instead of just feeling sad,
I felt frustrated too.
I'd followed in his footsteps
and become a cop,
hoping I could actually
work with him.
But then, all of a sudden,
he was gone.
It's been three years
since the Lost,
and I know there are
a lot of people who've given up.
But not me.
I will never give up.
I believe that my father
is still alive somewhere.
[YUKI crying]
[YUKI]
It's good.
Thanks.
[jet passing overhead]
Okay, so where
are we off to now?
Hey, wait.
Isn't this Lacuna's
research facility?
[RYOKO]
I gotta go.
[YUKI]
Um...
before you leave...
listen to my story.
Ryoko, I want
to tell you everything.
About where I was...
and what was done to me.
[RYOKO]
Unforgivable.
♪
How much longer?
[footsteps approaching]
[TSUKI]
I apologize for the wait.
Hello there.
I'm the head of public relations
for Lacuna Chemical.
And we're from the first
division of investigations.
Pleasure to meet you.
[TSUKI] How can I be
of service to you today?
Just following up.
We heard there was a burglary
that took place
at this facility the other day.
[TSUKI]
Indeed there was,
but we've already filed
a report with the police.
-Was there some sort of problem?
-No problem.
But do you mind if I take
a look around the place?
We have a strict
confidentiality policy here,
so I'm afraid
I can't allow that.
But if you have
a search warrant,
you'll have
our full cooperation.
[playing "Moonlight Sonata"]
[knocking on door]
-It's open.
-[door opens]
[TSUKI]
Pardon the interruption.
[TAIYO]
Do we have a guest?
[TSUKI] The police came by
asking questions.
It might be nothing
to worry about,
but there's
a slight possibility
that they've encountered
the test subject.
[TAIYO]
Oh?
How long do you plan
on ignoring her?
Just look at
what's become of Souma.
[TAIYO] I see more potential
in the older sister.
She was able to create
a Lost-like phenomenon
without the use
of an artifact.
I'm curious to see
what else she'll do
while she's roaming free.
[TSUKI] If she becomes
an obstacle to our plans,
I'll have her eliminated.
Keep that in mind.
That's awfully harsh of you.
Put a cap on your curiosity.
[continues playing
"Moonlight Sonata"]
[CHIEF]
What were you thinking?
Stay clear of that area!
That's a direct order
from our superiors, got it?
Don't make me repeat myself!
Just do your job
and stay out of trouble!
What do you mean "that area"?
If you keep on meddling,
I won't be able to protect you.
I'd just like to add that
none of this was my idea.
I just got dragged
around all day.
[CHIEF] Shut up and get back
to your post.
Uh... yes, sir.
See, what did I tell you?
You can't just go
rogue like that.
I'm on the right track,
I'm sure of it.
When people start applying
pressure like that,
what it usually means is you're
getting closer to the truth.
You gotta stop.
Finally.
I think I'll be able to get
my father back now.
And also...
♪
That is unforgivable.
Thank you for sharing with me.
[YUKI crying softly]
I'm sorry. That must
have been so hard.
But don't you worry, Yuki.
I'm going to drag the Agency
out into the light.
I made a promise.
♪
Whoa, I'm sorry.
Hang on. Takuya?
[TAKUYA]
Hey, Yuki.
Oh, Takuya, A-are you okay?
Never better.
[GEEK]
You can barely walk, man!
Well, let's go.
♪
There it is.
Yep, that's definitely
the guy, all right.
I gotta hand it to you, Ryoko.
You've got killer instincts.
I can't believe
we're wasting our time
looking through these
old real estate documents
in the dead of night.
Sometime before
the Lost happened,
a certain factory site
was put up for sale,
and Lacuna Chemical
put in a bid for it.
They even announced their plans
to make it
a second research facility.
Oh, yeah. But wasn't
Sugisawa Industries
actually the highest bidder?
Yes, everything changed
after they were caught
in the Lost, though.
It was a lucky break for Lacuna
and of course a huge hit
for Sugisawa Industries.
I found it!
This is the contract!
According to this,
the highest bidder
was Lacuna Chemical,
but they retracted it?
Wait a minute,
the second largest bidder,
Sugisawa Industries,
ended up buying the land?
[SYUNPEI] It's pretty weird
that they'd retract their bid
after winning out.
[RYOKO]
And the date of the sale is...
It was right before the Lost!
[gasps]
That means the Agency
knew exactly
when the Lost would happen
and how big it'd be!
I finally have proof!
Hey, let's take this document--
[grunts]
[RYOKO gasping]
[SYUNPEI] Well, you should
have listened to the Chief
when he told you
to stay out of it, Lieutenant.
[RYOKO] You're a part of...
of the Agency?
[SYUNPEI]
For what it's worth,
I was just starting to like you.
But I gotta say, that mirin rice
you're so damn proud of?
Seriously, it tastes like shit.
I'll be taking this.
Excellent work.
[RYOKO continues gasping]
[door opens, closes]
[car engine revving]
[YUKI]
You wanted to see me?
[YUMIKO] I know things
have been hard for you.
You finally managed
to escape the Agency,
and then you killed
your own brother.
However, that's not
what happened.
Well, since you asked,
there is something
I think you'd be interested
to know.
Yuki's brother Souma.
He's actually...
-[YUMIKO] He's alive.
-[YUKI gasps]
♪
[SOUMA groaning]
[YUKI]
He really survived?
[YUMIKO] If you continue
to head towards Lost,
he's going to keep on
appearing like that.
Do you understand?
It means you'll have to fight
your little brother.
Are you prepared
to do that again?
Because if you're not,
then please leave Takuya
out of this.
[YUKI]
Souma is my brother.
If he's alive...
I'll save him!
♪
[TAKUYA]
Next Episode, Affection.