[TSUKI]
It only takes a tiny leak
to sink a great ship.
No matter how solid
everything else might be,
the smallest crack
can bring about the end.
The one at the top
must always be vigilant
and hyper-aware
of every movement
in their periphery.
I just hope we both live
to see the end of this.
Well, I, I trust you to
take care of this, minister.
Good luck.
[ANNOUNCER] The legendary
long-lost treasure
Tsuki's Tears,
which sank with a luxury liner
in the Pacific
at the beginning
of the 19th century,
has now been found.
The discovery was made
by an oceanic research team
at Inada University.
The large ruby
is currently valued
at 500 million yen.
[YUJI] Please, you can't
keep doing this.
[exhales]
It's still early.
[KEIGO]
What about you?
What happened to your revenge?
You remember
Ryoko's partner, Aoyama?
He was found dead. Drowned.
The higher-ups
have shut it down.
Investigation Division.
The chief was transferred out.
[KEIGO]
Hmm.
Please, sir.
[grunts]
I'm just as frustrated as you!
Can't you please tell me
what you know?
The Agency...
just who in the hell are they?
Tell me!
[knock on door]
[door opens]
Detective, um...
[KEIGO]
Hey. It's Mister Famous.
[YOSHIAKI]
You wanted 500,000 yen, right?
[ANNOUNCER]
A few days ago,
the long-lost art piece
known as
Tsuki's Tears was discovered...
I've seen that.
Seen what?
Souma was holding something
just like it.
If that's the case,
then it's possible
that you were looking
at an artifact.
[TAKUYA]
An artifact?
I used to work in research.
A coworker specialized in them.
Even objects can contain souls.
The will of the one who made it,
and the will of all its owners
throughout the generations.
When those wills combine,
sometimes an item will manifest
a mysterious power.
♪
Why would Souma
carry something like that?
[EIJI] It seems that the power
of objects like those
can magnify
a human's innate abilities.
There are rumors the Agency's
been collecting them
from all over the world.
[rapid beeping]
We found him
sniffing around the mansion.
He said he has
some business with Takuya.
What should we do?
[GEEK]
It's the magician.
That guy, Yoshiaki!
When the hell did you have time
to make friends
with such a famous person?
Who was it
that told you about me?
I can't say.
[GEEK]
This is bad.
Doesn't this mean
that someone out there
is looking into Takuya?
So what's your business, then?
The Phantom Thief Brigade X.
Does that happen to ring a bell?
You've come into contact
with them.
A number of times.
Hmm.
♪
[laughs]
Nice try.
[gasps]
♪
[groaning]
[YUMIKO] Thanks for the walk
down crappy memory lane.
Okay, so what do you
have to do with them?
[YOSHIAKI]
Their leader, Tsubasa,
he's my older brother.
Seriously?
[YOSHIAKI] I haven't seen him
in over ten years, though.
One day, he just up
and disappeared.
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
And?
[YOSHIAKI]
Look...
I'm here to make a deal.
[YUJI]
Kinda crazy.
Going this far
to meet a long-lost brother.
It's weird, isn't it?
I mean, at this point
they're basically strangers.
Yeah, but those two
lost their parents
at a really early age.
They depended on one another
to survive when they were kids.
Oh.
Well, the magician is late.
Could be trouble.
You think maybe he told them
about your involvement?
He might be a giant wuss,
but he's not dumb.
Hmm.
[YOSHIAKI]
These are the things
the Phantom Thief Brigade
has stolen.
Every one of these
is a piece of art
that's worth hundreds
of millions of yen.
Does that mean they're only
in it for the money, after all?
[YOSHIAKI]
Look at this.
There's a jewel here
called Hoshi's Tears.
[gasps]
You've heard of the recently
recovered Tsuki's Tears?
It's a legendary treasure
that pairs with this item.
I have no doubt
they'll target it.
So what you're saying is
that you want me
to catch your brother?
What's in it for us if we do?
Well, plenty, I think.
Recovering the stolen treasures?
Besides, if you catch them,
you'll find out
how they sell the goods.
♪
[RUI] This is
unfinished business, that's all.
Yeah.
Don't see any reason
to ask the boss.
[RUI]
How are things going?
Still researching, stand by.
[humming]
The Phantom Thief Brigade
stole Hoshi's Tears.
But I know the Agency
has it now.
So they're connected
to the Agency?
Takuya, this must be a trap.
Yeah.
I'm sorry,
but I can't trust someone
who won't tell me the source
of their information.
I mean, I really don't want
to do anything rough, but...
Are you sure about that?
I've told my manager.
If anything happens to me,
he'll tell the police
and the press about this place.
So you're threatening us now?
That's a problem.
[YOSHIAKI]
If I let this chance go,
I'll never see my brother again.
Hmm.
-Hey, um...
-[EIJI] Hmm?
Is it possible an artifact could
change someone's personality?
There's a chance, yeah.
[gasps]
If we examine Tsuki's Tears,
maybe we could find some way
to change Souma back.
Hmm.
Jeez.
-[keyboard keys clacking]
-Infiltration successful.
Hey, what's your brother's deal?
Why's he leading
the Phantom Thief Brigade?
[YOSHIAKI]
I don't know.
[TAKUYA] He's been super quiet
ever since the Lost.
What's he been doing lately?
[YOSHIAKI]
I don't know.
[TAKUYA] Not the tightest
of brothers then, huh?
[WOMAN 1] They say it was
a traffic accident.
[WOMAN 2]
How terrible.
[WOMAN 1]
Her children are still so young.
♪
[YUKI]
Father.
I promise, I'll work hard.
Souma will be fine.
I'll make sure of it.
♪
How long are we gonna
tail these guys?
And how is some dumb magician
supposed to help us?
Hmm?
[KEIGO] We're following
this man named Takuya.
He was the last person
she was chasing after.
And in the past, he's been known
to be involved with the Agency.
[YUJI] You should've told me
that from the start.
[yells]
Whoa! What the hell?
Did you guys see that?
Oh, um...
Well, I'm...
I'm a magician and all.
But that was...
[SOUMA]
So?
Any thoughts on my plan?
I mean, it'd be boring
if we just got
a backup for this thing,
don't you think?
I know I do.
Let's take this chance
to roundup those artifacts.
And we should use
that guy to do it, Tsubasa.
[TSUKI] You think it'll be
as easy as that?
[SOUMA]
Don't look down on me, old lady.
You little...
They'll totally take the bait,
won't they?
Yes. No doubt.
This girl has already
failed us once.
We can't leave things
to her again.
If we do that, we're fools.
-Oh, I don't know.
-Huh?
Experience is important.
Hmm.
[SOUMA scoffs]
Too bad for you.
-Let's go, Suzuna.
-Right.
[door opens and closes]
[sighs]
How troublesome.
We should have just
brainwashed the boy.
[TAIYO]
He's more interesting this way.
Kids are cuter when they're
a little bit cheeky.
But I'm the one
who gets inconvenienced.
I'd very much prefer not to get
bitten by yet another pet dog.
♪
[YUJI]
Huh?
[KEIGO]
What is it?
[YUJI]
Nothing.
-Uh-oh.
-[ALL] Hmm?
♪
[KANA]
Hey. Found you.
Yep, this is bad!
-Oh, crap.
-Be careful.
♪
[tires screeching]
What happened?
[DRIVER] Someone attacked us
right outta the blue!
[groans]
Huh?
[laughs]
You lose, dude.
I'm afraid we'll be the ones
taking Tsuki's Tears.
Have a nice day.
[TAKUYA]
They're playing with us.
[YUMIKO]
Everyone all right?
Ow, ow, ow. It's fine.
I just found out where
they're keeping Tsuki's Tears.
[YUMIKO]
Not in their research tower?
Nuh-uh.
And it looks like
they're moving it
to a different spot tonight.
Tomorrow, important people are
apparently gathering to see it.
Well, either way,
we can't move forward like this.
My brother.
How could he do this?
[water falling]
Hmm.
[MAN 1]
You want to retract your bid?
No, you can't be serious.
[MAN 2] Prime real estate
like this isn't easy to come by.
[TSUKI] We're making
some rather drastic changes
to our business plans.
[MAN 3]
Are you sure?
I'm afraid the penalties
will be awfully high.
[TSUKI]
Yes. That's not a problem.
[TAIYO]
In the end, it will all be gone.
-[MAN 3] What?
-[thuds]
[gasps]
-[explosions]
-[gas hissing]
-[MEN coughing]
-[MAN 2] What's happening?
[yells]
[groans]
♪
[whimpers, gasps]
[gasps]
-[gunshot]
-[groans sharply]
[panting]
You're such a failure.
[TSUBASA]
Shit!
♪
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Tsubasa's data?
Yes, it was still in
the detective agency's database.
Look at this.
It's the institution
he was in as a child.
[TAKUYA] "Light of Hope Academy
for Disabled Children."
Yoshiaki, too, then.
Probably so.
[TAKUYA]
Poor guy.
Who do you think
put him up to this?
[crying]
♪
[TSUBASA chuckles]
Are you crying again, Yoshiaki?
Brother, it hurts.
[crying]
[TSUBASA]
Come on, don't cry.
Here. Watch this, okay?
Oh, wow. It disappeared.
Along with those tears, right?
From Takuya.
Oh, thank you.
[YUKI]
What kind of person was he?
-[YOSHIAKI] Huh?
-[YUKI] Your brother.
[YOSHIAKI]
Oh.
He was a pretty cool
big brother.
But he was a strange person.
In what way?
For instance,
how do you eat
fried pork cutlets?
Huh? I don't know.
With sauce, like normal?
'Course you do.
My brother takes
the breading off
before he eats them.
-Huh?
-Weird, right?
Even with siblings,
I guess there are things
you'll never understand.
Yeah.
We don't need you
around anymore, Akira.
Some security guy.
Couldn't even keep her safe.
Don't worry about us
from now on.
Why don't you go hang around
Dad or something?
Your father has
ordered me to stay here.
[grunts]
Mind your own business!
[gasps]
What's wrong, Souma?!
[SOUMA grunts]
[GEEK] The Phantom Thief Brigade
is definitely around.
[KANA] Those guys showed up,
just like we thought.
They're not getting off
with a warning this time.
They simply refuse to learn.
Let's just get this over with.
-[rattles]
-[gasps]
-Hmm?
[SOUMA] Are you guys
that Phantom Thief Brigade?
That a kid?
Shouldn't you be in bed already?
[SOUMA]
More like the cosplay brigade.
Didn't you hear?
Halloween's come and gone.
What'd you say?
How'd you get that?
What are you doing with it
in the first place?
[coughs]
[RUI]
Check it out, boss.
[ALL chuckle]
[TSUBASA]
What the...
[JACK] All it means
is that we're fine on our own.
It's okay.
We'll all survive
if you wanna rest like this
every once in a while.
[TSUBASA breathes heavily]
Sorry, I'll pull my weight
next time.
But seriously,
how'd you guys manage it?
[laughs]
[TSUBASA]
Huh? What is it?
What is it?
[TSUBASA laughing]
This is a fake.
-[RUI] What?!
-[KANA gasps]
[JACK] That has to mean
that they knew we were after it.
[KANA]
How? No way.
-[TSUBASA] Eh, don't worry.
-[ALL] Hmm?
This is still pretty nice.
It's a good little trinket.
See?
It's beautiful up there.
I knew this chandelier
was missing something.
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
When it came down to it,
in the end,
we never found the real thing.
Anyway, who the hell are you?
Who knows, right?
Perfect timing.
This way, we can steal it
right along with Tsuki's Tears.
It'll make our leader
very happy.
Are you guys really that stupid?
-[SUMIRE] Hmm?
-[RUI] Huh?
[ALL gasp]
Tsuki's Tears is gone?
But how?
Was it him?
My brother?
-[loud thud]
-[SUMIRE screams]
[gasps]
[YUKI]
Souma!
Hey, there, sis.
[chuckles]
The hell's going on?
Lucky me,
running into you like this.
Thank goodness.
Thank goodness
you're all right.
[gasps]
What, are you this kid's
allies or something?
Better think carefully
about your answer.
You're all his subordinates,
aren't you?
Why is he holding
Hoshi's Tears?
The thing you guys stole.
[RUI]
We have the same question!
Are you sure you guys
should be bickering right now?
There's no time for that.
Tell me where you've hidden
all the artifacts
that you've stolen.
If you don't,
then she's gonna die.
♪
[shuddering]
I'll tell you
what you wanna know.
You're messing
with the wrong people,
you little brat.
[yells]
♪
[grunts]
-[gasps]
-No way.
[BOTH groan]
This is starting
to get troublesome.
Please stop this.
Maybe I should just
kill all of you now.
Souma, stop it!
Tch.
More to the point.
Why the hell
are you still alive?!
♪
[gunshots]
[grunts softly]
Well, what have we here?
Long time, no see...
Akira.
[YUKI]
Next Episode, "Parting."