[grunts]
♪
-[gasps]
-No way.
[BOTH groan]
This is starting
to get troublesome.
Please stop this.
Maybe I should just
kill all of you now.
Souma, stop it!
Tch.
More to the point.
Why the hell
are you still alive?!
[gunshots]
[TAKUYA gasps]
♪
[grunts softly]
Well, what have we here?
Long time, no see...
Akira.
♪
[YOSHIAKI gasps]
Tama-shi?
[TAKUYA]
There's no time to explain.
[grunts]
Are you guys planning
to fight me or what?
[YUKI]
Please open your eyes, Souma!
If anyone's daydreaming here,
it's you.
[groaning]
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[panting]
[groaning]
[SOUMA] Yeah, like I thought,
you don't get it at all.
Do you, sis?
Your presence just annoys me
for some reason.
[grunts]
[gasps]
Listen, if you can't do
anything to help,
just stay down.
[panting]
[SOUMA laughs]
[SOUMA] Well, come on,
let's finish this.
[grunts in effort]
Why are you even trying?
[YUKI gasping]
[YUKI] If only he didn't have
that artifact.
Yuki and I were both caught up
in the Lost, but we survived.
That means we're special.
We were meant
for something better.
Unlike you, a wimp who couldn't
even protect himself.
[panting]
-[YOSHIAKI] Hey, you okay?
-Huh?
Here, let me see.
Sorry, I wasn't able to
completely erase the wound.
[JACK gasps]
So you have the same power
as our leader.
Hold on. Is it possible
you're the boss'...
Where's my brother?
Hmm.
[RUI]
He'll be back with us soon.
No doubt. The boss
will most definitely return.
[panting]
[grunts in effort]
♪
[YOSHIAKI yelling]
[groans in pain]
[groans, gasps]
I'm a little busy right now,
but I'll take my time
with the rest of you later.
[SOUMA gasps]
[gasps deeply]
[groans weakly]
[gasps]
It worked.
Nah. I'm kidding.
Since it would appear
that none of you have a clue...
allow me to be the one
to enlighten you.
[gasps]
You have Tsuki's Tears.
[scoffs]
♪
[YOSHIAKI]
Brother?
[gasps]
-It's the boss!
-He's back?
[panting]
[TAKUYA]
Damn it!
Tsubasa?
♪
[groaning sharply]
[gasps]
Akira!
Oh, no.
[ALL gasp]
[rumbling]
He's here.
[panting]
[YUKI gasps]
Oh, no!
[panting]
This is some kinda
shitty reunion,
wouldn't you say?
[RUI]
No, something's wrong.
That guy can't be him.
[growls]
♪
Damn it to hell.
Well, there goes the last
of my severance pay.
Ten years at the factory
and they give you 30,000 yen.
That's a straight-up insult,
Kankichi.
I don't need the opinion
of a guy who lives in net cafes.
You just hurry up
and find a job.
Yeah, I've been looking.
Problem is, though,
for outcasts like you and me,
the only jobs available
are super-shitty ones.
Hey, what do you think,
should we do it
for real, or what?
-Huh?
-[machine thuds]
[MAN 1]
Shit. What the hell, man?!
You think you can
pull one over on me?
-[MAN 1 grunts]
-[machine thuds]
Give me back my money, damn it.
-[MAN 1 grunting]
-[machine thuds]
You've gotta be
freakin' kidding me!
Stupid machine.
[JACK] You're pretty noisy
over here, old man.
Huh?
[JACK] What'd that machine
ever do to you?
[RUI]
Leave your wallet and get out.
Huh?!
-[onlookers gasp]
-[murmuring]
Hey, what are you trying to do?
Think you can scare me
with that little toy?
-[RUI] Huh?
-[MAN 1, mockingly] "Huh?"
You got
some kinda problem, trash?
Why don't you try going out
and working for money?
Well? Answer me, kid.
It's because of garbage
people like you that the world--
[MAN 1 gasping in disbelief]
[screaming]
[MAN 2]
He sliced his tie.
[murmuring]
-[MAN IN COAT laughing]
-Huh?
[MAN 3]
What the hell?
That thing's just a toy.
So what was the other guy
screaming about, then?
-[MAN 4] How stupid.
-[WOMAN] Let's get out of here.
Huh?
[RUI]
Hey. Wait up a second.
Oh, it's you guys.
Well? What was that about?
[JACK]
And who the hell are you?
[scoffs]
Something similar
to what you are.
[gasps]
Oh, that's right.
You guys are free, aren't you?
Well, in that case,
want in on something better?
[RUI groaning in pain]
[RUI, weakly]
Boss.
[groaning continues]
What the hell?!
[grunts]
All right, what'd you do to him?
Answer me!
You just never learn.
[gasps]
[YUKI sobs]
[SOUMA] Go ahead,
hurry up and finish him.
Do it, Tsubasa.
♪
[groaning]
[screaming]
[SUMIRE gasps]
-[BOTH gasp]
-Sumire, no!
[groaning]
[screams, gasps]
[grunting in effort]
It's that guy.
[YUKI]
Akira!
[muffled groaning]
[AKIRA, weakly]
Miss Yuki, be strong.
You have to use your will.
You can do it.
[YUKI crying]
No, I can't.
I can't.
[SOUMA]
You're wasting your time, Akira.
It's impossible for you.
You cannot protect anyone.
[gasps]
[groaning sharply]
No! Stop it!
[groans sharply]
[YOSHIAKI]
Stop this, right now!
Forgive me, I've failed.
[YOSHIAKI]
I think that's enough.
Aw, what's got you down,
my friend?
I want you to tell me
what you did to my brother!
[snickers]
[SOUMA]
What do you say, big brother?
Feel up to killing a sibling?
Is it really you?
[grunts]
He's missing me on purpose.
[BOTH gasp]
Brother.
♪
[SOUMA] What do you think
you're doing?!
Hit him properly, now!
[grunts]
♪
[SOUMA]
Give it back!
[crying]
Brother, it hurts.
[TSUBASA]
Well, I guess you can't help it.
Did you trip on this rock
or something?
Come on, don't cry.
Here. Watch this, okay?
♪
Oh, wow. It disappeared.
Along with those tears, right?
[gasps]
[YOSHIAKI] Brother,
do you want me to erase this?
[coughs]
Where are you?!
It's mine!
Give it back to me!
♪
[grunting in effort]
Stop this!
[YOSHIAKI grunting]
[SOUMA groans weakly]
[TAKUYA]
Yuki!
[YOSHIAKI panting]
♪
Hmm.
[YOSHIAKI]
Brother.
I'm surprised he's still here.
Tsubasa's Tama-shi.
I think he's held here.
Their mutual affection
keeps them tethered.
[TSUBASA] Light of Hope.
Guess we'll see.
Be great to find it here.
Hope, that is.
-[excited chatter]
-[laughter]
I heard we're getting
plastic models today.
-Amazing.
-[BOY] All right!
♪
[DOCTOR 1]
He shows some potential.
[DOCTOR 2]
Maybe, but you have to admit,
number 57
has quite a bit more.
[DOCTOR 1]
You mean the little brother?
-[glass shatters]
-Huh?
[DOCTOR 2] Hey, number 24.
What do you think you're doing?
[groans]
[DOCTOR 1]
Let go!
[ALL gasp]
[DOCTOR 2]
Whoa. It disappeared.
[DOCTOR 1]
What does this mean?
[TAIYO]
What happened?
[DOCTOR 3]
The artifact, it disappeared.
Oh?
Well, it's not the power
we're looking for,
but it seems like
a useful one.
Very useful, indeed.
♪
[TSUBASA]
I should be enough for them,
they don't need you, too.
Yoshiaki. I swear to you,
I will erase all the Artifacts
in this world
before your power awakens.
If I do that,
then, you'll be free.
It's okay.
We'll all survive if you wanna
rest like this
every once in a while.
[TSUBASA breathes heavily]
Sorry. I'll pull my weight
next time.
But seriously,
how'd you guys manage it?
[laughs]
[TSUBASA]
Huh?
What is it?
[TSUBASA laughing]
This it's a fake.
-[RUI] What?!
-[KANA gasps]
[JACK] That has to mean
that they knew we were after it.
[KANA]
How? No way.
-[TSUBASA] Eh, don't worry.
-[ALL] Hmm?
This is still pretty nice.
It's a good little trinket.
See?
It's beautiful up there.
I knew this chandelier
was missing something.
[panting]
[keys clacking]
♪
[gasps]
Where are you?
Taiyo!
Give Yoshiaki back!
Give him back!
[gasps]
Yoshiaki.
♪
My brother, thank you.
I... I just never knew.
[RUI]
Thanks, boss.
I hope we meet again.
Huh?
Holy crap, is that...
[BOTH laugh]
[RUI]
He still had it, after all that.
[JACK]
Not funny. Show some respect.
-[SOUMA groaning]
-[JACK] Huh?
Hey, look who's awake.
Mornin', kiddo.
I'll be happy to cut him up.
-[YUKI] Wait.
-[ALL] Hmm?
[SOUMA groaning]
[YUKI]
Come back to me, Souma.
[SOUMA, weakly]
You haven't changed, sis.
You always think you know best.
Even now.
You know what?
I hate that part of you.
[scoffs]
You do this thing.
You carry yourself as if only
you can save everyone.
[inaudible]
♪
[grunts softly]
[SOUMA]
What do you know...
about what I can bear?
Was I always just
a weight on your back?
Don't treat me like
I'm still a child!
You're the one
who should come with me.
I'll be the one to save you.
I will. I have to...
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Souma.
[weeping]
I didn't understand.
I never knew you felt this way.
♪
That's why I told you.
Not only did Souma's plan fail,
our enemies have him now.
It's a very upsetting
state of affairs.
So, then, tell me how you
didn't see this coming
with your powers?
Why didn't you tell us?
Wasn't this the result
you wanted?
[TSUKI]
Hmm?
♪
I have no idea when he will
regain consciousness.
But as long as
he keeps resting here,
his body should recover,
I feel certain of that.
[TAKUYA] We have do something
about this soon.
Before the Agency
takes him back.
[TAKUYA]
Sorry I'm late.
[YOSHIAKI]
Not at all.
This way.
[YOSHIAKI]
Hey.
Are you really planning to go?
I mean, if he were
to wake up right now...
[TAKUYA]
Yeah, that's why we're leaving
before he regains consciousness.
I want to do what I can,
and to do that,
I need some solid proof
of his relationship with them.
Will you come with me?
[KEIGO]
Hey, you must be Takuya.
[TAKUYA] So these were
the guys watching me?
Yeah, we know you're very sharp,
but we're not the enemy.
We'd like to go with you
to the Light of Hope Academy
for Children with Disabilities.
[BOTH gasp]
[YUJI]
Our friend was murdered.
[KEIGO]
We're not after you guys, okay?
So that's how it is.
[YUKI]
Yumiko.
[YUMIKO]
Sorry, did I wake you?
Where's Takuya?
[YUMIKO] Well, I don't know,
he went out pretty far today.
[YUKI]
Huh?
[YUMIKO]
Looks like it finally got him.
It's time to face his past.
♪
[TAKUYA]
Next episode, "Regret."