[FEMALE SERVANT 24A]
Young master, please stop!
Don't go in there!
[YAKOU] So you must
be my familiar.
Yes, I see.
You're different.
Someone from the branch family
becomes the familiar of
someone from the head family.
That must be the reason
you were chosen for me.
What precisely
is a familiar?
[YAKOU] Uh... Basically,
it means you serve me.
And I'll protect you in return.
Here.
[YAKOU grunts]
[YOUNG HISHAMARU whimpers]
Hey, you know
what I think?
You're very pretty.
[YAKOU] I'm counting
on you, now.
You can call me...
[TOUJI]
What are you gonna do?
[HARUTORA] First, get Natsume
back and then go find Suzu.
[KON] Um, M-Master Harutora!
[CROWS shriek]
Stupid-tora!
[DASSAI]
Listen to Zenjiro!
I'll go with you to apologize!
Of course they're here.
Should've known.
So you won't let us pass?
[CROWS whimper]
Then, bring it on!
[CROWS yell]
Aahhh!
[CROWS caw]
[SUZUKA] Order!
[CROWS yell]
[TOUJI] Suzuka!
We can be decoys while
Harutora gets away.
Sound good?
[SUZUKA] Mm.
Touji, no!
Don't worry about us;
just do what you gotta do!
[HARUTORA] Mm.
[KOKURYUU scream]
Are you gonna do this
with me, Suzuka?
[SUZUKA whimpers]
Stupid-tora.
If you die in the place of
Natsume, I swear I'll--
I will die to bring you back,
do you understand me?
I hear you, but
I'll be coming back.
So please wait.
Wait for me!
You ready for this!
Now, Kon!
[KON]
Yes, sir!
[CROWS] Aaahhh!
Order!
I'll be back.
[TOUJI] I know...
We'll be waiting for ya.
You can do it!
[HARUTORA] Heh.
Raven Coat, come now!
[HARUTORA] Touji, Suzuka, Kyoko,
Tenma, and Mister Ohtomo.
Because they all
supported me
with everything they had,
I'll see Natsume again.
[KON] Master Harutora!
[HARUTORA] Kagami.
I'm drawing out Ohtomo and
I'm gonna use you as bait.
Well, someone took good
care of this guy, didn't they?
[HARUTORA] Shut up!
Natsume and I almost
died because of him!
Oh, I'm sure it was a good
lesson for you, though.
But, uh...
From what I've heard,
your precious girlfriend learned
her lesson a little too late.
He said shut up!
[HARUTORA grunts]
Huh? Are you ready
to fight, now?
Let's have it, Harutora.
I'll be sure to
beat you up real good,
exactly like I promised I would.
Order.
Order!
What are you
playing at?
Order!
Principle of the Five
Elements, wood begets fire!
Kon, I'm counting on you!
[KON] Yes, sir!
[HARUTORA] I need to get
to Natsume while I can.
[KAGAMI] Not too bad.
[HARUTORA]
He's so fast.
But how?
Spirit pulse?
The spirit step.
[KON gasps]
Master Harutora!
Ah! Damn you!
Official business!
I've gotta purify the disaster!
What are you planning?
Didn't you hear me?
I'm purifying the
spirit disaster!
After all, that Raven
Coat is a magical tool
designated for use
of forbidden magic!
[HARUTORA grunts]
No you don't!
[laughs]
Master Harutora!
[HARUTORA] Tanyata udakadai
bana enkei enkei sowaka!
Hhhaaaaaa!
[HARUTORA]
I can't dodge it!
This must suck for you.
[KON] Stop it!
[KAGAMI] Huh?
[KAGAMI]
You little brat.
[KAGAMI yells]
[HARUTORA] Kon!
[KON gasps]
[KAGAMI] Get out of my way.
[HARUTORA] Kon!
[OHTOMO recites spell]
♪
[KOGURE] Let's say he gets
to perform the Ritual.
Do you think it
will be a success?
Because if it fails...
I couldn't protect her.
I already failed one.
That's why I'll allow them
to do what they want.
One of my students
said it would work.
What's wrong with
believing that?
Besides, it looks like
Suzu is involved now, too.
Jin! You don't still
trust her, do you?
Mostly. She's not the type
to get involved in things
without thinking first.
You're conveniently forgetting
an important fact, pal.
She betrayed the both of us.
I think you should
let that go.
♪
[DOMAN] Enough of this, boys!
[KOGURE and OHTOMO gasp]
This guy can't talk,
so I'm being very kind
and speaking for him.
Director Amami.
What an old fool
that poor man is.
Why can't he just admit
he's far too ancient
for this sort of thing?
Kon, no!
Hey! Come on, Coat!
I need to get down there
to her, now; let me go!
How pathetic you'd
actually sacrifice yourself
for your familiar?
[HARUTORA yells]
[HARUTORA grunts]
Kon!
M-Master Harutora?
[KAGAMI] I see.
My friend, you are
a genuine idiot.
[KON] Master Harutora!
You cretin! You'll pay!
[KAGAMI] Un!
[KON and HARUTORA yell]
Kon... Run away!
[KON]
I will not run.
I will not!
I did not wait this long to have
my master taken away from me!
Not by a scoundrel like you!
[HARUTORA] Kon, it's you.
[HISHAMARU] I'll keep
waiting for you.
Until time itself stands still.
[HARUTORA] Hishamaru?
[HARUTORA BABY cries]
[YASUZUMI] You really
waited all these years?
[KAGAMI] What the?
[KON grunts]
Noumaku sanmanda bazaradan.
Kan!
[KON-HISHAMARU gasps]
Shaver!
Go get him!
♪
[SHAVER] Ahh...
My head hurts so bad.
[KON-HISHAMARU gasps]
Don't underestimate me!
[KON-HISHAMARU yells]
[KON-HISHAMARU] I don't have
enough spirit energy.
[SHAVER]
This is all your fault.
[KON-HISHAMARU] At this rate,
I'll never make it.
I need to force open the seal.
But then, I'll have my
memories from the past.
[SHAVER]
You foolish creature.
Just you wait.
[KON-HISHAMARU]
It doesn't matter!
Memories from another life
should not be allowed to
trump the current master!
♪
[YAKOU] I'm counting
on you, now.
You can call me...
You crazy fool.
What the hell are you?
Get back, scoundrel.
[KAGAMI grunts]
Uh.
[HISHAMARU recites spell]
[KAGAMI grunts]
Oh, no you, don't!
That was amazing, Reiji!
Did you see?
Heh, heh! That was amazing!
[SHAVER laughing]
You filthy bastard!
[KAGAMI] Heh.
[HISHAMARU grunts]
[inaudible]
Kakugyouki!
Hey there, Hishamaru.
Having a little
difficulty, here?
Have you gotten soft?
It's an Ibaraki Ogre!
[SHAVER laughs]
You're just not
worth my time.
You're not strong enough.
[SHAVER] Ah. Uh!
Reiji! Those two!
I'll take them both on myself!
[SHAVER laughs]
We can't win. Retreat.
So Yakou's awakened?
Things will really get fun now.
But, they're mine! Ahh!
Some cloth!
[KAKUGYOUKI]
Oh yes, of course.
Always so very loyal.
[HARUTORA] Hishamaru.
Hey!
[KAKUGYOUKI chuckles]
And where the hell
have you been, Raven?
[HARUTORA]
It's fine, Hishamaru.
It's just how he is.
Can't blame him for that.
[HISHAMARU gasps]
What happens now?
What shall we call you?
[KOGURE] Jin. The Onmyo
Agency will be after you.
If I'm ordered to... so will I.
I'm sure you will.
Director Amami.
I will let this go
out of respect for you.
However, I'd like
to make a point
that The Onmyo Agency is needed.
And as long as there
are people in this world
who need the Onmyo Agency,
my sword will swing for them.
[TAKIKO gasps]
Hello, Harutora.
Should I still call you that?
Or do you prefer "Yakou," now?
Call me what you want.
[YASHAMARU] Hmm...
I see. Harutora, then.
I didn't mean to--
for that to happen with Natsume.
But I doubt what I say about it
really means anything
to you now, does it?
[HARUTORA] No.
[chuckles]
Well, what do you
want to do next?
[HISHAMARU gasps]
Princess?
I will give you Natsume.
Of course...
I'm not saying this will
atone for my actions.
Take her.
♪
Goodbye, Harutora.
We shall meet again.
[door opens, closes]
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have kept
you waiting, Natsume.
♪
Good to see you.
[KURAHASHI] Even so,
the path of Onmyo
will not come to an end.
Master. Thank you.
I appreciate you
accompanying me.
There's no need to thank me.
I was just returning a favor,
don't you remember?
[OHTOMO]
About that favor.
As I recall it was
because I won?
Indeed.
I lost to you in a contest of
magic fairly and squarely.
After you toppled me,
I should have been
purified without a trace,
so I can hardly
complain about this.
[OHTOMO] Tell me how you feel
about the repayment so far
of the debt you've
said you owe to me?
Well, to be honest, it
seems rather insufficient.
Agreed.
However, I'm thinking
you could repay
the rest of that debt in one go.
[OHTOMO] I would like you to
become my familiar, Master.
Familiar?
You realize you'll
be overcome by me?
Well, if that happens,
I'll give you my other leg;
does that sound
reasonable to you?
Afterwards, I'll just beat you
in yet another contest of magic
and take my freedom right back.
Oh-ho, I like that.
Yes. How fun!
You're selling your body
off one part at a time!
[OHTOMO] Your answer?
I'll do it.
From this moment on,
the Onmyo mage Jin Ohtomo
shall be my master!
Great. Thank you.
[KYOKO] Harutora.
I wonder if he managed it.
[SUZUKA] He promised me.
[KYOKO] Huh?
He promised to
bring Natsume back.
He promised to come
home safe and sound.
[TENMA sighs]
[phone rings]
It's Suzu!
[SUZU] Hello Tenma.
Good morning.
[TENMA] How's Harutora?
Did the Taizan
Fukun Ritual work?
[SUZU] Basically.
[GROUP gasps, chuckles]
[SUZU] I'd like to thank
you for your hard work.
We won't see each other
again for a while,
but you should stay focused.
[KYOKO] Hm?
[TENMA] What do
you mean by that?
Did Harutora
sacrifice himself?
[SUZU] Don't worry,
they're both alive.
Kind of.
What does that mean?!
[SUZU] A lot happened.
[TENMA]
Can you give us a hint?
[SUZU] Harutora wanted me
to say "thanks, man."
[TENMA]
So, he's with you then?
[TOUJI] Tenma!
Speakerphone!
[TENMA] Uh.
Harutora, you jerk!
Are you there?
Please, say something!
Stupid-tora!
[SUZU] My ear!
[HARUTORA laughs]
[click]
[GROUP] Ah! Harutora!
[phone rings]
[SUZU] It's me.
[GROUP gasps]
[SUZU] Please leave a message
when you hear the beep.
Come on, really?
Do you guys think
Harutora turned into Yakou?
I dunno, but I do think
we should ask him in person.
[GROUP] Huh?
Let's find him and ask,
"So who the hell are you, dude?"
And, "Did you forget about us,
or were you just
being a stupid jerk?"
I swear if that idiot
turned into Yakou,
I'm gonna smack him good.
Please do,
I won't stop ya.
Heh. He should apologize
on his knees first.
Just think about it.
He got us into all
kinds of awful trouble.
Anyway...
I doubt things will
ever go back to being
how they were before
this crazy adventure.
But that doesn't matter,
because we've got
the same goal now.
Together, we'll find
those two idiots
and seriously let 'em have it.
[TENMA] Hm.
[KYOKO] Hm.
[SUZUKA] Hm.
♪
[HARUTORA] Natsume.
Natsume.
[NATSUME exhales]
How are you feeling?
[NATSUME] What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Trust me; I'm fine.
[NATSUME gasps]
Stupid Natsume.
Tell me. Why did you
come and see me as Hokuto?
[NATSUME gasps]
Why?
That entire time, I thought
you were avoiding me.
It kind of hurt my
feelings, you know.
[NATSUME] I...
Harutora, I...
Oh, Harutora.
I love you.
You already knew that, though.
♪
[HARUTORA] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I must go.
But, I'm sure we'll
meet again, eventually.
Harutora,
please don't leave me.
Please, Harutora.
[NATSUME gasps]
[NATSUME] Harutora.
Just a little longer.
Just let me sleep a
little while longer.
[NATSUME] I need to be able
to build up enough courage.
Then, I can fly off on my own.