[HARUTORA chuckles]
[HARUTORA] Man...
the sky is so blue.
[HARUTORA] So this
is Onmyo Prep...
Not bad.
From what I've heard,
everything they have
is top of the line...
Guess when it comes to
training onmyo mages,
the elite don't
pull their punches.
[HARUTORA] This hasn't
really sunk in yet...
[ALPHA] Harutora Tsuchimikado
and Touji Ato?
Did that thing talk?
I think they're familiars.
[OMEGA]
We are Alpha and Omega.
High-grade artificial familiars.
[ALPHA] We have confirmed and
registered your spirit energy.
You may now devote yourselves
to becoming good onmyo mages.
[HARUTORA]
This place is ridiculous.
[OMEGA]
Harutora Tsuchimikado...
I have also registered
your familiar.
Huh? I don't know
what that means.
[MIYO] Welcome to Onmyo
Preparatory School.
Please come to the principal's
office immediately.
I'm Miyo Kurahashi...
and I'm the principal here.
I suppose the two
of you must be
Natsume's Hishamaru
and Kakugyouki.
You've heard the rumors,
too, haven't you?
About Natsume...?
They're saying she's
the reincarnation
of Yakou Tsuchimikado.
The "unfortunate"
attention Natsume receives
will probably be directed
at you now, as well.
We are certainly here if
you should need our help...
However...
I hope you can learn to
tolerate it as soon as possible.
Natsume has managed to.
[HARUTORA] I never thought
about how much crap
she must've been putting
up with this whole time.
So, let me ask you boys
what impression do
you have of Yakou?
He's an old,
famous relative
who's kind of annoying...?
I mean, he caused like
a lot of trouble, right?
[MIYO]
What about you?
[TOUJI]
Just the facts...
Back during the war,
he used his skills to develop
Imperial Onmyo Magic at
the request of the military.
Right before we
were defeated,
he completely screwed
up a magic ritual...
and that was what caused all
the spirit disasters in Tokyo.
He had good
and bad points
so it's kinda hard to express
him in a single word...
He was a genius...
I know that.
He liked to play shogi.
Although, he wasn't very good.
I think he liked it more
because he was bad at it...
He was always asking
people to play with him.
He would sulk when he lost...
and that didn't necessarily
go over well with everyone.
[TOUJI gasps]
You mean you've met him before?
I was only a child
at the time, but yes,
I have met him...
Yakou was human...
a regular guy,
just like you boys...
It seems sometimes
people forget that fact.
And worse...
there are more than a few that
refuse to accept the truth.
They're called
"Yakou devotees"...
they ignore his humanity...
blindly putting
him on a pedestal.
They are still
obsessed with him...
and have even tried to
make contact with Natsume.
[HARUTORA]
With Natsume?!
[MIYO] Remember, an impression
is one type of magic...
Rumors are yet another...
They affect people and can
very easily mislead them.
[knocking]
[OHTOMO] Principal?
My apologies, but please...
Tell me this whole thing
isn't gonna take much longer.
Not much longer at all...
We've actually just finished up.
[OHTOMO] Heh. Like it...?
Pretty awesome, doncha think?
I happen to be a sorry
excuse for an onmyo mage...
so I kinda like to bluster
around a little bit.
[HARUTORA]
This guy is weird...
Meet Mister Jin Ohtomo...
He'll be your homeroom
teacher this year.
Huh?!
Hey, what was
that reaction for?
[footsteps]
[OHTOMO]
Don't let her fool ya...
She's not just in charge here...
That old lady is
pulling more strings
than you can shake a stick at.
Who's Hishamaru
and Kakugyouki...?
The principal asked us if we
were Natsume's version of them.
[OHTOMO] Those are the names
of Yakou's familiars.
They were always
by Yakou's side...
and they did whatever
it took to protect him.
By all accounts, they
were incredibly strong.
Well, get on with it,
guys; greet your class.
Harutora Tsuchimikado... Hello.
And I'm
Touji Ato.
You're not gonna sell
yourselves any more than that?
[HARUTORA] Like it would
make a difference.
[HARUTORA] Natsume?
Sorry... didn't mean
to keep you waiting.
Now, Harutora and Touji
are behind the rest of you
by half a year, so please
help them out when you can.
[KYOKO] Excuse me!
[OHTOMO]
What's up, Kyoko?
You got a problem?
Maybe it's just me,
but uh...
a new transfer seems strange
at this time of year...
Wouldn't they like normally have
to wait for a new semester?
Did the Tsuchimikado family
have something to do with this?
If so, I don't
think that's fair!
[students whisper indistinctly]
[thud]
[NATSUME] These accusations
are outrageous.
Uh oh.
This won't be good.
[NATSUME]
Kyoko Kurahashi,
you've insulted the
Tsuchimikado family...
Apologize to him and to me!
If that's how you're going
to be, then bring it...
Confess...
I heard he's really
your familiar!
We have to assume
he's only a student
so you can have your
familiar nearby, right?
Why else would he
even enroll here?
Heh.
[NATSUME] Then, are you
accusing Onmyo Prep
of bowing to the whims
of a lowly student?
[KYOKO]
You're not lowly!
You're the next head
of the Tsuchimikados.
[NATSUME] Oh don't
start with that...
You know the current
Tsuchimikado family
is practically ruined.
As a matter of fact,
your family's the only one
who could get away with
something like that.
[KYOKO] Huh...?
More importantly...
your little opinion on
why they're enrolled here
doesn't matter in
the slightest...
My family doesn't care...
and I seriously doubt
the school does.
Huh?!
[HARUTORA]
Wow, she's cocky...
Look at her face; she totally
thinks she won this.
So uh...
...are you going to
stop them or what?
Whoopsie... I forgot
what I was doing.
[HARUTORA] Guess we
can't count on him...
You got any thoughts?
Wait, you look happy
about this, too!
What is wrong with everyone?!
Try not to let Kyoko
get to you, okay...?
You have every
right to be here.
[HARUTORA] Yeah...
sure I do.
Something tells me that girl
must always be freaking out.
Oh, yeah...
but what happened earlier
wasn't exactly a normal thing...
I don't usually get all
bent out of shape like I did.
Yes, never;
of course you don't.
This is weird...
Why are you two
acting so familiar?
I mean, you just met yesterday.
What's the problem,
Harutora,
are you
gettin' jealous?
What does it matter
to you, anyhow?
[HARUTORA] I dunno.
You okay?
Yep...
But there's really
nothing to worry about...
No need to
be jealous...
I can be
friendly to Touji
without knowing
him all that well.
Guess so.
Yeah...
And plus, um...
If I had to pick the
person I'm closest to...
Then I'd pick you, Harutora!
Huh?
[TENMA] Natsume!
Time for your
individual training.
Sorry, I have to go...
I'm studying a special
curriculum in another classroom.
[NATSUME]
Oh, hey, you guys?
I am really glad that
you two are here.
Yeah. Me too.
Sure, man.
Maybe it's the boys'
clothes, but uh...
she seems way less
mature than normal.
But like...
not in a bad way.
What ever you say,
dude...
now how bout it...?
Let's investigate.
Thank you for the food.
[TOUJI] What's up, man;
how's it going...?
I was wondering if
you could tell me
more about the school
and like class stuff...
What's your name?
Huh...? Who, me...?
I'm Tenma...
Tenma Momoe.
[HARUTORA]
Can I join you, too?
[TENMA gasps]
Quit being creepy,
Harutora...
So, Tenma, did you hear
about that rogue onmyo mage
out in the countryside?
Believe it or not, we sorta
got involved in that.
Huh? Are you serious?
[TENMA] So that's
what happened...
must've been pretty
difficult for you guys.
Yeah, I guess...
Anyway... That angry
girl from before...?
What family is she
a member of again?
Kyoko...?
Oh, she's a member of
the Kurahashi family.
Kurahashi...
Like the principal?
[TOUJI]
Miyo Kurahashi.
She's the doyenne of
the Kurahashi family.
[TENMA] Kyoko is actually the
principal's granddaughter...
Oh, and her father's
pretty important...
He's the current head
of the Onmyo Agency.
Wow, her family is
really distinguished!
Mmhm. But historically
the Tsuchimikado family
has actually had
a higher status.
That's probably why she thinks
of Natsume as her rival...
They're both so much smarter
than the rest of the school...
and I think they're
the only ones who have
defense familiars, too.
Defense familiars?
Still, I was pretty
surprised...!
I've never seen
Natsume get worked up
about anything like
he did earlier...
He always seems so calm
like nothing gets to him.
[NATSUME] I do not
have time to waste
by spending my days
idly or making friends.
You must be like pretty
important to him, huh...?
I mean, for him
to get so upset...
that was crazy.
Stupid-tora...
Are you an idiot?
I knew you were dumb,
but I didn't know
you were "should have never been
accepted into this school" dumb!
You didn't...?
I did.
[NATSUME grunts angrily]
[NATSUME]
Fine, Intense training for you!
We're going to make up
for the sixteen years
you completely wasted!
First, from An Intro to
General Onmyo Magic...
memorize the different types
of "Onmyo Magic Type Two."
And don't worry;
I know a spell that will let you
function without any sleep...
If you don't mind the
traumatic side effects,
you can easily stay awake
for an entire week!
[HARUTORA] Side effects?
What?! What are they?
What's gonna happen to me?
Hate to interrupt ya, but...
Oh... is it
that time already?
Guess we'll have to do
that intense training later.
[NATSUME] Borrow those
books from the library
and make sure you read them!
I wonder if there's
a spell out there
that could make a guy
like me smarter...
[TOUJI] Don't take this the
wrong way, but probably not.
[HARUTORA] Wow, thanks...
[HARUTORA] How long can
I keep going like this...?
Oh, yeah...
I've still got the familiar
Dad gave me as a goodbye...
Now, how am I supposed to
get this thing to work.
Huh?
[KON] Oh wow, it's an honor to
meet you for the first time!
You can call me K-Kon...!
Nice to meet you!
I-I have...
I have been charged
with the task
of protecting you,
Master Harutora.
I am still inexperienced,
but I hope that...
that you will understand!
Hold on
a second...
You mean
you're a familiar?
[HARUTORA] This is the
familiar Dad gave me?
Wow.
So why did you pop
out all of a sudden?
[KON] I was making
myself invisible
when I heard your voice,
so I became visible...
Wait... you mean you've been
like hiding this whole time?
Oh yes!
I had to because I must
always and forever
protect Master Harutora!
[OMEGA]
Harutora Tsuchimikado,
I have also registered
your familiar.
I... I don't really
remember it...
but your branch of
the Tsuchimikado family
has used me at some
point in the past.
You're saying I'm not the
first person in my family
you've appeared to?
All right, Kon...
How about you show off all the
cool stuff you can do for me?
Oh, yes, sir!
Invisibility!
Awesome...!
I can't see you at all!
Whoa... Cool!
[KON] It's because I'm separated
from reality right now.
Niice! That's a
great trick, Kon!
Thank you...
it was no big deal, though...
[HARUTORA]
What else?
I can fly in the air, too!
[HARUTORA] Ooohh!
What else, what else?
Ma-Manipulate fire!
That's real fire!
Anything else?
Huh? Lemme think...
I can turn any enemy of
Master Harutora's into rust...
My beloved sword, Kachiwari,
takes care of that!
Well, okay...
Understood...
And thank you...
Think you can put the
sword away now, please?
[KON] Huh? Yes, Master.
[HARUTORA sighs]
There's something
you should know...
I'm kinda new at this whole
magic world thing...
I honestly don't know
if I'll even be able
to use you properly.
What are you saying...
Does that mean that...
Do-Does that mean
that you don't need me?
[HARUTORA] No, no, no;
that's not it...!
It's just that I'm basically
like an apprentice right now.
I'm not a person you
should be bowing to.
[KON] No, that's
not true at all!
I was by your side and I
watched you for the whole day!
Then you should
know the truth...
[KON] I do...
And I am proud to be
Master Harutora's familiar.
[KON] Um...
Am I being a bother?
A bother...?
No way...
I'll be counting
on you from now on.
Oh, well that's good
to know; same here!
By the way what's the deal
with your ears and that tail?
[KON] Oh...
I'm a spirit fox.
Hmm...
Uh... you mind
if I touch 'em?
It's cool if you
don't want me to.
No; it's not that I
don't want. That is, I...
Well go ahead...
Really? Cool!
Oh, they're so fluffy!
Like my dog at home...! Hah, ha!
Can I touch your tail, too?
Oh, of course.
Oh wow...
This is a pretty
amazing tail, Kon!
Thank you...
I am delighted that you...
are having so much fun.
[HARUTORA] You can move this
however you want, right...?
How does it work?
How what...?
Well uh...
It... works... like...
Hm?
[KON] Like...
It works like this!
[NATSUME] Harutora...!
You didn't check out any
of the books I gave you--
Aaaahhh!
[HARUTORA yells]
Listen, this is so not
what it looks like...!
You have to believe me...!
Please, Natsume!
[NATSUME] What do you
think you're doing?
Nothing... Nothing!
Looks like you need a dose
of Pervert Punishment...!
Pervert Punishment...!
Order!
[HARUTORA screams]
[OGRE 4A] It's having more
of an effect than expected.
[MAGIC INVESTIGATOR 4A]
Yes it is, unfortunately.
[OGRE 4A] Don't you
think the people
of the organization
are being too careful?
After all, the king has
already been vindicated.
[MAGIC INVESTIGATOR 4A] We would
like to continue being cautious
for a while longer if possible.
[OHTOMO]
Pretty handy, isn't it?
After reaching the
Independent Exorcist Class,
taking care of a Phase 2
is really just that simple.
I'm surprised she
didn't kill me...
[OHTOMO] What are you spacing
out about, Harutora?
Uh--Uh?
You feelin' all right;
you look a little tired there.
[HARUTORA] No...
I'm fine; sorry.
[KYOKO] Um, sir...
Could you continue with
the lecture please?
I'd rather not waste more
time than we already have...
It's not my fault
people are so behind.
[OHTOMO] Hm. So you're saying
we should abandon students
who can't keep up? Yes?
That's right.
[OHTOMO] After all, there's
really no point in Onmyo Prep
rescuing anyone who won't be
useful in the future, is there?
The "soft" ones who don't
realize what's going on
should just leave now...
That is the school's policy
on the matter, anyway.
But you know what...?
As a teacher, I'm not
a big fan of this policy.
You're not a big fan...?
What does that mean?
Bit contradictory,
isn't it...?
Now, Onmyo Prep
knew how I felt...
But they decided to go ahead and
bring me in as your
homeroom teacher anyway...
Why do you figure they
might've done such a thing?
Wanna know my opinion?
[OHTOMO] In short...
the real world
can be complicated.
[OHTOMO] It's rough.
The world of adults very rarely
makes sense, and I'm sorry...
What are your thoughts on
the subject... Harutora?
Uh... I...
I dunno...
The truth is I have a hard
time following the lectures.
And honestly,
it'd help me a lot
if you took that
into consideration.
[KYOKO] So basically
you have no problem
causing trouble
for the rest of us?
[HARUTORA] No.
I never said that.
I feel really bad about it...
But just like you guys...
I'm a student at this school.
I have the right to be
here and to learn...
like anyone else.
I've sworn to become
an onmyo mage.
That's my first
priority, not you.
[OHTOMO chuckles]
Do you not get
this is a place
for those at the top
of their class?!
You have no talent, so why
the heck are you even here?
[KON] That's enough,
you scoundrel!
Aaahh!
How dare you be so rude?!
Just because my master is
dumber than everyone else,
doesn't mean you can sp--
You're the one being
rude right now, Kon!
How can you embarrass me in
front of all these people?!
And what do you mean I'm
dumber than everyone else?
You're making fun of me?!
How is that supportive?
You're supposed to be
my defense familiar--
[KYOKO]
Hakuou! Kokufuu!
[KYOKO] I can't believe you can
use defense familiars, too.
And why you couldn't be
upfront about it anyway?!
I'm really confused.
This girl keeps getting
ruder and ruder!
I'll no longer hold back!
[clapping]
Nice to see you're both
motivated and enthusiastic...
Gives me an idea...
Why not have a battle
of the familiars?
[HARUTORA] Ugh...
Of course he'd say that.
You know I've never done
anything like this before,
don't you?
Oh, I'm sure
you'll be fine.
And, novice or not,
you shouldn't belittle yourself.
To be honest,
I have doubted you...
But what you said before...
Well, it was reassuring...
I thought, "Even with
all that's happened,
he still wants to
be an onmyo mage."
All you need to do
is simply improve
your natural abilities
your own way.
[OHTOMO chuckles]
[HARUTORA]
Mister Ohtomo...?
What's up?
I have a favor
I'd like to ask you.
Um...
Master Harutora?
Now, I've gone ahead
and cast those spells
on the armor and
the wooden sword.
Oh... thank you sir,
I really appreciate it.
What's with that costume?
The familiars are
the ones fighting.
Why do you insist
on looking silly?
Insolent
little wretch!
[HARUTORA] Kon...
you can take care of
the light one, right...?
Just leave the dark
familiar to me.
Leave it to you?
Ah! I can't do that,
Master Harutora!
Stop messing around!
This is a battle of familiars...
you can only fight
with familiars!
[HARUTORA]
That's what I'm doing.
I'm a familiar too. Heh.
All right then...
Is everyone ready?
[OHTOMO] Begin!
I finally appeared
in the anime!
Yahaa!
Even better,
I'm here!
Me, too!
Yay!