Count your blessings.
It's time for the
big boys to play, kids.
For the time being,
you lucky brats
get to be guarded by me.
What the hell?
Why you?
Harutora.
This isn't the time.
Hm.
Hey, Shaver.
Watch them.
Sure.
♪
Hey, Kousaka.
Thanks for earlier, man.
Oh, yeah, no problem.
[MALE OFFICER 16A]
Is Kousaka here right now?
[MALE WORKER 16A] Uh yeah.
I just saw him at his desk.
We're Public Security
Division. MCIB.
[MALE OFFICER 16A]
Everyone, stop your work,
leave your desks,
and line up along the walls!
I repeat, stop working and
line up along the walls now!
[KOUSAKA] They're here!
Delete and destroy
anything and everything
that might be
seen as evidence.
Escape. Then gather
at the appointed place!
[GIRL] My mommy
told me to tell you
"thank you for
saving me, sir!"
You're welcome;
I'm glad you're okay.
I truthfully don't
know how we can
ever repay you.
Please. I'm just
doing my job.
Bye-bye!
[HIRATA] It's going well.
At each branch,
members who came up in the
internal investigation
are being checked
one after another.
Well, we have been
working on this for a year.
If it doesn't go well,
we've got bigger
problems than devotees.
[scoffs lightly]
And, what of Makihara?
No word yet, sir.
Mmm.
[AMAMI] Nothing will
really start until
this guy makes his move.
[KOUSAKA] A significant
number of people
have already been arrested.
[MAKIHARA] There aren't many
officers in Shinjuku yet.
Just come here.
[KOUSAKA] All right.
Thanks, Makihara.
[sighs]
[NATSUME] The investigation
is pretty ambitious.
Mister Ohtomo
said they were after
some big fish this time.
What's the deal with
our freaky new stalker?
[TENMA] They called
him "Shaver," didn't they?
[HARUTORA] That dude
is hella creepy.
I texted Suzuka
earlier to see
what she knew about him.
She's a Divine
General, so I thought
she might have an idea.
[digital tune]
[gasps]
Hey, speak of the devil.
[SUZUKA] Tell Stupid-tora
I hear Shaver is
a dangerous familiar
that Kagami's been
forbidden to use
by the Onmyo Agency.
No matter what
he looks like,
do not let your guard down.
You good?
What on Earth is
wrong with you, now?
Uh. Sorry, I gotta
go get new chopsticks.
Boring, boring,
boring, boring, boring,
boring, boring, boring.
[KAGAMI] Hey.
I wanted to talk to ya.
Get your ass over here.
What do you want?
[KAGAMI sighs] Is that how
you show respect to an elder
who's guarding you and
your little group of friends?
Calm down, tiger.
I just wanna know
what happened with Ohtomo.
[KAGAMI] Kogure's said to be
the one who drove "D" back,
but I know that guy
barely made it in time.
Which means, there was someone
keeping "D" busy until
Kogure got there.
I'm naturally
very curious as to
how that scene played out.
First, confirm something.
Is Ohtomo still alive?
Answer me.
Well, yeah, of course.
That guy's alive and kicking.
[KAGAMI laughs]
You call that
"alive and kicking"?
You sure don't expect
much for the guy
who saved your life,
do you, Harutora?
[grunts]
If you already knew,
then why ask?
So he looks rough.
I knew he couldn't
be doin' so hot
after a fight like that.
[HARUTORA] I hate this tool!
[KAGAMI] Will you
tell me about it?
[KAGAMI] You know, the
details of the magic battle
between Ohtomo and "D."
You were actually there,
but imagine how I feel.
Wouldn't you want to
know what happened, too?
So talk to me, kid.
Don't be so arrogant.
Talk to me.
♪
[KAGAMI] Wait. He chanted
"these bamboo leaves," right?
And then he pulled
out something that was
wrapped in bamboo leaves.
[KAGAMI] Interesting.
Uh! Salt! It was salt
that he sprinkled!
The Curse of the Calming
8-Holed Woven Cage!
You've heard of it before?
Yes, but I only
really know the name.
It's based on a spell
from the Kojiki.
But the bastard came up
with most of it himself.
And then?
What did Doman do?
[HARUTORA] He laughed,
said he didn't know
how to reverse it.
That was all.
What is taking that
loser so freakin' long?
[TENMA] His udon
must be soggy by now.
Thanks for the info,
but talking to you
about this is pointless.
The things you paid attention
to weren't off track,
but your explanations suck.
Eh! Gimmie a break, man.
I wasn't born a seer.
Well, I wasn't
aware of that.
But, I guess it makes sense.
[KAGAMI] You might
be spiritually tough,
but your handling of spirit
power is sloppy as hell.
The gears aren't in sync.
Basically, your power
and your gears
don't match up.
Something feels off
in its composition.
Maybe the Tsuchimikado blood
is having an adverse effect.
Yeah. Or it's just because
I'm a failure at life.
I don't care though,
because I'm gonna become
a professional Onmyo Mage!
[KAGAMI] Really? And then
what are you gonna do?
Uh.
I don't know what you mean.
[KAGAMI chuckles]
When all's said and done,
will you just be
an Onmyo office
worker or teach class
to a bunch of kids
better than you?
So what if I did;
what's terrible about that?
The world of Onmyo mages
is based on ability.
Those who have talent
also have a way of
rising to the top,
but those who already know
they're failures
will go straight to
the "insignificant" pile.
[KAGAMI] Whether you accept
it or not, you're path is
a very different one
from your friends.
Whether you
accept it or not,
you're a real bastard.
Eh!
[chuckles]
I bet you didn't know
that you're the first person
who's ever talked like
that directly to my face.
I'm here,
Master Harutora!
[KON growls]
[KAGAMI] No need to
worry about me.
I don't intend
to kick a stray dog
that hasn't been
trained properly.
[KAGAMI] After all, what
would be the point in that?
By the way, Harutora.
[KAGAMI]
If you're going to try,
you might as well
become an exorcist.
'Cause if you ever become
a halfway decent hunting dog,
I'll have no problem kicking
you without holding back.
I'll kick till you're
curled up, yelping for mommy.
Sounds like fun.
You gonna make it
worthwhile for me?
Begone, evil spirits!
♪
[KOUSAKA] We're under siege!
When the King
of the North Star
becomes aware of
our heroic deeds,
he will awaken
and rush to our rescue.
[DEVOTEES cheer]
[MALE DEVOTEE 16-1] Let's
rise up! As Yakou devotees!
[MALE DEVOTEE 16-2]
We are the rightful heirs
of Yakou's will!
[MAKIHARA]
Now that they're cornered,
they've lost the
ability to reason.
This is not righteous
indignation.
They're simply
letting their desire to
prove themselves right
get out of control.
[MAKIHARA]
They need a leader.
And that means the
responsibility lies with me.
[FEMALE DEVOTEE 16A]
King of the North Star!
Listen!
If you are truly
supporters of the king,
what good will it
do for you to die?
We need your lives once
the king finally awakens!
[DEVOTEES gasp]
Then what are you
suggesting we do to survive?
[MAKIHARA] First of all,
I need your help.
A number of spirit
disasters will
soon occur in
this branch office.
We'll use the
confusion to escape.
Mutobe left a
magical tool that could
manipulate spirit pulses.
It seems it belonged
to Master Doman.
[MAKIHARA] We were
entrusted with the device
for situations just like this.
All we need to do
is buy some time
before the spirit
disasters start.
Until then,
we'll be your shield!
For the King
of the North Star!
[DEVOTEES] For the King
[DEVOTEES hollering]
[MAKIHARA] It's me.
[ETOU] The preparations
are complete.
But I can't
guarantee you won't
be caught in the
spirit disasters.
[MAKIHARA] I understand.
At least the number of
exorcists gathered will help
prevent any civilian injuries
on the grounds of
the branch office.
I'd have preferred
it if no one was hurt,
but sadly, that option is
out of the question, now.
[ALL gasp]
[MALE DEVOTEE 16B] Makihara!
They're breaking through
the barricade, sir!
Damn, I thought
we'd have more time
before they made it this far.
[MAKIHARA] The spirit disasters
are still going to happen!
This is it. Everyone
get out of here, now!
[coughing]
[KOUSAKA] Aah!
[breathing heavily]
[cell phone buzzing]
[HIRATA] This is your liaison.
First, update me
on your situation.
We're almost annihilated.
We've all been
trying to escape,
but I don't know how many
of us will make it out.
[HIRATA] You're
trying to escape?
[MAKIHARA] Yes, using
one of Master Doman's
magical tools
left by Mutobe.
[HIRATA] Master Doman?
[MAKIHARA] Our plan is to use
it to create spirit disasters
and escape in the confusion.
[HIRATA] Good to know. I suppose
there's no going back now.
Right, if even
one or two of us can--
Sorry about this.
[gunshot]
[HIRATA] The Magical
Investigation Bureau
didn't know about
Doman's tool either.
I was right to come take
care of this in person,
take care of you.
The liaison, it's you?
You don't know the whole
truth, but it would be
problematic for you to fall
into the hands of the MIB.
Believe me.
[HIRATA]
I'm sorry, Makihara.
[cell phone beeps]
[HIRATA] It's finished.
However, there will soon be
spirit disasters
in the branch office.
Correct. The Twin
Horn Syndicate
within the agency
has been wiped out.
So Kagami can also--
Yes, I know.
I don't want him
near Kagami either.
[AMAMI] Would you mind giving
the phone to me next, Hirata?
[scoffs]
[HIRATA] I had a feeling
that you were on to me.
When did you realize?
My apologies,
but the only one who's
going to be asking questions
at the moment is me.
[gun hammer clicks]
[AMAMI] Actually, it's been
fascinating watching you work
so aggressively even after
the plan went into effect.
I was so impressed, I almost
felt bad about the fact
that I would
have to call you out.
I was shocked, though.
I didn't think murder
would be so easy for you.
[AMAMI] I believed I had a
pretty good understanding
of Yakou devotees.
But I never would have
imagined there was scum
like you on their side.
Now, calm down and don't
do anything stupid, Hirata.
[HIRATA] I am going
to restrain you.
Is this the part where
you try to brainwash me
into becoming
a Yakou devotee?
If I can welcome
you as a comrade,
it would be worth any risk.
And on top of that,
you'd be quite the catch.
[AMAMI]
I am terribly honored.
[HIRATA] Please,
don't move, Amami.
Let me be clear and say
this one more time, Hirata.
Calm down and
don't do anything stupid.
[groans]
[HIRATA] My movements!
Order!
Oh, don't bother with that.
You should have realized
I wasn't just talking
to hear the sound
of my own voice.
I've already made
the first move, kid.
You should be ashamed.
[HIRATA] Wait.
This is a high-grade spell.
Is this Kagami's?
[AMAMI chuckles]
Give me a break.
A real high-grade spell
is more elegant than that.
It's much more refined
and sophisticated.
A magical form of art.
[HIRATA] A magical tool?
There's probably a spell
on the other side of that fan.
No, there's more
to it than that.
Everything he's said up to now
has to have been
laced with curses.
[AMAMI] What's wrong? Feeling
a little cornered over there?
[AMAMI'S footsteps]
I'm calling for you, now.
You have Defenders?
Servant familiars?
Don't tell me this guy is...
An Imperial
pallbearer? Impossible!
[AMAMI] Just what
in the world are you?
[HIRATA'S FAMILIARS roar]
[AMAMI] Arrogant bastard,
aren't you?
Om biro bakisha
nagya jihata ei sowaka!
♪
That man's spirit power
is incredible! Kingi! Gingi!
[AMAMI recites spell]
[AMAMI continues]
One! Two! Three! Order!
Oh, there's no use.
Four!
Heh. How about that?
Stop! That's enough!
[AMAMI] Very impressive
spiritual pressure!
I must know.
What in the world are you?
I am a Yakou devotee.
I am someone who
has inherited his will.
So you don't consider
yourself the same
as the Twin Horn Syndicate?
I am nothing like them.
They genuinely
believe that as long as
Yakou is finally resurrected,
they will receive their
own personal glory.
But they've become
frustrated with
their faith's inability
to produce rewards, yet,
their lack of faith
causes them to blame Yakou.
Those people have
no shame to speak of!
From what I've heard
that's just the kind of
organization the
Twin Horn Syndicate is.
[HIRATA] Wrong! The Syndicate
was an organization
created in order to realize
Yakou's last wishes!
But instead,
they've been reduced to
a group of mindless,
ignorant fanatics.
[AMAMI] Hmmm.
So that must be
the reason you decided
to kill your former
comrades. Right?
[HIRATA] If they wanted
to be the foundation of
the realization
of Yakou's will,
then they should
have been satisfied.
[HIRATA] I regret
the sacrifices that
had to be made this time.
However, I plan
to bear the burden
of these sins personally.
[AMAMI] Isn't that
noble of you.
So tell me, then.
What exactly is the Syndicate
founded on, anyway?
How old is this group?
Is it true the
organization was formed
by contemporaries who were
taught by Yakou himself?
[HIRATA] Those who
follow Yakou's will are
divided into two groups.
One is the
Twin Horn Syndicate.
The other group is
the Onmyo Prep School.
[HIRATA] The Onmyo Prep
School was originally created
by Yakou from his
desire to raise new,
talented Onmyo mages.
In the same vein,
the Twin Horn Syndicate
was formed because
of his other desire.
We are all
students of Yakou,
and we are all here
because of Him.
I understand.
But I'm curious,
what is the other desire
of Yakou's
that you speak of?
What is it you're
trying to accomplish
for your master?
Director Amami,
listen to me carefully.
[gasps]
[HIRATA] Why? Why am I telling
him everything like this?
[HIRATA exhales shakily]
[AMAMI] Hirata?
Look at me. Just tell me.
What is it you're
trying to do?
[HIRATA] The director of
the Onmyo Agency's MIB
has lowered his guard
and is asking me
innocent questions?
This is wrong!
There's something
wrong about it!
[AMAMI] Concentrate.
Please. Talk to me.
[HIRATA] How could
I be so stupid?
This is all a spell!
Restrain him!
[AMAMI] Oh dear,
is that as much as I get?
Did you know
when you're dealing
with a rather
difficult familiar,
it's best to ensnare
its master immediately?
But how? When could
you have done it?
Why worry about
such minor details.
Now would you mind
handing me my fan?
[AMAMI]
It's right behind you.
♪
Divine Fan, Daizen Amami!
No. I've failed.
Don't worry about that.
[AMAMI] You did
pretty well, kid.
[thud]
I told you at the very
beginning, didn't I?
The only one
who's going to be
asking questions here is me.
Those Imperial Pallbearers
had me going for a while.
This was more of a headache
than I imagined it would be.
[AMAMI gasps lightly]
What? There's no way.
You've gotta be kidding me.
What the hell is going on?
[HARUTORA] Even if class is
over, it doesn't mean that
they're done hunting
the Twin Horn Syndicate.
I think we should
stick together
as much as possible.
Touji and Tenma are
looking for Suzuka,
so she can join us.
[ETOU] What are you doing?
How can you just
waste our time?
[ETOU] There are people fighting
desperately on your behalf.
I'm not sure what
you're talking about.
Does this mean you're not
going to help them, then?
Are those stupid
believers' simply
insignificant beings
that are beneath you?
Too worthless
for you to notice?
Please, enlighten me,
King of the North Star.
[NATSUME and KYOKO gasp]
The Twin Horn Syndicate?
Boring, boring, boring,
boring, so boring.
[KON] Let Master Harutora
have more to do next week,
please and thank you.