[TOUJI] I never
liked that damn kid.
Touji, what's goin' on?
Been awhile!
[TOUJI] My doctor's overly
happy son. I knew on the inside
he had to be looking
down on the half-ogre.
I saw it in his eyes.
What's wrong?
[TOUJI] I kicked and punched.
Beating those dark
emotions over and over.
[TOUJI] It made me feel better.
After that, I couldn't stop
smiling the whole night.
I smiled as I cried,
and everything changed.
♪
This guy is great.
An ogre.
Oh, I'm sorry,
a half-ogre.
What?
He's a half-ogre?
He didn't
tell anyone. Why?
[KAGAMI] Seems a little
half-assed right now, though.
You know, it would
be a whole lot easier
if you just let it take over.
[HARUTORA grunts]
[KON] Master Harutora!
[KAGAMI] Dairenji was like you.
In the spirit disaster
attack two years ago,
he became an ogre himself
and was the nucleus of
the entire catastrophe.
Let me guess;
this kid just happened
to pick up an ogre
about that time.
So what if he did?
Who cares?
An independent exorcist
can't just ignore
the seed of a spirit disaster.
Let him go!
[TOUJI] Get your damn hands
off me, you scarred freak.
I couldn't care less if you're
one of the Twelve
Divine Generals.
If you insist on acting like
a prick around a half-ogre...
You're gonna wind up dead!
Touji.
[TOUJI] You could hold back a
little, bro. Gimmie a break.
I'm at least attempting
to control myself.
Get away from him,
bastard!
Why cleanse an old
spirit disaster?
It's not like that's
part of your job, right?
[KAGAMI] Wow.
You guys finished yet?
[KAGAMI] Not that
I'm not having fun.
[HARUTORA] His spirit energy.
[DASSAI] Kagami!
What are you up to?
[KAGAMI groans]
[KOKURYUU] Dragon!
There's a dragon!
Kokuryuu, forget about that.
Focus on Kagami.
He's misbehaving again.
[KOKURYUU] Ah, Kagami!
Shut up.
[KOKURYUU] You dirty Ogre Eater!
What have you done now?
Are those crows?
[KOGURE] Kagami.
What happened to the nue?
Its presence
seems to be gone,
but it didn't feel
like it was purified.
Kagami let
the nue get away!
He messed up huge!
I've seen this guy before.
He's one of the
Twelve Divine Generals.
So, dude?
What's the word?
It's like they said,
the nue got away.
You seriously couldn't bring
it down? Well, why not?
[KAGAMI]
Something distracted me.
This is definitely
the Twin Horn Syndicate.
I figured as much.
I see the Onmyo
Prep School is here.
Jin did mention them to me.
All right, then. I'm heading
out, and so are you.
[KAGAMI] What?
[KOGURE] You heard me.
I'm sure Kagami was
charming as usual.
But we've got an
emergency on our hands,
so I'm gonna have to take
him with me right now.
Good luck!
The problem is
Kogure's too nice!
That's the reason
Kagami takes advantage!
[KOGURE] Quiet.
Let's go, Kagami!
[KAGAMI] Harutora.
Touji. Natsume.
Remember me.
Because I'll remember you.
He's gone!
He used a spirit step
to travel through the pulse.
One of the most
difficult techniques
of Imperial Onmyo magic.
So those guys are two
of the Divine Generals.
Ah-- Touji!
Are you all right?
Say something!
[indistinct crowd chatter]
How is he?
Dunno. He hasn't woken
up yet. They're still trying
to stabilize the seal
my dad put on him.
I can't believe
he's an ogre.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to all you guys.
Maybe I should have
said something earlier.
Don't be sorry.
What were you supposed to say:
"P.S. Touji's an ogre"?
Just promise me you
won't blame him.
He kept quiet about
it for my sake.
I swear the guy really is safe.
My dad's been treating him
for it for the last two years.
Whenever he took me with him,
it looked really painful.
Back then, he couldn't
help himself,
and he would lose control.
That's when he'd start
turning into an ogre.
But now he's okay! Please,
you have to believe me!
[MALE TEACHER 8A] There you are.
The principal would like to
speak with you for a minute.
Why would you ever involve that
irresponsible brat in this?
[AMAMI] Kagami is an
independent officer.
There will be times we
need him for purifications.
There have been four
confirmed nue so far.
Two at the demon gate,
and two at the back demon gate.
The ones at Ueno and Shinagawa
have been taken care of,
but the other two escaped.
The Clairvoyance
Bureau is searching,
but they still can't find them.
You barely manage your
job, and you get paid!
But you're fine with making
competent people work for free!
[AMAMI] Work for free?
Why would you say that?
I just got a fee
request from Miyo.
[OHTOMO] That greedy old bat.
[AMAMI laughs]
Yes, that's her.
Oh, one more thing.
The strategy they
used two years ago?
They're planning to go
with that this time, as well.
Classic Exorcism
Department's HQ screw up.
You're kidding me.
[KYOKO] No way!
How can you use Natsume's
family dragon as bait?
It's complicated,
but dynamic spirit disasters
prefer the refined yin
that dragons possess.
It's still not fair!
[MIYO] No one said he'd be
forced to do it, my dear.
Oh, and Kyoko.
[KYOKO] Huh?
You really should remember to
speak to me more politely here.
But he can't!
It's not safe!
My father... Did he
give his permission?
Yes, according to the
Exorcism Department.
In that case, I will
report to them right away.
[TENMA] Natsume!
[KYOKO] Please don't do this!
[MIYO] The spirit
disaster this time
is the same as the
one two years ago.
There is a very
high possibility
that this is a terrorist
attack by Yakou devotees.
In truth, it will likely
be safer for Natsume
to stay at the
Exorcism Department.
[phone rings]
Yes... Thank you
for letting me know.
[MIYO] It seems Touji
has regained consciousness.
[NATSUME] Great!
[HARUTORA]
Really? Is he okay?
[MIYO] I'm not sure.
They weren't watching him,
and he disappeared.
He disappeared?
I assume that he was
a little disoriented.
This is not a good turn
of events, I'm afraid.
[NATSUME] Stupid-tora.
[HARUTORA] Huh?
[NATSUME] Why aren't you
going after him right now?
What happened
to you, anyway?
The Harutora I know wouldn't
hesitate to go after his friend.
But I'm your familiar, and I
have a duty to protect you.
You're my responsibility--
[NATSUME] And you wonder
why I call you dumb.
How could you ever protect me
if you can't focus on
anything but him?
[HARUTORA] But still, I--
Listen to me, Harutora.
[MUTOBE] Soon, Chief.
Very soon.
[door opens]
Relax, guys; there's no
need to be on edge.
Come on in.
I'm Zenjiro Kogure,
an independent exorcist.
[panting]
[HARUTORA] Kon!
[KON] Yes, sir!
I need you to help me
find Touji immediately!
I will do everything
in my power, Master!
[HARUTORA] Tenma, you start
looking over there!
[TENMA] You got it.
[panting]
[KOGURE] Want some?
[KYOKO and NATSUME] Mm-mm.
[KOGURE] Suit yourselves.
They're good.
Sorry we had to call
you out here like this.
[KYOKO] No problem.
I think it'll be best if
you two just accompany me.
I'll basically be your personal
bodyguard; does that sound okay?
You're one of
the Divine Generals.
Yes. You shouldn't
waste time on us.
You're not a waste,
don't worry about it.
Besides, everyone in
the department will be
rallying today. It won't
turn into two years ago.
I hope not.
Natsume, the key to
this plan is you.
We have to lure out
the nue. We can't fail.
Positive you
don't want any?
[NATSUME] Thank you.
We actually haven't
eaten anything since lunch.
I'm starving.
By the way. Jin is your
homeroom teacher, isn't he?
By Jin, you mean,
like, Mister Ohtomo?
Yeah, we went to
school together.
Same place as you girls.
[KYOKO] What? Are you
telling me Mister Ohtomo
is still, like,
just twenty something?
[OHTOMO] Hm?
We were in the
thirty-sixth class, yeah.
Everybody called us the
Three Crows back then.
[KYOKO] If there were three
crows, who was the third one?
[HIRATA] Excuse me.
[KOGURE] This is Hirata from
the Magic Investigation Bureau.
He'll be coming
along with us today.
Nice to meet you.
I'm an MIB investigator.
We're glad you're here.
[NATSUME gasps]
[HIRATA] I know what you're
thinking, but my colleague's
actions were a disgrace
to the Bureau's good name.
I deeply and sincerely
apologize on his behalf.
Believe me when I say
I am on your side.
Yes. Of course.
Bring it down a bit;
that's a lot of pressure.
You're just making
Natsume feel awkward.
[NATSUME] No, it's fine.
[HIRATA] I'm only
trying to apologize.
Like I said,
I'll protect you.
But don't ever let
your guard down.
[KYOKO and NATSUME] Right!
[TOUJI] "You're an ogre.
Do you have any emotions?"
Who was it that said
that first? A teacher?
My mother, aka the mistress?
[TOUJI] Either way, it was true.
I had no feeling, or more
accurately, no passion.
I just kept looking for
something to fill the void.
Back then, I was
always on the hunt
for some sort of trouble
to get into. A distraction.
But I never expected to be
attacked by a real ogre.
I'd rather be in control
of how this ends.
So I might as well roll
with what's happening.
I don't really care what
goes down after that.
[panting]
[HARUTORA] Damn it. Where
did that idiot run off to?
[HARUTORA] Shibuya's too big.
I can't search every street.
[HARUTORA pants]
[DRUNK MAN 8A grunts]
[HARUTORA] I'm sorry!
[DRUNK MAN 8A]
You should be!
You need to watch
where you step!
[HARUTORA] Great. I don't
have time for this!
[DRUNK MAN 8A] I don't
like your attitude!
[KAKUGYOUKI] I wouldn't
fight him if I were you.
A boring fight isn't worth
it for the ones fighting
or the ones watching.
You should let it go at that.
Otherwise, the kid's gonna
get a little help from me.
And I guarantee I can
make it interesting.
[DRUNK MAN 8B] Let's go.
[DRUNK MAN 8C] Damn.
Lucky for them they
weren't too drunk
to make the right decision.
[HARUTORA] Thank you, sir.
I appreciate your help!
You looking for someone?
I don't know who that might be,
but I did see a boy
wearing your same uniform.
He looked a little strange.
You tend to remember the
ones that stand out, right?
That sounds like him.
Where'd he go?
[KAKUGYOUKI]
He's up that way.
The practical exam.
Thank you again!
I hope you
find him soon.
[HARUTORA] Me too.
[HARUTORA gasps]
[HARUTORA pants]
[NATSUME]
Listen to me, Harutora.
I can fulfill the
Tsuchimikados' duty by myself.
At the moment, you have
something far more important
you need to take care of.
Find your friend
and bring him back.
You can protect me afterwards.
I dunno; will you be
okay all by yourself?
[KYOKO] He won't be by himself!
I'll go with Natsume, so you
don't have to worry.
[HARUTORA] Are you sure?
Don't you remember
what you told him?
About letting others help?
You can depend on us,
too, you know.
Thank you.
[NATSUME] Harutora.
You need to get going.
Yeah. Right.
When you find him,
you should make him
buy you some sort of reward!
[HARUTORA] Touji!
[TOUJI] What're you here for?
Uh, to get you, obviously.
Come on, let's go.
[NATSUME] Most people still
blame the Tsuchimikado family
for the spirit disasters.
But at the same time,
we're the ones who make it
possible to purify them.
These exorcists must have
pretty conflicted feelings
about me being here.
But none of that matters now.
It doesn't change
what I need to do.
[MALE ANNOUNCER 8A] Chimera
Zero One, approaching!
[KOGURE] It's here.
[MALE ANNOUNCER 8A] Hokuto.
Approaching demon gate!
[TOUJI] This is
pathetic, isn't it?
Sure, the principal added
a few nails here and there.
But the lid,
it still opened.
[HARUTORA] I don't
feel the ogre spirit,
but I definitely smell an ogre.
[HARUTORA] That doesn't
sound like you, Touji.
What was it my dad said?
Something about the ogre living
in people's dark passions?
And you told Dad not to worry,
that you didn't
have any passions,
and that meant there was nowhere
in you for an ogre live.
That was back when you
were still pretending
you didn't care if
you turned into one.
[TOUJI] Yeah, well
nothing's changed.
It's not that I want
to be an ogre now.
It's more that I don't
really care either way.
Dude, for real.
No offense, but I think
your brain got eaten
by the monster inside.
[TOUJI] It's possible.
I don't know if these
are my own thoughts or what
the ogre inside is thinking.
Not that it truly
matters in the long run.
Can't change what's happening.
It's completely taken a
hold of my essence now.
Did you really
just say "essence"?
You're only a year
older than me.
Sorry, man, but we don't
have an essence yet.
[TOUJI] You're wrong.
I'm not the same as you.
There it is. That's what
all the hipsters say.
I get it.
You're special.
You think about crap
that doesn't matter.
[TOUJI] At least that's
better than being
an idiot who
doesn't think at all.
[HARUTORA] Hey, I know one of
those important historical guys
who said, "don't
think, just feel."
Now will you drop this
crap and come home?
We've got enough we're
dealing with already.
[TOUJI] Just leave me here.
Sorry, man,
can't do that.
Guess that's just my bad
luck kicking in again.
[HARUTORA] I think I'm
starting to get through.
So we go home.
And then, what?
Lemme guess: strengthen
the seal one more time
and trick the
ogre inside of me?
[HARUTORA] What do you expect?
Nothing works on the first try!
[TOUJI] I'm going to be forced
to live with a ticking time bomb
for the rest of my life! Do you
know what that means for me?
Do you have any idea
what that's like?
[HARUTORA] Isn't that why you
came to Onmyo Prep School?
To get rid of the ogre
completely someday?
[TOUJI] Someday?
Yeah, someday, right.
That sounds a little less
specific than I'd like.
How can you know I won't
lose control before then?
If it's gonna happen, there's
a faster way to get there!
I just have to let myself become
a full ogre, and be purified!
Then at least I'll know. And
I'll have some kind of control!
[TOUJI growls]
[HARUTORA yells]
[NUE roars]
Look at it.
I wouldn't be surprised if this
thing went into Phase 4 soon.
[KYOKO shudders]
Nou mak saraba tataki gyatei
byak. Saraba bokkei byak.
Saraba tatarata
sendan maka.
[KYOKO] Look out!
The miasma!
[NUE roars]
Miyachi saves
the day again.
[NUE roars]
Think this could happen
to Touji one day?
[HARUTORA] Come on!
[HARUTORA] You're acting
like a spoiled brat!
Now listen to me!
Your life isn't your own,
and, by the way, it hasn't
been for a long time!
Me and my dad. Hokuto.
Natsume. Kyoko. Tenma.
Your life is what it is
because of all the people
you've had around you!
And you can't just decide
out of the blue that you
want to give it all up!
[TOUJI] Do you really want
to fight? If you get hit by me
even once, your head will
be crushed into nothing!
Dare you to try!
You're a fool.
So what if I am?
[NUE roars]
Not Touji. No.
Why not?
[NATSUME] He always puts on
this cool act, you know?
But he's actually more like
Harutora than he thinks.
[NATSUME] Despite the fact
that he's been dealing
with something as heavy
as this, he was always
more concerned for his friends
than for his own safety.
I think that's why he
gravitates to people
who get themselves into trouble,
like me and Harutora.
He has an instinct to protect.
Touji would never turn into a
spirit disaster. There's no way.
I believe in him.
Harutora!
What's the matter?
Can't do it, huh?
Someone doesn't want to crush
their best friend's head!
We haven't been friends all
these years for nothing!
Come on, I know you well enough
to know you could never kill me!
Face it, dude, you
care about all of us
because that's just
the kind of guy you are.
Think of it as a
curse I put on you.
Nah. It's your fault;
you did it to yourself!
And this isn't the kind of
curse that a stupid ogre
would have the power
to destroy, either.
As long as it's with you,
you have no choice
but to fight the ogre with
everything you've got.
You need to accept
that fact already!
You are such a
pain in the ass.
[HARUTORA sighs]
Man. I'm getting
too old to get
caught up in
this kind of drama.
Stupid Touji.
[EXORCISTS] Om shuri mari
mamari mari shushuri sowaka...
[KOGURE] Seems to be going well.
It's a special barrier. The
Bond Princess must be here.
[MALE ANNOUNCER 8A]
Chimera Zero Two! Sighting!
[NATSUME and KYOKO gasp]
[KYOKO] The one from
the practical exam site.
[NATSUME] It's gotten bigger!
You're up, Natsume!
[NATSUME] Yes, sir!
Hokuto, lure it over here!
[HOKUTO DRAGON roars]
[NUE roars]
[MALE ANNOUNCER 8A]
Ready the barrier! Deploy!
[NUE roars]
[MUTOBE yells]
The spirit pulse!
[NATSUME and KYOKO gasp]
[NUE roars]
[MALE ANNOUNCER 8A] Confirmation
of a chain of spirit disasters!
Chimera Zero One,
moving to Phase Four!
moving to Phase Four!!
♪
[DASSAI] Kagami,
what are you doing?
[KOKURYUU] It's something
bad again, isn't it?
[DASSAI and KOKURYUU]
Kagami, Kagami, Kagami...