[HARUTORA] Crazy...
There's spirit
energy everywhere.
[HARUTORA] Hokuto...
I never had what it
took to be a mage...
But that's all changed now.
I'll do this...
For you.
[NATSUME]
Forward, Yukikaze!
[neighs]
[SUZUKA]
Not long now...
Have patience, brother...
I'll bring you back soon.
[SUZUKA]
We have company.
I see her!
[roars]
An armored demon?!
We have to find a way
to get through!
Yeah, I know...
But for now, maybe
we should just land.
[NATSUME] Right!
Here we go.
All right,
take us back up!
'Kay!
Suzuka!
This is a mistake!
Please! Stop!
It would only be a mistake
if I didn't know
what I was doing!
You know I'm strong
enough for this spell!
[NATSUME] Listen!
You can't control it!
In the end, you're
committing suicide!
[HARUTORA] Natsume!
All spells dealing with
souls are forbidden...
It is a form of magic
we should not meddle in.
That incantation...
It's a relic of a bygone era,
when people blindly
followed religion.
It's not to be
taken lightly...
You can't just go through
the motions with no faith.
I'm not the first to try
and revive this ritual...
The great Tsuchimikados
beat me to the punch...
I won't let your double
standards get in the way
of my success!
Now mind your own business!
Here comes another one!
Take us down, Yukikaze.
Uh!
Pincer attack!
That's bad news...
Dude, this sword
is incredible!
[NATSUME]
It's a defensive sword...
An antique specially forged,
and passed down
through the years.
Well that hit I just
blocked left a mark in it.
What?
[NATSUME whimpers]
No but hey, look.
You can barely even see it...
Oh just don't
worry about it,
now is so not the time.
[HARUTORA] It might help
if you fought too!
Gimme a break! Can't you
see I'm busy steering?
[HARUTORA] She's even
more nervous than I am!
[loud thuds]
Oh no...
The ritual has begun!
Heads up!
Yukikaze!
[HARUTORA gasps]
Harutora, no!
[HARUTORA] Aaaahhh!
[NATSUME gasps]
Please help him, Hokuto!
[HARUTORA yells]
Wait...
What'd you say...?
Did you call it Hokuto?
Natsume!
We have a dragon?!
[NATSUME] Of course
we have a dragon!
Hokuto has been a Tsuchimikado
guardian for generations;
she's practically
a family heirloom.
We're Onmyo mages,
remember?
[HARUTORA] And why weren't
we using her from the start?
[NATSUME] Well, she's not
completely under my control...
[HARUTORA] I can tell.
She's not freaking out.
[NATSUME]
Hokuto, listen...
I order you to defeat
the enemy familiar!
[HARUTORA yells]
[roars]
[HARUTORA] Crap...
I'm going to fall off!
Harutora, you're gonna
have to jump over to me!
[HARUTORA] Seriously?
That's crazy talk!
Aaaahhh!
[HARUTORA yells]
[NATSUME]
Got you...!
Just hold on!
[NATSUME]
Please be all right...
Are you hurt at all?!
[HARUTORA]
I'm fine, Natsume...
Calm down!
Seriously...
You can let go, already.
So listen, you think
the defensive sword
could be used for attacks...?
Huh?
[NATSUME] Sure...
I can try.
Nomak Samanta-buddhanam...
Indoraya sowaka!
[NATSUME] When we remove the
seal from the defensive sword...
It is imbued with the power
of the mighty Sakra...
Then it becomes
an enemy destroyer.
Awesome.
Now that you're
properly armed,
hand me that bow.
Sure thing, but...
No arrows...
I won't need them...
This is a peach bow,
infused with magical energy.
Trust me, it will
get the job done.
All right, then.
I'll create some
kind of distraction,
and you'll go stop
the ritual, okay?
I think that's a good idea...
But you're the familiar here,
so don't you think I should
be the one giving the orders?
Whatever...
Let's go!
Okay!
[HARUTORA yells]
Aaaahhhhhhhh...!
Well done, you got him!
Not yet!
[HARUTORA grunts]
No! Watch out!
[HARUTORA yells]
Aaaahhhhhhhh!
Natsume!
[NATSUME] Got it!
[NATSUME]
The barrier has fallen.
We need to make our move!
[HARUTORA]
Right on! Let's go!
[NATSUME] Kay!
I guess he's not done!
[HARUTORA]
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Having a dragon on
your side has its perks.
I think it's time to end this.
Absolutely.
It's not over yet.
[NATSUME screams]
[HARUTORA] The talismans...
[NATSUME]
They're pinning me down!
Wait...
She made all of these...
...with her own blood?
I am Onmyo mage
Suzuka Dairenji...
In humble supplication,
I offer myself as sacrifice
to the Taizan Fukun
god of the afterlife.
Uh... Natsume...?
What's that?
I'm not really sure...
But... Whatever it is,
it's definitely not a god.
Can you hear me,
brother...?
Please.
[SUZUKA] You came back!
Where... am I?
[SUZUKA laughs]
[SUZUKA] I'm so glad
you've come back to me,
Big Brother!
[blow lands]
Heh. It's not enough.
[TOSHIYA] Suzuka...
Look, I made a new
friend just for you!
[SUZUKA laughs]
I love them, thank you!
Brother?
[TOSHIYA]
It's not enough...
[SUZUKA chokes]
[TOSHIYA] It's not enough...
It's not enough...
It'll never be enough, Suzuka!
[SUZUKA]
No, stop... Brother...
Please, just wait...
I'll give my life...
I'll...
I'll give... my life...
...for you, just...
Just please...
let me be... with you...
for a little while... longer.
[HARUTORA] It was her...
Hokuto is dead because of her...
She deserves this...
Right?
No please...
Brother...
All right...
That's enough!
[NATSUME]
What are you doing?
You stupid brat...!
I said that's enough!
[HARUTORA yells]
Aaaahhhhhhhh...!
Natsume!
Burn these
talismans to ash!
Order!
Nice work...
Now... Let's go!
[HARUTORA]
A spirit pulse...?
I see...
It's acting like the
strings on a marionette...
[HARUTORA] Come on!
Aaaahhhhhhhh!
Harutora! No!
[HARUTORA yells]
Aaaahhhhhhhh...!
[HARUTORA]
Now do your thing...
Blood of the Tsuchimikado clan!
[HISHAMARU]
So that's that...?
Is there nothing that
will change your mind?
[YAKOU] Nothing...
Please forgive me.
[HISHAMARU] I'll keep
waiting for you...
Until time itself
stands still...
I am yours to command,
after all...
Master Yakou.
[NATSUME] Ban! Un!
Taraku! Kiriku! Aku!
Chain of Elements...!
Order!
[NATSUME]
Stop staring at it...!
If you keep looking
into the void,
you could lose your soul!
Is it... over?
[NATSUME] Yes, I think so.
[SUZUKA]
It's not fair...
It's not...
Why wasn't it me?
Yukikaze...
I think we're finished for now.
[SUZUKA] Just kill me
and be done with it...
I murdered your friend, right?
So kill me.
[HARUTORA] Don't say
things like that...
If you died now, there'd be
no one to mourn your brother.
[SUZUKA cries]
[roars]
Rest in peace... Hokuto.
[NATSUME] That talisman...
Hey, is this something
you could fix?
I'm afraid not.
The spirit it once
held has gone...
However...
Whoever you're calling 'Hokuto'
may still be out there.
Or maybe not.
Who knows?
Wait...
What does that mean?
This is a manipulation
type familiar...
Which means the
'Hokuto' personality
you interacted with
was actually a mage...
And that mage is
probably still around.
[HARUTORA] What...?
Who would do
something like that?
I suppose somebody out there
was watching over you.
You'd know better than me...
Yeah, right...
How was I supposed to know that
my friend was just a familiar?
[HARUTORA] I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry...
I hid the truth...
and tricked you.
[HARUTORA] I wonder...
Maybe someday...
I'll see her again...
I hope so.
[NATSUME] Yes...
Maybe you will.
[TOUJI] Man, that storm
was totally nuts!
[HARUTORA] Yeah.
But seriously dude...?
The Hokuto thing is wilder.
So how come you're
so chill about it?
I always had a
feeling there was
something strange
about that girl, bro...
Especially when it came to her
weird little obsession for you.
But if she was a familiar,
then who was
pulling her strings?
And why did she choose you
over awesomeness like me...?
That mystery may
never be solved.
[HARUTORA] Touji.
I've decided...
...that I should go to Tokyo.
[NATSUME] A familiar's
proper place will always be
at his master's side.
Therefore, I command you...
Enroll at Onmyo
Prep immediately!
The school accepted me...
because of my family or
the fight with Suzuka?
[sighs]
I guess it doesn't really
matter that much...
As long as I can be
there for Natsume.
[NATSUME] Stupid-tora!
Stupid-tora!
Crap, am I hearing
voices...?
[NATSUME] Hey...
Long time no see...
So, uh...
Sorry I wasn't here
when you arrived...
Been waiting long?
Wait... You're...
What the heck's going on?
[NATSUME]
Whaddaya mean...?
I just came to pick you up.
[HARUTORA] But why are you
talking like you're a guy?
And why are you
dressed like one?
It's a tradition of
the main house...
"The current heir to the
Tsuchimikado family...
must appear to be a man in
dealings with other clans."
The classes are fine
for the most part...
The tradition is a
little tricky, though.
Ohh kay...
Now I get it!
I'm glad we're on
the same page...
This is the way things
have got to be, okay...?
So deal with it.
So you're not who
you pretend to be.
You've just...
done what you had to.
So... You understand, then?
Thank you...
I was afraid you'd
be upset with me.
Nah...
You could've told me though.
Sorry...
I hid the truth...
...and tricked you.
Sorry.
Whoa... Aren't you
overreacting a little?
You didn't trick me;
I was just surprised.
Are we talking about
the same thing...?
Why'd you tell me you
got what I was saying?
Cross dressing is a family
tradition, that's all...
I mean isn't that what ya meant?
[NATSUME gasps]
[NATSUME] You didn't
get it at all...!
What is wrong with you?
Did your brain turn
into mush or something?
Okay, I'm lost...
Hey, I almost felt that...
[TOUJI]
Why am I not surprised?
You two are ridiculous,
you do know that, right?
[HARUTORA] Touji...!
You finished with
what you had to do?
Yeah... I just had to
check in on some friends.
Oh yeah. I'd like you to
meet my friend Natsume.
What is Touji
doing here?
What...? You mean that
you two've met already?
Touji decided to sign up
for Onmyo Prep with me.
Like seriously...?
He's an amateur, how'd
he even get accepted?
Are you for real?
Dude, I'm standing right here.
Yeah, I've been a seer ever
since the great spirit disaster.
You're a spirit seer...?
Then that means you knew...
I know the difference between
a familiar and a real person.
Pleased to meetcha
Natsume...
That's a very nice
ribbon you got there.
You know what, Chief...
The name 'Stupid-tora' kinda
sums you up, doesn't it?
What?
[NATSUME]
Aaagghh! Forget it!
You two have a lot
of catching up to do
if you want to
make it through...
Prepare yourselves!
[HARUTORA] Geez,
what's up with her?
Wow, sorry 'bout that...
I swear, she's usually
not like this at all.
I would say that's
exactly what she was like.
[TOUJI chuckles]
Wait...
Just what're
you staring at?
What...?
Nothing.
[NATSUME] Then get
moving, Stupid-tora!
Oh I'm sorry.
Whatever you say, Master.
[KON] It's finally
my turn to meet
Master Harutora in
next week's episode...!
Attack! Stab! Twist!