[TAKIKO] Thanks a lot!
I had no idea where Natsume
and Harutora's class was,
and I didn't want to wander.
So, are you like a friend
of theirs or something?
That's right.
It's quite a coincidence to
have you showing me around,
since I know your
father as well.
You know Dad?
[door knob turns]
[YASHAMARU] Hey.
What are you
doing in here?
I simply came to say hello.
Long time no see.
[KURAHASHI] You're looking very
young lately, aren't you?
[YASHAMARU] It wasn't
really my choice.
I have to match her.
And where is
Princess Souma?
She just stepped out.
Left rather early
to meet someone.
The next heir of the
Tsuchimikado clan.
You mean you still
haven't been able to
get a hold of your father?
No.
[TAKIKO]
Natsume! Harutora!
Takiko?
Hey! It's really good
to see you guys again!
[HARUTORA] Yeah.
Why are you here?
I'm supposed to take a tour
of the school grounds today.
You certain it's her?
I am.
[HARUTORA] She's the one we
were talking about before:
Takiko Souma.
[HARUTORA and NATSUME chuckle]
First the fire,
now this nonsense?
[KYOKO sighs]
[KURAHASHI] But I specifically
told her to refrain from doing
any excursions
on her own.
Oh Yeah?
Sorry about that.
She got somewhat carried
away when she heard
that we had tracked
down the Raven Coat.
[KURAHASHI] You mean all of
the memories are intact?
My memories?
They're clear up until my death.
That's why I'm filling in
the blanks as best as I can
for the time being.
[YASHAMARU]
But "The Great Purification
of the Dolls' Festival"?
What a fantastic name.
All in all, I guess
we were lucky to
get away with only
minimal damage.
Your strength seems to
have increased, as well.
Yes, I was surprised
by that outcome myself!
If someone like me
has become this strong,
[YASHAMARU] just wait
until the princess decides
to demonstrate her true power.
It will change our world.
No exaggeration.
[STUDENTS chatter]
So many tasty options,
how do you choose?
You haven't seen this
kind of thing before?
[TAKIKO] No!
Moving on.
[HARUTORA] Let's check
out the practice arena next.
Those buffoons.
Shouldn't they be dealing
with "other issues" first?
You're talking
about Kyoko?
Of course.
What else is there?
Well, Harutora and
Natsume both had
a lot on their minds
this morning.
Go on.
You don't know
'bout the fire?
The fire?
[TAKIKO giggles]
It seems like you're
having some fun.
I am!
It's always been my dream
to hang out with everyone
just like this.
Your dream?
I've always had to
study magic by myself.
But hopefully,
that's about to change.
Which means you were
lying when you said
you were already
a student here.
It's not a lie.
That is to say, I'm not
officially enrolled yet.
[HARUTORA]
What do you mean?
Look, it's...
it's still a secret.
Anyway, where'd Chief
Kurahashi's daughter go?
[HARUTORA] She's...
This idiot duo got
into a fight with her.
I'm sorry.
But that means you should make
up with her as soon as you can!
I know she'd understand
if you talked to her.
Do you really think so?
[FUJIWARA]
Excuse me, Natsume.
Please go to the office.
The principal said she had
something to discuss with you.
[NATSUME] I'll head
straight there.
The principal?
Yeah, it's probably
about the fire.
The fire?
That's horrible!
What happened?
Don't worry, it looks
like his father is okay.
[TAKIKO] The Tsuchimikado
main family. Vanished?
Then, when they said
they got the Coat...
What did you do?
[TOUJI and HARUTORA] Uh.
[footsteps]
[HARUTORA] Natsume!
[TOUJI] You find out
anything else?
No. They asked if I
knew anything instead.
So even the principal's
in the dark about this?
Allow me to explain.
This is tough.
But I don't want to hide
anything from you if possible.
[TAKIKO] First of all,
Yasuzumi Tsuchimikado is fine.
I don't know where he is now,
but he's the one who
set fire to the house.
Though it looks like
the aggressive actions
of the Onmyo Agency
were partly to blame.
Apologies.
That's a helluva way
to make a move.
You're saying the
Onmyo Agency attacked
the Tsuchimikado family.
And the fire was the
result of that mess?
Dead right.
However, the goal was never to
oppose the Tsuchimikado family.
It's just... Yasuzumi forgot
about his responsibilities.
If the confrontation
stemmed from that,
all I can say is that
it couldn't be helped.
Hold up a sec. What are
you trying to tell us?
Uh!
Back off!
Natsume.
My family has a bit of
a history with Yakou.
And I have a personal
interest in him as well.
[TAKIKO] Part of
the reason why I'm here,
why I'm so interested in you,
is because you're
his reincarnation.
Then you're just
another Yakou devotee?
[TAKIKO] No!
I'm not like all of those
weirdoes you already met.
I swear.
You have to believe me!
Takiko. What's your
angle on all this?
I just... I just
want to be your friend.
Really.
That's all I want.
I see how close
you guys are.
I've never had any
close friends like that.
[TAKIKO] I'm bad at
expressing myself.
I'm sure I've been rude and
impolite unintentionally.
But magic can communicate
things words might fail to.
So, Natsume...
Just this one time,
would you honor me
with a battle?
[NATSUME] Takiko.
So many things about her
are still a mystery.
[TAKIKO] Order!
[NATSUME] But I didn't sense
any deceit in her words.
Order, wall!
[NATSUME] Besides.
There was something about her.
She reminded me of me.
Of the old me.
[HARUTORA gasps]
Natsume! Watch out, she's
hiding another familiar!
[TAKIKO] Five Elements
sever the spirit pulse!
Order!
[SUZUKA] She severed
the spirit pulse?
Where'd you come from?
That means her dragon
has been sealed away.
Familiars, take form!
Order!
[BIRD FAMILIARS trill]
[TENMA]
Look at that!
Natsume's power level
is spectacular!
[SUZUKA huffs]
Spectacular?
Dude, you sound
like a movie review.
But you're not that far off.
[TOUJI] 'Cause
Natsume always works
harder than
anyone else around.
[BIRD FAMILIARS chirp]
What is wrong with you?
Yakou's techniques
would never be so weak!
[TAKIKO]
Aren't you a Tsuchimikado?
My name is Natsume
Tsuchimikado.
I don't know Yakou.
And I don't want to!
♪
[panting]
What next?
Do you plan on running away
from your fate forever?
[gasps]
One, two, three.
Oh no. This doesn't
look good, you guys.
[HARUTORA gasps]
[YASHAMARU] Do you really
think it was a good idea
to bring us back
from the dead, Chief?
We needed more pieces.
[YASHAMARU laughs]
I forgot how blunt you are.
So, I'd say getting
rid of Amami
proved to be rather
rash, didn't it?
A man of his talent is
simply irreplaceable.
Unfortunately, Souma
got a little carried away.
Oh. Well then forget
I said anything.
That's the reason
for my misgivings.
[YASHAMARU]
She is the princess.
I can't deny, she sometimes
ignores common sense.
But then, all of the ancient
priestesses were like that.
[TAKIKO]
Four, five, six, seven.
I have to ask,
now that the two of you
have become her familiars.
What are the new names
you're going by?
According to our Imperial
Pallbearer contract terms,
Mutobe is Kumomaru.
And as for me,
I was once Shido Dairenji.
Now Yashamaru.
Four, five, six, seven.
[HARUTORA groans]
Harutora!
Weird.
[SUZUKA] Something's off
with the energy flow.
Eight, Nine, Ten.
[HARUTORA groans]
[TAKIKO] Ord--
[OHTOMO]
What have we here?
[HARUTORA yells]
[OHTOMO] A supervised practice
match is perfectly acceptable.
But a real fight is a no-no.
[NATSUME]
Mister Ohtomo!
You're showing a lot of
improvement, Natsume!
Thank you.
[OHTOMO] And you are
Takiko Souma, I presume.
You show ample talent.
My, my.
That's a very intimidating
familiar you brought with you.
Kumomaru, keep back.
Yes, Miss.
[NATSUME] Those eyes.
I've seen them before.
Oh, you fiends!
I'm fine.
Hm. Well then.
Since I'm here,
why don't I show you around
the rest of the school?
Princess.
I think I'll go
home for the day.
[TAKIKIO] Thank you
for your offer, sir.
Takiko.
[TENMA] Mister Ohtomo!
I'm glad to see
you're up and around!
Why don't you just dye
the white hair, grandpa?
You've played hooky
for long enough.
[OHTOMO] Hello, Tenma.
You two, shut up.
When did it start?
The Meguro attack.
I heard you did a pretty
impressive job out there.
[OHTOMO] But this spell.
Oh, that? It's just what
Natsume used to
make me a spirit seer.
[NATSUME] What's the matter?
Did I do it wrong?
It might have
acted as a trigger.
However...
[OHTOMO] There's something
unnatural about
your current condition.
All I can say is that it
feels strangely artificial.
Suzuka. Since
I was kind enough
to remove the
seal on your magic,
would you please look
into this for me?
I need a better
reason than that.
[OHTOMO] If you were to help,
it would mean getting
to play around with Harutora's
body as much as you like.
[KON screams]
What the hell is wrong
with you pervert?
[laughs]
By the way guys, why
isn't Kyoko with you?
These bozos
ticked her off.
They're too scared
to say sorry.
And what started it?
Kyoko found out about
Natsume's dirty little secret.
Hm? What Secret?
[NATSUME chuckles lightly]
[OHTOMO] They pulled
one over on me.
This was about more than
fooling some immature students.
This was a disguise
meant to deceive
professional Onmyo mages.
I see.
It's a simple second-class spell
applied with artisanal mastery.
Kyoko believed that Natsume was
really a boy this whole time.
And what did Kyoko
have to say about it?
[NATSUME]
She called me a liar.
I see.
I wish I knew
what to do.
[OHTOMO] All right, Jin.
It's not the time for cryptic
aphorisms, no waxing poetic.
What she needs
is honest advice.
Hey, Natsume.
[OHTOMO]
You need to talk to her.
I don't think any harm will
come in sharing your feelings
honestly with someone
who is important to you.
Life's too short as it is!
Go apologize, now!
[gasps]
[OHTOMO] Say you're sorry
with all your might!
I said now! Chop, chop!
[OHTOMO chuckles]
Yes, sir!
[NATSUME breathes heavily]
[NATSUME]
Please forgive me!
I'm so sorry, Kyoko!
When I first started
at Onmyo Prep,
the consequences of
misrepresenting myself
never even crossed my mind.
[NATSUME] I had spent my
childhood in the countryside.
And I rarely had contact with
anyone except for my father.
The only person I
ever felt close to
was my longtime
friend, Harutora.
I hadn't even thought
about trying to make
any other friends.
And that's why...
...it was so much easier
for me to go to school
dressed in a boys' uniform.
I'd always been
around boys anyway.
But then we met.
[NATSUME] I was selfish,
and I didn't think
about how that would hurt you.
After you called me a liar,
I suddenly realized
what had happened.
You deserve more.
[NATSUME]
Please, let me apologize!
I'm so sorry!
[KYOKO chuckles lightly]
That was a brave
thing for you to say.
Really.
And you deserve the same
kind of honesty from me.
[KYOKO inhales deeply]
Natsume. You're being unfair!
[gasps]
[KYOKO] You think you can
just apologize like that?
So you get to feel better?
That just isn't how
it works, all right?
[NATSUME] No!
I didn't mean it that way!
[KYOKO] I know, but...
How could you not even notice
that, that I liked you?
[KYOKO] You had a dozen
chances to say something,
but you used your
"tradition" as an excuse
to ignore my feelings
because it was
easier than
confronting them!
--[NATSUME] Sorry--
--[KYOKO] Don't!
When all was said and done,
you didn't
care about me at all!
That isn't true,
I swear it!
And it never will be!
Kyoko, I promise you that
I treasure our friendship!
The fact that you
think otherwise.
It hurts.
'Cause there's no way I'd
ever stop caring about you!
[KYOKO] Stop it!
Don't you dare try to make
yourself a martyr with me!
[NATSUME]
That's not what I meant!
I just...
I don't want to
give up on what we have,
or had or whatever!
Because, it's like,
I love my dad and
Harutora and Touji,
but now I was finally
friends with another girl!
I was happy.
Because you might understand.
[street noise]
[KYOKO] I've been
to your house before.
As a child,
I played with a boy.
He was my first crush.
I always assumed that it
was you, but I was wrong.
Jackass!
He didn't even remember me
after I talked to him about it.
It's like, how
horrible can it get?
Does that mean?
Mm.
It's complicated.
Look who I'm talking to.
You like Harutora,
am I right?
If I told you that I still
plan to go for him anyway,
regardless of
how you may feel,
[KYOKO] what would you do?
Promise me,
when the time comes, we fight
for him fair and square.
Right.
[chuckles] Thank you.
[KYOKO] Oh yeah.
Promise me one more thing.
You've got to swear to tell
Harutora about Hokuto.
[NATSUME] How do you
know about that?
Once you've explained
that whole,
I dunno, total
mess of a situation.
Then, the two of
us will be even.
And back at the starting line.
[KYOKO] Agreed?
[KYOKO chuckles]
Best of luck.
[NATSUME chuckles]
I have an idea!
There's a fireworks
festival tomorrow night.
I can't think of a more
perfect setting for you
to finally reveal
your secret to him!
[MIYO] Takiko Souma?
[OHTOMO] Correct.
What do you know about her?
[MIYO] During the war,
Tsuchimikado was considered
to be the top of
the Onmyo world.
With total support from the
Kura-hashi and Souma clans.
We were defeated.
Then Souma, who had
controlled the military,
suddenly disappeared.
[OHTOMO] Perhaps Souma's
ties to the military
are still in effect?
The disappearance
of Director Amami.
The Tsuchimikado estate
burning to the ground.
And a girl named Souma
suddenly appears.
I find it hard to believe
Chief Kurahashi
would be so out of the loop.
Regrettably, I haven't
seen my son in some time.
Mister Ohtomo,
if you would,
please prepare your
resignation letter.
I see.
A sabbatical would
give me the opportunity
to look in on these issues.
[MIYO chuckles]
Well then.
If I start to move, the task
of watching out for Natsume
would fall upon whom exactly?
Naturally, I would be
glad to keep watch
over the boy in your stead.
"The boy"?
So no one's informed you
about the recent developments?
Why whatever do you mean?
[slap]
Ow! What's wrong?
[sighs] Stupid-tora.
[HARUTORA] My bad.
[KYOKO]
Wanna know something?
You were a lot cooler
when we were kids.
[HARUTORA] Sorry.
[KYOKO chuckles]
Stupid-tora.
Don't be late!
See you tomorrow.
[HARUTORA]
Uh. Right on!
[HARUTORA chuckles]
[MIYO]
What did you say?
Yes, I was not
expecting it either.
Then, Natsume is
actually a girl?
That cannot be right.
I would've sworn on my
life the child was a boy.
It's true.
Yasuzumi. You fool.
[YASHAMARU] Is there a
problem with Suzu Saotome?
[KURAHASHI] For one thing,
she's still missing.
Is that so?
If she's currently MIA, I guess
we should count her out then.
Tell me what transpired.
It turned into
a magic battle.
What?
Just a practice match.
One the princess requested.
Do stop trying to scare
me like that, Mutobe.
Forgive me,
I meant Kumomaru.
Well? She couldn't
have lost, surely.
No, sir. But she did lose
control of her emotions.
Is that all?
I just--
It scares me to think I'm
similar to those devotees.
[YASHAMARU]
You're not, princess.
What you want is not
Yakou Tsuchimikado.
What you want is a companion.
Someone to walk by your side,
someone you can have trust in.
More importantly,
is the revived Yakou
worthy to be your comrade?
That is the more pressing
question, if you ask me.
Miyachi brought this
with him upon his return.
Is it?
[YASHAMARU]
The Raven Coat.
[TAKIKO] Yashamaru!
With this, Natsume will
definitely become our comrade!
Yes. I sincerely
hope so, highness.
[phone rings]
[TAKIKO] Hello!
It's Souma.
[KYOKO]
Oh. Hi, Takiko.
[TAKIKO] I got your
number from your dad.
Sorry to just call out
of the blue like this.
No problem, what's up?
[TAKIKO] Well, I got into a bit
of a scuffle with Natsume today.
I was hoping you might be
able to help us make up.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry;
I forgot the two of
you were at odds.
No, that's over
and done with now.
We set things straight
this afternoon!
[TAKIKO] Really?
[KYOKO] Yeah!
We're all going to the fireworks
festival tomorrow night.
You want to come?
Then maybe I could
help you out, too.
[TAKIKO] That's
very kind! I accept!
Hey, before you go,
one thing.
Was your disagreement
about the "tradition"?
[TAKIKO] I don't know
what that means.
No? It's what
we fought about.
[TAKIKO] Hold on.
What tradition?
Well, here goes.
[TAKIKO] Natsume....
is a girl?
[eerie music plays]
Pluck! And pluck! And pluck!
Then cram it in your mouth!