[cell phone beeps]
[cell phone buzzes]
[SUZUKA sighs]
A tiger?
[SUZUKA] Darling!
Good morning, how are you?
[HARUTORA] Oh, hi Suzuka.
[SUZUKA] How lucky
am I to get to see you
first thing in the morning?
[STUDENTS whisper]
Oh, man, did you see that?
[SUZUKA]
Here. Take this.
[NATSUME] Huh?
[NATSUME yells]
And please be
careful with my bag!
That old thing!
It weighs almost
as much as me! Heh!
But that's no big deal
to you, am I right?
I just know you can handle it.
I mean, since
you're a boy and all.
This should be fun.
[TOUJI] Things are starting to
get interesting around here.
[HARUTORA]
Yeah, thanks for nothing!
[TOUJI] I mean I thought for
sure she'd rat you guys out
right away, but I
guess I was wrong.
Heh. She's definitely
got spunk, that one, huh?
[NATSUME] Oh man.
I thought I would never be
able to lift my arm again.
Okay.
The only thing I can
think of is negotiation.
[NATSUME] Huh?
[HARUTORA] Maybe I can talk her
out of treating us so crappy.
You think it'll work?
Yeah, just leave it to me.
[HARUTORA groans]
[SUZUKA] What? Do
you seriously think
the two of you can talk
your way out of this?
Thanks anyway.
[SUZUKA] What? You realize
you have no other choice
than to say,
"Yes, sir." right?
[NATSUME] Sorry.
Yes, sir.
[HARUTORA] Hey!
I got some!
Heh, heh. A-Aahh!
[SUZUKA] Hey!
Did you forget to say
"sir" to me yet again?
It's very
important.
Beginning and end
of everything.
Sir! Yes, sir!
Darling.
I need a vanilla shake.
As in now.
[HARUTORA]
My pleasure!
[HARUTORA] I'm sorry.
Your hair is losing its shine.
And you have split ends.
[NATSUME]
It's okay, Harutora.
Speaking of, your eyes kind
of look like dead fish eyes.
[HARUTORA] Well, let's
look at the positives.
At least we don't have
to see her face today.
[NATSUME] For real.
I think this is the most I've
ever looked forward to a day off
in my whole life.
[phone rings]
[gasps]
[FEMALE VOICE MAIL] The number
you have dialed is unavai--
[HARUTORA sighs]
[cell phone chimes]
[NATSUME whimpers]
[phone rings]
[gasps]
[ringing continues]
[phone beeps]
[HARUTORA laughs]
[SUZUKA]
Good morning, fools!
[HARUTORA and NATSUME whimper]
[SUZUKA chuckles]
[TOUJI yawns]
Hey, what's wrong?
It's tiny.
Tch.
Shut up.
[SUZUKA] Lucky cats.
Are you kidding me?
That's lame.
Don't tell me you got a tiger
because the last part
of your name means
"tiger." Ya loser.
Yeah, well I don't really
give a crap what you think!
[SUZUKA] Hmm...
Whatever.
[NATSUME] As a punishment
for not picking up the phone,
she made us show
her Harutora's room.
That makes total sense.
[SUZUKA] What's with
this varsity jacket?
Nerd alert!
Look, that's my
favorite jacket!
Why you gotta hate?
Because your fashion sense is
a nightmare; this is atrocious.
Eh?
A tiger...
So, what's the
big verdict?
It's boring
as all get out.
There's nothing cool here.
No nudie magazines or
anything even remotely fun.
Come on!
Go away!
Honestly,
I gotta agree.
He's kinda boring.
Dude, you need to expand
your horizons a bit.
[HARUTORA] Hey, what's
that supposed to mean?
Wait, I know where
you should look.
Check out
his closet.
[HARUTORA] Nooo!
Please, I'm begging you.
Please just go!
Gross.
It stops being fun once
they start the begging.
I guess we can just leave it
at you're lame and boring.
[HARUTORA sighs]
[SUZUKA] Moving on!
How about we hit up
Natsume's room next?
[HARUTORA]
Huh?
No way!
I refuse to let you in.
No means no!
[SUZUKA] What? Why would
you think it's okay
for you to speak
to me like that?
[SUZUKA chuckles]
[NATSUME] Order!
Oh no you don't!
[NATSUME] Aahh!
Let go! Let me go!
[SUZUKA]
No way, are you kidding?
What's wrong with
your room anyway?
This reaction just makes
me want to see it more!
Jeez, how bad can it be?
[NATSUME screams]
[SUZUKA]
Chill out, Looney Tunes!
[muffled yells]
[SUZUKA]
Go san goryoku.
Niku gyoichi yomi.
I knew she had to have it
protected with a spell.
[muffled scream]
[SUZUKA]
How careless.
Hah. Nothing but
a defense spell.
Yeah. Doubtful.
[SUZUKA]
Ugh. A tiger here, too?
Huh, I've never been in
Natsume's room before.
[TOUJI] With her reaction,
I figured there was
something awful in here,
but uh, maybe not.
Everything looks normal to me.
You are so wrong.
Believe you me.
This place is protected.
The barrier is well hidden, but
the spell is quite elaborate.
Whatever she's got,
it's in there.
[TOUJI] Wait, are you saying
she's using another spell
inside the room?
[TOUJI] Ow...
That hurt.
[SUZUKA] Idiots.
This one is a lot stronger
than the spell on the door.
You might wanna take cover.
How come this one's
so much worse?
It's just a stupid
closet door, right?
Yeah, but it looks like it'll
take some time to crack.
At least I'll have something
interesting to do!
On! Sojiri shu sowaka.
On! Makarishiei
jiribei sowaka...
[TOUJI]
What do you think?
Maybe we should just mosey
on outside for a little bit?
[TOUJI] Whoa!
[muffled screams]
[SUZUKA]
Oh, you're so noisy!
Do you want people to find
out that you're a girl?
I said, shut, up!
[muffled yells]
I can't watch anymore.
This is too much for me.
Kon, break the
binds on Natsume!
Um...
Master Harutora, what did the
witch mean by nudie magazines?
Will you just
do it already?
[KON] O-Okay!
[KON] No!
This is bad touching!
[SUZUKA yells]
I need you, Hokuto.
Come, now.
Guard the door.
[KON groans]
[yawns]
[beeping]
[KON yells]
Oh! Master Harutora!
Um. Good morning to you.
Yeah. Good morning
to you, too.
[HARUTORA]
Hey, Kon?
Yes, sir?
I'm just wondering why you're in
your physical form this morning.
[KON]
I-I didn't even realize.
[HARUTORA yawns]
[KON]
Ah! Master Harutora!
[HARUTORA] Hm?
I can't get rid of
my physical form!
[HARUTORA] Hmm?
[NATSUME] She can't get
rid of her physical form?
[HARUTORA]
Yeah, and I have no idea why.
Her invisibility
isn't working, either.
Of course. The familiar
can't function properly
if the master is weak,
now can it?
Tell me something.
Why are you just walking
with us like we like you?
So this is just a random
guess, but hear me out.
Yesterday, Natsume
threw Kon into Suzuka
while she was in the
middle of a spell, yeah?
Wouldn't you think this might
have something to do with that?
[HARUTORA]
Yeah, good point.
You know, maybe we should
ask Mister Ohtomo about it
when we get to school,
and see what he says.
[NATSUME] I don't think
that's what it is.
This has nothing to
do with my closet.
Something else must
be going on here.
And no matter what,
it's not like this is my fault.
So there's no reason
to tell the teacher.
Kay, darling?
[NATSUME]
Better keep moving.
[SUZUKA] Good plan.
Natsume wouldn't say anything
about what she has in her closet
even after Miss Fujino
asked her about it.
And Suzuka doesn't
want to tarnish
the innocent girl impression
she's been laying down.
Yep. Those two
are terrifying.
[KON] How unfortunate.
Look at me, stuck here
at home doing nothing.
Meanwhile nefarious people
could be out there
being disrespectful.
Ahh, I'm beside
myself with worry!
In the first place,
Master Harutora is too kind.
Oh, not that I'm criticizing
his kindness in the least.
I would never criticize anything
about Master Harutora.
I just have to take care
of those nefarious people,
so we won't have a problem.
There's no doubt about it.
I should be by
Master Harutora's side.
[KON bawls]
Ah! I know!
I can go and protect
him in disguise.
I don't have to
worry my master.
I'll just quietly protect
him from the shadows.
A protecting ninja!
Doesn't that sound cool?
I love making good decisions.
[KON] Don't worry.
I'll be right over to help,
Master Harutora!
[sniffs]
Wow! It smells
just like him.
[ALPHA]
Oh, if it isn't Kon.
[KON] Wrong!
I am not Kon.
Excuse me!
[ALPHA]
That was Kon, wasn't it?
[OMEGA] Yes, that
was definitely Kon.
[KON]
I can't see.
Fine, in that case.
Yay! I found you!
You'll be protected now!
Oh no, he's yawning.
Is he not getting enough sleep?
Oh poor master.
What? Natsume's mad at him!
Why? It was just a yawn!
Everyone dozes off now and then.
I can't believe Touji's
sleeping in class.
What a terrible
student and person.
[KON sighs]
I don't know if this
place is suitable
for my Master after all.
What a shame.
You know, I can't believe
the teacher hasn't noticed
and said something.
That's just bad administration.
If he left,
it could be just me and
Master Harutora together.
Oh, that would be great!
I like this plan already!
[bells ring]
[KON] No way.
Is it really lunchtime?
[murmuring]
[HARUTORA] Man, for some reason,
I'm really tired today.
I bet I'm using
my brain too much.
Your brain?
I doubt it.
You couldn't stop yawning for
five seconds during class.
Just another
guess here, but uh,
do you think it's because
your familiar has been stuck
in physical form all day?
I bet she's using up a lot
of spiritual energy that way.
[NATSUME]
Good point.
If you think about it,
keeping that up all day
must be pretty hard.
It looks like we'll have to
take care of this weirdness
sooner rather than later.
[TOUJI] So do you guys wanna go
ask Mister Ohtomo about it then?
I wonder what they're
talking about.
I can't hear anything.
Does that sound good
to you, Natsume?
[NATSUME] Yeah.
[FEMALE STUDENT 11D]
Aahh! What the heck was that?
Something just
touched my foot!
[MALE STUDENT 11E]
Hey, I felt it, too!
[FEMALE STUDENT 11E]
Omigosh me too!
Whatever it is,
it's soft and fluffy!
[FEMALE STUDENT 11-1] Fluffy?
[MALE STUDENT 11F]
Whoa, dude!
There's definitely
something under the table!
There's what?
[FEMALE STUDENT 11-2]
It went that way!
Look! There!
[MALE STUDENT 11-1]
Was that a tiger?
[FEMALE STUDENT 11-3]
I dunno, but it was soft!
[FEMALE STUDENT 11-4]
There's a tiger in here? Aaahh!
[TOUJI] Anybody know
what's actually going on?
[NATSUME] No clue.
Well, that was
a big mistake!
And my embarrassment
is my master's.
At this rate, all the hubbub
I'm causing is gonna mean
big trouble for Master
Harutora, I just know it.
[TENMA]
Oh. Hey, Kon!
[KON gasps]
You're in physical
form today!
I think Harutora is
over in the cafeteria.
Should you even
be here, though?
[KON] Hah!
[TENMA chokes]
Please forgive me,
gentle Tenma!
My goal is only to
protect my Master's honor!
[GIRLS yell]
[KON] I'm sorry!
[FEMALE STUDENT 11F]
A tiger! It's a tiger!
A tiger?
[gasps]
[FEMALE SCHOOL ANNOUNCER 11A]
Attention, students!
Please don't panic, but uh--
We have news that um...
A tiger-like animal is wandering
the school premises right now?
Everyone, please return
to your classrooms
and follow your
teacher's instructions.
[ALPHA]
What, a tiger?
[OMEGA]
That doesn't make sense.
How could a tiger
have slipped past us?
[KON] This is awful.
No one can ever
find out it was me!
[STUDENTS yell frantically]
[TENMA groans]
[TENMA]
What happened?
Hey! Kon!
[KON] Hah!
Why do you have
such bad timing?
[FUJIHARA] Tenma!
Talk to me!
Are you all right?
Aw, come on.
Tenma, noooooo!
It looks like this situation's
gotten way out of hand.
[crashing sound]
[KOGURE] Everyone ready?
Let's see what we're facing!
[DASSAI]
It's a tiger!
[KOKURYUU] Don't let your
guard down, Zenjiro!
[tires screech]
Everybody's here, right?
Everyone besides Tenma.
All right, well, stand by.
[HARUTORA]
Mr. Ohtomo, um--
[OHTOMO] Can you hold
that thought please?
I'm sorry, the principal
is asking for me.
I wonder what's going on.
I wonder where Tenma
disappeared to?
[MIYO]
Tenma? Oh dear!
So there's already
been a victim.
I still can't figure
out how it could've
slipped past Alpha and Omega.
What about this.
Could it be a familiar?
Maybe someone let theirs
out and it's on the loose?
[MIYO]
You think that's it?
[KOGURE] If so, whoever's
behind this is very skillful.
They broke the school barrier,
so they've gotta be at least
as strong as one of the
Twelve Divine Generals.
[SUZUKA gasps]
[MIYO] What on Earth
could they be after?
[KOGURE]
I don't know.
[KOGURE] Don't worry.
It's going to be okay.
You can count on us
to stop this thing.
Right, Jin?
[OHTOMO] Yeah...
Why don't you take
it down a notch?
Tiger!
[SOLDIERS] Tiger, tiger, tiger,
tiger, tiger, tiger, tiger.
I didn't mean for
this to happen.
[buzzing]
[SUZUKA]
What are you wearing?
Talk about lame.
[KON] Shut up!
[SUZUKA]
Oh, calm down.
This may come as a surprise,
but I'm just here to help you.
[KON] Huh?
[FUJIHARA cries]
[FUJIHARA]
Tenma...
[TENMA sighs]
[FUJIHARA] Huh?
[snoring]
[SUZUKA] The truth is
if they find you,
it could make me look bad.
You wanna get out
of here, don't you?
Well, I want you gone
for a while, too.
Okay.
So how do you propose I leave
without being seen, then?
[SUZUKA] Easy.
I'll use my invisibility
spell, and you walk out.
You can really do that?
[SUZUKA] Heh. Come on, never
underestimate a Divine General.
[KON] Is this an
invisibility spell?
[SUZUKA]
Of course it is.
Just remember, when you
get back to the dorm,
you don't know anything.
You can ask Mister Ohtomo for
help if you want, but make sure
your stupid master doesn't
start blabbing about me.
[KON]
D-Don't call him stupid!
That's rude!
[SUZUKA] Would you stop
moving around so much?
[DASSAI] Ah! It's over here!
[KOKURYUU]
Zenjiro, we found it!
[SUZUKA yells]
Order!
A familiar. I knew it.
Your spell is broken!
Well, that's probably because
you messed it up somehow!
[KOGURE] Stop now!
[KOGURE] These kids have their
whole lives to look forward to.
I won't let you hurt them!
Dispel darkness.
Slash into nothing.
Crushing blade!
[SUZUKA and KON]
Aaaahhhhhh!
[KOGURE] Justice.
What the hell?
[KOGURE] Hey!
[SUZUKA] That guy
is seriously insane!
[KON] But at least
we got outside!
We made it this far,
so we should be okay!
[OHTOMO chuckles]
[horn blares]
[HARUTORA]
Whoa, this guy is vintage.
I know 'cause it's just
like the one I've got.
Sure sucks to
be that loser.
Now, this is just
one more wild guess,
but that's probably
your jacket, bro.
What?!
I don't think we deserved
that much grief.
Jeez, this was a rotten day.
I still don't get why
I got in trouble, too.
It's because you
weren't properly
supervising your
familiar, Stupid-tora.
You're not allowed
to call me that!
Man, I'm so bummed
about my jacket.
[KON] P-Please forgive me,
Master Harutora.
Hey, at least you've gone
back to normal, right?
[KON] Heh, heh! That's true,
Master Harutora!
Oh, thank you,
thank you...
[HARUTORA] Alright.
[HARUTORA and KON laugh]
[SUZUKA] Hmph.
Hey, Suzuka, wait.
I'll see you
tomorrow, okay?
Uh.
[HARUTORA] Hm?
[SUZUKA chuckles]
[HARUTORA] Uhhh...
Where'd my porn go?
[KON] Begone evil spirits.
Begone evil spirits.