[HARUTORA] The Doman
Ashiya attack on
the Onmyo Prep School
came to a close
with a mysterious explosion.
[HARUTORA] Mister Ohtomo was
quickly taken to the hospital.
The damage from the
battle could be seen
all over the school.
[HARUTORA] In the end,
the Raven Coat targeted by
Doman had already
been taken away
by Natsume's father,
Yasuzumi Tsuchimikado.
[HARUTORA] While repairs are
being made at the school,
we're to report
to the Meguro branch
of the exorcism department.
The idea is for
students to continue their
magic training while
surrounded by professionals.
[HARUTORA] I've never
seen such raw power.
It's hard to believe
any of us survived that.
I'll be that
strong. Someday.
[grunts]
[KON grunting]
God of the Eastern Sea,
called Amei!
Of the Western Sea, Shukuryou!
[ALL gasp]
[HARUTORA] God of the
Southern Sea, called Kyojou!
God of the Northern Sea,
called Gukyou!
[HARUTORA]
Gods of the Four Seas.
Dispel a hundred demons,
and exorcise disaster!
Kon! Now!
Order!
Master Harutora,
he's gone!
Did I do that?
[KON] There!
Order!
[ETOU] Om bishi bishi
kara kara shibari sowaka!
[HARUTORA] Eh--ahhh!
Stop! That's enough!
I'm coming, sir!
Just hold on!
[grunts]
Big shocker.
[HARUTORA]
I can't do it like he did.
Are you hurt, Master?
There was no
need for you to use
a spirit disaster
counter spell against me.
If you don't even
know the basics,
don't be a copycat.
Take it easy now, Etou.
[ETOU] I thought it was
a bad idea from the start.
But you were insistent.
Learn your place, kid.
You're not ready to
train with the pros, yet.
Give it a few years.
[snarls]
These "pros"
you're talking about
couldn't handle their own jobs.
And now we're at the
point where students
are using your
facilities to train.
When the surprise
attack came to our school,
[NATSUME] where were
you "pro" exorcists?
You certainly
weren't helping us.
--[KON grunts]
--Natsume.
Burn.
[NATSUME] I'm proud of
you for trying so hard
in training, Harutora.
Regardless,
Etou was too strong.
[KON] Uh... With all
deference, Master,
I am of the same opinion.
[NATSUME] Harutora?
[HARUTORA] They were
amazing, weren't they?
The two of them.
Two of whom?
You know. Mister Ohtomo
and... and Doman.
[NATSUME] So you're
still hung up on that? Ugh.
What? Sorry. I guess
I kinda spaced out.
Never mind. It's fine.
[HARUTORA] Natsume.
That altar that was
on the school's roof?
[HARUTORA] It was exactly
the same as the one
from out in the
country, am I right?
So what do you say?
Should we go check it out?
[KON] I-I'll take point, sir.
Please allow me to lead the way!
[HARUTORA] Thank you, Kon.
[HARUTORA] What a mess.
I'm amazed we
even survived this.
[NATSUME] Yeah, if Mister
Ohtomo hadn't shown up
when he did we might not have.
[KON gasps]
What is it, Kon?
[KON] T-There's someone
at the altar, Master.
Who's there?
We're students who
go to this school.
Just taking a look around.
[HARUTORA] Look, it's
pretty dark up here, yeah?
I'm just going
to add some light.
Kon. Flames.
Tsuchimikado.
[chuckles lightly]
[GIRL] You're
Natsume Tsuchimikado.
Then that must make you
Harutora Tsuchimikado, right?
It's a pleasure
to meet you.
My name is Takiko Souma.
I'm a student like you.
Studying to become
a real Onmyo mage.
[HARUTORA] When I think
back to that night,
it was such a
strange encounter.
[HARUTORA] Then again,
odd encounters
happened to us all the time.
[YASUZUMI] So it begins.
The stars have crossed.
[NATSUME] Takiko... Souma?
[TAKIKO] Yes, that's right.
To think I'd actually
get to meet you in person!
If this is all a dream,
then please don't wake me up!
Uh...
So then, you must
be new at the school
or something, is that
right Miss Souma?
Please, just call me Takiko.
They've arranged some special
enrollment just for me.
That a fact?
Which is why we
haven't met before.
Such a shame!
Oh. Right on.
[clears throat]
So then, Takiko.
If you don't mind me
asking, why are you here?
The same reason as you
guys are here, I'd bet.
I came to see
the heavenly altar.
[HARUTORA] "Heavenly altar."
I didn't know
that was its name.
So... you came all the
way up here to see this?
[TAKIKO] That's right.
Do you have any idea
what it actually takes
to put this ritual
altar to use?
Of course not!
[TAKIKO] An amateur
like me could never
understand
the heavenly altar.
After all, this altar
is the essence
of Tsuchimikado magic.
They say it's the
greatest legacy left
by Abe no Seimei!
Some say that even
Yakou himself didn't fully
understand everything
about this altar.
I see, you are aware
of the ceremony
that takes place
here, though.
You mean the Taizan
Fukun Ritual? Naturally.
Isn't the Taizan Fukun
Ritual supposed to be
a secret of the
Tsuchimikado family?
Why don't you tell us
who you really are?
Like I already said,
I'm a fellow student.
I'm studying to
become an Onmyo Mage.
[TAKIKO] I can't say
much more than that,
or else I might
get in trouble.
I'll give you a hint.
Why do you think
the heavenly altar
is here in the first place?
Onmyo Prep used to serve
as Yakou's private academy.
[BOTH gasp]
They called it
the Yakou School.
Open to those with aptitude,
it circumvented antiquated
concepts like bloodlines.
You might even say
the alter was his legacy.
[TAKIKO] You should
ask Principal Kurahashi
for more details
on the whole shebang.
I mean, she was part of it.
She was part of what?
She's the one who
turned Onmyo Prep
into what it is today.
Tsuchimikado found her
when she was really young.
She was a charter
member when the
Yakou school
was first founded.
[gasps]
He liked to play shogi.
Although, he wasn't very good.
[TAKIKO] Some of Yakou's
personal records from that time
may still be somewhere
on school grounds.
Do you really think
you can trust some
random chick you just met?
I'm not sure. That's why
we're investigating.
[TOUJI] If what
she's saying is true,
then that rumor that
said the real Raven Coat
was being stored
here might actually
have a shred of credibility.
[TOUJI] Any way you slice it,
us digging through
all the records
here is going to be
a hell of a lot slower
than if we just asked
the principal
directly, y'know.
[NATSUME] She's busy
right now after the attack.
And she's cagier
than she looks.
With information in our hands,
she can't misdirect us.
If we can find records
from when the school opened,
we might stumble across
some intel on Yakou.
As much as I'd love to
spend hours blood-hounding
with you guys,
it's probably easier to
give Taco-
whats-her-name a call.
Uh yeah, we sorta forgot
to ask for her number.
[TOUJI] Awesome.
It's gonna be like
finding one needle
in a stack of 'em.
Don't sweat it, guys!
There should be a place
where all of the
school's records were held,
so we just have to dig
through whichever pile
of books that happens to be!
From now on, dude,
make sure when you
meet a woman
for the first time,
you get her
freaking number, okay?
Ya got it.
Next mysterious girl I bump
into at a creepy altar,
I'll totally
get her digits.
[KON humming]
Ah!
[shrieks]
[HARUTORA] Hmmm.
[TOUJI snoring]
[yawns]
It's useless! The tenth
class is as far back
as it goes. Nothing from
when it was founded!
[HARUTORA] I kind of wanted
to see what the principal
looked like before sixty
years chomped into her.
[TOUJI] You and me both, man.
Hey, it just came to me.
Mister Ohtomo's got to
be in one of these books.
Yeah, he does.
[HARUTORA] Kogure was
in the same class, right?
Ah!
Which class was it though?
[TOUJI] Hey, Natsume!
You know, don't ya?
Guys, can you please
take this seriously?
Fine. The
thirty-sixth class.
[HARUTORA]
Here he is. Jin Ohtomo!
Aw man.
What a rip off!
I wanted to see a
picture of him as a kid!
Let's see. "It was a
meaningful three years."
Well that's nice and
noncommittal, there, Jin.
[TOUJI] Talk about
a lazy quote.
Uh.
I guess he was
just as nerdy back then!
[ALL laugh]
And now for Kogure!
Where's he at?
What'd ya find?
Weird. Take a
look at this name.
Seems familiar to me.
But all I know is what
I studied in a few books.
[SUZUKA] It was a
report written by a person
called Ryou Saotome.
He had served under my
father in the Ghost Division.
[HARUTORA] Huh.
Mister Ohtomo and
Ryou Saotome were both
at school in
the same year?
I can't believe I didn't
check the old yearbooks.
I knew he was an alum!
I wonder if that Souma
girl you told us about
is really a student
like she claimed.
If most of the school
hadn't been blown to bits
during that fight,
we could've asked
the admissions
office about it.
No. I'd rather
ask Mister Ohtomo.
[car horn honks]
Fancy meeting you
in a place like this.
Oh! Hey Suzu!
Weird running into
you out in Ueno, right?
I had hoped to invite
Kon for a drive.
Y'know, once in a
while a serious answer
would be awesome.
Don't worry; I'll have
her home well before dark.
Uh yeah, that's not
really the issue.
[SUZU] I would, of course,
be willing to pay.
[HARUTORA] That has even
less to do with the issue!
Oh! How 'bout introductions!
[HARUTORA] Natsume,
you've already met.
Suzu, this is the
rest of the gang.
I'm aware.
[SUZU] Touji Ato,
Kyoko Kurahashi,
Suzuka Dairenji
and Four-Eyes.
--What?
--Ah, so you already
know them, then? Cool.
Well, I guess each
one of us is known
throughout the school
for different things.
Uh. What about me?
Uh.
[BOY] He's a familiar.
Created just for driving.
Heh.
Whoa. What the--?
Don't we all look
hale and hearty?
I was worried after our last--
--What? Wait.
--Shut your mouth.
--He... he said--
--Don't worry about him.
How could I
not be worried?
That kid's weird.
The child is defective.
What am I saying?
Of course he's weird.
He's with you.
I'm taking care of him.
He's the son
of a relative.
He threw a tantrum
and claimed I had to
take him to meet someone.
I guess I caved,
and now here we are.
[SUZU] By the time we
arrived, someone else was
visiting that person,
so we decided to leave.
Honestly though,
I'm kind of glad.
[BOY] Shall we?
We have to go now.
So all is normal and
I am completely lost.
Say hello to
the brat for me!
Something about that
whole convo was off.
I got the heebie jeebies.
[sighs]
[AMAMI] They say the
curse is mostly gone.
So what, was it
destroyed starting
at the roots or something?
For better or worse, white
hair is gonna be my new look.
I think of it
like my right leg;
it's just a change I'll
need to adjust to, that's all.
Well you routed
Doman Ashiya anyway
and we're all
very proud of you.
I hardly won an
all-out magical battle
against him, though.
It was just a demonstration
of skill, nothing more.
From his point of view,
my Onmyo posturing was
little more than
child's play, surely.
Nothing to be
embarrassed about.
You survived because
your strength was real.
Oh dear, you're not
going to get all
mushy on me now, are you?
Beware Greeks bearing
gifts they say.
So I'm guessing you're not
just here to tuck me in.
Mmm.
Yes, tomorrow, we're completely
cleaning house at the Agency.
You're gonna pull
the Syndicate out
into the light of day?
That's right; I can't
miss this opportunity.
This time I'll be
more thorough.
From the ground up.
That always has
been my objective.
We're conducting
internal investigations
in the departments.
Twin Horn
Syndicate excision.
This will most likely
be the last job
I do for the Agency.
But sir!
Call me sentimental,
but that's pretty much
the reason I came
by here today.
[AMAMI] Those rats
are going to resist,
and they just might get
it in their heads to go
and bother your
poor students again.
But this time, the
Onmyo Agency will provide
a proper guard for them.
So you can just
rest here quietly.
That's what I
came to tell you.
Can we get some food?
Come on, Reiji.
You told me we were
going to have some fun.
It's my first day
out in a while,
and all we're
doing is waiting.
[SHAVER] So far it's
been a real let down.
You've been acting
different ever since
you got that X
on your forehead,
I'll have you know.
C'mere, Shaver.
Yes? You gotta plan?
[KAGAMI grunts]
[SHAVER groans]
[KAGAMI] Shut up!
Hey! What's the
big idea, Reiji?
That's "Master."
[KAGAMI grunts]
[SHAVER groans]
[CROWD gasping]
[SHAVER] Wait. No, stop!
Master, please!
[cell phone ringing]
[SHAVER] Come on, Reiji.
What was that for?
Well, well.
We've got another
chance to show everyone
what you can really do.
[grunts breathily]
Knock, knock! You up
for some visitors, sir?
Hey!
Oh, hi there.
Kyoko, Suzuka!
It's been far too long
and I don't believe
I've had the pleasure
of meeting the rest of you.
What are you doing here,
Uncle Amami?
Wait, that's weird.
This guy's your uncle?
Family friend.
[KYOKO] He's the
Director of the Bureau.
Amami's the name.
Pleased to meet you.
Hi. It's nice
to meet you, sir.
What brings
the director of
the Magical Investigation
Bureau all the way out here?
Actually this
little visit of theirs
isn't surprising at all.
[SUZUKA] These two used
to serve together in the MIB,
and the old guy
also hangs out
with the principal sometimes.
I find it very inspiring
that you went out of your way
to visit a former colleague.
Thank you for taking the time
out from your busy schedule.
Hey, come on!
I should be the one
saying all that crap
to him! Not that I would.
[SUZUKA] Whatever. This old
fogey wouldn't come all the way
out here for any
ordinary Bureau drone.
[ALL gasp]
In fact, this confirms
all my suspicions.
[SUZUKA] He easily destroyed
the seal on my magic.
He knows cryptic
old spells that aren't
part of the Imperial style.
A prep school teacher
who fought Doman Ashiya
to a standstill?
And one who can enlist
independent exorcists
to help him win
such a pitched battle.
There's only one
person in the Bureau
other than the Divine Fan,
Amami, who has power like his.
They tried to hide
his title from us,
but it's obvious that
he's a Divine General.
[SUZUKA] Code-name "Shadow!"
Ta-da!
Gotcha!
What? I'm sorry,
you lost--
[AMAMI] Oh-ho! The little
lady is pretty good!
Hey, be quiet!
It's far too late to try
hiding it from them now.
And by the way,
the name "Shadow"
is pretty
pretentious, right?
Stage Hand is
more like it.
Are you joking?
"Divine Fan" is way more
pretentious
than "Shadow."
Okay, are you
being for real?
You used to be
a Divine General?
You know if that's the case,
it does explain
how he held his own
for so long in the battle.
But why would you
want to leave
the Magical Investigation
Bureau just to
become a prep school teacher?
[groans lightly]
If I was a betting man,
I'd say the reason
is you, Natsume.
[TOUJI] Mister Ohtomo accepted
a position at Onmyo Prep
about a year ago.
Around the same time
you enrolled in the school.
The principal probably
read the star charts.
She must've seen
the trouble you would
bring to the school,
then she went to
Director Amami to
recruit Mister Ohtomo
as a form of insurance.
It all fits
quite nicely, I'd say.
Good work, young man.
If you always rely on
others for your answers,
then you'll never be able
to think critically.
So then, you're saying
Touji was right?
[AMAMI] You should think
about what I've said too, boy.
In fact, I have a bit of
helpful advice for you.
Every adult is
cagier than they seem,
devious down to
their very bones.
Never take what they say
at face value, son.
Then you may learn to
stand on your own two feet.
[AMAMI]
Ohtomo, share with them
what we talked about earlier!
You might not be able
to contact me for a while,
but that's all
part of the plan.
Well take care of yourself.
[chuckles lightly]
But of course.
So come in!
Take a seat!
There are a few things
I should probably
fill you guys in on.
[HARUTORA] So wait.
The Twin Horn Syndicate
will be gone,
once and for all?
[OHTOMO] Well, that's
Director Amami's plan,
at the very least.
Even so, there's still
a reason to be cautious.
The Onmyo Agency
will be providing
a guard for you, but we
should all remain vigilant.
We don't know how
Doman is planning
to make his move, either.
[ALL gasp]
Whoa, Doman?
You mean he could
still be alive?
Oh no, he's dead.
Doman Ashiya is
definitely dead.
But we don't know
yet if he's been
completely destroyed.
Hey, you should all
be fine for a while!
Just make sure you don't
let your guard down.
That's very reassuring.
Takiko Souma, huh?
I've never heard
of her before.
[HARUTORA] She told us
that she was a student.
She has red hair.
A redhead you say?
[OHTOMO] I might
have had some students
with the last name Souma,
but I would remember
the red hair, for sure.
Doesn't sound
like one of mine.
Eh, thanks anyway.
There is another name.
Feel free to ask.
I can't promise
I'll know who they are.
I have a feeling
this one will be familiar.
Ryou Saotome.
[gasps]
[SUZUKA] Huh?
[OHTOMO groans]
I should be taking it
easy, not stressing out.
So you know who this
Ryou Saotome guy is, don't you?
Yeah, we were in the
same class at school.
Oh, so it was worth
coming all the way
out here to visit you!
[SUZUKA] Saotome was
a pioneer in the field
of Yakou research.
Did you know
anything about that?
You're talking about
the Raven Coat, aren't you?
Yeah.
[sighs]
[OHTOMO] There's one tiny
detail you guys got wrong.
It's "Suzu." It's written
as "Ryou Saotome,"
but read as "Suzu Saotome."
[ALL gasp]
So then
it's really... Suzu?
I know you kids
probably won't listen.
But be careful.
Saotome is trouble.
Not the easiest to
deal with, so watch out.
[TOUJI] As it stands,
no one's seen Suzu in a while.
And we don't have
anything on Takiko either.
Kyoko, have you
heard anything
from your grandmother?
[KYOKO] Sorry, I haven't
had the chance to ask her.
Poor Grandmother
has been incredibly busy
ever since the attack.
Harutora,
what's on your mind?
You've been sitting
there for a while
all spaced out.
What? Oh. Yeah.
It's nothing, man.
I doubt it's anything
more than a red herring,
but I was just thinking
of that upperclassman
named Suzu we met.
Suzu? You mean the
weird girl from yesterday?
[ALL] Hm?
[ALL gasp]
Count your blessings.
It's time for the
big boys to play, kids!
For the time being,
you lucky brats
get to be guarded by me.
[HIRATA] Prepare yourselves!
The Onmyo Agency and
the exorcism department
are taking down the Twin
Horn Syndicate immediately.
You insolent fool!
I'll have you know,
this isn't fake fur!
It's genuine!