[HARUTORA sighs]
Huh?
♪
No way...
A familiar?
[phone rings]
[TOUJI]
He's not picking up.
Sorry, we'll just have to
assume Tenma's not coming.
[SUZUKA] What?
I seriously misjudged
that four-eyed chicken!
He's being unbelievably
selfish, here.
Suzuka, look.
Tenma's practical skills
aren't exactly stellar.
He was probably afraid he would
hold the rest of us back.
[SUZUKA]
That's no excuse.
He shouldn't've run away.
[TOUJI]
Think about like this:
he's supporting us
from a distance.
Hey, no matter
how bad we mess up,
Tenma will still be around.
That's a good thing, isn't it?
Come on, you've got to
give him a break, Suzuka.
Unless you wanted his
life to be at risk.
[SUZUKA grunts]
Ok, that's
what I thought.
Any ideas on how
we should get in?
I suppose I could break
through the barrier
and then the security
surrounding the agency building.
I know of a few different places
that Stupid-tora might be.
[KYOKO] Wait, what
is going on with me?
[DOMAN] Heh!
Who would believe it?
Me, an equal of the
famous Abe no Seimei,
to be called out in
the middle of the night
and ordered
around like a child.
After you've been alive
a few hundred years,
there's no telling what
the future will hold.
[OHTOMO]
Do you have objections?
Oh, by no means.
Just to be sure,
you are not trying to
exact revenge for the dead,
you are instead simply trying
to recover what was taken?
And that is why we are here?
To recover Yakou
Tsuchimikado's reincarnation.
As in Harutora
Tsuchimikado?
I had a feeling
you already knew
what this little
adventure was all about.
Indeed.
But you still give me
far too much credit.
That's good to hear
and rather encouraging;
I believe the door to
the possibility of us
becoming friends has now
just barely opened, Master.
Is it my
imagination, Shadow,
or is this condescension
I hear in your tone?
[phone chimes]
[OHTOMO] Hm?
[OHTOMO chuckles]
Apologies, Kyoko.
This time, let the
adults handle it.
Ready, Master?
Just as we planned.
[DOMAN] Yes.
[OHTOMO] Well, then,
let's get this over with.
[HARUTORA] Uh.
Come with me.
[HARUTORA gasps]
[HARUTORA] It's you!
Listen, I'm sorry.
[HARUTORA] What?
Receiving an apology
might seem a little strange,
but even so, I owe you one.
[HARUTORA sighs]
[HARUTORA] Did you used
to be human, too?
Yes, I was known then
as Chihiro Mutobe.
When I was alive,
there was a period of time
I worked under Chief Dairenji.
So you were a part of the
Twin Horne Syndicate, too?
[MUTOBE]
Yes, I was also involved
in the spirit disaster terrorism
that happened in the spring.
I died right afterwards.
[HARUTORA gasps softly]
[MUTOBE] Come on.
How's Takiko?
I gave her something that
should help her sleep.
She didn't take the news
about Natsume well.
Hopefully, rest will
help calm her down.
[HARUTORA sighs]
Oh, and just so
you're aware.
My master was genuinely
hoping to become good friends
with the two of you.
And that's the truth.
'Cause of Yakou's
reincarnation?
[MUTOBE] No.
She was lonely.
She needed friends.
[ding]
[KURAHASHI] In case you
didn't already know,
I'm Genji Kurahashi;
nice to meet you,
Harutora Tsuchimikado.
[HARUTORA] This guy.
You don't seem
very surprised.
Even if you realized it
on your way in here.
You're more composed
than expected.
Wait, this is saying, the
real enemy... is Kurahashi.
[KURAHASHI]
You aren't going to ask?
About my daughter?
I don't need to; if
Kyoko knew anything,
she would have told
us a long time ago.
Is that so?
Now, just to be sure.
You can really do it?
You can bring
Natsume back to life
with the Taizan Fukun
Ritual, can't you?
I can.
But you do realize it
would be against the law.
And you're not going to
just bring her back to life
as Takiko's familiar
or whatever
Yashamaru's turned
into over there?
Oh, no.
There are several different
types of Taizan Fukun Rituals.
Strictly speaking, it refers
to the entire magic system
that can manipulate
souls by accessing
a spiritual being called,
"Taizan Fukun."
A magic system?
Yes. For example, Suzuka
only knows one method.
In particular, where the
user's life is sacrificed
in exchange for
the life of the dead.
Now, such a thing
is a possibility,
but there's so much
more that can be done.
In other words, it's only a
small part of the system.
By the way, Yakou's last Taizan
Fukun Ritual did not fail.
What?
Well, as you know, Yakou has
been reincarnated, right?
Additionally, we're
talking about magic
manipulating a single
individual's soul.
You can't believe that caused
such a destructive disaster.
The Great Spirit Disaster
in Tokyo happened, though!
[YASHAMARU] What I'm saying
is... Yakou didn't mess up
on the Taizan Fukun Ritual,
but on the system it's part of.
[HARUTORA gasps]
That's enough, Yashamaru.
Hm. Well, anyway everything
I promised about bringing
Natsume Tsuchimikado
back to life still holds.
And you can certainly
believe that.
[HARUTORA grunts]
[KURAHASHI] I'm sure you've
already heard an earful
from the Souma princess,
but our hope is to welcome
you as our comrade.
[HARUTORA] No, not me.
Yakou Tsuchimikado, right?
[KURAHASHI] You're wrong, we
want you, Harutora Tsuchimikado.
The son of Yasuzumi
Tsuchimikado.
And the next head
of the family.
[HARUTORA gasps]
Why someone like me?
I don't get it.
I haven't recovered my
memories from my past life,
and I'm not a genius like Yakou.
So what? You think
I'm just gonna wind up
an amazing Onmyo mage,
like Yakou was?
Besides that, what
exactly are you hoping
to accomplish by having
Yakou on your side?
[KURAHASHI sighs]
[KURAHASHI]
During the Pacific War,
Yakou Tsuchimikado sat at
the top of the Onmyo Bureau.
He unified the different
types of Japanese magics
as well as created
the extremely practical
Imperial style of Onmyo magic.
However, Yakou did not
achieve this acting alone.
[HARUTORA] Huh?
[KURAHASHI] Working with him
not only on Onmyo magic,
but on magic from other sects;
examining, sorting,
finding complements,
and creating a system,
were the powerful Tsuchimikado
branch family the Kurahashis
and the Souma family,
who had influence over
the Imperial army.
Souma...
If by the side of
Onmyo Mage, Tsuchimikado
stood Hishamaru
and Kakugyouki.
Then who stood by Tsuchimakado
as chief of the Onmyo Bureau?
And as the Head of Onmyo?
The answer is the
Kurahashis and the Soumas.
[KURAHASHI]
At one time, Tsuchimikado,
accompanied by
Kurahashi and Souma,
achieved the
revitalization of magic.
After that, they decided to
aim for even greater heights
and advancements,
but it was to no avail.
Things are different, now.
So the Kurahashis
and Soumas are ready
to take over Yakou's
great work once more.
After all, they finally
have their king.
We request your cooperation.
[HARUTORA] I see.
That must be it.
Must be what?
[HARUTORA] The real reason I
was raised in a branch family.
[KURAHASHI grunts]
[HARUTORA]
The whole family.
They were all trying
to protect me.
[YASHAMARU] Kurahashi.
[KURAHASHI] Hm?
[phone rings]
We have company.
[MALE WORKER 22A] What the?
[DOMAN laughs intensely]
[MALE AGENT 22C] Uh. Ah!
[MALE AGENT 22B] An attack!
[MARI] Everyone.
Stay behind the barrier inside!
[MARI gasps]
D?
But how; I thought
Kogure purified him!
[DOMAN laughs]
[DOMAN]
Hm? That spirit energy
looks like it belongs
to a Divine General.
He's a child?
I can't believe it.
Is this D's true form?
[MARI whimpers]
[DOMAN laughs]
[DOMANS cackle]
[MARI] I can't.
How am I supposed
to purify this?
[DOMANS laugh]
[MARI gasps]
[MARI] What's going on?
At this rate...
[phone rings]
[MIYACHI] Hello, Maririn?
You're here, right?
Yes!
[MIYACHI] Intensify the agency
barrier to maximum strength.
Right!
[MARI] Om, shuri mari mamari
mari shushuri sowaka!
[MARI gasps]
[DOMANS scream]
[DOMAN laughs]
[DOMAN] Wow, that was
terrifying, wasn't it?
There's almost no point
in asking, but...
To be sure, you are the
Flame Devil, are you not?
[MIYACHI] It is an
honor to meet you.
I am the Onmyo mage,
Iwao Miyachi.
[DOMAN] You saw
through his plan?
Very impressive.
Thank you,
but I had no idea
Shadow would bring
you out, Master.
What kind of magic could he
have used to make that happen?
Oh, no kind of magic.
We just happen to be texting
buddies, that's all.
"Texting buddies"?
You mean, that's all it takes
to bring out the great Doman?
Well, in that case, if
it's not too much to ask,
do you mind giving me
your number, as well?
Yeah, no problem;
you are welcome to it,
it doesn't come
very cheap however.
[MARI] Commander!
[MIYACHI laughs]
[MIYACHI] Sorry, Maririn.
I'm going to have to leave the
inside of the building to you.
Roger that, sir. And, please
stop calling me that name.
I must say, our enemy
is hardly a naïve one.
[OHTOMO sighs]
[KAGAMI] I have dreamed of
this moment so many times.
[KAGAMI] Un!
[OHTOMO] Not too bad.
Come on, teach, you don't
have to be so cold to me.
I came all the way out here
in the middle of the night.
You can at least play
with me a little.
[MIYACHI recites spell]
[DOMANS cackle]
[MIYACHI continues]
[SUZUKA] Go figure Doman
Ashiya, of all people,
would come back
to life right now!
We don't need to figure;
just be glad that he did.
While the Onmyo Agency is busy
trying to take care of him,
we'll get the
chance to go rescue
our idiot friend,
Harutora.
Guys, wait.
[SUZUKA gasps]
[TOUJI stammers]
Wait for what?
Kyoko?
Okay, what is it?
I don't entirely
know what myself.
But.
All righty, then, you can
stay here and be on standby.
Suzuka and I will go inside.
No, listen, that's not it.
Can you please
just hold on a sec?
Hey! Seriously?
Miyachi is holding
Master Doman back
at the front of
the agency building.
I have confirmed that Kagami
has made contact with Shadow
and is about to engage
in battle with him.
[YASHAMARU] Hm.
Then this is not the master
trying to get
revenge on his own.
[KURAHASHI] We should assume
he's on Shadow's side now.
I did not see this coming.
Miyachi can't move
at the moment.
The purification troops
from HQ are scrambling, too.
Only time can tell
what will happen.
And me?
What should I do?
Oh, I think it best if you stay
with the princess on standby.
Whatever you say, sir.
[HARUTORA] Mister Ohtomo?
And Doman is working with him?
Based on that reaction,
it would seem you
know who Shadow is.
Does that mean you
also know the reason
he came here to
pay us this visit?
Were you aware
that your friends
are somewhere nearby as well?
What? Are you serious?
You've probably
realized this,
but they're not going
to like the idea of you
reviving Natsume Tsuchimikado
with forbidden magic.
Since we're not afraid
of breaking those taboos,
we're the only ones
who will help you.
[KURAHASHI] Harutora
Tsuchimikado.
I hate to admit this,
but there are still
a couple of misunderstandings
we need to deal with.
Unfortunately,
I can't reassure you
these matters will be easily
resolved down the road.
There is no way anyone can
be certain what is to come.
However, we have no
choice but to move forward.
We must continue
making decisions.
Especially if our
ambitions and desires
are as outrageous as bringing
the dead back to life.
Make your choice.
[HARUTORA]
All right. I'm in.
[KURAHASHI] Hm.
[YASHAMARU] Heh.
[KON] Please don't!
[HARUTORA] Uh!
[HARUTORA] Kon?
What are you doing?
[KON] M-Master Harutora,
I know this is impertinent,
but please listen to
what I have to say.
You must not trust
these people, sir!
That fact is as clear as day.
Please, rethink what
you're planning to do.
Listen to me;
you have to reconsider.
[KURAHASHI sighs]
[YASHAMARU] Heh.
[HARUTORA]
Yeah, believe me, Kon.
I'm well aware that
I can't trust them.
It's not a surprise;
they already know I don't
totally believe what they say.
But I don't have any
other choice here!
What I feel doesn't matter.
Besides, I'm using them, too!
[KON] You're wrong!
Look. M-Master Harutora, you
do not get what I'm saying!
The normal you
would've understood
without ever having
to think about it,
but the you right now
simply does not comprehend.
Please listen to me!
Trust is not a thing you can
compromise and give up on
because you have no other
choice at the moment.
It's also not something
you can give up on
when it is more convenient.
Kon! Stop it right now!
No. You have to
listen to me, sir!
If you took a moment
to look at them,
it would be
obvious to you, too!
Think about what these
people have already done
to those who were
close to them,
to allies who fought
beside them and for them.
Tell me, out of everyone
you've met or heard of
who've been considered one of
their precious "comrades,"
is there even a single person
that has been left smiling?
Master Harutora, your
smile will not be found
on the path you are
heading toward now,
and you know without a doubt
you can trust me on that.
And even if they
kept their word
and Natsume were
to be revived,
I seriously doubt she would
be able to
smile in the end, too.
Please, try to
remember her, sir.
When she died there was a
smile on her face, Master.
This would taint
that moment entirely.
Is that what you truly want?
[HARUTORA] Shut up!
What exactly do
you want me to do?
So just because she
smiled when she died,
everything's supposed
to be okay?
Well to hell with that;
I'm bringing Natsume
back no matter what!
Master Harutora!
If that is the case,
then you must not leave
this to any other person!
Take the matter into your very
own hands and do it yourself!
[HARUTORA gasps]
[KURAHASHI gasps]
[YASHAMARU grunts]
[KON] I mean, you are
the reincarnation
of Yakou Tsuchimikado,
the greatest authority
on magic dealing with souls,
are you not?
Think about it, sir;
even these bad men agree
that Yakou Tsuchimikado
perfected the current
Taizan Fukun Ritual.
If you are indeed
his reincarnation,
you should be able
to perform the ritual
better than anyone else.
But, I can't.
That's impossible.
I don't have those memories
from my past life, Kon!
It's not like I know
as much as he did.
No. There's no way
I would ever
be able to use the
Taizan Fukun Ritual.
[KON] Master Harutora.
Do you realize how
pitiful you sound?
Did you or did you not
just tell me you would
do anything to bring
her back, no matter what?
[HARUTORA stammers]
[KON] If your desire
in this extreme action
is to repay Natsume from a
genuine and heartfelt place,
then I think you
should take on
that responsibility
yourself, sir.
Why would you consider
leaving it to someone else?
And to scoundrels, no less!
It's inexcusable at best, sir!
Have you thought about
how Natsume would feel
if that was the way she was
brought back into the world?
By those who care
nothing for her?
However, if you brought
her back by yourself
instead of relying on people
that you know you can't trust.
No matter what the result,
Natsume would be happy.
I know without a doubt she would
show you her smile again, sir!
What do you say, kid?
You're time's up.
The Spirit Disaster Purification
Unit will arrive soon.
So, what will it be?
[HARUTORA sighs]
[KON gasps]
[HARUTORA] Kon.
[KON] Huh?
[HARUTORA]
Thank you for that.
[giggles]
[YASHAMARU] Ugh.
All that hubbub for nothing.
[KURAHASHI grunts]
And like that,
back to square one.
We can't seem to win, can we?
Oh well. Let's talk about the
future in the morning, shall we?
[HARUTORA and KON grunt]
[YASHAMARU] Hm.
[YASHAMARU] Uh! Huh?
Kurahashi, the seal on
the Coat has been broken.
It what?
But there's no way!
[YASHAMARU]
No, it wasn't those three.
I'm positive we would have
noticed if it had been them.
[KURAHASHI]
Then whom?
[AMAMI]
What a splendid defense!
I had a boy come to me,
as well, you know!
[KURAHASHI grunts]
[AMAMI] Tsuchimikado,
call the Raven Coat!
Raven Coat!
Come!
Yashamaru!
All right.
What a ruckus.
If you could stay still,
that'd be great.
Do your thing, Kon!
[KON yells]
Uh!
[YASHAMARU] Oh dear.
Harutora, it'll be
hard for you to do
the Taizan Fukun Ritual
with that level of magic.
How dare you. Ahh!
Sit down, girl.
[KON] Aahh!
Om, bishi bishi kara
kara shibari sowaka!
[YASHAMARU grunts]
[chuckles]
That wasn't very nice.
You almost broke my monacle.
[HARUTORA gasps]
[KURAHASHI grunts]
[KURAHASHI] Ah.
That fan was
an armored familiar?
[HARUTORA] Uh. Go!
[KON] Hm.
[YASHAMARU] Namu,
Hachiman Great Bodhisattva.
Sorcery is fascinating and
generally used for humans,
which is why
it doesn't seem to
be aware of me
in the slightest.
[HARUTORA] Damn it.
[YASHAMARU chuckles]
Look who I found!