[chiming]
[YOUNG HARUTORA] Okay.
I'll become your
familiar, Natsume.
[YOUNG HARUTORA]
I'll protect you forever.
I swear.
[chiming]
[FEMALE TEACHER] Current onmyo
magic consists of Japanese magic
that was brought together,
refined, and simplified
during World War II.
[cell phone buzzes]
[FEMALE TEACHER] Using that
magic, the Onmyo Agency
has been undergoing purification
of the spiritual disaster
two years ago.
The Onmyo Mages who serve in
the Exorcism Bureau within
the Agency are responsible
for this purification,
while other Bureaus
within the Agency
offer their support
in various ways.
[cicadas chirp]
[HARUTORA]
Man, the sky is so blue.
[chiming]
[cicadas chirp]
[HARUTORA]
I'm so wiped.
Yeah, I can tell.
Aren't you?
It's freaking hot.
It's cooler here than it is
in Tokyo, that's for sure.
Gone.
I want more.
[HARUTORA]
Yeah, me too.
Awesome.
I've been cursed.
Big shock. I guess
that runs in my family.
Yeah, knowing the history,
I'd say that's
entirely possible.
She's here.
[HARUTORA] Huh?
[HOKUTO] Harutora!
H-Hokuto?
I've been calling you.
How come you didn't
answer? Stupid-tora!
[HARUTORA]
Because I was in summer school!
[HOKUTO] Oh.
Well, I suppose that makes
sense, Great King of the F's!
Okay, I'll accept
your lame excuse.
But I'm still gonna find a way
for you to make it up to me.
This is ridiculous.
I don't understand why I
had to buy you a snow cone.
Hey! That's mine; get
your greedy paws off!
Ow, my head!
I totally got a brain freeze!
Good, that's
what you get.
[TOUJI] So, Hokuto?
Isn't it about time for you
to start lecturing him again?
[HOKUTO] Hmph.
Harutora, have you
made up your mind?
[HARUTORA groans]
Become an onmyo mage.
You better not say "no"!
[HARUTORA] Uh--Sorry.
[HOKUTO]
Come on, Harutora.
You're part of the
Tsuchimikado family,
descendants of Abe no Seimei.
How could you not want to
be an official Onmyo Mage?
It's in your blood!
[HARUTORA] Hokuto.
I've already told you.
Yeah, I'm a Tsuchimikado,
but I'm from a branch family,
and besides,
I'm not a spirit seer.
I don't have any talents.
I'm just too normal
to be a mage.
Someone gifted should
represent my family,
not someone who has
to go to summer school.
Oh, you mean like that one
girl from the main family?
[chiming]
Yep. She's already been
named the next head,
and better her than me.
She's been in Tokyo at the
Onmyo Prep School since spring.
And she's totally different from
us losers, that's for sure.
[HOKUTO]
That's a buncha bull.
Why doesn't that bug you?
Because I like life better
without expectations.
[HOKUTO] For real?
[HARUTORA] Huh?
Harutora, you can't
honestly believe that
no one expects
anything of you.
Yeah. I do.
[NATSUME]
Liar. Liar!
[TOUJI] Harutora.
You're drippin' there.
Aaahh!
Hah! It looks like you peed!
Shut up!
Damn it.
[HOKUTO] Here.
[HARUTORA] Thanks. Jeez.
So, we're done with
career counseling now, right?
What's the plan for tomorrow?
Oh. This'll be your
first fireworks festival
since you got here.
You excited for it?
I guess.
So you're coming over
tomorrow, right?
We can head out as soon as
you finish with your checkup.
Yeah, that sounds
good to me.
Ow! I got a stupid
brain freeze again!
[HARUTORA]
Hey, that's mine!
[HOKUTO]
See you later, Touji!
[TOUJI] Later.
You should be
an onmyo mage.
Stupid-tora!
No! Go away!
[HOKUTO giggles]
[HARUTORA grunts]
[HARUTORA] Man, when
did she get so pushy?
She was pretty normal
until last year.
[TOUJI] Yeah, I dunno;
that girl is full of mysteries.
She doesn't know
jack, though.
Nobody cares if you're from the
Tsuchimikado family anymore.
I guess that's all
thanks to "Yakou," right?
That's right.
I mean, she's gotta have some
clue about all that, you know?
I'd be surprised if
anybody hadn't heard by now.
What do you think?
I dunno.
It's like I already said; that
girl is full of mysteries, dude.
[HARUTORA sighs]
[TOUJI] Harutora.
[HARUTORA] Huh?
You seriously don't even
want to give it a try, do you?
[HARUTORA]
Not you, too!
We both know I don't
have any talent!
It's not a matter
of talent.
It's a matter of will.
I did think about it when
I was a kid, if that counts.
You've got way more talent than
you give yourself credit for.
[HARUTORA] Huh?
[TOUJI]
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Sure thing.
One more year,
just the three of us.
[chiming]
[HARUTORA] Natsume?
How come you're
not back in Tokyo?
Oh, yeah.
Summer vacation.
Hello there, Harutora.
Long time no see.
So, uh--
So how are your parents?
I haven't seen either
of them in a long time.
I hope they're doing well.
Oh, they're doing good.
Really good.
We could go see 'em?
[NATSUME] I wish I could,
but I don't have much time.
[HARUTORA]
When are you going back?
[NATSUME] In a week.
[HARUTORA] Yeah?
Is school hard?
The classes are fine
for the most part.
The tradition is a little
tricky, though.
Oh. I mean--
school is fine.
Have you made any
friends so far?
Have I made friends?
I have the duty of
being the next head
of the Tsuchimikado family.
I do not have time to waste
by spending my days
idly or making friends.
Oh man, you need
to lighten up.
And you need to realize
that I am nothing like you.
Well, you would know, right?
You are the all mighty genius.
Who cares who's a
genius and who's not?
It's not gonna
change the truth!
What's wrong now?
You know, you
used to be cute.
[NATSUME gasps]
Fine! Keep being mean to me!
It's not like I'm trying
to make you change
who you are or anything.
You just go ahead
and do what you want!
The Tsuchimikado family
might be our family.
But don't worry; I can
protect us all by myself!
Have a nice evening.
Huh?
[NATSUME] Goodbye.
Have a nice evening.
[HARUTORA sighs]
[HARUTORA]
Not cute at all.
[TOUJI]
Hey, thanks for waiting.
[HARUTORA]
How'd it go?
Everything went just fine.
Your dad sure knows
what he's doing.
[MALE NEWSCASTER 1A] ...disaster
in Shibuya yesterday.
[TOUJI]
What's going on?
...and there's confusion
at the scene,
but it has been purified
by the Exorcism Bureau.
As you can see, the agents
are hard at work--Aah!
[AGENTS]
Kiosowaka!
[KOGURE] Om aromaya tengu,
suman kisowaka.
Om hirahiraken.
Hiraken nosowaka!
Whoa, that was amazing.
[TOUJI] He's one of the
Twelve Divine Generals.
A State Onmyo Mage First Class.
Tokyo is way more dangerous
than I thought it was, I guess.
No wonder Natsume was
acting so on edge.
[TOUJI]
Someone from a branch family
becoming a familiar to
one of the Head members.
I guess that makes sense.
It's kind of a tradition
in old families.
[HARUTORA] I think it's awesome
I'm not a spirit seer.
Last thing I'd want is to be
that warped girl's familiar.
[TOUJI] For real?
Natsume doesn't
seem that bad to me.
Dude, you were kind
of a jerk to someone
who was just trying to
tell you she was lonely.
But don't worry; I can
protect us all by myself!
[HARUTORA]
You're right; I'm a jerk.
[CROWD murmurs]
[HARUTORA sighs]
What's your problem?
Not like she rejected you.
Hey!
You shut up!
[HOKUTO]
Who rejected whom?
[HARUTORA]
Whoa. Hokuto.
You, uh--
[TOUJI] Ahem.
You're, um,
dressed differently.
Yeah. It's for
the festival.
That okay?
[HARUTORA] No, fine;
it's just kinda weird.
I didn't even recognize you.
It's not bad or anything,
just, like, weird.
It looks good
on you, I mean.
You mean it?
You look like,
more mature.
Thanks, I guess.
Awkward.
If you're finished
now, can we go?
[HARUTORA] Ahh!
Okay, so which one?
[HARUTORA laughs]
[HOKUTO]
Come on; this way!
[HARUTORA] How can you run so
fast while wearing that thing?
That girl is nuts.
Gotta give her a little
bit of credit, though.
She had that shy girl thing
going for like an hour.
[HARUTORA] Uh-huh.
[HOKUTO] Harutora!
Over here--
this looks like fun!
[TOUJI] Wow, this sure brings
back some memories, doesn't it?
Now, you need to go for
the light ones in the front
so you'll be more likely
to knock 'em over.
Whoops.
I missed it.
Then maybe you should've
tried listening to me!
Look, all I want
is that prize.
Get it for me, Harutora!
[HARUTORA] Why should I?
All right, fine;
gimmie the gun.
Just don't get all
pissed off at me if I miss!
[HARUTORA]
I lost so much money!
This is my last shot.
Sorry in advance that
I'm not gonna hit it.
Um. Hey, Harutora.
'Hey' yourself;
I'm trying to focus.
If you can get it for me--
I said I'm trying
to focus, so hush it.
Well then...
I'll kiss you.
[gun shot]
Yay!
[HOKUTO laughs]
Oh I guess, you uh--
I what?
Well, you said
if I got it, uh--
[FESTIVAL BOY 1A] Look!
See that one!
Yeah.
I know what I said.
And you got it, huh?
I don't like how you're
acting right now.
Acting?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
[TOUJI] Boom!
[FESTIVAL KIDS laugh]
[HARUTORA]
What is this?
Hey, check it out,
it's a bubble blower set.
This is what I was
actually after, though.
[HOKUTO chuckles]
[HOKUTO]
Now I look super cute.
[HARUTORA] I--
Don't you think I look cute?
Of course you do,
I'm adorable, so tell me!
Okay, fine, whatever!
You look cute! You look cute!
Really?
Yeah, yeah, really, really.
I think you look
really cute, okay?
[HOKUTO giggles]
I win!
You know this would
have been much easier
if you'd just said I was cute
from the very beginning.
Hold on.
Are you telling me you wore
that so I'd say you were cute,
and when I didn't you
made me pay a crapload
for a freaking ribbon
just to force me to?
Yep!
Aww... Boy, did I ever lose.
I'll keep it forever!
You do what you want.
I hope you know it cost way
more to win than it was worth.
Maybe, but I don't care.
[HARUTORA] Why not?
[HOKUTO chuckles]
Just 'cause, silly!
[KIDS yell and cheer]
[HARUTORA] Oh, man.
At least she's in a good mood.
[CROWD murmurs]
[SUZUKA]
Excuse me.
Huh?
[SUZUKA] You take
credit cards here, right?
Where'd she run off to?
You see her anywhere?
Over there.
[HARUTORA] There you are.
Whatcha writing?
Oh, nothing.
[HOKUTO gasps]
[HARUTORA]
Are you kidding me? Come on.
Look, all I want is
what's best for you, okay!
[HARUTORA]
Face it, Hokuto.
The truth is I'm
kind of a lazy guy,
and I don't have a ton
of skill or ambition.
It's who I am.
Oh, and surprise,
I like living this way.
Plus, why go do something
that keeps me from
hanging out with you guys?
Isn't that what
you want, too?
[HOKUTO] I uh...
I can't really explain it.
I just think you should
be an onmyo mage,
and I won't change my mind!
[NATSUME] Liar.
[loud clack]
[HOKUTO gasps]
[HOKUTO] You're so stupid!
You're so stupid!
Ah, yes, to be young.
So dramatic.
[HARUTORA] Yeah.
Hey, do you think I was wrong?
Nah. I think that
one's on Hokuto.
She should know by now that
you're a hopeless cause.
[HARUTORA sighs]
You've pissed two girls
off in one day. Nice.
Wow, no sympathy?
I'm a little depressed here.
Oh, sorry, dude;
you're depressed?
Imagine how she must feel.
Hey, you want motivation,
I can totally hit you.
Will that make
you go after her?
No. Thanks, but, uh,
something tells me that I might
end up regretting that more.
It's just these are supposed to
be the best days of our lives,
so I'd rather spend
them with you two.
[SUZUKA]
Hey, you. Genius kid.
Interested in taking
part in my experiment?
You're Natsume
Tsuchimikado, right?
Unfortunately. I'm just
a boring, regular guy.
I think this one here's
the one you're looking for.
[HARUTORA] Uhh!
You have to be joking.
[HARUTORA] I am a
Tsuchimikado, but--
[TOUJI] Haven't I seen
you in a magazine?
You're the youngest of
the Twelve Divine Generals,
aren't you?
The Prodigy, Suzuka Dairenji?
You know a lot for
just a regular guy.
But you--rumor has it you're
supposed to be this big genius.
You look kinda stupid to me.
Stupid?
That's rude!
Just go along
with it.
What for?
'Cause who knows, it
might be an adventure.
[HARUTORA]
You're messed up.
[HARUTORA sighs]
Okay fine, what do
you want from me?
[SUZUKA] I told you.
I want you to help me
with my experiment.
It's the same magic performed
by Yakou Tsuchimikado,
I'm sure you've heard of
the Great Spirit Method?
The Taizan Fukun Ritual.
[HARUTORA and TOUJI] Uhh...
[SUZUKA] A barrier?
Heh.
The Agency?
[MALE OFFICER 1A]
State Onmyo Mage First Class,
Suzuka Dairenji.
You're under arrest for
the use of forbidden magic.
Magical
Investigators.
Why is the
Bureau after her?
[MALE OFFICER 1A] Surrender!
We will shoot if we have to!
It's Asura,
the artificial-type Model M3
built by the Onmyo Agency!
[MALE OFFICER 1A] Huh?
I detest the countryside.
There are just far
too many bugs!
[OFFICERS yell]
[TOUJI yells]
[HARUTORA]
Touji! Touji! Aah!
[HARUTORA] Huh?
Want some?
Let me go!
Can't do that;
I need you too much.
[HOKUTO] Put him down!
[footsteps]
You let Harutora
go this instant!
Hokuto!
Don't be an idiot!
Run!
Did she
say Harutora?
What is the
meaning of this?
Stop it!
You shut your ugly mouth!
My dear boy.
Are you underestimating me?
Nope.
Not at all.
[SUZUKA]
Tell Natsume Tsuchimikado
something for me, would you?
Tell him I'm coming for him.
Fail to deliver my message,
and I'll have to
cut off your balls!
[HARUTORA whimpers]
Oh, by the way.
Is that your girlfriend?
[HARUTORA] No.
Oh good.
Then she won't mind.
[gasps]
[KON] I will attack!
I will stab! I will twist.
And then, I will sharpen.
I will attack.
I will stab! I will twist!