[YOUNG HARUTORA] Okay.
I'll become your
familiar, Natsume.
[NATSUME] With this, you are
mine. Forever and always.
I'm really happy you
came here to Tokyo.
We've made so many friends.
Everything's just perfect.
[HARUTORA] Natsume!
♪
[HARUTORA grunts]
[HARUTORA] Natsume, hang on!
I'll fix it.
I'll fix it all right now.
Order!
No! Order!
Order! Order!
Order!
Order! Order! Order!
[TOUJI] Harutora.
[SUZUKA gasps]
[HARUTORA whimpers]
[HARUTORA]
I'm going to save you.
I know I can fix this!
You've gotta hang on,
understand?
Just please, don't go.
Harutora.
Touji?
Reboot. Now.
[TOUJI sighs]
Harutora...
[YUKIKAZE neighs]
[TENMA] Kyoko!
They're over here!
You were able to find him?
How is he?
Tell me.
[KYOKO and TENMA gasp]
[KYOKO] Natsume?
Don't just stand there!
We have to call an ambulance!
N-No.
[HARUTORA]
I've got it.
I can ask my dad for help.
I know he could do something.
Harutora.
Old man's a professional
Onmyo doctor.
After all, he sealed away
your freakin' ogre!
Right. That's enough.
Yeah, Pops could set
it right no problem.
Dad actually knows
what he's doing.
I mean the man's
a real Onmyo mage.
He could even raise
the dead if he wanted.
Harutora!
[HARUTORA] Uh.
No mages are strong enough.
Your father isn't capable
of pulling someone
back from the dead.
[HARUTORA]
Back from... the dead?
[TOUJI] Hm?
[HARUTORA exhales]
[SUZUKA] Huh?
Harutora, no! You can't.
[HARUTORA and TOUJI] Uh.
[MALE EXORCIST 21A]
This is the Exorcism Department
of the Onmyo Agency!
You are all now under arrest!
Harutora!
Do what he says!
[MALE EXORCIST 21A] Don't move!
No!
Get out of my way!
[SUZUKA gasps]
That idiot!
Dammit!
[TOUJI] Harutora!
Get it together!
We can sort things
out on the ground!
[SUZUKA]
Stupid-tora!
Magic investigators, huh?
Where?
Have some of this!
Those things aren't
on autopilot.
Someone's controlling them!
Who are you?
Nooo!
[recites spell]
[HARUTORA panting]
Harutora.
[HARUTORA gasps]
[SUZUKA gasps]
Suzuka.
The Taizan Fukun Ritual.
If I can perform the ritual,
then it might bring
Natsume back to life!
You know everything
I need to do it.
Now tell me how to
start the ritual!
You need to back off
from her now, dude.
Tell me.
I can't.
Suzuka!
Shut up! Do you think
this is some kind of joke?
I'm serious here!
How dare you?
You were all high and
mighty about stopping me
when I tried before!
You stinking coward!
Then there's the offering.
What were you going to do
about the ritual offering?
I'll die.
Stop this nonsense!
Natsume...
She's dead and
it's all my fault.
I won't lose her.
Help me, Suzuka.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Hey man.
I don't think we should
just leave Natsume
lying there like that.
[ALL] Huh?
[YASHAMARU] Good evening.
Pardon my intrusion.
How?
It's my dad.
It's so nice to see
you again, Suzuka.
But you shouldn't freely
admit I'm your father.
Take my word for it.
I wouldn't want you to
be cursed like I've been.
I taught you better
than that, my dear.
You really must work harder
on your high-grade
spell recognition.
Be careful.
[SUZUKA] You shouldn't be here.
You're supposed to be dead.
Is "Dad" a creepy
nickname of yours
for Mister Monocle over there?
[YASHAMARU] Ha, ha!
That's quite amusing.
Coming from the fellow
wearing that headband.
How nice to meet you.
You may call me Yashamaru.
But when I was alive,
I was Shido Dairenji.
[TOUJI exhales]
[YASHAMARU] I've heard
all about your situation.
Come now, don't look
at me like that.
For when all is said and done,
the two of us are cut
from the same cloth.
[TOUJI] What's that
supposed to mean?
We've been given the
same divine protection.
Now, King of the North Star.
Or--would you prefer
for me to call you Yakou,
your eminence?
[SUZUKA] Huh?
My name is
Harutora, buddy!
It's Harutora Tsuchimikado!
Very well,
Harutora Tsuchimikado.
To be honest, I hadn't
planned to make a move yet.
I would rather bide my time
a little while longer.
Hey, Stupid-tora!
Don't listen to
a word the man says!
Remember, he's the
former head honcho
of the Twin Horn Syndicate!
Suzuka, I'm glad to see
that you and Harutora
have become friends.
The two of you could be
together for a long time,
if you came over to our side.
There are a couple things
I'd like to confirm.
That familiar earlier.
Was it you?
Ah yes, I'm
guilty as charged.
This little fellow
helped me see everything.
So, what do you want?
[YASHAMARU] I was
feeling mischievous.
Overcome by an urge
to be meddlesome.
Since those mass-market
artificial familiars
were able to do some damage.
It must mean Harutora hasn't
gotten back his true power yet.
Or regained all of
Yakou's memories.
All right, then.
Now the next question.
Believe it or not,
we just had an altercation
with the master of a familiar
that goes by the
name of Kumomaru.
So I gotta know, fancy pants,
are you with them?
That is correct.
We're both familiars
to the same master.
Her name is Takiko Souma.
[HARUTORA grunts]
[TOUJI]
First seal. Purge!
Order!
Is that really
all you've got?
You definitely haven't gotten
your true power back.
[HARUTORA] Uh.
H-ya!
[HARUTORA groans]
[TOUJI grunting]
I was really quite good
in my younger days,
I'll have you know.
[TOUJI grunts]
[YASHAMARU] But now,
I fight more like this.
Om, jiri chei sowaka.
[TOUJI groans]
[YASHAMARU] Ha!
[TOUJI] Ugh!
No you don't.
I think some apologies
are in order.
For your rash behavior
toward my master.
But perhaps after this
one-sided display of power,
you may consider the undeniable
benefits of joining us
on our Onmyo path?
Of course, we would
provide suitable compensation.
For example.
The Taizan Fukun Ritual?
I am an authority
when it comes to
magic dealing with souls.
After all, I'm the
not-quite-living proof it works.
Besides. I won't
be asking you for
your immortal soul or
anything so boorish.
Certain conditions
will need to be met.
But I can help you bring that
friend of yours back to life.
[SUZUKA grunts]
Natsume Tsuchimikado died
without any of the
proper preparations.
Consider all that
I've said, young master.
The ritual must be
conducted quickly.
Before it's too late.
[MALE EXORCIST 21A]
This is the 5th Platoon
of the Exorcism Department!
Harutora Suchimikado,
Touji Ato, Suzuka Dairenji.
Give yourselves up quietly!
[TOUJI grunts]
[SUZUKA gasps]
Natsume.
[SUZU] Foolish to
expect anything
from the one-armed ogre.
Too bad.
Up to me now.
What a bother.
[CHIZURU]
Natsume is...
We never should have
allowed those maniacs
to take the Raven Coat!
We shouldn't have
given it to them,
no matter what they
might have done to us!
[CHIZURU sobs]
Harutora?
I don't know.
Power is increasing at the Onmyo
Agency at an alarming rate.
From the Imperial pallbearers.
It's Souma.
She finally brought
them out of hiding.
I am afraid we are
simply too late.
[KYOKO] Grandmother.
Natsume is...
Natsume's gone.
[MIYO]
Zenjiro, my dear.
Would you be kind enough to
fill me in on the details?
I assume you're somewhat
familiar with the Raven Coat?
[KYOKO gasps]
Yes.
[KOGURE] What do you
know about the person
who has the Raven Coat?
Who now?
A girl named
Takiko Souma.
She came to look around the
school grounds yesterday.
It's because I told her we were
going to see the fireworks.
[TOUJI]
You kidding me?
You can't think Natsume
died just because
you were being polite to her.
Stop being so ridiculous.
[KYOKO] But!
Kyoko, Natsume is
dead because of
the magic in the Raven Coat
that took over Harutora.
He was out of control when
he was under that curse
and she made a decision.
[KYOKO and TENMA] Hm?
[TOUJI] That idiot Harutora
just kept ranting on
about how he killed Natsume.
Do you blame him too?
[KYOKO] Mm-mm.
It's the same thing.
Natsume isn't dead because
of you or Harutora
or anything the two
of you might have done.
[KYOKO sobs]
And Harutora?
He's been detained
by the Bureau.
They're interrogating
him as we speak.
That poor boy.
So this is where
everyone is.
Principal Kurahashi.
Miyachi?
[MIYACHI] Ever since that
moron Kagami got suspended,
I keep getting stuck
with night duty.
I've heard that the
Magical Investigation Bureau
is interrogating
a student of mine.
If it's possible I would
like to be there with him.
My apologies,
Principal Kurahashi.
But the higher-ups at the
Onmyo Agency have determined
that Harutora's power
fluctuations are beyond
the ability of a mere prep
school to keep contained.
The Onmyo Agency will
be taking care of him
from this point forward.
[TENMA] But sir.
And Natsume?
I'd like to pay
my last respects.
I am sorry.
[MIYO]
Commander Miyachi.
One of our teachers here is a
former magical investigator.
I understand the Agency's
security concerns.
Do you think he would be
permitted to bid Natsume
farewell on behalf of all
of our students and faculty?
[FUJIWARA] This is Fujiwara
from Onmyo Prep School.
Anyone here?
Huh?
[FUJIWARA] It's open.
Ohtomo?
[OHTOMO] Mister Fujiwara.
Now how did you
get in here?
The door? Let's just
say I have my ways.
And lock-picking is more
entertaining than paperwork.
Teachers don't go on
many special missions.
If you're worried about
the fellow outside,
he'll awake
unharmed soon enough.
That's good, but it
isn't what I meant.
In the long run,
I was useless.
By the time I figured
out what was going on,
it had all come to an end.
And when the dust settled,
this sweet child was dead.
[FUJIWARA] Uh. Ohtomo.
[OHTOMO] I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Natsume.
I couldn't--
I beg your forgiveness.
Look, Ohtomo.
I think it would be best if
you came with me at once.
We should make sure
the principal knows
everything we know.
[OHTOMO] Thank you
very much, Mister Fujiwara.
[FUJIWARA gasps]
[YASHAMARU]
Harutora Tsuchimikado.
Yours truly just came from
meeting him in person.
Explain.
I wanted to check in
on the status
of Yakou's re-awakening, Chief.
To determine if it was just
his soul that has been reborn.
Or if his memories or
abilities from his past life
were still intact.
Have we heard anything about
Yasuzumi and the others?
[KURAHASHI] Our operatives
haven't reported
any new information as of yet.
[YASHAMARU] Hmph. Do you think
it's plausible that Yasuzumi
is still in the dark
regarding recent events?
[KURAHASHI] No. The man is a
master at reading the stars.
If anything he's waiting for
the perfect time to strike.
[YASHAMARU] Mm-hm.
So what you're saying is,
there might be a chance
that he would attempt
to rescue Harutora himself.
[KURAHASHI] He'll have Takahiro
and Chizuru fighting for him.
Takahiro is a skilled former
magical investigator.
We need to be careful with them,
but at least we have
Miyachi on our side.
However, we still have
other causes for concern.
There's also the matter
of a troublesome teacher
at Onmyo Prep School.
Oh? Who?
[KURAHASHI] It's Shadow.
What? I was under the
impression that he retired.
He resigned from the Bureau.
Then my mother hired him.
He was Natsume Tsuchimikado's
homeroom teacher.
Oh my! What an
unfortunate situation.
Now we have to deal
with Shadow as an enemy?
That might prove annoying.
[KURAHASHI] Don't worry.
I have just the man for the job.
[KURAHASHI] This can't
be made public.
Reports indicate that
a skillful Onmyo mage
has infiltrated
the Onmyo Agency.
I need someone like you
to take him out.
I'm in.
Who's the target?
[KURAHASHI] Shadow.
Eh?!
[glass shatters]
[MALE BARTENDER 21A sighs]
[KURAHASHI] Independent
Exorcist, Reiji Kagami,
I hereby release you
from your suspension.
Report to the agency
offices immediately.
I can have some of the
agency staff drive you.
Why don't you kids go
on home for the night?
He's right, Kyoko dear.
Leave this to us.
[KYOKO] Impossible.
Go home and do what?
[KYOKO] Crawl into bed
and go to sleep.
Then face a tomorrow
with no Natsume.
Can I do that?
Is that even a possibility?
Principal Miyo!
Have you seen Mister Ohtomo?
What? Why would
you ask me that?
[FUJIWARA] It's something
best discussed in private.
[TOUJI] This is as
good a time as any.
Here goes.
Once we get outta here,
I'm breaking into the Agency.
[inaudible]
He did what?
[TOUJI] The Onmyo Agency
is the belly of the beast.
I'll be damned before
I leave my buddy to rot
in a place like that.
I'm going to sneak in
and break him out.
That's impossible, moron!
Now listen.
Let's say you sneak in.
You have no idea where
Harutora is being held.
And there won't be a map
with a "you are here" sticker.
You're right.
[TENMA]
Doing something that stupid
isn't going to
accomplish anything.
You might as well stay at home.
[TOUJI sighs]
Stop and think.
Let's talk with Kogure
and the principal.
We might have a chance to win,
then, even if it's the slow way.
I'm sorry, Tenma.
But I'm thinking about what
that Yashamaru dude said
after the fight.
Like how we're running
out of time to conduct
the Taizan Fukun Ritual
and bring Natsume
back from the dead.
[TENMA gasps]
[TOUJI] If we're doing it, then
tonight's our only chance.
And Mister Monocle
backed off long enough
to give us time to
think things over.
I think we have the opportunity
to use that time against him.
I'm telling you, this might
be our one and only shot.
I can feel it in my bones,
this is the perfect
time to make a move.
I don't know what choice
Harutora will end up making.
I feel that given
the opportunity,
he'd sacrifice
himself for Natsume.
If that's the case,
then so be it.
At that point
it's his decision.
But up until that moment,
I will do whatever it may take.
I'll stay with him
until the end.
And see his resolve
with my own two eyes.
Touji...
Oh, and there is one
thing I know for sure.
No way in hell will I be
able to go back to the dorm
and just sleep with all
of this stressing me out.
[KYOKO gasps]
That's the one thing
I definitely couldn't
do right now.
So I'm fighting back.
Don't care if it's stupid.
I'm doing it.
[KYOKO] Well then...
you can count me in too.
[TOUJI] Mm.
You guys are
freakin' dumb.
Hmph.
You got a plan?
Yeah, sort of.
Hanging around here will
only draw their suspicion.
We let them
take us home.
Then double back to
the Onmyo Agency.
[KYOKO gasps]
Huh?
[SUZUKA] Hey, Four-Eyes.
What about you?
Care to join us?
[KYOKO gasps]
Yeah.
[KYOKO]
What just happened?
Your ride is here.
Please come outside.
[KYOKO] When it's
all said and done,
what will become
of us after this?
[phone rings]
[OHTOMO] Master.
[DOMAN]
Oh, I didn't expect you!
What do you need?
[OHTOMO] The situation has
changed since last we spoke.
I hate to ask for help after
what I said at the hospital.
But I desperately need to cash
in on that favor you owe me.
[DOMAN] My, my. That came
completely out of the blue.
So, what would you ask of me?
[OHTOMO] I'm currently
on my way to attack
Onmyo Agency Headquarters.
Would you care to join me?