[TOUJI] The spirit
disaster created by
the Twin Horn Syndicate that
day was painstakingly purified
and the government declared
a state of emergency.
The incident was called
"The Second Purification
of the Dolls Festival,"
and the news ran with the
story for days afterwards,
reporting non-stop about
the widespread effects.
[TOUJI]
A month after that...
[MIYO]
To all our new students,
welcome to Onmyo
Preparatory School.
My name is Miyo Kurahashi,
and I am the principal here.
There are a lot of new
kids starting this year.
Fun to get some fresh meat.
Uh huh.
Hope they know how
important the first day is.
Uh oh. I know that tone.
You're gonna go all delinquent
and scare em, huh?
Be quiet.
And would you stop looking
around like an idiot?
At this time, why don't
we hear a few words
from a representative
of the new students?
I'm sure they'll
all be very brave,
and, of course, terribly strong.
Not to mention fashionable.
At least they
better be, because
the judgment around
here is strong.
Yeah, from you.
Just don't do any
permanent damage
to their delicate psyches.
Oh, for the last
time, shut up!
This is Miss
Suzuka Dairenji.
You might know her
as the Prodigy.
[ALL THREE] Huh?
[SUZUKA inhales]
Nice to meet everyone
this beautiful morning!
My name is Suzuka Dairenji.
[applause]
[HARUTORA, NATSUME, and TOUJI]
What?
My name is
Suzuka Dairenji.
[applause]
[HARUTORA, NATSUME, and TOUJI]
What?
My goodness.
Thank you.
I've been so nervous about
speaking up here today.
You shut your
ugly mouth!
But I'm happy to be here!
There are just
far too many bugs!
I've always had
a secret dream.
To practice magic
with other kids my age.
And this year,
I'm finally able to do that.
And I'll have to
cut off your balls!
[SUZUKA giggles]
Thank you for helping
my dream come true!
[HARUTORA groans]
Right. Dream come true.
More like nightmare.
[TOUJI] Vulnerable smile.
Profile, 38 degrees
to the right.
Which is a completely
calculated angle.
That girl knows
exactly how to pose
to look as cute
as humanly possible.
Wonderful! I'm so glad
you're impressed!
I don't get it.
What the hell is going on here?
[HARUTORA] Aw, crap!
[HARUTORA] Yeah, definitely her.
No doubt.
[feedback]
[SUZUKA] Oh, my!
Did I see you out
there, Harutora?
[audience gasps]
[MIYO] You did.
Now, how do you
know him, my dear?
[SUZUKA] How?
Oh, well, he was the first
boy that I ever kissed.
[feedback]
[audience reacts loudly]
[HARUTORA whimpers]
[KYOKO] You were the
Prodigy's first kiss?
You went to a lame, normal
school with lame, stupid kids.
How and where did you meet
someone as amazing as Suzuka?!
Ugh!
[HARUTORA] Calm down,
you're turning all red.
Of course
I'm turning red!
This whole absurd story
is practically killing me!
There were special
circumstances, okay?
No, it is not okay!
That girl is the face
of the Onmyo Agency,
an idol in this world.
And she has the skills
to back it up.
I mean, honestly, she's who the
rest of us are trying to be!
[HARUTORA] Seriously?
So fess up!
Why on Earth would she
kiss someone like you?
Nothing personal,
but you're a loser
from a pretty
scandalized family!
On top of that, why?
Why would she make you her
once-in-a-lifetime first kiss?
That's just weird! Don't you
think it's weird? It's weird!
Maybe you could tell us all the
details to help us understand!
Yeah, spill it, loser!
Are you two like
totally going out?
Did you do more
than just kiss?
[squeals and laughter]
[KON] You better watch it!
Keep on yapping, and I'll bite!
It's okay, Kon.
There's no reason to get upset.
We're not attacking
him or anything.
[KON] I can feel your
thirst for blood, lady!
But don't you
wanna know why?
You see, one of the
Twelve Divine Generals
kissed Harutora for some reason.
Do you know what a kiss is?
[KON] No...
It's when lips touch
and smooching happens.
Smooch?
[HARUTORA] Kon, not you too!
Hey, Touji!
You guys went to the
same school, didn't you?
You know anything?
Kinda.
I hadn't heard about
the kiss, to be honest.
But let me think.
Must've happened the
night of the festival.
[squeals]
[HARUTORA] You are
such a bastard!
[NATSUME] Excuse me.
[NATSUME] I need a minute.
Let's talk, Harutora.
[OHTOMO] Seriously, what could
the Onmyo Agency be thinking?
Why do they insist on foisting
the Prodigy off on us?
Let me guess. It's her penalty
for what happened last year?
Correct. She had
special circumstances.
Apparently, her family life
left her with a shortage
of common sense.
At least, that's what
they're saying.
[OHTOMO] And of course, if
something were to happen now,
they'd want to take
care of it quickly.
So this school was the best
choice for her re-education.
Yeah. That's pretty much it.
"D" is keeping us
fairly busy on our end.
[OHTOMO sighs]
Well, Suzuka is officially
one of our students now.
I don't know what the Agency
is expecting from us, exactly.
But at the very least
we'll be sure to take
good care of the girl
while she's with us.
You sound like you care.
That's kinda cool.
Cool, huh?
It's my job.
[HARUTORA] I told you,
it wasn't a normal kiss
or anything like that!
I mean, technically if
you had to have a name
for what it was--I guess--
Yeah, it does sorta fit the
description of a first kiss.
But not a real one!
Seriously, there
weren't any feelings
or anything behind it, I swear!
[NATSUME] I don't care
about the stupid kiss.
Aren't you
forgetting something?
That she's seen me?
I was there with you last
summer, and I met her too.
[NATSUME inhales]
She knows the
truth about me.
I was dressed as a priestess--
a girl--the whole time!
[NATSUME] All I could think
of during the assembly
was to use an invisibility
spell and keep hidden.
But at this rate, I'm done
for when she sees me.
[HARUTORA]
Don't you worry.
I'll go talk to
her after school.
[HARUTORA]
What, she went home?
When?
[FEMALE STUDENT 10A]
Oh, she like just left.
[FEMALE STUDENT 10B]
I'm bummed; I was hoping
we could walk home together.
[FEMALE STUDENT 10A]
Yeah, even getting the chance
to talk to her was hard.
She was surrounded!
Well, thanks for
letting me know.
[FEMALE STUDENT 10A]
Oh my gah!
You're the boy that
kissed her, right?
So what, are you like
exes or something?
[HARUTORA] No, she's really
just an acquaintance.
You paused for a sec!
What does that mean?
You at least know her
well enough to kiss her!
[squeals and giggles]
[HARUTORA groans]
This morning had to be her sick
and twisted version of payback.
Even so, I can't believe she
said I was her first kiss!
[KON] So then, what she said
about you was really true?
[HARUTORA] Please, Kon, I don't
wanna talk about it anymore.
But don't you think that girl is
a little too young for you, sir?
How could you kiss
her to start with?
Look, I couldn't move!
She forced herself on me!
I didn't have a choice, okay?
What do you mean
forced on you?
I mean it's a
misunderstanding!
So you don't have any
feelings for her, then?
No, of c-c-course I d-don't!
What's up?
[HARUTORA] Who is that?
I didn't notice her at all.
[SUZU] A little girl.
[HARUTORA] What?
[SUZU] It's a little girl.
Little-- Hold on.
You talking about Kon?
It's a little girl fox.
She's a cute little
girl fox, too.
Yeah. She's my
defense familiar, too.
Cool, huh?
[SUZU] She's a cute
little girl fox familiar?
[HARUTORA]
What is her deal?
I suppose this means that
you're Harutora Tsuchimikado.
Wait, how do you
know who I am?
Oh right, because of the
assembly this morning.
I did not attend
Okay. So how
do you know me?
[HARUTORA] Alrighty, you're
starting to weird me out now.
Who the heck are you, anyway?
Who the heck I happen
to be is your senior.
Like a third year?
Oh, uh, I apologize
if I was rude.
[SUZU] You did it
because I'm small.
No, not really.
[SUZU] Because I look
like a little girl.
I said that wasn't it!
I understand. People often
mistake me for one.
You mean cause you look like a
first year? Not that you do.
I look very young.
It makes sense to me.
Well, don't worry about
it because I don't think
you look anything
like a little girl!
[SUZU] Hmph.
[HARUTORA]
Does that mean she's mad?
Okay, so did you need me
for something, or what?
I saw the little girl,
so I came over.
[HARUTORA]
Are you for real?
You're into little
girls that much?
[SUZU] No, it's not that.
I knew the son of the
Tsuchimikado branch family
had a familiar like her.
[SUZU] What's that?
What's what?
Oh yeah, that's
kind of a long story.
It's a spell.
[SUZU] It looks weird.
Well, I didn't ask you!
[HARUTORA]
Is she laughing now?
[SUZU] I'll see you around.
Just go home already!
[HARUTORA] Not here, either.
What kind of little
girl has a thing
for other little
girls? It's weird.
[SUZUKA]
Hey, Lolita Complex!
[HARUTORA] It's you!
[SUZUKA] Still got the same
stupid look, huh?
Don't stare at my
pigtails like that,
or people will get
the wrong idea.
Or maybe the right one?
I'm not staring!
I don't even care.
What I really want to know is,
how difficult was my very
special announcement
this morning for you?
It was awful.
And I'm sure that's
exactly what you wanted.
That's what you get!
You little brat!
Why do you have to be
so damn fake all the time?
Um, obviously, I have to
think of my public image.
Of course, your image.
So out with it, tell me the real
reason you were enrolled here.
[SUZUKA] I don't get
why I should have to
talk to you about that.
Oh, don't be defensive.
I mean, I was your
first kiss, right?
Darling.
[SUZUKA sighs]
[SUZUKA] It's my
punishment. My penalty.
[HARUTORA]
Because of last year?
If everything had gone
according to plan,
I wouldn't even be
in this world anymore.
But thanks to
somebody, I'm here.
It's pitiful, isn't it?
Well, I dunno.
Seems like it was a good
thing somebody was there.
[SUZUKA grunts]
[HARUTORA]
What about your brother?
Did you get a chance
to bury him properly?
[SUZUKA]
Mm-hmm.
That's good.
So, this penalty,
how long's it last?
Three years?
That's nothing.
Ah, they let you off a whole
lot easier than they could've.
[SUZUKA] What?
Are you stupid?
[HARUTORA] What's that?
Is it a spell?
Yeah.
They did it to seal
away my magic.
[HARUTORA] Whoa.
Well. No biggie;
it's only temporary.
And it's not like I couldn't
take you down
with my eyes closed!
[HARUTORA] Okay, okay.
Are you still worried about
what happened that night?
[SUZUKA] Huh! For real,
self-centered much, are we?
Oh wait, new topic!
Where's the next head of
the Tsuchimikado family?
If Natsume is still taking
classes in a place like this,
he's no rival of mine.
[HARUTORA] She doesn't know
who Natsume really is yet.
Speaking of which,
I don't think I've ever seen
Natsume Tsuchimikado before.
So you should
introduce me to him.
What?
[SUZUKA]
I'm counting on you, Darling.
[HARUTORA] Oh, great.
[SUZUKA] Just kill me
and be done with it.
I murdered your friend, right?
So kill me.
[HARUTORA]
Don't say things like that.
If you died now, there'd be
no one to mourn your brother.
[SUZUKA] Even though
you were an enemy,
you saved the life
I had thrown away.
And now I need to
turn into a new me.
But how?
[SUZUKA] How could I?
I killed her.
[murmuring]
A disguise?
Don't judge me; you're
the one who was stupid!
Her magic being
sealed is a plus,
so we've got that, at least.
If anything, it'll be harder
for her to see through
the fake version of
Natsume since it's magic.
Besides, no matter
how amazing she may be,
try to remember
she's still just a kid.
And she's not completely
heartless either.
[SUZUKA] Harutora!
Good morning, how are you!
She's here!
Better make
yourself invisible.
[HARUTORA]
Oh, hey there, Suzuka.
It's been forever!
[SUZUKA]
Whatcha talkin' about?
We met yesterday after school.
You're always so silly.
Wait a sec.
Was that supposed to be a secret
just between the two of us?
Oh no, I'm sorry!
[HARUTORA] Uh.
So did you need something?
Oh no, I just think it's lame
not being able to see you
even though we go
to the same school.
I wanted to see
your face and say hi.
So, hey there, mister!
I just can't see you enough!
[HARUTORA] Thank
you. That's very sweet,
but you didn't need
to come all the way
to the second-year classroom
just to tell me that.
Get out of here!
It's totally for real!
Good for you, buddy!
I wish I could be that bold!
You rock!
[HARUTORA] Will you
stop doing that?
[SUZUKA]
I can't help it.
The first-year
classroom is boring.
[HARUTORA]
Then try making friends!
How could I do that?
I'm too good for them.
I'm far too good for you, too!
I'm sure if you looked you
could find someone tolerable.
[SUZUKA]
No way. Too tiring.
Yeah. That's because
you don't know
how to act like a real person!
Let go.
You're hurting me.
[HARUTORA]
Oh. Sorry.
I have a question.
Natsume Tsuchimikado.
He's in your class, right?
What? Yeah, maybe,
I mean, at least I think so.
You're not
making any sense.
Which one is he?
I want you to introduce us.
Hey, wait, slow
your roll a second.
Today's not a good day.
Now, who is this person again?
[SUZUKA] What?
Do you have brain damage?
Stupid-tora.
[SUZUKA] Harutora!
Do you wanna eat
lunch together today?
It's invisibility time.
You need to memorize the
books from here to here
by the end of the day.
You're kidding me, right?
When am I supposed to sleep?
[SUZUKA] Harutora!
Invisible.
Aw, what do you
think you're doing?
Those books are too hard.
They're totally
wrong for you, silly.
[HARUTORA] What?
You think so?
[HARUTORA chuckles]
[SUZUKA] Harutora!
Get going.
Hey there.
My goodness, what a mess!
[NATSUME] I can't
take it anymore.
My body won't last.
[HARUTORA] Yeah.
Mine either.
My brain's fried, too.
I think the only option you have
is for Harutora to
tell her the truth.
You think?
Why me?
Face it, man.
You're the only one
she might listen to.
[SUZUKA hums]
Look who it is!
Hey, Harutora, honey!
Where have you been hiding?
I wasn't hiding.
Actually, I've been looking
everywhere for you!
Really?
C'mon, let's go for
a walk, darling.
[SUZUKA]
Wait, where are we going?
Harutora just
made a major move.
Yes, he did! They're basically
a for-real couple now!
A couple.
Like, a "couple"!
[KYOKO] I can't! I can't
even! I just can't!
[HARUTORA]
What's wrong?
[SUZUKA] What?
Nothing's wrong, stupid.
[HARUTORA] Huh.
Wonder if she gets out much.
[SUZUKA] Hm? Ugh,
stop doing that.
Whatever you're thinking, I'm
sure it's super disrespectful.
Ooh, perceptive.
If you wanna know the truth,
I was thinking,
"You know what, this kid's
still pretty cute."
How annoying! You're not
that much older than me.
Tell me, how are you
liking Onmyo Prep?
I said stop it.
You're being all condescending!
Why aren't you hanging out with
any of the kids in your class?
They're boring,
that's why.
Fine. But I'm sure you must
know some interesting people.
Shut up. You're starting
to sound like an old man.
You better hurry up and eat
that, or it's gonna get cold.
[HARUTORA laughs]
Here you go.
I could have done
that for myself!
Of course you could.
I'll cut them off!
Don't think I won't!
[HARUTORA] Why put on a show?
You should just act like
yourself at school.
[SUZUKA] I told you, I have
to keep up my public image.
Does your image as
a Divine General
really mean all
that much to you?
Because I don't think it should.
[HARUTORA] What happened
with your brother is over
and you're at a
different school now.
It's a fresh start.
You might even find
a new you, ya know?
Hey, I'm sorry.
That was kinda
inconsiderate of me.
My bad.
So, like, um...
Why--Why don't you
seem to resent me?
Resent you?
Why would I?
[SUZUKA] Because of what
happened to that familiar!
I completely obliterated her.
I don't understand how
you can be nice to me
after I did that to you.
[HARUTORA] I get it.
She's been stressing
the whole time.
This is the turning point.
I can't get this wrong.
There's no need for lies.
[HARUTORA] Don't be stupid.
I'm bugged about that
enough for us both.
Besides, I was the
one who was a coward.
I think it's best if
we put that behind us.
What about you?
You might've been going about
it wrong, but it was our fault
that you ended up not being
able to see your brother.
[HARUTORA] It must
be unbelievably hard,
knowing that you'll
never have him back.
I can't even imagine
how awful that is.
[SUZUKA] It's terrible.
It really is.
[HARUTORA] For what it's worth,
it's not like Hokuto's dead.
It's a funny story.
Yes, she's a familiar,
but she was created
with a different sort of spell.
Basically, someone
was controlling her
from the outside.
What? You mean remotely?
That's impressive.
[HARUTORA]
Yeah, I guess someone made her
to become friends with me.
And that person is
probably still around.
That's one reason
I started school here.
I thought maybe I would get the
chance to meet whoever it was
that controlled Hokuto.
Pretty crazy, huh?
[SUZUKA] What the hell?
Huh?
[SUZUKA] That's pretty
freaking annoying, you know.
Why bring me here
and preach at me?
What do you think you'll gain?
Okay. What are you saying?
I'm saying this.
When I decide who the new me is,
it'll be my choice, got that?
So you can stop spying
on me, you creep!
Your invisibility spell has
been too weak this whole time!
[NATSUME yells]
Natsume?
What the heck are
you doing here?
Natsume?
What?
[SUZUKA gasps]
She's that priestess!
All right.
Finally, things are gonna
start to get fun around here.
Good morning, darling!
I hope you're having
a good day so far!
[HARUTORA]
Oh. Hey there.
What's wrong, dear?
You're looking a little
bummed out today.
Are you Natsume
Tsuchimikado, by chance?
[NATSUME] Mm-hmm.
[SUZUKA] Why, I could not
be happier to meet you!
The truth is...
I've been wanting to be
introduced to you forever.
[TENMA] Those two are
destined to be friends.
After all they're both geniuses
and birds of a feather
flock together, right?
What an amazing moment!
[SUZUKA] Oh, I think we are all
going to be very best buddies.
Don't you guys agree?
[NATSUME and HARUTORA whimper]
[NATSUME and HARUTORA]
This is gonna be a nightmare.
I'll cut off your balls!
Chop! Chop!