[MALE ANNOUNCER 8A] Confirmation
of a chain of spirit disasters!
Chimera Zero One,
moving to Phase Four!
I repeat, confirmation
of a chain of spirit disasters!
Chimera Zero One,
moving to Phase Four!
[KYOKO] The nue's running away!
[NUE roars]
[MIYACHI] He's all yours.
Okay, I'm on it! C'mon!
Hirata! Get these kids
to a safe zone, now!
Yes, sir!
[KOGURE] Miyachi.
You handle the rest!
Get going, would ya?
Good luck.
What the...?
You wanna draw out the nue,
you need Hokuto.
And if you want my dragon,
you're taking me.
No!
Heh. You got a deal. Let's not
tell Jin, though, kay?
[NATSUME] Kurahashi!
[KYOKO] Eh?
I'll be back soon!
But we're not
supposed to--yaah!
♪
[KOGURE] Found him.
[KOGURE]
Kokuryuu! Dassai!
Reisen! Hou'oubiden!
[squawk]
[NATSUME]
Quite the escort!
And this motorcycle
is a familiar too?
Yeah. It's pretty
weird, right?
Go after the nue!
I need you guys
to stop him in
the outer gardens!
[squawking]
[NUE roars]
It's falling on
Jingu Stadium.
Then we'll meet it there.
[KOKURYUU]
It dodged our attack!
It's got mad skills!
Well, bring it down
already, guys!
If it gets any further,
he'll be on Aoyama street!
[NATSUME] I think I can help.
Hokuto, he's getting away!
[KOGURE] Wicked.
[KON] Master Harutora!
With all due respect, I could
just pick you up and fly.
I don't plan to waste your
power on getting around.
I'm counting on you
when the time comes.
Oh, yes, of course!
Just leave it to me!
[KON coughs]
All right, let's go!
Yes, Master!
Glad to see you're
finally awake.
Where's Harutora?
[MIYO] I would say
your friend is probably
headed towards
that as we speak.
[TOUJI] That damn idiot.
[MIYO] There's something you
should know about, Touji.
I slightly loosened the seal
that's been
restraining your ogre.
Your half-ogre symptoms must
be a result of my tampering.
But why?
So that you could learn
to control the ogre inside.
Not just hold him back.
Do you understand
why I would do that?
Nope.
Because when you
enrolled in this school,
you made a commitment to train
to become an onmyo mage.
And you have a rather
unorthodox path open to you.
Harnessing the power of the ogre
instead of fighting
to keep him at bay.
You mean I
would control it?
[MIYO] Officer Kagami,
also known as the Ogre Eater,
subdues his prey
only to utilize them
as a power source
for his later consumption.
In fact, that ability is what
earned him his fierce nickname.
[TOUJI] Type Ogre
spirit disasters...
Their power can
be used that way?
Does that mean mine can, too?
[MIYO] Perhaps.
But your doctor set up
parameters for this.
A stipulation for certain
criteria, if you will.
He required that his son
be the one in control.
This was the only
condition he had for you.
You mean Harutora?
[EXORCISTS] Om bishi bishi
kara kara shibari sowaka...
Om bishi bishi kara
kara shibari sowaka...
Amazing. I wonder if I'll
ever be this powerful.
Hey, where you
think you're goin'?
It's too dangerous here.
Move it, now!
[KYOKO] All right.
You'll be safe, Miss.
I'm gonna head back in.
[roars]
[KOGURE] Looking good.
[HARUTORA] Natsume?
Harutora!
You know that guy?
It's Mutobe.
[roars]
[NATSUME] They're passing
the outer gardens!
[KOGURE] What should I do?
[NATSUME] I'm on it!
[KOGURE] Hey!
Hold on!
[KOGURE] Wow, kid. You're a lot
more gung-ho than I thought!
I'll send my familiars
to escort you.
I'll follow once I've
taken care of Mutobe.
Just don't do anything rash!
[DASSAI] Into the sky. Jump!
Kon, do you see Natsume?
[NATSUME screams]
[KOKURYUU] Right!
Get on, kid!
[HARUTORA screams]
[NATSUME screams]
Be careful how
you're grabbing me!
I'm gonna die!
I'm so gonna freakin' die!
So you're Mutobe.
You're Abhijna's sword?
We don't have to do
this if you don't want.
You can still walk away.
Stop the bike!
I want to get off!
Watch your hands,
Harutora!
What are you trying to do,
you freaking pervert?
I'm not trying
to do anything!
[NATSUME] Hokuto!
[HARUTORA] Hokuto.
Take me with you, alright?
Kon, I need you to come too!
I'm on it! You can
count on me, Master!
Promise you'll be careful!
[MIYO] Your ride is here.
The Tsuchimikado family
familiar, Yukikaze.
Natsume's father somehow knew
you would need him tonight.
He reads the
stars very well.
Must've had a hunch that
the horse would be required.
He can read the stars to
determine a half-ogre's fate?
You're right, he must
be really good.
[TENMA] Hold on! Touji!
[TENMA pants]
[TENMA] Hey.
Listen, I wasn't
sure how I felt
after I found out. I was
afraid I wouldn't be able
to act the same
around you anymore.
Sometimes I can be
a little bit awkward
about stuff
like that, you know?
But everything's fine. I mean,
you're still just Touji!
Half-ogre or not.
Thanks, man.
Can you give this
to Harutora?
I'm betting he's
going to need it.
Sure. You have my word.
That's good
enough for me!
Y'know, I've heard
all about you.
Rumor has it you're really fast.
Well, don't hold back. Let's see
what kind of speed you've got.
[HARUTORA yells]
Tremble before Kon!
Servant of the Tsuchimikados.
Descendant of Kuzunoha, the
legendary fox! Prepare yourself!
[KON yells]
[KON screams]
Kon!!
Order!
[DASSAI] Yeah! Blast
that jerk right in the eye!
[KOKURYUU] Time to join
in on the fun! Let's go!
My first attack
may have failed,
but like I told you
before, I am Kon.
Descendant of the
legendary fox Kuzunoha,
and loyal retainer to
the mighty Tsuchimikado--
[KON screams]
Kon!!
[HARUTORA wails]
Oh, please, no!
You insolent heathen!
How dare you handle my
Master so discourteously?!
Don't worry about me!
Just promise that
you won't give up!
[KON whimpers]
Your will be done, sir.
Oh, man, this Nue
is hardcore.
Master, watch out!
Kon, no!
[TOUJI] It's time to accept it.
To face this head on!
I have friends
that will help me.
Friends that will
always be by my side.
I'm not scared of you, ogre.
I refuse to be
afraid of my future!
[TOUJI] I can feel
my blood boiling.
The ogre's raging. Alright...
I'll show you how
to focus your anger!
[HARUTORA] Somethin'
wrong, half-ogre?
All that power you had
yesterday is gone?
Like it or not,
looks like we're stuck
with each other for a while.
[TOUJI] Harutora!
[TOUJI yells]
[HARUTORA yells]
[DASSAI] That kid just harnessed
the power of the half-ogre!
[KOKURYUU] It's show time!
[HARUTORA] This ends here!
[NUE roars]
Come on. Are you
kidding me, dude?
Qiyi Qiyi, weave a shape
out of formless clouds.
May the firstborn son
of all the world pierce
through the mantras, through
space and time themselves.
May he traverse
the very heavens.
To move the hand of the Creator!
Qiyi Qiyi, please hear
our prayer!
Now! By the power and
benevolence of the Creator.
Heaven's fury!
Purify this evil miasma!
Order!
[HARUTORA] Huh?
[HARUTORA] The purification...
It worked?
[DASSAI] Yeah,
you're number one!
[KOKURYUU] Eradication
celebration time!
For real?
[HARUTORA screams]
[HARUTORA] Not again!
[KON] Don't worry,
I'll catch you!
I'm sorry, but my
power's all used up.
[HARUTORA yelps]
[HARUTORA] Oh, thank god.
[TOUJI] My timing was flawless,
if I do say so myself.
[HARUTORA] Touji?
Why're you riding Yukikaze?
Are those horns?
Pretty cool, right?
Yeah, man. Not bad!
[KAGAMI] The amateurs
pulled it off! Ah, the irony.
That was one
hell of a display.
And now the rumors about
Natsume Tsuchimikado will gain
even more ground and Yakou's
followers will be re-energized.
[HARUTORA] Can't believe
we never thought
of taming the ogre.
[TOUJI] Yeah, well...
This whole "ogre power"
thing is just a trial run.
No telling what might
happen next time.
What's the matter, Mr. Cool?
You afraid of a little work?
Big talk from a guy who
just got smacked around.
And if I lose
control as an ogre,
remember you're top candidate
for getting eaten first.
If you're as late then as
you were today, no worries.
Seriously, though! Today was
a little crazy, wasn't it?
This morning, all I
could think about
was the exam to move
up to the next grade.
[TOUJI] Yeah, right?
I guess it's like they say--
"Every cloud has
a silver lining."
Silver lining?
What silver lining?
Stupid-tora.
Being half-ogre sucks,
but because of it I met you.
Which makes me feel a little
grateful for the lame-ass thing.
D'ya look at that?
Touji's getting all
sentimental on me now.
[TOUJI] Nah.
I think you must've
hit your head.
[HARUTORA] Anyone have a tissue
for poor, sweet little Touji?
We should just stay
out of their way.
Huh?
Of course, I know that!
But I--I still feel
a little jealous.
Yeah, right?
I wish I could connect
with him like that.
It's no fair.
They make it look so easy.
[KAGAMI] Something different
about that half-ogre.
Somehow this reminds
me of Dairenji's
crazy little experiment.
I can practically
smell it on him.
That's no ordinary
ogre in there.
Heh. That's great.
Seriously the best.
Guess it'll be faster
to just let it take over.
Sounds fun.
[OHTOMO] Always pay attention
to your surroundings,
no matter what.
Didn't they teach you that
on the first day of training?
Pretty sneaky for a man
with one leg, Shadow.
It has been awhile,
hasn't it, Ogre Eater?
[KAGAMI] So how's the
retired life treating you?
[OHTOMO] It gives me
time for hobbies.
Like taking nighttime walks.
But I like to keep
busy, you know.
So I decided to try
my hand at teaching.
I'm back at Onmyo Prep.
[KAGAMI] Is that so?
Maybe I should pay you
a little visit one day.
You seem to have some very
interesting students.
Yes, but sadly, you
won't have the time.
You'll be far too busy.
I imagine it will
take you quite awhile
to break through
all of these spells.
What're you talking about?
While you were busy making
those thinly veiled threats,
I was casting a litany of spells
I thought you might
find diverting.
And they're all spells
you'll need to look up
in ancient documents if
you hope to break them.
You're just bluffing!
That kinda fake-out is
wasted on me, four eyes.
I've known you too
long for it to work.
And what have you learned
about me in that time?
You know what kind
of person I am.
Think back to your training.
Remember how I always
made you go with me
to the harshest battles
whenever it was possible?
I wanted you to witness
the lengths I would go to
should the situation
ever force my hand.
You've also known me
long enough to realize
that even if ninety percent
of what I've said is a bluff,
ignoring the other ten percent
could still prove costly.
But you knew all that.
Didn't you now?
Well, have fun
with your research
if you choose to go that route.
I certainly wouldn't
try to dispel anything
I don't understand.
Oh, and Kagami?
Remember this.
While there is still
life in my body,
you will not lay a
finger on my students.
[KAGAMI] So first I
find a half-ogre kid
and the possible
reincarnation of Yakou.
And now I get to laugh
in the face of Death.
Not a bad day. Heh.
[KAGAMI] I can't wait.
One of these days,
you'll screw up.
And then I'm gonna knock
you down a peg or two.
Come on, then.
There's no need to wait.
[KOGURE] Right!
Let's leave it at that, Jin.
[OHTOMO] Hm?
Zenjiro!
What were you thinking,
letting an amateur do your job?
So, did you take
Mutobe into custody?
Well, he died.
[KAGAMI] What?
[KOGURE] We're not sure yet,
but it seems he used
a suicide spell.
You constantly take it
too easy on your opponents.
Wait. You mean he's
always been like this?
Yes, I'm afraid that's
forever been the case.
Why is talking trash about me
the only time you guys agree?
[OHTOMO] Uhh!
So you sense it too.
It can't be.
Did they open up
the streets again?
Master Harutora, be on guard!
[DOMAN] I was planning
on retrieving
a little bit of its essence.
But your successful exorcism
means I won't find a trace.
No point crying
over spilt milk.
After all, you did let me
enjoy myself tonight!
I'm looking
forward to it all.
But the anticipation
is killing me!
You're all still just baby
chicks in this world.
Freshly hatched,
completely unaware.
You should study diligently.
And when you're
finished with that,
perhaps we'll find
a place for you.
[NATSUME gasps]
But we don't know who you are!
[DOMAN] Then let me
introduce myself.
I'm Doman Ashiya.
What the...?
Freaky.
I don't know what
just happened.
It can't be.
We have to find help.
[HIRATA] In humble supplication.
I offer up myself as a sacrifice
to the Taizan Fukun god
of the afterlife.
[HIRATA] Brother Mutobe.
Thank you for your hard work.
[HIRATA] Please leave
the rest to me.
[phone rings]
♪
[DASSAI and KOKURYUU]
Kagami! Kagami! Kagami! Kagami!
[KAGAMI] Shut up.