[distant door opens]
[HARUTORA] Natsume.
[gasps lighly] Huh?
[HARUTORA] Gotta admit, a little
weird seeing you like that.
[NATSUME] I can't imagine what
school will be like tomorrow.
[HARUTORA] Everyone's
probably heard by now.
Should make things
a little bit easier.
[NATSUME] Yeah,
I guess that's true.
I'm worried
about Kyoko, though.
[HARUTORA sighs]
[HARUTORA] Me too; we all
lied to her together.
Well, I guess the only thing
we can do is prepare ourselves.
[NATSUME]
Prepare ourselves? For what?
So we can face her
straight on
and start apologizing
non-stop.
It's a chance to
be real friends.
You know, the kind who don't
feel the need to hide the truth
or anything from each other.
You crack me up; you're
always so optimistic.
Yeah, that's the only thing
I've got goin' for me.
Do you really think so?
Hey, you were supposed
to contradict me there.
[HARUTORA and NATSUME laugh]
It's already been a year.
It still seems like
yesterday, though.
[NATSUME] Harutora, I--
[HARUTORA] Hm?
I've been meaning
to say, "thank you."
[HARUTORA] Uh?!
It's been a great year.
And I'm happy you got
to be here with me.
Uh...
I might not be exactly
dependable quite yet,
but I'm a pretty
decent familiar.
True!
[KON] M-Master Harutora.
I am terribly sorry to
interrupt this moment--
[HARUTORA] Kon?
It's... It's not t-technically
an urgent matter,
but it's important.
Kon. I'm really sorry.
It's my fault I kept
sending you spirit energy.
It's--It's all right.
My job as a familiar is to
receive my master's powers,
and, I'm, I'm
e-extremely grateful.
I'm still sorry.
It wasn't on purpose.
Not, on purpose? Oh no.
Begging your pardon,
but your magical power
is lacking much needed
stability, Master Harutora!
This is a very
serious matter, sir!
Nah, it's totally fine.
I'm keeping things
in check now, right?
Yes, Master.
But still!
[yawns]
Please stop stressing and
let me get some sleep today.
I gotta go back to school
bright and early, ya know.
G'night.
[TOUJI] Looks like
we were right, guys.
They're all staring at us.
The news about Natsume is out.
Hey!
[TENMA]
Good morning, everyone!
[NATSUME sighs]
Hey, bro.
How you doing?
I'm okay; thanks.
You went through
a lot, didn't you?
You're living in the boys'
dorm still, yeah?
But you're good?
Yes. People are keeping
their distance, though.
[laughs]
I'm sure everyone's
way confused,
but I'm glad it wasn't
too big of a deal.
Dude, Tenma!
I always thought you must
be a for real good guy,
and I was right.
Um. Calm down; I'm just
trying to be a friend.
You know. Guys like you
aren't easy to find, my man.
You should be
proud of yourself.
[TENMA] Come on, guys.
Back off.
I'm not comfortable
with all this touching.
Hey, I didn't see
you over there.
Yeah, poor thing was
waiting anxiously
by herself until I showed up.
I was not!
Don't tell lies, Four-Eyes!
For everyone's information.
I, like, just got here.
Whatcha got in
your hand there?
What? Well, this is
uh, oh, it's nothing.
[TENMA] Natsume, have your
parents said anything yet?
[NATSUME] Mhm.
Well, it's just her dad.
Natsume's mom isn't
really around anymore.
She doesn't talk to
her dad much, though.
So she might be able to hide
it until after graduation.
I guess Kyoko's
the only one left.
[HARUTORA] Yeah.
[TOUJI] Good news:
starting today
we'll get to see each other
whether we like it or not.
Hooray.
So lame.
[NATSUME] Mm.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Tsuchimikado.
I wanna say
thanks for saving us
if you all hadn't been there,
I probably would have died!
Yeah, same here!
We seriously can't
thank you enough!
But it was our fault.
We're the only reason
you got involved.
And you kept us
from getting hurt,
so it's all good.
I can't believe it.
Thank you, everyone.
[TENMA chuckles]
She's gotta hate me.
[bells ring in distance]
[whimpers]
[HARUTORA]
Hey, hold up a sec.
Kyoko, wait!
I'm sorry.
[HARUTORA] I tried to
explain it in my text.
You know what Natsume is like.
It doesn't matter
how unreasonable
this whole thing was;
to her tradition is tradition.
But... we feel really
bad about tricking you.
We've been jerks.
Big time.
So please, just
let us apologize.
[KYOKO] I told you.
I told you.
Don't you remember?
About how I met a boy at
Nastume's house as a kid?
And I said...
I liked him.
Do you remember
that at all?
Yeah. It was love at
first sight or something.
I know it's hard. I'm sorry.
But Natsume's a girl.
Yes, but I met a boy.
No...
And he was kind.
[HARUTORA] Uh.
I'll never forget that.
I was just some random,
annoying little girl.
[KYOKO] But he wasn't
bothered by me at all.
I asked him straight out
if he was a Tsuchimikado,
and he told me he was.
Say what you will; I know the
kid I talked to was a boy.
I'm sorry.
But there's some mistake.
You really mean it, you'll
look for my ribbon for me?
Yeah.
At least, I'll try.
Alright! You made me a promise.
Pinky swear you won't forget!
[KYOKO] It's not fair.
And I was planning
to apologize, too.
I can't believe all the
things I said to him.
I'm sure he remembers, now.
[KYOKO] This is the worst.
[SUZUKA]
You are bumming me out.
[KYOKO]
Oh, hey, Suzuka.
[SUZUKA] I'm gonna
need you to stop.
Your lame sadness is starting
to make me feel bad, too.
So like, what is wrong
with you today anyway?
[KYOKO] I dunno.
[SUZUKA]
Yes, you do too know.
You're totally emitting the
"I'm a girl who has
love troubles" aura.
Are you maybe a little drunk
with your own self-sufficiency?
Gimmie a break.
Why are you here?
Did you just wanna
argue with me?
I don't have the
time to argue.
I only came to see how you
were 'cause I was asked.
Four-Eyes wouldn't shut up
about it, so here I am.
[KYOKO] Tenma?
[SUZUKA] Yeah. Turns out
he's boring and annoying.
[KYOKO] Suzuka, you knew the
truth about Natsume, didn't you?
[SUZUKA] You mean
that she was a girl?
Well, duh.
I gotta admit, the whole
thing was pretty funny.
[KYOKO] I didn't know.
They had me completely fooled.
Well, who cares?
Why are you so depressed
about it, anyway?
What?
[SUZUKA] Shouldn't you be
getting super pissed, instead?
I mean, they all lied to you.
Yeah, but Natsume sorta had to
follow her family's traditions.
Oh, like that
makes it okay?
Maybe she shouldn't pick
traditions over her friends,
did ya think about that?
Plus Touji and I knew the
truth from the beginning.
A secret can't be a secret
if that many people knew.
Seriously.
I'm sure you know they
regret everything
and are like, way sorry.
But I think you should
still make sure
to give them a
piece of your mind,
just to shake 'em up and make
them know they're stupid!
Write "Loser" on
their foreheads
and force them to keep
it there a whole month!
[SUZUKA] Or make them say
"I'm sorry times infinity."
Thank you, Suzuka.
[SUZUKA] For real, those
people get on my last nerve.
They act all self-righteous
to everyone else,
but meanwhile, they're hiding
their shady business.
I mean, Natsume has yet
to confess her whole
Hokuto charade to Harutora.
Are you talking about
Natsume's familiar dragon?
Different Hokuto familiar.
[gasps]
Mm.
Ahhh.
Training camp.
Remember the story
that Stupid-tora told?
About the one girl
that he liked?
Long-distance manipulation?
The familiar girl,
yeah, sure.
No, you can't be for real.
By Natsume hasn't
told him, d'you mean...?
Now, I don't have
technical evidence,
but if you think
about it objectively,
who else could it be?
[KYOKO exhales]
Anyway, just stop.
You're being almost
as irritating right now
as those jerks are.
So hurry up and make up or
whatever with them already.
I got plans, so get over it.
Wait, what plans?
[SUZUKA gasps]
Nothing specific; we all
have plans, don't we?
You don't have to
know everything.
[SUZUKA] Aah...
Ahhh! No!
Don't look at it!
[KYOKO]
A fireworks festival?
No! No, it's nothing.
I just had that to doodle on.
It's not at all
what it looks like
or what you're
thinking it may be!
It's a scrap piece of trash
paper so give it back to me!
Give it!
Day after tomorrow.
No, it's not!
Don't worry.
I'll settle things with
them before then, okay?
It'll be fine.
Huh?
Thank you, Suzuka.
[SUZUKA]
Whatever. Quit it.
Let me go, you cow!
I can't breathe in here!
Pinky swear you
won't forget, okay?
And then I went
and totally forgot.
What am I supposed to say to
Kyoko when I see her again?
I can't sleep at all!
[HARUTORA snoring]
[cell phone ringing]
It's Dad.
What could he want?
"Things are all right
on our end,
so there's no need
for you to be worried."
The crap does that mean?
[MALE REPORTER 18A] Before
dawn, it was confirmed that
the fire at the home
of the distinguished
Tsuchimikado family
had died down naturally
before the
firefighters arrived.
The cause of the fire is
currently being investigated.
[birds chirping]
[crickets chirping]
Yasuzumi Tsuchimikado.
Current head of the
Tsuchimikado family.
I'm taking you into custody.
Independent exorcist.
Mari Yuge.
I do not wish to make
matters worse, sir.
I would appreciate
you coming quietly.
[YASUZUMI]
May I ask why?
[MARI] I have not been told
the details at this time.
In fact, you probably know what
this is about more than I do.
Will you come
along quietly?
No, I will not.
Oh my. You've got guts
walking in like that, dear.
[WOMAN] You didn't even
take off your shoes.
[MARI gasps]
Order!
[MARI] Uh!
No matter what, everyone
stay within my barrier.
If not, you'll die.
Oh my! And I was
holding back some, too!
Heh, heh, ha.
Even so you are pretty good.
Ms. Yuge is a State
Onmyo Mage First Class.
Oh?
Could you be the barrier-user,
"Bond Princess", by any chance?
And just who might you be?
Well, I used to
be your senior.
I'm sure you've heard of
"Lum of Akihabara"?
I have not.
The "Exorcism Bureau's
Sky God, Komachi"?
"Flashing Lady Thunder," maybe?
First time I've ever
heard of those names.
[CHIZURU] Really?
Well, you're still young, so.
[gasps]
And I haven't worked
for a while, either.
That woman is the
"Human Power Generator"!
Are you kidding me?
How come you only know
that nasty name?
[MARI] Have you heard
from the investigators
who went around back?
No reply yet, ma'am.
[MARI]
Understood; thank you.
[CHIZURU]
...that's the name to go with!
I am now taking you
both into custody.
What?
Oh my, so you're choosing
to face me head on?
From the East, akada.
From the West, shutakou.
From the South, satteiro.
Order!
[MARI] From the North,
sodamani sowaka!
[MARI] Om bishi bishi
kara kara shibari sowaka.
An immobilizing spell?
No point.
The Tsuchimikado barrier
won't allow it.
[MARI] Haa!
[CHIZURU gasps]
[CHIZURU] But how?
The barrier is...
It has not been taken down.
She looked at its construction
and rendered it ineffective.
[CHIZURU]
In that split second?
I am a barrier
expert, after all.
I would prefer it if you
could sit there quietly,
"Human Power Generator."
[CHIZURU] It can't be helped.
May I Yasuzumi?
[YASUZUMI]
Try to be gentle.
[CHIZURU grunts]
Electricity is coming
directly out of her body!
Is it a familiar?
That is correct!
[CHIZURU] Nou maku
san manda bonadan.
Indoraya sowaka!
[MARI grunts]
Don't underestimate me!
[CHIZURU] What?
Huh? What's this?
Some kind of barrier?
With a Divine General
for an opponent,
winning with a frontal
attack will be difficult.
[CHIZURU] Then why
don't you, I don't know,
try helping me out?
[YASUZUMI] This is not
the time for me to fight.
In these situations,
my familiars are
extremely capable.
[TAKAHIRO]
Chizuru's right, you know.
[MARI gasps]
You should put a little
effort into this thing, too.
Takahiro!
Sorry I'm late.
Made it in time, though.
[MARI] Impossible!
[MARI] Om bishi bishi
kara kara shibari sowaka!
A familiar?
[TAKAHIRO] You should
be able to move now.
And who are you?
[TAKAHIRO] Just a simple
country Onmyo doctor, ma'am.
[MIYACHI] Well, looks
to me like you're stuck.
It's not terribly surprising
considering the fact
you're facing the whole
Tsuchimikado family.
What? Miyachi!
[creaking]
[MIYACHI] You can
do better than that.
How can you greet a former
colleague so rudely?
Commander, I...
I gotta say,
good work, Maririn.
Please don't call
me Maririn, sir.
[MIYACHI] It's been
a while, you three.
Haven't changed a bit.
Presumptuous,
don't you think?
Even for a Miyachi.
[MIYACHI]
Come on now,
we can be friendlier
than this, can't we?
[CHIZURU] Why are
you showing up now?
After so much time,
why not just let it slide?
[MIYACHI] Now, don't
be so unreasonable.
You really haven't changed.
Miyachi, tell me,
you're fine with this?
[MIYACHI] Hmm...
Why, am I not supposed to be?
To be honest with you,
even I'm not on the
chief's side this time.
[TAKAHIRO] It certainly
appears as though
you've become rather dignified.
[MIYACHI]
Much obliged for that.
Now then, do you think you
can give me what's in the box?
Oh no, that would
be impossible.
Takahiro.
Got it. We get
to do something
death-defying for the first
time in quite a while.
[MIYACHI] Maririn,
do you think you could
strengthen the barrier
around this area?
Uh.
The last thing I'd want is
to trouble the neighbors
by burning everything in
this vicinity to the ground.
[phone rings]
[MIYACHI] Thank you
for your patience.
The Raven Coat is
now in my possession.
[OHTOMO] So you're saying
Yasuzumi Tsuchimikado's
whereabouts are unknown?
[KOGURE] Yes.
Anything from MIB?
[KOGURE]
Well, about that.
Considering how unsettled
they should be right now
with their director missing,
they're doing strangely well.
[OHTOMO] What the hell?
Yeah, those guys
are acting on orders
without knowing a single thing
about them. It's bizarre.
One more thing, Jin.
I get how you feel, but don't
go off on your own here.
[OHTOMO] Yeah, sure.
[phone clicks]
Uh--
[door creaks]
[exhales shakily]
[OHTOMO sighs]
I'm kind of a coward,
so can you please try
not to scare me, Master?
[OHTOMO] Thanks.
[DOMAN] Ah-woo!
[chuckles]
You decided to be
a child this time?
You have to have known
that's in rather poor taste.
[DOMAN] There are
various conditions
that need to be met
to be my host.
For the record,
I haven't done anything.
Not, yet.
Wonderful.
And what is it that brings you
to my room this fine evening?
[DOMAN laughs]
What do you think?
[OHTOMO] I don't know,
but I'm praying
you're not
here for revenge.
[DOMAN]
How regrettable.
Do you truly think
I would bother doing
something so
completely boorish?
It's the opposite, actually.
[OHTOMO] Which means?
[DOMAN] I came to
answer to the winner.
If someone bested me and
didn't receive anything
in return for their victory,
then my name would
become obsolete,
and we can't
have that, can we?
Onmyo mage, Jin Ohtomo,
what is it you would
like me to do for you?
Well, for the time being,
do you think you could
perhaps withdraw?
But if that's not possible,
just quietly stay
inside for a bit?
Boring!
You know those things are
hardly acceptable requests.
[OHTOMO sighs]
Well, Master, mind if I
ask you a question please.
The blast that was responsible
for blowing away your old body.
Was it the work of the
Twin Horn Syndicate?
[DOMAN] Most likely.
They wanted to keep me
from spilling secrets.
Then, I imagine it
would be safe to assume
you've parted from their
company at this point,
is that correct?
[DOMAN] It is.
I have no duty toward
those fools any longer.
Does that mean you
don't mind telling me
who's behind Twin Horn?
Because I'd really like to
know who that might be.
The collar on the
Twin Horn Syndicate
is very connected
to the Onmyo Agency,
although to be fair.
I bet you were already
aware of that fact.
[OHTOMO sighs]
This is fun; ask me
something else!
[OHTOMO] Okay.
Why did you want
the Raven Coat?
Oh, I just wanted that because
my disciple requested it.
Disciple?
That's right,
and, surprise,
she has somewhat of a
history with you, Jin.
Her name is Suzu Saotome.
Yes indeed.
Tell me, is she doing
all right these days?
[DOMAN] She's already left.
It seems she doesn't need me
anymore, so I don't know.
How impertinent.
Okay.
Let us leave it at that
for tonight, shall we?
I'll see you soon, though;
this conversation
is not nearly enough
to reward you
for your victory.
Oh no, it's plenty.
Why don't we agree that
I still owe you one anyway.
If you have something you
want to ask me in the future,
all you have to do is call.
And I promise to lend you
my power if you need it.
Uh, Master. I have to
say I'm a little afraid
that you are actually
trying to curse me.
[DOMAN laughs]
The fact you
truly believe that
is evidence of your
twisted personality.
Now, give me your
mobile telephone.
[DOMAN] I'm going to put
my number in it for you.
You have a cell phone?
Yeah. Of course.
Who doesn't?
Don't you find with the
technology nowadays,
it seems like only
a matter of time
[DOMAN] before our
magic will be obsolete?
Catch!
Well, when you say it,
it's difficult not to
believe that's the case.
[laughs]
We're two men
behind the times.
We should try to get along from
now on, wouldn't you agree?
Oh, man.
[MALE REPORTER 18A]
No bodies or remains
were found in the ashes,
and there has still
been no contact with
the owner of the building,
Yasuzumi Tsuchimikado.
The authorities so
far have no leads.
[KYOKO] Natsume's family home
burned to the ground,
and I don't even know
how she's dealing.
Enough.
[TAKIKO] Excuse me.
I was planning to go to Natsume
Tsuchimikado's classroom.
Do you think you can
show me where he is?
Okay?
Have we met before?
[TAKIKO]
We haven't yet, no.
Very nice to meet you;
I'm Takiko Souma.
Recommendation.
Right between the ears
is the sweet spot okay!