[HARUTORA] Aahh!
Now then tell
Natsume, or else!
All right, darling?
[HARUTORA]
Hey, are you okay?
How could you?
How could you be so careless?
You didn't even chase after me.
And when I come back, you're--
you're kissing that girl.
[HOKUTO cries]
[HARUTORA]
No, you've got it wrong.
She trapped me on that thing,
and then she kissed me!
I should be the one crying!
[HOKUTO] Stupid-tora!
You don't get it!
You hurt my feelings and now--
This is even worse.
The guy I like
kissed another girl!
You haven't talked to Hokuto
since the whole kissing thing?
She doesn't answer when I call,
or reply to my texts.
But you're still a hundred
percent sure she's okay, right?
[HARUTORA exhales]
[TOUJI sighs]
[TOUJI]
What about Natsume?
[HARUTORA] Same story.
I haven't heard back
from her, either.
I did some research
after that day.
You know about the last ritual
Yakou Tsuchimikado performed?
Yeah.
Of course.
Besides being family history,
it's in our schoolbooks.
Because it failed,
the Great Spirit Disaster
happened in Tokyo,
and so, the Tsuchimikado
family was disgraced.
I don't know the exact
contents of the ritual
or anything, though.
[TOUJI] That's what
she wants to do.
The Taizan Fukun Ritual.
[HARUTORA] Huh.
[TOUJI] Remember?
Crazy girl?
Thanks to Yakou,
the Great Spirit Method
caused a lot of damage.
Recently, there seem to be
more and more onmyo mages
who support him and
believe he wants to complete
the final great magic
working of his life.
They believe he's going
to be reincarnated somehow.
Is that kind of thing
even possible?
I dunno, but crazy girl
certainly thinks so.
Bet she wants to
use the same magic.
Only difference is she wants
to bring back someone else.
Well...
[TOUJI] Heh. There's a rumor
floating around, too.
About Yakou.
They say in preparation
for a future where
his onmyo magic
will take over,
he's already reincarnated
himself as a descendant
from the Tsuchimikado family.
It's Natsume.
I mean, it's gotta be her,
don't you think?
[cell phone buzzes]
[HARUTORA]
I got a text.
Is it Hokuto?
[HARUTORA sighs]
[HARUTORA] No.
[NATSUME] I'm sorry for asking
to meet you so suddenly.
That's all right.
I kinda felt we needed
to talk in person anyway.
[HARUTORA] Could she
be his reincarnation?
I'm so sorry!
[HARUTORA] Huh?
About what you
texted to me earlier.
You were placed
in serious danger,
and it was all because
some horrid person
thought that you were me.
And then you
had to kiss her.
Are you talking about
Suzuka Dairenji?
Wait, I didn't
think you knew her.
[NATSUME]
I don't know her!
Okay. So then why do you
sorta seem to hate her?
Um...
Well, I've just heard that her
character is questionable.
But she is a prodigy,
and the youngest
to ever hold the rank of
Onmyo Mage First Class.
If she ended up
finding me,
I really don't know
what I would do.
[HARUTORA] Did you talk
to your dad about it?
[NATSUME]
Uh--No, I didn't.
He's actually gone to
Tokyo for a little while.
Oh, really?
I didn't know.
He had business there.
That's why I returned home.
[rain falls]
Wouldn't it be better for you
to go back to Tokyo, too?
I can't do that right now.
I have to stay.
The altar for the Taizan
Fukun Ritual is here.
The altar is on a mountain
behind the main house
called "Miyama."
She'll most likely try to
perform the ritual there.
And if that's the case,
then as the next
head of our family,
I've no choice but
to protect the altar.
Okay, but--
How can you do that
when you just said
you didn't know what to do?
This is not a matter
of what I know
or what I can and cannot do.
It is my responsibility.
With my father gone, I'm the
only one who can keep it safe!
[HARUTORA sighs]
Yeah, well, I still think you
should go back to Tokyo.
I will not
abandon the altar.
[HARUTORA] Fine, then
let me protect it.
Let you?
[HARUTORA] Suzuka Dairenji
wants you specifically.
Seems like a bad idea
to be hangin' around.
Look, you said this
is the responsibility
of the Tsuchimikado family,
so I'll do it in your place.
I'm part of the Tsuchimikado
family, too, after all.
Besides, the Onmyo
Agency is on it.
All you have to do is
find somewhere to hide
until that girl's caught.
Then, we won't have
anything to worry about.
Here. I stole these from
my dad's examination room.
Figured they'd come in handy.
Just a bunch of healing
and defense talismans.
[NATSUME] Why?
I don't understand.
Why only care about
the Tsuchimikado name
at a time like this?
Because it is
a time like this.
You know?
[NATSUME chuckles]
And believe me, you don't
have to worry at all.
My luck can suck pretty
hard and everything,
but the worst never happens.
I'll be fine.
Crazy girl is too cocky.
But she can be cute;
I'll give her that.
She can't be all that smart
if she mixed us up, though.
I bet I can talk
some sense into her.
[loud thud]
[NATSUME] Oh, really?
She can be cute?
That must be nice for you.
[HARUTORA shudders]
[NATSUME]
Seems your luck is changing
since your first kiss
was with a cute girl.
No, wait.
She's not cute!
[NATSUME]
I'm going home.
It would be pointless
to talk any longer.
Excuse me.
[HARUTORA]
No, hold on a second!
You think she likes you
so she'll listen to you!
You might as well not
try to help at all
if that's what you're thinking!
Come on. That's not even
what I said, Natsume!
[HARUTORA chokes]
Are you all right?
Harutora, what's wrong?
[HARUTORA chokes]
A familiar?
Natsume? Natsume?
What happened?
My power, it's gone.
The familiar took
my spirit power.
[NATSUME breathes heavily]
[HARUTORA]
It was the kiss.
This is all my fault.
[NATSUME]
She's a Divine General.
You couldn't have known.
It's not your fault.
But it doesn't change the fact
that she has my spiritual power.
She's probably heading
toward the altar, now.
Take me to the main house.
There are magic tools there that
will help give me my power back.
Please, no matter what,
she has to be stopped.
[phone rings]
Bad news, Touji.
[TOUJI] Seriously?
What's going on?
Yeah, that's bad.
We've had some
movement over here.
About an hour ago,
things started getting noisy
by the police station.
Then, those Magical
Investigation Bureau cars
left in a hurry.
Someone figured out
what she was up to.
I'm hoping you have an idea
for what comes next.
Look, man.
You gotta do something.
I'm taking Natsume
back to the main house.
[TOUJI] Sounds good.
But that altar is right
behind there, isn't it?
Be careful that you
don't run into--
[tires screech]
[HARUTORA yells]
[car door opens]
[TOUJI] Harutora?
What happened?
We just ran into her.
Wow, you really do have
some of the worst luck ever.
You need to get
away from there!
[HARUTORA] No.
I'll make sure
Natsume gets home.
And I'm gonna stop
Suzuka somehow.
Come on! You can't
fight her--[click]
[HARUTORA]
As fast as you can.
[rumbling and creaking]
[HARUTORA]
She looks out of it.
I don't know what's got
you distracted, prodigy.
But you won't break
this 8-formation
anti-spirit-disaster
barrier that way.
Surrender now or else!
I detest the countryside.
There are just
far too many bugs.
I have a feeling you'd love
to see Yakou Tsuchimikado's
famous military familiar
up close and personal.
Technique release!
Come now, Tsuchigumo!
[MALE OFFICER 1A] It's an
armored demon soldier!
We'll have to
take him down.
[MALE OFFICER yells]
[FEMALE OFFICER 1A gasps]
[SUZUKA laughs]
Get 'em, boy.
[MAGICAL INVESTIGATORS yell]
[gasps]
[FEMALE OFFICER 1A grunts]
Aahhh!
Aaahhh!
[HARUTORA] Their power.
It's draining them.
[MAGICAL INVESTIGATORS yell]
Harutora.
I wish you knew
how much I love you.
[HARUTORA] Crap.
I gotta get back to Natsume.
[SUZUKA] Soon.
[SUZUKA]
It'll happen very soon.
That's right, big brother.
Not much longer.
[cell phone rings]
[SUZUKA]
Who's there?
[HARUTORA sighs]
[SUZUKA] Oh, it's you.
From yesterday.
Hey, what's up?
Who's calling?
Will they mind being ignored?
[ringing continues]
Oh, yeah.
I can't believe
you kissed me
just so you could plant
that freaky familiar.
What the hell?
Come on.
You should be proud that
you were my first kiss.
We have to admit it was good.
Right, darling?
What happened between
you and that ugly girl?
Did you
two fight?
Yes, we did.
Thanks to your
little performance.
[SUZUKA laughs]
That's what
you get!
She'd never believe
you'd choose her over me.
No use
lying to her!
I was wrong;
you are not cute.
[SUZUKA] Oh, how can you
say that to this face?
It doesn't matter
what you look like,
you're still terrible
on the inside.
So you admit I'm cute, then?
Can't deny it now.
Even if you are, you're
nothing but a criminal.
Look.
I know.
You just want to bring
your brother back.
I um--I'm an only child,
but I think I get what
you're going through.
But--What you're
doing is wrong.
You're hurting innocent people.
How do you think your brother
would feel about that?
Don't pretend like
you know how I feel!
[HARUTORA]
Your parents?
What would they say?
[SUZUKA] Shut up!
Joke's on you.
I don't have any parents.
Those disgusting creatures
were only using us, anyway.
[HARUTORA] Have a little
respect! What's wrong with you?
[SUZUKA] I don't have to!
Why do you think I
could become one of
the Twelve Divine Generals
at such a tender age?
Because ever since I was born,
even before that, they've
been experimenting on me.
More than a few experiments
used forbidden magic.
They went too far
with my big brother
and ended up killing him!
[HARUTORA gasps]
That's why I have to
bring him back home to me.
Now that I've got
the Tsuchimikado power
and a proper offering,
I know the Taizan Fukun
Ritual will work!
[HARUTORA] What do you
mean proper offering?
[SUZUKA]
My life, naturally.
[HARUTORA gasps]
That's correct.
I'll offer up my own life
in return for my brother's.
[HARUTORA]
You have to stop this.
Do you really think this would
make your big brother happy?
Yes, of course it will!
[HARUTORA] He'd have
to lose his sister.
Live knowing her death was his
fault, with no family left.
And why the hell
should I listen to you?
[HARUTORA] Please.
Please, stop this.
There's time.
Think it over again.
Your life is--
it's just beginning.
[MALE OFFICER 1A]
Bind! Order!
[HARUTORA and SUZUKA gasp]
[SUZUKA yells]
No. No one gets in my way!
[roaring]
[HARUTORA]
Stop it!
[HARUTORA gasps]
[HARUTORA] I'm dead.
[squelch]
[HARUTORA gasps]
[HARUTORA]
Hokuto...
No.
[HOKUTO] Ban, un, taraku,
kiriku, aku!
With the Laws of
the Five Elements,
break the walls within me.
Order!
[HARUTORA screams]
[HARUTORA]
Hokuto! Hokuto!
I called, but you didn't
answer your phone.
Stupid-tora.
Hokuto...
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
I hid the truth,
and tricked you.
[HARUTORA] You what?
I don't understand.
What is this?
What's going on?
[HOKUTO]
Harutora...
I love you.
That's all you need to know.
Listen to me.
Run away. Go, now.
If you die out here, I swear
that I'll never forgive you.
How gross.
I can't believe you made your
familiar be your girlfriend.
I'm still shocked
I couldn't tell.
[HARUTORA] Shut up.
Just shut up.
You should see
your face right now.
[SUZUKA] Next time,
I'll kill you, too.
[engine starts]
[HARUTORA] We first met
back in junior high.
[HARUTORA] It was
my first summer here.
I remember she acted a little
strange when she saw me.
[HOKUTO gasps]
[HARUTORA] From that day on,
whenever I turned around,
she always seemed
to be right there.
[HARUTORA] As soon as I saw her,
she'd just run away.
I started chasing after
her as kind of a joke,
and so that's how things went.
[HOKUTO laughs]
[HARUTORA laughs]
[HARUTORA] Then came the last
day of summer vacation.
[HARUTORA breathes heavily]
So I'm Harutora.
And I'm Hokuto!
[giggles]
[HARUTORA] She finally
told me her name.
[door opens]
[HARUTORA breathes heavily]
Natsume, has your spiritual
power come back, yet?
No, it hasn't
returned completely,
but I should have enough
to last the night.
You're still planning to
protect the altar by yourself?
I'm not gonna stop you.
But I need a favor.
Before you go, right now.
Make me your familiar.
[NATSUME gasps]
It's weird.
Going to school and
hanging out with friends.
That's all I ever wanted
out of life, you know?
I don't have talent,
and I'm not a seer.
But I've been so wrong.
I wish I was like you.
I didn't confront
my position at all.
Instead, I ran
away from myself.
[HARUTORA] Someone even
tried to tell me that,
but I wouldn't listen.
[HARUTORA] Please.
Stupid-tora.
You will agree then?
From this day forward,
you offer yourself up
to live as my familiar.
Are you prepared?
[HARUTORA] I am.
I will not hide anymore.
[NATSUME] Good.
Children hide from
what they fear.
And we are not children.
[NATSUME] Harutora.
I take you now and name
you as my familiar.
[NATSUME]
Close your eyes.
And now I,
Natsume Tsuchimikado--
--in the name of the
great Abe no Seimei--
--take you, Harutora
Tsuchimikado, as my familiar.
With this, you are mine.
Forever and always.
Take a look around
now, Harutora.
Can you see it?
[HARUTORA]
See what?
[HARUTORA gasps]
What? No way.
I used my magic
to help give you
the power to see spirits.
I guess it worked.
So what do you think?
[HARUTORA]
A spirit seer.
Amazing.
It's beautiful.
[KON] I'm stewing; I'm stewing;
I'm stewing for 2 more episodes;
I'm stewing; close the lid;
I'm stewing.