♪
What is this for, Dad?
[NATSUME] I was just about
to begin junior high.
That was when dad told me
about the "tradition."
And what was expected of me.
[NATSUME] Soon, visits from
Harutora became less frequent
and he wasn't even
allowed to sleep over!
[YOUNG HARUTORA] Okay.
I'll become your
familiar, Natsume.
[NATSUME] It's silly.
After all, we were just kids.
But the promise he made was the
only thing that kept me going.
[NATSUME]
Happiness and go?
Harutora said he thought
the girl in this ad
was kind of pretty.
♪
[HOKUTO chuckles]
[NATSUME gasps]
[NATSUME] I'm not
trying to brag.
But I did a pretty good job.
[BOTH laugh]
[NATSUME] She was a lovely girl
with a bright and happy smile.
I thought,
if I were somehow able
to reintroduce myself
to Harutora through Hokuto,
it would be a simple way for
me to stay close to him.
[NATSUME] Just like
when we were kids.
♪
[HOKUTO gasps]
[NATSUME] But it didn't work.
I kept trying.
And failing.
Time after time.
[NATSUME] I have
to do something,
the school year
is about to start!
[HARUTORA breathes heavily]
[NATSUME] Then came the last
day of summer vacation.
So, I'm Harutora.
[HOKUTO gasps slowly]
And I'm... Hokuto!
[giggles]
[NATSUME] I was finally
able to talk to him again.
[HARUTORA chuckles]
[phone chimes]
[NATSUME sighs]
[NATSUME] What a
beautiful morning!
This is a perfect day
for fireworks.
♪
[HARUTORA]
Hey, Natsume!
[FEMALE WEATHER PERSON 20A]
With no chance of rain
in the greater Tokyo area,
we're in for a beautiful
summer day!
[HARUTORA]
You coming or what?
[NATSUME]
Sorry, just a second!
[HARUTORA] We're just heading to
the convenience store, you know.
[NATSUME] A girl needs a little
extra time to get ready
before going out.
Mmm.
'Kay. I guess I'll
take your word for it.
[NATSUME] Mm.
[HARUTORA] Hm?
[NATSUME] Is your spirit energy
still pretty unstable?
Yeah, but I do feel
more control.
Well, sort of.
Shaved ice
doesn't change.
Tastes just like it did
back out in the sticks.
I see you got
melon flavor again.
[HARUTORA] Wanna bite?
Aaaaaa...
Uh.
Uh, Harutora?
Yours is spilling!
Aaahh!
[NATSUME] Here.
Thanks. Sorry.
♪
[NATSUME] Maybe now.
This might be the
perfect time to tell him
the truth about Hokuto.
[HARUTORA] Natsume.
Yes?
I'm just going to go
and wash up real quick.
[NATSUME sighs]
[KAKUGYOUKI]
Something's wrong.
The kid's cursed.
What's going on?
The Onmyo Agency has
the Raven Coat now.
[SUZU] What'll you do?
What will be, will be.
[SUZU] I know it's
gnawing at you.
Besides. What should be
may not even happen.
Things are...
getting bad.
And what does that mean?
It's something you
should see for yourself.
[NATSUME] Excuse me?
The effect of the curse
was only halfway undone.
[NATSUME gasps]
They have the Coat now.
It can't be worn yet,
or it might kill.
What is that
supposed to mean?
When things start
to get rough,
seek out Suzu Saotome.
Though she won't
move aggressively.
One arm missing?
That means you're...!
[KURAHASHI] I have
received confirmation
from the Meguro Branch.
It would seem that
Natsume Tsuchimikado
is most definitely female.
[YASHAMARU laughs]
[YASHAMARU] So then everything
we know about the situation
has been turned on its head.
[TAKIKO grunts lightly]
Very crafty, Yasuzumi.
He read it in the
stars decades ago.
"A child from your own
bloodline will one day
be the reincarnation
of the great Yakou."
I was there.
At his home when
the child was born.
Even if that were
the case, Chief,
I don't understand
why you're panicking.
So it turns out Natsume
Tsuchimikado is a girl.
That doesn't change
my outlook at all.
[KURAHASHI]
Well, it should.
The child born
that day was a boy.
[TAKIKO gasps]
[YASHAMARU] Hm?
It was my mother
who told me.
She saw it with her own eyes.
When Yuuko Wakasugi
was pregnant,
the child within
her womb clearly had
the male "yang" spirit.
[YASHAMARU] Of course.
So this tradition of
dressing like a boy
was simply meant to
act as camouflage;
another way to trick us.
How terribly embarrassing!
All these seasoned
Onmyo mages being fooled
by a simple,
second-rate incantation.
[YASHAMARU laughs]
Not too shabby,
Yasuzumi old boy!
Chief Dairenji.
You say it's just
a simple spell.
But I think you're
over-simplifying
the matter, sir.
That magic had a cost.
And the price of this
trickery was paid for
with the life of a young child.
[YASHAMARU] But he
was able to stall us
for over a decade
with that spell.
Sounds like a success!
But it was wrong!
[TAKIKIO] Why?
Why did Yasuzumi
Tsuchimikado do such a thing?
[KURAHASHI] I don't believe
he did it with cruel intent.
However, one
thing is apparent.
He has no wish for
the slumbering Yakou
to be resurrected.
So you're saying that's
the reason he set up a fake?
And sacrificed Natsume?
That is correct.
[door opens, closes]
[YASHAMARU]
That's excellent.
Simply excellent!
Kumomaru, I'll leave
the princess to you.
Right.
Well then.
What's eating at you?
[MUTOBE] Princess?
[TAKIKO] The time has come
for me to take action.
It'll be for their own good.
[MUTOBE] Whose?
[TAKIKO] You must have
noticed him as well.
I thought it was merely
a coincidence.
But he reacted to
the curse I cast.
I plan to break Yasuzumi
Tsuchimikado's spell.
And then I will awaken Harutora.
[FESTIVAL CROWD chatters]
[TOUJI]
One armed man?
But how can we be sure
he's the real deal?
Well, if we take his talk
about the Raven Coat
and add it to him
specifically mentioning
Suzu Saotome by name.
And then you subtract one arm.
My money says
he's Kakugyouki.
[TOUJI] Hmmm.
Lemme guess.
Even with all that going on,
he was clueless.
Yo, Touji dude!
Where are we
supposed to meet up?
[TOUJI]
How about over here?
[NATSUME gasps]
[NATSUME]
Oh. Thank you.
It's crowded and we don't
want to get separated so.
Geez.
Get a room, you guys.
Uh! Hey wait, hold up!
[HARUTORA]
With all that's happened,
there's plenty of stuff for us
to have to worry about, right?
That's why I think
the whole gang,
you, me, Touji, Kyoko,
Tenma and Suzuka:
we all deserve a day off.
Let's unwind! Agreed?
Yes!
Harutora,
thank you for this.
[HARUTORA chuckles]
[TENMA] Hey!
We're over here you guys!
You're late!
The sun has already
begun to set ya jerks!
Now, now.
[KYOKO] Looks like
everyone's here, finally.
[TOUJI] Damn.
Wow, you look really nice!
Of course I do.
Stupid-tora.
Are you going to tell him?
You made a promise.
Oh. Yes.
[KYOKO giggles]
[giggling]
Come on, losers!
Stop running;
you might fall down!
[SUZUKA]
Get it in gear, slowpoke!
[HARUTORA] What's that
you're drinking?
[TOUJI belches]
Vending machine beer, Broseph.
[KYOKO] Hey, Natsume.
Since it's just us today,
is it okay if I treat
you like another girl?
[NATSUME] What?
Uh, sure. I don't think
it'll be a problem here.
[KYOKO] Yes! Now we can
finally talk about boys
and dish on the other
girls we don't like!
[NATSUME] Seriously?
[KYOKO]
You don't wanna?
[NATSUME] No.
Yes. That's not it.
Listen, Kyoko. Thanks.
[KYOKO] Mm-hm.
[NATSUME and KYOKO laughing]
Yes! It's starting,
it's starting!
Hey, watch out, Suzuka.
Be careful!
[GROUP gasps and laughs]
This is nice.
All of us together.
Totally, man.
It's so pretty.
Uh--Yeah?
What's up?
Hey. Would you go buy
some drinks for us?
[HARUTORA] For real?
Ramune for me.
I want Cola!
I'll have another
refreshing barley drink.
Make mine
an oolong tea.
Ah, not you too.
Okay, fine, I'll go, jeez!
[KYOKO]
And Natsume can help.
Can't you?
[NATSUME] Uh!
I could use
the extra hands.
Sure. Then I'll go
with you, I guess.
[KYOKO chuckles]
[HARUTORA] Right on.
Thank you.
[KYOKO chuckles]
Oh wait I'd forgotten
all about her.
Takiko is running really late.
[NATSUME] I'm glad.
[HARUTORA] Huh?
[NATSUME] I'm glad we all
came to see the fireworks.
No, there's much more
to it than the fireworks.
I'm really happy you
came here to Tokyo.
And we've made so
many good friends.
Everything just
fits perfectly.
You're right.
[NATSUME] It was all worth my
working extra hard last summer!
[HARUTORA] Oh yeah?
What was it that had
you working hard?
[NATSUME] Um, well.
The wishing plaque.
[HARUTORA] The what?
[HARUTORA gasps]
Natsume... are you...?
[NATSUME exhales shakily]
This is awkward.
[NATSUME] It was me.
[NATSUME] I didn't know
how to tell you.
[HARUTORA] Hokuto?
[TAKIKO] I found you.
[HARUTORA] Takiko?
Harutora, believe me.
What I'm about to do...
I'm doing it for
the sake of humanity.
[NATSUME] Takiko?
[TAKIKO] Natsume.
You have my sympathies.
And once Harutora is awakened,
I'm sure you and I will
become comrades as well.
[HARUTORA]
Can somebody clue me in?
My words seem
to fall short.
Please forgive me.
[TAKIKO] Right after
the two of you were born.
You were made
prisoners of a curse!
[HARUTORA grunts]
[NATSUME gasps]
[TAKIKO]
Yasuzumi Tsuchimikado.
I will free them.
I swear it.
Master Harutora!
Please stand back!
[TAKIKO]
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
Order.
[HARUTORA groans]
[NATSUME] Harutora!
[TAKIKO] Crashing wave.
And sacred chime.
Crashing wave.
[gasps] The ritual...
[HARUTORA screams]
Stop it!
You'll kill him!
[HARUTORA groans]
Ahh!
[KON groans]
[KON] Natsume. Hurry!
Use a talisman. Quickly.
You must not interfere.
[NATSUME]
Move aside, now!
Order!
[NATSUME gasps]
[MUTOBE] Please, stop.
I have no desire to harm you.
I summon forth Hokuto!
[NATSUME breathing heavily]
[HOKUTO roars]
Namu, Hachiman
Great Bodhisattva.
Please stop them!
[TOUJI grunting]
[yells]
Really?
[TAKIKO] Decades ago,
the father of the Souma clan
gave an oath of
allegiance to Yakou.
We hoped to achieve
his long-held dream.
This dream was
broken but once.
And we refused to give up.
As heir to the Souma legacy,
[TAKIKO] I will carry
out the mission myself.
What mission?
Yeah, what mission?
[HARUTORA groans]
[TAKIKO] Natsume.
You are simply a substitute.
Harutora is actually the
child of the main house.
Yasuzumi Tsuchimikado's
real son.
What're you talking about?
[TAKIKO] Not only did he
abandon the sacred duties
of the Tsuchimikados.
The fool placed a curse
on the reincarnation
of his great ancestor
to misdirect us.
Harutora Tsuchimikado.
You are the
reincarnation of Yakou!
[NATSUME gasps]
[HARUTORA groans]
[TAKIKO] I will release
you from that spell.
I promise you.
As the descendant
of Yakou's sworn ally.
[TAKIKO] Go, Raven Coat.
Go to your master!
[NATSUME]
The Divine Crow!
[HARUTORA yells]
You've got to stop this!
[TAKIKO] What?
His energy won't settle down.
[TAKIKO] Was Yasuzumi hiding
another trick up his sleeve?
The Raven Coat isn't
actually a coat?
Who would've guessed it
was really a familiar?
[SUZUKA] Don't you dare
possess my darling idiot!
[HARUTORA grunting]
[HARUTORA yells]
[NATSUME gasps]
[NATSUME]
Harutora, no!
It can't be worn yet.
Or it might kill.
Hokuto!
[NATSUME]
After him, Yukikaze!
[HARUTORA yells]
[HARUTORA grunts]
♪
He's fading.
[HARUTORA] Natsume.
Stay with me!
I can't control it.
Go! Now!
[SUZUKA] Order!
Stop spacing out!
[TOUJI] Natsume!
Use Hokuto!
Hokuto!
[TOUJI] Harutora!
Open your damn eyes!
[SUZUKA] Stop it, moron!
What are you doing?
[NATSUME] Harutora, you've got
to get a hold of yourself!
[HARUTORA groans]
[SUZUKA] Bind him!
Om, bishi bishi kara kara
shibari sowaka!
[HARUTORA yelling]
Damn it!
None of our attacks seem
to be doing anything!
[NATSUME] What should I do?
Think, Natsume, think!
I'm the substitute.
And Harutora is the heir
to the main family.
Something's wrong.
The kid's cursed.
[OHTOMO] There's
something unnatural
about your current condition.
All I can say is that it
feels strangely artificial.
[NATSUME] Artificial.
Could he have meant the curse?
The fool placed a curse
on the reincarnation
of his great ancestor
to misdirect us.
[NATSUME] A curse.
A spell cast right
after his birth.
Something to prevent people
from noticing that
Harutora was really
Yakou's reincarnation.
[NATSUME gasps]
It always struck me as odd.
Even though he was part of
the Tsuchimikado bloodline,
he didn't have the basic
talent to be a spirit seer.
Harutora, who has such
an abundance of power!
What? Oh, this?
Natsume used it to
make me a spirit seer.
The effect of the curse
was halfway undone.
[NATSUME]
We were all fooled!
Harutora has always
been a spirit seer!
Dad just sealed his power away.
The ceremony we held didn't turn
Harutora into a spirit seer.
It simply broke part of the seal
Dad had already placed.
And now he's
suffering because
I only undid
Dad's spell halfway.
[HARUTORA groans]
[NATSUME] If that's the case,
then I should finish the job.
But how?
Haa!
Now, in the name
of Abe no Seimei.
Aaaahhh!
♪
[YUKIKAZE neighs]
[yells]
[NATSUME gasps]
[NATSUME]
Harutora Tsuchimikado.
As your master...
Natsume!
I free you...
from all your seals!
[HARUTORA] Huh?
[intense music plays]
[HARUTORA] Natsume?
Natsume, no.
Harutora, I'm sorry I...
...never told you
'bout Hokuto.
[coughs]
[NATSUME] I tricked you.
And I'm sorry.
But then...
You--You already knew
that, didn't you?
Stop it.
[NATSUME] Harutora.
Stop it!
[NATSUME] Listen.
Harutora...
I love you.
Promise me something.
Promise you won't die, okay?
Huh?
Natsume?
No. Please don't go.
Don't leave me!
Natsume! Natsume!
Come on. Please, wake up!
[HARUTORA]
Natsume! It isn't fair!
You can't go!
Natsume!
[HARUTORA screams]
[NATSUME] Stupid-tora.
I hadn't seen him in so long,
and all he says is,
"not cute at all."
I'll make that
jerk say I'm cute
when he sees me
tonight in my yukata!
But, if Harutora
sees this ribbon,
he's definitely going
to notice, right?
What will he say?
[HARUTORA]
Natsume. Natsume!
[NATSUME gasps] He's here!
I can hear him
calling my name.
[NATSUME] Even though
Harutora is my familiar.
Sometimes it seems as though
he's too busy playing around.
But at least he always
looks like he's having fun.
[HARUTORA] Natsume!
Natsume!
[NATSUME] Like he doesn't
have a care in the world.
Taking it easy
for the rest of us.
[YOUNG HARUTORA]
Hey, Natsume!
Let's go play!
[NATSUME]
It feels right.
I was finally able to
tell him that I love him.
I'm proud of you.
Oh, thank you. Heh.
[NATSUME]
Well, it made me nervous.
But I wish I could have
heard Harutora's answer.
I wonder what
he would've said.