[TENMA] Morning, guys!
[KYOKO] Hello, Natsume!
[TENMA] Well, we've
survived half our exams.
You guys ready for the next one?
[HARUTORA] ...which
invariably supersedes use
of a 2nd class general
purpose familiar...
[KYOKO] I take it
you studied all night?
Natsume's training
schedule leaves no time
for catching any Z's.
Listen, you're not gonna
be held back a year.
We'll do a last review
before your next attempt.
[HARUTORA] But I think my
brain's running out of storage.
[NATSUME] Oh? You've memorized
enough to ace this test?
[HARUTORA]
Well... Maybe not.
If you get s-stumped trying
to th-think of an answer,
remember
I'm by your side!
Oh, yeah! Good call.
[TENMA] But that
would be cheating.
[KYOKO] You'd get held
back if they caught you.
[NATSUME] You moron! Don't you
dare stain the family name!
Chill out, I was just joking.
[NATSUME] If there's room for
'jokes' in that skull of yours,
we can knowledge-cram Pre-exam!
[HARUTORA] Sure, sure.
Whatever you say...
[NATSUME] Stupid-tora!
It's time to knuckle down!
[KON] Stupid-tora?
That's so rude!
[HARUTORA] C'mon,
we're gonna be late.
[NATSUME] Just concentrate!
[HARUTORA] I know,
stop worrying!
Hey, man. What is it?
Nothing.
[TOUJI] Six months
sped by so fast...
♪
[PROCTOR] Pens down! Pass
your papers forward, please.
So. How'd it go?
This blows.
I'm gonna fail.
Not yet! You can
pass the practicum!
Now's our chance!
[KON] Haaaa!
Gotcha!
[NATSUME] All right!
[TENMA] You've learned
a ton in six months.
Just look how much you've
improved, Harutora!
Master!
You were magnificent!
Well, I couldn't have done it
without your flawless timing!
[KON] It's an honor
and a privilege!
I don't deserve such
generous praise!
Under normal conditions,
my familiars
work as a pair, y'know.
You were victorious, Master.
Listening to a sore loser
like her is below a
man of your station.
I heard that, you rat!
[KON] Heard what?
You must be overtired.
Natsume! Looks like
I've got a chance
at passing this thing after all!
[NATSUME] Yeah? Well,
you rely far too much
on the staff to
convert magic for you!
The practical prohibits
the use of magic tools.
Talk about a buzzkill.
[TENMA] You didn't let any of
that stop you
from cheering for his victory.
Fine, I cheered.
But that's only because
I was caught up in the moment--
Never mind! Listen up!
Before tomorrow's
practical exam,
we're gonna drill your
magic-handling skills, got it?
[HARUTORA] Your momma's
gonna drill some magic skills.
Burn. Am I right?
Where's Touji?
[TENMA]
He's with the principal.
[TOUJI] Purification
of a spirit disaster?
Correct. It's a fine test of
skill for our practical exam.
You and your classmates
will be tasked with
quelling a simulated
spirit disaster.
[TOUJI] Why're you
telling me this?
[MIYO] Because you have
a handicap when it comes
to this type of testing.
Two years ago, you fell
victim to the spirit disaster
and have since struggled
with its aftereffects.
We have, of course, thoroughly
discussed the implications
of your exam with your
doctor, Harutora's father.
By the way, he's another
graduate of our fine school.
[TOUJI] Look, I
appreciate your concern,
but I don't need any sympathy.
[MIYO] Hm. That wasn't
my intent, I assure you.
[TOUJI] Sorry.
Sensitive subject.
When someone reminds
me I'm a spirit disaster victim,
I tend to get a
little bit annoyed.
Didn't mean to snap.
Thanks for the heads up.
I'll try to be careful.
[MIYO chuckles lightly]
[MUTOBE] I am
in your debt, sir.
[DOMAN] All I did was
prepare the pieces, my boy.
Still, seems like such a waste.
You don't plan to
survive this, do you?
I suppose it doesn't matter.
The show must go on.
[MUTOBE] The time has come.
Farewell, Doman.
Chief Dairenji.
Please watch over me now.
[HARUTORA] Hang on!
You can't be serious!
[NATSUME] I am! You're not
sleeping tonight. Sorry!
[laughter]
[HARUTORA] But that's not fair!
[MUTOBE] King of
the North Star...
[HARUTORA] Have a heart!
[MUTOBE] I pledge
my soul to you.
[MUTOBE] That boy...
[OHTOMO] Sir, I don't
think the taxpaying public
would approve of our meeting
in a place like this.
Take it easy, it's not
like that at all!
I paid for everything myself.
Tell me. Is Miyo as
stubborn as ever?
[OHTOMO] Principal Kurahashi?
She's quite the taskmaster.
[AMAMI laughs]
She may look sweet, but she's
not beyond using people.
[OHTOMO] MIB'S gotten some
negative press lately.
[AMAMI] If we worried about
what other people thought,
we'd never get anything done!
Well? Why did you call for me?
I already turned in my
resignation, Director Amami.
I don't work for you anymore.
[AMAMI] I crumpled it up
and threw it away. You don't
honestly think a little scrap of
paper makes us even, do you?
[OHTOMO] Incorrigible.
So? Who're you hiding?
Oh, him? That one's our
new hope. Atsune Hirata.
Current director of our Twin
Horn Syndicate investigation.
Long story short,
he's your successor.
It's nice to meet you,
Mister Ohtomo.
I've heard quite
a lot about you.
And most of it
unflattering, I'd wager.
[HIRATA] Right hand man of
our current Divine General
"Divine Fan" Daizen Amami
and former member of the
Twelve Divine Generals,
Jin Ohtomo.
AKA "Shadow."
I am honored to make
your acquaintance, sir.
[AMAMI] The kid's a natural!
Honest! Figured
it out himself!
I told him to keep a lid on it,
so stop worrying.
[HIRATA] If I may...
[HARUTORA sighs]
I can't remember
when I last ate.
You've worked hard,
so enjoy it, Master.
Thanks for the grub!
Eh... Uh?
[NATSUME] I'd love to know
what you think you're doing.
There are things you should
be filling your brain with.
Which means there's
no time for you
to bother with
filling your stomach.
What? You're a monster.
[KON] How dare you interrupt
my master's meal?!
Even from you,
it's unforgivable!
[NATSUME] Have you forgotten?
I'm his master!
[KON] And I'm telling you,
it's unpardonable!
[NATSUME] Everyone else
has gone without food or rest.
I haven't eaten a thing!
[KON] Well then, that makes
two of us suffering!
[NATSUME] Don't even! I'm
working way harder than you!
[KON] You can't be serious!
[NATSUME] You bet I am!
[KON] That's it!...
[HARUTORA] What is he doing?
[HIRATA] Two years have passed
since the terrorist attack.
The Great Purification spirit
disaster was perpetrated
by the Twin Horn Syndicate under
the guise of the Ghost Division.
[HIRATA] Their former organizer,
Shido Dairenji, is deceased.
The Ghost Division disbanded.
However, the Twin Horn Syndicate
still maintains a presence.
Terrorist scum. They're too
cowardly to show their faces.
[HIRATA] Of course, I'm sure
you knew this already.
Right, "Shadow"?
Look, kid. You've really gotta
stop calling me "Shadow."
I resigned from that
job, kay? I'm just
a regular old schoolteacher
these days, that's all.
[AMAMI] A schoolteacher
with whom I'd like
to conduct business.
If I'm not mistaken,
you have a student
named Tsuchimikado.
Well, well. I never
would have thought
you'd take teaching
so seriously, Ohtomo.
I take it very seriously.
Especially after cleaning up
the sizable mess you
made six months ago.
Don't I know!
Miyo gave me all kinds of
hell after that incident.
You're barking
up the wrong tree.
I'm finished with
that kind of work.
We're short-handed,
to be frank.
We have Kogure
working nonstop as it is.
[OHTOMO] Perfect.
He's very capable.
He should be, he's a
former classmate of yours.
And you might be
interested to know,
the work Kogure's done for us
has kept Kagami on the bench.
[OHTOMO] Is that so?
The Principal's son
is the head of the Exorcism
Bureau now, correct?
So tell me.
Has he discovered
some new way to tame that
self-absorbed little brat?
Consider the vitriolic little
S.O.B. chained and collared.
But I know better than to remove
the fangs of a guard dog.
Look. Why don't you just tell
me why you called me here?
I'd rather we cut to the
chase and save some time.
The Twin Horn Syndicate
is planning something new.
Something big.
Wait, do you mean he's back?
[HIRATA] There's no doubt it
was D. He was recently spotted
in the area, contacting a member
of the Twin Horn Syndicate.
His contact was Chihiro
Mutobe, a mage formerly with
the Ghost Division, and right
hand man to Shido Dairenji.
[MIYO] To put it bluntly, I have
a hard time reading your stars.
That's due to
the aftereffects.
And I'm afraid all I can see
is overwhelming confusion
awaiting you in
the future, Touji.
I cannot offer you
any help directly.
But I can teach you
to marshal your energy
so that you may master it
when the time comes.
My sincere hope is that
doing so gives you
a chance to live life
on your own terms.
[TOUJI]
That's nice and all.
But as far as
living my life goes,
it's not like I'm making any
long-term plans or anything.
Not now. That's fair.
Please think about
what I shared with you.
After all, it's not smart to
limit any future possibilities.
Future possibilities.
Right. What are those?
[door opens]
[HARUTORA] Yo!
Hey, what's up?
[HARUTORA] What're you
doing up here alone, man?
You look all broody. You wanna
cigarette or something?
I have a no-smoking policy,
Your Dweebness.
[HARUTORA] So what?
You can't sleep?
[TOUJI] I could ask
the same of you.
Is Natsume's special
training finished?
[HARUTORA]
Yeah. Sort of.
[NATSUME] Waffles...
[HARUTORA] I can't believe
tomorrow's practical
is a spirit disaster
purification.
[TOUJI] No biggie.
It's just a simulation.
With the whole class involved,
it shouldn't be that hard.
[HARUTORA] And Natsume
only has to watch.
She lucked out.
[TOUJI] That just means
they don't think she needs
to prove anything. The school
works on a merit system.
[HARUTORA] Yeah,
I guess the test is just
for the normal losers
like us, huh?
Wow. We are so not in
the country anymore.
For real.
So how bout it, man?
Anything new with you?
[TOUJI] Same as you.
No. You know
what I'm asking.
What, the aftereffects?
[HARUTORA] Yeah.
I don't have anything
new to report, sir.
Just the same crap as before.
Except now I'm more aware
of spirit energy, I guess.
So, what? Does that mean
you can control it now?
[TOUJI] Probably.
I know you're worried
about what it'll turn into,
but there's no need for that.
Your father's treatment
is working out perfectly.
And I'll be careful.
[HARUTORA] Of course.
[TOUJI] After all, it's your
job to go overboard.
Yeah, I excel at taking things
a little too far, don't I?
At least you're aware of it.
That saves us some time.
Yeah? Your momma's
aware, bro.
[TOUJI and HARUTORA laugh]
Peace. I'm out.
Cool.
[HARUTORA] Hey, dude. Let's kick
that test's butt tomorrow!
That's a pretty good idea if
you don't wanna get held back.
Right!
No pressure, huh?
I'll worry about it
after I wake up.
[door opens and closes]
Seriously.
Like father, like son.
I get check ups from both
of them like clockwork.
[FUJIHARA] And now
we will commence
with the practical exam.
[STUDENTS] Yes, sir!
[KYOKO] Good. Hang on!
Just a bit longer!
Oh, man.
Don't freak out on me now.
Take a deep breath.
Or not. Is it the breathing
that's making you sick?
Master! Give the word, and
I'll do whatever you need!
No, I can do it!
Get a hold of yourselves!
Let's take our time and make
sure this gets done correctly
or what's the point, right?
How are you doing
over there, Touji?
I'm fine. No problems here.
I'm in complete control.
[HARUTORA]
Rin! Pyo! Tou! Sha!
[FEMALE STUDENT 7A]
You're being too forceful!
Kai!
[FEMALE STUDENT 7B]
Now it's too weak!
Jin!
Would you stabilize
your output already?
[HARUTORA]
Hey! It's not my fault!
I never volunteered for
the tic-tac-toe mantra job!
Sir! Please let me in,
they need me!
No. This is the best way
for them to realize
how much power they are
capable of wielding.
[HARUTORA] That's not
fair and you know it!
[FEMALE STUDENT 7B]
This is strange!
[FEMALE STUDENT 7C] The spirit
energy's getting stronger.
[STUDENTS scream]
[KYOKO] Everyone strengthen
the barrier! We must contain it!
[MALE PROCTOR 7A] Barrier group,
maintain present conditions!
[MALE PROCTOR 7B]
Purification group,
retreat behind
the barrier, now!
Well done.
Hold on a bit longer.
[KYOKO] Yes, sir!
[FUJIHARA] Tenma, contact
the Exorcism Bureau's
emergency call center at once!
[TENMA] Right!
[KYOKO] Touji!
What's wrong?
Touji?
[FUJIHARA] Not now!
Maintain your focus!
[HARUTORA] On it!
What's wrong with you, man?
[TOUJI] Hands off!
[TOUJI grunts]
I don't... need your help!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 7A]
A spirit disaster
has just broken out in Shibuya!
[MALE OPERATOR 7A] Sightings
in Shinagawa and Akihabara!
Spirit Pulses are popping
up all over the city.
Sighting reported in Ueno!
Confirmed dynamic
spirit pattern.
It's a Chimera type! A Nue!
[MIYACHI] Akihabara and Ueno.
Shinagawa and Shibuya.
All the major
Demon Gates in Tokyo.
This is precisely what
happened two years ago, sir!
Do you think it's
a terrorist attack?
[NUE roars]
[STUDENTS scream]
Watch out!
I can't hold it
for much longer!
[TOUJI grunts]
That cannot be good.
Hokuto! Come forth!
I command you to expel
the vile miasma
of the shadows!
[KON squeals]
[KYOKO screams]
Quite a grand entrance from
the Tsuchimikado guardian.
Very impressive,
to say the least.
Is everyone okay?
Nobody was hurt?
Good work. We're all alive,
thanks to you.
But maybe dial it
back some next time?
[TOUJI] No!
You okay, Touji?
Guys, you gotta get everybody
away from here, okay?
Right now! Go!
There's not much time!
[TOUJI screams]
Touji!
[KON] Master Harutora!
[HARUTORA gasps]
[NUE roars]
A phase three Nue? Oh, no!
[grunting and bracing]
[FUJIHARA] Order!
I'll act as a decoy! Evacuate
the students immediately!
But sir!
Just do it! Otherwise,
we're all gonna die!
[HARUTORA]
Natsume?
Yeah, I'm on it. Hokuto!
Come on!
Harutora. Just leave me
here, you stubborn idiot.
Not gonna happen, buddy.
He's feverish.
We need to hurry.
Kon! I need your
help over here!
Kon?
[KON] Master Harutora.
The Nue has been wounded.
It's afraid of something.
[HARUTORA] It is?
[KAGAMI] Well, well.
Looks like my quarry
interrupted a field trip.
Badass! Is that a
freakin' dragon?
[MALE PROCTOR 7B]
This doesn't look good.
[FUJIHARA]
It's the Ogre Eater.
[KAGAMI] Hey there, Pops!
I don't like it when people
call me that, capiche?
Use my real name.
It's Reiji Kagami.
And have some respect when
you talk to a Divine General.
Or you might end up hurt.
Guy's a total sociopath.
[MUTOBE] It can't be!
The Nue led him right to
the King of the North Star.
[FUJIHARA] Hey!
Don't provoke that thing!
[NUE roars]
[STUDENTS chatter]
Not this again. Shut up.
He used a high-grade spell!
Who the heck is this guy?
Un!
Now where do you
think you're going?
Runner on first makes a
break for second base,
but can he make it? Or will he
get tagged in the rundown?
Incredible!
Such power!
[FUJIHARA] Kurahashi!
Mr. Kagami! We need to get
the civilians to safety!
Kurahashi? You guys're
from Onmyo Prep.
That makes you the
Bureau Chief's daughter.
So, our dragon friend here
is with a Tsuchimikado.
Which means one of
you is allegedly--
and I can't stress
that word enough--
the reincarnation
of Yakou.
[KAGAMI] You.
Aw, damn it!
[FUJIHARA] Kagami!
Stay away from them!
[KAGAMI] Freeze, Gramps.
[KAGAMI] Hmm. You look
like the textbook example
of a rich little brat.
It is you, isn't it?
Tsuchimikado?
[NATSUME] That's right.
What's your name?
It's... My name is Natsume.
Wanna know
what I heard?
Rumor has it you beat up that
Lolita-Goth Dairenji chick.
She may be the weakest of
the Divine Generals, but hey!
That's still a victory
you should be proud of.
And I'd like it even better
if you were, y'know?
Because every time
a brat tries to look cool,
it makes them infinitely
more fun to mess with!
[NATSUME grunts]
[NUE roars]
Natsume!
[HARUTORA] A speed mantra! Wow!
No incantations or anything!
Well, maybe we
deal with him first.
Try using your dragon
to purify this thing.
[KAGAMI] Kid. Don't you
have a real live dragon?
Why be afraid of a little Nue?
[NATSUME] How dare you call
yourself an exorcist?
What?
[NATSUME] What exorcist
would screw around
during a spirit disaster?!
[KAGAMI] Hah!
[footsteps]
That's great. You're really
playing to my sympathies.
How motivational!
[HARUTORA] Get your damn hands
off him, you scar-headed freak!
Moron!
And who's this?
Harutora Tsuchimikado.
Son of a branch family!
From a branch family, huh?
[KAGAMI] Hehe... That's
really great, kid!
On gozu deiba suigan
zuiki enmei sowaka.
[screaming and chatter]
[HARUTORA] Huh?
[NUE roars]
Huh. Looks like the
miasma restored that ape.
It's riding the spirit pulse?
[TOUJI groans]
[HARUTORA] Touji!
C'mon, man! Wake up!
What, two spirit disasters?
That's no Nue.
Look at that energy, though.
Seems like there's
something stuck to the barely
conscious kid there. Ha!
[KAGAMI] You guys are a
blast to hang out with.
Seriously, I mean it!
No, leave him alone!
Yeah, that one
hurt a bit.
[KAGAMI chuckles]
Oh, right.
[KAGAMI laughs]
What a fine half-ogre
specimen you are!
Just a tiny step away
from being complete.
[KAGAMI laughs]
♪
[KON] You're a blast.
Seriously, I mean it.