[SUZUKA] Hey, Four-Eyes.
What about you?
Care to join us?
There's just gotta
be a better way.
[SUZU] You're late.
[TENMA gasps]
Hello, my name
is Suzu Saotome.
Tenma Momoe, you are the key.
I'm counting on you.
So please don't
screw this up.
[TENMA] Excuse me; my older
brother, Kenichi Fujiwara,
is in the general
affairs division.
I brought him a
change of clothes.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, come on in.
I'm really sorry about
having to do this,
Mister Fujiwara's nephew.
[SUZU] You're planning
to sneak into Onmyo.
What? How did
you know that?!
Obviously because I'm smart
and mostly know everything.
The agency already has
their eye on your friends.
Touji, Kyoko,
and Suzuka Dairenji.
So, it is too late for them
to turn the situation around.
That's true for Ohtomo
and the Tsuchimikados,
as well as myself.
Pardon me, where's the research
and development division?
[SUZU] The Onmyo Agency is not,
however, watching you.
Because you are far
beneath their notice.
Think of it this way.
It's as if you have
the power to cast
a very strong
invisibility spell.
Even the walls of a great
castle will come crashing down
if the cornerstone is removed.
Depending upon the situation,
even a small pebble on the side
of the road can be a weapon.
You're a pebble.
Understand?
You can do this, Tenma.
I am going to aim and
fire you on the enemy now.
Smash that
cornerstone for me.
Take the Onmyo Agency down.
Oh, and if you fail,
I'll make sure
you never have kids.
[TENMA whimpers]
[TENMA] The entrance
is right there.
It's out in the open.
[TENMA gasps]
[TENMA]
A trick spider?
That was one of
Mom's inventions.
But only two of 'em
were ever made.
Why is it here?
Hey, Mom, can I have
this spider, can I, please?
No, sweetie.
There's someone else who
thinks that trick spider
is pretty interesting, too,
and he already has dibs on it.
Aw.
"With this, I can peep
on whomever I want
whenever I want! Ha ha ha!"
That's what he said.
He was a strange old man.
It can't be.
[rumble]
[EMPLOYEES scream]
[MALE EMPLOYEE 23B]
Evacuate! Evacuate!
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 23A yelling]
[EMPLOYEES yelling]
[TENMA gasps]
[DOMANS cackle]
[whimpers]
It's Doman Ashiya!
But why?
[DOMANS groan]
I've gotta find a way
to get over there.
[DOMANS chuckling intensely]
Someone's put up
a magical barrier.
[TENMA] But it doesn't look
like it'll last long.
[TENMA sighs]
Om, mari shiei sowaka.
Om yamari shi sowaka.
Becoming a
professional mage
requires more
than raw talent.
Try to envision Onmyo magic
as a grand tapestry, in which
the sum total of each mage's
talents acts as a single thread.
Like the skills of
your departed parents.
[TENMA] Om yamari shi sowaka.
Om yamari shi sowaka.
[DOMANS cackle]
Om yamari shi sowaka...
[TENMA] I may be dull
and boring and useless,
but that's the only reason
I could get this far.
With magic, depending
on how it's used,
this can be a weapon, too.
[TENMA] Om yamari shi sowaka.
[TENMA] The trick to the
invisibility spell is to
erase consciousness of self.
I always thought that
meant to empty your mind.
But that's not it.
You're supposed to look
at yourself objectively
and accept yourself honestly.
I accept it.
I am inferior to
others around me.
Is that why people
unconsciously look down on me,
are weirdly nice, or just
ignore me altogether?
Whatever the case, they lower
their guard around me.
I can sneak in through
the opening that creates.
[TENMA] Om yamari shi sowaka.
Om yamari shi sowaka...
[DOMANS yell]
♪
[MIYACHI reciting spell]
[DOMAN laughs]
[DOMAN] Wow, that was
terrifying, wasn't it?
Congratulations; that
level of Buddhist magic
looks like it rivals
the Grand Master's.
[MIYACHI] I appreciate
the compliment,
but even when I'm
feeling arrogant,
the most I would offer is
that I'm a spell artisan.
[DOMAN] I see.
You are very skillful, but why
just keep using the fire mantra?
You do know other
spells, don't you?
[MIYACHI] Unfortunately,
the only thing I have
worthy to show you is
this particular spell.
If you ask me, you exorcist
lot completely lack flair,
which gets rather tedious
after a while, you know.
My new buddy is so
much more fun than you.
Wow, it seems as
though you have taken
quite a liking
to Shadow, Master.
[DOMAN] Oh yes, I must
say that Jin Ohtomo
is a pretty fine fellow!
No offence, but
compared to him,
you're practically a sedative.
You're going to have
to do better than this.
Or else, you'll
never get my number.
That would be
disappointing.
I'll try harder, then.
[DOMANS yell]
Om bishi bishi kara
kara shibari sowaka.
[KAGAMI] With the green of these
leaves from a bamboo tree,
with their withering goes
the withering of the green.
And with the ebb and
flow of these tides,
ebb and flow, ebb and flow!
And with the sinking of this
rock, be engulfed, be engulfed!
Have a taste of
your own medicine.
And tell me how you like it!
Blah-blah, order.
[KAGAMI] Heh.
Not that I don't
appreciate your affection,
I just don't have time
to play these games.
Now, don't be
so hasty, teach.
I'm only barely warmed up!
Noumaku sanmanda
bazaradan chanda!
[OHTOMO recites spell]
[KAGAMI] That barrier!
[OHTOMO] Kanman.
[KAGAMI grunts]
♪
[KAGAMI]
I'll stop you!
Saratei saratei sowaka.
Om mari shiei sowaka!
[KAGAMI] Un!
♪
[KAGAMI] The variety and
finesse of his spells
are impressive on their own,
but his tactics
show the true skill.
Damn it.
I should have expected this
from a first class mage!
[OHTOMO] Kagami.
Go away.
[KAGAMI] Huh?
[KAGAMI] Oh crap.
[TENMA] Huh?
Cut it apart.
Order!
Heck yeah!
[DOMAN] Huh?
What is that?
[YASHAMARU gasps]
[YASHAMARU] Kurahashi the seal
on the Coat has been broken.
But there's no way!
Okay, you're free now.
You can go save Harutora!
[TENMA]
What? Hey! Whadda--
[TENMA yells]
I must apologize, Kagami.
You moron.
You won't pass me!
Tell you what.
I'll break the spell from
the other day in return.
You think that bluff's
still gonna work on me?
Spell release, puraju
varo-shu niisha.
[KAGAMI screams]
[screaming continues]
[OHTOMO laughs]
You're suffering because
of that pretentious habit
of wearing sunglasses inside.
[KAGAMI] Bastard!
You bastard!
That was a pretty good
lesson if I say so myself.
Well, later.
Aahh! I'm not done!
Aah!
You just wait, Jin Ohtomo!
I'll kill you!
You'll die for this!
The Raven Coat.
It must be.
Interesting.
Neither Ohtomo nor
I pulled this one.
It seems to me that the motives
of a lot of people around here,
who are less than
pleased with you,
are coming together
at the perfect moment.
Delightful, simply delightful!
That's what I call
a shrine of curses!
Oh my, you are unexpectedly
easy to attack from the rear.
I'm willing to bet that's
because you are always
fighting common
spirit disasters.
I'm much obliged.
I won't let you go.
Surely you realize that.
I'd never allow such rudeness.
Sorcery is fascinating and
generally used for humans,
which is why
it doesn't seem to
be aware of me
in the slightest.
[HARUTORA] Damn it.
[YASHAMARU chuckles]
Look who I found!
[HARUTORA and KURAHASHI grunt]
Touji!
Harutora!
[KYOKO] Now!
Spell release, confusion!
Order!
[KURAHASHI grunts]
[YASHAMARU] Hm.
[TOUJI] C'mon!
[KURAHASHI recites spell]
[YASHAMARU] Hm.
Unappreciative child.
You got in!
Why so surprised?
A few punches aren't gonna be
enough to stop us, you know.
[HARUTORA] Mm.
[TOUJI]
Let's get out of here!
Kyoko and Suzuka are guarding
the back entrance for us!
[YASHAMARU] Looks like a hole
was made in the barrier.
It must have been in order to
gain access to the Raven Coat.
What will you do while
I head out after them?
Check on something.
♪
[yells]
[DOMANS yell]
It's like there's
no end to these freaks.
Keep at it, Suzuka;
we can't close this door!
[SUZUKA] What the hell
is taking them so long?
[DOMANS cackle]
They're here!
Huh?
Second seal. Purge!
[DOMANS yell]
Sorry about the wait.
But on the bright side,
I managed to rescue
our captive princess.
Kyoko. Suzuka.
Stupid-tora.
[HARUTORA chuckles]
[YASHAMARU]
You forgot something.
[GROUP gasps]
I'd say you kids got a little
carried away tonight.
Wouldn't you agree?
[TENMA yells]
Tenma!
The Raven Coat?
♪
Oh, of course.
Now you decide to show up.
[YASHAMARU] I'm sorry,
but they got away.
Yasuzumi made an appearance.
He had sorcery against Imperial
pallbearers ready for me.
Don't worry about
catching them.
They'll come back since we
still have Natsume's body.
[YASHAMARU] Roger that.
[SUZUKA] Four-Eyes!
Why is the Raven Coat with you?
None of us thought
you were gonna come,
so what are you doing here?
Were you working
all alone?
Sorta.
Look, Harutora.
I've got a message for you.
Message from who?
[TENMA]
Suzu Saotome.
[GROUP] Huh?
She wanted you to know
that if you planned on
performing the Taizan
Fukun Ritual on your own,
she's more than
willing to help you.
[HARUTORA] Uh?
[TENMA] Apparently,
she's waiting for you.
She's the one who told me you'd
need the Raven Coat, too.
So you mean you
went and grabbed
the Raven Coat
all by yourself?
You snuck into the agency?
[TENMA] Yeah, pretty much.
But, that doesn't really
matter at the moment.
[TOUJI] Uh...
[TENMA] Harutora, are you
going to revive Natsume?
Yes.
Everybody, listen up.
I'm gonna bring Natsume back
using the Taizan Fukun Ritual.
And I'm gonna do it myself.
I owe Natsume.
That'll be my atonement.
Tenma, did Suzu know
I would choose to do this?
To perform the ritual without
any help from those jerks?
[TENMA] Possibly.
But Harutora, when it
comes down to it,
you know that girl
a lot better than I do.
[TENMA chuckles]
[HARUTORA] I knew it.
How do you know
she can be trusted?
No one seems to know her!
Because Natsume said to.
The one-armed ogre told her,
"when things start to get rough,
seek out Suzu Saotome."
Yeah, and you
can't be sure
if you can believe that
stupid ogre, either!
No, I can't.
Look, Natsume said it herself.
She told us magic
dealing with souls
is not something humans
should be interfering with.
She did. And I'm
dreading her lecture.
But I still have to do it.
[SUZUKA] Mmm.
Oh, by the way.
Suzu told me something else.
"Don't be afraid
of the Raven Coat.
But also, don't be
overcome by it."
As expected from a
classmate of Mister Ohtomo.
Don't get me wrong,
she was weird,
but I think we can trust her.
[HARUTORA sighs]
Touji, Kyoko,
Suzuka, Tenma.
I-I'll be back.
[KOGURE] I can't allow this.
[GROUP gasps]
[KON] I'm here, Master!
No matter what the
situation may be.
I cannot simply turn a blind
eye to forbidden magic.
As their teacher,
I'm sure you agree with me.
Right, Jin?
[gasps]
[groans]
You're the one
responsible for
bringing out Doman
Ashiya, aren't you?
I can't believe you had that
much mistrust in the agency.
You didn't mention it
to me, but I get that,
I figure you respected
my position.
All you wanted was
to free your student.
And once you got yourself
on that wanted list,
everything would be resolved.
Your unrelenting consideration
is irritating per usual.
Just how I am.
[KOGURE] Harutora.
Forbidden magic is a game,
a game that uses the
world as collateral.
What? A game?
If you win, the reward
will be great,
but if you lose, you risk
sacrificing the rest of us.
The damage won't stop with the
mage who performed the spell.
Innocent people could be hurt.
Even if you win the game,
forbidden magic will
destroy your body.
It's like poison.
It will gnaw away at the mage.
Gnaw away at his heart.
Your teacher over there
knows this all too well,
so he won't be interfering.
[KOGURE] Jin.
I'm taking responsibility
for these kids.
No matter what the
main agency says.
I will not let them go.
That work for you?
I won't make you help.
But don't get in my way.
Huh? [gasps]
[groans]
[KON grunts]
Listen to me.
Natsume Tsuchimikado...
...is dead.
[KYOKO gasps]
--[TENMA] Kyoko!
--[HARUTORA] Kyoko!
--[TOUJI] Kyoko!
--[SUZUKA] Kyoko!
[KYOKO - SPIRIT] Stars.
Am I? Is this?
Reading the stars?
[KYOKO - SPIRIT gasps]
[gasps]
[KYOKO - SPIRIT whimpers]
Yes, I see.
I can see the
whole universe.
This world is just one of many!
I can see the
whole universe.
This world is just one of many!
The rules of
what is forbidden
are only things that have
been decided by man!
The rules of what
is forbidden are
only things that have
been decided by man.
[OHTOMO] Uh--
[KYOKO/KYOKO - SPIRIT]
Harutora.
[KYOKO - SPIRIT exhales shakily]
[KYOKO - SPIRIT sobs]
Oh, I can see
Natsume's stars!
[KYOKO] Oh, I can
see Natsume's stars.
[KYOKO - SPIRIT]
Natsume is out there.
She's waiting for you!
[KYOKO]
She's waiting for you.
--[KYOKO - SPIRIT] Go!
--[KYOKO] Go.
Go to her, now.
[KOGURE]
Is this a star reading?
Is that even possible?
What did she mean
by Natsume's waiting?
[OHTOMO chuckles]
I swear, my classroom
is downright packed
with problem children.
Don't do this!
Too late.
[KOGURE]
Damn it! Sorcery?
[KOGURE] Ah!
Tenma! How is she?
She's only passed out.
Hurry!
Bastard. How could you?
[OHTOMO] Honestly, I never
imagined teaching would ever
be this difficult, so I
wouldn't recommend it.
[KOGURE] Are you insane?
[OHTOMO] Probably.
I might be making
a mistake here.
And yet...
...in the end, this is
the path I've chosen.