[rain]
[KAKUGYOUKI] Doman.
[DOMAN] Oh, it's you.
Good job making
it all the way here.
[KAKUGYOUKI]
The magical labyrinth?
That wouldn't stop me.
Your familiar said you
were about to make a move.
I must've heard wrong.
[DOMAN] That impertinent
little blabber mouthed fool.
Why do you tolerate
impertinence?
Try tightening
the familiar's leash.
[DOMAN laughs]
That one is almost too
feisty for an old man,
such as myself, to handle!
But then, that just makes
it even more thrilling.
Course it does.
You've been alive too long.
I choose to keep young
by having some fun,
which is more than
anyone could say for you.
[KAKUGYOUKI] Unfortunately,
cheap thrills don't
do much for me.
If that's so, then what
do you bother living for?
Are you wandering
around in the dark
simply to avoid
having to choose a path?
I live simply to find
out why I'm still alive.
[KAKUGYOUKI'S footsteps]
[HOKUTO]
Harutora. Harutora!
Hey, Harutora!
Huh?
Man! Stupid-tora,
you're always so slow!
--Hurry up, would you?
--Whoa.
Hold on, Hokuto! Be careful.
Stupid-tora. Don't worry
about me; I'm good!
[NATSUME] Hey, what's up?
Is something wrong?
[HARUTORA] Natsume?
[KON] M-Master Harutora,
is everything all right?
[HARUTORA] Kon?
Nah, I'm okay. It's nothing.
But... But are you sure?
[HARUTORA] I said it's nothing.
I'm sorry I woke you up.
[MALE TEACHER 13A] The doctrine
of the Five Elements
consists of two principles:
the rivalry and the
harmonious relationship
between each element.
The principle of rivalry states
that wood draws energy...
[HOKUTO] I'll keep it forever!
[HARUTORA] Do what you want.
I hope you know it cost
way more to win
than it was worth.
Maybe, but I don't care.
[HARUTORA] Why not?
Just cause, silly.
[MALE TEACHER 13A]
Reciprication.
In the principle of
harmonious relationship,
wood begets fire,
fire begets earth,
earth begets gold,
and gold begets water.
[OHTOMO]
These are Swallow Whips.
Little guys were designed
to detect and bind
any source
of spirit energy.
[OHTOMO] Hide your spirit
energy, and they'll fly on by.
Uh!
Well, I'm afraid Harutora's
out of the running.
You couldn't even reach
the three-minute mark, huh?
[OHTOMO] Having an abundance
of spirit energy is good,
but you need to control it.
Focus on containing
the wellspring
and try to keep your cool.
Hey, I'm cool
as a cucumber in a
big bowl of ice cream, man.
Ooh, a simile?
Ten points extra credit!
[KON] Oh, my poor Master!
Kon?
[KON] Don't worry
Master Harutora!
Your loyal servant
Kon will get you out of...
whatever this is!
[OHTOMO] It's nice that you
care so much for your master,
but stay out of the way, okay?
You impudent hayseed!
Get your paws off of me!
Whoa! Kon, just
calm down already!
Come down to my level!
[KON] Let me go,
you big meanie!
He's distant. Like he
doesn't like me anymore.
If you can honestly
think that nonsense,
then you're dumber than
I thought you were,
ya big dweeb.
Lame-brain over there
admitted he had
feelings for Hokuto.
And that would mean
he feels the same way
towards you,
now wouldn't it?
--But...
--Uh...
[TOUJI] Look, if you're not
going to say anything to him,
then maybe I could
talk to him for you.
No, please don't
do that! You can't.
It's something
I should do.
[sighs]
So wonderful to
have rain again.
[SUZUKA] Oh! There you are!
I watched the
whole thing, darling.
Wait, so you
saw me in there?
[SUZUKA] I was secretly spying
on you guys the whole time, duh.
No one even had
a clue I was there.
Weird.
An invisibility spell, huh?
Classic Divine
General hijinks.
It's really a
rather basic spell.
But you can't even
do that right, can you?
How do you expect to improve
if you don't practice, silly?
[HARUTORA] Uh.
All you have to do
is completely release
everything
cluttering your mind.
Which for you, shouldn't
take very long at all.
Huh?
If I do empty my
mind, then, like,
how'm I gonna
remember the spell?
Shut up. Listen.
You need to keep training
until the spell
is second nature,
and you can chant the
damn thing in your sleep.
Uh...
[KYOKO]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
About time, Kyoko.
[KYOKO] It takes a bit longer
for a girl to get ready.
But then, I wouldn't
expect a guy with
less than zero class
to understand.
Oh! Hello Suzuka!
Gross.
You're looking
cuter than ever!
Just like a little
porcelain dollie!
[SUZUKA] Stop glomping
on me you mammary monster!
K, I'm lost.
Since when have the two
of you become so chummy?
Ah-uh! Our Secret.
We aren't chummy!
Aw! You're so cute
when you're angry!
Wait. Where's Tenma?
[TOUJI] He went home already.
[KYOKO] That's weird.
Though now that you mention it,
he did seem a little down.
[KYOKO] I wonder. Maybe his
family said something to him.
[HARUTORA] What do you mean?
The Momoe clan is an
influential Onmyo family
and Tenma is their
successor, so they can
be kind of tough
to deal with.
That's rough. I guess I
don't know much about him.
[TENMA]
I have a question, sir.
Is Onmyo magic
aptitude entirely
dependent on innate talent?
It doesn't seem like
something you can master
with hard work alone.
You do need talent.
How many spirit seers
do you think there are now?
It's shocking how
few of us are around.
Only a small percentage
of the population
has the ability,
and fewer still go on
to become pro mages.
These days, there are
very few occupations that
have to be as
selective as this one.
Do you think I
have what it takes
to be a working mage, someday?
[OHTOMO] I don't know.
Becoming a professional
mage requires
more than raw talent,
you understand.
[TENMA] Sure.
Try to envision Onmyo
magic as a grand tapestry,
in which the sum total
of each mage's talents
acts as a single thread.
[OHTOMO] Like the skills
of your departed parents.
[OHTOMO] Thanks to the
innovation of their company,
Witchcraft Corp.,
the power of familiars
has become accessible to
ordinary people everywhere.
You understand the value
of that, don't you?
[TENMA] Specializing
familiars for specific duties,
like construction,
increased their general
usability and appeal.
[OHTOMO] Correct. They made
artificial familiars mainstream
by standardizing
the power output,
effectively taking
the magic-user's strength
out of the equation.
[OHTOMO] Your parents even
invented these Swallow Whips.
They truly were visionaries.
I shouldn't
have to remind you of
just how important these
supporting industries are
to the spread of Onmyo magic,
and to our very future.
[OHTOMO] We accepted you
into this school based on
your qualifications. Please,
have faith in our judgment.
And don't forget to
have some in yourself, too.
[TENMA] Excuse me. Is there
something I can help you with?
Ah, good afternoon, sir.
My name's Atsune Hirata,
nice to meet you.
[HIRATA] I'm a magical
crime investigator.
I have a question
about an old familiar
we have back at the bureau.
I was hoping that
you might be able to
help me out with it.
The familiar.
Was it something that
my mother helped develop?
Yes.
If that's the case,
then you really should
contact Witchcraft
Corporation directly.
Yes, of course.
I suppose you're right.
Well then,
sorry to bother you.
Thanks, Tenma Momoe.
Oh. Yeah, no problem.
Wait a second.
That was weird.
[TENMA] I never
introduced myself to him.
♪
Huh?
[MALE AGENT 13A]
The hell? An owl?
[MALE AGENT 13B]
It's a familiar!
[DOMAN'S VOICE]
My name is Doman Ashiya,
and I will take the
Raven Coat tomorrow!
[KOGURE] Bad news!
♪
Miyoshi. What've you
been able to sniff out?
[MIYOSHI] All preliminary
reports seem to indicate
the direct involvement
of "D" himself.
Hm.
Well, if this is Doman's
talisman familiar,
then that means
we've got a leg up.
Only if we assume
it's genuine.
Whatever the case,
Mister Ashiya has
some questions to answer.
[AMAMI] No matter the cost,
I want him caught.
[huffs]
[AMAMI] Miyachi. How is
our interception system?
We've completely
deconstructed and rebuilt
the magical defense barrier,
with it now
centered on Maririn.
It seems iron-clad.
Please, sir. I don't
like being called Maririn.
Hirata. What have
your people
at the Bureau discovered?
Sir. In regards to
the "D" personage,
there is still so much
we just don't know,
and I'd rather
not misinform anyone.
[AMAMI] I appreciate the
discretion, but I'd still
like to hear your
thoughts on the matter.
[HIRATA]
If you insist, Director.
I think it is
extremely likely that
the Twin Horn Syndicate
is manipulating
this situation
from the shadows.
And it is my opinion
that the only hope we have
of stopping that
organization is our ability
to effectively
apprehend this "D" fellow.
[AMAMI chuckles]
Precisely what I wanted
to hear. Well, Chief?
[KURAHASHI] Pass the word
along to your subordinates.
The Onmyo Agency
will intercept "D"
with the entirety
of its resources.
[KOGURE] Whoa, hold up!
Hmmm?
I have some information
I think I should
report, Commander.
[MIYACHI]
I'm listening.
It's about the
Raven Coat, sir.
Is that so?
Well then, let's
hear what you've got.
Well, there's a rumor that's
been going around lately.
About the Coat
at the Agency.
They're saying
it's a replica.
Really?
[KOGURE] They say the one
at the Agency is a fake.
And that the real one
is kept at Onmyo Prep.
So I guess,
long story short,
there's a chance
that "D" will make
an assault on
the school instead.
Has the Director
considered that possibility?
Kogure. Director Amami
is most likely
already aware of this.
He knows more about
the various details than
all of the rest
of us do combined,
so try to have a little faith.
After all,
he's the director of
the Magical
Investigation Bureau.
Plus he's our key strategist
so I trust his judgment.
I'm pretty sure he
would've confirmed the facts
for himself over at
Onmyo Preparatory.
You don't even
wanna check it out?
[MIYACHI] If he thought
any threat could come of it,
he'd have sent us.
I guess.
[MIYACHI]
Just think it through.
If there's any truth
to this rumor of yours,
then it would mean
Chief Kurahashi himself
is the one who hid the
Raven Coat at the school.
But. Why do
something so reckless?
Have you forgotten
last summer?
We can't make any
assumptions at this point,
do you understand?
[KOGURE]
Wait. Are you saying...?
[MIYACHI] If the real Raven
Coat truly is at Onmyo Prep,
as the rumor suggests,
what do we do,
go and pick it up?
Lead the Twin Horn
Syndicate right to it?
That would be worse than
if "D" got his hands on it.
So yes we are taking
quite a few risks,
but in the long run,
it ends up being
a reasonable compromise.
You should try to
focus on your orders
for the time being,
and not get distracted.
Just hold up your
end of the operation
[MIYACHI] and it'll
be easier for all of us.
[MIYO] Are you certain?
How can that be right?
[AMAMI] Well if it's
a practical joke,
it's been
quite well executed.
I can't imagine anyone
could have the power
to so thoroughly alter
Kurahashi's predictions.
Doman Ashiya.
[AMAMI] It figures.
When we're chasing him,
we don't even
glimpse his shadow.
Then he makes a flashy
entrance at our headquarters.
Now he's got my
boys at the bureau
second guessing themselves.
Which is precisely
the reason I came here.
The rumor says that the Raven
Coat at the Agency is a fake.
And Onmyo Prep is safeguarding
the actual Raven Coat
which Doman has
been searching for.
[AMAMI] There any
truth to that?
[MIYO] Perhaps.
[AMAMI] Hm.
I prefer to be
completely prepared
regardless of where
the authentic Coat
is actually being held.
I just wanted to make
sure you fully grasped
the severity of
this situation, Miyo.
[MIYO] I am aware.
And Amami?
[AMAMI] Mm?
[MIYO] Thank you.
I need you to get
a hold of Mister Ohtomo
and Mister Fujiwara,
please. Yes.
[MIYO] Consider it urgent.
[HOKUTO yells]
Ow, my head! I totally
got a brain freeze!
Become an Onmyo mage.
You better not say "no!"
[HOKUTO]
Get it for me, Harutora!
If you can get it for me,
well then, I'll kiss you.
How could you?
How could you be so careless?
[HOKUTO] You didn't
even chase after me.
And when I come back, you're,
you're kissing that girl.
Stupid-tora!
You don't get it!
You hurt my feelings,
and now...
This is even worse.
The guy I like was
kissed another girl!
[HARUTORA] What if
Hokuto actually was
Natsume the whole time?
Harutora!
[groans]
[exhales deeply]
I'm so dumb.
I just--I just
have to tell him.
Hokuto is actually me.
And that I've felt like this...
for such a long time.
Things can't
stay like this.
I'll talk to her, tomorrow.
[commotion]
[NATSUME] I'm done. See ya.
[sighs]
[HARUTORA]
Hey. Are you leaving?
[NATSUME] Uh. Mhm.
Gimme a break.
♪
Aw man, it looks like
it's about to rain again.
Yeah.
But summer starts when
the rainy season is over.
Uh-huh.
Summer time is, uh.
Festival time. Usually.
[HARUTORA] Have you ever been
to one in the countryside?
They wear yukatas
and you know, stuff.
Yukata?
Never mind! I was
just rambling, it's dumb.
[HARUTORA] C'mon you coward!
I thought you decided it was
time to talk to her for real.
Natsume!
Harutora, I...
What is it, Harutora?
So, Harutora.
What were you were saying?
[SUZU] So this is the
second-class magic
called young love
that they speak of.
[HARUTORA] Hey, what's up?
[NATSUME] Oh. Hello there.
Those of us who
love little girls
get to dwell in
youth eternally.
Sorry?
So you haven't
met this one yet?
The Senior obsessed
with little girls.
My pleasure.
Now you're blushing?
It's not like it's a secret.
You must be
Natsume Tsuchimikado.
Right. It's nice
to meet you.
My name is Suzu.
But please call me
Little Girl Senior.
Oh, I will.
Count on it.
[crowd commotion]
So Doman.
You made your move.
[clock chiming]
Seriously, bro. This is
just getting ridiculous.
Hm? What's that
supposed to mean?
The two of you morons.
[MALE TEACHER 13A]
Take your seats, everyone.
Class is now in session.
[MALE STUDENT 13A]
Pardon me, sir.
But where's Mister Ohtomo?
Is he sick or something?
[MALE TEACHER 13A] Mister
Ohtomo has been called away
on urgent matters.
I'm afraid you're
stuck with me for now.
[commotion]
[MALE STUDENT 13A] What? Your
teacher wasn't in class either?
[FEMALE STUDENT 13A] Yeah,
apparently he was needed
for an emergency.
[MALE STUDENT 13A] How weird.
[SUZUKA] Something strange
is going on, right?
[TOUJI] Yeah.
I've heard that none
of the practical skills
instructors have even
been to the campus today.
I guess that could
just be gossip.
[KYOKO] The whole
thing is suspicious.
[MALE STUDENT 13A]
What's going on?
[STUDENTS gasping]
[FEMALE STUDENT 13A]
No way that's true!
[MALE STUDENT 13B]
Everybody just quiet down!
We are reporting
live on the scene
at the breakout
of a new crisis.
At high noon today,
an attack began on
the Onmyo Agency
Headquarters in Akihabara,
located in the
Taito district of Tokyo.
[FEMALE REPORTER 13A]
This video is coming to you
live from the scene.
[gasps] Those are...
Oh no.
They're Tsuchigumos!
No way! It should
be impossible
to control that many!
[gasps]
[HARUTORA] It can't be.
Harutora?
Master!
Now then. Shall we begin?
[KON] If I am to properly
preview the next episode,
I must return
to the beginning.
I will stab!