[CROWD cheers]
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
--[DAISUKE grunts]
--[PLAYER 05A grunts]
[CROWD gasping]
[PLAYER 04H grunts]
[PLAYER 05C grunts]
[PLAYER 05D sighs]
--[DAISUKE grunts]
--[SOUICHIROU] No!
[PLAYER 05D gasps]
--[cheering]
--[GIRLS gasp]
[sighs]
I see why he's the ace.
He stopped them before
they could take the lead.
He just got insanely lucky.
The last half-dozen pitches
he threw would have been
a homerun with a good batter.
It's a miracle that
he gave up only one run.
[KUROYANAGI] Our second basemen
keeps changing his positioning.
You tell him to do that?
Yeah, and it was
an effective strategy
until the previous inning.
Right now, our pitches
are too slow and weak.
The way Nikaidou's
pitching today,
any one of our backup
pitchers would do better.
I didn't ask for your
color commentary, did I?
Just think of it
as a fresh new game!
It's our ace against
theirs from here on out.
--Got that?
--[PLAYERS] Yes, sir!
[NARRATOR]
Batting fourth, Imagawa.
[bellows]
[NARRATOR]
Batting fifth, Koma.
[KOMA grunts]
[NARRATOR]
Batting sixth, Murotani.
That's three up...
...and three down.
[CROWD applauds]
[CROWD cheers]
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
[TOUMA] What, are you
taking in the scenery?
Hurry up and do
your warm-up pitches.
[TOUMA]
What's that about?
[OOYAMA]
But seriously, I had no idea!
How long ago did
you get remarried
to that beauty, Eisuke?
[EISUKE] Huh? It's been
about seven years now.
Ah! That far back, huh?
Why didn't you tell me
about it, aren't we friends?
[EISUKE laughs]
Give me a break!
You know as well as I do that
you make yourself hard to find
so the people you owe money
to don't come a-knockin'!
[OOYAMA]
About that.
You'll notice there's
extra, for interest.
What exactly have you
been up to lately?
Nothing.
[EISUKE]
Is this dirty money?!
[OOYAMA] Whoa! I'm not doing
anything illegal, don't worry.
I'm takin' it that
guy's the late husband
of your current wife?
That's right.
I've seen him somewhere before.
Yup, that's Sawai.
[OOYAMA]
Ah-- You mean that Sawai?
Uh-huh. The very same.
The one who was
two grades below us.
To be perfectly clear,
me and the wife never
spoke much about the guy.
I thought it better not
to ask too much about him.
So I only learned who
he was after we got married.
[OOYAMA] Really? Well, your
wife must have been surprised.
[EISUKE]
Nah.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm?
Far as I can tell, she doesn't
know a thing about it.
Apparently, Sawai
rarely talked about
his high school days,
baseball or otherwise.
That so?
Well, it's not like
you can blame the guy.
Oh, hello.
Are you leaving already?
But I just bought some more
beer in case you both ran out.
Oh, really? For us?
Ah!
Uhh, uhh-uhh!
Go on. Take these
and drink'em at home.
Oh. That works, too!
[OOYAMA] They only made it to
the third round this year, too.
[EISUKE]
Yeah. Even with the good fortune
of facing three weak teams.
[OOYAMA]
Oh, one more thing, pal.
[EISUKE]
Yeah?
[OOYAMA] Can you maybe
lend me some money
for my train fare home?
Huh? Like how much?
[OOYAMA]
Thirty-thousand yen.
Thirty-thousand?!
Just how far away do you live?!
[OOYAMA]
Well, I'm in Kyushu, so...
I don't have that
kind of money to lend!
Sure you do!
I just gave it to you.
[EISUKE] So, what was the
point of you paying me then?!
[OOYAMA]
Thanks again!
[EISUKE]
And don't come back!
Wait. You can come back, but
don't forget you still owe me!
[EISUKE sighs]
It's already past one o'clock?
Even if I leave right now,
the game will be over!
Out of all the times to show up,
it had to be during a game.
Idiot.
What did you
say his name was again?
Mr. Ooyama?
[EISUKE]
Yeah, Gorou Ooyama.
He used to be our
captain way back when.
[MAYUMI]
Oh, of the sumo club?
[EISUKE]
Baseball!
[CROWD cheering]
[PLAYER 05E grunts]
[PLAYER 05F grunts]
[exasperated sigh]
[gasps]
[PLAYER 05B grunts]
--[PLAYER 05C grunts]
--[PLAYERS cheering]
[PLAYER 05G grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[OTOMI snarls] That guy had
no business showing up
and taking the mound like that!
Y'know what?
It's the manager's fault, too!
What's he thinking?!
Otomi, not so loud.
That old guy over
there's giving you
one heck of a stink eye.
[OTOMI growls]
Meh!
Don't antagonize him more!
Welp, we all tried our best.
Good game.
Uh-huh. Until just moments ago.
Yeah.
--Manager!
--We're playing a game.
Whatever it is can wait.
Right.
[NARRATOR] By the beginning
of the final inning,
there was no "number-one
uniform" on the Meisei bench.
[grunting]
This guy's not too bad.
Yup. And deservedly, he won.
[CROWD cheers]
[NARRATOR] Win, and reach
the height of pure joy.
[OTOMI snarls]
[NARRATOR] Lose, and show
frustration from deep within.
Those who choose to play the
game have to be ready for both.
[TOUMA]
All right. Time to go home.
[cicadas crying]
[vacuum whirring]
[TOUMA yelps]
Hey!
Can't you see
I'm trying to clean here?!
Get out of the way!
Would you stop?!
If you ruin this shirt,
you're gonna pay for it
out of your allowance!
[SOUICHIROU yawns]
[OTOMI] C'mon! Just let go!
Seriously, you're such a jerk!
[SOUICHIROU] Hey, Touma.
Wanna go for another run?
Sure.
If you two are itching
for a workout that badly,
why don't you
just go to practice?
No way! If I ran
into our manager right now,
I don't think I could resist the
urge to clock him in the jaw.
Yeah. I guess I'd have trouble
listening to him after
that last game, too.
[PUNCH whines]
[OTOMI] But what do you guys
plan to do from now on?
[TOUMA] We've been thinking
about that a lot.
--Haven't we, Sou?
--Yeah.
Could you be more cryptic?
[doorbell rings]
[OTOMI]
Coming!
Afternoo--
[gasps, chuckles]
--[SOUICHIROU] Nishimura.
--Uh, hey, Tachibana brothers!
This is weird.
How'd you find our address?
[NISHIMURA chuckles]
I asked around the neighborhood
and got a quick answer.
Home of remarried
couple, each with kids.
The two sons are both
in the same grade.
And they have a sister who's
one year younger than them.
Speaking of which.
That's her, right?
[SOUICHIROU]
Yeah.
She's pretty cute.
So I hear you didn't
make it past the semifinals
at the Tokyo Tournament.
Yeah. We missed our chance
of getting into the
Kanto Tournament by a hair.
But... It's pretty
obvious why we failed.
Why did you?
Well, when it comes down to it,
I've never been blessed
with a good catcher.
What's her name?
Huh?
Your sister, duh.
[growls]
Otomi.
Oh, cute name, too.
That's enough. Why are you here?
[NISHIMURA] Oh, I was wondering
if you'd be interested
in meeting my dad today.
[BOTH]
Hmm?
If you seriously
wanna make it to Koshien,
you're gonna need
to make some changes.
You know the spring tournament?
Seinan High made it there.
My dad's the current
manager of the team.
Whaddya say?
Team up with me
and we'll make it far.
Beyond Koshien,
we'll go to nationals!
Sorry, but I have
no intention of leaving Touma.
Totally fine!
My dad's looking for
a solid third baseman, too.
Come on, what
have you got to lose?
Just come take a peek at Seinan.
You'll start dreaming bigger!
Your thoughts?
Well, we have been
thinking about other schools.
And we've got
nothing else to do.
That's the spirit!
Hey, maybe your sister
wants to come along.
She does not!
What's that school?
That one over there?
That's Kenjyou High School.
If I'm remembering right, it
used to be called Sumi Tech,
but they changed the
name a few years back.
I'm pretty sure that's
the opponent Meisei High
faced in the finals
the year they made it
to the Koshien Tournament.
Yeah, and now both teams
are equally uncompetitive.
It's pretty crazy
how much has changed.
Come on! A little further!
[PLAYERS talkin]
[NISHIMURA] Excuse me! Is my
dad-- Uh, is the manager around?
[PLAYER 05I] Yeah. He's watching
our pitchers practice.
[PLAYER 05J]
Nice!
[NISHIMURA]
Hey, Dad!
[ISAMI sighs]
What's up?
I brought a couple of guys that
I thought you might
want to meet.
Are you busy?
[ISAMI] I've always got time
for the Tachibana brothers.
[BOTH]
Hmm
Do you know 'em?
Coach Kamata has been
singing both their praises.
He's had his eye on them
for quite some time.
Oh...
Sorry to hear about
the summer tournament.
You made top four, right?
Yeah. Winning
a tournament that size
is no cake walk,
that's for sure.
But, I can tell you
the exact reason that we lost.
[PLAYER 05J grunts]
One more, just like that!
[ISAMI] It's become
increasingly clear to me,
since the Spring Tournament.
What this team really
lacks is an ace pitcher
and a main catcher.
[PLAYER 05L grunts]
That's it!
[NISHIMURA] Heh! Just you
wait two more years, Dad!
'Cause then the best pitcher and
catcher duo in Seinan's history
will have arrived!
And his brother
will come with him?
Oh, he's a great third baseman!
He's fast and
his throwing arm's--
[ISAMI] Hold on.
You're a pitcher, right?
[NISHIMURA]
Eh?
[ISAMI] What's more.
The word on the street
is that you're every bit
as talented as my son.
What?
[ISAMI]
I'm told that if you join us,
my son may not be able to
wear the number-one uniform.
So, I should
probably pass on it.
Who said that?
[ISAMI]
If you must know.
It was actually
your current manager.
Really...?
Well. Not that
I believe what a manager
with no achievements
has to say.
I only trust talented sources.
You might not
know just how bad
that man's reputation is.
No surprise there.
Ah. Hmm...?
[ISAMI] Show me a pitch.
One'll be enough to tell.
Know why? Because I know
how to manage a team.
Whoa, give it a shot.
[TOUMA]
Hmm...
[SOUICHIROU]
Can I ask you a question?
If you must.
Given they were talented,
would you ever consider
giving the ace number
to someone other than your son?
[ISAMI laughs]
Get a load of this guy, Takumi!
Listen up. Don't ever forget.
There's no such thing as
a pitcher more talented than
the manager's flesh and blood.
Any coach with a son
will tell you that. 'Kay?
[laughs]
[PLAYER 05J yells]
[ISAMI]
Hah?
[PLAYER 05J groans]
[ISAMI gulps]
[TOUMA]
How was that?
Uh... So sorry, kid!
I wasn't looking,
gimme one more!
Might I suggest
you use a different catcher?
[ISAMI]
Hmm.
[PLAYER 05J whimpers]
Hey, Yamakura!
[YAMAKURA]
Yeah?
[YAMAKURA groans]
--[ISAMI gulps]
--[NISHIMURA gasps]
You were right.
It does look like you gotta do
something about your catchers.
Uh, yeah...
I'm sorry, Nishimura.
I want to see my brother
wearing the number-one uniform.
While we're on the same team.
Besides...
I think we've had just about all
we can take of doting fathers.
[laughs]
I can't blame you for
trying, Takumi,
but they're just not
meant to be here.
Let's get this straight.
First of all,
I hate Meisei High School.
I feel sick every time I take
a glance at that uniform.
But! To be fair.
Since becoming manager,
I haven't lost a game to them!
And it's pretty nice to have
a team that you know
you can destroy.
[laughs]
Seriously though,
they've turned into
such a pathetic
excuse for a team.
It's a damn shame.
[SOUICHIROU]
Touma. Let's go.
Okay.
[ISAMI]
Hmph.
After all these years.
Seeing him pitch reminds
me so much of Uesugi.
Why is that?
[NISHIMURA]
Tachibana!
Let me ask you just one thing!
What is it?
I wanna know how you
spell your sister's name.
[baseball bat clanks]
[window shattering]
[TOUMA] Nishimura's
pretty skilled. Isn't he?
[SOUICHIROU]
His dad, too. Right?
[TOUMA]
Seems so.
[ISAMI] They've turned into such
a pathetic excuse for a team.
Man, you know what sucks?
What?
How much it pisses me off
when someone else says it.
When they say what?
Bad stuff about Meisei.
[SOUICHIROU]
I gotta say, I'm surprised.
It's not easy to imagine
our manager saying
you're a better pitcher
than Nishimura.
I doubt it's true.
I mean really, that's
probably the last thing
the guy would ever say.
[SOUICHIROU] Yeah. The
man's trying to rein us in--
Why would he talk
about you that way?
[TOUMA]
Yup! Now you got me thinking
about how horribly he
handled our last game!
We could have won!
Doesn't he want us to do well?
He's so bad!
[SOUICHIROU]
I agree. Unless, for instance,
that was Nikaidou's
last time taking the mound.
Well, it was.
It's his last summer
in Junior High School.
[SOUICHIROU]
No. That's not what I mean.
I meant ever.
[OTOMI]
Hmm? [yelps]
[OTOMI] It's their stupid
baseball team manager.
Is that all he came here to do?
[TOUMA]
Next time, on Mix.
[OTOMI] Spring is almost here!
And you know what that means!
--[TOUMA] Grad ceremony.
--[SOUICHIROU] Strawberries.
--[TOUMA] Entrance ceremony.
--[SOUICHIROU] Clams.
--[TOUMA] Cherry-blossoms.
--[SOUICHIROU] Sakura mochi.
--[TOUMA] Moving.
--[SOUICHIROU] Bamboo shoots.
--[TOUMA] Festivals.
--[SOUICHIROU] Whitefish.
--[TOUMA] The Spring Tournament!
--[SOUICHIROU] Spring cabbage.
[TOUMA] Dude. Can you say
something other than food?
[OTOMI] Next time:
"When Spring Arrives."
[TOUMA]
Now I'm hungry, thanks a lot.
[barks]