[MAYUMI sighs]
I wonder how it's going.
Well, I hope!
[PUNCH barks]
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once‐triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
He looks just like him.
[ICHIBAN] Top of the eighth.
Top of the order.
[DAISUKE]
Hmm..
[ICHIBAN] Oh! You'd
better watch this first.
[NARRATOR]
Okay, then! Previously on Mix!
[NARRATOR] The fight for a spot
in the summer Koshien kicked off
with the start of the
East Tokyo Tournament!
After 30 years,
Meisei High School
is giving their all to
return to their former glory.
Their first opponent
of the tournament
is Kenjo High School, and their
famed slugger, Tomohito Akai.
By the way, they used
to be called "Sumi Tech."
[TOUMA]
Hmph!
[NARRATOR]
It's the bottom of the eighth,
and, trailing Kenjo
by a single run,
Meisei is batting from
the top of the order.
[ICHIBAN] Shouldn't we be happy
they're going back to the top?
[DAISUKE]
Hmm...
[ICHIBAN]
Although, our first two batters
haven't found their timing yet.
[UMPIRE 13B]
Out!
[OOYAMA]
Hmm.
Right!
[MUROTANI grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Batter's out!
[sighs]
[ICHIBAN] Oh, man, we're up
to two outs now. Not good.
But Souichirou is up next,
and I know he's got this.
[ICHIBAN]
Surely.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Foul! Ball four!
[ICHIBAN]
And he got nothing to swing at.
So...
[ICHIBAN] Guess it's up
to our cleanup hitter!
[DAISUKE] Whaddaya think‐‐
can we trust his swing?
[ICHIBAN] Hmm. Uh, well, as a
person, sure, we can trust him,
I think he's a good guy‐‐
pretty sharp out there.
Someone you can rely on.
[DAISUKE]
No doubt.
He's saved my ass plenty
of times, that's for sure.
[ICHIBAN]
Wait? You mean in a game?
[DAISUKE gasps] I will not
tolerate any bad‐mouthing him.
[ICHIBAN] Ah, like I said,
I think he's
a really great player,
a very reliable guy!
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
Did I make a mistake
with this lineup?
[TOUMA] Tadashi was fourth in
the lineup back when he was
a second‐year in junior high.
Just so ya know.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm?
He's pretty good with cleanup.
Well, most of the time,
I wouldn't worry.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm..
[TOUMA] But take note:
I said most of the time.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Ball!
But in this at‐bat,
he's got that vibe.
He looks like
a real cleanup hitter.
Um, are you sure?
[TADASHI grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
You see that swing and a miss?
Cleanup hitter.
I guess, if you say so.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Ball!
Ball! That's four!
[BOTH growl]
That pitcher has some
really good instincts.
Yeah. Two outs,
men on first and second.
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
Number five, Ogi.
Center field. Grade 12.
I dunno. Did I make
a mistake with this lineup?
Yes?
[KENJO SCOREKEEPER 13A]
Consecutive walks after
striking two guys out.
You think he's getting tired?
I think he's
being overly cautious.
You know what I mean?
No.
Always keeps a cool head.
That's a pitcher who
knows how to win a game.
Kita.
[ICHIBAN]
Get on base!
We gotta get the next
batter on, no matter what!
[TOUMA]
Focus.
Okay now, tell me the truth.
Did I make a mistake?
Yes?
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
Oh, boy.
Kenjo may still
be an incomplete team,
there's no denying that.
But we have what it takes
to win this tournament.
[KOMIYAMA]
The offense is a given.
But our pitchers are solid, too,
and the infield defense may
all be 10th graders,
but they're an iron wall.
Our outfield's great, too.
With one glaring exception.
[TODOROKI pants]
[KOMIYAMA]
Our right fielder Todoroki
can't cover much ground.
[KOMIYAMA gasps]
Don't dive for it!
You'll never catch up
to it at that speed!
[TODOROKI grunts]
[TODOROKI groans]
[BOTH grunt]
[gasps]
Ah‐‐!
[CROWD cheers]
[TOUMA]
Hm?
[CROWD cheers]
All right! We've taken the lead!
Guess I didn't
make a mistake, after all.
[DAISUKE]
Speaking as a pitcher,
that guy's the last batter you
want to face right about now.
[ICHIBAN]
Yeah, you're right.
I'd never want
to challenge Touma
in a high‐stakes game like this.
[DAISUKE]
No doubt.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
Come on, boys.
We can't let Meisei ride this
momentum any further.
[PUNCH barks]
[TOUMA grunts]
[KITA gasps]
[UMPIRE 13B]
He's out!
[CROWD cheers]
That infield defense,
like an iron wall.
[TOUMA groans]
[YAMAJI]
What's wrong, Kita?
Are you feeling down
about giving up the lead?
Not that.
[TOUMA sighs]
[KITA]
I'm watching that guy.
He's good at more
than just pitching.
[TODOROKI]
Damn it!
I only missed that catch
by a few inches!
I could've sworn that
ball was gonna carry
a lot farther. Talk about
bad luck, am I right?
If he's relying on luck
when he fields, we're doomed.
On another note,
what do you guys think
about this matchup?
There are way better
teams out there.
Why'd we get them for
our first opponent?
Yeah.
And I bet Meisei's over there
wondering the same thing.
[CROWD cheers]
[TOUMA sighs]
[ICHIBAN] Taking the mound
right after running
full out like that. A one‐run
lead in the top of the ninth.
And the other guys,
they're batting from
the top of the order.
[DAISUKE]
So, what about it?
[ICHIBAN]
Doesn't that make you nervous?
[DAISUKE]
Have you forgotten?
[ICHIBAN]
What?
[DAISUKE]
That guy was my rival.
I was always trying
desperately to crush him.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike three! Batter out!
[CROWD applauds]
[TOUMA grunts]
[ICHIBAN]
Oh, man! That's awesome!
[DAISUKE] Even though
I really hate to admit it.
I can't deny it.
Just how terrifying he can be.
What? Even against
my hand‐picked lineup.
That kid's gotten
seven strikeouts.
[SOUICHIROU] Do you take
him lightly? My brother?
I never saw my father pitch,
so I don't know how
good he really was.
But I have faith
that my brother can
take us to the championship.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm...
[ANNOUNCER 13A] Number three.
Right fielder. Todoroki.
Are we going to lose? To them?
And in the first round?
[KOMIYAMA]
Hmm...
[TODOROKI grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Foul!
[KOMIYAMA] Two years ago,
when I first became
the assistant manager...
...that kid was
only a first year.
And he was the single
bright spot on a lousy team.
[KOMIYAMA] Pretty soon, he was
starting, then batting cleanup.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Ball!
But, sadly, we just
kept losing all our games.
And after a while,
that broke his spirit.
By the time
he got to 11th grade,
he'd lost his motivation,
and got lazier and lazier
with every practice.
Sure, but, he's
still got a great swing.
Yeah. Ever since you
tenth graders joined the team,
he's started to get
his old shine back,
and play more like
he did two years ago.
[TODOROKI grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Foul!
Out of everyone on the team,
he's the hungriest
for a victory.
[TODOROKI growls]
[KOMIYAMA]
No doubt.
[gasps]
[TODOROKI huffs]
[UMPIRE 13B]
Out!
[CROWD cheers]
[TODOROKI snarls]
[TODOROKI] If you guys had
joined the team a year earlier,
I would have made it on base.
I know it. I swear!
I know you would've.
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
‐‐[MEISEI TEAM whoops]
Well, you broke your promise.
I thought you said you
were gonna end the game
by striking out
their cleanup hitter.
Their number‐three
batter wouldn't
let me lose focus.
I just couldn't do it.
[SOUICHIROU]
The older Akai brother.
I gotta say, he doesn't come
across as the bad guy
you made him out to be.
Yeah. And, if that's the case...
He could be a pain.
We did lose, after all.
To those guys.
In the first round.
It was my mistake.
'Cause you took them lightly?
No, It's not that.
It happened a long time ago, and
I can't seem to figure it out.
How did that battery
fly under my radar
back in their middle
school days?
[DAISUKE]
You have me to thank, coach.
[ICHIBAN] Hmm? Uh,
did you say something, dude?
I didn't say anything.
Y'hearin stuff?
[NARRATOR]
Meisei High School.
They made it through
to the second round
of the East Tokyo Tournament.
[door click]
Dinner isn't ready yet?
No, I just got a call from Mom.
She says she's running late
and wants us to wait
for her to get here.
[AKAI] Aren't you gonna
ask me how the game went?
I'm not interested, honestly.
Oh. But as for my team‐‐
Meisei, that is. I heard we won.
Three to two.
But I don't remember
what team we were playing.
What was that for?
Because you're wearing
my new shirt without asking.
I didn't know. Mom probably
put it in my drawer.
I guess she made a mistake.
I can wash it and give it back.
[AKAI]
Don't bother. I don't want it,
now that you've worn it.
I guess it's yours now.
Your birthday's tomorrow,
that can be your present.
[sighs]
[PUNCH snores]
[OTOMI]
So? What happened next?
[EISUKE snores]
[TOUMA yawns]
Let's see... Sorry,
where did we leave off, again?
Top of the fifth.
Kenjo was up at bat.
Oh. Yeah, I guess
it was around then
that I started to get
a tighter grip on the ball
and pitching way better.
[SOUICHIROU]
Stop being modest.
You were pitching well
from the beginning.
Otherwise, you would never
have escaped that lineup
with just two runs on a homer.
And no doubt the mercy
rule would have been
in effect against
an average team.
Ohhh... Against the team
that used to be Sumi Tech?
To put it different way,
if we'd been facing an average
lineup, they would have found it
nearly impossible to get a
single hit against Touma
the way he pitched today.
Whoa! Seriously? That's awesome!
You're amazing, Tou!
[TOUMA]
Uh... I, uh, gotta pee.
[SOUICHIROU gasps]
[OTOMI] Hey, Mom, can I
have another cup of oolong?
Oh? Sure.
[EISUKE snores]
[yawns]
Yes?
You can go to bed
now if you really want to.
I can keep Otomi entertained
from here on out.
[TOUMA]
Nah, it's fine, I'm good.
[OTOMI]
Tou!
This could go on
all night, you know.
That's cool.
[TOUMA] I mean, I tried
my best today just so I could
see that look on her face.
[SOUICHIROU sigh]
[PUNCH snores]
[ISAMI] Did you hear?
Meisei won three to two today.
Yeah, playing against Sumi Tech.
So, who cares?
You moron! You should
be reading up on them.
Kenjo was one of the favorites
to win the tournament.
You should care.
Apparently, their team
that started this spring
has over a 90% winning record.
The school that used to be
Sumi Tech is strong now.
'Kay.
And Meisei, they just
beat them in the first round.
That's a team resurrected.
Cool, cool. But why
do you look so happy?
[ISAMI growls]
Because it isn't as exciting
unless we're all there.
Meisei, Sumi Tech, and Seinan.
All of us.
What's the big deal?
[ISAMI]
You don't have to get it.
You just have to stay
healthy and on your game.
You start in five days,
don't forget it.
[NISHIMURA]
Roger that.
[ISAMI]
And until then...
You better not get caught
taking creepy pictures.
[TOUMA]
Next time, on Mix.
[SOUICHIROU] There's just one
thing the Meisei team lacks.
Can you guess what it is?
[TOUMA]
Come on, there's more than one.
I can think of two:
offense and defense.
[SOUICHIROU]
Not that.
[TOUMA]
Endurance? Concentration.
[SOUICHIROU]
Nope.
[TOUMA]
A manager who perseveres?
[SOUICHIROU]
No.
[TOUMA] Then what is it?
Intelligence? Magical powers?
[SOUICHIROU]
No! We're lacking girls!
Next time! "Full of Spirit!"
[TOUMA] But, admit it, there are
a lot of other things we lack.
[PUNCH barks]