[NARRATOR] The East Tokyo
Tournament has begun,
and a spot in the summer
Koshien is on the line.
After 30 years,
Meisei High School
is giving their all
to return to their former glory.
Their first opponent
of the tournament
is Kenjo High School, and their
famed slugger, Tomohito Akai.
[TOUMA]
Hmph!
[CROWD cheers]
[TODOROKI grunts]
[UMPIRE 14B]
Out!
[siren blares]
[NARRATOR] In what turned
out to be a nail‐biter,
Meisei High had
the fight of their lives,
and just barely
earned their victory.
[PUNCH]
Awr?
[barks]
[barks
[OTOMI]
See you later!
[PUNCH barks]
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
This is the story
of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventure
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[yawns]
Wow, that's quite a yawn
first thing in the morning.
I guess you had a
pretty late night, huh?
Yeah, I did.
I'm happy to see you
made a full recovery from
your made‐up illness.
Yeah, and all thanks to you.
Oh! Morning, Akai. How are you?
Otomi. Good morning
So, your brother...
How is he holding up?
Oh.
He's fine. I guess. Thank you.
Yeah, Well.
He can't be blamed for the way
the whole thing went down.
He was two for three
against Tou,
who happened to be
on top of his game.
He hit a homer with
two runs batted in.
As the cleanup hitter,
he more than fulfilled his duty.
[yelps]
‐‐Ugh, move.
‐‐Hey!
Ah! Oh, hey there, Akai!
I wanted to say happy birthday!
So, um, this isn't
really anything special.
It's just a moderately
expensive mug.
Even though it was pricey,
don't let that stop
you from using it.
[RYOU]
Oh. Thank you. How nice.
‐‐[OTOMI grunts]
‐‐Excuse you.
[OTOMI groans]
[RYOU sighs]
[OTOMI]
Today's your birthday? Cool!
What? Yeah..
I'd totally forgotten
about it until just now.
Really? Well, happy birthday.
I'm sorry I didn't
get you a gift!
[giggles]
No, you did, though.
Your smile is enough.
Hey! Uh, Otomi!
Do you happen to know
when my birthday is?
[OTOMI giggles]
Hi, Yoshiko!
[ICHIBAN]
Hmm...
‐‐When is it?
‐‐Uh?
Your birthday.
Tch! How dare you! That's
private information, mister!
[NARRATOR] What's up next
for the Meisei Baseball club?
Well, the East Tokyo
Tournament continues!
Who will they play in round two?
[NARRATOR]
Sankou High School!
Huh? That name sounds familiar,
but I'm not sure why.
[bat clangs]
[SANKOU COACH 16A]
C'mon! Hustle! Here it comes!
Now! Ready in left field?
[SANKOU TEAM 16C]
Ready!
[SANKOU COACH 16A]
Second base, here it comes!
[TEAM chanting]
Sankou! Sankou! Sankou!
[SANKOU COACH 16A]
Next, first base!
Aw, c'mon.
[grunting]
[HARUKA] Dang it!
This thing is a real pain.
[gasps]
Lucky!
[SANKOU STUDENT 16A]
Hey, Yokoyama.
Has anyone come out
to fix the old referee chair?
No, not yet. At least,
I don't think they have.
It seems kinda dangerous
to leave it out there.
Somebody might sit in it and
get themselves hurt real bad.
I don't think
that'll be a problem.
All the club members
know about it.
They won't be trying to use it,
if they know what's
good for them.
[SANKOU STUDENT 16A]
I guess you're right.
[YOKOYAMA]
Yeah.
So how was that?
It dropped, right?
Yeah. It sure did.
[TEACHER 07A]
Miss Ooyama!
I haven't seen her.
She hasn't come back
from her roadwork yet.
And it's been a long time.
[Are you serious?!
What is it with her?
She pulls this crap all
the time. I'm tired of it!
That one dropped, for sure!
[chair rattling, creaking]
Yep, it dropped.
[NARRATOR]
And, so did she, incidentally.
So, the following day.
[HARUKA sighs]
[TEACHER 07A whimpers]
[GYMNASTICS STUDENTS gasp]
Really...?
[OOYAMA]
So, there ya have it.
She can't go back
to gymnastics like this.
So, this young lady will serve
as the baseball team's trainer.
Miss Haruka Ooyama.
Hey, guys.
[MEISEI TEAM gasping]
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
That's it!
This whole time, I've felt like
the team was missing something!
Now I know what it is!
A cute trainer!
There isn't any rule that says
we absolutely need one.
Well. I've known for a long time
that Haruka's wanted
to do this for us.
I mean, when it comes to
baseball, Haruka has a habit
of letting herself get a little
bit carried away by the game.
As her father,
it was kind of a pain
to have her around
for that reason.
So, I forced her to keep
her distance up till now.
Then, this happened.
She broke her arm.
And it was while spying on
the Sankou High School
baseball team for us.
So, I've got no choice.
[HARUKA giggles]
[OOYAMA]
But!
Three conditions,
with no exceptions.
Three, huh?
Condition number one.
Under no circumstances will
you interfere with my coaching
or training methods.
Sure.
[OOYAMA] Number two. No romance
with any of the team members.
[MEISEI TEAM]
What...?
You heard me!
And? The third one?
[OOYAMA] Hmm... In the evenings,
I'm allowed to have
up to two large bottles of
beer without any lip from you.
No way.
Come on!
Of the three conditions,
this one is by far
the most important!
Two medium bottles, then?
Declined.
[OOYAMA growls] It doesn't
have to be every day!
How 'bout four days a week?
Tuesday, Thursday,
Saturday, and Sunday!
[HARUKA] Let me think about it
and get back to you.
[SOUICHIROU] All right,
folks, we better start practice.
[OOYAMA]
Throw me a bone here!
[HARUKA sighs]
[OOYAMA] Aw, why are
you ruining my life?!
[PUNCH barks]
‐‐Maybe I'm imagining things...
‐‐[YOSHIKO] Hmm?
...but didn't we just have
a swim class the other day?
I'm sure we did.
Yeah, we did. Episode 14.
I knew it! Also,
why don't the boys ever
have scenes where
they're wearing swimsuits?
[SWIM STUDENTS screaming]
[screaming continues]
[TEACHER 14A]
Mr. Fumimura!
What exactly do you
think you're doing?!
[FUMIMURA chuckles]
Oh, well, um, you
wouldn't have happened
to have seen any random car keys
laying around here, wouldja?
We've seen nothing
of the sort here, sir.
Besides, men are not
permitted in the area
during this class period!
I'll have to ask you to leave!
[FUMIMURA] Ah! Yes,
of course, pardon me.
‐‐Sorry.
‐‐[SWIM STUDENTS scream]
Sir, please go!
[FUMIMURA]
Yeah, I hear you. So sorry.
[SWIM STUDENTS grumbling]
When will this
country get serious
about punishing
men like that?
Perverts who think it's
okay to leer at young girls.
[whistle blows]
[TEACHER 14A]
Everyone, gather round!
Now, as tradition dictates,
we're going to have a 50‐meter,
freestyle race between
the swimmers who
got the top five times
in the last swim class.
Tradition?
[TEACHER 14A] If I call your
name, please step forward.
[TEACHER 14A]
Miss Itou!
[ITOU]
Yes.
[TEACHER 14A]
Miss Nakao!
[NAKAO]
Yes.
[TEACHER 14A]
Miss Sono!
[SONO]
Yes.
[TEACHER 14A]
Miss Mita!
Yes.
[TEACHER 14A]
Miss Tachibana!
[OTOMI gulps]
Yes.
[sighs]
[SWIM STUDENT 16C]
Good luck!
Arisa, Don't lose to them!
Otomi! You got this, girl!
Just so you know...
I am in peak
condition for this race.
Huh?
In the last one,
I only lost because I had
sprained my neck in my sleep.
Do I even remember
the last race?
[ARISA] When I'm in
top shape like I am now,
there's no way that
you can outswim me.
Which you're about to find out.
[OTOMI]
Hmm...
Hey, look! Miss
Meisei's gonna race!
And it's against Miss Runner Up.
That's awesome!
[SOCCER STUDENT 16B]
We gotta watch this! Let's go!
Morons. You can hardly
even call that a race.
Otomi's gonna kick Arisa's butt.
[TEACHER 14A ]
Ready!
[whistle blows]
[SWIM STUDENTS cheering]
[SOCCER STUDENTS cheerin]
The Miss Meisei runner up
sure can swim fast!
Huh? Where's Otomi?
Otomi hasn't risen
to the surface yet.
Is she all right?
She'll come up in a sec,
after she's secured
a healthy lead.
[ICHIBAN whimpers]
She's giving them
a handicap to make the race
that much more exciting!
Good strategy, there, Otomi!
Mm‐hmm!
Check it out!
She's already passed
two girls in no time flat!
Nice! And the only one
left to overtake is...
Keep it up! C'mon, Otomi!
Arisa! Don't let
her catch up to you!
Wah! This is such
an exciting battle!
You're right.
Miss Meisei and the
runner up are neck and neck!
[SOCCER STUDENTS cheerin]
[SWIM STUDENTS cheering]
Aww, yeah!
[YOSHIKO]
Aw...
What happened...?
[RYOU]
Ah...
Ah‐ha‐ha‐ha‐ha!
You're not gonna tell me
that you sprained your neck
in your sleep, are ya?
Oh, no, don't worry.
I'm in excellent condition.
Ah‐ha‐ha‐ha‐ha!
You were amazing
out there, Arisa!
Yeah, that was so exciting!
I can't believe how fast
you were swimming!
What were you
doing out there, Otomi?
She's the one person you
can't lose to intentionally.
You'll never hear the end of it.
That's not it.
I didn't lose on purpose.
She was way faster
than last time, honestly.
Maybe Arisa really did
sprain her neck in her sleep
before the last race.
She did not, and you know it!
She was obviously
making crappy excuses!
Well, if that's the case...
She must've
practiced really hard.
[ARISA]
Ah! Ha‐ha‐ha‐ha‐ha!
Ah. It's him again.
I can't believe he's
still sneaking around,
trying to get a peek
at us, the perv.
Excuse me, Mr. Fumimura?
Huh?
[OTOMI giggles]
[FUMIMURA]
Huh?
[OTOMI]
Here!
[FUMIMURA]
Ah!
You'll never guess
where they were!
Bottom of the pool!
[FUMIMURA]
Oh! Thank you, young lady!
Uh, Otomi. Could that
be why it took you so long
to surface after
you first dove in?
[inaudible]
[RYOU gulps]
Man, I wanna go
swimming now, too!
[SOCCER STUDENT 16B]
Why do they always make
the boys play soccer?
[ICHIBAN]
Hmm?
[RYOU]
Natsuno.
Yeah, what?
[RYOU]
I'm... in love with Otomi...
[ICHIBAN growls]
What?! How dare you
tell me something
so personal like it's nothing!
I was not at all ready for
this level of disclosure
in P.E. class!
How am I even
supposed to respond to
a confession like that?!
[MEISEI TEAM yelling]
[OOYAMA]
Center field!
[OGI] He's got the
speed of a fighter jet!
Look at him go!
Center field!
Twelfth grade!
[OGI]
Yutaka Ogi!
[OOYAMA] Infield! Look
alive, coming your way!
I can play any
of the infield positions!
My strongest suit is defense!
Eleventh grade!
[MUROTANI]
Kenjirou Murotani!
[KOUMOTO]
I love flyballs! Twelfth grade!
Shigeru Koumoto!
[OGURA]
I have a great throwing arm!
Eleventh! Shuji Ogura!
[TADASHI]
Hey!
[SHIGEMATSU]
Leave the grounders to me!
Eleventh grade, Shigematsu!
[HIRAO]
I'm fast and good, too!
Twelfth grade! Hirao!
[TAKESHITA]
Any time, any place!
I'm your guy, Takeshita!
[We really gotta do
something about that.
They're overselling every play.
I think it's awesome.
They're so full of spirit.
If that's all it is, then fine.
But...
[NANGOU grunts]
They're all trying way too hard.
I think the guys are trying
to show off for Haruka.
Well, let's just
hope it doesn't have
a lasting effect
on their swings.
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
Whose swing did he
say would be affected?
Yeah...
[TOUMA]
Next time, on Mix.
[SOUICHIROU] Our second game
is against Sankou High School.
Apparently, they've got
a stellar cleanup hitter.
[TOUMA]
Sankou High School.
Why does that
name sound familiar?
[SOUICHIROU] I think it's 'cause
that's who Mita from Toushu
played in his debut match.
[TOUMA] No, I know it from
something before that.
[SOUICHIROU] Back in the day,
they made it to Koshien
two years in a row.
[TOUMA]
No, even before that.
It was something to
do with Meisei High.
[SOUICHIROU] Next time:
"He Reminds Me of Someone!"
[TOUMA] I remember! That one
game from 30 years ago!
[PUNCH barks]