[NARRATOR] It's the first
game of the semifinals
in the East Tokyo Tournament.
A trip to Koshien's on the line.
[NARRATOR] Meisei High School
versus Toushu High School.
This game has everyone on
the edge of their seats.
Who will win in the end?
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[CROWD cheers]
[MORI] Meisei High School's
tenth-grade pitcher,
Touma Tachibana.
[TOUMA grunts]
[MORI] And here is tenth-grade
catcher, Souichirou Tachibana.
Fun fact, he and his brother
Touma share a birthday.
[HYOURI] I see,
that's pretty interesting.
Like hot springs're
known for eggs,
Meisei is known for twins.
That's just how it is, you know?
[MORI growls]
Well, as I'm sure
the majority of our viewers
are already aware,
these two aren't actually
fully biological brothers.
They're not?
[MORI] It's the second
marriage for both parents.
While that in and
of itself isn't
anything particularly unusual.
But considering the fact that
both boys happened to be
born on the same day,
you get a sense that it was
all meant to be somehow.
Sounds like a novel.
Meant to be, huh? Oh, well.
Hey, speaking of birthdays,
I was born on the same day
--as the famous Hachiro--
--[bat clangs]
And he hits the fourth
pitch but it's a soft hit,
not very promising.
Right fielder, Koma, runs in
and makes the catch.
--One out.
--[CROWD cheers]
[squeals, laughs]
[TSUKIKAGE]
Hmm.
[TSUKIKAGE] Oh. So you
weren't joking, after all.
[MAYUMI]
Sorry?
[MORI] With one out, Mita, ninth
up to bat, connects ball to bat.
And it splits the
outfield defense.
That's a double.
The first extra-base
hit of the game
goes to Toushu pitcher Mita,
the team's star.
That's one out,
runner on second.
[SOUICHIROU]
I see what's up.
Your plan is to force him
to run around the bases
in order to tire him out, right?
I can't that say I'm impressed.
Come on, gimme a break.
I lost control of the pitch
and it drifted a little high.
First time this game!
So, listen!
From here on out, you
better include any mistakes
I might make in
your calculations.
You're not the boss of me.
[SOUICHIROU]
Keep your guard up.
What?
Let's avoid getting
a runner on third
when we only have one out.
I get it.
Why are you so worried?
It's not gonna happen.
[OTOMI]
Really? Are you sure?
[TOUMA]
Come to think of it...
[SOUICHIROU]
Seriously?
[MORI gasps]
He's running!
[MAEDA gasps]
[MORI]
Is the pitch out?
[gasping]
--[PLATE UMPIRE 22A] Out!
--[MORI] Outta there!
Mita had a great lead for
the steal, but gets tagged out
in a close play. The Meisei
battery read that one well.
You gotta be kidding me!
That pitcher is still throwing
in the scorching heat!
And there's no way anybody
could have known that Mita
was gonna try to steal third!
That was nothing but
a buncha dumb luck.
Did you give the signal?
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
Surprising, isn't it?
[bat clangs]
[TOUSHU MANAGER] One run on
this flyball to the outfield.
That was the plan.
[MITA]
I'm sorry.
I was one 100% certain
that I could make it.
Yeah, and I was 200% sure
you'd be safe, too, as soon
you made a break for third.
Jeez. Did these
Meisei kids know?
You're fast, but...
We've kept that a secret.
Well. There shouldn't
be anything down
in the record books about it.
Not since I came to
this school, anyway.
[SOUICHIROU]
That was too close for comfort.
Who would've thought
he'd make a break for it?
I was joking about running him.
Shoulda kept my mouth shut.
Yeah, you're right.
Wha...? Did something
tip you off?
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
[OTOMI]
Really? Are you sure?
[TOUMA]
I'm not making it up.
I can't beat him on a
straightaway, but when it comes
to rounding the bases,
I'm way faster than Sou.
[OTOMI]
Because Sou insists everybody
keep it straight and narrow.
[TOUMA]
Gimme a break.
[OTOMI]
Come to think of it,
Arisa was bragging about that.
She said that when her brother
was back in grade school,
he was known more
for his running speed
than playing baseball.
[OTOMI] He was a hero
on every sports day.
[TOUMA]
Call it a wild hunch. 'Kay?
[NISHIMURA]
This isn't like Toushu at all.
They should play like
they've already won this thing.
What are they so afraid of?
I don't know,
but the longer this goes,
the more likely it is for
Meisei to show their weakness.
Toushu has no real reason
to be worried about them.
Well, that is,
if they don't get in their heads
and start thinking
about what's up next.
The final game.
[MITA pants]
[TADASHI] He seems to
be breathing heavier now.
[TADASHI]
Heh!
The perfect time to crush him!
[gasps]
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Ball!
[MORI] And he walked him!
That's unusual.
Mita, known for his control,
just walked the batter
on the fourth pitch.
Could it be that running
that double and then
stealing third is taking
a toll on his stamina?
[HYOURI]
I'd say so.
Baseball fans may talk about
this kid like he's a monster,
but, regardless,
at the end of the day,
he is still human.
I'd say so. This is
a great opportunity for Meisei.
Don't you think
that walk seemed
suspiciously easy, though?
He didn't have enough
time to recover from
that sprint around the bases.
Tou planned that?
Think so.
[MITA pants]
[gasps]
[TOUMA] What happened
to all that heavy breathing?
[TOUMA grunts]
[NANGOU grunts]
[MORI]
Impressive!
[ALL gasping]
[MORI] Mita's just
struck out the side again!
[CROWD cheers]
[ISAMI]
Hmm...
Man, that guy... is a monster.
[TOUMA pants]
[ANNOUNCER 22A] Batting fifth,
first baseman, Fukabori.
[TOUMA]
Hm?
Oh, boy..
Guess the heat made me
lightheaded and I checked out.
What is going on?
[MORI]
Runners on the corners, one out.
Bottom of seventh, and Toushu is
poised to score the first run.
After the first out,
the second baseman
was late covering
a ball hit right at him.
Followed by a lapse in defense
when the centerfielder misjudged
the ball and let it slip.
Meisei High School now
finds themselves in a jam.
You can't help but
feel a little bit sorry
for ace pitcher Touma Tachibana.
[HYOURI] Nonsense. Toushu's
just been hitting well,
including that line drive
to third by Sakai.
So, no. I don't feel sorry
for Tachibana in the least.
Plus, it's kind of
to be expected,
when you think about it.
We are going through the lineup
for a third time, after all.
The batters are showing
what they're made of now.
[MORI grunts]
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
These guys're getting tenser
with every inning.
Infielders, outfielders,
the whole lot of them
are feeling the pressure.
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
It's an important game,
in front of such a big crowd.
Plus, the way it's
played out so far?
It's not surprising
they'd be feeling that way,
green as they are.
[TOUSHU TEAM 23B]
A squeeze bunt?
[TOUSHU MANAGER] Don't be silly.
That's our cleanup hitter.
He's had time to get
a bead on the kid's pitches.
Tachibana's exhausted.
His pitches are losing
speed and movement fast.
[TOUMA pants]
We'll crush him
and then take command
of the game!
--[MITA] Well, we'd better.
--Huh?
Because, as far as I remember,
if he gets over this hump.
He'll come back to life,
get a second wind.
I'll be the first
to admit my mistake.
I never imagined we'd have so
much trouble against these guys.
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Foul!
[MORI]
Fukabori, batting fifth,
hits for the fences
on the first pitch.
[HYOURI]
He's looking great!
Seems like he's
figured out the timing.
[sighs]
So hot.
[SOUICHIROU]
Get us out of this, Touma.
A run right now
would be a fatal blow.
[TOUMA grunts]
[SOUICHIROU] Well, you'll never
do it with a pitch like that!
[MORI]
Fukabori hits it square on!
A loud crack as the ball
connects, and the ball...
...finds its way right
into Tachibana's glove!
[CROWD cheers]
[MORI] What's this? The runner
gets caught off base!
All right!
[gasping]
[MAYUMI]
Did he...?
That's a double play.
[MAYUMI]
Hmm...?
It's fine, you can celebrate.
Oh! Oh, great,
that's what I thought!
Yay! [laughs]
[MORI] Toushu High was
still unable to score.
One out, runners
on first and third.
Touma Tachibana was
able to wiggle out of
quite a tight spot!
I gotta admit,
he navigated that
exceptionally well.
He should be proud of
the way he's pitching today.
The East Tokyo
Tournament, folks.
The Semifinals, game one,
top of the eighth,
and we're still scoreless.
I'm sorry.
That's baseball. No sweat.
[MORI] Most people probably
assumed this matchup would be
a one-sided affair,
favoring Toushu,
but we've been treated to
a masterful pitchers' duel.
[MORI] I'm sure seeing the
Meisei uniform brings back
memories for longtime fans
of high school baseball.
It's been more than
three decades since
that magic national
championship year.
Can this Meisei team perform
a miracle of their own?
Maybe, but...
[MORI]
At this point in the game,
Mita's pitches seem to have
gotten even more powerful!
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Three outs! Change!
[CROWD applauds]
[ISAMI]
It's only a matter of time.
Their luck's about to
run out, oh, I can feel it.
The way Mita's pitching today?
I can't see this lineup scoring
any runs against him.
[bat clangs]
[grunts, gasps]
[BASE UMPIRE 22A]
Safe!
To tell ya the truth,
this team should never have
made it this far in
the tournament at all.
[ISAMI] It's clear
he's reached his limit.
[TOUMA patns]
[ISAMI]
Yep. A matter of time.
Right. We better get
back to the others now.
Time to go.
[NISHIMURA]
Hmm...
[TOUMA grunts]
--[bat clangs]
--[SOUICHIROU gasps]
--[MAEDA grunts]
--[MORI] What's this?
A well-hit ball, right
between first and second,
somehow nails the runner
right on the foot!
And they call him out!
That's what I call a lucky
break for Meisei High School!
--[NISHIMURA] Hmph.
--[TOUMA pants]
[NISHIMURA]
Only a matter of time, is it?
[TOUMA panting]
[ARISA] You finally decided
to sit and watch the game.
--Huh?
--[ARISA] Over here.
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
--[CROWD applauds]
--[TOUMA pants]
Wait... I think...
With that out, the first
game of the semifinals
is going into extra innings!
Extra innings?
[SEINAN TEAM 23B]
That's ridiculous!
You kidding me? No way.
[MITA]
Maeda. Koga.
Play your defense
farther forward.
I won't let them hit
anything through the infield.
So, you shouldn't either.
Not off weak hits.
[BOTH]
Right!
Um, don't you think
we should change pitchers?
This is a first for me.
I've never seen Mita this happy
to be heading out on the mound.
[AKAI] You're sitting
in the neutral seats.
[ARISA] Because I'm not
a Meisei High student.
I go to the junior high, so...
[AKAI] I thought you didn't
even like baseball.
Change your mind?
[ARISA]
He's been hounding me.
My brother. I got
tired of hearing him.
And he insisted
I come watch this game.
He says it might be his last
one as a high school pitcher.
[AKAI] Was he joking?
Doesn't seem like the type.
What makes you say that?
[MITA grunts]
[MORI] Wow! Mita has just
thrown his fastest pitch yet!
[HARUKA] How are we supposed to
score against a beast like that?
Beats me. I have absolutely
no clue whatsoever.
None.
[HARUKA] Okay, but that's
nothing to cry about, jeez.
[OOYAMA]
Have you forgotten?
Every year in front of the TV,
even if it was a game between
two teams I didn't know,
no matter how lopsided
the score might be...
...I would always cry when
I'd hear the siren signaling
the end of the game.
Getting to see a game
like this up close?
It's over. Niagra Falls.
[sobs]
Yeah, but the game isn't
finished yet, you know!
[OOYAMA]
Souichirou. I'm replacing Touma.
My lack of preparation
is to blame.
I was happy just being hired to
coach my old high school team.
I was in over my head.
I came in without
a firm grasp of the strengths
and temperaments
of all the players.
I owe the seniors
a huge apology.
I wanted a competitive team.
Next year, and the one after,
so I neglected you guys.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
That was the right call.
If we keep going like this,
we'll just be waiting
for Touma to burn out.
Hmm?
Where is he?
[SOUICHIROU] He's on the
mound, getting warmed up.
But he's way past
his limit. Isn't he?
[SOUICHIROU]
Yeah. But, from what I can see,
he may have just leveled up.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm?
--[SOUICHIROU] Manager.
--Ah?
Please, sir. Leave Touma to me.
He's not about
to break down yet.
Thanks to Mita
raising the bar consistently
out there, before
we even knew it,
Touma was playing
beyond his limits
and getting better
in the process.
I need you to trust me.
I promise you.
I'll throw in the towel
before he breaks down.
One, two, and...
Three! Strikes.
[MORI] That's 20! Monster Hiroki
is a thing to be feared!
[CROWD cheers]
We've got to respond with
that kind of pitching.
[MORI] Meisei High School
was still unable to score
in the top of the tenth inning.
Now Toushu hopes to
score in the bottom half.
And if they can,
the game ends there,
and they'll earn
a spot in the final.
After pitching nine innings.
Meisei High School's tenth
grade ace, Touma Tachibana,
heads back out to
the mound once again.
Just checking the stats.
Apparently, it's been three
years since the last time
a single pitcher kept Toushu
from scoring through
nine innings in
an official game.
So, I'll ask you one more time.
What're some of Tachibana's
good qualities as a pitcher?
Wha--?! Gimme a second.
Let's see, good qualities.
Uh, his sparkling
personality, maybe?
Look, my editor
told me to just ignore
deadlines and stuff, so...
Huh...?
Now. Touma turns to his team.
It seems like he's trying to get
them pumped up or something.
[TOUMA] Mix the anime is
playing on TV to great reviews!
Are we sure he
hasn't broken down?
Because...
[MORI] Wow. Tachibana also
throws his fastest pitch today.
But it misses, slightly,
and he walks the batter.
I don't know what
to feel right now.
Should I be glad or worried?
For the time being...
...let's settle for surprised.
[MORI]
They've got runners on base.
And they've moved them
into scoring position!
[sighs]
[MORI]
Here's the pitch.
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Out!
[MORI] The Meisei battery won't
let them get that next hit!
When we played,
you were the only one who was
able to score runs against me.
[AKAI]
Hmm.
[ARISA]
What's so funny?
[AKAI] Don't you feel anything?
Watching your brother pitch?
Before he started
playing baseball,
we were inseparable.
Everyone talked about it.
How well we used to get along.
Unlike you and
your brother, right?
[AKAI] Speaking of which...
Is Ryou here?
Cheering Meisei on?
[ARISA] The soccer team
is at a training camp.
You didn't even know that?
[ARISA] All he ever does
these days is play baseball.
You know at first,
my parents used to tell him
to hang out with me.
They said we were supposed
to spend time together.
[TAKESHITA grunts]
[MITA'S MOTHER] Whoo! That's
another strikeout, Darling!
[laughs] Dear, you should
maybe calm down a bit.
Hiroki! You're doing great!
But ever since they
realized how much potential
he has, they've been nuts.
And they say, "Don't
get in the way of his practice!"
Or, "Stay out of trouble!
You wouldn't want to
embarrass your brother!"
I've lost all of the
freedom I used to enjoy.
[AKAI] That's why he
wants you to watch him.
Huh?
Hiroki.
[HYOURI]
This sure has been a long one.
Who would've expected that, ah?
[MORI]
That's extra innings for ya.
[SOUICHIROU]
Next time, on Mix.
[OTOMI]
We're in extra innings now!
[HARUKA] We could have
up to 15 of those!
[TOUMA]
I'll be fine.
[HARUKA]
Even in this heat?
[OTOMI] He's reached the limits
of his physical strength!
[SOUICHIROU]
He'll be fine!
[OTOMI] How much longer
is this game gonna last?
[HARUKA] Will they tie
and have to play a rematch?
[TOUMA] We're gonna
finish this here for sure!
[HARUKA] How can you say
that with such certainty?
[OTOMI]
Yeah! How?
[SOUICHIROU]
Well, because...
[TOUMA]
Next time! The final episode!
"Don't You Think They're Alike?"
[HARUKA, OTOMI]
Interesting.
[PUNCH barks]