[PLAYERS whooping]
Oh, wow! They're
playing a baseball game!
[EISUKE]
Who's on the mound?
[laughs]
Hey! Touma's throwing.
What are the odds?
[EISUKE]
Hmm?
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
Oh, hi! What a nice surprise!
You're home early.
[EISUKE]
Yeah. But because I left early,
I saw something
I'd rather not've.
Dare I ask what it was?
[EISUKE] I caught a baseball
club practice game.
Oh. I heard all
the cheering and wondered
what was going on over there.
Makes sense they're
playing a ball game.
[EISUKE] Touma's throwing,
if you can believe it.
[MAYUMI]
What?! That's wonderful!
And he's only in tenth grade!
That no-good Ooyama--
he's doing this so he can
hold it over my head.
Now I get all that "rumors
don't do him justice" crap.
Shameless flatterer.
He's thinking
it's a way to mooch
a few beers offa me.
[growls
We'll see about that.
I'm gonna drink every damn
beer in the house before
that freeloader gets here.
That'll show him!
[MAYUMI]
Hey, calm down!
Judging by the crowd noise,
the game was, uh...
Ah, yeah. We're losing, bad.
Five to nothing in the fifth.
At this rate, it's all over.
They'll score more runs.
[MAYUMI]
Who are they playing against?
Huh? I think...
Toushu!
Really? Who's that?
You serious?
They're only one of the best
high school teams
in all of Japan!
They made it
to the quarterfinals
in last summer's Koshien!
And they've got this amazing
pitcher named Hiroki Mita!
They got totally robbed
in the spring tournament,
but they are definitely
the favorite to win
the whole thing this summer!
Oh, man!
[gasps]
[sighs]
That team!
Ha! No wonder!
[MAYUMI]
Hmm...?
[PLAYERS yellin]
[EISUKE] It's them,
for sure! Toushu High!
And, of course,
the normal starters.
That's him. Their ace...
[NARRATOR]
All right, on that note,
let's get back to the
practice game, shall we?
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
[PLAYER 09A grunts]
[UMPIRE 08B]
Out!
Well, I'll be. Nice play, kid.
Oh, no. If only first base had
just been a little bit closer.
Too bad for Meisei.
[ICHIBAN growls]
[UMPIRE 08A]
Strike three! Batter's out!
[TOUMA groans softly]
How about that last pitch, huh?
Fastest he's thrown all day.
I know. Pitching like
that against a tenth grader?
Seems kind of immature, right?
[ICHIBAN]
Five to nothing.
--So, um, Miss Tachibana?
--[OTOMI] Hmm?
You know those rare games where
not a single player
gets on base?
Remind me what
those are called again?
All you need to know
is baseball games
have nine innings,
and patience is a virtue.
Hey. Isn't that right?
[ICHIBAN sighs] To be honest...
I wouldn't be too surprised
if we did give up
a perfect game today.
That Hiroki Mita's a beast.
--[bat clangs]
--[PLAYERS gasping]
[UMPIRE 08B]
Out!
[ICHIBAN] I'm amazed
by something else, too.
[UMPIRE 08A]
Strike three! Batter's out!
[TOUMA grunts]
He's out!
This whole time...
...he's been shutting them down.
He only gave up that one, weak
hit against Toushu's lineup!
Obviously, a tenth-grade
pitcher is big news,
he's surprising everyone!
[YONEYAMA] What's going
on out there, Manager?
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
Hmm?
I'm Yoneyama, the club advisor.
Oh, of course.
I appreciate your help.
So, why can't they get any hits?
There were tons of pitchers
as good or as better
than this kid at
Koshien, you know?
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
You're right about that.
[YONEYAMA]
Why, then?
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
We can get hits.
If they'd settle on a few
pitches, we'd adjust.
[YONEYAMA]
Hmm?
[TOUSHU MANAGER] He won't let
us sit on any particular pitch.
That catcher, I mean.
[sighs]
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
[OOYAMA grunts]
[OOYAMA]
Koma! Nangou!
You're pinch hitting!
Both of you,
get out there and hit
like your life depends on it!
[KOMA, NANGOU]
Yessir!
Looks like the manager's playing
the lottery with us.
Wow, seems risky.
[SOUICHIROU] If we're
not getting hits anyway,
at least playing the
lottery lets us keep...
--[bat clangs]
--[PLAYERS murmuring]
...dreaming?
[GROUP gasps]
[PLAYERS gaspin]
[UMPIRE 08B]
Out!
[KOMA groans] How's that?
I hit it farther than anyone.
Higher, yes.
If the wind had picked up,
it would've been
carried outta the park.
Yeah, whatever, dude.
If the wind had picked up
enough to do that,
it would've blown down
the outfield fences.
[bat clangs]
[UMPIRE 08A]
Foul!
[gasping]
[NANGOU growls]
Hey, that was
actually a decent hit.
Yeah. Although, based on
where it was thrown,
the only way that
could've gone was foul.
Hopefully, he won't start
swinging at just anything.
We'll see.
[MITA gasps]
[gasping]
[UMPIRE 08B]
Out!
[BOTH]
Man! [growling]
[NANGOU sighs]
He could be
a tough guy to deal with.
That's good.
You're right, even though
he's a power hitter,
he uses his brain, unlike some
other power hitters I know.
Oh? Who ya mean?
[BOTH gasp]
[HARUKA]
Hey, Otomi!
[ICHIBAN]
Hmm?
Hi, friend!
How's it going out there?
The seventh inning just ended!
It's not going well--
we're losing five to zero!
What? Wait, isn't
Touma pitching, though?
He gave up five runs?
[OTOMI] No! Since the moment
Tou went out onto the mound
in the third inning,
they've only gotten one
sad, pathetic, hit!
And they definitely haven't been
able to score another run!
Ah, that makes more sense.
I was scared something
was wrong with him.
[TEACHER 07A]
Miss Ooyama!
Practice isn't over,
get back in here!
Oopsie. I'll see you later.
Bye, Otomi!
--[OTOMI giggles]
--Whoa, who's that?
She's so hot.
Haruka Ooyama.
Her dad's the manager of the
high school baseball team.
Oh, I see. Hey, wait a minute--
does she have any idea what's
going on out on the field?
What do you mean?
You told her that Meisei
hadn't scored at all yet,
and she acted like that was
a totally normal occurrence!
Does she have any idea
what kind of lineup
Touma is pitching against?
[OTOMI]
Good question.
[PLAYERS]
[SOUICHIROU] He doesn't have
experience playing this long,
so he's starting
to lose velocity.
[SOUICHIROU]
But thanks to all the running,
he's built up lower
body endurance.
He's got a good,
stable foundation.
[SOUICHIROU] It's an old
saying in baseball that,
as long as you can
maintain accuracy,
the ball will always be hit
to the fielder's front side.
[SOUICHIROU]
But, of course...
The pitcher can't be held
responsible for errors.
[SOUICHIROU]
It's all right!
[PLAYER 09B]
[SOUICHIROU] Let's just hope
he can maintain that accuracy.
[UMPIRE 08A]
Out!
[UMPIRE 08B]
Out! Three outs!
Change!
[TADASHI chuckles]
[sighs]
[MITA]
Hmph
[NARRATOR] So... Meisei
seems to be holding their own
against Toushu, but, still...
[PLAYERS whoopin]
[OOYAMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 08A]
Strike three! Batter out!
[NARRATOR] Once again,
it's three up, three down.
I forget: how many
innings are there in a game,
Miss Tachibana?
[OTOMI groans]
[PUNCH barks]
[OTOMI giggles]
[PLAYERS yelling]
[NARRATOR]
So, here we are.
It's the top of
the ninth inning.
Final stages.
[MITA]
What do you think?
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
Hmm?
That kid.
How does his pitching compare
to mine in tenth grade?
Ah. Come on.
It wouldn't really be fair,
stacking a little guy
up against a prodigy like you.
You remember, right?
Your first time
out on the mound?
A practice game like this.
Playing Sankou High School.
[TOUSHU MANAGER] That's right.
They were the team to beat.
At that point, Sankou had been
to Koshien two years running.
But, unfortunately, the game
got rained out after
the seventh inning.
Before there was even a
single point up on the board.
That Sankou lineup had
their hands full with you.
They couldn't get anything going
and you just a tenth grader.
That's when we all knew.
How many hits did they
get against you, you remember?
[MITA]
Two hits.
I still see it,
just like it was yesterday.
The look on that
Sankou manager's face
was really priceless!
[laughs]
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
Atta boy!
[MITA]
That's the second one.
He's only given up
two since he started.
And, you know...
This is his seventh
inning out there, too.
[TOUSHU MANAGER growls]
[PLAYER 09C gasps]
[TOUSHU MANAGER growl]
[gasps]
I also remember
the manager's face.
Looked exactly
like yours does now.
[TOUSHU MANAGER whimpers]
[PLAYER 08A grunts]
[SOUICHIROU]
Five.
Four.
Three.
We got 'em good.
Yeah, heh.
A Double play!
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
Gah! We need a perfect game.
That's what it'll take.
To make these guys forget
all about his great pitching.
To shut 'em out and
make this one a game
these kids will wish
they could forget.
[MITA] That's been
my intention from the start.
My sister. She doesn't
know very much about baseball.
I need to post a record
even she can grasp.
That's the only way
I'm going to impress her.
Whatever it's gonna take,
but I still think it's unfair
for you to compare
this kid to yourself.
[UMPIRE 08A]
Three outs! Change!
[NARRATOR]
Bottom of the ninth inning.
Meisei's last time up at bat.
Now!
You all know this is our last
chance to turn it around!
Who's up?
Huh?
Uh, well, we've only had
three bats in each inning.
So our seventh batter's next.
[OOYAMA] Only three up
in each inning? Gimme that!
Hmm... This. Is. Perfect!
Is he seriously
only noticing that now?
[KOMA]
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Here it is. Our final shot.
[OTOMI]
Seventh, eighth, and ninth!
How did it come to those
three at the exact right time?
Who would've thought!
Such drama! I love it!
First up...
[UMPIRE 08A]
Strike three! Batter's out!
Strike out. And now...
[UMPIRE 08A]
Strike!
Foul!
[UMPIRE 08A]
Strike three! Outta here!
Strike out.
[OTOMI gasps]
[TOUMA] Good to know I can
rely on my older brother.
[SOUICHIROU]
Hmph.
Yeah, just laugh it off.
All right, there's two outs.
Come on, man!
[UMPIRE 08A]
Strike!
[TOUMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 08A]
Strike!
Ugh! This really isn't good.
Here we go!
[UMPIRE 08A]
Batter out! That's game
[PLAYERS cheerin]
[sighs]
So, uh? It's over?
You know him.
Whatever you expect,
he'll do the exact opposite.
Well, yeah, but... I meant...
[OOYAMA]
Hmm...
[SCOREKEEPER 09A]
Manager?
[OOYAMA]
Hmm? Oh.
[gasps]
Good game, boys,
nice hustle out there.
[TOUMA]
What was that about?
His pitching was on fire
in the ninth inning.
[SOUICHIROU]
He was sending a message.
We were surprised by
his skill level already,
right up through
the eighth inning.
You think he was telling us
to give up because, no matter
what, we'll never be
as good as him?
Oh, come on, we both know
it wasn't anything that petty.
Not throwing heat like that.
[TOUMA]
Yeah, you're right.
[MITA]
Where's my sister?
She was--?
Oh, uh...
If you're looking for Arisa,
she said she was headed
over to the junior
high soccer field.
Akai's match was about to start,
and she wanted to watch.
Yeah, she left right
after the eighth inning.
[BOTH gasp]
[growling]
Excuse me?
[BOTH whimper]
Oh, ah... I...
I'm sorry.
[MITA] Hey, this Akai kid, the
one who's on the soccer team.
What's he like?
Well, he's the class
rep, so there's that.
And he's the team captain, too.
He's a great student
and nice to everyone.
He's popular, and pretty
much universally liked.
But, having said that,
he's really handsome,
very sociable, and virtually
faultless across the board.
So, to be honest, all the guys
think he's kinda boring.
Oh, but don't worry,
he's not someone you should
concern yourself with.
I don't think he's interested in
your little sister in the least.
You "don't think
he's interested"?
Please shut up?
Yeah, he may be
so perfect that it's boring,
but I will say he has
great taste in women.
You care to elaborate
on that, buddy?
I guess what
I'm saying is that
your little sister
is kind of a-- [whack]
--Ow, my head!
--Shut your mouth!
[TADASHI]
What are they fighting about?
[MITA]
You take that back!
You're lucky there's
a net between us!
[ICHIBAN]
Her personality sucks!
[OTOMI]
Shut your face!
All right! That was
a good game, pack it up!
[OTOMI] That Mita.
He kinda freaks me out!
He was totally ticked
off by that stupid Natsuno!
The dummy.
If the netting
hadn't been there,
I think that loud mouth would've
gotten himself beat up!
[TOUMA] Too bad Mita
didn't kick his butt.
If Hiroki Mita had gotten
mixed up in a fight like that,
he would've been forced
to quit the team,
which would make
the summer tournament
way more interesting.
--[OTOMI growls]
--[PUNCH barks]
Don't joke around like that.
--[TOUMA] Who's joking?
--Jerk.
[TOUMA]
Come on. I'm only half serious.
[thunk]
--[TOUMA] Ow!
--[PUNCH barks]
Of course you wouldn't
understand a guy
who cares about
his little sister!
I could say the same
thing to you for hitting
your loving brother over
the head with a bucket!
You're right.
My poor brother is no match
for his little sister!
You poor thing, are you okay?
Oh, just shut up!
[PUNCH barks]
Shut that dog up, too!
Really. Can you take
him for a walk already?
[OTOMI]
Fine.
[PUNCH howls]
Be safe! You two
have fun on your walk!
How long do you plan
on wielding that stupid bucket?
[OTOMI chuckles]
[OTOMI]
Hey, Akai!
Ah. Hi, Tachibana!
[RYOU]
Good afternoon to you as well.
What's up with your leg?
Did you get hurt?
[RYOU] Oh. I just sprained
it during the game,
no big deal.
But we still beat those
guys two to nothing.
So, it was worth it.
I had a goal and an assist!
Never mind the game.
I'm more concerned
about your injury!
Don't worry, the school
nurse took a look at it.
She said it isn't serious.
That means nothing!
She says that about everything
just so she doesn't
have to deal with it!
You need to go to the doctor
and get it checked out!
All right, all right!
I'll sleep on it, and if it
still hurts in the morning,
then I'll go have it looked at.
[OTOMI]
No way! We're going right now!
Come on. I'll push
your bike for you.
Uh, okay. I guess.
[OTOMI]
Now, then, you get on the back.
[RYOU] We can't both ride,
that's not safe!
I'm just gonna push it for you.
It's fine, don't worry.
I'm kinda heavy, though.
[OTOMI]
Stop fussing and get on.
We've gotta get
that leg looked at.
[RYOU]
Yes, ma'am.
[OTOMI]
'Bye! I'll see you later!
[RYOU]
Nice to meet you!
[OTOMI]
Ready? Hold on tight!
[RYOU yelps]
Well, Punch.
At least we're covered if
you make a big poopums.
--Let's go.
--[PUNCH barks]
[OTOMI]
Next time, on Mix.
[HARUKA]
Ugh.
[OTOMI]
What's wrong, Haruka?
[HARUKA] I was thinking
of going out next Saturday,
but getting where I want to
go is kind of an epic journey.
[OTOMI]
How far away are you going?
[HARUKA] It's two hours by
train, with three transfers.
Then a two-hour walk
from the station.
Then over a mountain, through
a valley, and you're there.
[OTOMI]
Where in the world...?
Next time:
"Just a Walk."
I'm dying to know
where she's going!
[PUNCH barks]