[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[phone rings]
[MAYUMI]
Otomi! There's a call for you!
[OTOMI]
'Kay, thanks!
[jingle plays]
[OTOMI]
Hello? Oh.
Yeah.
Sure! Got it!
[NISHIMURA]
Whatever!
I can't believe his stupid face
is all over that article!
Why aren't you more upset?
This is exactly what
I was telling you about!
A reference record by
itself is not good enough!
They got that
coverage for a reason.
People love a comeback.
The public never gave them
the time of day before this.
Not that battery,
or even Meisei itself.
That's why they're so appealing.
You don't say? I get it now!
So, if I pulled the same thing,
no one would be surprised
because they expect
me to be that great!
[ISAMI]
Oh, yeah, sure.
[NISHIMURA]
Uhh...
[ISAMI] At this point,
there's only one person
who wouldn't surprise anyone,
and that's Hiroki Mita
of Toushu.
Throw me a bone.
You should know me
better than that.
I'm the type of person
who performs better
with positive reinforcement.
Meaning... You want me to stroke
your ego so you can
feel better. Right?
[NISHIMURA growls]
[ISAMI] I know that feeling.
I am the same way, after all.
Point taken.
We're related, yeah, but
we're not exactly the same.
We share some qualities.
Being similar doesn't mean we're
identical in every single way.
[ISAMI] Well... I hope so.
For your sake.
For example...
You're way too old-school to
know how to use one of these.
[ISAMI]
Hmm?
Speaking of!
I'm gonna use it to give Otomi
a call and congratulate her!
Heh, heh! Now, let's see...
What was her number again?
[ISAMI]
In our next life,
I'll make sure to live
next door to you!
[ISAMI]
Then we can always be friends!
And then, 30 years pass. Huh.
[NISHIMURA]
Really? She went out?
But I thought she had the day
off 'cause of Foundation Day.
Heh. Of course I know about it.
I looked it up on the Internet!
Hm? Nah. Nah, that's
not creepy at all!
It's totally normal nowadays!
But, uh, never mind that.
Who did Otomi go out with?
Huh? What do you mean "that
isn't any of my business"?
Ha! C'mon, man! Wait, hello?
We might not be the same,
but we're pretty damn close.
[NISHIMURA]
Hmm?
[NARRATOR]
It's a rainy Foundation Day.
[MEISEI TEAM grunting]
[OOYAMA] The schedule
getting pushed back a day
was a big help.
Especially for Touma.
Is that your plan
until the finals?
You're using Touma
as the only pitcher?
[OOYAMA] Well, ideally, if we
could win with the mercy rule,
it would cut down on the innings
he would need to pitch.
But we don't have the
offense needed on our team
to support that. It's fine.
We'll just go as far
as we can-- Huh?
You said "finals"?
[HARUKA]
Mm-hmm. I sure did.
Hang on.
You don't actually think
we'll make it that far?
I do.
Seriously?
But it's only been four months
since I became the manager!
I think you're getting
ahead of yourself!
I guess you have a point.
If we wanna keep on winning,
we can't rely on
your management skills. So...
That's not what matters!
We need to focus on
what's important right now!
[HARUKA]
But this is important!
You're supposed to be
a leader, right, Dad?
Well, this is your chance
to show Mom how great
of a leader you are!
You put in all that effort
when you were the coach,
but she never came
to see a single game!
She just doesn't get it!
But I know how much
you really care!
[OOYAMA sighs] No, that's not
the problem. She gets it.
[gasps]
She saw how committed
I was to baseball.
I was just following my passion.
But that led to empty bank
accounts and a neglected family.
Guess that made me
a pretty lousy father.
Doesn't that bother you at all?
I don't have time
to be bothered!
I'm too preoccupied with living
my dream as Meisei's manager!
[HARUKA]
That's not it.
Huh?
I'm pretty sure your dream
is to take Meisei back
to the Koshien again! Isn't it?
Oh. Yeah.
You're right about that.
Almost forgot about the Koshien.
I wonder.
What's up?
[HARUKA] Are you actually
a "great leader"?
I guess?
You did put in a lot of
time and effort as a coach,
but all you did was turn
a mediocre baseball team
into an ordinary one.
Sure, the club members
liked you and everything,
but they treated you more like
a friend instead of a coach
they actually respected.
Yeah, and?
How were you able to
become Meisei's manager
in the first place?
[OOYAMA]
Uh... Well...
Did you get a special
referral from someone?
No, I didn't.
Maybe nobody
else wanted the job.
Hold on!
[HARUKA] Did they pull your
name out of a hat or something?
[OOYAMA]
That's enough outta you!
--[PUNCH whines]
--[telephone rings]
[OTOMI]
I'll be back later!
[MAYUMI]
Otomi! There's a call for you!
[AKAI]
You're in the way.
[ARISA gasps]
It's you again.
Is Ryou not home?
Well. I haven't
been able to check
if he's there,
so I have no idea.
What do you want?
I promised Ryou that
I would let him borrow
one of my books to read.
I was planning on giving it
to him at school tomorrow.
But then, I just happened
to be in the area.
[AKAI] You really have
nothing better to do?
[ARISA]
Wh-- Ugh!
[AKAI]
Hey! Ryou!
It looks like he's not home.
[ARISA] Okay. Guess I'll
get going, then.
[AKAI]
Hey!
Hold on.
You said that you were one of
Ryou's classmates, didn't you?
Yeah, I did. So what?
Then that must mean
you go to Meisei, too.
Obviously.
[AKAI] So, why are you
wearing a jacket that says
"Toushu High School" on it?
[ARISA]
Oh, this?
I didn't want one of my
own jackets to get soaked
in the pouring rain.
That's why I borrowed
this one from my brother.
It's your brother's?
Tell me again.
What?
Tell me your name.
Why do you care?
It's Mita.
Mita.
[AKAI]
Wait.
Huh?
Come inside for some tea.
Okay?
[TOUMA pants]
[TOUMA sighs] Man, the rain
started coming down
super hard outta nowhere!
And that's exactly
why I told you
to do your laps in the gym.
I don't like exercising indoors.
It just doesn't feel the same.
[TOUMA gasps]
[SOUICHIROU]
What's up?
[TOUMA] Ah, dang it. I don't
have a change of clothes.
You've gotta be kidding me.
All right, fine.
I'll call Otomi and have her
bring you something from home.
[phone rings]
[MAYUMI]
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Hello?
[SOUICHIROU]
She went out?
Mm-hmm. Okay. Got it.
She said to go get it yourself.
Aww...
[SOUICHIROU]
It's not a big deal.
We live across the street.
Did Mom just say
Otomi's not home?
[SOUICHIROU] Yeah. Apparently,
she left in the morning.
[TOUMA] What could she be
doing in the kind of weather?
Apparently, she's on a date.
What? But it's raining.
[SOUICHIROU]
She can still go on a date.
[TOUMA]
But the rain's really bad.
[SOUICHIROU]
Doesn't seem to matter.
[NARRATOR]
It's a rainy Foundation Day.
In the afternoon.
[pins clattering]
[gasps]
[thunder rumbles]
[TOUMA]
Was that thunder?
Yeah. I heard it, too.
Sounded far.
I'm goin' for it.
I was jogging in
the rain earlier,
so running home should be fine.
Do you wanna call first?
Nah, I'll be okay.
I have a key with me.
I meant, call Otomi first.
[TOUMA]
I wouldn't bother.
She might resent us if we try
to meddle in her business!
[thunder cracks]
Whoa. Better hurry.
[pins crashing]
[RYOU growls]
Yikes. That's rough.
Tch!
Stop it with that grumpy face!
It's supposed to be fun!
So, just try to relax!
I am not grumpy.
That's just how my face is.
[ICHIBAN]
Huh?! A seven-ten split!
Hmm!
[chuckles]
Here ya go! I got you a drink!
Oh? Thank you.
Hurry and bowl your
second ball already!
[RYOU]
Hmph!
[ICHIBAN] That's a good
representation of the distance
between you and Otomi.
You can try as hard as you want,
but it's never gonna work out!
[laughs]
Uh!
[gasps]
So close!
Way too close!
[growls]
[ICHIBAN]
All righty! It's my turn!
Watch closely!
This one's for you!
Yeah. Sure.
[RYOU]
What does he think he's doing?
[ICHIBAN]
Let's do this!
[NARRATOR]
Kids, do not do what he's doing.
I'm glad I was able
to get his call before
I left home today.
He asked me if I was planning
to meet up with you later,
so I told him I was!
That's why he tagged along!
Why'd you have
to tell him about this?
It was supposed to be our date!
Uh... Our wha...?
--[pins clatter]
--[BOTH gasp]
All right!
[RYOU gasps]
Come on. Didn't you say
you wanted to go bowling?
I thought you meant
you wanted to go out
and get some exercise together.
So, I figured if
that was the case,
the more the merrier, right?
[pins clatter]
Yeah!
Yay!
But, you...
It took a lot for me
to ask you out.
I was scared you'd say no,
but I finally worked up
the courage to do it.
[ICHIBAN laughs]
Never underestimate
the instincts of
a pitcher like myself!
I'm always gonna be
one move ahead of you,
so you better step it up!
The way I see it,
you're light-years away
from outwitting someone
as clever as me!
But I can let you try.
Hurry and bowl your second ball.
We're waiting.
[ICHIBAN growls]
I already did.
[RYOU]
You left so many pins standing.
I'm the type of pitcher
who mixes things up
and throws to the corners.
Throwing it straight
down the middle
is just too boring for me.
I'm not a normal pitcher, so
don't lump me in with them.
[OTOMI] Well, if that's how you
wanna play, then be my guest.
But I hope you haven't forgotten
that the one who scores
the lowest pays for
the games we bowl.
That's what we all agreed upon.
[laughs]
I didn't forget!
No way!
I'm playing with
a handicap of 20,
so it's a little
different for me.
But while you've been
busy aiming for the corners,
Akai's been catching up
to you bit by bit.
Watch out.
Huh?! No way!
[ICHIBAN] So, if I scored this,
he would have to score that,
--and I'd still win...
--Sorry. I was insensitive.
I'll be more careful.
What?
So close!
I understand that you
wouldn't hurt me intentionally,
and I don't want you to feel
like you're being insensitive.
So don't worry.
There is no need to apologize
to an idiot like me.
This is all my fault.
I jumped to my own conclusions
and I'll do better next time.
Sure, but, uh...
An average girl would've
picked up on that kinda stuff.
I think.
[RYOU] I don't think
you're an average girl.
You don't?
You're special to me.
I just want you to know that.
[OTOMI gasps]
So this is probably
the part where an average girl
would fall for you. I think.
[ICHIBAN]
Okay, I figured it out!
The only way for me to lose
now is if I throw gutters,
and Akai finishes the final
frame with two strikes,
but that won't happen.
Wow, that's impressive!
You calculated that
all in your head?
Naturally.
[OTOMI] Okay, then!
Time to bowl my second ball!
[NARRATOR]
I'll say it one more time--
Definitely do not do
what she's doing.
That there represents
the distance
between me and Otomi.
Nailed it!
[ICHIBAN]
Hmm!
Huh.
[ICHIBAN growls]
Ugh.
Okay! Get ready, Akai!
We'll settle this
at the batting cages!
That is not what we agreed!
[ICHIBAN] It's fine!
He'll have a handicap!
My pitches will be set to 130,
and yours'll be a hundred.
The one who gets the highest
number of clean hits
will be the winner.
And Otomi decides
which hits are clean.
[OTOMI]
Uh?
[ICHIBAN]
How 'bout it?
--You're on.
--[OTOMI] Ah?!
Then it's settled!
No backing out of it now!
Let's hurry up and get going
to those batting cages!
[BOWLING CLERKS, OTOMI]
Huh...?
[TOUMA]
Interesting. Let's see...
Otomi got a call from
Akai a little bit after 9
and he invited her
out to go bowling.
Then, after she was ready to go,
it was around 10:30.
That's right! Those times
all sound correct to me!
And how did she react to that?
[MAYUMI]
Huh?
A. She seemed happy about it.
B. She looked like
she was unwilling.
C. She got so excited,
she was skipping
straight out the door.
[MAYUMI]
Hmm... "A," I guess?
But she only mentioned that
she was going bowling, right?
And she didn't say anything
about it being a date?
[MAYUMI]
That's right.
But still! A date's a date!
I wouldn't say that.
It all depends on how
she interprets it.
If she doesn't realize it's
a date, then it isn't one.
So. To figure out
what she thought, was she--
A. Wearing something
kinda fancy.
B. Dressed normal.
C. Wearing a jersey.
[MAYUMI]
Let's see...
'Kay! I'll be back later!
Well... I'd say she wore
what she normally wears.
That's great.
It was raining,
so I think her outfit
was appropriate.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Rainy day wear, huh?
Oh! I almost
forgot to mention that
she got another phone call
the moment before
she went out the door.
[TOUMA]
Another? From who?
Let's see...
He plays baseball, too.
It's the boy who's also
in Otomi's class.
And he has a funny name.
Ichiban Natsuno?
Right! Him!
That's the boy's name!
[TOUMA] She didn't tell him
what her plans were, did she?
About how she was on her way
to go bowling with Akai?
[MAYUMI]
Yup, she sure did!
She included all the details,
like when and where
they were meeting.
[TOUMA]
Hmm...
[phone rings]
[TOUMA]
Phone's ringing.
[MAYUMI]
I got it!
Tachibana residence!
Hi there, Sou.
Okay, got it.
Message for you!
"Your meetings
are about to start
and they need you
at school. Now".
That's what Souichirou said.
I forgot! I only
came home to get changed!
--[PUNCH whines]
--[TOUMA] See you later!
[MAYUMI]
Goodbye!
Huh?
How was that?
Seemed clean to me!
Yeah, we can count that one.
[bat clangs]
[OTOMI gasps]
[ICHIBAN gulps]
[jingle plays]
So, how many hits does
a home run count for?
That only counts as one!
Bases don't matter!
[ICHIBAN whimpers]
[gasps]
[jingle plays]
[ICHIBAN] I thought this guy
was on the soccer team!
[SOUICHIROU]
Next time, on Mix!
[TOUMA] Eisuke Tachibana:
The head of our household
is a man of many mysteries.
[SOUICHIROU] On the outside,
it seems like
--he's a standard businessman.
--[TOUMA] If that's the case,
how could he have afforded
this house and giant yard?
[SOUICHIROU] He tells us
that he doesn't like to talk
--about his work.
--[TOUMA] So we have no idea
what he does in the day.
But all he does is drink
and sleep in the evening.
[SOUICHIROU] But he's
somehow able to support
a family of four.
[TOUMA]
Next time, "Do You Envy Them?"
[SOUICHIROU]
Yeah, I kinda do.
[PUNCH barks]