[NARRATOR]
East Tokyo Tournament.
Semifinals. Game one.
Meisei versus Toushu.
[STADIUM murmuring]
[MORI] Superstar phenom and
south paw ace Hiroki Mita
of Toushu High is on the mound.
The pro scouts have their
eyes peeled, and, of course,
he hasn't allowed a run yet
in this tournament.
With Mita backed
by a powerful lineup,
Toushu has its heart set on
the national championship.
[NARRATOR]
They're all different.
None of them thinking
the same thought.
[NARRATOR]
Even him?
[NARRATOR] The game
we've all been waiting for
is about to begin!
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Play ball!
[siren blares]
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Strike!
[STADIUM cheers]
[OOYAMA] There is one
saving grace in this game.
Everyone on the team's
already confronted him once.
So, you know what it's
like to face his pitching.
A batter's mentality?
That can evolve after
just one encounter.
He's got fastballs.
And those wicked breaking balls.
We all know exactly what
to expect from this kid.
[MEISEI PLAYER 22A grunts]
[HARUKA whimpers]
See? Just as expected.
He's throwing heat
right from the start today.
Because his manager's got
a plan up his sleeve.
Mita won't pitch the whole game.
They're hoping to get ahead,
and build a lead early on,
then pull him so he can
rest up for the final.
Well, I'll be.
[STADIUM applauds]
[HYOURI] He struck out the side,
folks, and the crowd goes wild
for Mita's phenomenal pitching!
[laughs]
[MORI clears throat]
[HYOURI]
Oh, pardon me.
[HYOURI] Now, here's
where things might start
to get interesting!
I'm sure that inning got
pitcher Tachibana all fired up.
Maybe he'll show
us that famous arm!
Let's see if he lives up
to the rumors! We shall see.
He's all the sports papers
have been talking about since
the tournament began! Uh-huh.
[ANNOUNCER 22A]
Toushu High School is up to bat.
First to go, second
baseman, Maeba.
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
As soon as we get four runs,
you can bow out of
the game, Mita.
That could be as soon
as the next inning. 'Kay?
Have you already forgotten, sir?
In our whole lineup,
no one's ever scored a run
against that pitcher.
[EISUKE grunts]
[OTOMI gasps]
[HYOURI whimpers]
Did this kid...
strike out the side?
[STADIUM cheers]
[TOUSHU MANAGER growls]
Wait a second.
Did he pitch like
this last time?
[MITA] I guess that practice
game was different, after all.
In an official game, everyone
plays better, even them.
In any case, I'll do
my best until we get four runs.
Right, please do.
[MEISEI PLAYER 22B, TOUMA]
Yeah!
[MEISEI PLAYER 22C laughs]
Hey!
Thanks, thanks. And thank you.
[OOYAMA] He's looking great
out there, don't you think?
[SOUICHIROU]
He's totally inconsistent,
even more than usual.
[OOYAMA]
Huh...?
His form and his arm.
They both seem consistent,
but not his fastball velocity.
[OOYAMA]
You think?
Makes his pitches
tough to catch,
but that means they're
even worse to hit.
Yeah...
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Strike three! You're out!
Strike three! He's outta there!
[STADIUM cheers]
But it's not nearly as
bad as facing Mita, right?
Yeah.
[MORI]
That's six strikeouts in a row.
It's odd to see
cool-headed Mita like this.
He's going all out
from the beginning.
Totally overpowering
these Meisei hitters.
[HYOURI]
No way.
He looks no different
now than the Mita
I'm accustomed to seeing.
It just seems that way because
he's facing subpar batters.
If there's anybody
you need to watch,
it's that Tachibana kid, y'know?
Things went well for him
in the start of the game,
but he can't get overconfident.
Especially with the kind
of batters he's facing.
[TANI grunts]
[MORI] Tani, batting fourth
with an aggressive swing.
That one's headed
right for the stands, folks.
I got it.
[HYOURI whimpers]
M-Must have been the wind...
[STADIUM applauds]
[MORI] Nope, there is
no wind out there today.
Ooh! Fukabori, batting fifth,
hits the third pitch
with a ground out to first.
[STADIUM cheers]
[MITA]
Well, he avoided the trap.
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
Hmm?
I was hoping he'd
keep leaning on strikeouts
for a while longer,
but I'd forgotten about
that savvy catcher of theirs.
They're both still only in the
tenth grade, huh? Incredible.
Well, in any case,
I'll continue doing my best
till we get four runs.
Yes, please do.
[HARUKA] He pitched like a
different person in the second.
Yeah, I made
a little deal with him.
I promised him that he could
pitch however he wanted
for the first inning.
If he's not careful,
he'll be tempted
to pitch like that guy, and
then he'd burn out in no time.
There's a big difference
in strength between
a tenth and twelfth grader,
and we're talking about
the legendary Hiroki Mita here.
Isn't that correct Manager?
Hello?
Huh?
[SOUICHIROU] Today is
supposed to be the hottest day
of the year so far.
[SOUICHIROU] The challenge
we face now is how to keep
the pitch count down
so Touma can throw
as many innings as possible.
Isn't that correct Manager?
Hello?
Ah. Oh. Uh, yeah.
That is the truth.
Huh?
Earlier you said,
"There is no plan!
We're going for broke!"
I wonder where the old man
who said that went.
[OOYAMA] Uh. No idea what
you're talking about.
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Foul!
Okay. Right fielder
Koma, batting eighth.
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Foul!
[MITA grunts]
[IMAGAWA] He doesn't seem
too worried about getting
the ball over the plate.
Even if he times
his swing to the fastball
or breaking ball, there's still
a lot of movement on the pitch.
So the batter may make contact,
but it still won't go very far.
On the other hand,
thinking about my pitches...
Are you saying my balls
have no movement?!
What? Nobody's saying that!
What's your deal, man?
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Foul!
At least we have an edge.
We can make the Toushu
lineup hit into outs.
But only because Souichirou's
leadership and your control
can deliver the ball right
where Souichirou wants it.
Our ace in the hole.
Well, that's nice of you to say.
I'm just curious.
Your talent for controlling
the ball when you're not trying
to throw too hard.
Is that natural, or what?
Heck yes!
[MORI]
One meter from the plate,
the catcher picks
it up bare-handed.
[MORI]
That's two outs.
--[GIRLS cheering]
--[MEISEI PLAYERS groan]
All right! How 'bout that, boys?
At least I put a stop to his
run of strikeouts, am I right?
[laughs]
[IMAGAWA]
Hey, Koma, your optimism.
Is that a natural talent?
[KOMA]
Yes?
[MORI]
Three outs. Toushu's up.
[EISUKE]
It's crazy for it to be so hot
this early in the morning.
Yeah, and I bet
it's even worse out there
on the mound.
Yeah. Still,
no matter how hot it gets...
...I would've loved
to take the mound just once,
and wear Meisei's
number one uniform.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I guess that was all
my dad's fault, huh?
[EISUKE laughs]
[STADIUM applauds]
[EISUKE] Is that boy
out there really my son?
[EISUKE] Sou's hardly
even had to move his mitt
to catch Tou's pitches.
I never had the
confidence to maintain control
of my pitches right up
to the end like that.
Maybe it's because
Touma's always had Souichirou
to play catch with,
ever since he was a little kid.
Huh, I wonder.
Although, when they
used to play catch,
it was more like
they were fighting,
throwing the ball as
hard as they could.
In fact, sometimes it
would turn into an actual fight.
When that happened, it'd be
weeks before they played again.
And then, every time...
[EISUKE]
Every time what?
[OTOMI grunts]
[OTOMI pants]
[grunts]
[OTOMI laughs]
[OTOMI grunts]
Want to rest for a bit?
Are you tired?
[OTOMI]
No, I'm all right. Let's play!
C'mon! Throw!
[TOUMA]
Hmm...
[OTOMI laughs]
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Strike!
Your brother can
throw heat, too, I guess.
[SOUICHIROU]
He's just like you, Mita.
Loves his sister more
than anyone in the world.
Always has.
But he and I...
[MITA gasps]
We used to fight
with each other all the time.
[SOUICHIROU]
Where are you trying to throw?!
[TOUMA]
Shut up!
[TSUKIKAGE]
Hmm...
[DRIVER 22A]
What would you like to do?
Get me out of here.
Wait a moment.
Sure.
[BURGLAR 22A]
Quiet... Gotta be quiet...
Huh...?
[BURGLAR 22A]
What a crappy mom.
Her sons are battling it out
on the field with a trip
to the finals on the line.
But she won't even go to
the game to cheer them on?
[BURGLAR 22A] I only came here
'cause I didn't think anyone
would be home--assumed
they'd all be at the stadium.
[BURGLAR 22A] Darn it!
Guess I gotta move to plan B...
[TSUKIKAGE] That won't work.
Do you have a plan C?
[BURGLAR 22A gasps]
Oh, hello, ma'am.
[TSUKIKAGE]
What's going on here? Burglary?
[BURGLAR 22A]
Uh. What if it is?!
[TSUKIKAGE shrieks]
[TSUKIKAGE yells]
[BURGLAR 22A groans]
[BURGLAR 22A yells]
[TSUKIKAGE grunts]
[BURGLAR 22A bellows]
[BURGLAR 22A gasps, screams]
--[blows landing]
--[BURLGAR 22A grunting]
[BURGLAR 22A groans
[MAYUMI]
Ah--
Oh, hello.
This guy tried to rob you.
[MAYUMI] Thank you
so much for helping me
with that horrible man.
I don't know what I would have
done if you hadn't shown up.
It was nothing. Oh, also...
The baseball team
that practices here.
Is today their day off
or something?
Sorry?
[PUNCH snores]
[STADIUM cheers]
[MORI]
Three outs!
And another scoreless inning
for Touma Tachibana.
East Tokyo Tournament
semifinals, game one.
Meisei High School versus
Toushu High School.
After five innings,
the game's still tied 0-0.
[TSUKIKAGE]
So...
To be clear,
this is the semifinals?
That's what the man said!
And, in the
East Tokyo Tournament,
more than a hundred high
schools compete, right?
[MAYUMI]
Yep, that's exactly right.
[TSUKIKAGE]
How can Meisei still be playing?
[MAYUMI]
Who knows?
[KOMA growls]
[MORI] Up to this point,
both teams have only gotten
one real hit.
[laughs]
[HYOURI] They may have
each gotten one hit,
but Toushu's the only one of
the two who cracked it
deep into centerfield. Uh...
Meisei's was a weak hit
that just so happened
to drift over the infielder's
glove by dumb luck.
I mean, really, you can
hardly classify those two things
in the same category.
[KOMA grunts]
There's no denying
that was clean!
--[MORI] Centerfield!
--[STADIUM cheers]
Yeah!
Hold on. What the...?
He didn't even
watch the pitch,
he timed his swing to the
fastball and went for it.
Nice work. I guess.
Of course, if it weren't
for his quick swing,
the results would have
been very different.
[MORI] One crucial man on base
in a tied game with no outs.
So, naturally...
Ah?
[MORI]
No matter what it takes...
...get him in scoring position!
[TANI gasps]
[STADIUM cheering]
[MORI] But that's
easier said than done!
[HYOURI] Yeah, you got
that right. And Mita's not
the kind of pitcher you
can get a sacrifice bunt
against very easily.
[MORI growls]
[HYOURI] Anyway, even if they
get the ball on the ground,
the guys on first and third will
dash in and grab it, no doubt.
I don't know if you're
aware of this, but those two
are great at handling
the ball. Sorry, Meisei!
[ANNOUNCER 22A] Batting second,
second baseman, Murotani.
[OOYAMA] The infielders are
back to their normal positions.
Yeah, that's because
there are two outs.
Question.
Who on our team
is best at bunting?
Be honest.
[IMAGAWA]
I'd say Murotani for sure.
[OOYAMA]
Agreed
[IMAGAWA]
Hmm?
Huh?! Hmm!
But... there are two outs.
[OOYAMA]
Yeah, so what?
[MITA grunts]
[MORI]
Murotani bunts it!
Third baseman, Kaga, wasn't
expecting that and reacts
a little too late getting
his hands on the ball.
But he makes up for it
with a lightning fast play
to first base.
That's the ball
handling I mentioned!
Top notch!
But, unfortunately,
he throws it off the mark,
pulling the first baseman's
foot off the bag!
[BASE UMPIRE 22A]
Safe!
[STADIUM cheers]
[MEISEI PLAYERS chuckling]
[OOYAMA] All right,
who's the most reliable batter
we've got on the team?
[IMAGAWA] Hmph.
Guess that would be me.
I do bat cleanup.
He-he!
[OOYAMA]
Hmm...
[ANNOUNCER 22A]
Batting third--
Catcher, Souichirou Tachibana.
But, Dad, in both
of his at bats so far...
...he's gotten struck out
swinging for the fences.
That is the whole point.
We can count on him here.
[TSUKIKAGE] I'm sure this boy
is popular with the girls.
You're right.
He is my son, after all.
He-he!
Oh...
[gasping]
[PLATE UMPIRE 22A]
Foul!
[STADIUM applauds]
[gasping]
[MORI]
And the crowd here is stunned!
He got all of the ball,
but it just barely drifted
to the right of the foul pole.
The Meisei dugout's
looking frustrated.
Among those expressing
their frustration
is lovely Meisei scorekeeper,
the manager's daughter,
Haruka Ooyama.
I just love her!
That girl is cuter
than a pop idol!
[TSUKIKAGE]
You're right.
She is my daughter, after all.
Huh? So that means...
[TSUKIKAGE]
He's my husband.
[MAYUMI]
Oh, I see.
You've been swinging
for the fences and missing
every time Mita threw
the ball to that spot.
All so you could have
a chance here.
Sorry? Were you
talking to me just now?
[TANI] Hmph. Typical.
An annoying tenth grader.
You can say that again.
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
[MORI] Three outs,
bottom of the inning.
He finally decided to show me
one of the pitches
he's famous for.
[TOUMA]
That's a good thing.
He used up a lot of his
strength throwing that one.
[TSUKIKAGE] And this boy.
He's pretty handsome, as well.
[MAYUMI] You're right.
He's my son, too, after all.
[TSUKIKAGE grunts]
Would you please cut that out?
[MAYUMI]
Hmm?
[SOUICHIROU]
Next time, on Mix.
[TOUMA] We're finally to the
middle innings of the game!
[SOUICHIROU] It's gonna
be hard to get a single run
off that monster.
[TOUMA]
You're right.
[SOUICHIROU]
This is a tense pitchers' duel.
We can't let them score first.
[TOUMA]
You're right.
[SOUICHIROU] Also,
what is with this heat wave?
I'm getting dizzy out there.
[TOUMA]
You're right.
[SOUICHIROU]
Wait! Just like that,
one out with runners
on first and third?
[TOUMA]
Wha--? You're right!
[SOUICHIROU] Next time:
"It's a Matter of Time!"
[TOUMA]
Hey, who's this random guy?
[barks]