[NARRATOR]
A long, long time ago...
...the two kids who were
stranded in the mountains,
unable to get home...
[NARRATOR] ...were saved by the
Seinan High School Team bus.
Or, so the story goes.
Just going for
a walk. That right?
Uh-huh.
So you're saying you're
all the way out here,
alone with a girl, when
it's pitch black outside?
What do you guys want me to say?
We didn't know the bus
wasn't running today,
and we got stranded.
[ISAMI] Then what's your
relationship? You two dating?
We're childhood friends.
[ISAMI]
Mm-hmm.
Hold on! I don't
think that's fair!
We never really knew each other!
[ISAMI]
Childhood friends, huh? I see.
Well, isn't that a nice thought?
Sure, but, I dunno.
Does it count if I can't
remember when we me--?
Oh, shut up! That is so unfair!
I would kill to have
a cute friend like her!
What's unfair about it?
[ISAMI] At Meisei High.
That's practically a tradition.
Uh, what?
Oh, by the way.
Um, Nishimura?
Can I borrow your phone?
It's gotten pretty late,
and I want to call my parents
so they don't worry.
You tellin' me you
don't have a phone?
You're a high-schooler
now, buddy--
no phone means no social life.
[TOUMA]
Shut up.
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
Hello? Tachibana house.
Tou, thank goodness!
Where are you right now?
Huh? Tanuki?
Take out the "Te" and "Ke"?
I don't get it.
Hey, is Haruka with you?
Huh? Uh, yeah she is.
I'll tell you the details later.
I just called to check in,
case you guys were worried.
I should be home
in about an hour or so.
That's your sister, isn't it?
Gimme back my phone!
--[OTOMI] Hmm?
--[TOUMA] Hey!
Hey, Otomi! It's me, Nishimura!
Huh? No. Not
"Shimura," you silly.
Huh? Ikariya? No.
Not that one either.
I'm the 10th grader
from Seinan?
Takumi Nishimura!
All of Japan'll be
talking about me
when the summer Koshien starts.
Y'know, the guy who became
the ace pitcher of Seinan
in his first year
of high school.
So, check it out,
we had an away game today.
I had a shutout of course,
but they got two whole
hits on me!
I know I can do better, but
sometimes the pressure--
--[receiver clicks]
--[beeping]
Huh? Guess we got disconnected.
That's okay,
I'll just call her back.
--[ISAMI] Mita from Toushu, huh?
--What?
[ISAMI] Pitched a perfect game
against you the other day.
[NISHIMURA]
That's weird...
He did.
[TOUMA]
He outclassed us in every way.
We got destroyed.
[ISAMI] Hmm, maybe...
But that's not all.
I also heard you pitched
seven straight innings.
And with you on the mound,
Toushu got zero runs
and only two hits.
Well, you're not wrong,
but it was only a practice game.
[ISAMI]
Oh, and don't you forget it.
The difference
between an official game
and a practice game
is like night and day.
[NISHIMURA] Wait, no!
It says I have service.
Why's is it disconnecting then?
It starts ringing, then, poof!
It sounds like you've been
keeping your eye on them.
Is there any particular
reason for that?
Hah! Just thinking it'd
be nice to face them
at the summer
tournament for a change.
But obviously,
that's just wishful thinking.
Because every year, by the
time we reach the third round,
Meisei High has already
been eliminated.
This year'll be the same.
Don't worry about that.
They won't be
eliminated this time.
[NISHIMURA gasps]
Home... phone?
Because now they've
got Touma Tachibana.
So you'll face them.
As long as you're not
eliminated before then.
Count on it.
[laughs] That's exactly what
a childhood friend would say.
It's like I said!
We never really knew
each other growing up!
[NISHIMURA]
Hello! Otomi? You there?
Hello?!
[PLAYERS murmurin]
[NARRATOR]
Sunday.
[TOUMA grunts]
[NANGOU growls]
What his problem?!
The big guy's got pretty great
bat control, doesn't he?
[TOUMA] I thought I
explained it to you already!
That was just a walk we were
on yesterday, nothing more!
We only got back late because
the busses weren't running--
Oh, crap!
Nan was pretty surprised.
To think, you beat him
to the punch by years.
Well, before he even got
a chance to meet her,
there you were.
I told you already!
I don't remember a single thing
about meeting her as a kid!
I know. I heard
you the first time.
I know exactly how
crappy your memory is.
[TOUMA]
I was three years old! Come on!
All right, we're
switching batters!
[SOUICHIROU]
Okay, it's my turn.
You'd better watch out!
I've got even better bat
control than that guy does.
So, get ready.
[TOUMA groans]
[KOMA chuckles]
Huh? What are you looking
at over there, Koma?
Nothin'. Otomi's just
hanging up some underwear
she washed, so I
thought I'd take
a little peeksie and--
Hey, watch it, pal!
What are you doing?!
That hurts, man!
[TOUMA] I could do a lot more
with this bat if you keep it up!
I get it, I get it! I heard you,
so can you stop swinging
that thing at me, please?
--[glass shattering]
--[RYUUICHI] A burglar!
Watch out! He's got a knife!
Shut up!
Oh, no!
Move it, ya old lady!
[TSUKIKAGE yells]
[BURGLAR 11A grunts]
[BURGLAR 11A rasping]
[TSUKIKAGE] Who are you
calling an "old lady," huh?!
I appreciate it,
but I think that's enough, Miss.
Oh, yeah.
[BURGLAR 11A groans]
[TSUKIKAGE]
Hmph
[door bell rings]
[CAT meows]
[VETERINARIAN 11A]
Seems pretty cut and dry.
He's suffering from
heat exhaustion.
[OTOMI] But it's not even
the hottest time of the year.
[VETERINARIAN 11A]
Then he must be eating too much.
[OTOMI]
What do you mean, "then"?
Can you please just
actually check on him?
He's been looking exhausted
and won't make a sound,
no matter what I do!
[VETERINARIAN 11A]
Not to worry.
When he gets hungry,
he'll start barking.
Based on that belly and
the greedy look on his face,
there's no doubt in my mind!
He's been eating too much!
Okay, we're done here.
[OTOMI]
Gimme a break.
If something bad happens to
Punch, I'm gonna sue that guy.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm?
[HARUKA] It just came out.
I hear it's selling well.
Do I really have to tell you not
to have her over while I'm away?
What's the problem?
It's not like you got
divorced or anything.
You're just not living together.
Yeah, well, she's
the one who wanted
to move out so bad! And you
remember what she said to me?
Seeing my face every day, all
she could write were comedies!
C'mon, Mom's talented!
And that's not all she said.
Remember? She said that if she
didn't pursue her talent,
she'd regret it
for the rest of her life.
And I don't think
that's very responsible
when you're a mother.
All I can really say
is that Mom trusts me.
And she thinks that
as long as I'm around,
she doesn't have
to worry about how
you'll manage while she's gone.
I don't think that's
very responsible
when you're a father!
I have two parents who are
both pursuing their dreams.
I think that's pretty awesome.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm...
[OOYAMA] So, it's selling
well? That's good.
[HARUKA] Seems like she
gets a ton from royalties.
Wait, how do you know that?!
I better not find out you
took any money from her!
[HARUKA]
Don't worry.
She tried to leave money
with me, but I turned it down.
I know you would have
hated if I took it.
[OOYAMA]
Hmph. That's right. Good call.
[OOYAMA] So how much
money we talkin' here?
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[OOYAMA]
Uh... You know what? Never mind.
[TOUMA whimpers]
[TOUMA gulps]
[TOUMA gasps, coughs]
Why are you being so loud?
[coughs] Sorry. I think I got
something caught in my throat.
[coughing]
I'll go gargle some water.
[SOUICHIROU] Or maybe
you could just get Haruka
to throw some soda in your face.
You're not going to let
this go anytime soon, are you?
[SOUICHIROU snores]
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
[PUNCH breathes heavily]
Hey, what are you
still doing up so late?
Punch is still so
quiet. Too quiet.
[PUNCH breathes heavily]
He doesn't feel like barking.
The vet told you not
to worry, didn't he?
So don't worry.
I can't trust that vet--
he's the worst!
He didn't even examine Punch!
[TOUMA]
He's a professional.
At the very least, if Punch was
dying, he would have known.
[OTOMI]
Don't say that!
[TOUMA chuckles]
[TOUMA sighs]
[OTOMI]
I feel bad for not remembering.
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
You know, when my Dad died.
I doubt I understood
what was happening.
Not enough to cry
about it at least.
Apparently, he was
a very kind man.
And Dad, he showered me with
a lot of love and affection.
At least that's
what Mom tells me.
But it's sad, to have
a dad like that pass away,
and not even be
able to cry about it.
I didn't cry, either,
till I got a face full of soda.
[PUNCH whines]
[TOUMA] I guess seeing him this
quiet does worry me a little.
He's usually so loud.
[OTOMI] I know, right?
But that stupid vet was like,
"He just ate too much,
he'll be okay!"
Wait, what?
He said Punch will bark again
once he gets hungry enough,
but it's not like I've been
giving him more
than I usually do!
So you fed him? When?
[OTOMI]
Early evening.
I fed him, too. When I got home.
[OTOMI]
Huh?
His bowl was
empty so I filled it.
[SOUICHIROU] It was empty
when I gave him food, too.
[TOUMA, OTOMI]
Hmm?
Huh?
[stomach growling]
[barks]
[TOUMA]
He'll start barking again
"when he gets hungry enough."
Guess so.
[pants]
Would anyone mind
if I smacked him?
Just a little?
[OTOMI]
I'm going to bed
[PUNCH barks]
[GIRL 06C] Hey,
what are you boys looking at?
Shouldn't you be in class?
Yeah, there it is!
[SOUICHIROU]
What are you so excited about?
You're falling back
into old habits!
I am?
You're opening your body
and releasing
the ball too early.
Show me your form again.
[TOUMA grunts]
Yeah, that's all wrong.
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
There we go!
[sighs]
Good job. Now take a lap.
[TOUMA]
Sure thing.
[OOYAMA]
Souichirou!
[SOUICHIROU]
Huh?
[OOYAMA]
I want you to try pitching.
Okay?
[OOYAMA]
After that summer,
he began to adore Meisei's
number one uniform.
[OOYAMA] His seniors had left
the team the previous autumn,
so Eisuke Tachibana became the
number two starting pitcher.
Not only that,
but the starting pitcher,
Obokata, lost his form and was
having trouble getting it back.
[OOYAMA]
Since it was his senior year
and last summer tournament,
it was the perfect chance
for Eisuke to earn
the number one spot.
That's what you'd think.
[NISHIO]
Well, Tachibana?
You can tell he's
much better, right?
Much better
compared to who, sir?
[NISHIO chuckles]
[laughs] Don't let it
bother you too much, kid.
At the end of the day,
it doesn't matter
what number you are!
So, you're telling me...
that you've made up your mind?
[NISHIO]
Hmm...
How does 11 sound?
Or 12, if you prefer.
[OOYAMA]
Give it up, Tachibana.
He's much better.
[TADASHI]
Hmm?
[TADASHI gasps]
I see Souichirou's throwing with
the same form
and grace as always.
Wait, he pitches, too? Really?
Uh, yeah. Did you
really not know that?
On their team
in elementary school,
he and Touma competed
with each other
over who'd become
the ace pitcher.
He could compete
for the position right now.
If he decided he wanted to.
Yeah.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm...
Why did you give up
on becoming a pitcher?
Rock-paper-scissors.
'Scuse me?
When we started Junior High,
Touma and I decided who'd pitch
with rock-paper-scissors.
You did?
Based on our track
record, I was pretty confident.
I was a shoe in.
But of course, I lost that day.
First time, I think.
He had always lost to me before.
You need that.
What?
That type of extra crazy
strong luck he has.
And you're okay
deciding by pure luck?
[SOUICHIROU] To be honest,
I've always had a disadvantage.
[OOYAMA]
Whaddya mean?
When Touma pitches,
he's got Souichirou Tachibana
catching for him.
And that's just not
possible when I do it.
[OOYAMA]
Huh?
[laughs]
Know what, kid?
I'm startin' to think
I've got that luck, too!
With the two of you
on my team. Amiright?
Rock-paper-scissors.
Shoot.
[KOMA, TADASHi sigh]
[OOYAMA laughs]
[ICHIBAN grunts]
[OTOMI]
Hey, Akai!
[RYOU]
Hmm?
Hi.
Hey, Otomi! You come
to watch me play?
What are you doing?
Don't take your
eyes off the game.
Okay.
He's doing well
out there. Isn't he?
Yeah. When it comes
to playing baseball
he's not just all talk.
You can tell he
loves to practice.
And he studies the
game with passion.
[ICHIBAN grunts]
[OTOMI]
Now that I think about it,
his form is getting
pretty similar.
Huh?
[OTOMI]
To Tou's form, I mean.
Well, everyone learns
from someone.
Tou's form originally
came from Sou.
[RYOU sighs]
Guess your brothers get along.
I'm glad to hear that.
Well, they don't
sugar-coat things,
so they end up
fighting pretty often.
What about you? Any siblings?
[RYOU]
Yeah. I have one older brother.
Hyah!
You're really good
at sports so I gotta ask.
Was playing baseball not an
option for you growing up?
Yeah, you could say that.
Anything but baseball.
Whoa!
[ICHIBAN]
Yo, Akai!
How much longer do you
plan on starin' at me, dude?
Hurry up and get back
to soccer practice already!
Oh, man. He's right,
I should go now.
See ya! Keep it up, Natsuno!
Have a good practice.
[ICHIBAN]
Wha-- Hey, come on!
You don't have to
leave, too, Otomi!
What's that school?
Oh, that's Kenjyou High.
I'm pretty sure it used to
be called Sumi Tech, I think,
but they changed the
name a few years back.
The year Meisei
made it to the Koshien,
this was the team they
faced in the finals.
Different name now but
it's the same school. Huh.
Yeah, and now both teams
are equally uncompetitive.
It's pretty crazy how
much has changed.
[TOUMA]
Would you get outta here?!
[splash]
[TOUMA] What was that?
A big fish or something?
I should get going.
All right "Kenjyou High School."
Let's both do our best.
[NARRATOR] At this point,
all participating schools
still have a chance...
[NARRATOR]
...on the road to Koshien.
[OTOMI]
Next time, on Mix .
Hey, Haruka. What do you
recommend at Ramen Dragon?
[HARUKA]
Gyoza and the special ramen!
[OTOMI] Sounds good! Especially
when it's called "special!"
[HARUKA] Also, our special
tenmen and special dandan !
[OTOMI]
All right, jotting this down.
[HARUKA] And the special
black vinegar ankake
with all the toppings!
[OTOMI]
That sounds incredible.
Next time, "Aren't You
Taking Him Lightly?"
[HARUKA] But the best has
to be our kiriboshi daikon.
[PUNCH barks]