[CROWD cheering]
[BASE UMPIRE]
Fair ball!
[CROWD cheering]
[TOUMA]
How do you explain this?
Every single one
of my borderline pitches
is being called a ball,
and all of their stupid swings
have been turning into hits.
Do you think I used up
all my good luck
in the last game
with that no-hitter?
I dunno about that.
They're not having
a lot of luck, either.
You've been complaining
since the game started,
but they're at four
hits and three walks
and still haven't
managed to score.
They do look pretty frustrated
over there, don't they?
Well, anyway, they don't
have any power hitters.
All they want is
to keep the ball in play.
[SOUICHIROU]
They won't get great hits,
even if you throw it
right down the middle.
Overpower them with
that arm of yours.
[TOUMA]
That's what Haruka said...
At the team meeting
we had, remember?
Uh...
Huh?
What do you mean, "huh"?
Were you even listening to her?
She stood up too fast,
and a button on her
shirt came undone,
so, she had to hold it closed
while she was trying to talk.
[HARUKA sneezes]
[OOYAMA]
Hm? You got a cold?
[HARUKA]
No, I don't think so.
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer,
and now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
This is the story
of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher,
along with their younger sister,
they face life's countless
adventures while
aiming for the top.
The three share one goal--
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[TOUMA grunts]
[CROWD clapping, cheering]
[TADASHI] Y'know what you should
be doin' out there, Touma?
[TOUMA]
Hm?
I've been thinking about it
since the start of this game.
These guys, they haven't got any
real hitters on their lineup,
so, all you've gotta
do is overpower them,
you know?
Oh, you've been
talking to my brother.
What?
Okay, you are the former
junior high team captain,
and that's worth
something, I guess.
Thanks, man.
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
Safe!
[CROWD cheering]
Aw, yeah! Good hustle!
Nice work, Sou!
[OTOMI] You could have
been a star athlete
no matter what sport you
went into, Akai, even baseball.
No way. Baseball is
the one sport I've never
had a shred of
confidence playing.
What?
[NARRATOR] And here we
have a baseball team member
paying because he
lost the challenge.
After all, I did grow up living
in the shadow of a prodigy.
I would call that the ideal
learning environment.
I just don't like being
compared to other people.
What's wrong with it?
That's natural for brothers,
and you're the younger
one, so that's your lot.
[RYOU]
Yeah. We're brothers, all right.
Although, not by blood.
He came into my life when
I was just four years old.
[OTOMI]
Hm?
Our parents both remarried.
We're technically stepbrothers.
Wait, for real?
That's like my family!
I'd no idea!
[RYOU gasps]
Are you serious? Hold on.
Why do your brothers
get along so well, then?
And, I thought that they
were fraternal twins.
[ICHIBAN]
Come on!
[RYOU, OTOMI gasp]
Are you saying you'd
never heard that before?
In this area, everyone knows the
Tachibana boys aren't brothers!
[gasps]
[BASE UMPIRE]
Out!
[CROWD cheers]
[SHIRAISHI PLAYER growls]
[TOUMA grunts]
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Strike three! Batter out!
[CROWD cheering]
[MEISEI ALUM A]
Hold the phone, guys.
You're telling me this
team is really Meisei High?
I just figured that
no-hitter last game
was nothing but a fluke.
Honestly, I only came
here today for the laughs,
but this seems a lot
like that one.
The opposing team hasn't
even gotten a decent hit,
on a tenth grader.
Yeah, and that catcher who's
batting third is a power hitter.
Those attempted steals?
Caught all three of 'em.
They're really something,
this famous brother battery.
[MEISEI ALUM C]
But, have you heard this part?
They work super well together,
even though they're not
actually related by blood.
[MEISEI ALUM A] Yeah, idiot,
of course I knew that.
--[RYOU] Hm?
--[MEISEI ALUM B] Yeah,
they live across the street
from the high school,
and it's the second marriage
for both parents, right?
[MEISEI ALUM A]
Exactly.
I challenge you to find a single
person living around here
who doesn't know
about those guys.
[RYOU gasps]
Mm? Hmm?
[ICHIBAN] You'll never find her
if you keep looking over there.
Otomi's that way, man.
You see her now?
[ICHIBAN]
She's on loan to the band,
playing the flute,
like she does.
[CROWD cheering]
[bat clinks]
[SHIRAISHI STUDENT A]
Yeah!
So, tell me,
do ya envy them yet,
Mr. Soccer Star?
There's no bigger summer
event in Japan these days
than the High School
Baseball tournament.
Yeah...
[RYOU]
...I do envy them.
You're not about
to tell me that you're gonna
join the baseball team, are you?
When it comes to baseball,
I've never had any real
belief in my own ability.
Yeah, I heard.
[RYOU]
But, the other day,
I beat the ace pitcher
and cleanup hitter
in a batting challenge,
so there's that.
What? You idiot!
I was facing faster pitches!
80 miles per hour, to your 60!
But, still...
...it boosted my confidence.
Come on. Are you for real?
I'm messing with you.
[ICHIBAN gasps]
[TOUMA grunts]
[CROWD gasps]
[KOMA gasps]
[BASE UMPIRE]
Out!
Stop prolonging the scene
for no good reason.
[HARUKA] He followed up his
no-hitter with a total shut-out!
Great pitching! Great game!
What's great about it?
[HARUKA]
Hm?
The way Touma threw today,
it's almost a miracle
they didn't score.
I was sweatin' bullets.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, I guess you're right.
We also have their
manager to thank
for making all the wrong choices
and unintentionally
sabotaging his own team.
If anything won the game, it was
Souichirou's leadership skills.
[HARUKA] Yeah, and we only
got charged with one error,
something we were
both worried about.
[OOYAMA] We made five mistakes
that won't get recorded
in the record books, both
in offense and defense.
[HARUKA]
Good!
You seem to be paying attention
to all the right things!
Uhh...
Good doggy.
Hey, stop that.
[CROWD cheering]
It's true, though.
[RYOU]
I do envy them.
[BAND MEMBER A]
Let's see...
That guy over
there, and that one,
and... I see him pretty
often, too, I think.
[OTOMI]
Oh?
Are these people all
Meisei alumni or something?
I'd say yes, probably.
Hey!
That man over there with
the weird hat and sunglasses?
He comes to almost
all the games.
[OTOMI]
Oh, yeah?
I usually see him watching
quietly from the corners,
but then, the other day,
during that big no-hitter,
he was more excited
than I've ever seen him!
Well, yeah,
he's quiet, not dead!
What a great game!
I hope he's not
skipping work for this.
That would be bad.
Nah, he seems like someone
with lots of spare time.
An office worker couldn't
miss that much work.
[OTOMI]
You're right about that.
[PUNCH barking]
Oh, be quiet,
you know it's just me!
[EISUKE]
I'm home!
Hey, Dad!
Oh, thank you.
Boy, it's a hot one.
I was outside, making the rounds
all day. I thought I would melt.
You want to take the first
bath tonight, dear?
Yeah, sounds good!
[OTOMI]
Aren't you gonna ask?
[EISUKE]
Hm?
How today's game turned out...
Oh, uh, yeah, of course!
How did it go? [laughs]
My mind's so focused
on work, I totally forgot!
So, did we win?
Yeah, we did.
Oh! Well, that's just great!
You're telling me we shut
them out, three to nothing?
[OTOMI]
Hmm...
Careful, you wouldn't
want to get fired.
[EISUKE giggles]
[PUNCH barks]
Goodness! Well,
this brings me back!
You got him that silly
hat for Father's Day,
and I'm pretty sure you were
still in elementary
school at the time.
Adorable!
These sunglasses were
a gift that year, too.
I remember when Sou
and Tou picked them out.
[EISUKE sighs]
Yep, this is the life!
[EISUKE laughs]
[EISUKE] ♪ We pledge our loyalty
to you, dear, old Meisei High! ♪
Well, he's in
a good mood, how nice.
[EISUKE]
Hurrah! Hurrah!
No wonder he never
gets promoted at work.
[MAYUMI]
What did you say, dear?
[OTOMI]
Huh? Oh, nothing.
[NARRATOR] The Meisei
High School Baseball Team.
[NARRATOR] They're in the
top 16 for the first time
since that famous year.
The nostalgia surrounding
the Meisei High name
gradually makes the school
the talk of the town again,
and day by day,
excitement begins to build.
[NARRATOR]
School representatives
are starting to get restless,
and the alumni are
getting ahead of themselves.
[SPECTATORS chattering]
[TOUMA]
What do you think?
'Bout what?
We've only won three games,
so all this seems premature.
They're all getting
too worked up.
Not to mention the average age
of the spectators, they're old.
[SOUICHIROU]
Our school has a lot of fans
who aren't even alumni.
You know that.
You wanna know
somethin' I heard?
The year we won it all,
the whole country was behind us.
That was back in the day.
It's got nothing
to do with our team.
And we know that
from this point on,
all of the teams are gonna
be playing at a high level.
All this "support" ends up
feeling like nothing
but added pressure.
[TOUMA] That's not
what I'm talking about.
They can't get excited yet.
They've gotta wait until
we beat Toushu, at least.
[SOUICHIROU]
Hmm?
And when we get to the
finals and defeat Seinan,
that's when the excitement
will reach its peak!
It'll be maximum Meisei Fever!
[SOUICHIROU] Your confidence
is kinda baffling.
I have no idea where
it even comes from.
Oh, I'm not
confident, not at all.
We don't have any experience.
[SOUICHIROU]
Huh?
I just think it
would be a lot of fun
if that's how it all
went down in the end.
He gets it!
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
That's right. The will
to win starts there.
Ah, come on. Wait a second.
Take this, it's a video
of Toushu's last game.
It aired on TV.
Luckily, I recorded it.
Oh, thanks.
Shouldn't we stay focused on
beating Houkaidai Sankou first?
What is your problem?
If we beat them,
then win the next game, we'll
be facing Toushu in no time.
No time?
You're one of those
guys who only thinks
about the next step
when you're walking,
so you're always
running into poles.
What kind of stupid
comparison is that?!
[NANGOU chuckles]
Hey, Chuckles. What's so funny?
[NANGOU]
Hm?
[TADASHI] You can't
tell a bitter persimmon
from a sweet one
just by looking.
What kind of comparison is that?
Uh, beats me. Sheesh.
[NARRATOR]
And now...
[PUNCH snoring]
[NARRATOR]
...summer vacation...
...is here!
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Strike three! Batter out!
[CROWD cheering]
[BAND MEMBERS laughing]
Yes! They made it past the top
16 and into the quarter finals!
They really did it!
I thought they would,
and they did!
[EISUKE laughs]
Yes!
[EISUKE] ♪ We pledge our loyalty
to you, dear, old Meisei High! ♪
[EISUKE laughs]
[MAYUMI] Okay, Otomi,
thanks for doing that!
[OTOMI]
Sure!
Oops.
Forget something?
I need to keep
the chart up to date!
That looks better. Nice!
[OTOMI]
All right. See you later!
My goodness.
[indistinct chatter]
The crowd of spectators just
keeps getting bigger every day.
Well, that makes sense.
Oh! Hey, Otomi! Congrats to ya.
Your brothers are doing well!
[OTOMI]
Yes, thank you!
[SHOP CLERK A]
I'm rooting for you guys.
Here's a little extra.
[OTOMI]
Wow. You sure? Appreciate it!
[FISH SHOP MANAGER]
And this one's on the house.
[OTOMI]
What? That's not necessary!
[FISH SHOP MANAGER] I know,
my treat! A good luck gift!
[FRUIT SHOP MANAGER]
Otomi! Otomi!
[SHOP CLERK B]
Hey! Otomi!
This is heavy.
People don't know how much
weight their kindness carries.
[OTOMI]
Hm?
[OTOMI panting]
[OTOMI]
Hmm?
Mita?
[OTOMI]
Interesting.
I wonder who that guy could be.
[KOMA] That's Ryou Akai's
older brother.
[OTOMI]
Huh?
Whoa, okay.
Who is this person talking
to me like we're friends?
Yo!
What, Koma?
I hope you're not stalking me.
[KOMA]
No, no, no.
It's just that there are
so many Meisei fans around,
I can't seem to get
a break from all of it.
I was about to pass out from
lack of air, so I dressed up.
[OTOMI] And you're
skipping practice, too?
I like to refer
to it as a break.
Not that it's
really my business,
but your outfit,
what's the deal with that?
I can't exactly walk around town
wearing my uniform these days,
so I came up with this disguise.
Seems like you've taken
"breaks" like these before.
Wait did you say
Akai's older brother?
Oh, back to that subject?
[inaudible]
That's the stepbrother
he can't get along with,
the baseball genius, who happens
to be Kenjo's cleanup hitter.
Uhh...
Are you for real?
I hadn't heard
about all that drama.
Is he dating Mita?
If so, since when?
[KOMA]
I'll go ask 'em. [gasps]
No, you will not, blockhead!
What?
[OTOMI grunts]
Right.
[OTOMI] Since we're almost
out of time in this episode,
I'll pretend
I didn't see anything!
[KOMA]
Huh?
[KOMA] Got a lot to carry.
Been shoppin'?
I didn't plan to. My dad
begged me to pick up a copy
of every morning sports paper,
and people just gave
me all this stuff.
[KOMA] Your dad must be
thrilled about the whole thing.
To say he's thrilled is the
understatement of the year.
He was going on about
it the whole night.
Talk about disturbing
the peace, right?
He's not the only
one going nuts.
Lots of people are freaking out.
Yeah, you're not wrong.
Toushu's next if we win?
[KOMA]
That's right.
[OTOMI]
Hm?
[KOMA]
Things seem to be
going too well.
Yeah, now that you mention it,
developments like this
always make me a little uneasy.
--[horn blares]
--Just because--
[gasps]
[KOMA, OTOMI]
Hm?
You idiot! You trying
to get killed?
[bell rings]
Do you know that guy?
I don't, not at all.
All right! I can see it now--
The Koshien!
[SOUICHIROU]
Are you serious?
Next time, on Mix :
[TOUMA]
Huh? Where'd our manager go?
[SOUICHIROU]
If I remember correctly,
he's at the local shrine.
[TOUMA]
Let's see...
Pray for the safety of your
family, a thriving business,
good health, safe delivery...
He got all these amulets?
[SOUICHIROU] There's even
a pressed four-leaf clover.
[OOYAMA]
I also pulled a fortune slip!
[SOUICHIROU] Next time,
"You're Praying for Help."
[TOUMA]
What does the slip say?
[OOYAMA]
Meager luck.
[PUNCH barks]