[cicadas crying]
[laughing]
[ISAMI]
In our next life,
I'll make sure to live
next door to you!
Then we can always be friends!
[ISAMI]
Thirty years.
Whoa. Guess time
really does fly by.
[NISHIMURA]
Are you crazy or something?
This game is taking forever!
How much longer are these
jerks gonna let this go on?!
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[HARUKA] Who were you thinking
of putting on the mound next?
[OOYAMA]
Hmm?
Y'know, to replace Touma?
[OOYAMA]
Hmm...
[HARUKA] You'd be asking a lot,
making them step into
this high pressure situation,
not to mention facing that
intimidating Toushu lineup.
In fact, you'd have
trouble finding anyone
in the country who'd
be willing to fill in.
[OOYAMA] True. Whether these
guys manage to score or not,
the moment I take
Touma out of the game...
...this thing is
as good as over.
So, I'll ask again:
who are you going to stick
with doing the dirty work,
and the responsibility
of losing the game?
The dirty work, is it? Huh.
[NARRATOR] Jingu Stadium,
a long, long time ago.
[EISUKE] No way! I can't
do it! It's impossible!
[NARRATOR] Touma,
Souichirou, and Otomi's dad,
Eisuke Tachibana.
At the time, he was a senior
and member of the Meisei team.
[OOYAMA]
Don't sweat it, Eisuke.
Every single person watching
is thinking the same thing.
[NARRATOR] A younger version
of the current Meisei manager,
Gorou Ooyama.
He was also a senior
at the time.
They all assumed they knew
how this game would end,
from the moment
that Sawaii got hurt.
No one will be surprised
if you get hit,
and no one'll blame you, either.
I can't imagine
anything less stressful.
[EISUKE]
Yeah, you're right.
Huh?
I get it! It's the truth!
I've got nothing to worry about
because no one's
counting on me out there!
[EISUKE] That's great news!
Let's do this!
All righty, then, Tachibana.
You've got ammunition
that Sawai didn't have.
[EISUKE]
Hmm! Sure do!
[NARRATOR] The quarterfinals
of the East Tokyo Tournament.
[NARRATOR] After pitching
two straight shutouts,
Meisei's ace pitcher was
about to throw another,
limiting his opponent to just
two hits in seven innings.
Keiichi Sawai, tenth grade.
Souichirou and Otomi's
biological father.
[NARRATOR] Sawai was
going for the third out
in the seventh inning.
And while he was
covering first base,
he crossed paths
with the runner.
[NARRATOR] His pitching
hand caught a spike,
and he was rushed to
the hospital immediately.
The team was about ready
to throw in the towel,
when number 12 suddenly
got sent out on the mound.
[NARRATOR] His Meisei
teammates weren't the only ones
who felt deeply disturbed
by the incident.
The guilt of injuring
the opposing team's ace pitcher
was weighing heavily
on all the batters.
[bat clangs]
[NARRATOR]
Their fighting spirit faltered,
and their
concentration suffered.
But, on the other hand,
the Meisei substitute pitcher--
who usually threw pitches
that begged to be hit--
seemed a little
sharper than usual.
As a result...
[NARRATOR] Naturally, no one on
the team was more surprised
than the guy in the
number 12 uniform.
--[OOYAMA grunts]
--[NARRATOR] And then...
[NARRATOR]
In the top of the ninth,
Meisei scored a run on
an error by the opponent.
This gave number 12 the chance
to be the winning pitcher.
That set the dugout on fire,
along with the crowd, who
had assumed all was lost.
The opponents, who'd given up
their lead and found themselves
on the verge of defeat,
were focused solely on the game.
But uniform
number 12 had misjudged
the situation and was
suddenly very nervous.
His mind was consumed
with fear of giving up a hit.
[EISUKE grunts]
[EISUKE yells]
Why was I such an idiot?
I'd give anything
to go back in time!
[NARRATOR] Eisuke Tachibana,
currently 43 years old.
Would you stop
talking to yourself?!
It's starting to drive me crazy!
I'm having a hard time
focusing on the game!
Oh, sorry about that.
[OTOMI]
Maybe I'm imagining it,
but his pitching seems
to have gotten even better
since we went
into extra innings.
There's no way.
That can't be right.
Yeah!
Don't get too confident,
because that's usually
when people get careless.
Trust me.
[TOUMA]
Maybe I'm imagining it.
--[SOUICHIROU] Hmm?
--I feel invincible!
Like no one could get a hit off
me right now. It's amazing!
[SOUICHIROU]
Don't get carried away.
You've had help
from these guys--
swinging at balls
outside the strike zone.
That's what happens
when high-scoring teams
like this panic.
They come close to
scoring but fail to clinch it,
and that goes on,
inning after inning,
until, finally,
we're in extra innings.
It's such an unexpected
development
for a team like Toushu that it
really disrupts their batters.
But...
I'm keeping that in mind and
calling pitches accordingly.
[TOUMA]
Interesting. That makes sense.
I see what's happening now.
I couldn't figure it out before.
Here I am, completely
exhausted, and yet...
So, you two can agree. Wow.
What? I don't always disagree
with what Souichirou has to say.
When it comes
to baseball, that is.
And you're not
wrong in this instance.
But, still... That's not all.
There's more, right?
Yeah.
Come on.
It'd be dumb to flatter him now.
We're in the middle of a game.
I find no lie in that statement.
He's a smart guy.
[MORI] East Tokyo Tournament
semifinals, game one.
In this matchup between
Meisei and Toushu,
both teams are still
scoreless after 12 innings.
According to the rules,
they'll keep playing
until the 15th inning.
Will we have a winner by then?
Or will the game end in
a tie leading to a rematch.
While Toushu was up to bat,
we saw their batters
being overly aggressive,
swinging at every pitch,
even the bad ones.
Do you think this is a sign
that the Toushu lineup
is starting to panic?
--[MORI] Mr. Hyouri?
--Huh?
What are you so
engrossed with over there?
Oh. I, uh...
It's about Tachibana's
pitching a few minutes ago.
Quite intriguing. Is this
the kind of pitcher that he is?
Sorry? As you may
recall me pointing out
before the game started,
along with Nishimura, the
pitcher for Seinan High School,
both boys are only
in the tenth grade--
Jeez, I know that--how many
times are you gonna say it?
Shouldn't he be sitting down
to get all the rest he can
before the next inning?
He knows what he's doing,
just let the guy work.
Let him work?
He's a stone cold thief.
Let him steal.
What the heck?
Right here. Check it out.
This is a record of the
way Tachibana pitched in
the beginning of the game.
Huh. It was a great start.
I was impressed a tenth
grader struck out the side.
[HYOURI]
Is that what you think?
Seems more like a kid
being reckless and throwing
as hard as he could to me.
There were some innings
where he appeared to focus
more on control,
but even then
he put unnecessary
burdens on himself.
Not the form of a pitcher who
could last a full nine innings.
But then something happened.
In the late and extra innings,
when he had to be
at peak exhaustion...
And here in this last inning.
How do you explain it? Bizarre.
Uh, sorry, you're gonna
have to be more specific.
[HYOURI] Can't you figure
it out from context clues?
This is the form of
a pitcher who's on track
to throw a complete shutout!
It's the mirror image
of his form.
It's Mita to a T.
[NISHIMURA huffs]
You've got it wrong.
[MORI]
Foul!
He hits the ball, but it just
barely rolls out of bounds.
[TOUSHU TEAM 24B growls]
[MITA]
That's right.
Much better.
What's going on?
Are you Meisei's
new pitching coach now?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know me: it's just
my love of baseball again.
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
Hmph.
[MITA]
No need to worry.
In terms of skill, there's still
a huge gap between us.
Well, unfortunately,
I am very worried.
Only because Toushu's
not going to have you holding
the team together next year.
[grunts]
[CROWD cheering]
You okay?
If this ends in a tie and
rematch, if at all possible,
you should probably
have somebody else pitch.
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
A tie and rematch, huh?
We're way past
joking about that.
[MORI] Looks like
a pop up's all he's got.
Fukabori on first only
has to take a few steps
to make the catch.
Three outs.
Hiroki Mita has not
allowed a single runner
to get on base since
the extra innings began.
He's been perfect.
The rumors are true:
this kid's a monster.
If there was any
doubt about it before,
it's gone.
This is the best
game Mita's pitched
in his high school career.
He's trying to
send you a message.
A challenge to catch up to him.
Not quite.
I'm not the one he really
wants to send a message to.
Look.
You're not staying
to watch to the end?
No, I've reached my limit.
I endured this because
I thought it would be
over in nine innings.
[AKAI]
So, what? You've gotta pee?
[ARISA growls]
Are you two really brothers?
Both you and Ryou?
[AKAI]
Yeah, we're brothers.
We're just not related by blood.
[ARISA]
What an odd coincidence.
[AKAI]
What do you mean by that?
It's the same situation
as the Meisei battery.
[gasps]
--[TOUMA grunts]
--[TOUSHU TEAM 24D grunts]
[HIRAO gasps]
[gasping]
[TOUSHU TEAM 24D pants]
[HIRAO chuckles]
[gasps]
--[CROWD groaning]
--[sighing]
[TOUSHU MANAGER growls]
[MORI] Runners on
the corners with one out.
In the bottom of the 14th,
Toushu has a great chance
to end this game.
After the first out, the
shortstop was late covering
a ball hit straight to him.
That was followed
by some poor defense
when the right fielder
misjudged the ball.
Meisei High School now finds
themselves in quite a jam.
You can't help
but feel a bit sorry
for the pitcher, Tachibana.
This scene is...
--Huh?
--Oh. Sorry, I was saying.
With an inning like this, you
can't help but feel a little bit
sorry for Tachibana,
the pitcher.
[HYOURI]
I agree.
[MORI] Meisei High School's
really in a tight spot.
This kid's been able
to shut us down
this whole time, even with
that defense behind him.
That pitcher...
I hope that you
praise him when you give
your victory interview.
Yeah. I'll mean every word.
[MORI]
Kaga, batting third,
swings for the fences
on the first pitch.
[HYOURI]
He's looking great!
Seems to have
figured out the timing.
[TOUSHU TEAM 23B]
A squeeze bunt?
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
Don't be dumb.
That's our cleanup hitter.
We'll crush this guy, and then--
[bat clangs]
[TOUSHU MANAGER]
What the--?
This scene feels
oddly familiar somehow.
Wait! What just happened?!
[MORI]
Kaga hits the sweet spot!
There's a deafening crack
as the bat hits the ball...
[MORI] ...and finds its way to
Tachibana's glove once again!
The third base runner
is caught between the bags!
All right!
[MORI] A line out to
the pitcher for two outs!
And...
[siren wails]
I wonder where everyone went?
[gasps]
So, he was watching this?
[TOUMA]
It's been forever.
[AOKI] The skies above Koshien
are bright and sunny today!
The time has come to
crown the winner from
the 3,647 participating
high schools.
[EISUKE]
Touma. Dinner is almost ready.
[EISUKE] The rolled omelet
turned out pretty great.
So, let's share some of it
with your mother, all right?
[bell tings]
[AOKI]
It picks up speed!
Tatsuya Uesugi of Meisei
has got one heck of a fastball!
'Kay. We can
keep watching it after
we finish eating.
[EISUKE] They're not
all the same, are they?
Skill levels as different
as night and day.
Hey, what's your problem?!
Do you realize how annoying you
two are being over there,
insulting me?!
[CROWD cheers]
[siren wails]
[TOUMA gasps]
[MAYUMI] Oh, Touma!
I didn't know you were awake.
There, you see?
That's what you
get for being so loud.
You woke him up, Otomi.
[OTOMI]
What? I did not!
You can go back to sleep now.
We didn't save any cake for you.
He's lying. Of course
we saved you some.
It's in the fridge
when you want it.
[TOUMA]
And the video?
[SOUICHIROU] I stopped it
for you when you nodded off.
You should really copy
it to another platform.
You're gonna ruin it by
watching it over and over.
[TOUMA]
Right.
Here. Hurry up
and eat it, though.
We don't have any for Dad,
so we don't want him to know.
Oh, he'll be fine.
He'll get over it, as long as
he still has some snacks
to go with his beer.
[SOUICHIROU] Dad's been
watching that tape every day
since we lost the game.
The poor guy.
[OTOMI] He and our dad
watch it together, I guess.
[MAYUMI chuckles]
[cicadas cry]
[PUNCH snores]
[In any case,
they gotta learn sometime.
All the hopes
and disappointments
of their baseball forebears.
I think it helps them
play better, right?
Or at least not take it
too hard when they lose.
What do think, Sawai?
[EISUKE]
Okay, you're on, Tatsuya!
Time to be the national
Champions once again.
Meisei High School!
[AOKI] The skies above Koshien
are bright and sunny today!
Hey, Mayumi,
don't you think he looks
a little bit like Touma?
I think so!
[screams]
What am I gonna do?
--All is lost!
--Is something the matter, dear?
[EISUKE] Of course there's
something the matter!
The tape! The most
important tape ever broke!
What's with all the racket?
[EISUKE] We've got to fix it!
Or find another copy somewhere!
I was smart and copied
the contents onto
a DVD years ago. Dad's got
nothing to worry about.
Tell him, before
he hurts himself.
[TOUMA sighs]
[SOUICHIROU]
What was that?
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
Wasn't Otomi saying
something to you?
[TOUMA] Hmm...
Yeah, she did say something.
[EISUKE]
Save the tape! Save the tape!
[CROWD cheers]
[MAYUMI hums]
Oh! [giggles]