[NARRATOR]
The weather is perfect today!
[PUNCH barks]
[NARRATOR] Otomi is taking
Punch out for a walk.
[ARISA]
Oh, hey. A real-life stalker.
[NISHIMURA grunts] Uh!
Who are you calling a stalker?
Don't talk to me like I'm some
kind of deviant creeper!
Well, If the shoe fits...
Look, my name
is Takumi Nishimura!
I'm in the tenth grade
at Seinan High,
I'm the ace pitcher for
the baseball team, and,
once the summer
tournament starts,
the whole country's gonna
be talkin' about me!
'Kay, so how's that
explain the binoculars?
Uh, I'm friends
with her brothers,
so I'm looking out for
her like a good friend.
Uh-huh.
Come on, it's the truth.
This area's gotten kinda shady,
with the creepy guys preying
on young girls, even
in the daytime!
Hang on!
See, here comes one of
those dirty predators now!
[NISHIMURA]
Mm... Nah.
Never mind; that actually looks
like a pretty cool dude.
I think you need to have
your eyes examined!
[NISHIMURA]
Hmm?
[ARISA]
That guy is a notorious playboy.
He's known as, the "Red Smile."
He draws them in with
that charming, boyish grin,
then breaks their hearts,
leaving sadness in his wake.
[NISHIMURA whimpers]
What?
[OTOMI]
Hate to say I told you so,
but I told you not to
trust a single word
that school nurse said.
You did, and you were right.
It was a good thing we went
to the hospital when we did.
Oh, and another thing--
[NISHIMURA]
Red Smile!
Get away from Otomi! Hey!
[yells, grunts]
I know exactly what you're
after here! [growls]
Leave her alone, or you won't
like what happens next!
Huh?
Are you trying to be funny?
[ARISA]
Oh, wow!
Is it that Nishimura guy
everyone's been talking about?
Nobody more than Miss Tachibana.
She tells me that
he's the ace pitcher
for the Seinan High
baseball team.
I do what?
She goes on and on
about this guy.
She's been worried that all
the girls will be after him--
once the summer
tournament starts
and the whole
country takes notice.
It's really sweet, the way
she gets so worked up!
You are that Nishimura, right?
Okay?
Hey, Akai, let's go.
We wouldn't wanna interrupt
these two lovebirds.
C'mon! We better
give them some space.
Oh, I get it. She wanted
to get him away from me.
[NISHIMURA]
Otomi! Are you okay?
He didn't hurt you, did he?
Did he do anything bad?
Are you injured?
Emotionally scarred?
I'm fine, jeez!
[KOMA] Hey! What do you
think you're doing?
[OTOMI]
Hmm?
[yelps, grunts] If you so much
as touch one hair on her head,
I'll punch you in the face!
[ICHIBAN]
What? Otomi! What's up?
What's going on?
Who is that, anyway?
[arguing continues]
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[TOUMA groans]
Man, I am freaking starving!
Well, Otomi is going
to be home any minute now.
Just hang in there till then.
She said she'd make her special
Spaghetti Napolitan for you
when you finally got out of bed.
Why's it always
gotta be special?
I mean, jeez. Not every single
thing has to be special.
Normal is good enough.
I've never once
complained about
regular old spaghetti.
But she has to make it all fancy
and add random ingredients
for no reason.
[MAYUMI] She has
a tendency to go overboard
where you're concerned,
Touma, whether you ask or not.
--But be nice.
--[TOUMA sighs]
Think of it this way,
she's showing kindness
and compassion for you, so why
not let her do what she wants?
[TOUMA]
Fine.
[MAYUMI giggles]
I'm grateful.
For what?
If it weren't for the
influence you've had on them.
I'm not sure Otomi and
Souichirou would've grown
into the lovely people
they are today.
Yeah, right?
When I first met those two,
they were a couple of
awkward shut-ins who
almost never left the house!
But now they're both popular
and have so many friends
they don't even know
what to do with themselves!
You're popular, too! Just look!
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
[MAYUMI] You've been getting
cards and gifts ever since
that practice game
the other day.
Our poor mailbox.
Who's this stuff from?
[MAYUMI]
But, in any case.
I have a feeling Otomi is always
going to be your number one fan.
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
I. A. O? Who is that?
[gasps]
[OTOMI]
Hey, I'm home!
Good, glad you're back!
[TOUMA sighs]
I'd better get something to eat.
[NISHIMURA, KOMA, ICHIBAN]
Don't forget about us!
Wha--? What are
you guys doing here?
[OTOMI] I have no idea why,
but they insisted on
walking me all the way home.
Jeez, what is this, Momotaro?
[barks]
What the heck's going on here?
Well, the thing is,
the Momotaro gang
got here before you did.
Oh!
And it looks like you brought
the villain of the story.
Very funny.
We saw each other
at the noodle shop,
and he decided
to follow me home.
Villain?
What the heck did I do
to deserve a day like this?
How many times
do I have to tell you?!
I dunno, how many do you got?!
Jeez, do you
know anything at all?!
[NISHIMURA] You don't
understand these things!
--Why don't you shut up?
--Yeah, yeah, whatever, weirdo.
Hey, wait. Where'd Touma go?
[OTOMI]
I dunno.
[TOUMA] Maybe it's not
I-A-O, but something else.
Could it be One A-O?
First year. Class A. Ooyama?
[HARUKA]
This may be forward,
but when we're done with
our midterms next week.
I'd like us to go out on a walk.
If that'd be too much
of a hassle, forget it.
But, if you want to join me,
then tomorrow I'll say,
"good morning."
If you say it back to me,
I'll know you wanna go.
If you'd rather not,
then just say,
"Ahnokutara Sanmyaku Sanboudai."
That'll be our code
for "No, thanks."
Huh? What the--?
Ano-ku-ta. What now?
[HARUKA] P.S. At the request
of the noodle shop manager,
I've taken a part-time job at
Ramen Dragon when it's busy.
If you're ever in the area,
feel free stop by.
I'll throw in an extra slice of
meat for you. Haruka Ooyama.
[TOUMA]
Hmm...
Now it's all starting to
make more sense.
Ah... Mm!
[KOMA gulping]
[grunts]
Hey! Stop!
[NISHIMURA]
Wanna make me?
[KOMA] Can't you keep your
elbows outta my space?
[NISHIMURA]
I'm a pitcher!
I can't help it if my arms
need more room!
[TOUMA]
Hmm.
I thought I understood,
but now I'm all confused again.
[STUDENTS murmuring]
--[SOUICHIROU] Later.
--Bye.
I started studying a while back.
I think I'm gonna do
really well this time around.
[TOUMA] Anyway. This walk could
really turn into a hassle.
So, it'd be safer
to just decline.
All right. What am I
supposed to say to decline?
[TOUMA]
Ano...?
Ano... Kuta... ra...
[HARUKA]
Good morning.
[TOUMA]
Hmm? Oh, good morning.
[HARUKA giggles]
Uh...
[TOUMA] Dang it! That
response is so automatic!
She made it hard to say
no on purpose, didn't she?
[TEACHER 7A]
Five more minutes, folks.
[HARUKA]
I'd like us to go out on a walk.
[gasps]
[TOUMA] Don't get distracted!
Gotta focus. Focus!
[TEACHER 7A]
Right! Pencils down!
[TOUMA grunts]
[OTOMI]
So? How'd your test go?
[TOUMA]
All my answers were guesses,
so we'll see when I get it back.
[sighs] You say the
same thing every test.
[SOUICHIROU] This one
might be particularly bad.
--Don't get your hopes up.
--[TOUMA] Huh?
I couldn't help but notice
that you've had trouble
concentrating. This whole week.
And what makes you say that?
Also, it's about time.
Time for what?
[SOUICHIROU]
It's been over ten minutes.
You know, since you
added the hot water
to your instant noodles.
[TOUMA groans]
How is it?
Delicious! Thanks.
Hey, now that I think about it,
you never eat noodles at
home anymore, do you, Sou?
Yes, I do.
Why would you say that?
[TOUMA]
Hmm...
[HARUKA] I've taken a part-time
job at Ramen Dragon
when it's busy.
[TOUMA] Hmm. This could
become a problem.
But, wait. Why?
What is there to worry about?
I mean, it's not
like I did anything wrong.
And it's not like
I have any idea
how Sou feels about her, either.
Besides, we're just
going for a walk.
Hey. Since tomorrow's Saturday,
you don't have
baseball practice, right?
Right. They'll be working
on the field all day,
filling in the sunken parts.
[TOUMA]
Oh, yeah. A free day.
Our only one for a while.
[OTOMI]
Well, perfect.
Then you guys wanna go
see a movie tomorrow?
[grunts, coughs]
What is your problem, man?
[TOUMA]
Oh, crap. She just said a walk.
She didn't say anything about
a time or place for it yet.
We haven't settled the details.
Wait, that's perfect!
If I already have
plans for tomorrow.
[slurps]
Let's do that!
Going for a movie sounds fun!
[MAYUMI]
Hey, kids, I'm home!
Oh, hi, Mom.
Touma. There was another letter
in the mail for you.
A fan letter!
[TOUMA]
Uh. Crap. Well, this sucks.
I read this before I could
finalize any other plans.
[MAYUMI]
Otomi. Can you do me a favor?
Will you take this gift over
to the Idas's house tomorrow?
Tomorrow? Wait, what?
Have you forgotten already?
You're the one who suggested
it when we went over there
to visit them last week.
You said that you would give
their daughter flute lessons!
I swear!
[gasps]
Uh, guess I forgot.
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
Well, I guess we can
all go to a movie
the next time parts of the
baseball field start to sink.
The team really
can't afford for that
to keep happening,
just so you know.
[TOUMA]
Which would mean.
[TOUMA] Well then, the two of
us can still go. How 'bout it?
I don't wanna go with just you.
Okay, then.
[TOUMA] There's no reason
to keep it a secret from him...
...but there's also no reason
to tell him, either.
And besides.
We're just going for a walk.
[PUNCH barks]
[HARUKA giggles]
[NARRATOR]
The weather is perfect.
A great day for a trip!
[TOUMA]
How far is this place?
Just a bit farther.
[TOUMA] Of course.
It is just a walk, after all.
Hey, how much
farther are we going?
[HARUKA]
Relax, we're almost there!
[TOUMA] She keeps saying that,
but we took three trains
to get this far, and we've
been walking forever.
This is just a walk, isn't it?
Oh! I remember those rocks!
Should be just
downhill from this marker.
Hey! Wait for me!
[HARUKA]
Bingo! We finally made it!
We did?
Here, look at this.
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
[HARUKA] That's a picture
of me at three years old.
[HARUKA]
Ha! Finally! Mystery solved!
[TOUMA]
Uh? Mystery?
It has been bugging me forever!
Every time I've seen the photo.
See right there.
It's the little persimmon
on the corner of the sign.
Oh, yeah.
[HARUKA]
Isn't that weird?
Like, why would they put a
random persimmon there?
That's a good question.
Nothing that would
bug me, though.
That's the mystery.
So, I've been thinking.
Maybe there's another clue on
the sign, on the part that
you can't see in the picture,
'cause it's hidden behind me.
I've been dying to find out!
Now, follow me over here...
[HARUKA]
Ta-da! Check out this guy!
In Japanese, "tanuki"
also means "Take out the ta!"
Okay?
So cut the "tas" from,
"Katatataki"--the falls.
"Kaki."
Right, the Japanese
for "persimmon!"
So, we just solved the riddle!
Doesn't it feel great?
[TOUMA]
I guess?
It's nothing to write home
about, that's for sure.
[HARUKA]
Wow! So satisfying!
I'm so glad we came!
[TOUMA] I don't mean to dampen
the mood--no pun intended--
but It's gonna be
getting dark soon,
so I think we'd better
start heading back.
Yeah, but there's
no rush, or anything.
There's a bus stop
not too far from here.
If we hike that way,
we'll run right into it.
There it is. I told ya so.
How do you do that?
I can't remember anything
from when I was three.
I gotta say, I'm impressed.
Why, thank you.
I guess that means you don't
remember us getting into
that little fight, huh?
Ah, wha--? No.
[TOUMA]
Fight?
[NANGOU growls]
[RYUUICHI]
Welcome, boys!
Huh? Where's Haruka?
Well, she took
the day off, so I dunno.
She said something about
plans for a little day trip.
--Anyway, what can I getcha?
--[door rattles shut]
[RYUUICHI]
Bye...?
Will you please
stop following me?
[PUNCH growls, barks]
[SOUICHIROU]
Huh? Manager?
Hey! I'm glad to see you boys!
Nobody was answering,
so I was at a bit of a loss!
What are you doing here?
I just figured Haruka
would have gotten home by now,
but she hasn't yet.
Where is she?
Well, I'm-- I'm not
quite sure, actually.
So, why are you here?
I assumed you knew.
Wherever she went,
it was with Touma.
[BOTH gasp]
[MAYUMI] Hello, there!
What are you all doing?
Please, come inside.
[OTOMI]
Hmm?
Good idea,
I'm gonna need some answers.
[SOUICHIROU]
Right this way, Manager.
Tell me everything you know.
[TOUMA]
Where's the dang bus?
Good question.
It should have been here by now.
[TOUMA] Hmm? What's this piece
of paper on the ground?
[TOUMA] Huh? Are these
annoying riddle signs
a tradition around
here, or what?
I think it may have
been posted on this.
"Losing hair can mean
take away the 'Ke' in Japanese."
So, that's...
"Hotenjitsu, batesu, yatesumi."
That doesn't
mean anything at all!
This is stupid.
[HARUKA] Hold on.
Look there-- the drawing.
The writing for
"lost hair" is sloppy,
compared to the rest,
and "sloppy" can
mean "take out the 'te.'"
Ah-ha! Just take
out 'ke' and 'te!'
[TOUMA]
Huh?
When you take those away,
what does it mean?
[TOUMA] "The bus will
be out of service today."
Awesome!
"Awesome"? Sure,
we solved the dumb riddle,
but the bus won't
come until tomorrow!
[HARUKA]
Uh... Got a phone?
Nope, I sure don't.
Two modern teenagers.
What are the odds that neither
of us carry a cell phone?
[TOUMA]
Perfect.
[SOUICHIROU] You're saying they
met when they were both three?
You sure about that?
[OOYAMA gulps]
[EISUKE]
Oh, yeah, I remember it now!
It was at my late
wife's funeral--
I can't believe I forgot!
Oh, yeah.
[EISUKE] A little girl
threw soda in Touma's face
and got him all upset,
poor little guy!
Whoa, that's just crazy.
So, that little
meanie was Haruka!
She really did that
at his mom's funeral?
[OOYAMA]
Sure did.
[TOUMA mimics plane sounds,
laughs]
[TOUMA gasps]
[wails]
[OOYAMA] All the adults
at the funeral were crying,
but he was romping around
laughing and making
lots of noise.
Apparently, Haruka took
major offense to that.
Touma didn't mean any harm.
He didn't understand
his mom had died.
He was little.
And, also, he always
got overexcited
around big crowds.
With all that going on,
it's no wonder that happened.
I'm amazed two kids the same age
could be so different.
Our Haruka is a bit
of an oddball in that way.
She still remembers
the whole thing.
All these years later.
I guess she must feel a
kind of nostalgia toward Touma.
[NANGOU growls]
You're gonna break
the glass, jeez.
She's told me Touma
turned out exactly
like she imagined he would.
And she was thrilled she got
to see him once again.
You know, Touma can't
even remember what he had
for lunch, let alone
something that happened
when he was three years old.
Now that I think about it,
Touma may very well have
been Haruka's first love!
[laughs]
--[glass shatters]
--[NANGOU snarls]
[SOUICHIROU]
Hmm?
[OTOMI]
Nan, are you all right?!
I hope you didn't cut yourself!
[SOUICHIROU sighs]
Moron.
They were toddlers,
you can hardly call
something like that "love."
[OTOMI]
Hmm?So how old were we?
[SOUICHIROU]
Huh?
How old were we
when we first met Tou?
Well, I was six years old,
and you were five.
Well, then, I lose.
It's not like it's a competition
or anything, you weirdo.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm... In any case...
Those two aren't back yet.
[TOUMA]
What is going on?
This is really starting
to freak me out.
We've been walking forever,
but we've yet to
come across anything
resembling civilization.
You're not wrong.
Why is it so
freakin' dark on this road?
I wonder if now's
the time to start worrying.
Seems like it.
I'm gonna apologize in advance.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Wait, "in advance"? What?
If something happened,
then it would be too late.
What does that mean?
[HARUKA] If something happens,
you can blame me--I don't care.
Okay, maybe I'm not being clear.
What do you mean by "something?"
[HARUKA]
Hmm, for example...
Just come out and say it!
You're really starting
to freak me out!
This is a paved road,
with streetlights!
Cars gotta pass by
here often enough--
--[horn honking]
--[gasps]
Well, speak of the devil
and he just might appear,
--am I right?
--[chuckles] We're saved!
[TOUMA]
Next time, on Mix!
[SOUICHIROU]
An unlikely rescue.
Touma and Haruka are lost
on a dark mountain road,
when all of a sudden,
the Seinan High school bus
comes barreling
out of the darkness!
Then, the father-son Nishimura
interrogation team bombard
the two with questions!
Also, the bus is haunted
by ghosts and goblins!
Will our friends
make it home alive?
Whatever will become of them?
Next time, "Try Pitching."
[TOUMA]
Jeez, stop exaggerating!
[barks]