[UMPIRE 1A]
Strike Three! You're out!
[CROWD cheering]
[CLUB MEMBERS yelling]
[ANNOUNCER 1A]
Meisei are the champions
in their first ever trip
to the tournament!
[ANNOUNCER 1A] Astonishingly
the team's ace, Tatsuya Uesugi,
pitched the entire game!
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[NARRATOR]
Meisei High School only tasted
a championship victory once.
Many summers have
followed since their win.
And though generations
of teams tried their best,
the school never again
managed to return to Koshien.
Will you squat already, Tou?
You're the one who
should be squatting, Sou!
Y'know, most kids do what their
big brothers tell them to.
[TOUMA laughs] Why would
you be my "big" brother?
We were born on
the exact same day!
[SOUICHIROU] Yeah, but you've
seen the birth certificates.
I was officially born ten
minutes earlier than you!
[TOUMA]
And why should I trust those?
For all I know, my hospital
could've just been lazy!
Or maybe they forgot to check
the time and just guessed!
Even if mine's right,
yours could've been wrong!
They were probly sick of waiting
for you and just wrote down
whatever time they wanted.
Plus! We have no way of knowing
if the clocks in
either one of our hospitals
were right that day. Heck,
they could even still be off!
Man, it sure sounds
like someone's put
a lot of thought into this.
But whether you like it or not,
officially, I'm
the older brother
and you're the younger one.
Sure, whatever!
[gasps]
--[MAN 1A grunts, yells]
--[crashing]
Are you kidding me?!
You kids are trespassing
here again?!
[OTOMI gasps]
[MAN 1A]
Hey, get back here, ya brats!
[NARRATOR] Our story
follows Meisei High School.
Champions on their
first and only trip
to Koshien Stadium 30 years ago.
[TOUMA] Oh, cool. Looks
like it stopped raining.
[SOUICHIROU]
Is spring vacation really over?
Come on. Don't you think we
deserve more time than this?
[TOUMA]
Don't blame me.
[SOUICHIROU]
Make the break longer!
[TOUMA grunts] How would
I even do anything about it?!
[SOUICHIROU] Hey! What the...
What are you doing?!
[TOUMA]
Oh, you'll see!
--[SOUICHIROU] Get away from me!
--[TOUMA] Hey, cut it out!
[SOUICHIROU]
You cut it out!
[OTOMI gasps, yelps]
[NARRATOR] This boy is
main character number one.
Touma Tachibana,
13 years old.
This boy is
main character number two.
Souichirou Tachibana,
also 13.
Stop messing around.
Get dressed, come downstairs,
and eat your breakfast
or you'll be late for school.
[NARRATOR]
And this is their little sister,
Otomi Tachibana.
Twelve years old.
Think of her as
main character number 3.
[OTOMI]
Let's go, Sou. Let's go, Tou.
I'll be right down, Otomi.
Man, I wish everyone
would stop calling me that.
What? Why?
Calling me
an appendage on your foot
isn't exactly flattering!
Oh! Well, what I did was take
Touma and chop off the end.
That's all.
And?
[OTOMI]
And I'm still calling you that.
What, your sister can't have a
silly nickname for her brother?
Maybe it'll catch on!
[TOUMA]
Ugh. Whatever.
[yawns]
You give us a hard time
about being late, look at you.
[MAYUMI] Her entrance
ceremony's tomorrow.
So she doesn't have to go today.
[laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Mother. Mayumi Tachibana.
Thirty-eight years old.
[EISUKE sighs] Otomi's finally
entering junior high school.
I can't believe it!
She's become such a fine lady!
[giggles]
[NARRATOR]
Father. Eisuke Tachibana.
Forty-one years old.
[EISUKE giggles]
That better not be my uniform!
Come on, Dad, you're gonna
get it all wrinkled doing that!
[MAYUMI]
She's right, honey!
Sorry.
Anyway, now you get it.
I'll see you at school tomorrow.
Now get going.
[BOTH sigh]
[SOUICHIROU]
I'm headin' out!
[TOUMA]
Same!
[TOUMA] It's annoying
that the high school is only
a minute from our house.
[SOUICHIROU] Two more years
and we can sleep in.
[NARRATOR]
After leaving home...
...walk halfway around
the High School grounds...
...cross one street,
and you'll arrive
at Meisei Junior High School.
[TOUMA] Doesn't matter
if we go left or right
around the High School.
Same amount of time.
[NARRATOR] It's really not far
enough to be complaining.
We could always just
cut through the grounds.
It'd be a straight shot, y'know.
[NARRATOR] Most of the other
students don't live as close.
So they commute
by train, bus, or bicycle.
Is it just me,
or does this dumb light
take forever to change?
[NARRATOR]
Stop complaining, you're lucky!
--[SOUICHIROU] Hmm?
--[TOUMA] Huh?
[cross walk jingle plays]
[tires squeal]
Have a good day, young sir.
[SOUICHIROU, TOUMA]
Morning.
[TOUMA]
It may be a new school year,
but I've still gotta deal
with the same rude people.
[SOUICHIROU]
We need longer vacations.
[school bell chimes]
--Hey, Otomi.
--Huh? What's up?
Clean the storeroom with me.
It would be a big help!
That seems random. Why?
Oh, it just came to mind. So?
Yeah, okay.
[MAYUMI]
Great! [giggles]
That's too bad.
I was hoping I'd get to
watch their first practice.
--[CLUB MEMBERS yelling]
--[bats clanking]
[CLUB MEMBER 1A grunts]
[CLUB MEMBER 1B grunts]
[DAISUKE grunts]
[TOUMA sighs]
[sighs]
[KUROYANAGI]
Nikaidou. It's that time.
Manager. I'll head out,
then. Thank you.
See ya. Good work out there.
That's exactly
one hour today, too.
[KUROYANAGI]
All right, listen up!
New students start tomorrow.
Which means we'll have
people interested in joining.
After that long break, you
should get yourselves back
into shape so we don't look bad.
--[CLUB MEMBERS] Yes, sir!
--[TADASHI] You two.
[TOUMA]
Captain?
It's just not gonna
happen today.
Yeah, we kinda figured.
[TOUMA]
I'm home!
Short practice?
[TOUMA] They're not gonna
overwork us on day one.
Did you get to pitch at all?
Not once. The manager was
watching the whole time, so...
[OTOMI]
Well, that's a relief.
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
I didn't miss you throw.
[TOUMA]
Oh, I getcha.
So where's Sou at?
On a date.
[OTOMI] That sounds like him.
I should have guessed.
[TOUMA]
What is it?
[OTOMI]
Like something to drink?
[TOUMA]
Sure.
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[ICHIBAN]
Interested in baseball, eh?
[OTOMI]
Hmm?
[ICHIBAN] Hmph. You're name's
Tachibana. At least, I think.
And you're...?
Ichiban Natsuno!
Oh! Yeah, that rings a bell!
Though if I'm being honest,
I only remember you because
I thought your name was funny
the first time I heard it.
[ICHIBAN]
Wow, That's mean.
You're entitled to your opinion,
but I like my name.
Ichiban means number one!
And likewise,
Natsu means summer!
So I'm destined to go
to the summer Koshien.
And be the ace pitcher
while I'm there!
So you won't be
at the spring Koshien?
Uh... Well...
I might be there, too,
they're not mutually exclusive.
So I take it you're
joining the team?
[ICHIBAN]
Mm. Yeah, it's my destiny!
[OTOMI]
Good luck with that.
From what I hear,
it's pretty tough.
What do you mean?
[CLUB MEMBER 1A grunts]
[CLUB MEMBER 1B grunts]
[DAISUKE grunts]
[ICHIBAN]
So is that guy our ace pitcher?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
That's Nikaidou.
He's in ninth grade.
[ICHIBAN] Huh. I figured I'd
have to wait a year at least.
But I'll be number
one in no time.
Whoops! Just talkin' to myself!
You speak pretty
loudly for someone
who's talking to himself.
So, you wanna become a pitcher?
[ICHIBAN]
Yeah! Ichiban Natsuno!
The ace of summer!
It's my destiny to
stand atop the pitcher's mound
at the summer Koshien!
So you're not gonna
be at the spring one.
Uh. I mean, I could be,
they're not mutually exclusive.
[gasps]
Tachibana, huh?
Yeah.
The name's Touma Tachibana,
eighth grade. Nice to meet ya.
Yeah.
[TOUMA]
Well, back on topic.
Koshien is a tournament
for high school teams.
No need to rush.
Take your time.
I don't know about that pitcher,
but the guy who's
catching is somethin' else.
That's Souichirou Tachibana,
also eighth grade.
[ICHIBAN]
The same last name?
Are you two brothers?
[TOUMA]
Yup.
[ICHIBAN]
You don't look all that alike.
For twins, at least.
That's probably
'cause we're not twins.
[ICHIBAN]
Huh? But...
Oh. I see.
You two were born
almost a year apart,
within the same school year!
We share a birthday. So, no.
[gasps]
[TADASHI]
New members, gather 'round!
[CLUB MEMBERS]
Right!
I'm Kuroyanagi,
the club manager.
To start, let's have you
all show me your stuff,
so I can put you in
the right positions.
Those of you
who want to be a pitcher,
step forward.
[ICHIBAN]
That's me!
[FIRST YEAR 1A]
Yeah.
[FIRST YEAR 1B]
Me, too.
[KUROYANAGI]
Hmm...
[ICHIBAN]
Hmm!
[FIRST YEARS whimper]
Tachibana. Catch for them.
Five pitches each
should be enough.
All right.
Oh. Sorry about that.
Won't happen again!
Hey, come on, man!
You can't let your nerves
get the better of you.
[FIRST YEAR 1A]
Sorry again!
[sighs]
[KUROYANAGI]
Next!
[FIRST YEAR 1B grunts]
[KUROYANAGI]
Okay, next!
[ICHIBAN]
I'm up!
Ichiban Natsuno!
About to shock and awe!
You know, he's not half bad.
Sorta. Yeah.
[ICHIBAN] I'm gonna hit
yah with a slider next!
[CLUB MEMBERS gasping]
All right, that's enough.
Natsuno!
Yes, sir?
I think the outfield might be
the best place for you.
So head on out there.
What?!
Manager. I'm leaving now.
Right. Nice work today.
Outfield?
If I were in his shoes,
I'd make that face, too.
Yeah, huh...
[ICHIBAN] I don't get it!
What is that manager thinking?
Hate to say I told you so,
but I kinda told you so.
Oh! By the way...
The two Tachibana brothers
on the baseball team.
You mean my brothers?
What about 'em?
[ICHIBAN] They're in the same
grade with the same birthday
but aren't twins?
How can that be?
Doesn't makes sense.
Oh, yeah. It's because--
[YOSHIKO]
Hey, Otomi!
[OTOMI]
Yoshiko.
I talked to my mom this morning.
She said you can come by
and pick out a puppy
whatever time works
best for you.
Really? That's awesome!
--[giggles] Puppy!
--Hey, wait!
Don't leave me hanging.
At least finish your thought.
[CLUB MEMBERS talking,
bats clanking]
Manager. I'm heading out.
Okay. Nice job today.
[ICHIBAN] Does that guy always
get to leave practice early?
I thought he was our ace.
[TADASHI]
He is, and yes,
he leaves after about
an hour every day.
This is a more relaxed
club than I expected.
I guess. We've kinda
gotten used to being weak.
And we're not the
only ones who have.
The High School team
is just as easy-going.
[ICHIBAN] But the team's
been to the Koshien tournament
before, right?
The High School team, I mean.
Yeah, sure, but that
was practically forever ago.
And it was only once.
[CLUB MEMBER 1C grunts]
[CLUB MEMBER 1E groans]
Man. I clearly should
have done more research
before I chose
to go to this school.
[SOUICHIROU]
Touma.
[TOUMA]
Yeah?
I just saw the manager leave.
He'll be gone for a while.
Roger that.
[TADASHI grunts]
[ICHIBAN] What's the
deal with the Tachibana
who isn't a catcher?
Him? That's Touma,
he's been our third baseman
since the seventh grade.
I see.
[ICHIBAN]
Huh...?
[gasps]
[FIRST YEARS gasping]
[ICHIBAN whimpers]
What position?
I don't think I heard you right.
Third base.
[SOUICHIROU]
I'm home!
[TOUMA]
Me, too!
Man, I'm thirsty. What's this?
Oh, that on the table?
We found it while
cleaning out the storeroom.
Maybe it belongs to Dad.
Nah. This isn't his.
[NARRATOR]
Well then. This uniform.
Number One.
Whose could it be?
[OTOMI]
Next time, on Mix .
[TOUMA] Hey. So which
one of us is the big brother?
[SOUICHIROU]
Hm? You can be.
[TOUMA]
No, no, no. You can.
[SOUICHIROU]
No, you.
--[TOUMA] You.
--[SOUICHIROU] You.
--[TOUMA] You!
--[SOUICHIROU] You!
--[OTOMI] Then I'll be it!
[TOUMA, SOUHICHIROU]
Why you?
[OTOMI]
Next time,
"I'm Big Brother,
and You're Little Brother."
I don't care.
They're both big brothers to me!
[DOG 1A whines]
[barks]