[DAISUKE]
Tachibana!
Hey! Tachibana!
[TOUMA]
Um. Yeah?
Oh, you're not the right one.
I'm looking for
the other Tachibana.
You mean Souichirou?
He's not here today.
Not here?
Yeah, he's got a family thing.
Today's the anniversary
of his dad's passing.
He and his sister are visiting
the grave to pay respects.
[DAISUKE gasps]
Paying their respects...
Yeah.
[DAISUKE]
Nobody told me about that.
Really?
Well, that's kinda weird.
Pretty much everybody knows.
Anyway, he did get permission.
He talked to the
manager and captain
after practice yesterday.
Oh! I see what happened!
It was after practice,
so of course you weren't there.
That makes perfect sense.
Because you always leave
early, for some reason.
[TOUMA sighs]
You two seemed like you were
both ready for a fight.
Yeah. I don't think he was.
Lame.
[TADASHI]
Nikaidou!
Want me to catch?
We could do it like back in
the day, for old times' sake.
I think I'll pass.
We've got an important
game coming up.
I don't want to lose
my touch by practicing
with someone like you.
O... kay.
[ICHIBAN]
Wait a sec!
Our ace just freakin'
took off. What the heck?
Our next game is
gonna be our last.
Well, bye‐bye, tournament.
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once‐triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[NARRATOR] The National Junior
High School Baseball Tournament.
National Juniors for short.
The final round
of the preliminaries,
with a trip to the Tokyo
Tournament on the line.
[STUDENTS whooping]
[PLAYER 04A grunts]
[PLAYER 04B grunts]
[PLAYER 04C grunts, gasps]
[TOUMA] No matter how you
look at it, there's no way.
[pants]
[TOUMA] Not with that
speed or that force.
[GIRL 04A]
You've got this!
[BOY 04A]
Over the fence!
[DAISUKE grunts]
[STUDENTS cheering]
[SOUICHIROU]
Third!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[gasps]
Yeah!
[cheering]
[TOUMA]
How'd he pitch a whole game?
[DAISUKE bellows]
How do you like that, Tachibana?
It was pretty impressive.
Sorry, couldn't hear you!
Good game.
Say it out loud.
Tachibana. Tell me who the
ace pitcher of this team is.
Well, Nikaidou, you wear
the number one uniform,
so you tell me.
[DAISUKE] Did you hear
what he said, Tachibana?
Was that to me?
In your faces!
I guess he was trying to
prove a point to you, right?
All I said was that he wears
the number one uniform,
but... point taken.
[SOUICHIROU]
A complete victory today.
Not to mention Meisei's first
Tokyo Tournament in 20 years.
He's so puffed up,
I don't know how that
number one uniform still fits.
[TOUMA] Yeah...
This is really gonna suck.
[NARRATOR]
They were right.
And, as the saying goes:
when it rains, it pours.
[school bell chimes]
What?
With all the excitement
around the game,
this totally slipped my mind.
[KOMA]
Hey, there, nemesis.
I bet you're feeling kinda
cocky 'cause you beat me by
a measly five points on the
midterm exam, but this time,
I made sure to be prepared.
You're done for.
Moron! I told you I had a cold
during the midterm
and was feeling like crap,
and I still beat you!
Just you wait!
Excuses, excuses.
But, whatever helps you
sleep at night, buddy.
You're toast.
Okay, how 'bout this:
If I score higher than you,
then you have to agree
to let me take Otomi
out on a date.
[TOUMA]
Hmm...
And what happens if you lose?
I'll introduce you
to my little sister.
Are you kidding me?!
She just started elementary
school, you weirdo!
Anyway, Otomi's my stepsister.
I don't have a say
in who she dates.
Fine. I'll ask her real brother.
How 'bout it?
[SOUICHIROU]
Sure, go ahead.
‐‐Wait, what?
‐‐Yes! Home run!
For real?
Hey. I can't seem to figure
this one question out.
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
Where is Sou?
[TOUMA]
He's taking a bath.
‐‐Oh. Boo.
‐‐Is something wrong?
[OTOMI]
Never mind.
Whatcha doin' in here?
Isn't it obvious?!
Studying for a test!
Ever heard of tests?
Oh. Okay.
[TOUMA growls] Why'd you say
"Oh" all weird like that?
[OTOMI]
Good luck with your test.
[TOUMA]
And what're you grinning about?!
What's with you?!
[OTOMI]
I wasn't grinning.
[TOUMA]
You were so grinning!
[OTOMI]
No, I wasn't.
[TOUMA]
What is your problem?!
Can't a guy just
take a bath in peace?
[NARRATOR] That day, bookstore
gift cards were handed out
to every baseball club member.
The President and Chairman
of the Nikaidou Electric Company
sent them as congratulations
for getting Meisei to
the Tokyo Tournament
for the first time in 20 years.
The cards were
greatly appreciated...
After the test,
I'm gonna blow this on comics
and then throw it
right in the garbage.
‐‐[SOUICHIROU snores]
‐‐[TOUMA] Hmm?
Seriously? He's not even
the least bit concerned?
[dog howls]
[TEACHER 04A] I'm coming
around with your tests.
[KOMA]
Wow.
Well, you've gotten
better at guessing.
Ha‐ha! Statistical analysis
is way better than studying!
So, highest score is the winner.
What did you get? Touma?
[TOUMA snores]
Hey, wake up!
You can't avoid me like this!
Gimme that test. Jeez.
[TEACHER 04A] Now. As usual,
it's time to congratulate
the students with
the top five scores.
First place:
Souichirou Tachibana.
[STUDENTS gaspin]
[TEACHER 04A]
Second: Chie Komatsu.
[KOMA]
Hm! Ha! Forget the top five.
As long as I outscore this guy.
[TEACHER 04A]
And, fifth:
Touma Tachibana.
Like I said, who cares?
Huh?
[STUDENTS gasping]
[KOMA]
Uhh...
[TOUMA snores]
[OTOMI] Tou! Your dinner's
gonna get cold! Come eat!
Hey!
[SOUICHIROU]
You should just let him sleep.
He's been hitting
the books pretty hard.
What?
While it's true that Nikaidou
might be tenacious, and have
the focus to pitch a whole game,
he doesn't have
anything on Touma.
[OTOMI] I'm not quite sure
I understand the connection.
But I think you're
complimenting, Tou.
Is that right?
[SOUICHIROU]
Yeah.
Well. I'm glad.
Better rest up
while you can... Ace.
[TOUMA snores]
[NARRATOR] Now that they're
done with interim testing,
summer vacation is
right around the corner!
Which means, so is
the Tokyo Tournament,
and the excitement that brings.
[PLAYERS yelling]
[TOUMA]
What the heck is going on?
That guy hasn't even been
bothering to show up
for his usual one hour
of practice lately.
So much for our number one guy.
I guess winning
the block made him think
he doesn't have to
work for it anymore.
I don't know, it didn't
really seem that way to me.
Whatever. Think what you want.
I know I wouldn't complain if
he decided he wanted to retire
on a high note.
I can't imagine
he'd do that, either.
What're we gonna to do?
The first match of the Tokyo
Tournament is coming up quickly!
[SOUICHIROU]
Don't worry about it!
We've got a great
manager, you know!
No matter how tough
the situation,
we can always count on
our brilliant manager!
Are you done being stupid?
I got you this.
It's a DVD of the
first round opponent.
We're counting on you
to lead us to victory.
Study it.
Hey, what kind of team are they?
They're tough.
[PUNCH growls]
[TOUMA]
I'm not gonna peek! Gross!
Dumb dog.
[TOUMA]
What's the verdict?
What kind of offense
have they got?
[SOUICHIROU]
We can beat these guys.
But only if you're on the mound.
So...
[TOUMA sighs]
[SOUICHIROU] Getting a hit
is a different story.
Wait, why do you say that?
What's his curve like?
Drops off a freakin' shelf.
And his fastball. It's wicked.
Ace pitcher Takumi
Nishimura, eighth grade.
In the prelims, every game he
pitched was almost a no‐hitter.
Whatcha think?
The first round... Can we win?
[SOUICHIROU] Yeah. I mean,
if Touma is pitching, that is.
Oh... So, they're good, then.
[SOUICHIROU]
Yeah. Really good.
[NARRATOR]
The day before the match.
[ICHIBAN] Oh, I see Nikaidou
finally decided to show up.
[TOUMA] Yeah. Without
so much as a "sorry," either.
Jerk.
[DAISUKE grunts]
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
[DAISUKE sighs]
[PLAYERS]
Left! Right! Left! Right!
What the‐‐?
Our Ace pitcher already
left and today of all days?
Yeah. Without so much
as a, "sorry," either.
Jerk.
[TOUMA]
Sou! How did he do?
Our ace pitcher who never
comes to practice, that is.
No speed or
movement on the ball.
So just like every other day.
No, it was even
worse than usual.
The jerk.
Of course. Why doesn't
he take this seriously?
[KUROYANAGI] I'm about
to make your day, boys!
We've been blessed with
some ice‐cold sports drinks.
They're sent to us as a generous
gift from Chairman Nikaidou.
You should appreciate
his kindness.
[PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
Really? He thinks he can
buy us off with sports drinks?
[NARRATOR]
The Tokyo Tournament has begun.
[PLAYERS murmuring]
[YASUNO] Huh? You sure
you want me to do that?
Manager!
[KUROYANAGI]
I'm counting on you, Yasuno.
[TOUMA]
Manager!
[YOSHIKO]
Otomi!
The game's about to start and
our ace hasn't even shown up!
[SOUICHIROU] So, both teams are
starting with backup pitchers.
But the circumstances
are completely different!
The other team is resting
their ace pitcher because
they don't think we're worth it!
Well, don't get mad at me.
Just shake it off.
We gotta focus on scoring
as much as possible
before he shows up.
Morons! Useless manager,
useless ace pitcher!
[growls]
[CROWD cheers]
[UMPIRE 04A]
Safe!
He's so focused,
even when he's angry.
Man. Amazing.
[NARRATOR]
The second batter sacrifices
to get Touma on second.
Batting third is
Souichirou Tachibana.
And, batting cleanup,
Tadashi Imagawa.
[CROWD murmurin]
[CROWD cheering]
All right! Way to put
us on the board with style!
[YASUNO grunts]
‐‐[PLAYER 04G grunts]
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
Tied it up already? Not good.
[PLAYER 04H grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
And now they're in the lead.
That was fast.
Don't sweat it too much, Yasuno.
You're pitching low, so they're
not getting any extra‐base hits.
They're not gonna be scoring
too many runs like that.
Right!
We're batting from the top of
the order this inning, boys!
You've got it, Touma!
[TOUMA]
Yeah! Make it two for two!
Yeah!
So, like, between
your two brothers,
Tou's the louder one, huh?
Sou seems quieter.
Tou bottles up his
feelings most of the time,
and then when
he gets onto the field,
he's suddenly able
to release them.
Been that way for two years.
[NARRATOR] With one out,
the second batter sacrifices.
Runner on second.
Who's batting next?
[CROWD murmurin]
[FEMALE STUDENTS squealing]
That kid sure is popular.
[UMPIRE 04B]
Ball four!
If we let guys
like that get a hit,
well then, we're just
adding to their momentum.
These dorks won't
know what hit 'em.
That's okay,
it's called "cleanup."
There's a reason for that!
[TADASHI grunts]
That's strike three!
Batter, you're outta here!
[CROWD groaning]
[NARRATOR] Two outs,
men on first and second.
No big deal, I'm one for two.
Still pretty good,
if you ask me.
‐‐[bat clanks]
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
[KOMA]
Huh...?
[PLAYER 04I gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
[MIZUKAMI MANAGER]
You're up, Ace.
'Kay!
[NARRATOR]
Struck out in three pitches.
Nice
I gotta admit,
this is shaping up to be
a pretty exciting game.
Sure is. Thanks to a
certain someone not being here.
[YASUNO chuckles]
[PLAYER 04J grunts]
[TADASHI grunts]
[UMPIRE 04B]
Three outs! Change!
[CROWD cheering]
Told you so.
These guys won't be
scoring too many runs.
Yeah. Right.
For two whole innings in a row,
we had three hits
and only one run.
Our offense had better
get it together fast.
[NISHIMURA]
We'll be in the lead soon.
Even if we score one at a time.
[MIZUKAMI MANAGER]
Hmm...
[sighs]
We're taking turns scoring.
This game is wrecking my nerves.
I can't handle it.
Yeah, I'm with you.
Don't worry, still
a lot of baseball to play.
[PLAYER 04K grunts]
‐‐[NISHIMURA grunts]
‐‐[gasps]
[NARRATOR]
Three up, three down.
Looks like it's gonna
be pretty much impossible
to get a home run now.
[CROWD yelling]
[TADASHI sighs]
‐‐[YASUNO grunts]
‐‐[PLAYER 04M grunts]
[PLAYER 04N groans]
[TOUMA] Don't sweat it!
He wasn't able to square up.
Uh, but they've cut our
lead down to a single run.
Exactly! We're still
beating these guys!
Even if by one.
It's the Tokyo Tournament!
And you started this
game off right, Yasuno!
Whoa. Yeah.
I guess you've got a point.
I did start us off.
Right. You got this dude, okay?
[YASUNO grunts]
[PLAYER 04G gasps]
[TAKEUCHI]
Hmm.
[YASUNO grunts]
[UMPIRE 04B]
Strike! Batter is out!
[TAKEUCHI gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
[YASUNO chuckles]
[TAKEUCHI]
I can't believe this!
That kid struck me out in three
pitches throwing like that?!
Against me, the freaking
cleanup batter! How?!
Maybe you went up
to bat with that attitude
and jinxed it.
Huh?!
[NISHIMURA]
That's Souichirou Tachibana.
I wish he was our catcher.
Be cool if we could
trade for him.
[TAKEUCHI gasps]
Why don't you say that again
to my face, Nishimura?!
[NISHIMURA]
So, the Tachibana brothers, huh?
[UMPIRE 04B]
Strike!
[TOUMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 04B]
Foul!
[TOUMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 04B]
Foul!
Hey, Touma!
Don't swing at anything
off the plate!
Right!
[TAKEUCHI sighs]
‐‐[TAKEUCHI gasps]
‐‐[NISHIMURA] Idiot.
This guy's been waiting for
my fastball the whole time.
[TOUMA] He figured me out.
In that case, I'll have to‐‐
[CROWD applauds]
[TOUMA]
Ugh!
[TAKEUCHI grunts]
[TAKEUCHI]
Dang it!
[UMPIRE 04B]
Safe!
Like I said, I want a trade.
[TAKEUCHI]
What'd you say?!
What's he looking at?
The stands?
[SOUICHIROU gasps]
He's here?
‐‐Yeah, he just showed up.
‐‐Just perfect.
Well, he's going in.
He's our ace pitcher after all.
[NARRATOR]
Second batter, sacrifice bunt.
He fails.
[ANNOUNCER 04A]
Batting third, catcher.
Souichirou Tachibana.
No one wants a catcher
who's too popular
with the girls.
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
[NISHIMURA] He seems like he's
in a bad mood all of a sudden.
Oh, well.
‐‐[NISHIMURA gasps]
‐‐Ah, crap!
‐‐[SOUICHIROU snarls]
‐‐[YOSHIKO] A double play.
Was that a tantrum?
That's unusual
for a guy like Sou.
Bet I can guess the reason.
[ANNOUNCER 04A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
announcing a player change
for Meisei Junior High.
Pitcher Yasuno will step out
and be replaced by Nikaidou.
Nikaidou is now ninth
in the batting order.
Ugh, I knew it. Him.
[SHIMAZAKI] We've been waiting
for you, ace! Go get 'em!
[TANAKA]
We're counting on you, kid!
[DAISUKE grunts]
[UMPIRE 04B]
Strike!
[SHIMAZAKI]
Atta boy!
[SUBORDINATE A]
Way to go, ace!
[chuckles]
So, I'm guessing that
guy's your ace pitcher?
Nah, man.
Just the guy who wears
the number one uniform.
He's nothing like
the ace on your team.
[NISHIMURA]
I'm convinced.
I definitely want a trade.
[CROWD cheers]
‐‐[doorbell rings]
‐‐[PUNCH grunts]
[doorbell ringing]
[SOUICHIROU]
Next time, on Mix.
[TOUMA] Hey. I think I've seen
that Nishimura guy before,
but I can't put my finger on it.
[OTOMI] Where do you
think you've seen him?
[TOUMA] Some TV show
from back in the day.
[OTOMI] That anime where
the guys' head is a bean bun?
[SOUICHIROU]
No. Come on.
[OTOMI] The one where
they collect seven balls
and get wishes?
[SOUICHIROU]
Seriously?
Next time,
"You're a Pitcher, Right?"
[TOUMA]
Oh! I just remembered!
[PUNCH barks]