[NARRATOR]
Okay, then! Previously on Mix !
[NARRATOR] The fight for a spot
in the summer Koshien kicked off
with the start of the
East Tokyo Tournament!
[NARRATOR] After 30 years,
Meisei High School
is giving their all to return
to their former glory.
Their first opponent
of the tournament is
Kenjo High School, and their
famed slugger, Tomohito Akai.
[DAISUKE coughs]
ICHIBAN]
Huh?
[TADASHI]
[TODOROKI]
Wha--?
[TADASHI yelps]
[TODOROKI growls]
[TADASHI]
Phew!
[UMPIRE 13B]
Out!
Gettin' to old for this.
[NARRATOR] In the middle
of the fourth inning,
the score is tied at zero.
Yum!
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventure
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[STUDENTS chatting, laughing]
[YOSHIKO]
Otomi!
[OTOMI]
I'm coming.
Hmm?
[whistle blows]
[TEACHER 14A]
Everyone, gather 'round!
[CROWD chatterin]
[MUROTANI gasps]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Out!
I almost feel bad for them.
With Kita's irregular form
and off-speed pitches,
there's no way they can adjust
to him in a single game--
[CROWD cheers]
[KOMIYAMA gasps]
--Touma.
--Yeah, Coach?
Your brother is staying
uncomfortably calm
in this high-pressure situation.
I guess.
He's just always been kind
of a weirdo like that.
Okay! My turn!
Ah, crap.
--[CROWD cheers]
--[UMPIRE 13B] Out!
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike three! You're out!
[OOYAMA]
Hmm... Still sittin' at zero.
[TOUMA] Hopefully, that'll
change in the second half.
But those pitches
are gonna be a problem.
Only obnoxious
weirdos could adapt
to those things on the fly.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm... Koma. Nangou.
You two are pinch hitting.
What's he implying?
[NANGOU]
Hmm...
[CROWD murmuring]
[cell phone rings]
[ICHIBAN]
Hmm?
Hello?
[OTOMI]
What inning is it?
[ICHIBAN]
Ah! Otomi?
I uh, I have no idea
what you're talking about!
I've been at home sick all day!
I think I must've caught
a cold or something.
[coughs]
[KENJO TEAM 14D grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
You're out!
[CROWD cheering]
[OTOMI] Well, you must live
in a pretty lively home.
[ICHIBAN] Oh! That's because
a popular manga artist
just passed by!
I wouldn't be surprised
if the whole neighborhood
was following him!
I think another
one of his works--
Don't you lie to me!
I'm ditching class right
now to call you for an update,
so I don't have a lot of time.
[ICHIBAN]
Wait, what class?
[OTOMI]
Swimming class.
[ICHIBAN]
Ah, okay, okay.
Ah! So, are you...
wearing a swimsuit?
Why does that matter?!
[ICHIBAN] So, could you maybe
send me a picture of it, or...?
[OTOMI]
Don't be gross!
Stop asking stupid questions
and tell me what's happening
in the game.
[ICHIBAN]
Yeah, sure! Uh, let's see....
It's the bottom of the fifth,
and Meisei's up to bat.
Touma's actually in the batter's
box right now, batting sixth.
[OTOMI]
Great!
[ICHIBAN] But, the opposing
pitcher is a lefty who throws
some pretty unusual pitches.
Meisei's only been able
to get in two hits in so far.
[OTOMI]
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
[ICHIBAN] But the first
time he was up to bat,
Touma couldn't figure
out the timing at all
and struck out swinging.
[OTOMI]
He'll figure it out!
[ICHIBAN]
I dunno.
Those pitches do this little dip
thing, and it's really ha--
[OTOMI]
Come on, Tou! Hit the ball!
[ICHIBAN] Would you listen
when I'm talking to you?
[bat clangs
[CROWD gasping]
[MEISEI TEAM gasping]
[KOMIYAMA]
Hmm...
[CROWD cheering]
Yeah! He knocked
it outta the park!
[ICHIBAN]
Okay, so...
Now in the bottom of the fifth,
Meisei is up one to nothing.
Awesome!
I'm counting on you to text me
an update after every inning.
[ICHIBAN]
Can do!
So, where'd we land on that
whole swimsuit thing--
--[beep]
--[ICHIBAN] Uh...
[DAISUKE]
You had to make it awkward.
Correct me if
I'm wrong, but, uh...
Otomi's in class now, right?
She is.
[TOUMA]
'Kay. That's what I thought.
Must be hearing things.
And here you called
your brother the weirdo. Huh.
[TOUMA]
Hmm...
[NARRATOR] Then, with one
out in the fifth inning,
Meisei's pinch hitters,
Koma and Nangou
get on base
with consecutive hits.
[MEISEI TEAM cheers]
[NARRATOR]
However...
[NARRATOR] Their lead stays
short with just one run.
Looks like our team
is full of weirdos. Huh.
[NANGOU, KOMA growl]
[ICHIBAN sighs]
Still the same score.
Oh, right! Gotta
send the update!
[ICHIBAN] Hmm...?
She hasn't read it yet...
[DAISUKE]
Maybe she's getting changed.
[ICHIBAN]
G-Getting changed?
[whistle blows]
Huh?
[KOMIYAMA]
I suppose, in hindsight,
I should've done more
research on them.
Meisei has surprised me.
They've only
scored a single run.
I'm aware of that.
And I'm also well aware
that our own team
won't go down so easily.
So, don't worry.
[inaudible]
[TEACHER 14A]
Akai? Akai!
[gasps]
Uh, right. Mitsuru Adachi.
Tell me more about this person.
Other than the fact
that he's a manga artist?
[TEACHER 14A]
That's right.
[RYOU]
Let me think.
I explained it all to
the class a moment ago.
[ARISA]
Teacher! If I could interject.
He was a big fan of the--
[TEACHER 14A]
Miss Mita! I wasn't asking you.
[ARISA growls]
Well then?
[RYOU] I'm sorry, sir.
I wasn't listening.
Stand at the back of the class!
[RYOU]
Yes, sir.
[CLASSMATES laugh]
[OTOMI sighs]
[CROWD murmuring]
[cell phone rings]
[ICHIBAN]
Hmm?
Hello?
[OTOMI] I forgot to
ask you this earlier,
but how's Akai's brother doing?
You know who he is, right?
[ICHIBAN]
Akai's brother?
[gasps]
Don't tell me Kenjo's cleanup
hitter is also Akai's brother!
I guess he is.
Wow, who woulda thunk it?
[OTOMI]
So how's he doing?
[ICHIBAN]
Oh, yeah. Let's see...
I remember he had
a double his first at bat.
Then we lucked out and
he hit into a double play.
--[ICHIBAN] And then...
--[bat clangs]
--[CROWD gasps]
--[ICHIBAN] Oh...
[CROWD cheers]
[ICHIBAN]
And then his third at bat...
[ICHIBAN] He made a comeback
and hit a two-run homer.
[PUNCH barks]
[TOUMA] Didn't think
someone could hit a home run
off that pitch.
Apparently, he can.
Without breaking a sweat.
Dang. It sucks
that he's playing us.
If only he was facing
a weaker team,
especially for the opening game.
He could've made a much
stronger debut as a hitter.
[SOUICHIROU] Hmm...
A home run and a double?
Plus, the out at first base
that could've easily been
an extra-base hit.
His debut is plenty strong.
What if he strikes
out his last at bat?
[gasps] In any case,
the batter before him reaching
base safely after the
strikeout is bad news.
Oh, yeah, and I wonder
who's fault that is.
It's yours! Don't be stupid!
You know that anyone could've
seen that wild pitch coming!
Before you talk, you should
really follow through with
what you said
you were gonna do.
Come on! There's
no reason to argue, guys!
The comeback starts right now!
And we're only down
by a single run!
That's encouraging and all.
But I'm not sure that should be
coming from our cleanup hitter.
Especially when he can't
bring our third batter home,
who's been on base three times.
You listen here!
The comeback starts right now
whether you like it or not!
Come on, Imagawa!
Not during the game!
[TADASHI]
But you heard what he said!
--[MUROTANI] Imagawa!
--[sighs]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Hey, you! Break it up!
[overlapping yelling]
[ICHIBAN] I hope those
guys can work things out.
[DAISUKE] They'll be fine.
Since I'm not on the team.
An impressive hit.
It was luck. That's all.
Well, that's humble of you.
I never pegged you
as the modest type.
Regardless, that
home run of yours
is still a home run.
And taking the lead this late
into the game gives our opponent
fewer chances to
make a comeback.
[AKAI]
We're only leading by one.
[KOMIYAMA]
Hmm?
Just one.
[TOUMA grunts]
I'm not going to let
my guard down yet.
Especially against them.
[KOMIYAMA]
Huh.
[TOUMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike three! You're out!
Baseball, like any sport,
is played to win.
Wouldn't you agree, Akai?
[ANNOUNCER 13A] Bottom
of the seventh inning,
batting sixth for
Meisei High School,
pitcher, Touma Tachibana.
[MEISEI TEAM laughs]
Aw, yeah! Let's see ya hit
another home run, Touma!
Don't psyche him out.
Okay! Comin' right up!
Ah, crap.
[KITA]
Hmm...
[KOMIYAMA growls]
[TOUMA gasps]
[gasping]
[CROWD murmuring]
[BOTH gasp]
[OOYAMA gasps]
[MEISEI TEAM 14A]
Hey! Tachibana! You all right?
That guy's got some nerve!
--[OOYAMA] Koma!
--[KOMA growls]
[OOYAMA]
You gotta hold Nangou back!
Uh, wha...?
[NANGOU roars]
[BOTH grunt]
[TOUMA groans]
Oh, boy.
So. No hard feelings
if I "accidentally" hit you
when you're up to bat next.
[AKAI]
Yeah. Go ahead.
If that's the kind of baseball
you prefer to play. Sure.
[cell phone rings]
[ICHIBAN]
Hello?
[OTOMI]
Go get 'em! You got this, Tou!
[ICHIBAN]
Um, actually, about that...
Huh? Hang on. Isn't
Tou up to bat right now?
[ICHIBAN]
He was, but then, uh...
[TADASHI]
Was that just an accident?
Or was it on purpose?
Dunno. Doesn't
really matter though,
since we can't prove it
one way or the other.
[grunts]
[NANGOU grunts]
--You're out!
--[CROWD applauds]
Huh. Looks like we're
starting to run out of steam.
[TADASHI] Hmph. 'Kay, guys!
Let's do our best out there!
[ICHIBAN]
The seventh inning is over,
and Kenjo leads two to one.
You should've
gone for the right arm.
[KOMIYAMA] That way, you
would've hindered his pitching.
I'm only kidding.
It can be easy to misinterpret
your serious expression.
Just a heads up.
Be careful of that.
Right.
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
Top of the eighth inning,
batting seventh for Kenjo High
School, is pitcher, Kita.
Better watch your back, Kita!
And your arm!
Wouldn't want you
to get hurt out there!
[laughs
[gasps]
[KITA growls]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
Strike three! You're out!
[CROWD cheers]
[KITA]
Nice pitching.
[TOUMA grunts]
[YAMAJI grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
You're out!
[CROWD cheers]
That makes five
strikeouts in a row!
[TOUMA]
Hmph!
[ICHIBAN gasps]
[DAISUKE]
He's the real deal.
[ICHIBAN]
Huh?
[DAISUKE] He deserves to wear
the number-one uniform.
[MAYUMI]
I'm home!
[PUNCH barks]
[MAYUMI sighs]
Today sure is a scorcher.
Well, would ya look at that?
You were a legendary
pitcher, weren't you?
[home phone rings]
[MAYUMI]
Hello? Tachibana residence.
Oh, hi, dear.
Huh? The result?
For what? For the game?
Oh! That's right.
[MAYUMI] No. I haven't
heard from them yet.
They said they'd call when
they're done with the game,
so I imagine
they're still playing.
[MAYUMI]
Yes, I know.
But there isn't anything
I can do about that!
All right, dear. I understand.
I'll see you later. Bye!
You never told me
much about it,
and you didn't have to.
I know your dream lives on.
Souichirou shares the
exact same dream you did.
[MAYUMI] And he's met the
best partner he could ask for.
[MAYUMI]
Of course!
I can't believe that
I didn't realize it sooner.
Now I finally understand
why I was able to move on
without any regrets.
It's all starting to make sense.
Oh! That reminds me.
I picked up something
at the bookstore.
[MAYUMI] I'm going
to study so I can cheer
those kids on properly.
And I just know you
and Touma's dear mother
will be cheering for them, too.
[PUNCH barks]
[MAYUMI gasps]
Please try and
keep it down, Punch.
I know you haven't
appeared much lately,
but you can't make
a scene like this.
[PUNCH barks]
[MAYUMI sighs]
[MAYUMI] I wonder if
we're winning. I hope so.
[NARRATOR]
No. We're losing.
[HARUKA]
Next time, on Mix .
[OOYAMA]
Hmm...
[HARUKA] Sounds like
something's bothering you, Dad.
[OOYAMA] I'm just wondering
what the best order would be.
First up, I'll start with beer.
Second, some tofu.
Third, sashimi.
Fourth, fried chicken.
Fifth, skewered chicken.
I'll put whisky and soda sixth.
Seventh, Kimchi, and
eighth smashed pickles.
[HARUKA] I thought you were
talking about batting order!
Next time: "I wanted
to See That Expression."
[OOYAMA]
I'll top it off with some ramen!
[PUNCH barks]