[TOUMA]
Hmm...?
[SUBORDINATE 06A] Hey! What
do you think you're doing?
Oh. I, um...
I'm just curious,
has this family suffered
some misfortune recently?
[BOTH]
Hmm...
[TOUMA whimpers]
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
Dang it! Well, it looks like
we worried for nothing.
They insisted there's
been no misfortune
for the Nikaido family lately.
Makes sense. I hear it
was more like a miracle.
[TOUMA]
Hmm? What do you mean?
Well...
[TADASHI]
Hey! Sorry I'm late.
[NARRATOR]
A long time ago,
the ace pitcher's father was
also on the Meisei team,
and in the very same position.
[NARRATOR]
Although, unlike his son,
in all the years he spent in
junior high and high school,
he never wore the ace uniform.
But, in those six years,
his genuine personality,
in stark contrast to his severe
looks, was the source
of countless fond memories
shared by the team.
Helping the boys forge
lifelong friendships.
The man's talent
would continue to bloom
after he took over
his father's business,
which he developed into
a successful major corporation.
Because of his stern look,
some were wary of him.
But those who knew him
well never had a harsh word
to say about him.
Or, so it goes.
The man had his only child,
a son, later in life.
He cherished the boy more
than most parents might.
When his son
began to play baseball,
the father was overjoyed.
He didn't care what anyone
thought when he bragged
that the boy was
a veritable prodigy.
In autumn of the
boy's seventh grade year,
the man couldn't help but
weep at the sight of his son
in the number one uniform.
Even though the team
manager had been
the man's best friend
since they were boys,
the man believed in his son's
talent and never doubted him.
It never crossed his mind
that the manager
might be playing favorites.
Then, six months later,
the son was diagnosed
with a rare heart condition.
[CROWD whooping]
[NARRATOR] But, for now,
let's change the subject.
[OTOMI gasps]
[NARRATOR] Otomi has come to
the local pool to have some fun
and relax with her girlfriends.
[OTOMI]
What do you want?
[NARRATOR]
You remember Otomi. Right?
Did you hear me?
What do you want?
Hi?
Oh. Hey, Natsuno.
Didn't see you.
I went by your house,
but your mom was
the only one home.
She told me you came to
the pool, so I ran over.
What can I do for you?
Oh. Uh...
To tell you the truth,
I'm actually looking
for your brothers.
But when I heard you were out
swimming, I had to stop by.
[splashing
Right! I almost forgot!
The manager of the baseball
team just up and quit
without warning!
Huh?
[ICHIBAN] Yeah, he didn't even
tell anyone why or anything!
He bowed and apologized,
and that was it!
Oh, and check this out.
He wants us to convince
Souichirou to be
the new team captain.
Whoa...
That's why I had to talk to you.
Can you tell your brothers
to please come by
the baseball field?
Like, as soon as they can?
You got it. Later.
[ICHIBAN]
Oh, hey, wait!
I-I'm free all afternoon!
Good for you. Later.
Huh...?
[ICHIBAN]
Uh, what just happened?
[NARRATOR]
The doctors called it a miracle.
That's how slim the chances
of the operation
succeeding were.
I hadn't thought about
what I would say in this moment.
Never imagined I'd live.
So besides your
parents and doctors,
the manager was the only person
who knew about your condition.
I bet you guys
have been talking
a lot of smack about me.
I've daydreamed about
you learning the truth.
I hoped you'd get wind of it
and live the rest of your lives
regretting all the
times you judged me.
Come on, man,
now you're just being rude.
[DAISUKE]
Only my dad had any hope.
He was sure the operation
would be a success.
Why were you so sure
it would be a failure?
Your dad was right.
But would you say he was right
when he told everyone
I was a baseball prodigy?
I didn't think I had much time.
So, the best way I knew to thank
my dad for believing in me
was to wear the
ace uniform and pitch
as many games as possible.
I mean, I can
think of other ways.
I dunno, like not dying
before your time?
You shouldn't hate
the manager for this.
I insisted on being
the ace pitcher,
and he was a loyal friend.
He refused to crush my father's
dreams and his unwavering belief
that I really was ace material.
Well, he took responsibility
and ended up quitting.
[DAISUKE] Yeah. I tried to stop
him, but he wouldn't listen.
Look, I'm not
going to apologize.
'Cause, like I said, I was
convinced I wouldn't make it.
You can call it self-indulgent.
I was dying.
Sure, fair enough.
Oh, I get it.
And I'm not gonna apologize
for all the smack
I've been talking
about you this whole time.
[DAISUKE]
I can understand that.
[SOUICHIROU]
What's wrong?
Would'ya look at that.
Another former pitcher who
never got a chance to wear
the ace uniform and
lives through his kids.
[PLAYERS yelling]
[TOUMA]
Although...
The biggest difference between
the two is that Nikaidou's dad
is a high-functioning member
of society, unlike our--
[grunts]
How's that for
"high functioning"?
With hearing and aim like that,
how come he was never the ace?
Come on!
[SOUICHIROU]
Where's Otomi?
She went to the pool a while ago
and hasn't come back yet.
The pool? Who's she with?
[MAYUMI]
You're so overprotective.
Yoshiko and her other
friends came to pick her up,
and they all went together.
You have no idea what it's like!
She's parading around half-naked
for dudes with one-track minds!
That's one way to put it.
[SOUICHIROU] Touma!
You better go pick her up!
Come on, man, really?
It's still light outside.
[SOUICHIROU]
The sun will set in no time,
and she'll be out
there in the dark!
What if something
happened to her?
I would hold you responsible!
If you're so worried,
why don't you go
and get her yourself?
Because it's your duty
as her older brother
to make sure she's
safe at all times!
[TOUMA]
You know what?
Despite how she looks,
Otomi is pretty capable of--
[SOUICHIROU] Stop talking
nonsense and go get your sister!
Hurry!
[TOUMA]
So lame.
When it comes to Otomi,
he's crazy.
[OTOMI]
Hey, Tou! Where are you going?
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
[BOTH chuckle]
Aw, give me a break!
Tell people when you're home!
[horn honks]
[DAISUKE'S FATHER] You're Touma
Tachibana, aren't you?
[TOUMA]
Uh, yeah?
[DAISUKE'S FATHER]
My son asked me
to personally
deliver this to you.
[DAISUKE'S FATHER]
For a single game,
the pitcher who will become the
next ace is supposed to borrow
the previous ace's number,
then replace it with a new
number one after that.
It's an old tradition in
the Meisei baseball club.
Well, you've got to follow
a prodigy like my son.
I'm sure you're feeling a
tremendous amount of pressure.
[NARRATOR]
He feels no pressure.
Whatever you do,
make sure you pitch in a way
that won't bring shame
to that ace number.
[laughs]
[NARRATOR]
That's going to be easy!
And please return
the number after the game.
It is a treasure
in our family, after all.
Yes, sir, I understand.
[DAISUKE'S FATHER]
Right. I'll be going now.
[TOUMA]
Oh, the surgery!
I'm really happy
it was a success.
[DAISUKE'S FATHER grunts]
[TOUMA]
They both act so tough.
Like father like son
[EISUKE chuckles]
[OTOMI]
Hmm!
[NARRATOR]
Touma Tachibana.
Age, 14 years and two months.
The Meisei Junior High
School baseball team's
number one pitcher.
[NARRATOR]
Now, then.
Because of the fact that
Manager Kuroyanagi just resigned
without giving the
team any explanation...
[NARRATOR] ...many of the
players left and never returned
after the Tokyo Tournament
because they were fed up,
[NARRATOR] On top of that,
most of the players who left
were in their
final year at Meisei
and had the most experience.
However, the Meisei
Junior High baseball club--
a mostly new team now made up
of seventh and eighth graders--
were still an elite force with
just enough members to play!
[PLAYER 06A grunts]
[NARRATOR]
Of course...
[PLAYER 03F gasps]
No need to rush! There's plenty
of time to get him out!
[PLAYER 03F grunts]
[PLAYER 03E gasps, grunts]
[UMPIRE 06A]
You're out!
[NARRATOR] ...that doesn't
mean all nine guys
in the starting
lineup are elite.
[TOUMA]
Sou!
[growls]
Sorry-- "Captain."
Yeah, whaddaya want?
You haven't given me
a single sign
for a fastball this whole time!
Shut up, moron.
Don't you dare
talk to me like that, ya jerk!
You know your
fastball wouldn't even
make contact with their bats.
What?
[SOUICHIROU] What our
guys need most right now
is practice fielding in a game.
So, that's what I'm focusing on.
[ICHIBAN]
He's a good captain.
[TOUMA]
Oh, I get it!
Then how 'bout I just
throw you a breaking ball
that won't hit the bat either.
Is that what you want?
[SOUICHIROU]
Moron.
[TOUMA] I told you not to talk
to me like that, dammit!
Know why your
breaking balls work?
It's because of how effective
your fastball is.
He is a good Captain.
[TOUMA growls]
Hey, Manager!
[TOUMA]
Manager!
[MIKAMI]
Hmm?
Hmm...?
You think you've got
a hang of the rules now?
I think so. I had no idea
there were so many
wonderful baseball
comics out there!
This is gonna be
a major test of their patience.
Especially for Touma.
The new captain is just
trying to help us save face.
For my dad and I, that is.
If a new ace stepped
on the mound
at the first practice
and blew them away,
it would put us in a bad light.
When you're in high school,
can't you keep playing baseball?
I've got a new lease on life,
it's a miracle I'm
even standing here.
Asking to play on top of that
seems pretty selfish.
[TADASHI]
Good point.
[PLAYERS yelling]
[TOUMA]
Finally. I've been waiting
all practice for that sign!
[yells]
[PLAYER 06D gasps]
You moron.
[PLAYER 06D whimpers]
[UMPIRE 06A whimpers]
[TOUMA chuckles nervously]
If anyone is gonna
show us another miracle...
...it'll be those two.
[DAISUKE]
Yeah.
[NARRATOR]
Before you know it,
one season
gives way to the next.
[STUDENTS cheering]
--Go!
--You got this! Stay focused!
Straight ahead!
[ISAMI]
And the Tachibana brothers?
How've they been doing lately?
Oh, man.
She's gotten even cuter.
Don't you think so?
[ISAMI] Uh... I asked you a
question about the brothers.
Yeah, I know.
The younger one's
Meisei's ace pitcher now.
Or at least
that's what I've heard.
[NISHIMURA]
Huh, fascinating.
[ISAMI growls]
[PLAYER 06E grunts]
Strike!
Wow. I guess he was right.
Yes! Awesome!
[NISHIMURA] Hey, Otomi!
It's been a long time.
[PLAYER 06E grunts]
[UMPIRE 06B]
Strike!
Heck, yeah! So, uh,
who are you, again?
Well, um, starting next year,
I'm going to be Seinan's
first-year ace pitcher.
--[bat clanks]
--My name's Nishi--
[OTOMI]
You got this Sou!
Awesome! No hits! No runs!
[laughs]
No-hitter? First time
he's thrown one?
If so, what of it?
Uh, nothing at all.
Just, congrats.
[OTOMI]
What do you want, Mr. Nishi?
Oh, actually, yeah,
my name's not Nishi.
--It's, uh...
--[GIRLS laughing]
That was amazing!
I had no idea
your bother was so good!
[NISHIMURA]
No, that's fine. That's cool.
[TOUMA growls]
I would think you'd
look a lot happier.
Why? Even if
I threw nine innings,
it's not like it
would be a record.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
There's no good reason
to get carried away
over something small like this.
After all, Nishimura's made
this kind of game a habit.
How 'bout you shut your mouth?!
We both know if it hadn't
been for your two errors,
I would've had a perfect game!
Right. Don't forget the two
that would've been
base hits if I hadn't made
fantastic plays on 'em.
[TOUMA]
Those weren't even great plays!
They were two easy fly balls!
[NARRATOR]
Whatever the case.
Thanks to their achievements
at the Tokyo Tournament
in their ninth-grade year,
the Tachibana brothers
have begun to make
quite a name for themselves.
[PUNCH barks]
[TADASHI]
Tachibana!
[SOUICHIROU]
Hm? Captain!
Nah, you're looking
at a lowly, new member
of the high school team.
You'll always be captain
in my heart, buddy.
You guys came close
at the Tokyo Tournament.
If only that moron
hadn't slammed
his stupid finger in
the door at the clubhouse.
--Sheesh.
--[TOUMA chuckles]
You've gotta keep
an eye on him
so he doesn't hurt himself.
You know that guy never
watches what he's doing.
[PLAYER 06F] Imagawa! Hurry up
with those balls, man!
Yeah!
First year of high school.
I bet it's tough.
It's nothing.
Especially compared
to how happy I am
that you guys'll be
on the team soon.
I can't wait
[PUNCH pants]
[SOUICHIROU]
Hmm?
[HARUKA]
Oh! Sorry about that!
You moving in?
I am.
[OOYAMA]
Hey! What are you doing, Haruka?
We haven't got all day!
'Kay!
I appreciate it.
[NARRATOR]
Then, when winter arrives...
...they meet again.
[OOYAMA]
Cheers!
[NARRATOR]
The man and the boy, that is.
Hey! Here come the
famous Tachibana brothers.
[SOUICHIROU]
Hmm?
This guy's an
old friend of my father's
from back in high school.
In town from Kyushu, apparently.
He was the captain
of their baseball team.
Wow, so you must've
gone to Meisei, too.
Watch what you say--
this jerk's no friend of mine!
Not till he pays me back!
Always so rude!
And in front of your children?
Anyway, you must
be proud of your boys.
You're the father of the
legendary Tachibana battery.
[EISUKE]
Never mind that! Cough it up!
With that attitude, it's no
wonder your wife got fed up
and walked out on you!
Hey, you better
show some respect.
You shouldn't talk to
your captain like that!
Well, captains
should act like captains
and pay their debts!
Here, here!
Pay back!
[OOYAMA]
So, which is which?
Who's pitcher and who's catcher?
Oh, uh, my son
is the pitcher,
and Sawai's son's the catcher.
Oh.
[EISUKE]
What? Are you surprised?
[OOYAMA] Well, sometimes
the apple does fall far
from the tree. You know?
Looking forward to watching you.
[BOTH]
Huh?
He tells us that
he's got a daughter.
She'll be at the same high
school as you in the spring.
She here?
[OOYAMA]
She's still back in Kyushu.
Until she graduates
from junior high.
Oh, I see.
[OTOMI, SOUICHIROU]
Hmm...?
[OOYAMA] My income will
stabilize starting in April.
After that, I'll be
able to pay you back.
What kind of work are you doing?
Oh! I'll be managing a baseball
team over at Meisei High.
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[EISUKE]
Ah?
[PUNCH]
Aroo?
[EISUKE] You better be joking,
you big jerk,
or I'll toss your
butt out into the cold!
[OOYAMA laughs]
[barks]
[OTOMI]
Hmm?
[CHILDREN]
Goodbye!
[TOUMA]
Otomi!
Oh! Hi, Touma!
[grunts]
[TOUMA]
Whoa, are you all right?
That hurt!
I can't walk. Carry me.
Don't be ridiculous.
That wasn't even
a bad fall to begin with.
[OTOMI]
Carry me!
[TOUMA]
Stop your whining.
[OTOMI]
That's amazing!
The snow covered
everything so fast!
[TOUMA] I hate it. Why is
it still snowing like this?
It's March, for crying out loud!
[OTOMI]
Who do you think's gonna win?
What do you mean?
You and Sou's competition
to become ace pitcher.
Oh, that. Well, the thing is...
He turned out to be much
stronger competition
than I thought he would be.
If I got to pick the winner,
I would definitely choose you.
And why's that?
Because when
you throw a baseball,
you shine like a
star or a rainbow!
What's that s'posed to mean?
And also...
[TOUMA]
Also what?
[OTOMI]
Because you carried me tonight!
[TOUMA]
Sheesh.
Here's the big hill.
It gets dangerous
when it's all snowy.
Only thing more dangerous
than walking uphill--
[MAN 06A gasps, wails]
[grunts]
Is going back downhill.
See?
[OTOMI] It's one of my most
vivid memories of Touma.
And something else
just came back to me.
I heard a weird sound
coming from Touma's boot
that night while
we made the trip home.
On his way to get me,
he'd taken the same route
and had a bad fall on the hill.
He tore the nail
off his big toe,
and the inside of
his boot had been
slowly filling up with blood.
[OTOMI wails]
[OTOMI] When we got home,
I saw the bloody boot and toe.
I cried like a little baby.
Tou laughed,
thinking it was funny
that I got so upset
over his toe.
But then Sou
misunderstood the situation
and punched Tou for laughing.
That's why Tou ended up
becoming the ace pitcher.
Heh. Just kidding.
[ICHIBAN]
Hey, Otomi!
Where ya head--
[yelps, yells]
[grunts]
Are you all right, Natsuno?
I hope you didn't
tear your nail off.
[ICHIBAN]
Huh...?
When spring comes,
you're off to high school.
Crazy.
[ICHIBAN]
You'll be in ninth grade, too.
[OTOMI]
Yeah. I suppose so.
Next time, on Mix!
[TOUMA] Apparently, Meisei High
School won the national trophy
in something other than
the Koshien tournament.
[SOUICHIROU]
Yeah. Rhythmic gymnastics.
[TOUMA]
That's not what I expected.
I wondered what
was going on in the gym.
Hey.,where are you going?
[SOUICHIROU]
Out for a jog.
[TOUMA]
Oh? Then I am, too!
[OTOMI] The gymnasium's
the other way, guys!
[OTOMI]
Next time: "Worried?"
Hey! You better stop peeking!
[PUNCH barks]