[NARRATOR] The National High
School Baseball Championship.
Strike three! You're out!
[CROWD cheering]
[NARRATOR] Finally, a top-ranked
high school is making
an appearance!
It's been 30 years since
that glorious summer.
And now, the once triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
This is the story
of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher;
along with their younger sister,
they face life's
countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal.
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[CROWD chattering]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
[CROWD cheers]
[SOUICHIROU]
I hear you, but...
How do I put this?
We won't even be facing Seinan
unless we make it to the finals.
[HARUKA]
Then make it to the finals.
[SOUICHIROU]
Okay, but to do that,
we need to defeat Tousei,
a top-ranked school.
And just so you know,
they won their last game
in five innings because
of the mercy rule.
[HARUKA]
Then you'd better defeat them.
[SOUICHIROU] Yeah, okay,
gotcha, but think about it.
Our team has a long
list of weaknesses
when you compare us
to a top-seeded team.
There's no contest.
Look, I'm not saying you
have to win all ten games
against them.
Just beat them once.
It's not rock-paper-scissors.
That'll be tougher
than you think.
It's a nine-inning game.
Winning by chance is rare.
Are you the type of
person who just likes
to contradict everything
anyone says?
Hey, take it easy.
It's the catcher's job to
observe things objectively.
I gotcha covered, 'kay?
[HARUKA] This isn't news
to me or anything,
but you and I will
never get along.
Huh?
Uh... Wait a minute!
Don't you know what they say?
Opposites attract,
especially when we're talking
about romantic situations.
What do you mean, "romantic"?
Relationships with
team members are--
[CROWD cheering]
[NISHIMURA]
Dang it!
I really had my heart
set on this game
being a no-hitter.
But with that, it'll be nothing
but a reference record
in the end.
Stop being such a perfectionist.
Get out there and
greet the other team.
Yeah, I'm going.
[UMPIRE 13A]
By the mercy rule, Seinan wins!
Thank you for playing us today!
--[CROWD clapping]
--[alarm blaring]
[HARUKA]
What? No way!
How can the game
be over already?
This whole thing is your fault!
Yeah, but, you know.
If we end up making
it to the finals,
then there's a high
likelihood we'll play Saijyou,
and they're the team
playing in the next game.
Well, this seems to be
a lucky coincidence.
Guess we better go ahead
and find ourselves some seats.
--[bat striking]
--[PLAYERS chatter]
[NANGOU yelling]
[TOUMA]
Nangou seems really angry.
What do you think he's
so worked up about?
Come on, isn't it obvious?
He's mad that the
manager sent Souichirou
to the game with Haruka
instead of with him.
That'd make no sense.
He sent the team member who's
best at collecting data.
Of course, but try
explaining that to him.
He won't listen to reason.
Hey, check it out!
Haruka and Souichirou
just showed up!
Oh, give it a rest!
How will we know what
we can do until we try?
Look, like I said,
baseball's not the same kinda
game as rock-paper-scissors!
[HARUKA]
Don't you think I know that?
You must think I'm stupid!
[SOUICHIROU] No, I don't,
but you keep saying things
you can't be sure of!
Ugh! Just forget it!
If I continue with
this conversation,
I might end up hating
baseball altogether.
Hey! Don't do that!
[SOUICHIROU]
Hm?
What's that about?
Never mind, just hurry up
and get changed already.
[SOUICHIROU]
You got it.
You don't see that every day.
A girl getting irritated
with Souichirou?
That's the truth.
[SOUICHIROU]
Praying to the baseball gods?
[OOYAMA]
Hm?
Oh! Souichirou!
Welcome back.
Look! A Meisei baseball relic.
It's a ball signed by the whole
national championship team.
[SOUICHIROU] So, what did you
ask the relic to help you with?
Making round 16.
Or the quarter finals.
What, do you think I'm
asking 'em for too much?
[SOUICHIROU] I can't believe you
two are father and daughter.
Uh... Wha--?
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
Ugh. I'm sorry.
The hose was coming
unscrewed, see,
and I was just
trying to stop it.
I don't have the use
of my left arm, after all.
You sprayed me on purpose.
No, I did not!
If I'd done it on purpose,
I wouldn't have gotten myself
soaking wet, too!
As a catcher,
why don't you
"observe this objectively."
Uh... Hey!
[SOUICHIROU] I can't drink
another one of those, jeez!
[OTOMI]
I heard you went to a game.
One of the top-ranked schools.
Sure did.
I thought we'd make it
in time for the Seinan game,
but it ended right
when we got there.
[OTOMI]
Okay.
But I thought you wouldn't
even have to face Seinan
unless you made
it to the finals.
Yeah, that's true.
[TOUMA] Then we'll
make it to the finals.
[PUNCH panting]
Right, but, to do that,
we'd also have
to get past Toushu.
[TOUMA]
Then we'll get past them.
--[PUNCH barks]
--[MAYUMI] Touma, dear!
It's getting late,
time to take your bath!
[TOUMA]
Okay!
[TOUMA] If all the seeded
schools get to the finals
like they're expected to,
then it won't be
a very interesting tournament.
[PUNCH barks]
But with us in there?
That's exciting!
Just imagine the hype if Meisei
High was able to defeat Toushu!
[barks]
That is a good point.
And then we can face Seinan.
Nishimura, you'd better be
ready to bring your A-game!
Yeah. I'll bring it!
[MAYUMI] Don't make me
say it again, Touma!
For now, you better
focus on your bath.
[TOUMA]
Okay!
He's optimistic.
[door closes]
He's another rock-paper-
scissors type. Great.
[OTOMI]
Hm?
[SOUICHIROU]
We're nothing alike.
You and who?
[SOUICHIROU]
Me and Touma.
Yeah, that's the truth.
You two are like night and day.
[TOUMA]
♪ On a journey ♪
--Here I go!
--[splash]
[SOUICHIROU]
When we were little,
we fought all the time,
didn't we?
[OTOMI]
You sure did.
[SOUICHIROU]
But now,
we get along
pretty well, I think.
Do you agree?
[OTOMI]
Are you kidding?
You two don't just
"get along pretty well."
You work together better
than anyone in Japan!
Both as brothers
and as a battery!
[SOUICHIROU]
Good.
It'll be fine.
[OTOMI]
What will?
[SOUICHIROU]
Good.
[barks]
[SOUICHIROU] Hey, Mom,
want me to toss this trash?
Hold on a second,
Sou, that isn't trash.
Take a closer look!
I'm looking really closely.
[MAYUMI] Your father said he
wants to fold a thousand cranes
to bring you boys good luck.
So, I'm teaching him how.
[OTOMI]
Those're cranes?
I'd say there are only three
here that look anything
like cranes.
Well, that's not too bad;
997 more to go.
[PUNCH barks]
[TSUKIKAGE]
Are you covering the same topic?
What's wrong with that?
Take a defiant stance.
Half-hearted tricks
will only make you look
like an amateur.
And the truth is,
I don't think anybody has
high hopes for you,
so it doesn't even matter.
At least not at
this stage, anyway.
[HOST 17A]
Interesting.
Do you have any response,
Anonymous Mr. A?
What do you think of
Ms. Tsukikage's advice?
Do you find it helpful?
I do apologize.
I know it's a bold thing to say,
especially considering
how little I know
about high school
baseball manga.
I know I've seen that
lady somewhere before.
It's bugging me.
She seems to be all over
the TV lately, that's for sure.
I hear that she's
a popular novelist.
What?
Speaking of high
school baseball,
we're gearing up for
some intense games!
A lot of them happening today
as teams throughout Japan
fight to make it to Koshien!
They can kiss my butt.
[HOST 17A]
Uh...?
Oh. What? You say something?
[HOST 17A]
Why don't we go to commercial?
[RYUUCHI]
What did she say?
All right, what am I
feeling hungry for today?
Hey!
I'm sorry, sir. We're closed.
Come back tomorrow.
Huh? You literally just opened!
[RYUUCHI] I said we're closed!
Now, beat it!
[CUSTOMER 17A]
I didn't do anything!
[RYUUCHI]
That's it! You're banned!
[CUSTOMER 17A]
Banned?!
[CROWD chattering]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Ball!
[EKODA]
What's going on?
He's not that great at all.
You must have confidence.
There's no need for any
of you to be intimidated
by a pitcher like that.
Yes, sir!
[HARUKA] Is the other team's
manager doing okay?
Seems like he's having
trouble standing up.
That's Manager Ekoda.
The man's a veteran--
he's been manager
of Sankou High's team forever.
More than 30 years.
And his team has
made it to Koshien twice.
They're a traditional
high school yet post
a decent record every year.
They're not a top-ranked school,
but according to the
rumors, they're fielding
the best team they've
had in a while.
Their cleanup hitter
in particular is a major
point of pride.
Sounds like inside info.
Who gathered that for you?
'Cause it wasn't me.
Uh...!
I know things, too.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Ball four!
Speaking of the other
teams' manager...
He's not the only one having
trouble staying on his feet.
I heard that this kid pitched
quite an impressive game
in his previous matchup.
But in today's game,
he seems to be having
a hard time finding the plate.
I'm right, huh, Morishima?
Uh, the name's Kondou, sir.
[EKODA]
Oh! Of course it is!
Morishima quit the team
two years ago, didn't he?
Actually, that was
three years ago.
[EKODA] Hm?
This, and this, and then this.
--[SANKOU TEAM 17C yells]
--[CROWD gasps]
--[UMPIRE 13A] Dead ball!
--[CROWD cheers]
No outs, men on
first and second.
[HARUKA]
And now, their pride and joy.
The cleanup hitter.
[EKODA] This kid's only
a first year, after all.
His failure to properly
prepare for a game
will prove to be a good lesson.
Well, what do you
think, Watanabe?
Once again, the name's Kondou.
[EKODA laughs]
I'm just pulling your leg!
And now, our lineup shows
off its hitting power!
You guys are without
a doubt the best team
Sankou High School
has had in years.
[EKODA]
So, have some confidence.
There's no need to be
intimidated by a pitcher
like that.
[SANKOU TEAM]
Yes, sir!
[CROWD cheering]
[TEACHER 04A]
All right, folks.
As is our tradition when
tests are handed back,
we'll announce the students
who got the top five scores.
[STUDENTS groan]
So. How'd you do?
[OTOMI]
I mean...
I studied hard for
this one, and I do think
my score is pretty high.
Good.
Why, what's up?
Oh, her.
She's got terrible dark
circles under her eyes.
But that doesn't mean
there's any reason to worry.
It's not like that girl's ever
been in the top five before,
as far as I remember.
She's a dummy.
[TEACHER 04A]
First place. Arisa Mita.
What'd he say?
Yes!
Now, calm down.
There's no need to
make a big production.
It isn't very polite to gloat.
Second place is Otomi Tachibana.
Good job!
Yes!
[STUDENTS chatter]
Are you deliberately
disobeying me?
Sit back down!
[TEACHER 04A]
Third place. Ryou Akai.
--[OTOMI] Wow!
--[ARISA] Congrats, Akai!
[TEACHER 04A]
Fourth place. Jiro Yamada.
Fifth place, Miyuki Kashima.
Good job, guys.
The average score
was higher this time.
The top five scores were
exceptionally close, actually.
As your homeroom teacher,
I gotta say, I'm pleased.
Now, let's get
back to the lesson.
[ARISA snoring]
Wake up!
This isn't nap time, folks!
[CLASSMATE 17A]
She's a first-place napper, too.
Why?
[ARISA snoring]
[OTOMI]
That girl.
I think we may be
underestimating her.
She could be more
amazing than we know.
[YOSHIKO]
Hmm...
[ICHIBAN]
Well, enough about the test.
We have bigger fish
to fry, don't we?
[OTOMI]
Hm?
Aren't you nervous, too?
About your brothers' big game.
You didn't catch
a convenient cold?
[ICHIBAN chuckles]
It wasn't for lack
of trying, believe me.
I reached out to the
teacher this morning,
but he threatened to post
my score unless I came in.
Wait, he knew all along?
Ridiculous.
[ICHIBAN] So, you're worried
about the game, right?
It's not just me?
[OTOMI]
Nah, not at all.
There's no reason to
worry about Tou today.
[ICHIBAN]
Huh?
[OTOMI chuckles]
This morning he said
that his shoulder
was feeling especially light.
He did?
[OTOMI]
I've noticed a pattern.
Ever since grade school,
when he wakes up
saying stuff like that,
he hardly gives up any hits.
[ICHIBAN]
Really?
[UMPIRE 13A]
Ball! That's four!
[CROWD clapping]
[OOYAMA]
Hmm...
[EKODA chuckles]
[SOUICHIROU] Come on,
would you get it together?
You've been putting runners
on base every inning!
That's not me!
They're only on base 'cause of
errors in the second and fourth!
Even that's your fault.
Those happened 'cause your
pitching rhythm's off today.
And because of that,
our offense is affected.
We're hitting the ball,
but it's going right to them.
[TOUMA]
That's so weird.
I'm even feeling
really light today.
So what's up?
[EKODA] It looks like he's
gonna self-destruct for us,
my young friend.
Here's hoping.
Yes, well, you might be right.
But, still...
Uh, never mind. It's nothing.
[CROWD cheers]
[EKODA] Now that I get
a good look at that kid...
...I feel like I've seen
him somewhere before.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike three! Batter's out!
[UMPIRE 13C]
Out!
[CROWD cheering]
We're putting runners in
scoring position every inning,
but then we can never seem
to get that next hit.
When you say "next hit,"
what do you mean?
Because we haven't
gotten any hits yet.
Oh, come on, there's
no reason to start
getting worried right now.
We've put together
our best team in years,
no question about it.
In our last game, in the
seventh inning, we had...
[KONDOU]
Twelve hits?
[EKODA] Right!
Twelve hits and nine runs!
Any team I'm in charge
of always puts
their primary focus on offense.
I've been managing the
Sankou team for over 30 years.
We may have lost some games,
but we've never let any
team get a no-hitter on us,
not in all that time!
--[UMPIRE 13A] Strike!
--[EKODA] Wha--?!
Nice!
[KONDOU]
Did you say never? Never ever?
I did! And if you
don't believe me,
you can take a good
look at the records!
I've always been known for
the accuracy of my memory--
my mind is a steel trap!
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
[CROWD claps]
[EKODA chuckles]
Two more innings.
That's plenty!
After all, like I said earlier.
You guys are the
best team this school
has put together in years!
[SANKOU TEAM]
Yes, sir!
I only wish I could
figure out where I've
seen him before.
That pitcher...
[TOUMA]
Ah, now I get it!
[CROWD cheering]
[EKODA]
No need to start panicking!
Two innings--plenty of time
to turn the tables.
Stay confident, boys.
Don't let yourselves
get intimidated
by a pitcher like that!
Yes, sir.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike three! Batter's out!
[EKODA] Over 30 years of
experience managing baseball.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
[EKODA]
We may have been shut out,
but we've never lost
a game without any hits.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike three! You're out!
[CROWD] One more out!
One more out! One more out!
One more out!
[chanting continues]
[EKODA gasps]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike three!
Batter's out!
[CROWD cheering]
Did you remember where
you've seen that guy?
[cheering continues]
[OTOMI]
Next time, on Mix!
[ICHIBAN] Hi, Otomi?
What are you up to today?
We were supposed
to have practice,
but it got cancelled
because of the rain.
So, I was just wondering
what you were doing.
I don't remember if you
mentioned you had plans.
Are you busy right now?
I know the weather sucks,
but we should go somewhere
since we're off.
Yes? No? Maybe?
Heh heh heh...
But, I mean, it's totally
up to you whatever we do.
[MAYUMI]
Otomi! The phone's for you!
[OTOMI] Next time,
"On a Rainy Day Like Today."
[ICHIBAN] Oh, Mrs. Tachibana?
Where's Otomi?
[PUNCH barks]