[NARRATOR] The preliminaries
for the summer Koshien continue
with the East Tokyo Tournament.
[NARRATOR] For the
first time in 30 years,
Meisei is a major contender,
and, because of that, people
are beginning to pay attention
to the team's progress and
support them like they used to.
[NARRATOR]
Excitement is mounting
as this team comes to life,
and people are starting
to remember the
legendary Meisei team
that won Koshien in their first
tournament 30 years prior.
[NARRATOR] All of the focus
is on the impressive,
first-year battery,
the Tachibana brothers.
It's now the quarterfinals,
and if they continue to win...
[NISHIMURA] Toushu High
will be waiting to face
Meisei High in the semifinals?
Are they serious?
Do these jerks really
think that'll happen?
Us facing them in the finals?
--[ISAMI] Not possible.
--[NISHIMURA] Hm?
A hundred percent true.
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer,
and now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
This is the story
of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher,
along with their younger sister,
they face life's countless
adventures while
aiming for the top.
The three share one goal--
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[NARRATOR]
East Tokyo Tournament.
The quarterfinals, day one.
[bats clinking]
[bat clinks]
[CROWD cheering]
So, it's Toushu after all.
[TADASHI]
Yep.
No upsets this time around.
And get this, they won with
the mercy rule again.
[KOMA]
Hmm.
[TADASHI] Their ace, Mita,
only pitched five innings.
And to add to that,
they got to play one fewer
game 'cause they're seeded.
I see how it is.
They have the advantage
of getting more rest
and settling their nerves.
[TADASHI] Welp, we only
have to worry about that
if we win tomorrow.
It's crazy. My whole family
is going nuts over this,
like, the extended family.
[KOMA]
Huh? Are they really?
[TADASHI]
Hm?
Eh. Nobody in my family
gives a crap about baseball.
None of 'em.
In fact, I'm not even sure
they know I play a sport at all.
[TADASHI chuckles]
I find that hard to believe.
It's the truth, though.
My parents don't have
time to think about it.
They barely notice me.
As long as I don't
get killed or arrested,
they literally pay no attention.
[TADASHI grunts]
They both have busy jobs?
[KOMA]
Yeah.
I see.
Must be tough. What do they do?
If you don't mind.
They're a doctor and a lawyer.
[TADASHI grunts]
Ow! What the hell?
What'd you do that for?
[SPECTATORS chattering]
[ASAKO] Wow! Look at the
movement on that pitch!
[SOUICHIROU]
That's it for today, boys!
[TOUMA gasps]
Hey, come on, man!
Ten more pitches!
[SOUICHIROU]
I said we're done.
[TOUMA]
Hey!
Souichirou!
[SOUICHIROU]
Yeah?
[HARUKA]
Here. Good work today.
[TOUMA]
Uh?
Cool, uh, thank you.
I almost forgot!
Did you hear?
Katatataki totally washed away!
Huh?
The other day
that area was inundated with
torrential rain, literally!
It caused a major landslide and
changed the terrain forever!
[TOUMA]
Hmm.
Ohh. That waterfall.
I bet it's the karma police
making them pay for
those stupid riddles.
No doubt.
But, aren't you sad?
[TOUMA]
Hm?
[HARUKA] You and I shared
some lovely memories there!
And now it's gone forever!
You call them
memories, but I mean...
That's how people
talk about things
that happened back in the day.
Just seems weird for
you to use that word
when we just went to that
place pretty recently.
[sighs]
[HARUKA]
Fine, whatever.
So sorry. I didn't mean
to interrupt practice
with something so trivial.
Hey, the water?
[groans] Thank you...
[OTOMI]
Punch.
[PUNCH barks]
[SPECTATORS chattering]
[OTOMI]
Hmm?
[yelps]
[inaudible]
[PUNCH whines]
[OTOMI] They've been
friends since they were kids.
That must be it.
[PUNCH barking]
[TOUMA]
Mm?
Hmm.
Okay, bring that to me
when you're done.
Yeah, I'm on it.
I don't have to
be honest, or do I?
I guess not.
That is, if you don't
care what they say
about you when you
get introduced on TV.
[TOUMA]
Mm? You got an eraser?
You bet.
Where's Souichirou?
The manager called for
him a few minutes ago.
I think he's in the club room.
[HARUKA]
Thanks.
[TOUMA grunts]
[TOUMA]
Hm?
Hmm?
[TOUMA]
What is it?
[HARUKA]
Nothing.
You said the club room?
Think so. Yeah.
[HARUKA]
Gotcha. Club room, club room.
[OOYAMA]
Hmm.
The cause is clear.
He's been pitching every game.
[OTOMI]
Huh?
Hey, did you say
something just now, Punch?
[PUNCH whines]
[NARRATOR]
Day two of the quarterfinals.
Game one.
[NISHIMURA grunts]
[CROWD cheering]
[ISAMI] It's clearly 'cause
he's pitched every game.
[ISAMI]
Toward the end of the last one,
he was having trouble keeping
his pitches inside
the strike zone.
If it weren't for the
catcher's leadership,
they wouldn't have been
able to hold onto their lead.
[IZUMI PLAYER A grunts]
--[CROWD cheering]
--[BASE UMPIRE] Out!
[ISAMI] Even with
time off between games,
a first-year can
only endure so long.
At some point
during today's match,
that weakness will
start to show.
And even if he's able
to pitch nine innings today,
he'll have nothing left next
time when he's facing an ace.
You know what that means?
Means we can hardly expect
it to be much of a game.
A hundred percent, huh?
--[IZUMI PLAYER B grunts]
--[PLATE UMPIRE] Strike!
Yeah.
I said a hundred percent.
Our opponent in the final...
...will be Toushu.
[NARRATOR]
And, so, game two ends.
[CROWD cheering]
[TOUMA]
Manager!
[TOUMA growls]
Say somethin'?
[ISAMI] 'Member when I said
100 percent? Well, scratch that.
Meisei High School
could end up being our
opponent in the final game.
[OOYAMA]
I read it absolutely wrong.
You've got that right.
This summer, I'd planned
to get as far as we could
with just Touma and figure
out our team's issues
from the games that
we played as we went.
That's honestly the only
thing that I expected
would come of this tournament.
You've got that right.
[OOYAMA]
But then, the next thing I knew,
we found ourselves
in the quarterfinals!
The next thing you knew...
...touma the tenth-grader had
thrown four straight games.
That's why I'm telling you
I read it all wrong!
Never in my wildest dreams
did I think we'd get this far!
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Ball! That's four!
[CROWD clapping]
You've got that right.
[COLORCASTER] Ogi, batting
second with a great eye.
Meisei High's Takeshita in his
first start of the tournament,
with one out,
he's already allowed
a really quick runner
to get on base.
[ISAMI] The chance
of Meisei being our opponent
in the finals is no longer zero.
[ISAMI]
But, at the same time,
the chance that
they'll lose this game
just shot up exponentially.
[COLORCASTER]
Ogi has a big lead off the base.
He heads up the team
in steals for this tournament.
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Ball!
[TAKESHITA grunts]
They don't take you seriously.
That's their mistake.
[COLORCASTER]
Pick-off throw!
[BASE UMPIRE]
Safe!
[CROWD clapping]
[TADASHI grunts]
Not the kind of
pitcher you'd expect
to face in the quarterfinals.
His pick-offs and fastballs
are below average.
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Strike!
[gasps, yells]
[BASE UMPIRE]
Out!
[CROWD gasps, clapping]
I'm sorry, what were you saying?
That's two outs!
Yeah.
[KAIOU PLAYER A grunts]
All right!
[NANGOU grunting]
[BASE UMPIRE]
Out!
[CROWD clapping]
Well, jeez, that was terrifying.
With this lineup we've
gotta play good offense.
There's no telling how
many runs we'll give up,
so we have to score
as many as we can, too.
[COLORCASTER]
Touma Tachibana is batting first
and playing left field today.
[grunts]
[COLORCASTER]
He hits the first pitch.
Ah, but it goes right
to the center fielder.
[COLORCASTER] Karashima
takes the mound for Kaiou Nishi,
a rare submarine pitcher
in his second start.
He's given up one run in
nine innings this tournament,
and that includes relief.
He's been incredibly
consistent up to this point,
let's see if that continues.
Murotani, batting
second for Meisei...
[BASE UMPIRE]
Out!
[CROWD clapping]
[COLORCASTER]
...hits the third pitch out
to the shortstop for two outs.
His face and his pitching
form are both awful.
Hey, looks don't mean
anything in baseball.
Am I right, Nangou?
[NANGOU grunts]
[COLORCASTER]
Between first and second!
He stopped it!
Throws to first!
[BASE UMPIRE]
Out!
[CROWD cheering, clapping]
That was at least close.
[SOUICHIROU] But it wouldn't get
us on base with any of the teams
we have left to face
in the quarterfinals.
Other than us, of course.
[OTOMI] Did you know that
Touma wouldn't be pitching
in today's game
before you got here?
Yeah, I did.
Ooyama told me over
the phone yesterday.
[OTOMI]
Interesting.
I guess he's satisfied
with just making it
to the quarterfinals
and no further, then.
You've got it
all wrong, ya dummy!
[gasps]
And who might you be, Miss?
Someone who came to give you
a message from your boss,
who called the house
looking for you.
He said to stop
telling obvious lies,
you're embarrassing yourself.
Also, as a courtesy, he delayed
the afternoon meeting
to three PM,
and you're very welcome.
I got the call just as
I was leaving the house.
But why would my boss
call the house?
Because your cell went
straight to your voicemail
since you turned it off!
Oh, that makes sense.
[bat clinks]
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Strike!
[TAKESHITA grunts]
[KAIOU PLAYER B grunts]
--[PLATE UMPIRE] Foul!
--[KAIOU PLAYER B sighs]
[OOYAMA]
Am I imagining things?
[bat clinks]
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Foul!
They can't hit
Takeshita's pitches.
Seems like they're struggling.
You're not imagining it,
their timing's really off.
It does make sense, though.
They've won all their
games up to this point
facing the most talented
fastball pitchers in the area,
throwing 90 mile pitches.
I think that means
they've probably been
practicing under
the assumption that
they'd also be facing
Touma's fastball.
Well, then that's
too bad for them.
But, still...
Kaiou Nishi is a team
known for their hitting.
Once they can see
the ball, we're toast.
[OOYAMA]
Yeah, I get it.
Seems like the theme
of today's game
is the pitching and timing
of our senior pitchers.
Here's the part where
I show what I'm capable of.
[COLORCASTER]
Bottom of the second inning,
and Meisei High School
is up to bat.
Next up is Imagawa,
batting fourth.
There's the pitch,
and... strike!
[RYOU'S MOTHER grunts]
Hey, Ryou?
[RYOU]
Hm? What is it?
[RYOU'S MOTHER]
Would you do me a favor?
Can you take these bags up
to your brother's room?
You know if I go in there
without his permission,
we're only gonna end
up fighting again.
Don't worry, I'll
tell him I was the one
who brought them in there.
Please, sweetie?
This stuff is
getting in the way.
[COLORCASTER]
Here's the second pitch.
[RYOU]
Okay, fine.
[RYOU grunts]
Mita?
If he didn't have such
good control out there,
then all of his pitches
would definitely be hittable.
He's consistently keeping
'em low to the ground.
[KARASHIMA grunts]
[BASE UMPIRE]
Out!
[KARASHIMA chuckles]
[HARUKA] Seriously! I can't
decide which is worse,
his form or his face!
Again, looks mean
nothing in baseball!
--[bat clinks]
--Right, Nan...
...gou?
[NANGOU]
Hm.
[CROWD cheering]
[OOYAMA]
What did I tell ya?
Looks aren't
important out there!
They sure took the lead
pretty quickly, didn't they?
Yeah, but in a game
like this, one run, no fun.
[NARRATOR] Second time at bat
for the Kaiou Nishi lineup.
[CROWD cheering]
Whaddaya know, those guys
took the lead in no time!
Scary.
Four innings with just two runs?
That's all right.
[bat clinks]
[COLORCASTER] Souichirou
Tachibana sends the ball
right between the out fielders!
The out fielder takes too long
and Tachibana makes it to third!
Bottom of the fourth,
still one out.
[COLORCASTER]
Cleanup hitter Imagawa
with a high flyball
to the outfield.
--[CROWD cheering]
--And the game's tied up again!
[EISUKE]
Yes!
What a game.
This one's really
wearing me out.
Ooyama expected it
to go down like this,
right from the start.
The main theme of today's game
is to give Touma's
throwing arm a rest.
Doesn't matter
if we win or lose.
Hey, hold on.
Even if we were to beat them,
if we make the
semifinals without him,
we might as well
throw in the towel.
To stand half a chance
in the next pitchers' duel
we need to send Touma to
the mound in peak condition.
If we lose this one he'll have
the whole rest of the summer
to get into peak
condition. Y'know?
[OOYAMA]
I want to see it!
How Touma's pitching stands up
against Toushu in
a high-stakes game!
You want to see
that, too, right?
Rather than wasting him
on a mid-range opponent
like these guys,
I wanna see a tenth-grader
make a shocking debut
against the south paw that
all the pros are raving about!
I guess I see where
you're coming from, sure.
And I know in my heart
it's what they want, too!
The Baseball Gods want
it just as much as I do!
To see that matchup!
I see now.
[bat clinks]
[HARUKA]
You're praying the Baseball Gods
can get us through this game.
[SOUICHIROU]
Next time, on Mix !
[TOUMA]
Summer, the ocean, and Koshien!
[SOUICHIROU] Hey, Shakespeare,
don't get ahead of yourself.
--We still have--
--[TOUMA] The semifinal
--[SOUICHIROU] Well, yeah,
--against Toushu.
but first we've gotta win
this game against Kaiou Nishi.
[TOUMA]
I'm finally pitted against Mita!
[SOUICHIROU]
Unless we win this game,
you won't get that matchup!
[TOUMA] If I beat him, I'll
face Nishimura in the final!
[SOUICHIROU]
Will you listen?!
The game continues
in the next episode!
[TOUMA]
Wait, it does?
[SOUICHIROU]
Next time, "If."
[TOUMA] So, the game
will be decided next time?
[barks]