[YOSHIKO'S MOTHER]
Now, Otomi, are you sure
that's the one you want?
[OTOMI] Totally! Had my heart
set the moment I saw him!
[DOG pants]
[YOSHIKO'S MOTHER]
As long as you're sure.
[YOSHIKO]
Just promise me you're not
gonna change your mind later.
[OTOMI]
I promise.
[YOSHIKO]
Take good care of him, okay?
[OTOMI]
I will!
We'll have lots
of fun together, Punch!
[PUNCH barks]
[NARRATOR]
With a name like "Punch,"
you've got to have
a stronger bark!
[PUNCH growls, barks]
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is
the story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face life's
countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[PLAYERS talking]
[PITCHERS groaning]
Nice catch, man!
[SOUICHIROU] It doesn't
look like there's much hope
this time, either.
Yeah...
Our pitcher's the problem.
We need someone else
on the mound.
That way we could
at least put up a fight.
But unfortunately
for us, the manager's the one
who gets to make that call,
and he only likes one player.
[SOUICHIROU]
Yup. Nikaidou.
He's only gonna be our ace
until this summer, though.
[TOUMA] Well, I certainly hope
you're right about that.
[MAYUMI]
Souichirou! Tou, dear!
Hope you're hungry,
'cause I bought some taiyaki!
Come home soon
so you can have some!
Hey, Tou, dear. You hear that?
Shut up.
[TOUMA] Could you just call me
by my full name already?
You worry way
too much about that.
I'm your mother, can't I have a
cute little nickname for my son?
And before you say anything,
no one thinks you're
five little tootsies.
Nobody in this
neighborhood at least,
they're used to it.
Oh, she's telling the world,
even explained it to the
mailman the other day.
[MAYUMI laughs] Well, I want you
to be comfortable with it.
And besides you call me
"mother," even though
I'm technically
your step mother,
so you deserve
an endearing name, too!
[TOUMA] You want me to
call you "step mother"?
By the way...
Could someone explain
why this little furball's
slinking around the house?
There you are, Punch!
[BOTH]
His name's Punch?
[PUNCH grunts, barks]
[MAYUMI] That's the puppy
Otomi got from Yoshiko.
I'm sure you remember
us talking about it.
[OTOMI giggles]
What made you decide
to go with the name "Punch"?
[OTOMI]
Well... It's kind of silly.
But before I went
to bed the other night,
I was trying really hard
to think of a good name.
[OTOMI] And then this strange
person appeared in my dream.
[OTOMI]
He gave me the idea, said he's
"leaving the rest to me,"
and disappeared.
[MAYUMI] Interesting. Then he
was meant to be named that.
It must be fate.
[TOUMA, SOUICHIROU groan]
Wanna say hi, Punch?
These are your new
human big brothers!
Meet Souichirou and Touma!
[PUNCH whines]
[OTOMI]
Don't be shy!
[PUNCH grunts]
[SOUICHIROU, TOUMA]
Argh!
--Throw that dog away!
--It's all over the table!
[MAYUMI]
He's full of spirit!
[NARRATOR] There are
two portraits displayed
in the adjacent room.
[NARRATOR] One of Souichirou
and Otomi's late father,
and one of Touma's late mother.
When their current parents,
Eisuke Tachibana and
Mayumi Sawai fell in love
and got married,
big brother, Souichirou,
and little brother,
Touma, were six,
while the youngest--
their little sister Otomi--
was five years old.
[school bell chimes]
[NATSUNO] So, I understand
your family now.
[OTOMI]
Hmm?
Got lucky. I overheard your mom.
She was explaining it
at the taiyaki place.
You know, the one
right by the station?
She wasn't quiet.
She explained
the whole family structure.
[MAYUMI] And they both play
baseball! It's so funny!
Wish I could
say I was surprised.
[NATSUNO]
Now that that's out of the way,
I wanted to ask you something.
What is with our baseball club?!
It's all over the place!
Anyone with a brain
can see that your brother
is leagues better than
our current ace pitcher!
Obviously.
That's not the half of it!
The team doesn't have a single
decent backup pitcher, either.
So why'd I get stuck
kicking dirt in the outfield?!
Well, in a way,
that's actually proof that
you've been recognized
as a decent pitcher.
I-- What does that even mean?
I swear, nothing they're doing
makes a lick of sense!
What's the point if they're not
even gonna be serious about it?
Well, they've got some
really good gear and facilities,
don't they?
Wait, What?
[NATSUNO] She was right.
They are pretty nice.
Hmm.
[KUROYANAGI]
New members, over here!
Ah.
[KUROYANAGI] An alumnus of
this club, Chairman Nikaidou,
sent you these
training uniforms.
Wear them to all
future practices.
You can express
your heartfelt gratitude
by taking proper care of them.
[PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
Did he say Nikaidou?
Ah.
Clean these up for me, Miyata.
[MIYATA]
Yeah. You got it.
Hey, Nikaidou.
[SOUICHIROU] We have new
first years on the team,
so it's time you relieve
Miyata of his duties
as your personal laundryman.
[SOUICHIROU]
Don't you think?
[DAISUKE]
You want out, Miyata?
Ah. I, uh...
[TOUMA] If you don't wanna
do it anymore, just tell him.
He isn't some total jerk.
He wouldn't take advantage
of the fact that your dad
works for his to make
you his lackey.
He's too good for that.
Right?
Tachibana.
I've heard things.
Like what you do after I leave.
They say you've been
secretly practicing pitching.
You're wasting your
time doing that.
As long as I'm here, you
have absolutely no chance
of taking the pitcher's mound.
[DAISUKE]
You can count on that.
Oh, I'm fully aware.
But you won't
be here much longer.
Just until fall.
[gasps]
I guess you're right.
I'll need to have a nice,
long chat with the manager.
We'll see what
happens after that.
[NATSUNO]
So that alumnus called Nikaidou.
Any relation to our ace?
[TADASHI] Yeah. He happens
to be our Nikaidou's father.
[TADASHI] President of
the appropriately named
Nikaidou Electric Company.
[TADASHI] Every year, he gifts
a ton of expensive equipment
to our club.
So that's where
we got all this stuff.
[TADASHI]
It gets more complicated.
He and our manager are former
players of the junior high
and high school teams.
And they're apparently
still pretty good friends.
[TADASHI] In case you
haven't put it together,
that's the reason that
our club's selfish ace gets
a free pass to do
whatever he wants.
Well, that explains a lot. Wait!
You're not telling me you're
okay with that, are you?
You're the captain Imagawa,
you should do something!
I wouldn't hold
your breath for that.
You see, Nikaidou and
I have known each other
since we were in grade school.
We may not be very close,
but I still consider
him a friend.
Don't know if he does.
[NATSUNO]
Hmm.
[SOUICHIROU]
Touma. Wanna throw? I'll catch.
But the manager hasn't left yet.
He's right there.
And why should
we care about that?
Good point. Why should we care?
[PLAYERS groan, chuckle]
Look at that throw.
[TEACHER 02A]
Miss Tachibana!
Break time is already over.
Would you be so kind as to
return to your seat now, please?
Natsuno, you want a turn?
Show us your arm.
[gasps]
Yeah, that'd be great!
Don't try copying
Touma's fastball.
Just focus on pitching
with your own style.
Okay!
Hey, Tachibana. Just checking.
I didn't approve or
disapprove of this, did I?
Sure didn't. Just like usual.
It's all us.
That's the right answer.
[NATSUNO growls]
Hang on. I know this tune.
Don't they often play
this song at the Koshien?
I'm pretty sure they do.
I want to say it's
from that baseball anime
they had on TV a long time ago.
Uh... What's it called?
I think it's--
If you're not
gonna pitch, then I will.
Right.
[TOUMA groans]
Hey, Sou? What time is it?
[TOUMA]
Sou!
Hmm?
[TOUMA yawns]
[gargling]
Morning, everyone.
[OTOMI] Hey, lazy. Do you have
any idea what time it is?
I know it's Sunday,
but you still shouldn't
sleep in until 11.
[TOUMA] I tried to ask Sou
the time, but he disappeared.
Seen him?
He's on a date.
With who now?
No idea. With all these
girls lining up to date Sou,
there are too many
to possibly keep track of.
[TOUMA]
What about Mom and Dad?
They're on a date of their own.
Apparently, they're visiting
the Asakusa area.
They're eating lunch out
and should be home
before it gets dark.
[PUNCH snores]
[TOUMA] It's nice that
they still do stuff like that.
I know, right?
[TOUMA]
Although...
Mom's lowered her standards.
Seriously. They're both
just so different.
It's kinda funny.
Do you really think so?
Depending on the
angle of the shot,
Dad could pass as
a pretty good-looking guy.
Just like your biological Dad.
If you can show me
even one photo that proves that,
I'll treat you to all the cake
you can stuff your face with.
Whoa, really?
Challenge accepted!
Never mind.
If I keep looking,
it'll confirm I'm wrong.
You've gotta be
pretty familiar with Rakugo
to understand this.
It's fine,
I'm just happy to be here.
[TOUMA sighing]
Look at these.
Our Dad's an idiot.
He's got no decent photos.
[TOUMA groans]
Why am I not surprised he was
like that in school, too?
[TOUMA] Your double-digit number
is nothing to brag about, Dad.
[TOUMA] Yeah, this pitching
form says it all.
[TOUMA]
Man. So lame.
[OTOMI] Are you planning
to sit there all day
and make fun of our Dad, Tou?
Will you stop
calling me that already?
It's kinda confusing.
Confusing?
Because of the homophones?
I don't think so.
You're the only one
who has a problem with it.
[PUNCH chuckles]
[TOUMA]
Is the dog laughing?!
[sighs]
Whatever.
[TOUMA]
Now that I think of it.
There's something
about that uniform.
Oh, yeah. You're right.
Did you ask Dad about it, yet?
[TOUMA] I actually don't think
we should tell him we found it.
But why not?
I dunno, think about it.
He could have stolen it from
the club for all we know.
I kinda doubt that.
Hold on.
It's not as ridiculous as
you're making it sound.
You remember what he says
after a couple of drinks?
Come on...
[TOUMA] How just one time,
he would've loved to wear
the number one uniform
back in the day?
[EISUKE]
If I could just wear it once...
That is true.
[TOUMA]
So, let's keep our mouths shut.
Until he confesses.
Roger that!
[OTOMI]
Uniform number one.
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
[OTOMI] I'm looking forward
to when you take
the pitcher's mound...
...and are finally
Meisei's number-one.
[barks]
[OTOMI] Hey, if you feel like
going out somewhere, go ahead.
I'll hold down the
fort while you're gone.
Oh.
I did tell Koma I'd hang out
with him one of these days.
[OTOMI]
See you later.
[TOUMA]
Hmm?
[PEEPERS grunt]
Run!
[PEEPER 02B]
Hmm? Hmm?! Ahh!
[TOUMA groans]
[SOUICHIROU]
Thanks for today.
It was a lot of fun.
I should be thanking you!
You're not the only one who
thought today was a blast.
Sorry I don't have
more room in my schedule.
We'll have to spend more time
together on our next date.
Totally! I'd be happy to!
We'll talk again soon, okay?
Sounds like a plan.
Feel free to call me anytime!
I'll be waiting
to hear from you!
[gasps] Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what are you doing here?
I was just passing by,
no need to get so offended.
And where do you plan on going?
What's with the third degree?
Koma's house. I was gonna
go play some games with him.
And where's Otomi?
[TOUMA]
She's back home.
Didn't you notice
that Mom and Dad
aren't at home today either?
[TOUMA]
Yeah, I did.
And yet, you still left
her all by herself?
What's there to worry about?
She's not an elementary
schooler anymore.
[gasps]
Are you a complete idiot?
The older a girl gets, the more
dangerous it is for her
to be left on her own.
Go back home right now!
The only reason I made plans
today, despite Mom and Dad
going out, was because
I thought you'd be with Otomi.
[TOUMA]
That's not fair!
If that's how you feel,
why don't you go home
and stay with her!
You're finished
with your date, right?
The first game of the day. Yeah.
[TOUMA]
Huh?
But I've got
a doubleheader lined up.
[GIRL 02B]
Sou! Sorry if I'm a little late!
No worries!
I just arrived myself!
Listen, just turn
your bike around and go.
If anything were
to happen to Otomi,
I won't hesitate to beat
the crap out of you.
Come on, Sou.
You'll scare the
poor guy like that!
[SOUICHIROU chuckles]
I was just kidding, don't worry.
What do you say
we get outta here?
[TOUMA groans]
[NATSUNO chuckles]
[TOUMA]
Natsuno. What's up?
Not much. Hey, is Otomi
home today by any chance?
[growls]
And if she is? What's it to you?
Huh? Oh, nothing.
I was... Never mind.
Tell her I said "hi"...
--[TOUMA] Natsuno!
--[NATSUNO whimpers]
Yeah? That's me!
About your pitching form.
You've gotta relax your elbow
more, otherwise you'll end up
hurting your arm, and
then you'll be done for.
Keep that in mind.
Whoa. Okay.
Thanks a lot for
the advice, man.
[TOUMA]
Give me a break...
Two dates in one day?
[sighs]
He's so full of himself.
And why do I have to--
[PEEPERS chuckling]
--[PEEPERS scream]
--Get lost, you buncha perverts!
[PEEPER 02B] We weren't
doing anything, I swear!
No shame. [gasps]
[flute playing]
[MAYUMI] Otomi is an
especially shy girl, Tou, dear.
[TOUMA]
It took her... a whole month.
Hey, I'm back.
That was a short trip.
Was Koma not at home, then?
[TOUMA sighs] No. I never
made it to his place actually.
I remembered we had an argument
and didn't want to see him.
[OTOMI]
If you forgot about it,
it couldn't have been
that big of a deal.
[TOUMA]
I just didn't feel like going.
Yeah, I felt you the first time.
[barks]
Punch seems to have
really taken a liking to you.
That was fast.
[TOUMA] A far cry
from someone else I know.
Huh?
Nothing. Don't worry about it.
[OTOMI]
Hmm.
[barks]
[OTOMI]
Next time, on Mix.
What do you like about
Meisei High School?
[SOUICHIROU]
It's one minute from home.
[OTOMI]
What else?
[TOUMA] If you run,
it could be 30 seconds.
[OTOMI]
What else?
[SOUICHIROU] I can
come home during breaks
to get things I forgot.
[TOUMA] I can get up that
much later in the morning.
[SOUICHIROU]
I won't get wet on rainy days.
[TOUMA] My friends
can come straight over.
[OTOMI] So really, all you
care about is the distance.
[TOUMA, SOUICHIROU]
Huh?
[OTOMI] Next time, "The Heck
with Meisei High School."
What I like about it is... Huh.
[barks, chuckles]