[PLAYERS chatting]
These guys are great.
So, you're telling me that
they're only first years?
[KOMIYAMA] That's right. I can
show you their student IDs.
No, I believe you.
That's beyond impressive.
This lineup is a real threat,
no matter how young.
[KOMIYAMA] Still, it's hard to
say how things will pan out.
We won't know for sure until the
tournament actually gets going.
And, after all,
I'm new--this is only my
first year as manager.
Let's talk about your opponent,
Meisei High School.
This is your first
game against them
in quite a while
if I'm not mistaken.
Yeah, you're right,
and we're having
a hard time getting
any good data on them.
You wouldn't happen
to have any, would you?
You guys know the inside scoop.
[REPORTER 08A]
Let's see...
According to my sources,
they got a new manager recently.
That's right, and they've
been in a major slump
for decades, I think.
Well, that sounds
familiar. Like us.
Not at all!
Matter of fact, Kenjo has been
in the spotlight this summer!
[REPORTERS gasp]
I heard a rumor
that you had to raise
the height of the right
fence because of Akai.
Yeah.
It was definitely cheaper
than buying more balls.
[REPORTERS gasp]
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once-triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
[NARRATOR] This is the
story of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face life's
countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
How on Earth could it
possibly take you this long
to make a simple delivery?
If you don't like it,
then how 'bout you come
get your own stuff?
I'm in training
camp now, you idiot.
I don't have time to do that.
The game is
at 10 AM on the 9th.
Will you come cheer us on?
As awesome as
that sounds, I can't.
I've got class.
Even if I could, I wouldn't.
Heh. Oh, that's right.
I'd forgotten.
The first opponent we're
facing is Meisei High.
[AKAI] I guess you wouldn't
root for my team, would you?
I wouldn't.
[RYOU] And if you know what's
good for you, do your research.
Get to know
Meisei's baseball team.
[bat clangs]
Nangou!
[NANGOU grunts]
--Come on!
--[HARUKA] Shirou!
--What--?
--Listen! What are you doing?!
[NANGOU]
Hmm?
[BOTH grunts]
Keep your hip lower!
And bring your
glove up to the ball!
You wanna be
in the starting order?
You won't get there
just on your batting!
When Kenjo players hit the ball,
it comes at you way
faster and harder
than when that old man hits it!
Jeez. Ouch.
Especially the third,
the fifth, and seventh!
Third baseman, you need to watch
out for the softly hit balls!
Those first and
second hitters run fast!
Her heckling sure is detailed.
Yeah. I had her do
a little bit of spying for us.
She caught
a Kenjo practice game.
She's got a good eye
and a mind for baseball, too.
[HARUKA] And watch out for their
lefty Akai, batting fourth.
Do not throw him any soft
pitches--do you hear me?!
[TEACHER 07A]
What do you think you're doing
out here, Miss Ooyama?!
You're skipping practice to
heckle the baseball team?
Uh... Sorry.
What in the world
am I supposed to do with you?
Now, just be honest with me.
Do you even want to
do rhythmic gymnastics?
[HARUKA]
Hmm...
Don't think too hard about it,
we really need you on the team!
You're the best hope we've
got at the championships.
You're like a ray
of sunshine out there!
I'll let it slide this time,
just come back
to practice, okay?
[SOUICHIROU] So? What do you
make of her intel in general?
That all the rumors are true.
They're a team with a powerful
lineup and great mobility.
The rumors are true.
So, he says.
Interesting.
Which is good news for us.
It means they're no better than
the rumors say, at least.
[SOUICHIROU]
Yeah, that's true.
[TOUMA]
I'm not worried.
You're not worried? Huh.
[HARUKA] The Kenjo High
School baseball team
will be celebrating their
60th anniversary next year,
and that includes all the
years they were Sumi Tech.
And, ever since
a few years ago,
the school has pulled out
all the stops to redeem
the baseball team's reputation.
The manager, Shinpei Komiyama,
coached a prestigious
baseball club in Shikoku
until three years ago.
He faced criticism for
his controversial coaching style
and some of the
guidance he gave,
He got into an argument
with administrators and quit,
which is when Kenjo
offered him a job.
For his first two years,
he was the assistant manager.
He personally visited junior
high schools across Tokyo
and made a list of
promising players.
He spent the
next year persuading five of
his top choices
to transfer to Kenjo,
then he was officially promoted
to Manager this spring.
[TOUMA yawns loudly]
Oh. Sorry 'bout that.
You want me to punch him?
Please don't.
Check this out.
It's a report I wrote
detailing all of my observations
about the Kenjo lineup.
My dad asked me to give it
to you so you could study it.
--If you're interested.
--I'll pass. I'm way too sleepy.
Maybe later, though...
[yawns]
Show my brother. He's in
charge of that side of things,
he'll memorize your report.
I'm gonna take a nap now, 'kay?
Now do you want me to punch him?
No.
[HARUKA]
Do you think our ace pitcher
is feeling all right these days?
He does nothing but
sleep during his lunch break.
I think the fact
that he's sleepy is a good sign.
It means his body
is adjusting properly.
[HARUKA]
Get real!
Kenjo's lineup is
nothing to take lightly!
They're really powerful!
Yeah, yeah, I hear ya.
Did I leave something out?
There's nothing here
on Haruka Ooyama,
the data I wanted most.
--[HARUKA grunts]
--Heh.
Fine! I'll take
your response to mean
my observations
are nothing to you!
Hmph.
[HARUKA]
Is our battery all right?
They're both acting
a little off lately.
Ah, it's nothing to worry about.
They've always been
creepy like that.
I can guarantee you that much.
Creepy like what?
I'll put it this way:
your Kenjo report?
I bet you he's got the whole
thing memorized already.
You're joking, right?
Not at all.
[SOUICHIROU sighs]
[HARUKA]
Ah.
[HARUKA] Apparently, he hadn't
memorized the whole report.
[KOMA]
Yeah.
[CROWD murmuring]
[NARRATOR] The National High
School Baseball Championship,
East Tokyo Tournament,
has begun!
[OTOMI]
Hmm...
[RYOU] Just so you know,
the game's about to start.
[OTOMI]
Hmm?
Aw, man.
This is the worst time for
you to be telling me that.
[RYOU] It'll be all right.
They won't lose.
Not if I know your brothers.
Come on, your brother
is the player everyone
around the whole city
has been talking about!
Are you sure
you're rooting for Meisei?
[RYOU] Of course.
Meisei's my team, 100%.
I don't mean to pry,
but do you guys get along?
You and your brother.
Not really.
--[slam]
--Uh.
[BOTH]
Uh?
[ARISA growls]
--Jeez.
--What's her problem?
Heh.
[OTOMI]
Even though you're brothers?
[gasps]
Because we're brothers.
You really can't
take your mind off it?
No, Of course not.
If they lose once,
they're out of the tournament.
Aww. I wish I would've
faked being sick or something
and gone to the game.
[RYOU]
By the way, where's Natsuno?
[OTOMI]
Oh, he's out today.
He said he caught
a bad cold and he...
Hmm?
[OTOMI]
Aww!
[alarm blares
[CROWD cheers]
[ICHIBAN] This is the first
step toward victory.
For the New Meisei Team!
Go! Touma Tachibana!
[PUNCH barks]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Ball!
[ICHIBAN]
Crap.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Ball!
Strike!
[KOMIYAMA] Is he a breaking
ball pitcher? Or maybe...
They found out that
Teramoto prefers the fastball.
--[TERAMOTO grunts]
--[UMPIRE 13A] Strike!
[TERAMOTO sighs]
[KOMIYAMA] It's true that
he can't really handle
curves or sliders.
But if he just
needs to hit it...
...he knows how to do that.
[KOMIYAMA]
And if the ball rolls...
[TADASHI grunts]
[UMPIRE 13B]
Safe!
...then everything
will work out.
[KOMIYAMA] You're in
a pinch there, huh, Tachibana?
Teramoto's infield single.
[KOMIYAMA] Is as good
as getting an extra base hit.
[SOUICHIROU grunts]
He's out!
[CROWD cheers]
[KOMIYAMA]
Hmm...
[AKAI]
That sure was quick.
Oh. Yeah, that catcher of theirs
has got a good arm, right?
That's not what I'm saying.
I was referring to the ball
the pitcher just threw.
[KOMIYAMA]
Oh.
[TOUMA]
One out!
[PLAYERS whoop, cheer]
[TOUMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 13B]
Out!
[CROWD applauds]
Better not let those
low-level breaking balls
trick you out there, man.
[YAMAJI]
Hmph.
Kid's only in
10th grade, after all.
Hmph!
[YAMAJI] Jeez. What's the
deal with that pitcher?
[sighs]
[TOUMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike! Three outs!
Change sides!
[OOYAMA]
Yes!
It's that kid.
No way, man,
we were just passing by.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
Left-handed curveball, huh.
[UMPIRE 13B]
Out!
It must be a real pain,
facing our Kita's irregular
form and off-speed pitches.
And only seeing
them a couple of times...
...won't be enough to...
Here I go!
[CROWD cheerin]
...time their swings
to his pitches. I thought.
[UMPIRE 13A]
Three outs! Change!
We can hit this guy's pitches.
[TOUMA]
Speak for yourself.
[PLAYERS laughing]
[MAN 13A]
That's Akai.
[MAN 13B]
Wow!
[MAN 13C]
Oh, that's him?
[MAN 13D]
It's Akai!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
Top of the second inning.
Batting fourth for Kenjo High
School, first baseman, Akai.
--[CROWD cheering]
--[ICHIBAN] Akai?
How 'bout you hurry up
and "pass by," then?
[TOUMA] You know. They say first
impressions are everything!
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike!
[CROWD cheers]
So fast. But...
on the very first pitch...
...he threw a fastball right
down the middle against Akai?
[KOMIYAMA]
That kid is either reckless...
Or... maybe worse.
[TOUMA grunts]
[KOMIYAMA]
Is it... confidence?
[AKAI] Why don't you
clean up after yourself.
[TOUMA]
You gotta learn, slugger.
You need to be nicer to girls!
[AKAI gasps]
--[SOUICHIROU gasps]
--[bat clangs]
[CROWD cheers]
[TOUMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 13D]
Fair ball!
[TOUMA] He was able to
tell by my form that
I was throwing a change-up?
No way. You definitely
threw off his timing.
And yet he still got a double.
[SOUICHIROU]
That's why he only got a double.
[TOUMA sighs]
[SOUICHIROU]
Don't be hard on yourself.
Just don't let anyone
get on base today
before Akai steps up to bat.
[TOUMA]
Big brother Akai, huh?
[DAISUKE]
Oh, did you get a cold, Natsuno?
[ICHIBAN gulps]
Hey! Nikaido!
[DAISUKE] There's a bad
cold going round, clearly.
[coughs]
[ICHIBAN]
You're right, it is bad.
[coughs]
[DAISUKE]
What are you standing there for?
Let's grab a seat
and watch the game.
We're sick, after all.
[ICHIBAN]
Yeah, good call.
[TOUMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike! You're out!
[KENJO SCOREKEEPER]
In this inning,
both teams will start
with their second batter.
[KENJO SCOREKEEPER]
Up to this point,
it's been an equal
pitcher's duel.
[KOMIYAMA]
Not quite equal.
Huh?
Not at all, in fact.
Compare the lineups
between pitchers.
Uh...
[KOMIYAMA]
Compare Kita... to that kid.
[TOUMA grunts]
[UMPIRE 13A]
Strike! You're out!
Which middle
school did he go to?
That first-year Meisei pitcher?
According to this, he also
went to Meisei Junior High.
[KOMIYAMA]
That's odd.
I went to check out Meisei's
junior high team two years ago,
but they didn't have
a pitcher worth mentioning.
[PLAYER 13A]
Actually, I remember hearing
a rumor around that time.
What was it?
I just heard that Meisei had
some talented pitchers but
weren't ever allowed to pitch
back in those days because
some rich guy insisted
that his kid had to be the ace.
An ace pitcher who was only
there because of his father?
Oh, now that you mention it...
I seem to remember a ninth
grade ace who acted big,
but his ego didn't
match his talent.
[DAISUKE coughs]
[ICHIBAN]
Huh?
Wait, do you actually
have a cold?
[DAISUKE] No, just had
something caught in my throat.
[bat clangs]
[CROWD gasping]
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Wait... What the hell?
[CROWD cheers]
[SOUICHIROU] I thought I told
you that wasn't allowed.
[sighs] Is there some
kind of punishment for it?
Yeah.
[TOUMA sighs]
Now you had
better get a strikeout.
[ANNOUNCER 13A] Batting fourth,
first baseman, Akai.
[TOUMA] I'd better get
a strikeout, he says.
Great.
Although... I wouldn't
call that a punishment.
--No way!
--[gasps]
And remember, watch out
for their lefty Akai,
batting fourth.
Don't throw him any soft
pitches--you hear me?
[OOYAMA]
Oops.
--[KOMIYAMA grunts]
--[CROWD gasping]
[TODOROKI laughs]
[TADASHI]
Huh...?
[TODOROKI]
Wha...?
[TADASHI yelps]
[gasps]
[TODOROKI growls]
[TADASHI]
Phew!
[UMPIRE 13B]
Out!
[CROWD cheers]
Gettin' too old for this.
[TOUMA sighs]
[NARRATOR] An ace who
can't keep a promise...
A Kenjo lineup that
lives up to the rumors...
And a fourth batter,
who surpasses all the rumors...
Phew.
[NARRATOR]
This is sure to be a great game!
[OTOMI]
Next time, on Mix.
[ICHIBAN] The East Tokyo
Tournament has finally started!
--I'm pumped!
--[DAISUKE] Yeah.
[ICHIBAN] They're facing a great
team, in the very first game!
A lefty with irregular
form an iron wall infield!
[DAISUKE]
Yeah.
[ICHIBAN] Is our first year
battery gonna be okay?
--[DAISUKE] Yeah!
--[ICHIBAN] Are you sure?
Like, are you really,
surely positive?
[DAISUKE] Shut up! Be quiet
and watch the game!
[OTOMI]
Next time, "We're Losing!"
[ICHIBAN]
What?! We're losing?! No!
[PUNCH barks]