[COLORCASTER] It's the
bottom of the sixth inning,
and Meisei High
School is up to bat.
In the batter's box now is
the pitcher who entered
the game in the last inning.
Batting ninth, it's
number 11, Takaoka!
And there's the first pitch!
[NARRATOR] It's been 30 years
since that glorious summer.
And now, the once triumphant
Meisei baseball team
will be making its
electrifying return.
This is the story
of two brothers,
a pitcher and a catcher.
Along with their younger
sister, they face
life's countless adventures
while aiming for the top.
The three share one goal:
Get to the Koshien Tournament!
[CROWD shouting]
[TOUSHU MANAGER] Looks like
their lead has increased.
They've gotten themselves
out of a few jams,
but that's not the
interesting part.
They haven't used
their ace pitcher.
[COLORCASTER]
And strike three!
Guess that settles it.
We're playing Kaiou Nishi.
[MITA] So it seems, but are
you satisfied with that?
[TOUSHU MANAGER, MAEDA]
What?
[COLORCASTER] Up to bat is
left fielder, Touma Tachibana.
[MITA]
Don't you want to see him pitch?
If we played them, you could
see his form up close again.
If we do end up playing Meisei,
we'd use our official lineup,
unlike that practice game.
I suppose.
[COLORCASTER]
Tachibana gets a solid hit
on the ball after a bounce.
And off it goes
into center field!
[CROWD cheering]
[TOUSHU MANAGER] You better
hope Kaiou Nishi wins.
[MITA, MAEDA]
What?
Regardless of who we play,
I can't imagine us losing.
But that kid gives
me the creeps.
[MAEDA] He thinks that
Meisei guy is... creepy?
Does the manager mean
that as a compliment?
He sure does.
[COLORCASTER] Now entering
the box, batting third,
it's the elder Tachibana
brother, Souichirou.
[HARUKA]
I wonder,
could having Souichirou pitch
in this game be an option?
[OOYAMA]
Nope.
We can't afford
to take Souichirou
off his catcher position.
The cost of doing that would
greatly outweigh the benefits.
Without him acting as
the backbone of the team,
we wouldn't have a chance
at winning this game.
Yeah... You're right.
Up to this point,
he's thrown out
at least three runners on base.
[bat clinks]
[CROWD cheers]
[TADASHI grunts]
[COLORCASTER] With two outs,
Tachibana batting third,
and Imagawa up fourth,
Meisei High School scores,
bringing them within one run!
With a single point difference,
it's anybody's game!
[TADASHI chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
But...
...that didn't last very long.
[COLORCASTER] Meisei High
School is changing pitchers.
[COLORCASTER]
Bottom of the eighth,
and Meisei High
School is up to bat.
--[TSUKAMOTO grunts]
--[MEISEI PLAYER grunts]
[TADASHI grunts]
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Strike three! You're out!
[COLORCASTER]
That's three up and three down.
In the bottom of the eighth,
Tsukamoto of Kaiou Nishi
impressively gets the Meisei
batters out in order!
[ISAMI]
It's over.
Let's head back to school, now.
Okay...
[TSUKAMOTO grunts]
What's up? Is somethin' wrong?
Ah, no. It's nothing.
Is something wrong?
[SOUICHIROU]
No. It's nothing.
[COLORCASTER] Kaiou Nishi
has added another run
at the top of the ninth.
They now have a three-run lead.
[COLORCASTER] We've come to
the bottom of the ninth inning.
Meisei High School is up.
--[TSUKAMOTO grunts]
--[COLORCASTER] Taking the mound
for Kaiou Nishi is
ace pitcher Tsukamoto,
who entered the game
in the previous inning.
As you recall, he was able to
retire Meisei's lineup in order,
showing the crowd exactly
why he's the ace pitcher.
Seems like he's takin'
his time stretchin', today.
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Play ball!
[COLORCASTER] In three more
outs, Kaiou Nishi will take
their first ever trip
to the semifinals.
[TSUKAMOTO grunts]
[bat clinks]
--[TSUKAMOTO gasps]
--[COLORCASTER] It's a pop fly!
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Out!
[CROWD clapping, cheering]
[TAKAOKA]
Sorry, Touma.
[TOUMA, SOUICHIROU]
Hmm?
We weren't able to give you
the support you needed.
And it was all thanks to you
that we were even able to pitch
in such an important game
in the first place.
We feel awful. We really do.
Even if I wasn't around,
you would've had
your chances to pitch,
probably against an easier team.
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Ball! That's four!
[SOUICHIROU] Kaiou Nishi
has a powerful lineup that has
averaged more than seven
runs per game at this point.
You guys should be proud.
[COLORCASTER] Hirao hits
the first pitch! But wait!
It's heading straight
back to the pitcher!
With a double play here,
Kaiou Nishi could go
to their first ever semifinal!
Is this the end for Meisei?
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[MEISEI TEAM gasping]
[TSUKAMOTO whimpering]
What was that?
When he walked off the mound,
it looked like he
pulled a muscle.
How could this have happened?
They want to see him play, too.
[MITA]
The baseball gods, that is.
Gotcha!
[yells] Cut it out!
[WOMAN A]
No way!
[NEWSCASTER A] Meisei High
School somehow won this game,
but their semifinal opponent
is Toushu High School,
whose star player is Mita, a kid
the pros have their eyes on.
Just how will
this game turn out?
Oh, hi! [giggles]
[NISHIMURA]
What the heck are they thinking?
[ISAMI]
It's necessary.
They have to, to keep
the viewers satisfied.
[NISHIMURA]
Hmm?
Oh wait, you mean
Kaiou Nishi. Meh.
[NISHIMURA grunts]
[ISAMI] Well, they had
a stroke of bad luck.
It happens, but that's what
makes baseball so interesting
and also terrifying.
Yeah, well, my problem isn't
with the bad luck or the game,
it's the coverage!
There's more than just
one semifinal game, y'know!
And there's also another
first-year ace pitcher,
but I don't see them
talkin' about me in here.
[ISAMI] Maybe it's because you
don't come off as a first-year.
--[NISHIMURA] Hm?
--[ISAMI] You don't look
or act it.
Is that a good thing?
[ISAMI sighs]
[ISAMI] You can take
it however you like.
[NISHIMURA]
I say it's a good thing!
[OTOMI humming]
[TOUMA]
What the heck are they thinking?
That kind of stuff
is necessary, once in a while.
[grunts]
[TADASHI]
What're those?
Business cards.
I got 'em from some
supposed alumni.
There was a company president,
some general manager,
an editor, and a legislator.
I kept having to meet
these random fancy old guys
and pose for photo ops.
It's starting to get
in the way of practice!
[TOUMA sighs]
[TADASHI] Yeah. I guess
that's just how it goes.
If we do end up making
it into the Koshien,
the school's gonna
need the funding.
That means we gotta do whatever
we can to keep 'em happy,
so for the school's sake,
just keep playin' along.
Fine, I'll do what I have to do.
But they should do their
research before jumping the gun.
Excuse me, Touma!
Do you have a second?
[TADASHI] Looks like those
guys are next in line.
Better hurry.
[sighs]
[PUNCH barking]
[MAN A] Touma, please!
Just a moment of your time!
Wait. Where'd he go?
Hmm?
[TADASHI]
Huh, what's that?
Souichirou, where's Tou?
I told him to duck out
and go for a run.
Good call, right?
Uh-huh. Good call.
One question though.
How'd he get away
completely unnoticed?
Touma was practically
surrounded.
It's pretty simple.
Since we live next door,
the school has basically
been our playground
since we were little and
we'd sneak in all the time.
We know this whole place
like the back of our hands.
Which means we also know
the secret ways outta here.
[PUNCH barking]
[TOUMA]
Mm?
Be careful when you're
riding with the dog!
He's in the basket. It's fine.
He's too fat for that basket.
[barks]
[bat clinks]
[KOMIYAMA grunts]
[OOKUMA]
What's the matter?
Is that freshman prodigy
of yours in a slump already?
Ah, good to see ya.
He's having some
trouble bouncing back,
but his dream was shattered,
so I can't blame him.
He'll have more chances in the
next two years, so it's fine.
[KOMIYAMA grunts]
You're assuming that
his dream was Koshien,
but that isn't the case.
Really?
[KOMIYAMA] Ever since
he was in elementary school,
his goal has always
been Hiroki Mita.
The same Hiroki Mita
that goes to Toushu?
That boy idolized Mita.
And hoped that one day
he could face those pitches head
on and swing with all he had.
This year was his only chance,
and now it's gone.
[OOKUMA]
No, it's not!
Hey, it's not like
the guy died or anything.
Ya never know, the two
of them could end up going pro
and playing against each
other in the big leagues.
I'm afraid the solution
isn't that simple.
Counting the Sumi Tech days,
it's been almost 60 years,
and only one student's gone
pro, y'know what I'm saying?
I see your point.
That one pro never got
promoted to the first league,
and his career ended
after a measly two years.
[KOMIYAMA]
It wasn't that bad.
Things would've been fine
if he didn't have that injury.
That injury was a result
of him trying to reach too far
and achieve more
than he was capable of.
The truth is, there was
only one player
who was significantly
better than me,
and he was Sumi Tech's
one, true genius.
Mr. Ookuma! The principal
is waiting for you!
Okay!
[OOKUMA]
Manager.
[KOMIYAMA]
Hm?
[OOKUMA] That kid you've
got there is without a doubt
the second genius
this team has ever had.
Make sure you take
good care of him.
[KOMIYAMA grunts]
[bat clinks]
[AKAI grunts]
[AKAI]
What do you think you're doing?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[TOUMA]
Hey, been a while.
Our school was eliminated,
so what brings you here?
My dog. We were out here
taking him for a walk,
but then he got off his leash
and ran in this direction.
Your dog?
Oh, this is my sister.
I'm Otomi. Nice to meet you.
And his name's Akai.
That means you're Ryou's
older brother, right?
[TOUMA]
Wait.
Have you guys met before?
We haven't,
but I did see him with
Arisa Mita at the coffee shop.
[inaudible]
[AKAI grunts]
Hiroki Mita's little sister?
Hold on, I thought she
was into the younger Akai.
Unless...
Don't get the wrong idea.
I only met with her to
pick up an autograph board.
[TOUMA]
Autograph?
[AKAI] If you don't have
a real reason to be here,
then please leave.
What the...?
--[barking]
--[gasps, yells]
--Stop it, Punch!
--[AKAI groans]
What are you freaking
out about? He's just a dog.
[barking]
To be honest with you,
I despise dogs.
Well, the dog seems to like
you, so that's too bad.
I told you two
to get out of here.
You're not allowed to be on the
school grounds without a reason.
[TOUMA]
But I do have a reason.
[gasps]
When we played,
you were the only one who was
able to score runs against me.
So? What's your point?
Point is, the better I do,
the better it reflects on you
as a player and proves
how good you actually are.
--[PUNCH barks]
--Hope hearin' that
--[OTOMI] Hmm?
--makes ya feel better!
When you play
against Hiroki Mita,
you think you can win?
[TOUMA]
It won't just be him.
I'll be up against
the whole Toushu lineup.
[AKAI] And that lineup has
some of the best batters
in the tournament.
Yeah, well, I'm not
too worried about 'em.
None of them are as good as you.
[gasps]
[PUNCH barks]
'Kay, let's go.
Welp, see you around I guess.
Tachibana.
[BOTH]
Hm?
What if I...
[TOUMA]
If... you what?
[gasps, exhales]
This is ridiculous.
What are you talking about?
He just doesn't like to open up.
I wonder why?
Eh, who knows.
[OTOMI]
Hm? Hmm?
Hey, Touma? Where's Punch?
Huh?
[NARRATOR] The East Tokyo
Tournament Semifinal.
Meisei High School versus
Toushu High School.
The game everyone's been waiting
for begins tomorrow morning.
[NISHIMURA]
You have got to be kidding me!
I told you! There's
another semifinal game!
Hold on.
I'm not finished
talking, don't you--!
[horn blares]
Great!
Hey, Otomi!
Gimme a sec,
and I'll be ready to go!
Yeah, okay!
Hm?
Hey mom, are you sure you don't
wanna come to the game with us?
Someone has to stay back
and keep an eye on the house.
Especially after
one of the neighbors
had their place
broken into recently.
I have trouble keeping
track of the rules anyway,
so watching it on TV with
the commentary is better for me.
Don't worry, and just
go enjoy yourself!
[MAYUMI] The three of us
will be here rooting for them.
Right! Now let's go, yeah!
Don't you need to be in
disguise, Dad? Or am I wrong?
Don't you worry about that!
Because today is Sunday,
all across the nation! [laughs]
[PUNCH howls]
[NARRATOR]
Now, the time has come.
The East Tokyo
Tournament Semifinal.
It's the game between
Meisei High School
and Toushu High School.
[COLORCASTER] Behind the first
base dugout, third base dugout,
even behind home plate, there's
not an empty seat in the house!
[HYOURI] It's only because
of the media attention
on top of today's
being a Sunday.
The media jumps on a better
than average freshman,
and blows things
out of proportion.
They've been pulling
this stunt for years.
It's a nice story,
but it doesn't seem to mention
that Meisei was
on the receiving end
of Mita's perfect practice game
before the tournament.
Oh, did that really happen?
But there's nothing
about it here
in the information that
was submitted by Meisei.
Of course not, since
that manager of theirs
likes to pretend that
whole debacle never happened.
They're the sloppiest
baseball team I've ever seen,
just a mess.
As far as the
first-years are concerned,
Nishimura from Seinan
is a much better player,
but he's not popular
with the masses,
so he doesn't get
any of the attention.
I see.
So, let me just
spell it out for you.
There's only a single
aspect of the game
that's gonna be
interesting to watch,
and that's how bad
Meisei's gonna lose.
[ASSISTANT DIRECTOR]
On air in five minutes!
They'll all regret making
it this far in the tournament.
And after they get torn
apart, limb from limb,
they'll never wanna
play baseball again!
[chuckles]
[KOMA]
Well?
What do ya make of that
ace pitcher of theirs?
[SOUICHIROU] Hard to say
by watching the warm up.
[KOMA] Yeah, but can you tell
if he's having an off-day?
Any pitcher can have
one of those, right?
Yeah, maybe,
but look at all those
scouts in the crowd.
Even if he did have an off-day,
I doubt we'd notice.
He'd still be good
enough for the pros
to be paying attention
to him regardless.
[SOUICHIROU] It all depends
on Touma at this point.
How badly we lose is up to him.
[yelps]
What was that for?
For you giving up before
the game's even begun!
Yeah, right!
I'm only saying those things
to get Touma in
the right headspace.
I know him better than anyone,
and that's what works.
[HARUKA]
You sure about that?
Just trust me.
He's psyching himself up
for the game right now.
[gasps] Is he really?
[snoring]
[SOUICHIROU, HARUKA, KOMA grunt]
Hey!
Stop it! Wait!
Moments before a big game and
they're as easy goin' as ever.
Ya love to see it.
That's classic
Meisei right there.
Wait, hold on. The manager?
[NANGOU]
Bathroom.
[TADASHI]
Aw, come on.
I thought he just
went a second ago.
It's his third trip.
[TADASHI chuckles nervously]
[CROWD cheering]
We expect a smooth, fair game!
[ALL]
Let us all have a good game!
[COLORCASTER]
All right, then.
After some respectful
greetings by the two teams,
the starting members of Toushu,
who are batting in the bottom
half, take to the field.
The stands are packed today,
the crowd is ready to see
this highly anticipated match.
This game features
the prodigy from Toushu,
the left-handed,
ace pitcher, Hiroki Mita!
It won't be easy to score
against this pitcher.
He hasn't given up a single run
in the entire tournament.
Together with their powerful
lineup, this flawless team
has their eyes set on
the National Championship.
Many have considered Toushu
to be the overwhelming favorite
to win the tournament
from the very beginning.
I wouldn't be too
sure about that.
Much like any game,
you won't be sure of
the outcome until it's over!
So, keep an open mind!
The resurgence of Meisei
is nothing to scoff at,
so don't underestimate them!
Keep an eye on the first-year
ace pitcher, Touma Tachibana.
There's something special about
that kid, I can just feel it!
So, I'm sure we'll be treated
to an exhilarating game!
[COLORCASTER]
Hmm.
An insightful observation from
co-commentator, Mr. Hyouri.
[HYOURI]
That's me!
And no one's more excited
to watch this game than I am!
[COLORCASTER] The plate
umpire raises his right arm.
[PLATE UMPIRE]
Play ball!
[HARUKA]
Next time, on Mix .
[OTOMI]
The semifinals have begun!
[HARUKA]
And the opponent is Toushu!
[NISHIMURA] Seinan is in
the other semifinal!
[OTOMI] They're up against
the monstrous Hiroki Mita.
[HARUKA] How can our
freshman ace compete with him?
[NISHIMURA]
There is another freshman ace,
you know that, right?
[OTOMI]
All eyes are on this game only!
[HARUKA] It might as well
be considered the finals!
[NISHIMURA]
But it's not!
There's another semifinal
game with me in it!
[HARUKA] Next time,
"He Loves His Sister."
[OTOMI] I wonder who's
playing in the other game?
--[barks]
--[NISHIMURA] Shut up!