[ASURAMARU]
The non-human part of you
is about to lose all control.
[screaming]
[LACUS]
They suspect it's magic.
That the humans have discovered
a forbidden enchantment
that could destroy the world.
They called it.
"Seraph of the End," I think.
Snap out of it! Please, Yu!
[GUREN]
And so it begins.
[SHINOA] Yu! Stop it!
Please, you have to!
Or all of us are going to die!
Come back to us!
[SHINOA]
It's been five days.
What the hell did you do to him?
[GUREN]
What would you do to ensure
the future of humanity?
How can we survive
in this ruined world?
More importantly,
how do we completely
eradicate the vampires?
A Human victory will
require sacrifice.
[FERID] As usual, the
humans' lust for power
is out of control.
And we vampires are so arrogant
that we take things too lightly.
Wouldn't you agree with me?
Go, Shi!
Lend me your power, Mahiru.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Go ahead and kill me.
No one would blame you.
Don't mock me.
You could dodge if you wanted.
[GUREN] I wouldn't mind
if you were the one
who took my life.
Looking for atonement?
Sorry, but you're going to have
to live with your mistakes, sir.
My sister, Mahiru, loved
you, Lieutenant Colonel.
But she was
possessed by a demon.
Passion consumed her.
And then you...
[GUREN] That's right.
I killed your sister.
[SHINOA] But, Mahiru
didn't leave this world.
She became something else.
You used her to create
your Cursed Gear
and betray the Hiragi Family.
You're possessed by my sister.
Is that why you're
trying to manipulate Yu?
Because my sister
is telling you to?
What's your endgame with him?
[SHINOA]
Lieutenant Colonel.
If you're going to
end up hurting Yu,
even a bit, then I must
humbly ask you to stop.
Why?
Don't tell me you've
fallen for that idiotic kid.
[gasps]
[GUREN] It's true that
your sister is in here.
But I am the one
who's in control.
I'm not possessed by her.
Would you even know?
If she had you?
[GUREN] I don't care whether
you believe me or not.
Ah.
[sighs, groans]
[SHINOA]
You're always here lately.
What are you reading?
[YUICHIRO gasps]
You scared me, Shinoa!
Aren't you still supposed
to be on bed rest
and recovering?
I was going nuts in that bed.
Besides, I feel
totally fine now.
The doctors will decide
when you're back in
fighting shape. Besides...
What is it?
Nothing. Forget it.
[giggles] Wait, you're not
really reading this, are you?
I bet you're hiding
porn in here.
[giggles]
[YUICHIRO]
Hey, give that back. Come on!
Where'd you hide it?
[YUICHIRO]
Jeez.
[gasps]
[SHINOA]
Tell me.
Do you want to turn Mika
back into a human being?
[SHINOA]
If that's the case,
I might have some
helpful information.
Huh?!
[SHINOA]
Do you want to hear it?
Yeah. I do!
Aw, you're always
so cute and obedient
whenever you want something.
Hey, shut up!
Just tell me what
you know, okay?
First of all.
It's pretty rare that a human
is turned into a vampire.
The bloodsuckers like
to keep their ranks tight
and their numbers small.
More importantly,
within vampire society,
the nobles are the only ones
who have the authority
to turn a human.
Wait, so it wasn't random
that Mika was turned--
he was chosen?
[SHINOA]
Can you think of a noble
who might have picked him?
Yeah. Maybe.
You know.
It's our duty to destroy
vampires. All of them.
[YUICHIRO] Not him.
I thought Mika was dead.
But he's alive, and that's
enough. Tell me, Shinoa.
Do you have any idea
how to turn a vampire
back into a human?
[YUICHIRO]
I see. Well, now what?
[SHINOA] I don't think
that I've ever seen you
look so serious before, Yu.
It's almost like you've found
a whole new reason to live.
[ANNOUNCER] Special
Private Yuichiro Hyakuya.
Report to the First
Office immediately.
I wonder what Guren wants now.
No.
It's probably the Hiragi
family who summoned you.
Hold on, the Hiragi family?
You mean the leaders
of the Demon Company
that got Japan back on its feet
after the world went to crap?
[SHINOA] You really shouldn't
keep them waiting.
[YUICHIRO]
Uh-- Wait a minute.
Isn't your last name Hiragi?
Ah! You finally
figured out my secret.
I'm not just a sergeant,
I'm basically royalty.
Now, feel free to worship
me as much as you'd like!
[YUICHIRO sighs]
Okay, okay, all joking aside.
The Hiragis can be an extremely
intense group of people.
So be careful, okay, Yu?
[GUREN]
There's my favorite moron.
So, the most powerful
family in Japan pages you
and you come
running like a dog.
What?
Am I just supposed
to ignore them then?
I've got a little story for you.
Once upon a time, a wise
old man freed a doomed crane
from a hunter's trap.
In return, the crane
wove a beautiful cloth
from its own wings
as a gift for the man.
Huh? What are you talking about?
I am the wise man
who saved you.
Remember? And I was nice
enough to teach you
how to survive in this world
and protect your family.
[YUICHIRO]
What's gotten into you?
And why do I feel like
you're patronizing me?
[GUREN]
In a manner of speaking,
you can return the favor today.
Will you just tell me
what it is you want me--
[GUREN] I saved your life
and now I own you.
So don't go wagging
your tail for them.
[YUICHIRO]
So that's what this is about.
You don't control me.
You're wrong about that, Yu.
[YUICHIRO]
This is ridiculous.
I don't care about
whatever grudge you have
against the Hiragi Family.
It doesn't ma--
[GUREN]
Shut up and listen, kid.
You may not care
about army politics,
but that's the way
this world works.
You don't have to
worry about me, Guren.
Come on.
I'm not someone who
abandons his friends.
Haven't you learned
that about me yet?
[GUREN]
Hm? Yeah, I guess.
But that doesn't make
me feel any better.
After all, I am not your friend.
[YUICHIRO] Oh, yeah?
Well then, what are you?
Guardian. Your superior.
Life saver. I'm
basically your god.
Ugh. Please!
Huh?
What's up? Did you
get called in, too?
How did it go?
It was just a stupid interview.
Apparently, I'm moving
up a rank for my part
in fighting off the vampires and
my bravery on the battlefield.
[YUICHIRO]
A promotion, huh? Nice.
It's no surprise.
I totally deserve it,
don't'cha think?
If you say so.
Hey, wait!
You can't just say that
and then leave!
Huh?
[MITSUBA] You know I
shouldn't be promoted.
I was completely useless
when things got tough
on the battlefield.
Sure, I can talk a big game,
but I can't follow through.
It's because I'm, I'm so weak.
And yet, I bet I'm the
only one getting promoted.
Just because I'm part
of the Sangu family.
Go ahead and laugh.
Go on! I'm a failure.
Stop it. I'm not
laughing, Mitsuba.
It's weird. I mean,
you and Shinoa.
I had no idea until today
that we basically have
two princesses on our team.
Between the Sangus
and the Hiragis,
shouldn't we be
living in a castle?
You are... such an idiot.
Whatever.
Anyway, this promotion
is good news.
The higher you go, the more
you can help me out.
You mean your family, right?
Yeah.
[MITSUBA] They're going to ask
about that in the interview.
They think you might be a spy.
So I've been ordered
to keep an eye on you.
Oh? Wow.
Do you think that I'm a spy?
[MITSUBA]
I told them that was impossible.
And that, in my opinion,
you're not smart enough
to be a double agent. So there.
[YUICHIRO chuckles]
Thanks, I guess. But seriously.
I'm glad that you believe in me.
Wait, Yu.
[YUICHIRO]
Hm?
[MITSUBA] The Hiragi family
is terrifying. Watch yourself.
[YUICHIRO]
I will. Thanks.
[MITSUBA sighs]
[SHINOA]
Was that a sigh?
What do you have to
be depressed about?
[MITSUBA] Shinoa. What are
you doing out here?
Oh, nothing. Just out
enjoying a little walk.
Did the Hiragi
family talk to you?
Yeah, they gave me a promotion.
I'm now a Special
Second Lieutenant.
Oh, wow, that's super
impressive, Mitsu!
And so shocking that
a Sangu can get promoted
without actually working for it.
Ah--
[SHINOA giggles]
Oh, don't be upset.
Oh, yeah? What about you?
I bet they were falling
all over themselves
to move you up a rank and
make themselves even more--
No promotion here.
And besides, if they did
try to move me up a rank,
I would just kindly refuse.
That sounds about right.
The Hiragis do what they want.
[SHINOA]
Not all of us.
Actually, I kinda think my
family has lost all hope
for me these days.
Sure.
[SHINOA]
So, how much information
did you have to give up
in exchange for the promotion?
[MITSUBA]
What do you mean?
[SHINOA] They wanted to
know about what happened
when Yu freaked out, right?
When he lost control.
I told them that I
didn't know anything.
Seemed like they didn't either.
[SHINOA] If that's true,
then the experimentation on Yu
must not have been officially
sanctioned by the Demon Army.
Do you have any idea
what that was
on the battlefield?
I don't. I wish I did.
In a world like this,
it's not always clear
who's on your side
and who's not.
I just hope Yu's smart enough
to know the difference.
[knocking]
What the...?
[gasps]
Huh?
But how did a
vampire get in here?
[growls]
[grunts]
[VAMPIRE 13A groans]
Jeez, what kind of crap
are they trying to pull?
[KURETO] That was a test
of loyalty to make sure
you aren't a traitor.
Now, shall we go ahead
and start your interview?
Who the heck are you?
Kureto Hiragi.
Imperial Demon Army
lieutenant general.
Yuichiro Hyakuya.
Let's get a better sense
of how skilled you are
with a sword. But don't
activate the curse.
Sounds like fun.
But don't get angry if I
humiliate the almighty Hiragi.
Oh, Yu.
Perhaps it would be better
if you don't listen
to everything
brother Kureto says.
What?
[KURETO] Ignore him.
Possess me. Raimeiki.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
So this is the best you can do?
I have to admit,
I'm not impressed.
That was dirty.
Complain about
someone fighting dirty
in a real battle and see if that
keeps them from killing you.
ou do take orders
well, at least.
You didn't even hesitate
to follow my command.
Hard to believe you're
that disobedient Guren's--
Back off.
[YUICHIRO]
Well, look at that.
You'd be dead right now if your
comrade hadn't stepped in.
What? Why the long face?
You don't think
it was a dirty move
for me to attack
from behind, do you?
Heh. I take back what
I was going to say.
You are indeed
Guren's subordinate.
We're done?
That was pretty fast.
[KURETO]
Shinya.
Huh?
Aw, but I don't wanna.
This isn't my kind of thing.
I don't enjoy bullying the weak.
As an adoptive son,
you will do as you're told.
Man... Well, if I must. Fine.
Stop fooling around.
Who are you calling weak?
Why, you, silly boy.
Wanna try me?
[SHINYA] Well, that is the
order I'm supposed to follow.
Let's begin.
After him, Byakkomaru.
Bang.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[grunts]
That's it. It's over.
And I'm not even that
good at close combat
compared to Kureto or Guren.
My Byakkomaru is more of a
long-range specialty weapon.
You do understand
what that means
about your skill level, yes?
But, it's not your fault.
Seems to me like you
weren't properly trained
to use your Cursed Gear.
What a shame.
But, try not to
feel too pathetic.
So then.
Does that finally clear
me of any suspicion?
It's obvious he doesn't know me
or my fighting style. Okay?
Wait. What the hell was
that test really about?
They actually think that
I might be a traitor, too,
since I'm friends with
Guren. Crazy, right?
It does seem there's
a vampire spy
in the army somewhere, though.
For the Hiragis,
that's a huge problem
that must be dealt
with immediately.
Then leave me out of it.
'Cause if you think I'm the spy,
then you're out of your--
[KURETO]
Bring him along.
[gasps]
Let go of me!
[YUICHIRO]
Kimizuki! Yoichi!
All right, what have
you done to them?
[KURETO] I interrogated them
because we think you're the spy.
You're insane!
Let's start your interview.
You will speak only the truth.
Deceive us, and your
friends will die.
[gasps]
There isn't much background
here in your file.
And yet, you managed
to somehow attain
a Black Demon weapon.
As did your two
teammates over there.
Normally, there are
thorough background checks
conducted for
anyone going through
the Cursed Gear ceremony.
But there weren't
any for you three.
Why not?
Where did the three
of you come from?
What is your mission?
My mission? I told you!
Do it.
[muffled screaming]
[gasps] Stop it.
Then answer truthfully.
I am! I don't know
what you want me to say!
[KURETO]
The next one.
[muffled screaming]
[gasps] Please, stop!
I'll do whatever you want.
Ask me anything!
Good attitude. Let's talk
more about your past.
You grew up in the vampire city,
but you somehow
managed to escape.
It was during your
getaway that the vampires
brutally murdered your family.
Which is why you're
so hungry for revenge.
At least, that's what
it says in the file.
Is this correct?
Yeah.
There's no way I'm working
for those bloodsuckers.
[KURETO] Your protests aren't
doing you any favors.
Afterwards, Guren
Ichinose discovered you
and took you in.
The question is why?
Why did Guren take
an interest in you?
What exactly are you to him?
[YUICHIRO]
I don't...
Is Hyakuya really
your last name,
or is that a lie, too?
Are you of the Hyakuya Sect?
[gasps] No, I'm not.
It was just the name of
the orphanage I grew up in!
Are you aware that
the Hyakuya Sect
was the largest spellcraft
organization in Japan?
They routinely brought lost
children to their orphanage
and used them for
human experimentation
and to test out
new forms of magic.
You were likely a lab rat
for spellcraft experimentation.
Huh?
[KURETO] This is starting
to make more sense.
Guren must actually be
trying to use something
the Hyakuya Sect put inside you.
Come.
Work for me instead,
Yuichiro Hyakuya.
Allow me to be your new guide.
Let Yoichi and Kimizuki
go right now.
We're all done here.
[KIMIZUKI, YOICHI groan, sigh]
[YUICHIRO] I don't know what's
up between you and Guren
or what you're fighting about.
But at least Guren wouldn't
use this kind of torture.
[KURETO]
I know.
That's why I'm always
one step ahead of him.
You're free to go now.
[laughs]
What a messed up place this is.
But still, I can't wait to see
what you do next, lab rat.
You're so fidgety.
Are you really
that worried about Yu?
Huh?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I mean, why would I worry
about an idiot like him?
[gasps] Oh, Yu!
[MITSUBA]
Yu!
Whoa, Kimizuki and
Yoichi look terrible!
What happened to you?
What's going on?
That interview was total crap.
The Stupid Hiragi--
Guren! You better
start explaining!
[YUICHIRO]
Kureto said that me, my family--
all of us were used
as guinea pigs.
Experimented on by some weirdo
sect practicing spellcraft.
Tell me the truth.
Did you save me just
so you could use me?
[gasps]
That's right.
I don't have the
luxury of saving anyone
who doesn't serve
a higher purpose.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
So, what?
Are you gonna
start sulking now?
No. Regardless of your reasons,
I would've died if
you didn't find me.
All I wanna know is
if I'm of use to you
in our fight against
the vampires.
If I am, then you must wanna
recruit Mika as well, right?
He was a lab rat, too!
I don't care about whatever
the Hyakuya did to me.
I can't change that.
It's done. Just tell me
how I can get Mika back.
But, Yu...
[GUREN]
Like I said before.
Everyone here is your family,
and that includes me.
That means we'll work together
to get the rest of
your family back.
If that's true...
Then teach me how
to be a better fighter!
Show me the proper way
to use my Cursed Gear!
That was already my next step.
[MIKAELA panting, whimpering]
[MIKAELA grunts]
[panting]
[FERID] Why don't you take
a little sip already?
After all, Mika, this is
probably the best looking
you're ever going to be.
You wouldn't want to risk--
[DAIKI]
Excuse me.
Sorry.
But I heard that if I
offer my blood to you,
then you could make life
easier for me and my family.
Who told you such
a thing? Was it you?
[FERID]
Hm.
[DAIKI groans]
Here, Mika. Come and
taste this kid's blood.
Quench your terrible thirst.
[gasps]
[groaning]
[gasping]
[gulps]
[growls]
[DAIKI grunts]
It's against the rules to
drink directly from a human.
[FERID]
You're such a goody-two-shoes.
[DAIKI groans, coughs]
Or maybe... You're just
thinking of him.
You're scared that Yu will--
What are you doing here, Ferid?
[DAIKI coughing]
[FERID]
Ah! Right.
I came here to invite
you to something.
You must attend the next
Progenitor Council meeting.
[MIKAELA]
The Progenitor Council?
What do they want?
[FERID] It'll be so
much more interesting
if you find out for
yourself, Mika, dear.
Now, shall we go?
[grunts]
[panting]
It's so painful...
I need your help. Yu.
[YUICHIRO] Next time,
on Seraph of the End:
"Complicated Connections."