Listen to me
carefully, everyone.
During this mission, I won't
tolerate any failures.
Follow my orders to the letter
and don't fool around.
This mission will probably be
the most dangerous
you will ever have.
Many of you will die.
Remember, everyone
here is family.
That means those
who fall in battle
are our brothers
and our sisters.
But they won't die in vain!
Their sacrifices will
ensure our success.
Let me be clear.
Our goal isn't
to come back alive.
It is to be victorious
no matter what!
Do you understand me?
[YUICHIRO grunting]
[YUICHIRO]
Hey, Shinoa. How much longer?
[SHINOA]
We've got about 20 minutes.
[NARUMI]
Everyone. Fall in line.
I want to go over our
plan of attack again.
[IWASAKI]
We begin at 1400 hours.
Our gathered troops will move
in teams attacking in unison.
If all goes as planned,
eight targets will be executed
leaving two nobles alive.
Our target's a strong one.
Lucal Wesker. The
Fifteenth Progenitor.
We plan to engage him here.
If we're unable to
take him by surprise,
our priority is to cut off
his retreat and prevent him
from joining the other nobles.
Once our target is dead,
we'll hold off
any remaining vampires until
the Lieutenant Colonel
supplies us with new orders.
Best-case scenario,
all the targets are killed
simultaneously and we don't
have a problem regrouping
and killing the remaining
two nobles in Nagoya.
If the targets aren't
destroyed and the nobles
join forces, there's no way
we'll be able to beat them.
Look.
All of our targets are located
fairly close to one another.
But since our assembled
forces have been split
into small groups, it should
keep the targets busy.
Our team's one of the smallest.
That means there must be
high expectations for us.
Even though there aren't as
many troops in our squad--
Failure is not an option.
If you make a mistake,
it'll affect the lives of
all 100 of your comrades.
You have to remember that.
We will.
[YUICHIRO sighs] Right, so
basically all we gotta do
is kill this LuLu LaLa
guy, right? No sweat.
Come on, man.
Fooling around
will get us killed.
This is behind enemy lines.
Have you forgotten what the
Lieutenant Colonel said?
Huh?
I'm just saying that it's
not gonna be that hard.
Show some respect.
This kid. He's isn't serious?
Sergeant Narumi.
Can't we be reassigned?
There's no way I can trust
these kids to have my back.
Whoa. Calm down, Rika.
We have to work alongside them.
We don't really have
time to switch out.
This kind of unrest isn't good.
They hate us.
Go apologize.
[SHINOA] Um. I apologize,
Sergeant Narumi.
I'll make sure my squad
is ready to follow order--
I don't need
anyone to apologize.
Just remember, we need
to be on our toes.
If one person drags us down,
then we're all as good as dead.
I don't wanna lose a comrade
because of a single screw up.
What is it?
Do you not agree
with what I said?
[YUICHIRO]
No. I-I mean, yes.
What I'm saying is that
I feel the same way.
I don't wanna lose
any comrades either.
I don't need excuses,
I need you to act--
[YUICHIRO] Listen! Our squads.
We're in this together.
So I'll make sure that
none of us get hurt.
[NARUMI] Then the least
you can do is remember
our target's name. There's
more to being a good soldier
than the ability
to swing a sword.
There's no point in
remembering the name
of someone you're
just going to kill.
But I do remember
the names of the people
I'm going to protect. Got it?
Shinoa. Kimizuki.
Mitsuba. Yoichi...
[YUICHIRO] Makoto Narumi.
Yayoi Endo. Rika Inoue.
Taro Kagiyama. Shusaku Iwasaki.
I won't let my
comrades get killed.
We'll show Guren
we can be victorious
without losing a
single teammate.
Uh--
[SHINOA] I apologize if
my subordinate's attitude
is out of line, Sergeant Narumi.
But everyone on my
squad feels the same.
We're with you 100%.
We may be newbs, but we'll
follow our directives
and try our best not
to drag anyone down.
I swear this on my
honor and my life.
Fine, then.
The mission will begin
in six minutes.
Yayoi. Report.
Our target should
be in site soon.
Any second, according
to our intelligence.
He visits the park around this
time every day without fail.
[yawns] This sounded like
a good idea in theory,
but now that it's time,
I'm getting kinda nervous.
Keep it together.
We've got the upper hand today.
We're taking them
completely by surprise.
Let's do this together.
Without any deaths. No one hurt.
A victorious mission.
With all targets executed.
Got it.
We should get started.
[panting]
[SHINYA]
What's wrong, Yoichi?
You're starting to
make me nervous.
We've still got five minutes
before the mission begins.
Yeah. I know.
But what happens if we screw up
and the whole thing turns--
[SHINYA]
Don't even entertain the idea.
With any luck,
we'll finish him off.
Then we'll be war heroes.
[YOICHI grunts]
[SHINYA] Worry too much and
you'll mess up for sure.
Now, then.
This is your first
sniper mission, right?
Guren asked me to teach you a
few things to get you prepared.
Like I said, first,
you need to calm down.
Okay.
Great.
Try to take it easy and
remember that we're not alone.
If we don't take Wesker down,
then the others will.
That's the whole reason the
close-combat team exists anyway.
[YOICHI]
Right.
Snipers need to keep their cool.
It's the only way we're
gonna pick off enemies
and backup our comrades.
Or kill them if
they're captured,
saving them from
unspeakable torture
at the hands of the vampires.
[gasps] You'd kill
your own teammates?
If necessary, yeah.
But as long as we land our
shots, we won't have to worry
about anything like that.
So unwind, take a deep breath.
All right.
[SHINYA]
Relax your muscles.
Focus on trying to
slow down your pulse.
Once you're breathing steadily,
try calling for your demon.
Come out, Gekkouin.
Thank you for that.
I feel better.
Good boy. Stay alert.
Our target should show
himself any time now.
Go ahead and get the
park in your sites.
[YOICHI]
Okay.
[YOICHI] There are lots
of normal vampires
walking around down there.
[SHINYA] Ignore them.
Focus on finding that noble.
[YOICHI]
Right.
[SHINYA]
Here he comes.
He's the one in the hat.
That's Lucal Wesker.
[SHINYA] Don't get an
itchy trigger finger.
Wait until I give
you the signal.
Otherwise, all our plans
will be thrown off.
[YOICHI]
Got it.
[LUCAL] Hm... Not bad
today. Where's it from?
This was collected in Naka.
Prisoner 58. Female. Age four.
[LUCAL]
Hm...
I do love the mellow taste
of frightened young girls.
I insist that you
have a sip, Esther.
Thank you.
But I've already had more
than my share to drink today
thanks to your
generosity, my lord.
[LUCAL]
But this is a rare treat,
blood of the highest quality.
Perfection. It should be
savored while it's fresh.
Please, enjoy yourself.
I'll try it once we've
returned to the compound.
Very well.
Now, business.
What do you make of the
absurd letter I received
from Krul Tepes?
[ESTHER] I assume that you
are referring to her plan
to annihilate the Japanese
Imperial Demon Army?
[LUCAL] The arrogance of that
woman, handing out orders
from her fragile
throne in Kyoto,
insisting that we deal with
a few insignificant humans.
I don't like it.
Since when do I
follow her commands?
[ESTHER] We are affiliated with
a different political party.
There's no need for us to act
until we've received orders
straight from the
Progenitor Council.
[LUCAL]
Hm...
[ESTHER]
Although,
rumor has it Queen Krul
is coming to Nagoya
to oversee things herself.
Oh? Is that right.
Yes.
[LUCAL] Hm. Then perhaps it
would be wise to comply.
Difficult to say. Last I heard,
your actual boss,
Lest Karr, was still engaged
in a power struggle with Krul.
Meaning I'll be punished
if I help her.
Well. I suppose the
only thing to do--
[ESTHER]
Mm? Lord Lucal--
Everyone, take your curse
stimulant pills, now!
It's time. Let's
make this quick.
[LUCAL]
How unfortunate.
My sword. Drink of my blood.
[YOICHI, SHINYA gasp]
We missed!
[SHINYA]
Don't fall apart yet.
Take down as many
vampires as you can
before jumping to safety.
Yeah, okay!
Narumi! Let me take
the first strike.
I'll gauge the enemy's
strength. Just cover me!
You've got my permission.
Make it count!
[gasps]
Nice shootin', Yoichi!
The livestock are
attacking. How pathetic.
[YUICHIRO]
Call us whatever you want.
I'll show you who's
really pathetic.
I have to admit, I can't
wait to take your head.
Die!
[yells]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
You're finished!
Don't fool yourself, human.
[NARUMI]
This is checkmate.
[yelps]
Outta the way!
No!
[LUCAL] Such a weakling.
You were my target
from the beginning.
Crap!
[MITSUBA]
Tenjiryu! Protect them!
Fool.
[gasps]
[KIMIZUKI]
That's it. Die, Bloodsucker!
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
I don't think so, human.
[grunts]
Now, Shusaku!
Hurry up and do it!
Akahebi. Apprehend
this vampire scum.
[grunting]
Nice. Good work, team.
This is it!
[NARUMI, YUICHIRO grunt]
Overestimating
yourselves as usual.
Cover his escape!
We can't let him join up
with the other nobles.
Everyone, maintain
the formation.
Stick to our strategy and
we'll take him as a unit.
[LUCAL]
Interesting.
You lot must be the
humans that Krul Tepes
is so annoyed by lately.
You don't seem so tough.
We attack together.
[KIMIZUKI]
Hold up.
We can't keep this formation
and stop him from escaping.
We need to lure him in
close enough to surround him.
[NARUMI] That sounds a lot
easier than it actually is.
Unless you've got a plan.
[NARUMI]
What the hell are you doing?
Please, you can trust
them to handle this.
Tch.
[KIMIZUKI]
Hey, ugly bloodsucker.
You bastards can
reattach your arms,
but can you grow
a brand new one?
Why don't we find out?
You're making a mistake.
Human. You don't want
to make me angry.
It's your dominant arm, right?
Well, if you want it,
you better start begging.
I'll kill you.
Huh? What'd you just say?
That a fancy vampire noble
can't beat a couple of humans?
[LUCAL] Insufferable, livestock.
I'll kill every one of you.
Look sharp. This is it!
[yells]
Die!
[YUICHIRO] The only one
dying today... is you!
[yells]
[SHINOA]
Are you okay?
[YUICHIRO laughs]
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Damn... measly...
pathetic humans.
Yayoi! Finish him!
Right!
[yells]
I refuse to be
killed by livestock.
Yayoi!
You did it, Yu. Nice job!
Hey, don't forget
I provoked him.
Yeah, you're really
good at annoying people.
[YOICHI]
Yu!
[YUICHIRO] Hey, Yoichi!
Thanks for the backup.
We couldn't have
done it without you.
[laughs] Shinya taught me how
to be a much better sniper.
This proves it.
Working together, we really
can destroy the nobles.
[gasps] I wonder if the
other squads are doing okay.
[YUICHIRO]
Yeah.
[clanging]
[yells]
[MEL groans]
Don't think this means
you've beaten us.
We will destroy you!
Shut up. Die.
[pants]
Damn. That was too close.
[SAYURI]
Lieutenant Colonel!
Everything's fine.
This went just as planned.
Really? Because we almost
just got our butts handed to us.
Even though we're
the strongest team,
you should've given
us some backup.
Think about it, if we
struggled this much,
then it was definitely
the right move to increase
the manpower for
all the other teams.
Yeah, but none of
that really matters
if our commander gets killed.
And That's why I left
Shinya above ground.
If I die in battle, then
he'll step forward to lead.
[KUSUNOKI]
Lieu-Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
[KUSUNOKI grunts]
Kusunoki! What happened to you?
[grunts]
[panting]
[GUREN] Kusunoki, I'm afraid
you're not going to make it.
Please, report for your
comrades while you can.
What happened?
Sir. I'm sorry, but we
failed to kill our target.
Our 45-member squad...
They've been wiped out.
The vampires want you
to go to city hall.
They asked for you
specifically. You have to--
Why should I obey them?
They killed 19 of our men.
But the rest are
being held hostage.
[GUREN gasps]
They're all still alive.
Please forgive us--
It's all right,
it wasn't your fault.
This was my mission,
so the blame's on me.
You can relax now. Goshi.
[NORITO]
I'm already on it.
He'll sleep now.
Lieutenant Colonel, sir.
It's been such an honor
to fight for you.
To serve. Thank you.
[GUREN]
Rest.
You can watch us
defeat these bastards
from heaven, you poor idiot.
Let me be the first to say it.
This is clearly
some kind of trap.
We'd be fools to go.
That said. We're still
going, aren't we?
[GUREN] We'll join with
Narumi and Hiragi's squad.
Our target is the
Thirteenth Progenitor.
His name is Crowley Eusford.
[CROWLEY humming]
[YUICHIRO] Next time,
on Seraph of the End:
"Sword of Justice."