This human may have been
scared for her life,
but we can't take
her word alone.
Let me borrow five soldiers and
I'll go see what's happening
at city hall, just in case.
That's not a bad idea.
We'll regroup when you're done.
[MIKAELA]
That story protected Yu.
Maybe you were his comrade.
No.
You probably just used him,
like all the others do.
[MIKAELA]
Okay, follow me.
Let's see what's
going on at city hall.
I'm coming, old friend.
[gasps]
Is there something wrong?
[YUICHIRO]
Uh-- No.
It's just getting
really cloudy.
It's the perfect weather
to launch an attack.
Yeah. Let's get on with it.
[GUREN]
Hm...
[GUREN] Well, the
vampires are definitely
planning to ambush us.
I'll have to reconsider
what we should do next.
[YUICHIRO]
What are you talking about?
I mean,
we're gonna go and
rescue them, aren't we?
So you're suggesting
we walk head-on
into something we
know is a trap?
Yeah! If we have to.
[GUREN]
Everyone shut up.
[GUREN] Okay. We'll snipe
and see how they react.
Just to test the waters.
There are three targets
inside, powerful nobles
named Crowley Eusford,
Chess Belle, and Horn Skuld.
If it looks like our
enemies are too strong
for us to defeat,
we'll leave the hostages.
What? Give up?
There's no way I'm leaving
them hanging there like that.
Hey. You've gotta calm down.
Lieutenant Colonel.
What do you believe
is our top priority
at this point in the mission?
We can't afford to
lose any more troops,
especially elites like you.
That makes freeing the
hostages a secondary concern.
Moving forward, I'm
gonna need all of you.
What you're saying is...
this isn't over.
We have to survive because
there's another mission
waiting after this one, right?
Well, that's one
way to look at it.
We need to keep the
vampires in Nagoya.
Doing so let's our main unit
in Shibuya move undetected.
That's one of the primary
reasons we're here.
Wait, so the Shibuya team
is on the move right now?
Yeah. If things are
going as planned,
they should be on
their way to Shinjuku.
So basically, what
he's saying is that
this whole attack on Nagoya
was nothing but a decoy.
Not exactly, the
extermination of the nobles
will have a huge
impact on the war.
But from now on, our mission
is to keep the enemy
distracted as long as we
possibly can. Which is why...
...we're gonna see
how they react
to a little expert sniping.
If they attack
in force, we'll run.
But if we see an opening,
we'll try to save
all of the hostages.
Best-case scenario,
we'll kill the nobles, too.
Now you're dreaming.
Things never go that well.
Why are you always
such a pessimist?
C'mon, Guren, I'm just
telling it like it is.
Don't worry, I'm still
gonna kill these guys.
Pick a sniping perch, Yoichi.
Let's show everyone
what you've learned.
Right!
Look alive and
get into position.
Be ready for a
swift counterattack.
[KAGIYAMA]
Roger that!
We're prepared. Right?
Yeah!
Okay. I've got the fourth floor.
Focus your attention on the
windows in the next level up.
Got it!
[gasps] Hey. I've got
a visual on a vampire.
It's a noble! His back's to me.
I don't think he's
noticed us, yet.
Then take the damn shot! Now!
Fly true for me, Gekkouin!
[CROWLEY]
Hm?
What is this thing? How strange.
Sir. I failed to hit my target.
Ordinarily, even a
noble wouldn't have
been able to dodge a shot
like that. Which means...
...that this guy must be an
extremely powerful vampire.
It's no wonder nine
of our strongest teams
couldn't handle him.
We don't stand a chance.
He's right.
I recognize this guy,
we've faced him before.
[YUICHIRO]
Huh?
He's the vampire we fought when
we were headed to Shinjuku.
And his comrades are with him.
[gasps]
Hey. Gimme that!
Are you okay, Lord Crowley?
What was that weird thing?
Some kind of exploding bird?
It would appear that
we have some visitors.
[gasps] Yoichi's right!
That guy is big trouble!
He's, like, insanely strong.
I see.
Then I highly doubt we could
beat him by force alone.
So then... what?
[SHINYA]
We've got two choices.
We can shoot our comrades now,
before they're tortured and then
get the hell out of this town.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
You can't be serious.
[SHINOA]
Hey, don't freak out yet.
That's one way, but
what's the other option?
We somehow manage to
split up the nobles,
then save the
hostages, and retreat.
Naturally, that plan's
more dangerous.
I doubt we'd all survive.
We're not leaving our
comrades behind, right?
Guren?
I think...
...the smartest move
is to kill the hostages
and run.
They didn't attack us after
Yoichi's failed shot,
so we're not important to them.
We should retreat while
we're still able to.
You bastard! Don't be stupid!
You're the one
who's acting stupid.
[gasps]
I've got close friends
in that group of hostages.
It's killing me to even think
of leaving them behind.
But you don't see me making
a scene like a spoiled brat.
[SHINOA]
But, Lieutenant Colonel.
This is still a decoy
mission, isn't it?
If we leave the nobles alone,
aren't we putting the
Shibuya unit at risk?
[GUREN]
Yes.
Well, in that case--
Yeah, I know.
There's no way around it,
we have to attack.
We'll put on a big
show so they think
we're the main unit.
I'm not against killing
the bloodsuckers.
But I don't see how we stand a
chance with them waiting around
for us like this.
If they start to overwhelm
us, we'll retreat.
Come on. We should
move locations.
[HORN]
How odd. There's no second wave.
We could have some fun and
go hunt them down ourselves.
I would bet that's exactly
what our enemies are hoping for.
We'll be patient and
let them come to us.
They must've realized
that they didn't
stand a chance against us after
their first attack failed.
Maybe they just got
scared and ran away.
Humans have a bad habit
of making stupid decisions.
Especially when the smart choice
is against their orders.
Huh? Wait, what do
you mean, Lord Crowley?
They've been commanded
to destroy us,
so there's little chance
they're going to back out now.
They're loyal, even in
the face of certain death.
[CROWLEY]
Or there's something else.
It's possible they
have a hidden agenda.
Ferid's going to want
to know everything
about this attack.
We should gather as
much intel as possible.
I don't like Lord Ferid--
he's always trying to
seem so mysterious.
It's annoying.
You know, Chess, for once,
I actually agree with you.
He can be a little much.
But you have to admit,
when he's around,
there's never a dull moment.
All right, ladies, here's
our new plan of attack.
We capture the commander,
since he's the one who'll
have the most info. Got it?
--[CHESS] Okay!
--[HORN] Yes.
[GUREN] Pay attention.
Here's the new plan.
Shinya and the rest
of my team will attack
Crowley Eusford
and his comrades.
Shinoa and Narumi's teams
will attempt to rescue
the hostages while
we're fighting.
Do you think you'll be
all right with just you guys?
Our basic strategy will
be to strike and run away.
We should be able to
hold them off for a bit.
That's only gonna
give you five minutes
to rescue all the
hostages you can.
After that, we have to retreat
and join the other teams
at the Nagoya Airport at once.
Where are we going after
we get to the airport?
There should be a
transport helicopter
waiting for us there,
along with new directives.
We'll follow those orders.
We attack in seven minutes.
Everyone, take your positions.
[SQUAD MEMBERS]
Yes, sir!
[GUREN]
How does it look, Shinya?
Our enemies aren't
making any moves.
But then, they're most
likely waiting on us.
Who knows, what's
inside, though?
We're walking into
this partially blind.
Lieutenant Colonel, are we
really attacking them first?
Yeah. With Goshi's
Illusionary spell,
he can make it look like 200 men
are fighting alongside of us.
Isn't that right?
Sure, but there's one
big problem with your plan.
I'd have to get dangerously
close to our enemies.
Then why are you
still standing here?
Wha--?
[laughs] Sounds like Goshi's
our first casualty.
[NORITO] Geez, thanks for
the vote of confidence.
Should we do this together?
No.
If we're going to free
as many of them as we can
in five minutes...
[NARUMI]
...then we should go separately.
Okay. Good luck to you.
[SHINOA]
Thanks.
Oh, yeah. And one
more thing, newbs.
Ah.
Don't you dare die.
Same goes for you guys.
Oh, I'm not concerned
about my squad
surviving this.
Not when they've got an
incredible team leader like me.
[NARUMI]
That all. Let's move.
We've got comrades to save.
[KAGIYAMA, RIKA, IWASAKI, YAYOI]
Roger that!
We should move to
our positions, too.
Yeah.
All right. There's no
use putting this off.
If you have any last words,
now's your chance.
We're ready.
You can count on us.
[SHINOA] Okay, everyone,
let's synchronize our clocks.
Please set an alarm
for exactly five minutes.
When it goes off,
we have to retreat,
no matter what's
happening at the time.
Do you understand?
This is an order.
When our time is up,
we leave the battlefield,
no matter how many
people we've saved.
That's the only rule
for this mission.
It can't be broken.
That means, even if we have
to leave someone behind,
we retreat.
But--
No buts, Yu.
I'm the team leader here.
We can all make it out of this.
But disobeying puts
us all at risk.
So please. Please
follow my orders.
Be a good soldier.
[YUICHIRO]
I will.
It's a simple job.
All we have to do
is save everyone.
I don't think you get how
hard this is going to be.
No.
I think this is gonna work out.
Our teamwork has gotten
a lot better, too.
And, on top of that,
we've all become
really good friends.
That might be an exaggeration.
Hey. Why are you so mean?
[KIMIZUKI laughs]
I'm just kidding.
[rumbling]
[ALL gasp]
It's time to move out!
Yeah!
[GUREN grunts]
[MITO grunts]
[VAMPIRE D groans]
[GUREN grunts]
Lieutenant Colonel,
what are you doing here?
They're too powerful!
You've gotta get out of here,
just go on without us.
[VAMPIRE B]
Go! Get them!
[VAMPIRE C]
Damned livestock!
All right! Do it, Goshi!
Behold, the Demon
Army's best men.
Let's do this!
Attack!
[VAMPIRE E grunts] Don't let
them into the building!
[RIKA yells]
[KAGIYAMA yells]
[NARUMI yells]
Are they just gonna
leave us all hanging here?
Are you okay?
Narumi? What's going on?
Kagiyama. Yayoi. Rika.
Get the other members
of Kato's team free!
Shusaku, you're coming with me.
[YUICHIRO yells]
There we go.
Things are finally
getting interesting.
Ah... I've seen
that face before.
You must be leading
this hopeless assault.
I'm here to destroy
you, bloodsucker!
Looks like you're pretty strong.
But that's not enough.
[CROWLEY]
What about you, Commander?
[SHINYA] Rookie mistake.
Not watching your back.
Well, I guess
this is checkmate.
[GUREN grunts]
[SHINYA, GUREN grunt]
[SAYURI, SHIGURE]
Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
[NORITO]
Leave it to them.
If we step in and try to
help out, we'll only end up
getting in the way.
We have to!
I've got a better idea.
What are your orders?
Continue the mission as planned.
Move fast and save as many
of the troops as you can.
Shinoa, should we
try and help them?
Are we just gonna let Guren die?
Let's get up there and
take out some nobles!
Not a bad idea.
We might be able to launch
some kind of pincer attack.
Yeah, Shinoa. Let's do it!
Okay. We've got three minutes.
Plenty of time to save
the day. Let's go!
I'll come up with
a plan on the way.
Please promise that
you'll do as I say.
[SHINYA, GUREN panting]
Ugh. That guy's
gonna be a problem.
He's on a totally different
level than the other nobles.
I'm afraid this
might be it for us.
No way. Things are
all going as I planned.
Who are you trying
to kid, Guren?
At least we did a solid job
of getting their attention.
You and I make pretty
good bait. You done resting?
'Cause I'd kinda
like to escape, now.
[CROWLEY] You can't leave,
the fun's just getting started.
It'd be a shame for you two
to miss the main event.
I insist you stay,
I can't allow you
to disappoint Lord Crowley.
Why can't we just
start the show already?
I'm feeling thirsty.
I don't wanna be rude.
Then I guess we
have to stay here
and keep the three
of them entertained.
[YUICHIRO]
Why are you going that way?
Guren and Shinya are
on the fourth floor!
Just stay quiet
and follow my lead!
You heard her.
[GUREN yells]
[GUREN grunting]
[SHINYA]
Stop moving so much!
[yelps]
Lord Crowley. Shall we
join this dance?
Don't worry.
I can handle these
two on my own.
You shouldn't take
your eyes off of me!
[CROWLEY] Mm. You're finally
starting to put up a real fight.
[GUREN grunting]
Mahiru-no-yo!
Now!
[gasps, groans]
This is going to get boring
if you keep repeating
that same move.
[CROWLEY] Oh. It appears
that they've escaped.
So how badly are
you wounded, Shinya?
Could be worse.
I could've broken all my bones.
If you're strong enough to joke,
then walk on your own.
You're not getting
rid of me that easily.
This way, I can hold
them off behind us.
Hey. Why are you running away?
To be honest, I've never
really liked running.
[SHINYA] You could
always stop chasing us!
You guys attacked us first,
and now you don't want
us coming after you?
I'm always amazed at how
selfish humans can be.
[GUREN]
Are they coming?
No.
Maybe I managed to
scare the bastards off
with that last shot.
Shinya!
[yells]
[groans]
Guren!
Oops, I forgot I'm not
supposed to kill you.
At least, not until after you've
answered all of my questions.
Dammit!
I'm already dead, Shinya!
You need to take command and
finish the mission without me!
[gasps]
Go!
That's an order, Shinya.
You should listen
to your commander,
before I decide I need
two subjects for intel.
[yells]
[YUICHIRO] Next time,
on Seraph of the End:
"Demon's Lullaby."