[YUICHIRO gasps]
Guren. You're all right!
Let's go!
Good. You're here.
I was hoping that you would be.
[gasps]
[MIKAELA]
This is what happens
when you put your
trust in humans.
Out of the way, vampire!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
Why're they fighting Guren?
He's strong.
What's the matter?
You put up a much better
fight in Shinjuku.
[MIKAELA]
He's like a different person.
[MIKAELA grunts, groans]
[YUICHIRO groans]
[KURETO]
That's enough!
Let's begin.
Drink the blood of
a human, a demon,
and a progenitor.
Hey, Guren! What's wrong?
Why're you fighting us?
What is all this?!
The Seraph of the End.
[gasps]
[VAMPIRE A, TROOPER A groan]
[ALL gasp]
[VAMPIRE B, TROOPER B groan]
[VAMPIRE C, TROOPER C groan]
[gasps]
It's coming. See it?
Our punishment for
breaking their taboos.
It's heaven's judgment.
We must seize control
of that power!
That light. What is it?
It's... an angel.
Mirai!
[SHINOA, YOICHI, MITSUBA gasp]
You humans are blasphemers.
You've brought this
on yourselves.
[horn blows]
[VAMPIRES, TROOPERS
gasping, yelping]
[FERID]
Well, well.
That's quite
impressive. Let's watch.
Hurry, capture the angel.
No, you monsters!
That's my sister!
What have you done to her?!
[KIMIZUKI groans]
Enough, kid.
Time to stand down.
[KIMIZUKI groans]
[YUICHIRO]
Have you gone insane?!
[yells]
[YUICHIRO grunting]
[grunts]
[grunts] Now, Yu! Attack!
[yells]
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you've
gone soft on me.
This isn't right, Guren.
This isn't you!
Did they brainwash
you or something?
You trained us.
You taught us to never turn
our backs on our comrades.
[YUICHIRO] Stop smiling
and say something already.
You know who we are.
Please. We're still
your family, Guren!
You're crying?
[groans]
Yu, no!
Is he okay?
[GUREN cackles]
[GUREN laughing]
Mirai!
There it is.
Blowing the Fifth
Trumpet summoned
the demon of
destruction, Abaddon.
[KURETO] Our enchantments
and curses worked.
We've succeeded in controlling
the Seraph of the End.
[ABADDON roars]
Aoi. You know what to do next.
Sir!
[DEMON A roars]
[VAMPIRES gasp]
[TROOPER F yelps]
[screams]
[SHINOA]
Everyone. We need to retreat.
C'mon. Let's go, Kimizuki.
Get off of me. I'm not
leaving Mirai behind!
No, wait! Don't do it!
Go ahead and escape.
This battle is personal now.
[KIMIZUKI groans]
Kimizuki!
[SHINOA]
Mika.
This is the end of it all.
There's no future
for any of us now.
Move!
[panting]
[YUICHIRO]
Where is he?
[MIKAELA]
Yu! Good, you're awake.
We're gonna find a safe place.
Somewhere they won't
be able to reach.
I have to help Guren.
He was crying earlier.
It's still him.
Are you kidding me?
Forget about Guren.
And Shinoa. Where
are my comrades?
I think they're staying
behind to fight.
We have to go back and help,
I can't leave them to die.
Mika. They're my family.
No, I'm your only family, Yu.
Listen to me!
There's Guren, and Shinoa,
Yoichi, Kimizuki,
Mitsuba, and you!
You're all people I have
to protect. Understand?
[DEMON C growling]
[gasps]
[DEMON C roars]
[MIKAELA grunts]
[gasps]
You're hurt.
Oh, crap! Quick, you
have to drink my blood!
No. That won't help me.
There's something about this
demon that affects my healing.
[YUICHIRO]
Then what can I do?
You can save yourself.
Look at that thing.
There's no way we
can take it down.
Your family is in
danger. Go save them.
Shut up!
It's not like I can
leave you here to die!
Not now. I just got
you back, Mika.
I won't lose you again!
Just go, you idiot. Hurry.
Or else you'll lose
your whole family again.
[YUICHIRO] All I need to do is
kill that big monster, right?
That'll save everyone.
Including you.
You've always had
the worst ideas.
Use your damn head for once.
That thing's huge.
No one can kill it.
Maybe not. But I'll
sure as hell try.
Yu, don't!
[grunts]
You really wanna
save 'em that badly?
[YUICHIRO]
Yup.
I'm afraid my power
won't be enough.
[YUICHIRO]
I know.
Then you're really here
to betray me, huh?
You've come back for
the golden trumpet.
I told you it was bad news.
[YUICHIRO]
It's the only way.
[ASURAMARU] If you use
that thing, you'll lose
your humanity. You'll
become something else.
Your family might not
recognize you anymore.
[YUICHIRO]
I don't care.
Anything to keep them all safe.
[inhales]
[grunting]
[gasps]
Uh-- Queen Krul.
This is bad.
They've stopped attacking us.
What's going on?
Maybe that thing's to blame.
Probably a safe bet.
It's Yu!
Yu?
My sister.
Please! You gotta help her!
[yelling]
[YUICHIRO screaming]
[KURETO]
What is that tower of flame?
[AOI]
Kureto, sir.
We're getting new
Seraph of the End readings.
They're coming from the fire.
[KURETO gasps]
Well, what does that mean?
I'm not sure.
But, sir, if we fail
to investigate it--
Then we might watch the
world end again, right?
This must be heaven's wrath.
But even if God
himself is our enemy,
humankind will defeat
him here! Aoi!
[AOI]
Sir.
Destroy it.
Sir! All units,
move in! Strike hard!
Destroy that Seraph!
You, too, Abaddon!
[ABADDON growls]
[ABADDON roars]
[YUICHIRO] The time has
come to end this world.
[YUICHIRO] I'll judge every
human who's broken our taboos,
and turn them into
pillars of salt.
What the--?
Uh-- Get outta the way!
[TROOPER I]
We don't have time!
Fire!
[roars]
[gasps] That's the
Second Trumpet.
Lieutenant General Kureto,
it's the King of Salt!
[KURETO]
I don't care. Kill him!
[roars]
[ABADDON roars]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[YUICHIRO grunting]
[yells]
No!
How?
[SHINOA]
Yu.
It's over.
The lust for power that drives
you humans ends today.
All before me will
become pillars of salt.
[KURETO panting]
[KURETO grunts, yells]
[yells]
[KURETO groans]
All units, target
Yuichiro Hyakuya.
Capture him!
[TROOPERS]
Sir!
[GUREN]
Whoa, interesting.
You've gone crazy.
Welcome to the club.
Humans aren't worthy
of this world.
[ASURAMARU] You're losing
sight of your goals, Yu.
I said I'd help you
get your vengeance.
Unfortunately, right now,
there's only one way
for me to do that.
I have to take complete control.
Not good. We have to get him!
We should go, too, Queen Krul.
Are you healed enough?
[MIKAELA]
I'll be fine.
Good. Don't let the
humans get a hold of him.
You've seen what they'll do--
[MIKAELA]
Right.
I'm not done, yet!
Really? Because I beg to differ.
[gasps]
[FERID giggles]
My queen. You've panicked.
And left your beautiful
neck wide open!
Bastard!
Queen Krul!
[KRUL]
Forget me!
Mika. Go! Now!
[inaudible]
That's better. Wow, Ferid.
You've captured
the queen. Impressive.
I guess I was a
good distraction.
You sound as though
you doubted me.
[CROWLEY]
I'm curious.
Where does that leave
us now that our leader
has been taken out
of the equation?
[FERID]
Listen, vampire brethren!
We've just discovered
that Krul Tepes
is guilty of high treason
against our kind!
She was involved in the
humans' Seraph of the End
experiment that could have
completely destroyed us.
Therefore, as the
Seventh Progenitor,
I, Ferid Bathory,
am assuming control.
Oh. So you're still alive.
I'm glad you managed to
make it out of this okay.
Narumi.
I'm short on time.
Hurry up and give him to me.
[NARUMI]
I'm sorry, Lieutenant Colonel,
but I can't follow your orders.
Not after what you've done.
What are you doing?
Take him!
Step aside.
[KURETO]
Don't let them escape!
[AOI]
Lieutenant General.
They're coming!
Always more vampires. Kill them!
[VAMPIRES, TROOPERS yelling]
[SHINYA]
What the hell's going on, Guren?
Ha...
[SHINYA] Don't laugh
at me. Explain yourself!
[coughs] You can't be
mad at me, Shinya.
I'm just doing what we
dreamed about way back
when we were kids.
What're you talking about?
I'm changing the whole world.
It's gonna be a different place.
One where second-tier
people like you and me
can actually move up.
Have you lost your mind?
You killed our own men!
Your betrayal destroyed us.
Our comrades are dead!
[SHINYA]
No...
You've been possessed.
Hey. Listen to me!
You're still in there somewhere!
Shinoa, wait!
What about Kimizuki's sister,
she's still back there.
It's okay.
[YOICHI]
Are you sure?
[gasps]
Hand over Yuichiro Hyakuya
immediately, that's an order!
We no longer take
orders from you.
As of now, my team's withdrawn
from the Demon Army.
[TROOPERS grunt]
More will follow them. Hurry!
Move it. Fast as you can.
I'm not losing anymore
comrades today.
Kureto, sir.
Everything's in order.
We're ready to advance.
[GUREN] Excellent. Let's
not waste any more time.
[hellicopter blades whirring]
Now, this is where things
get really interesting.
[footsteps scuffing]
Is that the last of it?
[YOICHI]
Yeah.
Where are those two?
They'll be out in just a minute.
You're taking your time.
You're always in a
rush. That's all.
[grunts]
[MITSUBA]
Yu. Where's your demon?
Oh. Sleeping.
Don't worry about it.
Let's get going!
We'll rescue
Kimizuki's sister
and that idiot, Guren, too.
We'll get him back
to his old self.
[NARUMI] You're sure
the Lieutenant Colonel
is really in Sanguinem?
[SHINOA]
Yes. The intel I got was solid.
[YUICHIRO]
Jeez.
We ran away and now we have
to go all the way back?
What a pain.
[MIKAELA] Just don't do
anything dumb like grow wings
and try to kill us all
when we get there.
[YUICHIRO] Why would you say
something like that, Mika?
Besides, I saved the day.
[KIMIZUKI] You should bring
back the demon horns.
It was a good look for you.
[YOICHI giggles]
It's gonna be a long trip.
[SHINOA giggles]
[MITSUBA]
Yu will be fine.
I mean, there's no way
things could get any worse
than they were, right?
[MIKAELA] Did you hear
that? It's all good.
[splashing]
[MIKAELA]
Yu?
[YUICHIRO]
It's starting to rain.