[knocking]
Bring Guren to me.
[YUICHIRO]
Argh. What is the deal?
Why can't I fix it?
[KIMIZUKI] Stop going to
sleep with wet hair, idiot.
Why won't it just work
with me and lay down?
Guess it's not that bad.
[KIMIZUKI chuckles]
Right.
At least it still looks
better than yours.
[KIMIZUKI]
What'd you say?
[YUICHIRO]
Nothing.
C'mon, we're gonna be late.
[KIMIZUKI] I hope they
got breakfast waiting.
I'm starving.
Who knows with those two?
They've probably got
a whole feast ready.
[YUICHIRO]
More importantly.
Any idea what this is about?
It's kinda early for a meeting.
[KIMIZUKI] I hope there's
coffee and donuts, too.
Yeah.
Maybe they've got a
fancy breakfast planned.
[YUICHIRO]
Hey, are you guys ignoring me?
Tell me what's up!
Shinoa will explain soon enough.
Until then, focus on
taming your stupid hair.
This is ridiculous.
Why am I left in the dark?
[MITSUBA screams]
[MITSUBA, SHINOA screaming]
Hey!
What's wrong, why
are you screaming?
What the hell are you doing?
How can you be so bad at cooking
that you set an omelet on fire?
I read somewhere
that adding alcohol
to the pan makes
it taste better!
[YUICHIRO]
Is that for us?
[YOICHI]
Uh...
[MITSUBA, SHINOA gasp]
It's done. Now let's eat.
[YUICHIRO] Man, Kimizuki,
this is really good.
Where'd you learn how to cook?
Anyone with half a brain
can make an omelet.
[SHINOA] I would've made
you a great breakfast
if Mitsu hadn't been
there messing things up.
[MITSUBA]
I'm telling you,
flambéing is a
legitimate technique!
Don't worry.
I'm sure you were just having
an off day in the kitchen.
You can cook us
breakfast some other time.
Keep a fire
extinguisher on hand.
[YOICHI, YUICHIRO laugh]
So, what are we
doing here, guys?
I get the feeling that
I'm being left out.
And I thought we
weren't supposed
to keep secrets from each other.
[SHINOA] There are two
things we need to discuss.
First, that you've
been the subject of
some kind of
human experimentation.
and that you lost control
in the heat of battle
and tried to kill me.
[gasps]
[SHINOA] Second. The
lieutenant colonel...
Are we sure that Guren
is truly on our side?
What do you mean
"is he on our side?"
He's the one looking out for us.
[SHINOA] It's possible
that he's been using us
this whole time,
specifically you.
How did he manage to put such
a powerful team together
in such a short amount of time?
It could just be that
he's trying to intimidate
his superiors for some reason.
But we have to consider
that there might be
something bigger at stake.
All this stuff about
Guren is news to me.
[SHINOA]
Whatever the case.
We have to decide if we're
going to stick by Guren.
If we do, we might end up
traitors to the army.
Even if we are just
following orders.
That's why we called you here,
so we can figure all
this out together.
So basically,
you wanna discuss
the idea of abandoning
the Lieutenant Colonel.
[SHINOA]
That's one of our options, yes.
[gasps]
[VAMPIRE A sniffs]
[VAMPIRE A] It's blood.
I can smell his blood!
Blood!
[VAMPIRE A grunts]
[sighs]
[GUREN]
This is disgusting.
Kureto Hiragi.
You took your time getting here.
[GUREN] Is this a
Cursed Gear experiment?
Yes.
[KURETO] I'm trying to find an
efficient way to turn vampires
into demons whose
powers we can harness.
Unfortunately, we're not making
much in the way of progress.
Low-level trash like these
specimens are worthless.
Dispose of 'em, will ya?
You didn't bring me
here to kill vamps.
Just cut to the chase already.
[KURETO] Did you really
come here on your own?
Those were the orders
that I received.
You weren't afraid that
I was going to kill you?
[GUREN] What reason do
you have to kill me?
Because you're a cocky idiot?
[chuckles] If that were the
case, you'd've killed me sooner.
Besides, you won't get rid of
me while I'm of use to you.
[KURETO]
Hm.
You've got a point.
But that does make me wonder
how useful you really are.
And, more importantly, what
you've been working on lately.
I think it's time we talk about
this team you've put together.
Yuichiro Hyakuya.
Yoichi Saotome.
Shiho Kimizuki.
Where did these boys come from?
How did you manage
to find not one,
but three Black Demon prospects?
I got lucky.
It was pure coincidence that
these three recruits ended up--
[KURETO] I don't believe
that for a second.
All Black Demon prospects
have been subjected
to human experimentation.
Even then, the success
rate is extremely low.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm happy to have more
Black Demon users in our ranks.
Perhaps you should be
in charge of overseeing
all our Cursed Gear trials.
[GUREN] Seems like a
waste of my talents.
Is this why you had me
meet you out here?
Because, if that's it,
I'll be on my way.
One more question.
What's your reason
for assembling
these Black Demon users?
Are you trying to plan a coup?
[GUREN] If my goal was
to get rid of you,
I would cut you down
right where you stand.
[KURETO]
You wouldn't land a single blow.
[GUREN]
Wanna bet?
This brings back memories.
I didn't mean to get
you so fired up.
All in all, you're
doing a good job.
[GUREN]
Hm.
[KURETO] But, I know
your weaknesses, Guren.
Love, friendship, honor.
You never learned to set aside
your emotions in order to lead.
That's something that makes you
stronger and holds you back.
And it's why I know
I can trust you.
You'll never become
a threat. Will you?
I don't think someone who cares
so much about his comrades
is capable of betraying them.
So, this is the part
where you play
the hostage card again, right?
Who'll it be this time?
What is it that you
want from me, Kureto?
[KURETO]
Don't sound so upset.
Tell me, Guren.
What do you think the
future holds for all of us?
What's the point in living
in a world like this one,
fighting extinction?
I'm sure you've
asked yourself that.
Did you call me here
so you could complain?
[KURETO] I'm just curious
to know what kind of faith
you have in humanity.
This forsaken world is almost
completely devoid of hope.
And yet, you continue to
build your military power.
I want to know your intentions.
[GUREN]
We need more power because
the world is this way. Right?
That may be true.
But no matter how strong
we are, we're as good as dead
if we don't have a clear
vision for the future.
Everything we do must
be for the greater good.
You agree?
Yeah. The greater good.
[KURETO] I'm going to
recover the world, Guren.
Since the vampires destroyed
our communications network,
we haven't been
able to make contact
with anyone outside of Japan.
But there must be other human
organizations that survived.
[GUREN] I'm sure.
So your goal is what, then?
To search for humans abroad?
Try and reestablish
communications with them?
[KURETO] No. My next step is
to destroy every last vampire
in this country. After that,
I will systematically crush
all of the remaining human
organizations that are left.
Putting the world under
The Demon Army's control.
I didn't know you
were such a dreamer.
[KURETO]
Sounds like fun, right?
[GUREN]
Heh.
[KURETO] As my opening move,
I'm going to thin their ranks
and exterminate all
of the vampire nobles.
[GUREN] You seem pretty
sure of yourself.
[KURETO]
I am.
There are currently
25 nobles in Japan.
And I know where each of them
is located at this very moment.
[GUREN] If you're wrong,
the army's finished.
Then my only option
is to win. Right?
[GUREN]
How do you know your intel
isn't some kind of setup?
I've considered that.
But we don't have time
to investigate further.
What's got you in such a hurry?
[KURETO] In one month,
the vampires are launching
a full attack on Tokyo.
[wings flap]
[KURETO]
If we continue as we are now,
humanity will be
crushed in an instant.
But if we're proactive--
[GUREN]
We can gain the upper hand.
Correct. I want you
to take your team
and 100 of the Moon Demon
Company soldiers to Nagoya.
There, you'll find a base that
houses ten vampire nobles.
Kill all of them and
claim the facility.
If we attack, they'll realize
what you're planning.
[KURETO]
Perhaps.
But it'll be worth it if we
can distract them for a while.
In the meantime, we'll
prepare for the final battle.
[GUREN chuckles]
So, we're disposable?
[KURETO] This is a very
important mission, Guren.
I've come to you because I
need someone that I can trust.
If you can accomplish this task,
I can take over from there.
So what you're actually
saying is that you don't
wanna tell me your
whole plan right now.
And I thought you trusted me.
Your directive.
Go. That's an order,
not a request.
Just wait. I'm gonna
show you a world
where it's the vampires who
serve as our livestock.
[gasps]
Don't be fooled, my love.
It's my orders that you're
supposed to be following.
Remember.
I'm the only one who can
make your wish come true.
Shut up.
--[door creaks]
--[gasps]
Lemme guess, you've spotted
some girl taking
off her clothes.
Ugh. How come
you always assume
I'm doing something perverted?
Why else would you
be staring so intently?
[YUICHIRO]
Is it true what you said?
Did I really almost
kill you, Shinoa?
[SHINOA] Well, yeah, but the
nice thing is you didn't
actually go through
with it in the end.
Whatever your intentions were,
I'm still alive and kicking.
Try not to beat
yourself up about it.
We'll figure out
what's going on.
But normally,
I would spend the entire
fight protecting you.
Oh. I'm glad to hear
you've finally figured out
your role in our team's
formation. You and Kimizuki.
You guys are like the linemen,
the strong knights
of Shinoa's Squad.
Your job is to
protect the queen,
and lay down your lives
to ensure my safety.
Hey, Yu?
[YUICHIRO] Did Guren plan
on me losing control?
Was that what he was
going for the whole time?
[SHINOA]
Probably.
I understand if you haven't
made up your mind yet.
I was looking to the West.
[SHINOA]
Uh?
Hey.
The next time we're up
against those bloodsuckers,
will you promise
to stay by my side?
What's gotten into
you all of a sudden?
Uh... Well, if I lose control,
you can stop me by--
[SHINOA] We'll make sure
nothing bad happens to you.
[YUICHIRO]
Thanks, Shinoa.
I'm just doing my job
as the squad's leader.
Don't worry. We're
in this together.
I know that. All right.
We should go back.
The others are probably mad
that I've taken so long up here.
[YUICHIRO] I've decided I'm
going to stick with Guren.
[MITSUBA]
Huh?
Family.
That's what he's called our
team from the very beginning.
Mitsuba. Yoichi.
Kimizuki. Shinoa.
You're my new
brothers and sisters.
[YOICHI, SHINOA,
KIMIZUKI, MITSUBA] Huh?
[YUICHIRO]
I really believe that.
You're all important
to me, but...
I can't forget
about Mika, either.
He's also an important
member of my family.
My parents abandoned me,
so I never really
learned how families are
supposed to work, but...
I'm pretty sure you
don't turn your back
on your brother just because
he kept a secret from you.
Guren said he'd help
me get Mika back
and complete my family.
I'm going to trust his word.
I know I have no right
to get you all
involved in personal
issues like this.
If you want me to leave--
[KIMIZUKI]
I've heard enough.
[gasps]
You were right when you said
you can't turn your
back on family. Agreed?
Yeah!
Well, It sounds like we've
reached a conclusion.
We defend our family.
In this messed-up world,
most people are so busy
trying to survive,
that they forget
to look out for each other.
But Shinoa's Squad is different.
You can probably thank
my strong leadership.
[KIMIZUKI] Now, if we could
just do something about
our teammate's hair...
Wha-- Hey! Shut up!
[MIKAELA panting]
Mika. Oh. You're here.
I was just getting
some blood ready--
Were you really that thirsty?
There, there.
Drink your fill, my pet.
[MIKAELA gasps]
I, I'm sorry, Krul.
We all get a little ravenous
when we haven't
had enough blood.
[MIKAELA] Um. Can you
give me a little extra?
Of the serum, I mean.
Oh, I can give you
as much as you want.
[KRUL]
But, you know...
You won't last forever
on my blood alone.
The day will come when
you'll have to
drink from a human.
Wait outside for now.
I'll send for you when I'm done.
Right.
[KRUL]
Was there something else?
[MIKAELA] You were supposed
to kill Yuichiro and me.
So what are you playing
at by letting us live?
[KRUL]
You sound so serious.
Don't tell me you're worried
about my safety, Mika.
Why would you put yourself
at risk to save us?
It just doesn't make
any sense to me.
What are you planning
on doing with Yu?
And with me?
[KRUL]
Oh, Mika.
That's information I'd
rather keep to myself.
Don't mess with me!
If you're gonna
end up hurting Yu,
then I'll put a stop
to this right now.
How, exactly?
After all, you're just
my little pet, remember?
Stop it. I can't
do this anymore.
Come on. Now you're
just being dramatic.
Eventually, you'll
realize the vampires
aren't as bad as the humans.
It's for the better.
I like you and your old friend.
You expect me to believe that?
Without question.
[MIKAELA whimpers]
[KRUL sighs]
Fine.
If you're going to start
sulking, then I'll tell you why
I've kept the two of you alive.
And why I require the power
of the Seraph of
the End for myself.
[KRUL whispers]
[MIKAELA gasps]
Next month, we're attacking
the humans again.
This time we'll send in
our strongest units,
and we won't stop until
every one of them is dead.
This will be the final battle
between humans and vampires.
In order to save Yu,
you're gonna have to go
undercover and hide
from both sides of this war.
I'm giving you a secret mission.
And if you fail...
...then you'll be a
traitor to both sides,
and the whole world
will turn on you.
I understand. I'll save
Yu from the vampires.
And from the humans as well.
[knocking]
Come in.
Excuse me, sir.
[SHINOA] I thought
you'd like to know that
Yu and Kimizuki have
completed their training.
They have both
succeeded in possession.
Impressive.
Indeed.
[SHINOA] Last time we talked,
you had a question for me.
You asked if I'd fallen for Yu.
I don't remember
prying like that.
What's your answer?
I'm honestly not sure myself.
It's just, for the first time
in my life, someone needs me.
And I can't let him down
when he's counting on me.
[SHINOA] All right, then.
I'll see myself out.
Hold on. I've got a
new mission for you.
Come to the staging arena
tomorrow at 0600 hours.
[GUREN] We're going to kill
all the vampires in Nagoya.
[RENE] Looks like he
got the order, too.
We've been instructed to move
our main units to Nagoya.
We'll hit Tokyo soon after that.
Yes, I know.
[MAN 15A] Increase sensitivity
on the left side.
[MAN 15B]
Roger that.
[RESEARCHER 15A]
The preparation is complete,
Lieutenant General Kureto.
Begin.
[KURETO]
Increase the power.
Higher.
[RESEARCHER 15A]
But, sir--
If we go higher,
it's likely she'll die.
Do it.
[YUICHIRO] Next time,
on Seraph of the End:
"The Moon Demon's Orders."