[YUICHIRO]
Lend me your power, Asuramaru.
So, that's it. Now I'm
possessed, right?
True, but you're at the
lowest level of possession.
To gain more demonic power,
you'll need to cut yourself
on the blade and ask your
sword to drink your blood.
Blood?
Sounds like my sword
is some kind of vampire.
Well, there is a pretty
interesting history
between demons, devils,
and bloodsuckers.
Let's see, where to begin?
Don't. You can spare us
the lecture, Shinoa.
Let's do this.
[MITSUBA]
Hold it!
[KIMIZUKI, YUICHIRO gasp]
You're gonna try it
at the same time?
What if something goes wrong?
Your demon could
get out of control.
You remember when
Yoichi tried to kill us?
That's why we came out here,
so you can't hurt anything.
Out of control?
Huh? What did you say?
Nothing.
[YOICHI]
Hey, guys!
[MITSUBA]
What is it?
It's The Four Horsemen of John.
[YOICHI] Three of them.
No, make that five.
Crap. We need to deal with 'em.
All right, let's get
this over with, fast.
[exhales] Destroy our
enemies, Gekkouin!
Let's protect everyone.
[BOTH gasp]
Whew!
You guys, I did it!
Did you just
manifest your demon?
Since when can you do that?
Explain how that's
possible, Shinoa!
Have you been giving him
private lessons or something?
No, Yoichi's mastered
manifestation on his own.
He's always had exceptional
curse-control abilities.
He's got a surprisingly
strong relationship
with his demon.
Seriously?
Yeah.
I've been talking to my
demon before I go to sleep
and in my dreams, now I
just sorta get how to do it.
[chuckles]
[YUICHIRO]
Okay, Asuramaru. Drink my blood!
Yu, wait!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Prepare to fight!
[gasping]
[gasps, groans]
Is he okay?
What just happened?
I'm not sure.
He didn't immediately
go berserk,
so that's a big improvement.
Right now, he's more than likely
trying to make contact
with his demon.
We'll have to
stand watch over him
until he regains
full consciousness.
Don't look so worried.
We're here to look out
for our family, aren't we, boys?
[KIMIZUKI]
Hmph. Trouble as usual.
What do you mean?
It's not Yu's fault.
I'm just saying.
Yoichi and I were interrogated
and tortured by the Hiragis.
The whole reason is because
they wanted to know
more about what he did.
Yeah?
And what did you
tell them about it?
Exactly what you ordered us to.
That I didn't know what
they were talking about.
You did the right thing.
And you still think
it's smart that we don't
tell Yu he completely
lost control?
Because it kind of looks like
you're trying to manipulate
him for some reason.
But you wouldn't do that
to your teammate, right?
What if I did?
[KIMIZUKI]
I don't know.
I'd still follow orders
to keep my sister safe,
but I'd have to swallow down
vomit every time I saw you.
Hey, You can't talk
to your superior like that.
Shinoa is just
trying to protect Yu
from the people in the upper--
It's okay, Mitsu.
And what about you, Yoichi?
What do you think?
Um. Well, I...
I get why you don't wanna
tell Yu about what happened
when he lost control,
because that might
cause him to freak out, but...
[SHINOA] You want a better
explanation, don't you?
[YOICHI]
We're comrades, aren't we?
So tell us your reasoning.
You're right about that.
We should trust each other.
Keeping secrets could
drive us apart.
All right then.
Let's talk about all
of this when Yu's awake
and the training's over.
Not just about what
happened to him.
but about where we
stand as a unit, too.
[groans]
[gasps]
Hey, can I get a little
help here, you guys?
[YUICHIRO grunting, groaning]
Hold him!
Looks like it's starting.
Yeah.
I think he's finally
found his demon.
[YUICHIRO groaning]
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO'S MOTHER sobbing]
He never should have been born.
We must kill the
Seraph of the End.
[YUICHIRO'S FATHER] He's the
devil's child, not our son.
The boy is a monster.
Dad? What's wrong?
Yu, don't fight it. C'mere.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO'S FATHER] I'm gonna
send you to a better place...
...son.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO screams]
[YUICHIRO'S FATHER pants]
You should have died here
with the others.
Everyone else is dead because
you ran away like a coward.
Fall apart, Yu.
[YUICHIRO]
If you think this memory
will make me lose
control, Asuramaru...
...then you've
underestimated me.
And how much there is at stake.
I made him a promise
and I intend to keep it.
Come on, Yu. Let's protect
our family together.
Please, I'm counting on you.
I know.
I couldn't save you if
you didn't want my help.
I won't fall for any
of your demonic tricks.
[ASURAMARU]
Aw, man.
I thought I had ya
there for a second.
I know how you fight,
and this time, I was prepared.
No need to act so tough.
After all, I know
all of your secrets.
Try to tear me
down all you want.
But if Mika, Guren, or Shinoa
and the others need my help...
I'll do whatever it takes
to keep them safe.
Oh, yeah?
You're stronger than
the last time we talked.
To be honest. This new
devil-may-care attitude of yours
is sort of annoying.
What're you gonna do about it?
I'm gonna kill ya.
[ASURAMARU gasps]
What the hell are you doing?
[YUICHIRO] I didn't come here
because I want to hurt you.
[laughs] Then what do you want?
I need you, Asuramaru.
Your strength.
Will you help me save Mika?
[ASURAMARU]
I suppose I could,
but what's in it for me if I do?
If you help me,
then I'll be your friend.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO] It's tough being
alone, and difficult to feel
like you're unwanted,
or that you've been abandoned.
I know what that's like.
And you think being my friend
will change all of that?
Yeah!
[sighs]
[gasps] He's awake!
Ah... Hey.
Hope I didn't cause you guys
to worry or anything.
You're back.
I mean, it's really you, right?
Jeez, you looked like
you were gonna die on us
there for a minute.
Oh, sorry, I didn't know what
was going on with my body.
So, were you
actually successful?
Then I guess it was worth it.
Am I the only one who's
exhausted from all this?
Let's just wait and do
Kimizuki's training later.
Huh? No way, we're
doing it right now!
It's getting late, and
honestly, I'm kinda hungry.
No one cares if you're hungry!
[laughing]
Well, It took you long enough.
So, how was it, are you okay?
I guess you were
able to fight off
the psychological attacks.
Yeah. But I knew I wasn't alone.
Not now that I have you guys.
Huh?
Never mind. It's nothing.
[FERID] Well, to put it simply,
the humans are being blinded
by their desire to defeat
us and are partaking
in forbidden experimentation
they don't fully understand.
It's quite unsettling.
If you'll just
watch this recording,
you'll understand
exactly what I mean.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO screaming]
[NOBLE 14A]
What was that thing?
[NOBLE 14B]
This could be disastrous for us.
There, you see? The humans
have finally succeeded.
They have managed to weaponize
the Seraph of the End.
I don't have to tell you what
a serious problem this is.
[FOURTH PROGENITOR 14A]
But Queen Krul put an end
to the humans'
experiments when she
exterminated the Hyakuya Sect.
[KRUL]
That's right.
This program was
dismantled eight years ago.
I killed the researchers
and every child
carrying even a trace
of the Seraph of the End
with my own hands.
[gasps]
Oh-ho. You're sure you killed
all the test subjects?
That's what I said, isn't it?
[LEST]
But if that's true,
then how has their
research come so far?
There were no
organizations anywhere close
to this sort of success
other than the Hyakuya Sect.
Krul, I'm afraid that if
your leadership failed,
this could end up a major
liability for the other--
Hold your tongue, Lest Kerr,
or I'll have it ripped
out and hung on my wall.
Oh, have I touched a nerve?
Perhaps this is
too much for you.
Maybe it's time I stepped
in as the new ruler of Japan.
Don't push me, little brat.
[chuckles] You're only 200
years older than me, Krul.
Besides, we both know that--
[FERID] Oh, come now.
Please don't argue.
Let's remember why we're here.
How do we respond to the humans'
successful weaponization?
What would you ask
us to do, Queen Krul?
This doesn't change
our basic strategy.
We'll send our strongest units
in to destroy the Demon Army.
Looking forward to your success.
[NOBLE 14A]
By the way, Ferid Bathory.
Who is the young boy
standing behind you?
[KRUL] What the hell do
you think you're doing?
[KRUL] How dare you
spring that video on me?
And bringing Mikaela
along as well.
Conspire against me
and I'll end you.
So scary. But you forget
that you can't kill me.
After all, if I died.
think about what might happen.
All the information I've
collected on you could
leak to the Progenitor Council.
[FERID] Besides, if they
found out I let Yu escape,
I'd be punished, too.
Hm. Dear. With all
these shared secrets,
it would appear that you
and I have no other choice
but to be allies. Hooray.
You might even say,
we belong together.
Ah, who am I kidding?
[laughing] What a fun game
this is turning out to be.
[growls]
Krul...
[KIMIZUKI groaning]
[YOICHI]
Kimizuki! You have to fight it!
Talk to me, Shinoa!
Was I this messed up?
No, we might be in for
a little trouble with him.
I think the demon
might be trying
to take over his body.
What?
What are we supposed
to do if it does?
[SHINOA] Yu! I need you to be
ready to attack, just in case.
[KIMIZUKI panting, screaming]
[giggles]
[growls] Die!
So desperate.
I'll make you yield
to me, Kiseki-o.
If that's the goal, you're
gonna have to try harder.
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
[KIMIZUKI groans]
[sputters]
Poor little weakling,
your body is all mine.
Now, to break you.
[gasps]
[knocking]
Big brother?
[KIMIZUKI]
Don't worry.
Ah.
[BLACK-HAIRED BOY]
So. How's Mirai doing?
[KIMIZUKI] Not good. I think
she's getting worse.
[BLACK-HAIRED BOY]
Look, we've got a problem.
Food's running out.
We won't last three days
with what we've got.
[KIMIZUKI]
What are we gonna do?
[BLACK-HAIRED BOY]
Leave.
Tomorrow morning
at the crack of dawn.
Can't we wait longer?
I'll have to figure out
how to move Mirai.
You have to leave her behind.
She'd just slow us down.
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, calm down!
We have to be logical.
Your sister is way beyond
our help. It sucks.
But we've gotta look out for
the little ones who've survived,
not to mention our own lives.
It's a crappy world, Kimizuki.
And we can't save everyone.
[BLACK-HAIRED BOY]
You take care of her.
It's what's best for all of us.
You monster. How could you--
[BLACK-HAIRED BOY]
Mirai's the one who came up
with the idea.
[gasps]
She said she doesn't
wanna get in your way.
But she can't take her own
life because she's too weak.
Come on.
[BLACK-HAIRED BOY]
If you can't man up and follow
through with this,
then I'll do it myself.
Ah!
[groans]
[BLACK-HAIRED BOY]
Hold on!
[KIMIZUKI panting]
Wait! Kimizuki!
[panting]
[knocking]
[BROWN-HAIRED BOY]
Open the door!
Let us in! Crap.
[BLACK-HAIRED BOY]
This way.
We'll climb over the balcony.
[gasps]
Why do you have a knife?
Dammit!
[MIRAI]
Hey, Big Brother?
I don't wanna see you
wasting away just because
I'm too sick to get out of bed.
Shut up, Mirai.
Brother. Please kill me.
[KIMIZUKI gasps]
Do it now and it'll all
be over before you know it,
you'll be free to live your
life however you want.
[KIMIZUKI]
Shut up! Just, shut up!
How can you say
things like that?
[KISEKI-O]
I can hear your thoughts.
Just now you were wondering
what it'd be like
to be rid of me.
[gasps]
[KISEKI-O]
"I'm sick of taking care of her.
She's holding me back.
I'm just a kid, too.
I shouldn't have to do this.
If I could just kill
my sister, right here..."
I didn't.
[KISEKI-O] "Wouldn't it be
easier if I ran away
from this burden--
Be quiet.
[KISEKI-O] That's what you
just thought, Big Brother!
Shut up!
[KISEKI-O]
I'm not wrong, Shiho Kimizuki.
Follow your instincts
and free yourself.
[MIRAI]
Thank you, Big Brother,
for finally putting me
out of my misery.
[KIMIZUKI]
I'm so sorry, Mirai.
[MIRAI]
You don't need to apologize.
This was all my idea,
remember? It's what I wanted.
[KIMIZUKI] Before I do this,
can I ask you something?
I recently met this
really stupid guy
who I absolutely hate.
Now I can't get seem
to get away from him,
even though he might be the most
annoying person on the planet.
Anyway, he says
he'll risk his life
to protect the people
he cares about.
Even if his "family" isn't
related to him by blood.
That's crazy, right?
I mean, The guy's a moron.
Indeed.
[KIMIZUKI]
I know.
And it's driving me
crazy that he might be
a better person than me.
He'd give up so much for
people he's not related to.
So how could I possibly
kill my own sister?
I'd rather...
[gasps] No, don't!
What are you--?
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
[KISEKI-O gasps]
It's over now.
Well, I'll be damned.
Come. Kiseki-o.
[YUICHIRO]
Huh?
[SHINOA]
He's possessed!
Whoa, relax, everyone.
There's nothing to worry about.
[ALL gasp]
It really is him!
[growls] Hey!
If that's true, then how
come you attacked me?
[KIMIZUKI] 'Cause we need to
settle this once and for all
and see who's
stronger, you or me.
You outsmarted your demon.
Yep, and now I can
use possession
to beat your ass at any time.
[YUICHIRO]
Oh, yeah? So, you wanna...
[MITSUBA] Hey, what are you
morons doing, stop fight--
Actually, this could
be very interesting.
[YUICHIRO]
Come, Asuramaru!
Fan out! Asura-Kannon!
[gasps]
Try not to cry, Kimizuki!
[KIMIZUKI grunting]
Nice try, but on
the count of nine,
I'm opening the
Devil's Coffin. Kiseki-o.
[gasps]
[KISEKI-O]
One, two, three, four...
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO yelps]
[KIMIZUKI] Hey! Don't you
run away from this fight!
[YUICHIRO] I'm not gonna
stand by and get killed
by some murder coffin!
That thing looks
super scary, man!
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
He may be dumb,
but he's got good instincts.
[YUICHIRO]
What?
Still, it was my
hatred for him that
helped me overcome my demon.
[KIMIZUKI]
I was just saying that
you're a real pain in my ass.
[YUICHIRO]
Oh, screw you!
If you think I'm bad,
wait till you get....
[YOICHI]
Come on, guys.
Can't we all just get along?
Well, I guess that
was interesting.
Yes. It's curious.
They both tried to
use special abilities
that should be way
above their skill levels.
[MITSUBA] And Yoichi was able
to conjure a manifestation
without any real training.
Where did Lieutenant Colonel
Guren find these guys, anyway?
[MITSUBA]
Wait, that can't be right!
[SHINOA]
There's nothing.
Their records start when
they joined the army.
All the data on their
past has been deleted.
[MITSUBA]
Who would do that?
[SHINOA] It had to have been
the Lieutenant Colonel.
[MITSUBA] You think Guren
is trying to hide his team's
history from the
higher ranking officers?
Possibly, but I
wouldn't be surprised
if there was more
to it than that.
Like what?
[SHINOA] Human experimentation
and war with the vampires.
I've got a bad feeling
that something horrible
is about to happen,
and that we're totally
unprepared for it.
[YUICHIRO] Next time,
on Seraph of the End:
"Ambition in the Demon Army."