[panting]
[KIMIZUKI panting]
So, what's going on, Shinoa?
[SHINOA] I don't know
anything more than you do.
[NORITO]
Where are the choppers?
Guren said they would be
here waiting to evacuate us.
We're not safe here.
The vampires will
be close behind.
We can't just stand around.
[MITO]
Major General.
These directives were in
the flight control room.
I think they're for us.
[NORITO]
Well? What does it say?
To stand by and
wait for new orders.
Stand by?
[RIKA] This is all your fault,
you spoiled little bitch!
Hey!
[RIKA]
Yayoi, Kagiyama...
They're both dead
because you betrayed us
and protected that vampire.
It's not fair that
you're still alive.
Maybe you should join them.
It's all your fault!
You got my friends killed!
I'm sorry.
[gasps] I'm not forgiving
you that easily.
You'll pay for what you did!
Stop!
[SHINOA]
It's fine, you guys!
[RIKA sobs]
I don't want your apology.
Save your breath.
It won't bring my friends back.
They're bleeding in the
streets. You killed them.
[RIKA sobbing]
[IWASAKI]
Rika.
Pull yourself together.
Killing her isn't going to help.
But... Makoto!
I'm not saying that
I'm going to forgive her
or her team.
I'm your leader,
so her blood should
be on my hands.
[SHINYA] Sorry, but that's
not your decision to make.
Then you're gonna
punish them, right?
They sided with a vampire
on the battlefield,
which led to our
troops being ambushed.
Like I said, you
don't get to decide
what happens to them.
Fine, then.
Prove you've got what it takes
to lead us and punish them!
[NARUMI] This entire
mission has turned into
a giant shit storm.
Just look at us.
We've lost several of our
comrades and our commander,
but we kept moving
forward, following orders!
And look how well
that's working out.
You want us to forgive these
traitors and "stand by"?
Are we supposed to just
lie down and die out here?
[SHINYA]
Escape in the chopper.
Then lead the vampires to a trap
waiting for them in Shinjuku.
That's what our
final mission was.
Only thing is,
Guren's not the one
who planned this.
[NARUMI]
Then who did?
Lieutenant General
Kureto Hiragi.
[ALL gasp]
[NARUMI grunts] Of course.
I'm sick of the Hiragis.
The selfish orders
they give out only serve
to give them more power.
Well, I refuse to
follow it anymore!
Just calm down.
Freaking out isn't going to
help us figure out what--
[NARUMI] Don't you dare
tell me to calm down!
[NARUMI]
We're abandoning this mission.
I'm going back to rescue
the Lieutenant Colonel.
If he's going back,
so am I. You coming?
If this wasn't Guren's mission,
I don't see any reason
to finish it. Right?
Goshi, Mito, Shinya. Goodbye.
Shigure! Sayuri!
Think about this!
This is starting to get
ugly. What should we do?
[SHINYA]
Hold on, Narumi!
I know I'm disobeying orders.
Go ahead and court martial
me for all I care.
Argh. Just--
Shut up for a second
and listen to me!
I'm trying to tell you
that we're aborting
this mission together.
What?
Let's do it.
We'll ignore the orders
from high command.
From now on, the Demon
Company has one goal.
The rescue of Lieutenant
Colonel Guren Ichinose.
[gasps]
Seriously?
You heard him. Let's go!
We're not going to
abandon our friend
when he needs our help.
[CROWLEY]
Mm...
It looks like we missed
an impressive battle here.
[GUREN groans]
[NOBLE A]
Start talking, maggot.
What were your plans?
[chuckles] You'll have to
hit me harder than that.
[NOBLE B] Queen Krul
specifically ordered us
not to kill him.
Tch. Soon, he'll be beggin'
to be put out of his misery.
[GUREN]
All right,
This is starting to
get a little painful.
Time to leak some false intel
and buy myself a break.
Let's see...
I've gotta get these
bastards to Shinjuku somehow.
They've probably beat me enough
to believe I've broken.
It's not naptime
for the livestock yet.
[GUREN groans]
[FERID] What a pleasure
to see you, Crowley.
It's been too long.
Five nobles were killed today.
The humans knew their locations.
I'm positive that
you had something
to do with this, Lord Ferid.
[FERID]
I'm hurt.
There's nothing worse than
selling out your friends.
Right? That's despicable.
Yeah. True.
But that's not what concerns me.
What bothers me is that
you gave the humans
my location, too.
And here I was
under the impression
that I was your friend.
But surely you
enjoyed the fight.
Well, yeah.
I guess it was a
pretty good time.
Then you should be
thanking me instead.
Besides, everyone knows
that we're friends, Crowley.
No one'll suspect I leaked
info if you were attacked.
[CROWLEY] I see, so you
were the one behind this.
You're only half right.
There's actually another
puppeteer pulling the strings
along with me.
Oh? Who is it?
[panting]
[FERID]
Him.
You must have some
kinda death wish, human.
Ah-- How dare you?
[GUREN]
Okay, I've had enough of this.
It's Shinjuku--
You're dead! Filthy human!
[NOBLE B] Hey, stop it.
He's saying something.
[NOBLE A]
I don't care!
[FERID] The Lieutenant
Colonel is a half-demon.
[CROWLEY]
Hm? A half-demon?
Although, he's actually
close to becoming complete.
Every day, he struggles
to keep two personalities
under control inside his body.
[FERID] One is an idealist
who wants nothing more
than to protect his troops
and his friends from harm.
[MAHIRU]
Come on, now.
You've had more than
enough of this, my darling.
Relax and let me
take over a while.
Get lost.
My poor little soldier.
You don't even have the strength
to push me away right now.
[FERID] But the other
personality isn't so nice.
It's his dead ex-girlfriend,
a perfectionist
who's been turned into a demon.
Look. The monster is coming out.
You're dead, human! Die!
[GUREN] Enjoy your last few
seconds alive, bloodsucker.
What? How dare you
speak to me like that?
[gasps] What the...
Give it here, Mahiru.
[gasps]
[KRUL] Oh, I see.
You're the one in control.
[GUREN grunts]
Help her! Kill him!
[KRUL]
Stay where you are.
Now then, you're
Mahiru Hiragi's messenger.
So where is she?
Mahiru is dead.
My deal was with her.
Before the world ended.
If she's dead, then there's no
reason for me to keep you alive.
Our agreement is null and
void in this circumstance.
[GUREN]
Then go ahead and kill me.
Oh, that's right.
You can't do it.
You've already
betrayed your kind
and need the humans to bail
your sorry ass out, right?
The Seraph of the End.
The experiment has
to succeed today
or you're totally screwed.
[groans]
[GUREN laughs]
Smart thinking.
Make 'em believe you're
still on their side.
Not a complete traitor.
They'll be testing
it at the airport.
[KRUL]
Attention men!
The humans are reassembling
at the Nagoya airport.
All units, move out!
[VAMPIRES]
Ma'am!
[laughs]
So, what's going to
happen now, Ferid?
What's the endgame?
The transformation of the world.
Vampires?
[MITSUBA]
Yoichi!
Right!
[SHINYA]
Don't fire!
They're ours. Those are
Demon Army aircraft.
[gasps]
[MITSUBA]
Big sister.
Ah--
[gasps]
[gasps] Hey. He's the
one who tortured us!
[gasps]
[KIMIZUKI]
Kureto Hiragi.
[KURETO]
Attention!
I'm Lieutenant General
Kureto Hiragi.
As you likely know, my family
controls the Demon Army.
[TROOPERS murmuring]
I've heard stories about him.
Me, too.
Rumor has it, he's
next in line as head
of the Hiragis and the army.
[KURETO]
Because of your efforts,
we're looking at total
victory over the vampires.
The sacrifices of
the Moon Demon Company
will not have been in vain.
You have ensured
humanity's survival.
My team will
take over from here.
Enjoy some much
deserved down time.
Disarm and relax.
[TROOPER B]
Huh?
Does that mean...
our mission's over?
Sounds like it.
Makoto! Did you hear that?
[NARUMI growls]
Everyone.
Stay at attention and
ready to fight, just in case.
[SHINYA]
"Total victory," huh?
Vampire nobles are headed
this way as we speak.
So, how do you plan
to defeat them, Brother?
Brutally.
We lost a lot of comrades here.
Don't we deserve to
know what your plan is?
Where is Guren?
[SHINYA]
He was captured by the vampires.
Huh? Please tell
me you're joking.
[gasps]
Dammit. That fool.
Is he turning on me as well?
Which personality was in
control when they took him?
Huh?
Come on.
You haven't figured it out yet?
[SHINYA]
Figured what out?
Well,
he did always try
to keep his comrades
protected and in the dark.
But I'm surprised
you didn't catch on
since you were so close.
What are you talking about?
Guren's been taken--
That's enough.
Your part in this is over.
Aoi. Do it.
Yes, sir.
[gasps] Wait, Kureto!
What in the hell is going on?
I told you, your role
in this is complete.
What are you planning to do?
Hey!
[KURETO]
Stand down. Right now.
I don't know who you are,
but I told you to relax.
Follow my orders.
Screw your orders!
What, you think you
can show up here and--
Calm down!
Makoto. Ease up.
[rumbling]
Not good. What've
you done, brother?
Don't bother. You can't
hope to protect him.
[growls]
We completed an
impossible suicide mission
behind enemy lines.
We did what you asked
of us, so just let us go.
And overlook this soldier's
rebellious attitude?
All right. I'll let it slide.
Don't wanna spoil the fun.
[gasps]
[KURETO] Besides, he's
going to die soon, anyway.
Shit!
Begin!
[gasps]
Genbushin!
[RIKA screams]
Rika!
[IWASAKI groans]
[NARUMI]
Shusaku!
No... Makoto... Run. Go!
[screams]
Damn you!
[NARUMI grunting]
I'll kill you!
Murdering bastard!
Back off.
Don't you see I've given these
soldiers honorable deaths?
Their sacrifice is
for humanity's future.
I spared them.
Just shut up!
[screams]
You... saved me.
[YOICHI]
Stop hurting my friends!
We need to retreat.
Don't worry, Shinoa.
You're safe.
Even if you don't act like it,
you're still
technically a Hiragi.
Fine. Die, then.
Yu's back!
--[MITSUBA] No way.
--[KIMIZUKI] Nice save!
But, he...
[SHINOA]
You're here!
Of course. You okay?
Yeah, but that was kinda close.
[MIKAELA]
I told you.
We shouldn't have come.
This is a huge mess.
Humans attacking other
humans. Just look.
No. I'm glad we came.
Bastard. What are you
doing to my comrades?
Ah. That's one of Guren's
Black Demon kids.
Do it.
They're coming from
the container.
Yoichi!
Damn it!
What've they got hidden
inside that thing?
It doesn't matter. Stop it!
[NARUMI grunting]
[yells]
[SHINOA]
Let's get outta here!
Come on, Yu.
[gasps]
All units, move in.
I don't want a single
human to survive.
[VAMPIRES yell]
This is the end.
We're destroying the
vampires right here.
Do it for humanity!
[TROOPERS yell]
Holy crap. What should we do--
Don't panic! This is
a great opportunity.
Yeah.
They're not paying
attention to us anymore.
This is our chance to escape.
[NORITO] You kids go ahead
and run while you can.
The seasoned pros
will provide you
with plenty of cover.
[YUICHIRO]
You guys...
[SHINYA] I'll clear a
path for us. Let's go!
For our comrades!
[VAMPIRES, TROOPERS yelling]
What're you doing?
That's it.
No more of my friends
are gonna die today!
You idiot! You're too far out!
No more!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Guren. You're all right!
Let's go!
Good. You're here.
I was hoping that you would be.
[YUICHIRO] Next time,
on Seraph of the End:
"Seraph of the End."