It's starting to get colder.
I like it better than the heat.
It feels so crisp outside.
Yeah, yeah, that's great,
now could you tell me
where we're going, Shinoa?
Relying on you to navigate for
us is getting kind of annoying.
Well, If we stay on this road,
we'll eventually
end up in Hakone.
There we could soak in the
hot spring, eat a feast,
and then wake up
relaxed and refreshed.
Doesn't that sound
like paradise, you guys?
Sure.
We're really headed to Ebina.
Ebina, huh?
I don't think I've heard of it.
Honestly, I'd rather
go to Hakone.
Oh, definitely.
But I'm afraid a vacation
just isn't in the cards.
Nagoya is our final destination.
Nagoya. Are you there, Mika?
[tires screech]
Crap, they came outta nowhere!
Kill them!
Go, Tenjiryu!
I'm not slowing down!
No problem! C'mon. Asuramaru!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
Kimizuki! Another one!
Hard right, quick!
Huh? What?
C'mon, can't we go faster?
Bye, bye, we'll
see you in Ebina!
Hey! Wait, where the
hell are you going?
[YUICHIRO]
Seriously?
[GUREN] Why are you
creeping around, Goshi?
Hey, look, Guren. You like?
[GUREN]
Do I like what?
[NORITO]
A little light reading.
It's been a long time
since we've seen girls
lounging around
in fancy underwear.
I can't even get Shigure or
Sayuri to wear bathing suits.
Ask me to again, and I'll
gouge your eyes out.
I guess I'd have to wear one...
If the Lieutenant Colonel
ordered me to, that is.
[NORITO]
Did ya hear that? Guren!
For the sake of morale, tell her
to fight in a bathing suit.
Will you shut up?
You're supposed to be
checking for vampires.
[NORITO] Oh, yeah, uh.
Mito's keeping an eye out.
How can you be so useless?
[MITO]
Guren.
I've finished scoping
out the interior.
There are no signs that
vampires have been here.
Hey, Mito, question.
Would you wear a swimsuit?
[MITO]
Why are you asking me that?
Well, Pervert Guren
over here wants to know
what your body looks like
under that uniform.
Huh? Wha--? But I...
What kind of dirty things
have you been talking about?
Do you really
wanna know, Guren?
Look. The troops have
started to arrive.
Don't ignore me!
[engine revs]
[SHINYA]
Good morning!
Whoa, Shinya, where'd
you get a car like this?
[SHINYA] It was abandoned
on the side of the road
so I hotwired it. Awesome, huh?
It's perfect for an impractical
Major General like you.
What are you doing here?
Brother Kureto told me
about your mission.
Sounds like you guys
are sacrificial pawns.
A hundred troops don't
stand much of a chance
against the vampire nobles.
Those bloodsuckers
are too powerful.
So I figured, why not bring
my impractical self here
and see if I can help out?
'Kay. You can thank me now.
You're such a moron.
Well, now we're definitely
gonna be late.
Um. Do you think
we'll get in trouble?
If Guren's mad,
I'll just tell him
it was Shinoa and
Mitsuba's fault.
How dare you sell
out your comrades!
[YUICHIRO] Comrades my ass.
You tried to leave me behind!
[SHINOA] Hey, we went back
and picked you up eventually!
[SHINOA giggles]
We'll leave here at 0700 hours.
Six hours later, we
will arrive in Nagoya.
The directives I
hand out will cover
specific strategic details.
Oh, nice of you to show up.
[YOICHI, MITSUBA, SHINOA]
Uh--
I'm surprised you didn't
miss the entire war.
[SHINOA]
Well. You see, sir.
We have a really good
excuse for being late.
It's not like we stopped
at the hot springs
--for a long, luxurious bath--
--[GUREN] Don't make excuses!
This mission isn't
some childish game.
If you can't follow
orders, leave now.
[TROOPERS murmuring]
Damn kids, screwing around.
Sorry, Lieutenant Colonel.
This is my fault.
I take all the blame.
Yu...
[YUICHIRO] We were late
because I took it upon myself
to fight the Four
Horsemen of John.
Does that mean you're
going to leave?
No, sir! Please let me stay!
I want to help
destroy the vampires.
Fall in line with the others.
Just know, you'll have to
face severe punishment later.
Yu, no.
Listen to me
carefully, everyone.
During this mission, I won't
tolerate any failures.
Follow my orders to the
letter and don't fool around.
This mission will probably
be the most dangerous
you will ever have.
Many of you will die.
Remember, everyone
here is family.
That means those
who fall in battle
are our brothers and sisters.
[gasps]
But they won't die in vain!
Their sacrifices will
ensure our success.
Let me be clear.
Our goal isn't to
come back alive.
It is to be victorious
no matter what!
Do you understand me?
[TROOPERS]
Yeah!
I just want to apologize.
This was all my fault.
Hey, don't sweat it.
What's the worst
Guren can do to me?
You can take all
the blame next time.
Special Private
Yuichiro Hyakuya.
We're waiting.
'Kay. It's time for
me to get an earful.
No, wait. Let me go in
with you and explain.
[MITSUBA]
Yeah.
And I was screwing around
on the road, too.
I'll tell Guren.
[KIMIZUKI]
Well, if this is a party,
guess I might as well
come. For backup.
Yeah! Me, too!
Nah, don't worry
about it, guys.
I'm kinda' used to Guren
yelling at me anyway.
[SHINOA]
But, Yu!
[SHIGURE] Lieutenant
Colonel Guren. He's here.
Hey. Idiot Yu. How's it goin'?
Huh? Why would you ask
me a question like that
when you're getting
ready to lecture me?
[GUREN] But none of this
was your fault, was it?
Uh. Well...
Taking the heat for your
comrades is admirable.
So what?
You brought me here
to reward me?
Oh, now you understand.
Our Guren here is
actually a big softie.
Huh? Hey, wait!
You're that guy from that
place I had to go that time.
You certainly don't
have a gift for words,
but you're right.
Good to see ya.
That's enough, we're
wasting time here.
Goshi, let's get started.
Yeah, yeah.
[YUICHIRO screams]
[GROUP gasps]
Yu!
[YUICHIRO]
Hot, hot, very hot!
I'm burning alive you bastard!
Come on, get me down from here!
--What?
--[YUICHIRO] Whoa, hot-ot-ot-ot!
Hey!
An illusion spell?
What kind of sick joke are
you trying to pull, Guren?
It's no joke, this is
your punishment, Shinoa.
[GUREN] This is what you get
for not 'fessing up yourself.
I'm here to show you
that not following orders
can easily get your
comrades killed.
Yes, I know that.
And I'm well aware that
what I did was wrong.
[GUREN]
That's not good enough.
You've never experienced
what it's like
to truly care for
another person.
And therefore,
you don't understand
the fear of losing someone.
[gasps]
But from now on,
things are different.
One wrong move could get
your comrades killed.
As team leader, their
lives are in your hands.
[SHINOA]
I said I know that--
And I said that's not
enough, brat. Remember?
Let me ask you something.
What would you do
if a huge threat
suddenly appeared right now?
Would you be able
to manage your team?
Right. Let's see.
A little test pitting
me, Mito, and Shinya
against you and your squad.
The fight begins in ten seconds.
Ten. Nine...
What? You seriously
want us to fight?
[GUREN]
Six. Five...
[SHINOA] C'mon, we need
to put some distance
between us and them.
[GUREN]
Hm.
You shouldn't be
so tough on Shinoa.
You know she's
trying really hard.
That's awfully sweet a' ya.
Why don't you show her
your support by beating us
instead of standing
here looking stupid?
'Kay, but don't blame me
when I embarrass you.
Like I'd lose to some kid.
[SHINOA] First, I want to
put the long-range fighters
up against each other.
That's Yoichi versus
Major General Shinya.
[YOICHI]
Got it.
[SHINOA] Based on what I
know about Colonel Jujo,
Mitsu and I should be
able to hold her off.
So our only real
problem is Guren.
Yes.
The Lieutenant Colonel is a
master of close quarters combat.
Kimizuki and Yu will team up.
If he manages to beat you two,
then this test is
as good as over.
No sweat, we just
have to take him down.
Yeah.
I've been waiting to get
a piece of that loser.
All right. Take your positions.
[GUREN]
Okay, kids. Here we come.
Shinya.
[SHINYA]
Allow me.
Come on, Byakkomaru. Get them.
Gekkouin!
[SHINOA, MITSUBA yelp]
[GUREN] Their formation
is already falling apart.
Everyone! Regroup!
I'll cover our backs!
You're not getting
away. Rookies.
Let's do this!
I won't let you
past me, Guren!
You're an Idiot.
[KIMIZUKI, GUREN,
YUICHIRO grunting]
Hey. You're not half bad.
Of course!
[MITSUBA, SHINOA yelling]
The fight is over, children.
[TROOPERS gasp]
[gasps]
Come on, Guren. Was
that really necessary?
Try not to cry.
I'm not done with you!
[GUREN]
Hm.
That's it!
Everyone get into formation
with Yu in the center!
Whoa, Lieutenant Colonel Guren
is fighting those newbies!
This must be some kind of
punishment for being late.
Wow, look at that kid.
Yeah.
He's matching the Lieutenant
Colonel's attacks pretty well.
There's no way
the kid'll beat him
with power alone.
[YUICHIRO]
What the hell?
[SHINOA] It's an explosion
spell! Let me disenchant it.
Not a chance.
Now's the time to admit defeat.
Before I blow your head off.
[YUICHIRO] If I explode,
then I'm taking you with me!
Whoa, now I'm terrified!
I'm just kidding. I figured
you'd try something.
[panting]
[GUREN]
There. I'm past your defenses.
That means all your
comrades are dead now.
[gasps]
Dammit!
Yu!
I'll stop you!
What a foolish move.
[gasps]
You should never
challenge someone
who is stronger than you are.
And you guys are way too late.
[YUICHIRO]
Stupid!
[GUREN]
What a disappointment.
You've got three Black Demon
holders in your squad,
and this is the best you can do?
The nobles are
stronger than we are,
and they won't hold back.
Do you really think you
stand a chance against them?
[YOICHI, KIMIZUKI grunt]
All right.
As you can see, these
rookies need a lot of help.
We're gonna have to
show them what it means
to be good comrades.
Are we totally sure
those three guys
have Black Demon weapons?
How'd they manage the trials?
The weapons don't matter.
Without teamwork,
they're all useless.
Guess that's why we
gotta look after 'em.
[YUICHIRO growls]
What's wrong?
You look dissatisfied.
I am.
I'm thinking about what
strategy we should use
the next time we face off
against your team.
[SHINYA]
Oh.
So the hotheaded little
rebel has brains as well.
Why are you touching me?
This test pointed
out your weaknesses.
Focus on your teamwork.
[NARUMI] Excuse me.
May I speak freely, sir?
These kids are dangerous.
Newbies have no place
on the battlefield.
They don't follow
orders or obey rules,
and they have no
sense of teamwork.
If you let them join us,
they'll only drag us down.
[GUREN]
Hm. Those are all problems,
but how do we fix them?
Oh, wait, I know.
I'm putting your team
in charge of them.
[GROUP gasps]
Shigure. Rearrange
the team rosters.
I want Shinoa's Squad
joined up with Narumi's.
Yes, sir.
[NARUMI] Wait, please rethink
this, Lieutenant Colonel!
This is Sergeant Makoto Narumi.
And that's Rika Inoue,
Taro Kagiyama, Yayoi Endo,
and Shusaku Iwasaki.
They're an excellent squad.
They'll train you well.
They don't seem too
thrilled to have us.
Please, sir.
Listen up! Playtimes'
over, so let's focus.
We've got a mission.
[TROOPERS]
Sir!
[YUICHIRO] I'm looking forward
to serving with you.
[grunts]
Thanks.
You had to go and open your
big mouth, didn't you?
Do you realize how
much work this is?
Well, They do seem to
have a lot of raw power.
With a little training, maybe
they'll turn out to be useful.
What's with
that Sergeant?
Can't really blame him.
He may be a complete jerkwad,
but he's dead right about us.
Hey. Everyone.
I'm sorry about how
things turned out.
All of this stuff is my fault.
Not just being late.
We lost because I'm incompetent.
I don't think I'm fit to
be called the commander.
Don't say that.
Did you not hear
what Guren said?
All we need to do is
learn to work as a team.
And the first step is
supporting each other.
We're a family.
The more we work together,
the stronger we'll be.
Yeah.
And that means we still
need a commander.
So, whaddya think, Shinoa?
Okay!
[BOY A screams]
[GIRL A] Vampires!
The vampires are coming!
[BOY A, GIRL A screaming]
[GIRL A gasps]
[whimpers]
[LACUS chuckles]
[GIRL A]
No! Please, don't hurt me!
[gasping]
[heat beating]
[LACUS] They're gifts for
the nobles in Nagoya.
If you want to take a little
sip, now's the time, Mika.
I'm not interested in
drinking human blood.
Wait, is that some kind of joke?
If you're afraid of getting
caught, don't worry.
You can trust me.
I won't tell a soul.
What a weirdo.
[MIKAELA pants]
The day will come
when you will have to
drink from a human.
[MIKAELA coughs]
[panting]
[GIRL B screams] No! Stop!
Please! I'm not going with you!
[GIRL B sobbing]
[heart beating]
[gasps]
[heart beating quickly]
[MIKAELA gasps]
[gasping]
[hissing]
See there. I knew
you looked thirsty.
[BOYS gasp]
[GIRL B grunts]
[CHILDREN yelp]
[gasping]
Yes, definitely a weirdo.
[YUICHIRO] Next time,
on Seraph of the End:
"Livestock Revolt."