Once upon a time,
there was a farmer.
The good farmer had been given
a keepsake by his grandmother.
But now, he could
not find it anywhere.
It was an old comb,
nothing more.
And he would leave
it lying around,
never paying
much attention to it.
But still, this comb was an
important memento
from his grandmother.
The farmer desperately
wanted to find the comb again.
Every day he would pray and
make offerings
to the god, Inari.
But the poor farmer could
not afford to offer money.
So, he would bring eggs
as an offering instead.
And then...
...on a clear, blue night...
It was the fox.
It brought the comb back to him.
And that's how it happened.
Once this news spread,
any villager who'd
lost something,
would bring eggs to
the shrine and pray.
Hoping for their
item to be returned.
But...
...in reality...
Get 'em all...
What you neglect, we collect.
People believed that the
foxes were loyal
servants of Lord Inari.
But when no one was looking,
they would take the things
people simply neglected.
Does that mean...
that foxes are thieves?
No, they're not thieves.
Sometimes people stop
caring for their things.
And that's when the foxes take
them to teach them a lesson.
They'll never hafta
do that to me.
That's cuz...
I take care of my things!
Then you're a good girl.
Ah, you don't
believe me, Mommy?!
I believe you.
It's really true!
Uh, okay.
I know what.
I show you how true it is.
Haruka...
...careful.
Lemme see...
Found it!
Ta-dah!
See!
It's the pretty
mirror you gave me.
And I always keep this with me!
You're right.
So Mommy...
I wanna know when you
can come back home again.
Hm.
I don't know.
Hey!
Why don't we ask Mr. Fox?!
Lord Inari...
Can I please...
...have my Mommy back?
Those guys are the worst.
Ew...
it's hot in here.
Hello.
Don't worry about it.
No one's here.
Come in.
I'm tired of asking him
to clean up after himself.
He's a mess.
I wish I had your place, Miho.
Everyone's house is the same.
I'm thirsty.
Hey, you want somethin'?
Yeah sure, that'd be great.
Tsch.
How's that new.
Wha...?
What again...?
What?
Oh, hi.
Haru?
You drank it.
Huh?
You drank my
ginger ale, didn't you?
Ohh.
Yeah, maybe.
What?!!!
Maybe you did?
Don't touch my stuff!
I bought that, y'know?
Pay me back!
Okay, I'm sorry.
I can't believe you!
Listen.
Good news.
Looks like I won't
have to work tonight.
Any food there for dinner?
How would I know!
It's not like I'm your maid!
Uh.
Miho...
You ever have something
you really treasured as a kid...
...and now when you look for it,
it seems to have vanished?
What're you talking about?
Ta-dah!
See!
It's the pretty
mirror you gave me.
And I always keep this with me!
My mother gave me this old
hand-mirror when I was little.
And I didn't go
anywhere without it.
I totally treasured
that thing...
...and yet somehow,
I still lost it.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I got this doll set for
Christmas once, and I loved it.
But I've no idea
where it is now.
Where's that stuff go, I wonder.
It's gotta go somewhere.
I mean even the important stuff.
Maybe memories go there too.
Huh?
Okay!
I'm gonna go to my Grandma's.
What? Didn't your dad say
he was coming home early?
Time for a change of scenery.
Going out again?
There it is.
Lord Inari...
I know my mother is gone.
But if you could find that
hand mirror she gave me...
...and somehow bring it back...
Ready?
Here we go!!
Fly!!!
Wow, look at it!
It's really flying!!!
It was totally worth
the extra money.
Yeah, adding the rubber
band is amazing!
It's what makes it all work.
Look at it go!
Dad, again?
What?
Hey Haru.
It looks like I've gotta
work late after all.
So if you get hungry just...
Yeah, I'm really sorry, but...
I'm actually not home today.
Huh?
I said I'm not home.
Goodbye.
Where are you?
I don't wanna go back home...
Gotcha.
Was that...?
That can't be the wind.
What is that?
Huh?
Wait.
Where could he have gone?
Huh?
Why is this water warm?
I've...
...touched...
...a Human...
Y-You talk...
Huh?
Uh, that hurt...
What?
Oh no.
Oh no, no, no.
What're you doing?
Hey, wait, what're you...?!
I just got back from
getting more of the forgotten.
Well go on, deliver it.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Hi there.
Just 3 cans, 4 bottles and
5 lousy planks today.
Please go back to
the people place.
Just hold on a sec.
Gimme a minute!
I wanna ask you somethin' first.
All this stuff here...
it's things...
...that you guys have
stole from us, isn't it?
No!
We don't steal it!
Yeah?
Really?
...what about that?
It's all forgotten stuff.
Things you guys just neglected.
Huh?
Neglected...?
Get 'em all.
Get 'em all!
What you neglect, we collect!
So...
...if all this stuff was
just left lying around...
...then my mirror...
C'mon...
...what are you doing?
You've gotta go!
Please, just leave!
Stop pulling!
Hey...
...maybe you've seen it.
It's a hand-mirror
about this big?
Hand-Mir-ror?
Understand?
It was mine.
How would I know?
Would you look for it with me?
Why would I do that?
Give that back!
This is mine you know.
But if you help
me find that mirror...
...then I'll give these
to you to keep.
So what would happen
if someone found out,
that a human was here?
I don't know what
the punishment would be.
But whatever it is...
I'm sure it's terrifying.
They'd probably confiscate
all my stamp cards.
Just when I've
finished 3 whole cards
and I'm nearly done
with my fourth...
Um, I was asking what
would happen to me?
I dunno.
Hey...
So, what's up there'?
Where do you think?
It's the Island.
The Island?
Whoa.
We're moving!
Y'see, we can't make
stuff like you Humans can.
So instead, we pick up whatever
Humans just leave lying
around and use that.
And fortunately for us,
Humans forget about
their things pretty quickly.
No wonder stuff
is always getting lost.
But we don't steal anything.
We only go after
things that are left behind.
If we were to
steal from the humans,
then they would come
here and attack us.
Like you did.
Humans are scary.
Hey wake up!
Ow!
Listen...
...you and me never had
a proper introduction.
Proper introduction?
I'm Haruka.
I'm sixteen and a freshman.
Nice to meet ya'.
Teo...
Very-nice-to-meet-you!
Lemme go!
Wow...
it's amazing.
This was all made
from neglected stuff?
Hey.
You look ridiculous
in that mask here.
Well?
How's this?!
C'mon... let's go.
Sure.
'Scuse me.
I'm looking for a hand
mirror about this big.
Have you seen it?
No.
Nothing like that here.
A mirror?
Exactly.
Hmm...
What's it look like?
How do I describe it...
Well...
...um...
Oh...
may I borrow this?
Sure.
It's shaped like this...
...and then on the back...
Just like this.
Have you ever seen it?
Hmmmm.
Nope, never.
For pricey stuff like that...
you're better off goin'
to Mabarowa's store.
Ma...
Maba...
Mabarowa?
What?
You don't know who Mabarowa is?
Y-Yeah.
Course I do.
Right, Teo?]
Teo?
What's goin' on Teo?
What're you doin' here?
Skippin' out on work again?
You slacker.
The only stuff you
bring back are things
we got no use for.
I'm kicking your butt!
Shut up! You'll pay for that!
Watch out.
Teo's getting angry!
Oh no.
Put me down.
Leave me alone.
Now get your hands off him!
Huh?
And just who the hell are you?
Acting all high and mighty.
You got some nerve!
You really want
to fight with us?
Wait a sec...
Don't tell me...
Tell you what?
You're Teo's girlfriend!
Excuse me?
A girlfriend?!!
S-She's not!
Okay!
Los the freaky mask
and show us your face.
What?
No.
What makes you think I
have to show you my face?
Teo, we're leaving!
Hold up!
Slow down you.
No way!
Now paws off.
Hey!
Don't pull me!
Come on... let's go
Sure...
What was that...?ii
There's something
fishy going on there?
Whatchya mean boss?
Is Tail fishy?
I mean the other one.
Hey... are those the only
friends you got around here?
Those guys aren't my friends.
Do you have friends?
Leave me alone.
Oh... ok.
What?
Wow!
Who is that ?
Oh.
That's the Baron.
Always lording over
us from his castle.
Wowi
He's got some bad taste.
Yeah.
Welcome.
May I help you
youngsters with something?
What do you two want?
I'm busy here.
Spit it out already?
Well...
I'm trying to find
an old hand mirror.
A hand mirror?
Tsk.
Someone your age
can't afford such a thing.
That would cost you over
a thousand stamp cards.
Now go home and leave me alone.
But...
that mirror is mine.
I remember it perfectly.
Huh?
It looks like this.
This is...
I recall this mirror...
...it's the Barron's.
I've seen it once myself.
It is indeed a truly
exceptional mirror.
This mirror has been
imbued with divine powers!
Uh, actually, it's just
a normal hand mirror.
A god resides
within that mirror.
It is of rare and
exceptional beauty.
With tremendous magical powers.
It was one of the Baron's mosti
prize possessions and he
took excellent care of it.
But then...
...somebody stole it from him!
And now?
And now...
I'm afraid its whereabouts...
...remain a mystery.
But...
it's not like it's some
super valuable mirror.
It's just mine,
and I really want it back.
Yeah but he doesn't have it.
Come on.
Thank you for all your help sir.
Hold it.
That's an unusual mask you have.
So...
...will you give it to me?
I'll give you another
hand mirror in exchange.
No.
I don't want another mirror.
Come on.
No, you can't--
She can't!
Because...
I gave this mask
to her as a present.
Okay, just go.
Hurry.
Thank you so much
for your time, sir!
This is Mabarowa...
Baron, sir.
We have an issue.
I'm afraid we have
a human in our midst.
And she appears to
be looking for the mirror.
So...
...time to give up and go home.
Thanks, I'm starving.
Huh?!
What is this?
It was caught fresh just now.
I can't take it!
She took off the mask!
I see her.
I see her. I see her.
Human?
Human.
You sure?
Just as I suspected.
An interesting turn
of events, huh?
What we do, boss?
Teo messed up big.
We'll make sure
he pays for this!
I can't believe this.
Those guys again?
Ah, man...
We're just here to have a
little chat with your friend.
Now go on and
take that mask off.
Why?
Off.
No .
Take it off!
No way!!
Vikki...
...get it.
Decargot, you do it.
Okay!
Grab her!
Get Teo, too.
Get them!!!
Moron, they're over there!
Go fetch that
thing from the factory.
I'm gonna get you, Teo.
I swear it!
Wow.
An amusement park.
Hey...
Hmm...
Hey.
H-Hold on.
Will you...
Wow...
What is this place?
It's "Oblivion Theater."
It's where they project the
memories of the
neglected things.
Huh.
That was my...
Cotton?
It's me.
Do you remember?
It's Haruka.
What is she doing?
Aagghh...
That girl is ruining my show!
Wait a sec.
I think it's a human.
A Human?
I don't know
how she got in here.
But she's clearly
the owner of that toy!
Now this is good drama.
It's a tearful reunion.
Lovely.
Cue the music!
Haruka...?
It's me, your owner...
Haruka.
Don't you remember?
Haruka...
But what about my show?!
That's right...
Haruka...
I remember a girl
named Haruka...
She threw me away.
My Haruka abandoned me.
Cotton?
But I...
I hate Haruka.
I'm so sorry.
I really am.
Please forgive me.
I shouldn't have neglected
you all this time.
I'm sorry.
I don't believe you.
Huh?
There's nowhere
to run now, Teo!!
You'll get a spanking!
Ain't no escapin' this thing!!!
Here we go!!!
Get back! Go! Go on!
Hey you can't just
run away from this!
Haru! Run!
Heeeyyy!!!
And what about my performance?
That ending was perfect.
Brilliant!!!
Sorry!
This way!
Get ready, Teo.
'Cuz you're in for
some serious trouble now!
This way!
We got 'em now.
There's no way!
My legs can't go any faster!!!
How 'bout you, Cotton.
You okay.
That hurt.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
I'll never leave you again.
I promise.
That's the truth!
To be honest...
I really missed you...
Haruka.
Cotton...
Wow...
So you live in this?
It's not that bad.
All better.
Thank you.
So what's up with this place?
Why're there
airplanes everywhere?
Because one day...
I wanna build a real airplane.
Imagine...
...soaring through the sky
like birds and humans.
Nobody here has
actually flown a real plane.
There's just the
Baron with his airship.
Yeah... but even
with a propellor,
it won't fly without an engine
Huh?
En...
...gine?
You're really
clueless, aren't ya'?
Look at this one.
It's got a rubber
band connected.
And that's what
makes the propeller spin.
Rubber?
So the rubber band
is the engine!
Well...
...sort of...
But...
...how come Cotton
can move and talk?
Magic?
Someone must've sewn a
piece of a mirror into him.
Mirror?
Mirrors have some
kind of a divine power.
With just a
little shard,
you can breathe life into
anything, even dolls.
Mirrors...
Hey, Cotton.
Do you remember
everything that
happened up up til now?
Of course.
So... then maybe
you remember that
hand mirror Mom gave me, too?
I remember.
Both me and the mirror were
picked up at the same time.
It was the Baron.
Oh...
That guy in the airship?
We were with him for a while.
And then one night,
some thieves came
and stole us from
the Baron's castle.
Both you and the mirror?
When they stole us,
they took us somewhere
underground...
To the thieves'
secret scary palace.
So... I did my best to run away.
It's the Petit Loss.
The Petit Loss?
They're bandits that
live underground here.
Look.
That's the entrance
to their hideout.
All the Petit
Loss live there.
They're so scary,
no one goes near 'em.
So then...
...that's where
my mom's mirror is...
Huh?
No way.
Don't even think about it.
Please?
Forget it!
I'm begging you!
That's just way too scary.
Hey.
Stand up.
That thing.
It's not a chair.
See this guy...
goes here.
And then this...
My Grandma had one of these.
It's called a "gramophone."
Amazing...!
Where you going?
Just to get some water.
Come with us and be quiet.
Let me go!
Now, now.
There is no need for violence.
It's... It's the Baron?
Shut your trap!
I know what you've done Teo.
That you've smuggled
a human in here.
If news of that
were to get out...
the punishment that must
befall you would be horrible.
And all the cards you have so
diligently earned
would be taken away.
So, with that in mind,
I'm truly hoping
you'll allow me to help with
this little problem of yours.
I believe you're aware
that the human
is searching for
a particular hand-mirror.
I want you to go with the human
and help her find that mirror.
And once it's found...
I want you to quietly
bring it back to me.
You see...
...that mirror was once mine.
And it's very precious to me.
If you do this...
I will reward you by making
sure no one finds out
that you were the one who
brought the human here.
And...
In addition...
I will give you
10,000 stamp cards.
10,000?!!!
So go on,
unhand him now.
Can you drive a
little slower, please!!!
In there huh?
That's the place where
I can find my mom's mirror?
Yeah, but, just
slow down a little bit.
Hey...
...you're making me nervoust.
Maybe we should head back.
If were turn back...
...everything we've done up
'til now will be pointless.
I'm kinda okay with that.
There's no retreat now...
It's just a mirror,
it's no big deal.
Let it go!!!
Um...
Teo...
Oww!
It's the Petit Loss!
Haru!
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes
and drive this thing!
I can't look down!
Then don't look down,
just look in front of you.
In front of you.
Look in front you, Haru!
What is that?
Haruuuu!
Agh, what is this stuff.
It tastes like...
...syrup.
Stop.
Stay back. Stay back.
I said stay back!
Come on.
Put me down already!
Cotton!
I'm coming!
There you are...
...my mirror.
Wait!
Hi mom...
Thank you...
...for everything.
I'm sorry I dragged
you into this.
I know you didn't hafta do it.
I owe you big.
If only I had
some magic then...
...maybe I could've gotten rid
of that thing much easier.
But it was you who made that
plane move at the shrine.
I saw you.
That was magic, right?
That's beginner stuff.
But it's the best I can do.
And...
...it's why I spend my
life picking up junk.
I guess...
I'm neglected junk, too.
You know... I'm
also neglected junk.
There's not a single person
who's worried about me.
Not for ages.
Teo!
What is this thing?
I feel like I've seen it before.
Yeah, I feel that way, too.
But where did we see it?
Well it came from up there.
--I know what it is!
Those things you ate!
Yeah... freshly caught!
I guess they...
...use these as bait
to lure them out.
Teo!
Get in!
Grab tight!
We made it.
Teo!
Bravo, bravo.
You completed
your task dutifully.
Get out.
Don't touch me!
Hey...
That's mine!!!
Teo.
What's going on?
Young Teo here
used the Human...
...to bring my precious
hand-mirror back to me.
And now...
...to show my benevolence,
I will keep the promise
I made to him.
Ten thousand stamp cards.
All for you.
Teo?
What are you doing?!
Look at me Teo.
Go ahead... take them.
You let Haruka go!
And who do we have here.
Cotton!
Be still!
What's gonna happen to her?
Just send her back to
the Human World okay!
Just let her go?
Oh, I have no intention of that.
I've always fancied the idea
of having a human servant.
We had an arrangement, Teo.
And I never made any
promises about her, did I?
I'm sure there's no
need to worry.
We can never...
...make friends with a human.
That's just the
way it has to be.
It's mine!
That mirror was a special
gift given to me by mother!
Now give it back!
From what I understand you
left it lying around neglected.
But not to worry.
It's in good hands now.
I'll take very good care of it.
I'm sure this mirror is happy
to be in my possession.
Yeah, well I'm
not gonna leave it
lying around anymore.
Give it back!
It belongs to me!
With this, I can concentrate
the power of 10,000 mirrors.
I can control thousands of
robots with this kind of power.
They can fetch new
things from the human world.
Things that we've
never seen before.
No more of this
old forgotten gargbage.
Then I'll raze this
miserable junkyard.
And with the power
of my machines,
I'll build a shiny new island.
And finally I will be
better than the humans.
I will have more
beauty and grandeur
than they ever dreamed possible!
Now, let's talk about you, dear.
Yeah, you're gonna hafta swallow
an the oblivion
drop, little one.
Once you swallow one of those,
you won't remember anything.
And you'll be a happy servant.
With you as my tool,
I could steal
anything I wanted
from the human world.
I'm actually
doing you a favor.
Without those
pesky memories
you'll feel much better.
No!
Don't you dare!
Stop it!
No!
Let me go!
Stop!
Behold!
Outta the way!
Move it!
--Teo!
--Hey, look... there he is.
C'mon.
He brought a human here.
He has to pay!
Everyone!
Please listen!
The Baron is planning on doing
something truly horrible to us.
He has the human.
He's gonna force
her to be his servant
and I've gotta go save her.
I knew you were
friends with that human!
You wanna save a human?
That's stupid!
Humans can be very nice.
They're not at all like
I thought they'd be.
They're not scary and evil.
They're good!
See... Look.
A human taught me
how to build this.
An airplane!
I've heard enough
of your babble.
Get him!
No!
I have to save her!
I need your help!
The Baron is gonna doing
something really bad!
We hafta stop him!
There's my stamp cards.
All 10,000...
Now stop standin'
there and build me a plane.
Turn it up.
Okay...
...we'll start by makin'
this thing bigger!
Ready.
There!
I don't know, Teo.
This things pretty heavy.
Do you really think
it's gonna fly?
I'm sure of it.
Don't...
...let...
...me...
...down!
So...
Stubborn, are ya'?
Giver her another drop then.
Swallow it... come on!
Teo is heading
straight for the castle!
C'mon.
Fly for me!!!
Oh no!
Gimme that.
I can do this!
Fly!!!
He's flying!
What happened?
What is this?
The Baron is the one
who's has your mirrors!
Charge!!!
Haruka...
It's the Petit Loss!
What the heck are
they doin' here?
Someone must've told them
we got all those mirrors here!
This is gonna be bad.
They're plastic.
Come on rubber band power!
Your Highness!
We've been attacked and
outnumbered by enemy forces.
And the Human escaped...
She what?
You worthless creatures!
Perhaps it's time...
...for a little trial run.
Watch this.
Haruka!
Now we got you now!
End of the line girlie!
Very well done.
You humans are so clever.
But it's over now.
Fire the net-gun!
Yes sir.
Uh, my bad.
Now that was a close call.
Be good and stay put.
You!
Give Haruka back!
Cotton?
Get off me!
Back to your posts, at once!
How dare you,
you dirty little fuzzball.
You annoying worthless,
forgotten piece of garbage!
That's enough!
Leave Cotton alone!
No don't!
Cotton! Cotton! No!
Cotton wait!
Oopsy... she fell.
Go get her.
I'm glad...
...that we got
one last chance...
...to talk.
Me too.
Me too, Cotton.
Really glad.
You made me happy.
Oh Cotton!
A flying machine?
Teo?!
Haru...
I wanted...
...to tell you I'm sorry.
Why that little...
Take 'em out!
Hang on!
Did we get them?
Fire the big one!
Wind the rubberband backwards.
Huh?
What for?
Just start peddling
the other way!
More more more...
Now let the pedals go!!!
Back up!
Haru!
Haru?
Are you hurt?
Come on.
Haru!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Teo...
Thank goodness.
I don't believe it...
...we're both all right.
Yeah, but we won't be for long.
The Baron will be
here any second, I'm sure.
We've gotta get out of here.
There it is.
There's what it?
The mirror...
Mom's mirror...
It's at the very
top of this thing.
Teo.
Please come.
Go with me.
Of course.
We'll take your
mirror back together.
Teo...
Ready... set...?
Look at that!
There it is.
Don't you touch it!
Don't you dare touch
my precious mirror!
Haru!
Quick!
Get the mirror!
Enough of this child's play.
Haru, go!
Grab it!
Get off of me, you little brat!
I won't let you have it!
Haru!
Teo...
--Wah!
--Ah...
Don't do that to me, Haruka...
...you scared me.
It's mom...
Can we do origami please...?
Sure.
But after dinner, okay?
I think...
...we're inside
the mirror's memory.
She's obviously
taking after me...
Let's just hope...
...she doesn't
have your messy side.
That's right.
Just my good sides.
Okay.
Right, left, right, left.
Look at...!
That's my girl!
She's getting kinda chubby.
That's 'cause you feed
her sweets all the time.
But she's so happy
when I give it to her.
You're gonna spoil
her, you know.
I wanna go...
I wanna see the fireworks!
Well... why don't
we go then?!
They're beautiful.
I think you'll like them.
They're really big!
And you can hear them go...
Boom!
--Boom! Like that.
--Really?
Boom!
When I grow up mommy...
...can I be just like you too?
Of course you can.
Or you know...
you could be like your dad, too.
I'd rather be mommy.
Oh... now poor
Daddy's all sad.
You know Haru fell
down in the park today,
but she
didn't cry at all.
She's growing up.
Humans forget the
most amazing things.
Come on daddy, please stay.
Don't go.
You neglect...
...even your memories.
Hey, what're you...
Haru!
No...!
Here...
Happy birthday, Haruka.
Go on... open it.
It's so cute!
Thank you!
This guy's name is Cotton.
Hello Cotton.
How old are you?
You got it.
I'm happy to be your big sister!
Take good care of him.
Your big sister will
take good care of you!
So mommy...
I want to know when you can
come back home again?
Hm.
I don't know.
Hey!
Why don't we ask Mr. Fox?!
I can't just keep crying.
These tears aren't
doing me any good.
Oh... Haru.
You're up early.
Hey daddy...
What're you doin' in here?
Take a look.
I made you lunch for you.
It's hamburger patty today!
I wanna eat it now!
He followed us!
I've gotcha now!
Haru!
We've gotta find
a way outta here!
Way out?
They're all just
different reflections.
There should be
one reflecting this place.
But there're so many of them.
They're everywhere!
I don't know which one it is!
Just where do you
think you're going!
Wait.
There it is!
Teo, it's behind the Baron!
That's it!
Okay, we've
gotta jump through it.
Mom!!!
You will not escape me!!
Teo!
Teoooo!
My mirrors.
Oh how I love all my mirrors.
The Baron!
Give her her mirror back!
Give it back!
Teoooooo!
Hey bro...
What happened, Boss...?
I think Teo...
...has done somethin' awesome.
Mister Arch Bishop!
Arch Bishop, sir!
Arch Bishop sir?!
Ow ow ow!
Your Benevolent Highness!
We're looking for you.
It's so cold...
Your...
your Highness...?
Huh?
Who's this?
No... no... don't look at me!
Please, wait for us sir!
Wait!
Teo!
Teo?
Teo...
Come on wake up.
Haru...
It didn't break.
What?
Look at you!
Look!
There they are!
They did it!
Thanks again.
Teo...
...you're far from
neglected junk.
You too.
Promise we'll meet again.
I promise.
As long as you don't forget me.
Why would I ever neglect you?
You'll be a precious memory
for the rest of my life Teo.
Goodbye.
What?
Oww...
Weird...
...no time has passed at all.
Hey Dad...
it's me, Haruka.
Oh, hey Haru.
About...
...earlier...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Huh?
When I got mad.
Oh, okay.
This is kinda
outta character for you.
You all right?
What?
Yeah...
I'm fine.
Oh...
...by the way...
...about dinner.
You wanna go somewhere?
Huh?
Yeah, sure.
It's been a while since just
the two of us had dinner.
Is that what you want?
Well then you pick the place.
You don't care?
No, your choice.
Well, what I want...
...is a hamburger patty!
Man... I'm so hungry!
♪ closing song ♪