[gasps]
Looks like the royal forces
finally found this place.
[DENNIS]
Yeah.
[LUKE] We've received a
communique from our recon unit.
They've found the
Scrapped Princess' party
near the mountains.
[PETERS-STAHL] Two more days
until the day of prophecy.
We'll do whatever it takes to
eliminate the Scrapped Princess
in order to appease
the wrath of god.
Have all of the Colossus units
converge on the mountains.
[SOCOM]
Call for a crusade if you like,
but we would prefer to
use a more reliable means
of eliminating the
Providence Breaker.
This is your final opportunity.
We will send an emissary.
[HOGUE]
Sir.
[FORSYTH]
Huh?
Chris.
Please forgive me for startling
you like this, Your Highness.
That's all right.
[FORSYTH]
How is my sister doing?
[gasps]
It was your team, wasn't it?
They say that you smuggled
the Scrapped Princess
out of the castle.
Your Highness.
I can't bring myself to believe
that she will destroy the world.
[FORSYTH]
I see...
So, you've come all this way
just so you could
say goodbye to me.
[CHRIS] Take care
of yourself, Your Highness.
[birds chirping]
[grunts]
[PACIFICA] You old folks
sure wake up early.
Shut up already.
It's beautiful.
I suppose so.
Tomorrow, when I
finally do turn 16,
do you think the sun will
come up just like always?
[PACIFICA]
Tomorrow morning,
when the sun rises again,
I wonder what's going
to happen to me.
[SHANNON]
Beats me.
You'll probably make
another lousy breakfast.
[PACIFICA]
It's hard to believe, isn't it?
I might cause trouble for
everyone in the world
just because I'll
turn 16 tomorrow.
[PACIFICA]
But, even so...
I still don't want to die.
Is that really selfish of me?
So wanting to live
is being selfish now?
I think that's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard.
[PACIFICA] Even if that
person was a criminal?
Even if it meant that
lots of people would die
if they stayed alive?
[SHANNON]
I'd still forgive them.
Hey there you two!
Pacifica, Shannon!
Breakfast is ready!
Okay!
C'mon! Let's go, Shannon!
Time to eat.
[SHANNON]
Uh.
[PACIFICA laughing]
[SHANNON]
Hey!
Good morning, Your Highness.
I hope you were able to
sleep well last night.
[FORSYTH]
Huh? Yes.
[HOGUE]
I'm glad to hear that.
I was deeply concerned that the
cries of the injured people
might've kept Your
Highness awake.
[FORSYTH]
Injured people?
[HOGUE] There has been a steady
stream of people arriving
who were injured in the
calamity at the capital.
So we have been using
part of the temple
as a makeshift hospital.
If you'd be willing,
perhaps Your Highness
could take some time
and go and visit them.
[gasps]
[TOWNSPEOPLE groan]
[HOGUE] They come here
because they have no money
to pay for medical treatment.
Those who have survived this
long will heal eventually.
However...
[FORSYTH] There are
still a great many more
who have lost their lives.
As long as the Scrapped
Princess still exists,
God's wrath will
rain from the heavens
and even more people will
be injured and killed.
Your Highness,
please act as an emissary.
Become god's messenger...
in order to save your people.
So, what are you so happy about?
Oh, this and that.
[PACIFICA]
Like what and what?
It's Chris.
He said, "Thank you," when I
brought him his breakfast.
I see! Heh, heh.
What are you grinning
about now, huh?
[SENES]
Hey.
The Royal Forces are
beginning to close in on us.
Get your butts back to camp now.
So, who cares about that?
Now look here, kid...
What am I supposed to do?
Washing the laundry's
all I'm really good for.
[SENES]
Maybe she was right after all.
I guess that's your
way of fighting.
What's that mean?
It's something Eirote said.
She once told me that everybody
has their own way of fighting.
Really?
My whole life,
all I've ever wanted to
do is change the world.
I swore I'd smash this
rotten world to pieces.
And yet... It's still pretty
far from being perfect.
But, maybe this world
isn't so bad after all.
When this ends, would you take
me to your village one day?
Sure! Of course, any time.
[WINIA]
I'll come, too!
Sure, sure! Come on over!
I'll cook you a huge feast!
[WINIA] That's okay.
I'll do the cooking.
[PACIFICA]
Uh! That's so mean!
[SHANNON]
Hey, watch what you're doing.
Those are supposed to be
finely sliced. Cut 'em thinner.
[LEO]
Oh. Right.
[PACIFICA]
You're so nitpicky, Shannon.
Mr. Berkens?!
Huh?!
It's Pops!
It's good to see you, Pops!
[BERKENS] Good to see
you too, little lady.
He says that he's got a message
for you. What do you think?
He's all right.
What's the message?
[BERKENS] Price Forsyth
says he wants to meet
with the little lady.
So... Who's this Price Forsyth?
Prince Forsyth is
your twin brother.
[RAQUEL gasps]
[CHRIS] But why does he want
to see her all of a sudden?
Well, his sister's
birthday's comin' up soon,
and he'd like to meet her
just once before she turns 16.
[gasps]
Your answer?
[PACIFICA]
My answer...?
How am I supposed to react
to that at a time like this?
I am the
Scrapped Princess, remember?
And he's the prince of a country
that's been doing everything
it can to try and kill me.
I guess you can
call him my brother,
but it's not like
we've ever met.
I wonder why he picked
now to want to see me.
What kind of guy is he?
If Prince Forsyth
became our king,
I doubt that he would go to
war without a good reason.
The prince has been concerned
about you for as long
as I've known him.
Perhaps he just wants to meet
you and see for himself.
See if you really are the poison
that will destroy this world.
[BERKENS] I'm supposed to
return to the holy city
with your answer.
We'll need to make
arrangements if you accept.
Otherwise, I'll just
head back to Grendel.
Think it over till this evening,
then give me your answer.
[PACIFICA]
What is it?
[LEO]
Oh, nothing. I was just...
[sighs]
thinking about how life
is so full of troubles.
Oh, right.
You were agonizing over what
chivalry is one last time.
[LEO]
Yes.
Did you figure it out?
[LEO]
No. Not yet.
[PACIFICA]
Oh.
[LEO] I always thought
that there had to be
a sense of justice that
everyone could believe in.
But, recently,
I've been thinking that
maybe there's no such thing
as one idea of justice
that works for everybody.
If I believed in
what the kingdom
and the Church of Mauser
told me is right,
then that certainly
wouldn't be what's right
from your point
of view, Pacifica.
Because of all that,
I no longer knew what was
right and what was wrong.
But, I realized something.
I realized that all
I really wanted to do
was protect you, Pacifica.
[PACIFICA]
Huh...
Oh, sorry.
That's enough talk about me.
I originally came down here
to try and help you out
with your problems.
[PACIFICA]
You wanted to give me advice?
Well, I'm not sure if
I'd be of much help.
[PACIFICA]
Of course you would.
You really mean that?!
When we talk together, Leo,
worrying about things seems
so stupid all of a sudden.
[LEO] Really?! They do?!
I'm so glad to hear that!
[chuckles]
And then there's the prince.
I hope he's a good person, too.
[LEO]
I'm sure he is!
Don't worry. Once he meets you,
I'm certain that he'll
like you immediately.
[PACIFICA]
You think so?
[LEO] All right, then.
I'll decide for you.
Let's meet him.
Huh?!
[LEO]
You only live once, after all.
Even if you fail spectacularly,
isn't it better to try and fail
than regret not trying at all?
Wow, Leo!
You never change, do you?
Sorry about that.
[PACIFICA]
That headband.
Uh, yes?
[PACIFICA] That isn't the
one I tied around your head
back when we first met, is it?
Um...
Yes.
You should wash it.
[LEO]
I will. I'm sorry.
[PACIFICA]
Leo?
What is it?
Thanks a lot.
[chuckles]
[FAFAL] They're just barely
inside firing range.
I wonder if they're
planning on launching
a full-out offensive at dawn.
Once the sun goes down,
we should make our move.
[WINIA]
Uh.
[CHRIS]
Here.
Oh. Thank you so much.
Chris!
What is it?
Pacifica.
It's just that she didn't...
She couldn't remember the
man she was staying with,
back when she had amnesia.
Pacifica didn't actually come
out and say it or anything, but,
I think that she
really cared for him.
She cared for him,
but she doesn't remember him.
Not at all.
[CHRIS]
And yet,
you're able to remember that
person clearly, aren't you?
[gasps]
[CHRIS]
Someone once told me
that people are the
sort of creatures
who can forget painful
things that happen to them.
That they can go on living
precisely because they forget.
I apologize for how I acted.
Ignoring you, I mean.
I didn't want to
get you involved.
This Scrapped Princess
business is dangerous.
I know.
It's okay.
It's all okay now.
What's the matter?
[SHANNON]
Leo said something to me once.
That she's got
a nobility to her
that you can't
find in commoners.
Guess it's no surprise.
I mean after all, she does
just happen to be a princess.
[RAQUEL] Did you want her to say
that she wouldn't go meet him?
If she does decide that
she wants to go there
and see her real brother,
I've got no right to
stop her now, do I?
Hey, tell me something?
What makes someone a
real brother anyway?
Who's always going to
be your little sister?
Is anything really
going to change?
Guess not.
[PACIFICA]
Hey Shannon!
Raquel!
[panting]
Um. Listen.
I've decided.
I wanna meet this guy.
I'd like to see this
twin brother of mine.
Of course. You should see him.
Mm.
So, shall we go, Your Highness?
Prince Forsyth.
Is something the matter?
Not at all.
[footsteps]
[PETERS-STAHL]
Don't mind me.
I just came out here to
get a little fresh air.
Yes, sir.
So, what's that?
[LUKE] Something my wife
gave to me when I left.
She told me to sow these
seeds as soon as I came back.
They're yellow violets.
My wife's favorite flower.
You found yourself a fine wife.
[LUKE]
And you, General?
Unfortunately for me, I haven't
been able to find someone
to spend my days with.
It looks like I'll end
up married to this.
[footsteps]
[SLEY]
Excuse me, Sir.
There's a message from Grendel.
As expected, the target's
been changed.
[PETERS-STAHL]
Excellent.
We will commence
our attack at sunset.
Hi, Zefiris.
[ZEFIRIS]
So you're going, then?
Huh?
[ZEFIRIS] It will be
midnight in a few hours.
You need to be on your guard.
I pray nothing bad happens.
Please be careful.
Thanks, Zefiris.
[PACIFICA]
Um... I guess...
[FORSYTH]
Well then, you must be Pacifica.
[PACIFICA]
Uh, yes. Nice to meet you.
So, um...
Uh...
Um.
So, what kind of food
do you like to eat?!
Uh?
[PACIFICA]
I like eggs. Well, egg dishes.
And I really love omelets!
Wow, that's funny.
I like 'em, too.
Oh! I knew it! Maybe it's
because we're both twins.
[PACIFICA]
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry for all the
hardships I've put you through.
Forgive me.
No! I don't blame you at all.
All this time, they've been
hunting you like some animal.
I've tried, but there was
nothing I could do to help you.
My brother...
[PACIFICA]
Please don't worry about it.
Some parts of my life have
been rough, it's true,
but not everything.
[PACIFICA] That's my big
brother and sister over there.
And those are some
of my friends.
They seem like they're
very nice people.
They are.
[gasps]
[FORSYTH]
I'm sorry.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[FORSYTH]
I truly am so sorry.
At last, I've met you, but...
[PACIFICA gasping]
[PACIFICA]
Why...?
[grunts]
[CHRIS]
Prince Forsyth!
[WINIA]
No!
Hey, wait a minute!
They're aiming at the church.
They wouldn't!
[FAFAL] I don't get it.
The prince is in there!
Pacifica...
Pacifica, no!
[SHANNON]
Pacifica!
[gasps]
Uh?
Pacifica.
[ZEFIRIS] Shannon. I may
be able to help her
through the use of my phase
interference capabilities.
It will take time though.
[gasps]
[SOCOM?]
I won't allow you to interfere.
[gasps]
Barrier.
Barrier, protect us!
[SOCOM] This was unexpected,
but very convenient for us.
Shannon Cassul.
[gasps]
[SOCOM] You and the
Dragoon will come with me.
If you refuse,
I will burn the capital
to the ground instantly.
Shannon...
[SHANNON whimpering]
[SHANNON]
Raquel. Take care of Pacifica.
Now, Zefiris.
[roaring]
[PETERS-STAHL]
God's messenger has appeared.
Step up the bombardment!
Prepare to launch at once!
But how...?
How could this have happened?
[WINIA crying]
Prince Forsyth. Why?
[FORSYTH]
Please forgive me...
As their prince, I had a
duty to protect my people.
But at least... I wanted
to die... with her.
[sobs]
[RAQUEL]
Pacifica...
[RAQUEL] Pacifica has been
stabbed by her brother.
Although her sister lies
bleeding before her,
Raquel can do
nothing to save her.
And Shannon, who must
save the capital,
is forced to fuse with Zefiris
in order to fight
the Peacemakers.
There are only 15 words
left in this final preview.
Next time, the finale
of Scrapped Princess.
"Symphony of the Protectors."
See you next time!