[LEO]
Miss Pacifica is...
...the Scrapped Princess...
[SHANNON]
You're awake.
It looks like you're
doing much better now.
You seem to be passed
the worst of it,
but it take it easy for a while.
Shouldn't the two of
you get some sleep?
A sick person doesn't need
to worry about others.
[RAQUEL] I'll bring you
something good to eat.
You have to build
up your strength.
[DOYLE] Looks like most of the
poison is out of your system.
You're healthy enough
to get out of bed now.
Just to be safe, take those
medicinal herbs one more time.
Sir Doyle...
You know, don't you? Who I am.
Yeah.
You left the Amber
Knights a long time ago
because of the
Scrapped Princess.
[DOYLE]
Yeah, that's right.
I'm the man who threw you
into a ravine 15 years ago
when you were just a baby.
And I don't expect to be
forgiven after all this time
just because I healed you.
Go on, you don't
have to hold back.
I'm sure there's plenty
you'd like to say to me.
I'm very sorry...
[PACIFICA I guess I turned your
life upside down, didn't I?
Sorry about that...
So you're apologizing?
But why? I'm the man
who tried to kill you.
How is it that a girl like you,
after all you've been through,
can be so strong?
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[DOYLE]
Deep down, I was terrified.
I thought that fighting
for my ideal of justice
meant that I had to
crush any other justice
that seemed to threaten it.
I was afraid that one day,
I would make a
mistake so horrible
that it could never be undone.
I was so frightened, I ran away.
But you...
I appreciate your concern,
but your words of apology
are enough for me.
You already carry the
burden of a cruel destiny,
and if you were to shoulder
the sins of my past,
then I couldn't go on
living as a human being.
Sir Doyle...
[RAQUEL] Are you sure we can't
give you a ride home, Sir Doyle?
[DOYLE] Thank you, but I'll
take my time and walk back.
[SHANNON]
Thank you for your help.
[DOYLE]
Just make sure to survive this.
That's all I can
really say to you.
Yes, sir.
No matter what.
--[snap]
--[LEO] Huh?
[PACIFICA yells]
Be careful! That's dangerous!
Sure it was, but your guard
was completely down, Leo.
You'll never make it as a knight
if you can't sense an attack.
[PACIFICA] Here, take a look!
I'm feeling perfectly fine now!
Although, don't you think
it was a little cold of you
not to visit me even once?
[LEO]
Well...
I see now!
Your words of love and
devotion to me were all lies!
You were toying with
my heart, weren't you?!
But I wasn't!
It's just... that I...
Don't worry, I know.
[LEO]
Huh?
Thank you, Leo. And I don't
just mean for getting me herbs.
Travelling all this way with
you has been a lotta fun.
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you about me.
I wasn't trying to deceive you,
it's just hard to tell
people who I am.
So I'm sorry.
Where's Leo?
Don't know. But his
horse is gone, too.
I see...
[SHANNON]
The next time we run into him,
we're gonna have
to be on our guard.
He might take a swing
at you outta the blue.
[PACIFICA]
But, Shannon!
Now that he's found out that
you're the Scrapped Princess,
anything is possible.
What're you saying?! Leo
would never do such a thing!
Anybody we meet can turn on
us, no matter who they are!
I don't want a repeat of what
happened yesterday, understand?!
Ah, it's you.
Sir Barrett, wait!
I... I don't know what
I'm supposed to do now...
If Miss Pacifica
truly is the poison
that will destroy the world,
then as a knight, I should...
And yet--
[DOYLE] I'm not a knight
anymore. I'm a doctor.
I'm not here to sort out
your doubts for you.
A doctor swears an oath to
help people no matter what,
even if his patient
is vicious or evil.
Of course, you might be killed
the instant you save them.
You talked of chivalry.
You described it as
wielding your sword
in the name of justice.
If that's true, then your
duty is to cut off her head.
That should earn you a
medal, at the very least.
That's the nature of
the path you've chosen.
[PACIFICA]
What d'you suppose
the Scrapped Princess
really is anyway?
[SHANNON]
Hmm?
I wonder how many people
will end up being hurt
because I'm alive.
[FORSYTH]
Say, Christopher,
if my little sister
is really still alive,
do you suppose that
she would look like me?
Yes, she would.
The poison that will
destroy the world...
What do you suppose that
revelation meant, exactly?
[CHRIS]
I'm not sure.
If it got out that
she was still alive,
I suppose there would be another
royal edict for her death.
I'm sure that our mother is
worried about her as well.
Are you referring to the queen?
Of course, I haven't seen my
mother in quite some time.
[door opens]
[FORSYTH]
Father!
I'm speaking with a
friend at the moment.
[KING]
Who is that with you?
Lift your face.
[CHRIS]
Yes, Sire.
My name is Christopher
Bairach, Your Majesty.
I am at your service.
Bairach's adopted son. Hmm...
Surprising, isn't it?
It's always been that way
between my father and me.
It's sad, but my
father hates me.
I was thinking, that assassin
with the instrument...
You mean the Silencer?
[PACIFICA] Do you think
he'll try to attack us again?
I don't think so.
He finally played nice and
agreed to withdraw back there.
Please don't tell me how you
got that guy to play nice.
It'll turn my stomach.
Who the heck is that?
Shannon.
[PACIFICA]
Hmm?
[GALIL]
Step forward, zguardians.
[SHANNON]
What the...?
What am I doing?
What's happening?
[SHANNON] This guy... This
guy's no ordinary human!
[GALIL]
It's futile.
I, Galil the Peacemaker,
have decided to get
personally involved.
It will not be like
the last time.
[SHANNON]
Like last time?
[SHANNON] He was the one
responsible for that?!
[PACIFICA]
Hey, Shannon?
[GALIL]
Scrapped Princess, do not move.
I will force these two to
kill each other if I must.
Humans have no choice but
to obey me. This is the law.
This is how it was and
how it always shall be.
[PACIFICA]
Big Brother?! Big Sister?!
[LEO screams]
[LEO] Damn it! Damn it!
What good is justice?!
What's the point of chivalry?!
[PACIFICA]
Shannon?! Raquel?!
Miss Pacifica...
Leo, I need you to help me fi--
[KEYDARF]
Silence.
That was the language of their
love for each other, huh?
How dull.
The Silencer!
[KEYDARF]
Well, well.
What were you doing with
that sword just now?
That young lady
next to you there
is the poison that
will destroy the world.
You weren't about to kill her
by chopping her in half,
now were you, boy?
Be quiet! I was just--
Your name's Silencer,
that right?
[KEYDARF]
Hmm?
[PACIFICA] Can bugs also be able
to be used to look for people?
[KEYDARF]
Uh... Well, yeah. I suppose.
[PACIFICA]
Will you make a deal?
[KEYDARF]
Hmm? What deal?
[PACIFICA]
I'll give you one of my hands.
Then you'll be able to collect
the bounty on me, am I right?
Miss Pacifica.
So you're saying that
you'll give me one of hands
if I agree to let you go
and say that I killed you?
[PACIFICA]
No, I'm not.
[KEYDARF]
Hm?
I said that I wanted to deal.
I'll agree to give you one
of my hands, however...
...in return for that,
you have to promise me
that you'll use your bugs
to find out where my brother
and sister have been taken.
You want me to what?
Leo. Can I ask a favor?
One last thing?
[PACIFICA]
Cut it off.
[gasps]
Please, Leo! Quickly!
I just watched Raquel and
Shannon get kidnapped.
This is all I can really do
to try and help them now.
I'm in a hurry.
[PACIFICA]
Please, Leo.
[LEO]
I won't.
I don't carry a sword in
order to do things like that.
A sword-- My sword...
...isn't used for cutting
down innocent people!
[KEYDARF sighs]
[KEYDARF]
Um...
Hey, look, I think there's been
a little misunderstanding here.
I know when to cut my
losses and call it quits.
Well, to be perfectly frank,
I sort of enjoy living.
And I don't relish the idea of
your siblings coming after me
for revenge because I hurt you.
But I have to find out
where he took them!
I'll help, but I'll do
it without the deal.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
The maiden offers her hand,
the knight his life,
and the poet will offer his
soul in return, like this.
[screeching]
[buzzing]
Fly, my eyes and ears!
[GALIL]
Lord Browning.
Here, in one of the fortresses
your kind was so proud of,
your last hope will
be extinguished.
Without her guardians,
I expect that the humans will
exterminate the lawbreaker.
[GALIL] Hmph. A relic from
the ancient world, huh?
What can a mere
bug do against me?
[ZEFIRIS]
Your disdain and contempt
for absolutely
everything but yourself
is what makes you a fool.
[KEYDARF]
Looks like they found them.
This one will show you the
way, so follow him close.
Thank you so much,
old man Silencer!
[KEYDARF]
Huh?
Old Man?
[GALIL]
I see now...
You tapped into the bug's
communications net,
didn't you, Zefiris?
[ZEFIRIS] The only one who
may call me by that name
is my D-Knight master.
A second-rate product like you
has no right to call
me by that name.
[GALIL]
A second-rate product you say?
Don't push me.
[BOTH gasps]
That's him!
He's over there! Hurry!
Leo?
What're you doing, Leo?
What's wrong with you?
[GALIL]
Second class divine retribution
enforcement configuration,
engage.
[LEO]
It's no use... I can't.
I can't do it. I can't disobey
my master's wishes.
What's wrong with you? That's
nothing but a stupid monster!
It's hopeless! I can't fight
against something like that!
[gasps]
Leo!
[LEO]
Miss Pacifica...
[GALIL] I realize that
you had been planning
to turn one of these guardians
into your new master,
but unfortunately for you, they
are under the rule of my law.
You have no hope of winning.
[PACIFICA]
Big Brother!
Big Sister!
[SHANNON] Does this mean...
that I can't protect her...?
[SHANNON]
He's just too powerful...
There's nothing I can
do to stop him...
[ZEFIRIS] Did you not
swear to protect her?
[SHANNON] You're right.
I swore I would protect her.
I promised that I would
protect her against anything
that tried to take
her away from us.
I want power...
The power to save her...
Enough power to change destiny.
Power to fight,
even if it makes the whole world
and god himself my enemy.
[ZEFIRIS]
If that is truly your will,
then I shall obey my chosen one.
Though it be temporary,
I recognize thee as fit to be
my controller, the D-Knight.
I, the ARFFI M4 Dragoon, serial
number 26 known as Zefiris,
shall be thy blade and slay the
enemy that stands before you.
[BOTH gasp]
[PACIFICA]
Shannon! Raquel!
[LEO]
Look out!
[GALIL]
Perish.
[roars]
[GALIL]
A Dragon?
[SHANNON]
What's happened to me?
Why do I suddenly
have this power?
[SHANNON, ZEFIRIS]
Protect our little sister.
[GALIL] I'll tear you apart
into subatomic particles.
[RAQUEL]
Barrier, protect us!
[GALIL]
Curse you!
What?!
[beeping, ringing]
[ZEFIRIS] I'm a weapon sent
to you from a time long past
to help you in your struggle
to protect your sister.
The last dragon,
hidden in a fold of the
fabric of space and time,
I have survived all these
years in order to aid you
once you possessed
the will to fight god.
The will to fight god?
But I don't understand.
All we did was...
[ZEFIRIS]
For now, that does not matter.
But know this: I am not
completely restored.
I have yet to regain
my full power.
The time I can spend
in this world is limited.
Also, I cannot interfere
in quarrels between humans.
I am not omnipotent
by any means.
However, when the
time comes for you
to fight the three
remaining Peacemakers,
and when you are finally ready
to fight the lord god Mauser,
you may call upon me.
Call my true name,
the one only my master
is allowed to speak.
Call Zefiris.
Zefiris.
[ZEFIRIS]
When that time comes,
I will become the blade
of D-Knight Shannon Cassul
and slay thine enemies.
A D-Knight?
[ZEFIRIS]
I have been waiting patiently
for more than 5,000 years
to assist you in your
struggle with god.
But I...
[ZEFIRIS] Until we meet again...
my temporary master.
[PACIFICA]
Big Brother?
What is she?
What is she... the
Scrapped Princess?
[LEO]
I was thinking...
I might go back to Taurus
and stay there for a while.
[SHANNON] Thanks for everything
you've done for her.
[RAQUEL]
We'll miss you a lot, Leo.
Miss Pacifica. My heart
is still very troubled.
I just don't know
whether chivalry is real
or if it's only some
sort of illusion.
However, I still want to
believe there is a justice
that everyone can have faith in.
But once I find the
answer to that question,
then that justice might force
me to become your enemy.
That's okay. I don't mind.
Until we meet again.
Till then.
[LEO]
Hyah!
[KEYDARF]
Those who are pursued,
and those who go off
in pursuit of something,
they both part ways.
And yet... And yet...
Hmm...
That was sort of lame.
So much for poetry.
[RAQUEL] Shannon comes
across a little girl
just standing in the rain.
The poor thing has no memories
of where she came from
except that her name is Cz.
This looks like it will be a
melancholy, rain-soaked story.
Next time on Scrapped Princess,
"Waltz of the Abandoned
Dog of a Girl."
See you next time!