Let's go.
We're getting out of here.
[LEO]
What?
It looks like
they're onto us now.
He probably got a
look at your face, too.
Why did you even open
the door for him?!
[FURET] If I hadn't,
he would've broken it down.
He's probably out there calling
for reinforcements as we speak.
Once they show up,
they'll storm the place.
We can't stay here any longer.
You're kidding.
But why?
[FURET]
What are you doing? Hurry up!
[gasps]
Right.
[knocking]
[SOLDIER A]
It's the Royal Forces, open up!
Open the door!
[SOLDIERS]
One... two...
[grunting]
[WINIA]
What is this place?
[FURET]
Beats me.
Looks like it's been
here a long time, though.
You mean, you knew
about this place before?
Yeah.
What's the matter?
This is a theatre.
A place where humans
escape into fantasy.
[SHANNON]
True enough.
The Cz I know
would've enjoyed it.
What, again?
[SHANNON]
Hm?
Somebody was in here yesterday
asking the same thing.
He wanted to know if
there was a blonde girl
with blue eyes around.
What'd she do, break the
law or something?
[SHANNON]
Shut your mouth.
[MAN A]
Huh?
[BERKENS]
Now don't you worry.
The patrols are still
out lookin' for her.
That means the Royal Forces
haven't caught her yet.
[RAQUEL] But where in
the world did she go?
She'll be okay.
Come on, that boy
she was staying with
looked like he had a good head
on his shoulders, didn't he?
I guess you're right.
[BERKENS] Anyway, they might
end up coming back here.
So let's wait for 'em
a little while longer.
[horse neighs]
[gasps]
Parabellum?
Parabellum!
What in the world
are you doing here?
I asked the innkeeper
to take care of you.
[SOLDIER B]
Who the hell are you?
Huh?
This area's off limits
to the general public.
If you've got no business here,
then clear out.
No, you misunderstand, sir.
This horse is my-- Uh...
[SOLDIER B]
Your what?
[LEO] Uh... Well-- Actually...
I-It's nothing. Really.
[LEO laughs nervously]
[SOLDIER B]
Hm?
What do you mean
you can't find them?!
We've confiscated
every stray horse
in the Capital
to slow them down!
We've also doubled our patrols.
They have to be hiding
in the city somewhere.
Find them. No matter what
it takes! Is that clear?
The future of the
Kingdom depends on it!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[LEO]
This complicates things.
I can't believe that Miss Winia
and I are wanted fugitives, too.
Plus, that guy upstairs told
me that someone was just here
asking if anyone had seen
a blonde-haired
girl with blue eyes.
[WINIA] There's a good
chance they'll find us
even if we stay down here.
At any rate, we have to get
out of the Capital quickly.
Look, guys...
There's still one thing that
I just don't understand.
Why do I have to
run away just because
I'm the Scrapped Princess
or whatever?
Uh, what do you mean?
It doesn't make sense.
I'm supposed to be
a Princess, right?
So why would they wanna
try and take me prisoner?
Your mere existence represents a
serious threat to the Kingdom.
[PACIFICA]
But why is that?
What's so threatening
about me anyway?
[FURET]
Beats me.
But the Church of Mauser says
that the Scrapped Princess
will bring destruction and
devastation to the world.
[gasps]
If I had stayed in the military,
then I'd probably be
hunting you down, too.
[WINIA]
You used to be a soldier?
[PACIFICA screams]
[ALL gasp]
[FURET]
What's wrong with you?
You just took the egg!
[FURET] Yeah, but there are
plenty more eggs left in there.
But that one was cooked
just the way I like it,
and I was about to pull it out!
Give me a break;
just grab another one.
[PACIFICA] You haven't bitten
into it yet, so hand it over.
No way! Forget it!
[LEO]
Um, Miss Pacifica?
It's Pamela.
Miss Pamela... If you like,
you can have mine.
[PACIFICA]
You've gotta be kidding.
That one's almost raw.
The outside of the egg
needs to be much browner.
That's why I want
the one that he took!
[FURET]
Give it a rest!
[KEYDARF]
The corn's done, everybody.
[WINIA]
Please forgive us, Keydarf.
Not only are you hiding us,
but we're imposing on
you for dinner, too.
No, please, it's fine.
Don't you worry about it.
If you make too
much noise though,
the owner's gonna get mad at me.
[PACIFICA]
I said, hand it over!
[FURET]
And I said, no way!
[PACIFICA]
Give it!
[WINIA]
Both of you, just shut up!
[JILL]
What's this all about, Chris?
[DENNIS] We know where the
Scrapped Princess is hiding now,
so why aren't we
moving in on the place?
[FAFAL gasps]
Now, now, be patient.
I'm sure that our
little Chris here
has something
special up his sleeve.
So is that true, Chris?
[CHRIS]
I'm sorry.
But to tell you the truth,
I don't know what to do.
We're supposed to hand
the Scrapped Princess
over to the Kingdom,
but I'm not sure that's the
right thing to do anymore.
That's all well and good,
but at this rate,
if we don't do something,
the Obstinate Arrows
will be disbanded.
Then what's gonna happen to us
if we have to break up the team?
[SUTTON sniffles]
Hey... Come on,
Sutton, don't cry.
[SUTTON]
I'm not crying!
[PACIFICA]
The thing is,
if everybody in the
Kingdom is actually
trying to hunt me
down and kill me,
then how far are we
going to have to run
before we can really be safe?
Is there any place
left that's safe?
Well, what if we went
over to the Giat Empire?
Then we wouldn't have to worry
about the Royal Forces
chasing us, right?
That might've been true earlier.
But not after the
Ginnungagap incident.
Relations with the Giat
Empire are strained now.
Trying to leave the country
would be far too dangerous.
[KEYDARF]
Well in that case...
How about going to
the city of Grendel?
[FURET]
Hm?
The city of Grendel?
You mean the Grendel that's also
the main temple of
the Church of Mauser?!
[KEYDARF] It's still
inside Leinwan territory,
but that's the one
region of the country
that's totally autonomous.
Even the troops of the Royal
Forces are strictly limited
in the type of weapons that they
can carry inside the holy city.
And I bet that you
running away to Grendel
would be the absolute last thing
they would expect you to do.
I've heard that a special
combat unit, the Purgers,
is stationed in the Holy City.
Still, I think it's better
than trying to go up against
the entire Royal Forces,
don't you agree?
Guys, I'm sorry.
Really, about everything.
I don't understand everything
that's going on here.
But you're risking
so much for me.
What're you talking about?!
[WINIA] Now that it's
turned out like this,
what else could we
do but help you?
[PACIFICA sighs]
I'm sorry.
[LEO] Miss Raquel must be
worried sick about us.
If we all suddenly disappear,
she'd think the
worst had happened.
[KEYDARF] That scary woman's
in the Capital, too?
[LEO]
Yes, she is.
If only I had asked them what
inn they were staying at
when I ran into them
at the food stand.
Can we afford to wait a
little before we leave?
[PACIFICA]
No. Let's go.
If we wait around any longer,
they're going to catch us.
If I run into your sister,
I'll be sure to tell her.
[FURET] Either way,
we're going to need horses.
Walking is out of the question.
[WINIA]
But from what Leo says,
the security out there
is awfully tight.
Every defense has
its vulnerable points.
I agree that we're going to have
to go and steal some horses,
but what if we're spotted
trying to and get caught?
That's true...
Why not wear disguises?
This one is perfect!
Winia, I think
you'd look amazing
in something daring like this.
[WINIA]
I don't know...
What is it?
Excuse me?
You have something
you wanna say?
I need to know something.
Is Miss Pamela
important to you, too?
Are you willing to risk
your life to protect her?
What's gotten into you?
[LEO]
Everybody in the Kingdom
wants the Scrapped
Princess dead, right?
And yet, here you are
putting your life on the line
in order to protect her.
Well yeah, I guess I am.
Maybe it's just
a force of habit.
Huh?
[FURET] When I was a bouncer,
I would let people go
who were on the
run or in trouble.
Is that the only reason?
What's yours?
What's my reason?
[FURET]
Well, it sounds to me
like she's pretty
important to you.
Important enough
that you're willing to
throw away everything
to protect her.
[gasps]
[FURET sighs]
I don't know if you're
an apprentice knight,
but there's no chance you'll
ever become a real knight now.
[LEO]
But why not?
Why do you think?
Properly speaking,
your duty is to cut off
the head of the Scrapped
Princess and bring it in,
isn't it?
[gasps]
You believe a knight's
duty is to kill people?
I don't believe that's
truly a knight's purpose.
I can't believe it.
[FURET]
Hmph.
[PACIFICA]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
So tell me, how do I look?
Huh?
Is something wrong?
Not really.
[PACIFICA]
Well?
[FURET]
Hm? Oh...
You could at least try to
say something nice about it.
[FURET]
Golly, it's so wonderful.
[PACIFICA grunts]
Just forget it!
There's no point in
showing off to you.
What are you doing?
Oh! Well, we're both
looking for disguises.
No need for that.
We've picked yours out already.
[LEO]
Huh?
Ta-da!
[PACIFICA giggles]
Resistance is useless.
[PACIFICA]
Maybe he needs more make up.
You can forget it!
[KEYDARF sighs]
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
You're so cute!
It's not just flattery;
that outfit really suits you.
I don't care what you think;
I don't like it!
Hey! Nice young girls
aren't supposed to
speak to people so rudely.
And what would you know about
being a nice young girl?
Oh, just shut up.
When a lady tells you to
do something, you do it!
[FURET]
Which one of us is the lady?
[PACIFICA]
Hush, you!
[SOLDIER C]
Hm?
Hey, wait a minute!
Hey!
This way!
[giggles]
[BOTH laugh]
[LEO] We'll go out and see
if we can steal some horses.
You two be patient
and wait here.
[PACIFICA] You're not gonna
do it in your disguises?
You're no fun!
[FURET] How're we supposed
to move in those things?
You better come back here
without hurting yourself.
Sure. Don't you worry about me.
Who said I was
worried about you?
If you get hurt out there,
it'll make lots of work
for the rest of us.
Bandaging you and stuff.
Silly me.
Anyway, I don't want to see
so much as a scratch on you,
you hear me?
Yeah, yeah, Your Highness.
That hurt, you little twerp!
You be careful too, Leo.
Thanks, I'll make sure to.
[PACIFICA]
Hm?
[LEO]
Um, Miss Pamela?
Yeah?
I promise that I'll keep
you safe no matter what.
I realize I may still seem
unreliable to you right now,
but no one wants to
protect you more than I do.
No one.
[LEO]
Well, we're off!
See you both soon.
[giggles]
[SOLDIER D groaning]
Wow! Leo sounded like a man.
[laughs]
It's really surprising,
hearing him say all
that stuff outta the blue.
So what do you think then?
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[WINIA]
About Leo.
I'm flattered he feels that way,
but doesn't he just seem like a
spoiled little rich kid to you?
[WINIA] Oh... Well, he is
a noble, after all.
[PACIFICA]
Really?
Anyway, I think he's nice
and all, but still...
[WINIA] You like Furet
better than him, right?
And what makes you think that?!
[WINIA]
But you do, don't you?
No, I don't...
I think it's just that...
I don't like him or dislike him.
I don't care which
one of 'em you pick,
but make sure
it's a fast runner.
[LEO] I've already
got mine picked out.
--[FURET] Huh? Don't!
--[whistles]
[FURET gasps]
[LEO]
Parabellum!
So is this one your horse?
[FURET] Looks like they're not
gonna let us leave so easily,
after all.
So it would seem.
Let's go.
Right!
Now, look here.
All this is just making
me look stupid, you know?
Come here.
Why should I?
Rain cannot harm the
body of a Peacemaker,
so why does it
matter if I stay dry?
[SHANNON]
Do it anyway.
You're getting wet.
If you continue like this,
your body temperature will drop.
[SHANNON]
Just shut up.
[FURET]
This isn't working.
Take the reins.
Huh?!
They're a lot
faster than we are.
They're gonna catch up.
You go on ahead without me.
[LEO gasps]
[FURET]
If we let them follow us back,
this will all be for nothing.
Take this! I'll catch
up with you all later.
Make sure you tell Pamela that.
I'm gonna hold them off here.
But I can help you fight!
[FURET]
You idiot!
A knight must
protect his princess.
It's his duty no matter what!
Yes, but--
[FURET]
Go on, then.
Tell me who's going
to protect Pamela.
Say it!
I will.
[FURET]
I can't hear you!
Say it like you mean it!
I will!
Then protect her.
Yes, sir!
--[FURET groans]
--[LEO gasps]
[SOLDIER E gasps, groans]
[SOLDIER F screams]
Get out of here!
Hurry!
Get going!
[FURET groans]
[gasps]
[LEO]
Miss Pamela!
Get on quickly. You too,
Miss Winia. Please hurry!
[SOLDIER 7 groans]
Leo, where's Furet?
[LEO]
He'll catch up with us later.
[SOLDIER 8 groans]
[grunts]
[FURET groans]
--[thud]
--[groans]
[SLEY]
That's enough.
You know what happens
to anyone foolish enough
to try to defy the Kingdom...
So why did you do it?
[FURET groaning, wheezing]
[FURET]
Damn it...!
Damn it!
[FURET]
God... damn it...
[SHANNON] He must've been trying
to go somewhere very important.
[CZ]
Go where?
How can he hope to get there?
This man's life signs
have already ceased.
[SHANNON] Wherever it was
he was headed to before,
there's obviously no point
in him going there now.
He can't go,
even if he wants to.
Unless somebody tells him that,
he'll never be able
to rest in peace.
[PACIFICA]
Leopold?
[LEO]
Yes.
You haven't been able to look
me in the eye since we ran away.
[PACIFICA]
Furet's going to come, isn't he?
[PACIFICA] I'm gonna go
back and look for Furet!
[LEO]
You can't. Miss Pamela, stop!
[PACIFICA]
Let go!
Let go of me!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[LEO]
Who are all you people?!
[footsteps]
[WINIA gasps]
[RAQUEL] Pacifica is
captured by Chris's unit
and locked away in a dungeon.
It's a cramped, dark and smelly
place that's very unpleasant.
Pacifica, lonely and
in low spirits,
realizes that someone is
in the cell next door!
Why do you suppose this person
was thrown in the
dungeon next to her?
Next time on
Scrapped Princess,
"Aria of a Mother's Sorrow."
See you next time!