[ZEFIRIS crying]
[BECKNAM]
Zefy, please.
[ZEFIRIS]
Lord Becknam!
[BECKNAM]
I want you to survive.
[sobs]
[ZEFIRIS gasps]
[ZEFIRIS]
Lord Becknam...
[SHANNON groans]
[ZEFIRIS] If that is
what you wished of me...
...then I will.
[yawns]
[PACIFICA]
Huh...?
Oh, right. I forgot
where we were.
[door hisses]
[RAQUEL]
Good morning, Pacifica.
[PACIFICA]
Morning.
So, did you sleep well?
No... Not really.
[RAQUEL]
Oh...
[PACIFICA]
Say, Raquel?
[RAQUEL]
Hm?
Tell me something.
What's this war about?
Hey, maybe you'd like to
freshen up a little bit.
I could draw you a bath.
[PACIFICA]
Huh? I don't see a bath.
It looks to me
like this room here
has everything you'll
need to take a bath.
[PACIFICA]
Hm?
This is their idea of a bath?
[PACIFICA gasps]
[yelps]
What is this crazy thing?
What the heck's going on here?
Wait a minute!
What's supposed to be
happening now? I don't get it!
[yelps]
Quit it! Somebody help me!
[PACIFICA sighs]
Well, that was an ordeal.
Still... It's pretty amazing.
Yeah. It feels like a dream.
This whole place
is unbelievable.
It's almost like
everything on this ship
is beyond our imagination.
--[intercom beeps]
--[SENES] Are you awake?
Would you two mind coming
up here for a minute?
[BOTH]
Huh...?
[PACIFICA] Wow! Look at
the size of that crayfish!
You're wrong.
It's called a lobster.
They're very delicious.
What's the deal?
What do you hope to get out
of us by feeding us like this?
I should warn you right now that
we don't really know anything.
[SENES chuckles]
I didn't expect to get
any information from you.
I just wanted to make sure that
you're still committed
to going back home.
[SHANNON]
Hm?
[CZ]
Come to the capital of Leinwan.
You have a grace
period of 15 days,
and 1,000 people will die
every day you are late.
[SENES] Well, I'm headed to
Castle Sauer for my own reasons,
so I guess my asking you is a
bit of a moot point, isn't it?
Still... Are you
sure about all this?
It's not like we
really have a choice.
[SENES]
It's a trap; no doubt about it.
You must've known that this day
would come sooner or later
when you made the
whole world your enemy.
I guess we did.
[EIROTE] Besides Steyr,
two additional Artillery-types
will most likely be waiting
for you at the Capital.
There's also a chance
the people at the Capital
have been turned into proxies.
[SENES] You don't have
a prayer of winning.
Not when Steyr gave you so
much trouble by herself.
I don't intend to go down
without a fight, however.
I'm sure you don't.
But it seems foolish to go
riding in on this fortress.
You'll just escalate
the situation.
It's been escalating
for a very long time.
The fate of the world hinges
on what's going to happen next.
Although to you two,
it might seem like
you're just trying to
protect your little sister.
Are you sure you're one to talk?
It seems to me that
you're doing all of this
just because you're
out for revenge.
[SHANNON]
You're heading to Castle Sauer
after dropping off
most of your men.
That's not a very rational
decision in my book.
[SENES]
I won't deny that.
I'm going to avenge my men.
I can't think of any
better reason to go,
off the top of my head.
If you'd like, we could still
drop you off on land somewhere.
[SENES] Hey, Shannon Cassul,
tell me something.
What will you do if your
little sister is killed?
Raquel Cassul, what about you?
[RAQUEL chuckles]
It's very simple.
We'll never let that happen.
Huh. That's a good answer.
However, you should
face the facts.
You're about to walk straight
into the jaws of death
for the sake of a
thousand total strangers.
[chuckles]
[PACIFICA]
But we have to go.
We don't have any idea what
we're supposed to do anymore.
And I certainly can't
seem to figure out
what the right thing
to do is all the time.
But still...
Nothing will change
if we don't go.
If we do go, things might
work out for the best.
That's why, we have to go.
"Might" work out? I see.
You can't rally
the troops to fight
with something that
"might" work.
Well, I guess I don't
have much choice.
The Skid will continue with
its raid on Castle Sauer.
Is that all right with you?
Have the three of you
ever given any thought
to how this continent
actually got its name?
"Dustvin"...
I believe it meant "garbage can"
in the old language.
I dunno who came up with
that name originally,
but it's a pretty insulting
thing to be called, huh?
Humanity's been locked up in
this trash can of a world,
and now we're supposed
to rot like compost.
What do you mean
we're locked up?
[EIROTE] The creatures from
the Genesis myths that
the Church of Mauser likes
to refer to as "demons"
were actually the Dark Lord
Browning and his faction,
who created powerful weapons.
Wait a second. Let me
make sure I've got this.
The one's who fought the gods
were our distant ancestors?
[SENES]
That's right.
Long ago, ancient humans fought
what the Church of Mauser
calls "God" and lost.
[EIROTE]
Humanity was sealed away
and is now ruled by
the Church of Mauser.
We are under the constant
observation of the Peacemakers
who have reigned for
the last 5,000 years.
Back then, Browning and his
followers had access to power
that we can't even dream of.
In other words, this Skid
here as well as the Dragoons
are weapons created
by our ancestors.
All of humanity's original
knowledge and civilization
were stolen long ago.
And human beings
were restricted to
living only on this
continent of Dustvin.
In the intervening millennia,
humans forgot that they had
been sealed into this world.
Our current civilization
is modeled after
a period of history
called The Middle Ages
that existed about
6,000 years ago.
Humanity is forbidden from
developing its civilization
while under
Peacemaker observation.
The few remaining human
forces on the outside
have put together a plan
to liberate humanity.
In order for us to break
the seal on this world
and finally be set
free from our cage,
we must first defeat
those Peacemakers.
[SENES]
Five thousand years ago,
outside humans sent
the genetic code
from the three of
you into this world.
They also sent the Dragoons
who were meant to support you.
Using something called
"genetic engineering,"
your DNA was seeded
throughout this world
according to
precise calculations.
Five thousand years later,
it has borne fruit.
Their scientific efforts
have produced you,
the Providence Breaker
and her Guardians.
[EIROTE] Even the Grendel
Revelations are nothing more
than a regulatory mechanism
for controlling humanity
through the Church of Mauser.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[SENES]
Your powers allow you to resist
the Peacemakers'
administrative privileges.
Since Providence has
no effect on you,
your will can defeat them.
[EIROTE] In addition,
you can share your resistance
with other people, giving them
the desire to fight.
Also, the Peacemakers
are unable to kill you.
They have not been
given the authority
necessary to
terminate your life.
[SENES]
Pacifica Cassul...
It turns out that you're
humanity's only trump card.
[chuckles]
[SENES]
This must be a bit of a shock.
[PACIFICA gasps]
I'm sorry...
But could you explain
that to me again?
From the beginning?
[SENES grunts]
Why you little brat...!
Now, now, Princess Senes.
Fine, to put it in
very simple terms,
the people who fought and lost
against the gods 5,000 years ago
did not give up.
Through their continued efforts,
they produced the three of you
and the Dragoons, as well.
She explained it. But still...
It doesn't make a
whole lot of sense.
Guess the two of them
don't get it either.
I guess it can't be helped.
We'll have to take a little more
time to explain things to them.
[PILOT A]
Director! We're 30 hectares away
from Leinwan territorial waters.
Good! It's time. Change the
Skid over to cruiser mode.
What the heck is going on?!
An earthquake?
Change is 48% complete.
All systems operating normally.
[PILOT A]
Ship changeover is now complete.
The Skid has entered
into cruiser mode.
[PILOT B]
Running a systems check.
All sections are green.
[SENES]
Good. Activate Skid.
Destination: Leinwan's capital,
Castle Sauer.
[WINIA]
I really appreciate everything
you've done for me, Leo.
I don't know how to thank you.
[LEO] Please don't worry
about it. It's my pleasure.
Besides, it was time for
me to head home anyway.
A problem shared is
a problem halved.
So anyway, why are you
headed to Sauer, Miss Winia?
To see the person who
just wrote me a letter.
[LEO]
Oh, I see. That's a good idea!
Maybe.
But I haven't told this
person that I'm coming,
so I'm worried about
causing him trouble.
[LEO] Of course. That's very
thoughtful of you.
But as they say, you've just
gotta take your best shot at it.
[gasps]
I mean-- You shouldn't
literally take a shot at him.
Okay.
[PETERS-STAHL]
It's entered our waters?
[LUKE]
Yes, sir.
Go on.
Reports say that
after exchanging fire
with the Giat Second Fleet,
the promontory which we believe
to be Scarlet's main fortress
began to maneuver.
Their base has now violated
our territorial waters.
So you're saying...
an island moved?
[LUKE]
Yes, sir.
The elite wizard
unit that I sent
to follow and observe
the Scrapped Princess
finally sent back their report.
The entire Giat Second
Fleet was wiped out.
During the battle,
my unit also observed
some sort of enormous
tentacled creature.
[PETERS-STAHL]
Hm...
Well then, Luke, your thoughts?
It is my belief that
this is the same creature
that was spotted in
the town of Taurus.
Interesting.
The Scrapped Princess
has made contact
with Scarlet as well
as the Peacemakers.
Well, that's food for thought.
The power output is dropping!
Speed has fallen below 20!
We'll be dead in the water soon!
What is it? What's going on?
I don't know.
[NATALIE] I've shut down
the propulsion systems
of this mobile fortress.
[PACIFICA]
Why would you do that?
This is unacceptable.
Deliberately heading
into a situation
that you know is a
trap is not rational.
What did you say?
[NATALIE] You should
maintain your position here
and wait until the Providence
Breaker's innate abilities
manifest in their true form.
But we have to go!
If we don't, they're going to
kill a thousand people every day
until we reach the Capital!
And those bastards
would do it, too.
We can't wait for the brat's
birthday to move out.
A rough calculation would put
the number of causalities
at over 40,000 people.
[NATALIE] We consider
those acceptable losses.
Zefiris, does this mean
that you agree with her?
I do.
So you'll just stand by and
watch while people are killed.
Nothing can be done about that.
[SENES]
Hmph. If the ship is stopped,
we just need to
get it moving again.
[PACIFICA]
It'll still move?
[SENES] Will you give
me a hand? Shannon Cassul?
[PACIFICA]
But how will you do it?
Oh, just relax. I didn't ask
for your help with this.
Nice attitude you've got there!
What the heck's your problem?!
It's not as if
Natalie has actually
destroyed the Skid or anything.
She's just sabotaged the ship.
And if she severed
the power linkages,
all we have to do is
reconnect them by hand.
Reconnect the linkages?
What does that mean?
Beats me.
Anyway, I'm sure that our
two difficult Dragoons here
were conditioned so
that they would be
unable to harm human beings.
It would explain why
they did something
as indirect as
stopping the ship.
[ALL]
Mm... Uh.
I don't really
understand any of this,
but if we can get the ship
moving again, let's do it.
[SENES] The area up ahead
is a sealed sector.
For the time being,
we'll have Eirote guiding us.
But even I don't know
what's going to happen
once we get in there.
[RAQUEL] I thought you
said this would be safe.
[SENES]
There's no guarantee
that we won't trigger
the security system.
If anything happens,
I want the two of you
to back me up in there.
So we're basically
playing this one by ear.
I still don't get
what's going on, though.
Just make sure that you don't
get in the way of the grown-ups.
What the heck is it with you?!
Why do you keep trying
to pick a fight with me
every chance you get?!
Let's go. We're headed
for the ship's core.
Hey, look at me when
I'm talkin to--!
Eirote! Open up!
[PACIFICA sighs]
Geez...
[PACIFICA]
Wow!
So this is the sort of place
that demons lived in?
Demons, huh?
After all we told you,
you're still spouting that
superstitious nonsense.
Oh, come on.
Natalie was the one who
taught you everything,
so don't act
so special, you know?
Get over yourself.
Seems like all you
do is back talk.
Your whole personality
is so twisted, you know?
Nice try. But that's my line.
[PACIFICA, SENES arguing]
Look at that.
Those two seem to be
warming up to each other.
Oh, wow!
This place is amazing.
But why did the humans build
this thing so big anyway?
[SENES]
They used it to fight.
[PACIFICA]
Against who?
[SENES]
Ugh.
Hey, Eirote, put it
into words small enough
for Her Highness to understand.
[EIROTE]
Yes, ma'am.
According to Natalie,
ancient humanity
came under attack
by what she calls
an alien intelligence.
[RAQUEL]
Alien?
[PACIFICA]
Hm?
[EIROTE] Dragoons, such as
Zefiris and Natalie,
as well as bio-weapons,
such as the Bugs,
were developed
one after another.
But unfortunately,
they were not enough
to help turn the
tide of the war.
In the end, humanity's leader,
a man named George Browning,
proposed a radical solution.
[SHANNON]
Browning?
[SENES]
It's a person's name.
[RAQUEL]
He was human?
[EIROTE] Princess Senes,
take the next right.
He installed the mind
of a woman named Celia,
who was the greatest
psychic of her time,
into a mobile fortress
like this one
along with special machinery
to augment her powers.
He thereby created a system
that predicted the future,
so he could counter
the aliens' attack.
To intercept enemies which
could appear from nowhere
out of thin air,
humanity responded
by pairing up a psychic
with the power of an enormous
artificial intelligence.
The psychic, Celia,
predicted enemy movements
with a high degree of accuracy.
Relying on Celia's predictions,
humanity was now barely able
to fight them on equal footing.
But that woman, Celia,
decided to betray humanity.
How come?
[growls]
[PACIFICA yawns]
[SENES grunts]
[PACIFICA yelps]
[EIROTE] Princess Senes,
please be careful in there.
I'm starting to have trouble
seeing you on the monitors.
[NATALIE] They've just
entered the interference field.
I think the fastest
way to deal with this
is to hack into
the field's systems
and brainwash the Guardians.
[ZEFIRIS] I was under the
impression that Dragoons like us
are not permitted to interfere
with the humans' free will.
[NATALIE] Perhaps. But I'm
no longer a Dragoon.
I'm a virtual personality
who is borrowing space
in the Skid's core systems.
[NATALIE]
You seem upset.
[ZEFIRIS] Your methods
are rather forceful,
don't you think?
[NATALIE] The years have
made you soft, Zefiris.
Our objective is to carry
out the plan no matter what.
Remember?
[ZEFIRIS]
Carry out the plan...
Natalie, is what we're about
to do really part of the plan?
[NATALIE] Have you
gotten attached to them?
Very well. If that's
how you feel.
Just make sure to
stay out of my way.
What should I do?
[footsteps]
Is your research
coming along well?
Prince Forsyth.
[FORSYTH]
It's not easy, is it?
All records dealing with
the Scrapped Princess
were destroyed years ago.
[gasps]
Tell me, Chris.
Who are you, after all?
[CHRIS]
I'm a weapons specialist
from the Obstinate Arrows
Special Forces unit.
I see. That explains it.
Chris, I have a favor to ask.
[CHRIS]
A favor?
[FORSYTH] I don't know why
you're investigating my sister
and you probably
can't tell me anyway,
but would you let me help
you with your research?
Sorry, but I can't.
[FORSYTH]
If that's out of the question,
would you at least tell me
what you've found out so far?
[FORSYTH] It's possible
I could have been the one
who was abandoned
instead of my sister.
I have a duty to find out
if that's really the case.
Possibly. But Highness--
[FORSYTH]
No, not Your Highness.
[CHRIS gasps]
Call me Forsyth.
[chuckles]
[SENES]
Damn it! Which way?!
Eirote!
Hey, Eirote!
Tch, she's not answering me.
[RAQUEL gasps]
Pacifica?!
[SENES]
Huh?
[RAQUEL]
Shannon? Pacifica?!
Where are they?
Damn it all.
Huh?
Pacifica? R-Raquel!
Are those Dragoons behind this?
Guess I should keep moving.
[NATALIE]
Shannon Cassul.
[PACIFICA whimpers]
I don't get it.
What's going on?
Come on, guys.
Where did everybody go?
Pacifica Cassul.
Huh?
Zefiris? Hey, look,
I got separated from
the others somehow.
What's the matter?
Pacifica Cassul...
What should I...
What should I do now, Pacifica?
[PACIFICA}
Huh?
[RAQUEL] This Skid mobile
fortress has lost power
and is dead in the water.
Natalie separates the
three Cassul siblings
when they try to reactivate it.
What is Natalie planning?
Is she doing this because
she can't stand how close
the three of them are?
Next time on
Scrapped Princess,
"Lost Quintet."
See you next time!