I'm tired.
Yeah, yeah...
[PACIFICA]
I said I'm tired!
Yeah, yeah.
[PACIFICA] I'm tired and
I wanna have a hot meal
and climb into a nice, soft bed,
and I want it right now!
[SHANNON growls]
Would you shut up already?!
Is this the mouth
that's been spouting
all that self-centered garbage?!
[PACIFICA] All we do is ride
in this stupid cart all day,
camp outside all night, and
then get up and do it again.
My butt is killing me
and I wanna take a bath!
Not till we've put
some more distance
between us and Manurhin town.
Jerk.
[RAQUEL gasps]
[BANDIT A]
Step down.
[SHANNON]
Oh brother...
[BANDIT A] Is that young girl
with you Pacifica Cassul?
In the name of the god Mauser...
[BANDIT B]
...she must be destroyed!
You better get behind me.
[BANDITS yelling]
Barrier, obstruct them!
[BANDITS groaning]
[BANDIT B]
Damn you!
[BOTH yelling]
[BANDIT E]
They're too strong!
[BOY]
Aren't you going to fight?
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[BOY]
You can't do anything, can you?
All you can do is
watch. I get it now.
Pacifica!
[BOY]
See ya.
Who the hell was that guy?
C'mon, let's go.
[BANDIT F]
You... You're the one...
You're the poison that
will destroy the world!
Hey, Raquel...?
[SHANNON]
There's a village up ahead.
I'm sure they'll have some
chicken feet for you to eat.
I want a fancy full-course
meal with dessert.
[SHANNON]
Yeah, yeah. Your highness.
[PRIEST]
So... You're here.
The assassins I sent earlier
have apparently failed.
The task before you now
is to lure that young
girl to this place.
The god Mauser watches over
your actions and blesses you.
[RAQUEL]
I'm done eating.
[SHANNON]
Mm-hm.
Fancy full-course meal
complete with dessert.
Ya gotta be kidding me!
That was delicious!
Aw! And it's such a shame
'cause it looks like
there's a little café in
the town after this one...
Listen, Missy,
don't you understand the
situation that you're in?
We can't afford to take a route
that might attract any
undue attention.
Not until we leave
the kingdom of Leinwan.
[GIRL A]
What's two times two?
[GIRL B]
Four.
[GIRL A]
Two times three?
[GIRL B]
Six.
[GIRL A]
Two times four?
Eight.
[GIRL A]
So, what's two times five?
[GIRL B]
Ten!
[GIRL A]
Wow! You're amazing!
[GIRL B]
It's no big deal.
[GIRL A]
I still don't get it at all.
[GIRL B]
If you use eggs to count,
I'm sure you'll pick
it up right away.
[GIRL A]
Really?
[GIRL B] Hey, have you
learned all your lines yet
for the play next week?
[GIRL A] I have 'em down
pat! It's no big deal.
[GIRL B]
Wow, you're amazing!
Pacifica...
[PACIFICA] How about you,
Shannon? Do you understand?
You are to address me as
"Your Highness," not "Missy"!
You got that?!
Now hand over that dumpling!
[SHANNON]
Hey, stop it!
Some princess you are,
you mangy stray cat!
[PAIFICA]
Whatever! Just hand it over!
--Huh? It's Pacifica!
--[SHANNON] As if!
[PACIFICA]
Huh? Ah!
I'm in paradise...
[humming]
[SHANNON] We're really sorry
about damaging your rice plants.
Don't worry about it.
It's quite all right.
I understand that you're all
friends with my daughter.
Yes, we met her
in Manurhin Town.
What a coincidence, running
into Auntie Diana like that.
I might just have to help
myself to a bath later on.
Now, wait a minute.
[RAQUEL]
Hmm?
Oh, how adorable!
Is she yours, Diana?
Yes, she is.
[BABY coos]
[BABY cries]
Oh no!
[DIANA]
I have to go check on the bath.
Can you look after
her for a while?
[RAQUEL]
Of course.
[crying continues]
Thank you.
Shannon, you made Pacifica
cry all the time, too.
I suppose I did.
Suddenly, we both had a new
kid sister on our hands.
I didn't know what
to make of her.
[SHANNON] And now, our
baby sister is 15 years old.
[PACIFICA] Honestly, it's been
forever since my last bath.
How many years has been
since we last saw you?
It's been about three, right?
[DIANA]
I suppose it has.
You know, I was born
right here in this village.
[PACIFICA]
Wow, really?
I have to admit; we
were really surprised.
We never expected
to run into someone
from Manurhin Town out here.
We'll find you
some dinner later.
Perhaps, one of those egg
dishes you're so fond of.
[PACIFICA]
Eggs? Really?!
But first, could you help me
with something, Pacifica?
[DIANA]
Is your father doing well?
[PACIFICA] Well, he... Daddy
passed away not too long ago.
[DIANA]
I see...
Daddy really appreciated
everything you did
to help us kids, Auntie.
I mean, after Mommy died,
he turned to you for
everything, remember?
When I had a fever, you'd
stay up with me all night
just to make sure
that I'd be okay.
And today, I drop in out of
nowhere and use your bath.
[chuckles]
[PACIFICA]
A church ?
[DIANA]
I always come here and ask them
to share their eggs with me.
Would you be willing to help
me carry them back home?
[RAQUEL]
Auntie Diana?!
[SHANNON]
She's not here?
[RAQUEL]
Neither is Pacifica...
You don't suppose
that... Auntie...?
I don't know. Let's find them.
[RAQUEL]
Huh?
Oh! I remember you!
We met you earlier.
[RAQUEL]
You haven't seen that girl
you were talking to
before, have you?
Couldn't say.
Oh, yeah!
The soy sauce dumplings
they make in this town
are really delicious!
[PRIEST]
So, this is the girl.
The girl destined to usher in
the destruction of the world
when she turns 16.
The "Scrapped Princess."
No way...
[PRIEST]
Well done. You may leave us now.
[PACIFICA]
But... Wait!
Why, Auntie?
[DIANA] I had no idea that you
were the Scrapped Princess.
What I'm doing is for
the good of the kingdom,
for the good of our
lord god Mauser!
You've only yourself to blame!
[PRIEST]
How foolish of her.
There's no need to feel shame
for performing a good deed.
There's not a single
place in this world
that will take you in, for you
are the Scrapped Princess,
the one Saint Grendel
spoke of in his revelation.
You are the great evil
that will destroy the world.
In the name of the god Mauser,
I shall purge the
Scrapped Princess.
[PRIEST]
Thunder, rumble in the heavens,
brandish your whip of light,
and show us now the
power of your wrath!
[PRIEST]
The man you call "Father"
gave his life in
order to protect you.
As long as you continue to live,
there will be more and more
people who will flock to
the aid of our god Mauser.
[PRIEST] Your very existence
on this Earth is a sin.
You should never've been
born in the first place,
for you were destined to
be cast away immediately.
[PRIEST gasps]
You have my sincerest
apologies, sir,
but I'm afraid I'm going
to have to put you
out of commission.
[PRIEST]
What's that?!
Uh... Big Sister, I...
[PRIEST] Thunder,
rumble in the heavens...
[RAQUEL]
People of the flames, dance.
[PRIEST yelps]
[PRIEST] Thunder...
rumble in the heavens...
People of the flames, dance.
[PRIEST]
...grant us your whip of-- Ah!
[PRIEST groans]
[RAQUEL]
People of the flames, dance.
[PRIEST screams]
That's impossible!
There's no way you could
cast a spell of that power
with so short a chant!
Do you mean to defy the god
Mauser with your blasphemy?!
Such insolence!
[RAQUEL]
My deepest apologies.
I will fight you to
the best of my abilities.
Class one, tactical grade
military offensive spell.
Come forth, Thor!
[PACIFICA coughing]
Don't you think
that was a bit much?
[RAQUEL]
Well, you heard him.
Oh, look, here comes Shannon.
[SHANNON]
"Oh" yourself, Missy!
Well, Sis, nicely done.
You've done a bang-up
job of showing the people
who are hunting us
exactly where we are.
[RAQUEL chuckles]
Oopsie!
Oh brother... Hey, Pacifica!
No more going out all
by yourself, got it?
You can't go wandering
off with strangers!
Auntie Diana wasn't a stranger.
[groaning]
[PRIEST]
Please... Help me...
[BOY] For one of the
church's elite Attenuators,
you're less than impressive.
I come all this way,
and this is what I find.
I'll have to kill the
Scrapped Princess myself.
[SHANNON] Don't be using
any magic, you got that?
[RAQUEL]
But why not? It's so convenient.
[SHANNON]
Because every third time
it's a total failure,
that's why!
Char-burnt barbecue, exploding
chicken... Do I need to go on?
[PACIFICA] She's right! I'm
sick and tired of lousy food.
You're in no position
to talk, little Missy.
Ah, I'm so hungry...
Don't eat it!
Ugh, it's still raw...
When you want something done
fast, magic is the way to go!
[SHANNON]
Hey, hold it!
[RAQUEL]
Ah, but why not?
[SHANNON] Aw, come on!
Just leave it alone already!
[SHANNON]
What do you want?
What's wrong with you?
You look like an old
man all hunched over.
Did you get out of bed just
to come pick a fight with me?
[PACIFICA]
Wow.
These nights are getting
colder and colder.
[SHANNON] Now you sound
like an old lady, Pacifica.
Shannon, my name... Pacifica,
who gave it to me?
[SHANNON]
What do you mean?
Mom and Dad gave you
your name. Who else?
[PACIFICA] So my real mom and
dad never gave me a name...
I guess they thought I wouldn't
be around long enough
for it to really matter.
[PACIFICA] I wish I could've
lived in that village forever.
With Dad, and Mom,
and you, and Raquel.
I could've gone to school,
and Mom and Dad would've
chewed me out for my bad grades.
And then I could've gotten mad
and asked them for a raise
in my allowance. And then...
Pacifica...
[PACIFICA] Didn't you
want that too, Shannon?
You know, you could've
taken over from Dad
and run the weapon
store yourself.
And then you could
live a normal li--
Someday, that's just
what I'm gonna do.
But you can't.
At least, not while I live.
I guess I really
am trash, aren't I?
If I were to die, I wonder if
all of this would be over.
Right?
It's time for Raquel
to keep watch.
Answer my question!
[SHANNON sighs]
That's a difficult question...
[SHANNON]
If...
...someday...
[SHANNON grunts]
You're that guy from
this morning, right?
Please die now.
Get inside!
[SHANNON]
Who are you?
Royal Forces Fifth Special Ops
Unit, the Obstinate Arrows.
Christopher Armalite,
combat weapons specialist.
But call me Chris.
I understand now.
This explains why you were able
to protect the Scrapped
Princess all this time.
[RAQUEL]
Oh my!
Did you ever get a chance to
try their soy sauce dumplings?
[giggles]
Well I guess it might
be a bit too difficult
to try and beat the
both of you myself.
I know it's rude
to attack and run,
but let's finish this
up another time.
[CHRIS] Oh, that reminds
me: One more thing.
Why have the two of you
decided to protect that girl?
You must know
about the revelation.
That girl is an abomination
who will bring down disaster
on the world when she turns 16.
No one will care if she dies.
On the contrary,
they'll celebrate.
What's the point in
protecting a girl like--?
[CHRIS]
Did I upset you?
Surely you've heard it before?
When she became
a part of our family,
my father and mother
gave that girl her name.
They named her with the hope
that everyone who met her
would grow to love her.
So you see, I'm always gonna
protect my little sister.
I'll protect her until
the moment I discover
that she really is the poison
that will destroy the world.
--[thud]
--[gasps]
That guy's tough. He's
different from the others.
You're right. An exceptional
adversary has appeared.
Hey, Big Brother?
[SHANNON]
Hmm?
If I...
If the Revelation is true,
and I really am the one who's
going to destroy the world...
...if that happens...
...then I want you to be
the one who kills me, okay?
[PACIFICA]
Aw, c'mon!
How much farther is it
to the next village?
[SHANNON]
Uh... I don't know.
[PACIFICA]
Yeah, right! Of course you do!
Your problem is you're always so
vague and wishy-washy like that!
And that's exactly the reason
why girls never go
for you, you know?
Yeah, yeah. Whatever you say.
[PACIFICA sighs]
Hey, Big Brother?
What is it?
The thing is...
[PACIFICA]
...I love you.
[gasps]
I knew that already.
Hey! Stop!
[PACIFICA]
How about blushing about it?!
Or maybe acting happy about it?!
I swear you can be
such a jerk sometimes!
What's the matter
with you, anyway?!
It's like you're an
old man or something!
--[SHANNON] Well, excuse me!
--[PACIFICA] You're so annoying!
[RAQUEL] The Cassul siblings
are attacked by bandits.
A boy who's passing by
decides to intervene
in order to rescue them.
What's more,
he decides to tag along even
though they tell him not to.
This could cause problems.
Next time on Scrapped Princess,
"March of the
Half-Baked Knight."
See you next time.