This is sudden, but I
require your assistance.
My assistance?
[PACIFICA]
What's this for?
[ZEFIRIS] That girl, the young
girl who is with you now.
[PACIFICA] You mean Cz? What
does this have to do with her?
I need you to kill that girl.
Huh?
[RAQUEL]
Shannon.
[SHANNON]
Hmm?
[RAQUEL]
Would you go check on Pacifica?
[SHANNON]
Pacifica?
Why? She'll be fine as
long as she stays in here.
[RAQUEL]
Shannon.
[SHANNON]
Hm?
Don't you understand?
[SHANNON]
Well, sure, but...
Fine, I understand
what you're saying.
Where Pacifica?
I go look for her.
[RAQUEL]
Hey, Shannon.
Don't you think it's
a little strange?
What's strange?
[RAQUEL] I know you
think the world of Cz,
but sometimes it's--
You're fond of her, too,
though, aren't you, Raquel?
[RAQUEL] I wonder if that girl
has some sort of power.
[SHANNON]
Hm?
Maybe that's what happened
when you found her.
If she used some
sort of power on you,
then maybe she's tricked
you into caring for her.
Oh, come on. You're reading
way too much into it.
Perhaps... I just
hope you're right...
[SHANNON]
Hm.
[PACIFICA]
What? What're you saying?
[ZEFIRIS]
I need you to kill her.
Thy brother and sister are
of no use to me right now.
That is why I am
asking for thy help.
[PACIFICA] Why do you want
me to kill a little girl?
Because she is dangerous.
But you're not making any sense!
[door opens]
[PACIFICA gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Cz.
I cannot intervene in this
situation. Kill her. Now.
What?! Are you insane?!
Why in the world would I wanna
do something so terrible?!
[ZEFIRIS]
Please do it quickly.
Otherwise, thy brother
and sister will surely die.
A Peace... maker is...
Did you just do that?
[PACIFICA]
Cz, say something already.
Come on!
[gasps]
[SHANNON]
What're you doing?
[CZ giggles]
[ZEFIRIS]
Thy brother and sister...
...they will surely die.
No!
Pacifica!
[SHANNON]
Are you all right, Cz?
[PACIFICA]
But, Shannon...
Apologize.
Huh?
Apologize to Cz.
Apologize? Tell me why I should
have to apologize to that girl!
Are you telling me Cz is more
important to you than me?!
Pacifica, do you have any idea
of how badly you could've
hurt Cz just now?
But you're not listening to me!
What's wrong with you?
Don't you trust me anymore?
You swore that you'd protect me,
but you don't care about me!
All you care about
is your stupid promise
and making yourself feel good!
Anyone'll do as long as
you can feel superior
by protecting them!
I don't matter to
you at all, do I?!
All you care about is yourself!
[SHANNON]
Pacifica!
[gasps]
After all we've been
through together,
is that what you really
think about me?
I'm disappointed...
...Your Majesty.
Let's go, Cz.
[PACIFICA]
But why...?
[sighs]
[RAQUEL]
I'm a little surprised.
You and Shannon don't
usually fight like this.
The two of you
should talk things out.
Especially at a time like this.
You think so, Raquel?
[RAQUEL]
Of course.
Because Shannon doesn't know
what to do about it either.
[SHANNON]
Raquel, can I talk to you?
What is it?
[PACIFICA]
What's the matter?
[SHANNON] I'm going into town.
We're getting rid of the wagon.
Huh?
Now wait just a second, Shannon!
How could you decide
without asking us first?!
We've already decided.
Huh?
I'm sorry, but we really
don't have any other choice.
[PACIFICA cries]
[PACIFICA]
I'm so sorry, Dragunov...
[CZ] Cz... Cz like Shannon,
Raquel, and Pacifica.
That's why... I is very sad...
Really, Cz?
[CZ] Shannon and Pacifica
both mad at each other now.
Well, yeah...
It happens sometimes.
Is because of Cz?
No, Cz, it's not your fault.
I'm pretty sure
we're all to blame
for what's been
happening recently.
[CZ]
Hmm?
[SHANNON] I wanted to
ask you something, Cz.
Would you like to stay
with us for good?
Want to stay.
The problem is,
if you stay with us,
you might just get
yourself killed.
You sure you still wanna stay?
[CZ]
Cz not die.
Well, Cz, the thing is...
Oh, really?
Well, it might take some
time to persuade her,
but I think Pacifica
will come around.
That's the kind of
girl she is, after all.
Well... She's not much
of a horse, is she?
[FEMALE MERCHANT]
Pretty, aren't they?
Every one of them is unique.
I put a lot of thought,
as well as a special prayer,
into each piece that I make.
This one pretty.
[FEMALE MERCHANT]
You have good taste, little one.
That pair is my
personal favorite.
Could we get a discount?
[SHANNON] Geez, those
things cost a fortune.
[CZ]
Uh?
Pacifica.
Give flower!
[gasps]
[horses whinnies]
[VILLAGERS gasping]
Shannon!
[VILLAGER A]
He got hit really hard!
[CZ]
Shannon!
[VILLAGER B]
Is he dead?
[CZ]
Shannon!
Hey.
[RAQUEL]
What do you mean, "Hey"?!
Shannon, what happened?!
How did you get hurt?!
[RAQUEL] So, Cz, can you
tell me what happened?
Don't you wanna tell me?
[PACIFICA]
Why won't you tell us anything?
It's not normal for
Shannon to get hurt.
And it's creepy that you
won't talk to us about it.
It was you, wasn't it?
It's because you were with him.
[RAQUEL]
Pacifica.
Cz is very sorry.
[RAQUEL sighs]
What is this?
That's for Pacifica.
[PACIFICA]
Of all the stupid...
He wants to use these
to make up with me?
He didn't really put much
thought into it, did he?
[SHANNON]
Do you like them?
Cz spotted them first.
She was the one who
picked them out for you.
The lady said they have
prayers of bonds in them.
Prayers that we would
always be together.
That even if we were separated,
we would eventually be reunited.
[SHANNON] Pacifica...
I'm sorry about everything.
[PACIFICA]
Mm-mm.
Thank you, Shannon.
Where is Cz?
[RAQUEL]
You mean she isn't with you?
[RAQUEL] I'm not picking
up anybody nearby.
[RAQUEL]
Where're you going?
[PACIFICA]
Where do you think, Raquel?
I'm gonna go look for her!
[RAQUEL]
Are you sure you want to?
I wonder sometimes.
I wonder if I'll turn out to be
a big sister like you, Raquel.
[RAQUEL]
Cz! Where are you?!
Where are you, Cz?!
Answer me, please!
[ZEFIRIS] What a sorry
sight you are, my master.
[SHANNON]
Zefiris.
I've had difficulties
of my own as well.
I was able to manifest
myself on this side earlier,
but I encountered
some interference.
What interference?
[ZEFIRIS] I have been
unable to speak with you
unless you are a
certain distance away
from that little girl.
Wait a minute, are you telling
me you know about Cz?
[ZEFIRIS]
Of course I do.
That little girl's original
designation is C-Z.
She is an artillery-type
Peacemaker.
[gasps]
[sobbing]
[PACIFICA]
Cz!
[gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Cz, where are you?!
Answer me!
[PACIFICA]
Cz!
Wait a minute! Cz, come back!
[PACIFICA]
Gotcha...
I finally caught you...
[PACIFICA]
Well...
I'm not really sure
what to say now, uh...
I'm so sorry... I guess
I was being a big jerk.
You don't have to leave
if you don't want to.
When you think about it,
Shannon and Raquel and I
lead pretty complicated
lives already.
Having one more person along
won't make that big
of a difference.
But I...
From now on, Cz, I want you to
call me your big sister, okay?
My big sister?
[PACIFICA]
Let's stay together.
It's a promise, okay?
[PACIFICA]
Now, now, don't cry...
Come on, let's go home.
[STEYR] I'm sorry to interrupt
this touching scene...
...but I'll take that child
back, if you don't mind.
[PACIFICA]
Who're you?
Who am I, you ask?
I am known as Peacemaker
Steyr Civilian.
Peacemaker...?
[ZEFIRIS] Humans are unable to
defy the will of a Peacemaker.
Pacifica Cassul is the lone
exception to that rule.
However, at present, her
power only manifests itself
at times of extreme
fear or anger.
That is the reason
why you were unable
to defy the will
of that girl Cz.
What're you talking about?
[ZEFIRIS] If Cz had
awakened to her true form
while she was with you,
she would've killed
all of you immediately.
But as long as she retains
the human attributes
of her child-like avatar,
I am unable to
physically touch her.
I suggested to Pacifica Cassul
that she eliminate Cz,
but it would seem that
she has not done so.
[gasps]
I had no choice, master.
That little girl is
far too dangerous.
[SHANNON] That's crazy.
Cz isn't like that!
[ZEFIRIS] The emotion
that you're feeling now
was manipulated by Cz.
[gasps]
You're wrong...
You're wrong. I'm
not being controlled.
[ZEFIRIS] We can speak of
this later, my master.
It would seem that another
Peacemaker is here.
It is now with Cz and
your younger sister.
[gasps]
[STEYR] To be perfectly
honest, I'm surprised.
You people were the last ones
I excepted to take her in.
I mean, after all,
don't you know that
little girl is one of us?
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[STEYR]
Shall I explain it to you?
Peacemakers were originally
designed to work in pairs.
The artillery-type Peacemakers
are typically too powerful
and difficult to use,
so they were kept stored
in a data-compressed state
in phase-shift space.
We had initiated the
decompression algorithms
in order to have them
to fight against Zefiris.
What? I don't understand
what you're talking about.
[STEYR]
Originally,
Galil had been chosen to
be that girl's counterpart,
but he got careless
and allowed himself to be
destroyed by you people.
So after she was decompressed,
she was tossed
out into the world
without knowing who she was
or what was happening.
I wasn't left with
much of a choice,
so I came looking
for her in his place.
Come to me now, Cz.
That girl's your enemy,
don't you remember?
What? Why don't you ask
her how she feels about it?
[STEYR] Because it doesn't
really matter, does it?
Cz, get out of here
now. Go, quickly!
[gasps]
[STEYR]
Come now.
It's time fo you to return to
your proper form, my darling Cz.
[gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Cz!
Big Sister, help!
Big Sister! Help me!
[gasps]
[STEYR]
How are you feeling, Cz?
Steyr, it's you.
If you are meeting me
instead of Galil,
then someone
must've killed him.
[STEYR] Yes. In fact,
the one who did it was him.
[SHANNON]
Pacifica!
[PACIFICA gasps]
Big Brother! Big Sister!
[RAQUEL]
Pacifica!
[SHANNON]
Where's Cz?!
[PACIFICA]
I don't know!
Who are those two?
I don't know that either!
What did you do with Cz?!
Tell us: Where did she go?!
[ZEFIRIS]
As you can see now,
Cz has become one
of our enemies.
[PACIFICA]
No!
You're wrong! She
can't be our enemy!
Forgive me, my master.
I must borrow your body.
[RAQUEL]
Pacifica...
We must be careful.
It seems the fusion of
Zefiris and her D-Knight
has already been completed.
Still, the Dragoon's restoration
remains incomplete.
There are gaps in her mental
unification with the D-Knight.
[SHANNON, ZEFIRIS]
Same goes for you.
You just been
decompressed, after all.
I doubt your powers
have been fine-tuned.
If you overexert yourself,
you could trigger
an atomic collapse.
Then I won't need
to destroy you.
That's a possibility.
But if I was able to
start a chain reaction,
then maybe I could take you
along with me when I go.
Would you care to give it a try?
I'm very sorry, but
I have no intention
of getting into a fight
with you today.
Well, are you ready to go, Cz?
[SHANNON, ZEFIRIS]
You're not getting away!
[STEYR]
You have my word, Guardian.
The next time we meet,
I will make sure to destroy you
and put you out of your misery.
[SHANNON] According
to what Zefiris told me,
there's almost no chance
that any of Cz's original
child-like personality
could still exist inside
that Peacemaker.
She also said that
the next time we meet,
Cz will do her best
to try to kill us,
and we should defend ourselves.
[PACIFICA] Do you really
think that there's no way
to turn her back
to her old self?
I thought I finally
had a little sister.
I thought it might
be kinda nice
to get to act like a
big sister for once.
I was just getting
used to the idea.
And now you tell me
that Cz is gone.
[RAQUEL] Travelling a snowy
road in the mountains,
Pacifica and the others
stumble across a village
hidden by magic.
The villagers who come out
don't seem to be very happy
to see them, however.
Maybe they just
don't like people.
Next time on Scrapped Princess,
"Requiem for the Heretics."
See you next time!