[REYNARD]
The time has come!
For years, we have obeyed
the Scrapped Princess,
endured patiently
in this village,
hidden ourselves from the world,
and gathered our strength!
But the world we
long for is at hand!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[ELFITINE]
The future...
[ELFITINE] Our future shines
so brightly before us now,
that it is blinding!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[BERKENS] Sounds like
they've started the party.
What's supposed to happen now?
Nothing very peaceful,
you can be sure of that.
I think it's about time we
found a way out of this place.
But they're still holding
Berkens somewhere!
[SHANNON] Who the heck
cares about that guy?
I'm gonna go find
out where he is.
[SHANNON]
Wait.
Pacifica!
The villagers are all here,
so I think she'll be safe.
Don't you agree, Shannon?
I guess, but that
man's our enemy.
[RAQUEL] You aren't feeling
jealous of Pops, now are you?
Oh, yeah right.
[WOMAN]
Lady Elfitine.
It is time for
your purification.
[ELFITINE]
I am coming.
[RAQUEL]
There's not even a guard posted.
[RAQUEL] This magical
wall is fairly powerful.
[SHANNON]
Well, I wasn't really expecting
to be able to just
waltz out of here.
Did that Lord Reynard
guy do all this himself?
I don't think that
his mental capacity
is great enough to do this.
Then are you saying there
must be other wizards here?
That, or maybe...
I sincerely hope that what I'm
thinking is completely wrong.
It might be nice to have a god
to pray to at times like this,
don't you think?
[REYNARD]
What's the matter, little one?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
[AUDREY]
Yes, sir.
[REYNARD]
Drink then.
By doing so, you will
help bring about
a proper world ruled
by Lord Browning.
[glass shatters, thud]
[REYNARD] That completes the
power necessary for the core.
This will be enough
to activate it.
[RAQUEL] I checked the
flows of magical force,
but there's something strange...
I sensed a place with
multiple signatures,
but all of them were faint,
like candles about to go out.
Most likely, it's beneath that
meeting hall from earlier.
Where's Mr. Berkens? He's gotta
be down here somewhere.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[PACIFICA] What the heck
is this big, ugly thing for?
[PACIFICA] Why is there
suddenly steam everywhere?
[ELFITINE]
Who's there?!
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry. Is there
somebody in here?
Whoa!
[ELFITINE]
You're one of those people
who came from the outside.
Yeah. My name is Pacifica.
Wait a sec...
Didn't I just see you in
the meeting hall upstairs?
Yes. Once I am finished here,
I will return to the hall.
You'll catch a cold standing
in wet clothes like that.
You're welcome to join me
here until they dry out.
[PACIFICA]
Really? Are you sure?
[ELFITINE] People from the
village come to join me here
from time to time.
We don't tell Lord Reynard
about it, though.
[PACIFICA]
Oh...
[ELFITINE]
To tell you the truth,
I'm in the middle of a ceremony
that's meant to purify my body,
and I'm not supposed to talk
to anyone during the ritual.
But I suppose I've already
spoken, haven't I?
All right! I haven't
had a bath in ages!
I'm sorry, could you help
me with these clasps?
They're sorta hard to reach.
[ELFITINE]
Yes, of course.
[PACIFICA] I always get
my sister Raquel to do it.
My brother Shannon does
it sometimes, though.
The three of you
must be very close.
[PACIFICA] Not really.
All we do is fight.
Thanks a lot!
[REYNARD] Today, the world
will finally be corrected!
The dark age of Mauser's
rule will come to an end,
and a new age will begin!
And we, the loyal followers of
Lord Browning, shall flourish!
How pompous and
boring can one guy be?
[REYNARD]
Now, behold!
[BERKENS]
Huh?
[REYNARD] Our glorious Lord
Browning has begun to stir!
The time has come!
The judgment of the true
god is about to rain down
upon the holy city of
Grendel and destroy it!
[sighs]
This is absolute heaven...
I guess it won't hurt anything
if I take a little break.
Life in the outside world
must be very harsh.
All of the people who
come to this village
seem to have met with very
difficult times out there.
But it's different here.
Here, everyone can
live together in peace.
Why don't you stay
here with us, Pacifica?
Say, I heard that you can see
into the future. Is that true?
[ELFITINE]
What? Yes...
Wow, that's so amazing!
So, tell me:
Can you see a boyfriend
somewhere in my future?
I'm sorry. I'm not able to
see everything and anything.
Oh, you can't? That's
kinda disappointing...
This is the first time I've ever
spoken with anyone like this.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[ELFITINE] Probably because I'm
the princess of this village.
Oh, yeah. That's right.
There's something different
about you, Pacifica.
Aren't you afraid of me?
[PACIFICA]
No, why?
People from the outside say
that the Scrapped Princess
is the poison that will
destroy the world,
and therefore,
she must be killed.
Between that and being
able to see the future,
it scares some people
away from me.
[PACIFICA] There's no shortage
of abnormal people in my family,
so I guess I can't talk.
In the Church of Mauser,
people with special abilities
like mine are shunned.
We're called the bastard
children of demons.
Having skills you didn't work
for is unnatural in their eyes.
My powers are considered evil.
That's why everyone picked on
me so much when I was younger;
I made them nervous.
It's the same thing with me.
What?
[PACIFICA]
I know where you're coming from.
I'm hated by the
god Mauser, too.
I don't have any special
powers or anything,
but everyone's
still afraid of me.
[SHANNON]
What the heck is this?
It's a pretty strange room.
[RAQUEL]
I knew it...
[SHANNON]
Hm?
[SHANNON gasps]
[SHANNON]
Hey.
[RAQUEL]
It's no use.
In this state,
he probably doesn't even
know who he is right now.
[SHANNON] So there's a
person in each of these?
[RAQUEL] Someone is
combining the mental capacity
of these people to amplify
the power of their spell.
They've been put into a
coma by some sort of drug.
[BERKENS] So this must be
how that bastard Reynard
was able to cast a
spell powerful enough
to hide an entire village.
When the people in the hall
upstairs started praying,
this pattern appeared in the
chamber above their heads.
That's from a spell circle.
Wait, are you saying
you've studied magic?
Yes, a little.
[BERKENS] I don't know how
they're planning to do it,
but they're trying to launch an
attack on the city of Grendel.
Is that even possible?
[RAQUEL] Yes, if they're using a
strategic-grade offensive spell.
[BERKENS]
"Strategic-grade spell"?
I don't like the sound of that.
[RAQUEL]
There are records of such spells
being used twice in the past.
In both cases,
the fatalities numbered in
the hundreds of thousands.
[BERKENS]
Are you serious? But still,
they couldn't possibly reach
Grendel from here, could they?
[RAQUEL]
If they used a long-range
strategic-grade offensive spell,
and enough powerful wizards
chanted it together,
it would be possible for
them to send this spell
from the edge of Leinwan all
the way to the Giat Empire.
But still, I don't
see how this village
could possibly cast a
spell of such magnitude.
[BERKENS]
What is it?
I'm afraid there might
be more of these.
Well, they aren't quite
dry, but what the heck.
Hey, I was wondering...
Everybody was gathered
in the meeting hall,
so is something
about to happen?
[gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Uh?
What's the matter?
[ELFITINE]
I'm scared...
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[ELFITINE] I couldn't bring
myself to tell anyone
about this before,
but I had a vision of the
future for this village.
Everything was dark...
It was as if there wasn't
a single soul left alive...
How could that be the
result of all our efforts
to correct the world?
What're you going to do, then?
[ELFITINE] Lord Reynard
says that he's going to use
a powerful spell to destroy
the Holy City of Grendel.
What? Why would he do that?
[ELFITINE]
Because Lord Reynard says
that destroying the city
is a righteous act.
Sorry, but that doesn't
sound right to me.
You don't understand.
If it hadn't been
for Lord Reynard,
I never would've
been able to survive.
Lord Reynard is different.
He's not like other people.
My childhood was miserable.
Everyone hated me.
I began to wish I had
never been born.
It was then that Lord Reynard
found me and gave me hope.
He saved my life then,
and I trust him now.
That is why I have
always believed
what Lord Reynard has told me.
I've always believed him.
All this time, I've believed...
You know something?
I was abandoned right
after I was born.
What?
[PACIFICA]
But I was lucky.
Shannon and Raquel's
parents took me in
and raised me as
one of their own.
I'm the person I am now
because Shannon and
Raquel were in that house.
They helped shape my character.
But if someone
else had found me,
I think I would've
had to believe in them
and rely on that
person's opinion of me.
I believe in them.
My brother and sister
are always there for me.
In fact, in this whole world,
my brother and sister
are the only two people
who truly believe in me.
So you see,
if it turns out that I never
should've been born after all,
I want the two of them to
be the ones who kill me.
Are you really the Scrapped
Princess, Elfitine?
[gasps]
[ELFITINE]
I... I'm...
It's just... Lord Reynard says
that I am, so I must be.
I'm sorry, but I'm
going to go tell them.
[SHANNON]
Hold it!
Where have you been?
You can't just go running
off at a time like this!
Wait, did you just take a bath?
Yeah, so?
[BERKENS]
Hey, there, little lady.
[PACIFICA]
Are you okay, Pops?
Don't worry, I'm doin' fine.
[PACIFICA]
I just heard something terrible!
Elfitine and I were talking,
and she told me
that her people--
Destroy the city of Grendel.
[PACIFICA]
How did you know that?
[SHANNON]
There's no time to explain.
We're getting out of here.
[BERKENS] You mean, you're not
gonna try and stop the spell?
Sorry, but that's got
nothing to do with us.
[RAQUEL]
Shannon!
[SHANNON]
Escaping comes first.
Oh, Shannon! Come on!
[BERKENS]
Are you serious?
Fine. I'll go take care
of this by myself.
[SHANNON] You must really
love your job, Inquisitor.
Are you trying to
move up the ranks?
[BERKENS]
It isn't about that.
[SHANNON]
Really?
[BERKENS]
The truth is,
it doesn't have to be
Mauser or Browning
or any god for that matter.
But I think it's only
natural for people to wanna
believe in something in order
to get through their lives.
Otherwise, life can be too
hard a thing to live through.
That said, don't you think
it's crazy to try and crush
an entire group of people
just because they believe
in something different from you?
Funny. That's exactly what
you people have done.
[BERKENS]
That's why I wanna stop them.
Don't ya get it?
I don't want them to make the
same mistakes my church did.
Man, what a royal
pain in the butt.
Just so you know,
there's no way I'm gonna
buy this screwy argument
that you're trying to feed me.
[RAQUEL]
Well, then. Shall we get going?
The flows of magical energy
are all converging
right below this area.
[REYNARD]
Elfitine, it's time to go.
We're leaving this village.
[gasps]
[ELFITINE]
What?
[PACIFICA]
What is this place?
[SHANNON] You mean to say there
are people in all of those?
This is how they're
collecting their power.
Hold on. There's
something wrong.
[SHANNON]
Hm?
The spell... It can't reach
Grendel, not by using this.
[BERKENS]
Hm?
[RAQUEL]
The way this room is set up,
their attack spell could
detonate right here.
If we don't stop the people in
the meeting hall from praying,
it'll be too late!
I don't think we're gonna
be able to do that.
We should go track down
that Reynard guy.
Chances are he's
run away already.
Give me a hand here for a sec.
[SHANNON]
Huh?
I want you to push down on each
of these figures one at a time.
Oh! I'll do it!
It's funny. These places always
seem to have stuff like this.
[ELFITINE] But why are we
leaving the village now,
Lord Reynard?
[REYNARD] I'm merely
following the strategy
I had in mind from
the beginning.
They're all going to die,
just as I planned.
[ELFITINE]
Who is going to die?
[REYNARD] I'm speaking of
those fools in the village.
What?
[REYNARD]
The deaths of the villagers
who worship Lord Browning
is what will fix this world.
They are the ones who are
in need of correction!
You don't need to think
about this anymore, Elfitine.
All you need to do is come
with me now to the Holy City.
[BERKENS]
Gotta give ya credit.
You're pretty good
at being two-faced.
[REYNARD]
The Heretic Inquisitor, eh?
Excellent timing.
You can come with us to the
Holy City and make your report.
You can tell them how I sent
a whole village of
heretics straight to hell.
I neglected to
mention this before,
but like you, I am also
a Heretic Inquisitor.
[ELFITINE gasps]
What could you possibly
hope to accomplish
by killing all of those people?
[REYNARD]
There's a foolish question.
Once they learn that I've
destroyed an entire village
of Browning worshippers,
my value in the Holy
City will skyrocket!
I'm going to become
the head of the church!
What is he talking about?
Central command will
never reward you
for the killing of
innocent people.
[REYNARD]
They won't, huh?
How unfortunate.
[REYNARD] Stand back!
I've nothing to say to you!
I can't talk to those
who are unable to understand
my righteous acts!
Hey! Whatever you're thinkin'
of doing, just forget it.
[ELFITINE]
I believe in you.
[REYNARD gasps]
I believe in you, Reynard.
[REYNARD]
Huh?
[REYNARD gasps]
[ELFITINE]
I have faith in you, Reynard.
Let's go back to
the village, now.
[REYNARD]
But you don't need to think!
You just have to come with me!
I can't do that. My place
is here with the villagers.
Those people believed
in me and followed me,
and I will not walk away now and
abandon them when they need me.
So I have made up my mind.
I will go back and
join the villagers.
[REYNARD] But you can't!
Just come with me!
You don't need to
think about anything!
[gasps]
[REYNARD gasping]
[REYNARD] Don't look! Don't
look! Don't look at me!
[REYNARD screams]
[thud]
[PACIFICA]
Elfitine!
[REYNARD]
Damn it all!
[BERKENS]
That guy's completely nuts.
So tell me something.
Are there anymore idiots like
him in the Church of Mauser?
How the hell would I know?
[ELFITINE] Everyone, please!
You have to stop praying!
Listen to me!
Your prayers will only lead
to your own destruction!
But, Lady Elfitine...
[ELFITINE]
Reynard has abandoned you.
And also,
there is something else that
I must confess to all of you.
I am... I am not really
the Scrapped Princess.
I have been deceiving
you all this time.
I'm so sorry...
Please, forgive me.
[VILLAGERS gasping, murmuring]
[VILLAGER A] Lady Elfitine.
Please, lift up your head.
[AUDREY]
Lady... Elfitine...
[VILLAGER A] If you go
straight down this tunnel,
you'll reach the Giat Empire.
[ELFITINE]
Thank you. Take care.
[PACIFICA]
You, too.
What's wrong, Elfitine?
[ELFITINE]
I don't know if I can do it.
Can an inexperienced girl
like me lead a village?
[PACIFICA] But you don't see
that dark future anymore, right?
Huh?
Besides, you're pretty
regal, Elfitine.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
[giggles]
[RAQUEL]
What about you, Berkens?
[BERKENS]
Hmm?
I'll hang out here and
see how things go
before I head back to Grendel.
I don't feel like
reporting back to base.
Oh, one more thing.
The real Scrapped Princess must
have it pretty rough, too.
There are Inquisitors in
the Giat Empire as well.
Make sure you keep
her safe, you hear?
I was expecting someone
more like a witch, but...
...she's really sweet.
--You can eat this on the way.
--[SHANNON] Thanks.
Thank you, Audrey.
[ELFITINE, AUDREY]
Safe trip! Goodbye!
[VILLAGERS shouting]
Goodbye, everybody!
[PACIFICA giggles]
We're close enough
to see it now.
[BARONESS]
There it is.
The castle where Queen Elmyr,
mother of the Scrapped
Princess, lives.
[RAQUEL] At a beach beyond
the underground tunnel,
Pacifica meets a
foreign princess
who commands a
group of soldiers.
Apparently, she's known
as the "Beast Princess."
What sort of princess is
a Beast Princess, I wonder?
Does she attack people
with tooth and claw?
Next time on Scrapped Princess,
"Rhapsody of the
Beast Princess."
See you next time!