Pacifica... is the
Scrapped Princess...?
[PACIFICA]
Say, Raquel?
[RAQUEL]
Hmm?
It's tough to have to
sit and wait, isn't it?
[PACIFICA]
I'm useless.
I can't do anything
right, not even cook.
Come forth, Mr. Soopie!
A multitude of you!
Raquel, what're you doing?
[RAQUEL]
Hmm...
I thought it might be fun
if Mr. Soopie came along
to help us out with--
I'll do it myself, just get
rid of these guys, okay?
[RAQUEL giggles]
[CHRIS] I can't have my valuable
hostage catching cold now.
I don't know if they'll
rescue me. They may not come.
They might decide that I'm not
worth it and abandon me here.
After all... that's
what always happens.
Even when my parents died,
none of my relatives could
be bothered to take me in.
The innkeeper felt sorry for me,
so he let me work there.
I've never had any
real family or friends.
[CHRIS] You want me
to feel sorry for you?
At least you're able to
remember your parent's faces.
Ever since I was a little kid,
I've been in Special Ops.
There was no one I could
count on or protect,
and I followed orders
and focused on training
and risking my life.
Of course, even if I did die,
I don't think anyone
would remember me.
Are you crying?
[CHRIS]
Crying? Who, me?
Not likely.
Then why...?
[WINIA gasps]
So soft... So warm...
You sure are persistent.
It irritates me just
to look at you people!
You say that you're
protecting the princess
that will destroy
this world, and yet,
you waste your time coming here
to save a girl you hardly know!
You don't even have
the guts or ruthlessness
to kill your assassins,
and you think you can protect
the Scrapped Princess?!
What's the point
of protecting her?
What do you hope to accomplish?!
[CHRIS] You're just reveling
in the self-satisfaction
of protecting your
poor little sister!
You could be right about that.
[growls]
[yells]
[WINIA]
No!
Don't do it!
You're just jealous
of them, aren't you?!
Of those who protect each other
and those who are protected!
That's just what I
expected; you're weak!
You'll be better off
killing me, ya know.
[SHANNON]
But I'm not going to.
[SHANNON] There's something
inside me that tells me
if I killed someone
to protect her,
then she really would become
the trigger of the apocalypse.
[SHANNON] At the very least,
my sister is the type of person
who would blame herself
if somebody ever got hurt
because of her.
[CHRIS]
Victory is yours.
If that's what you think, then
never show your face again.
You, too, Miss.
You're free to go.
Please, leave.
[WINIA] I was jealous
of them too, you know.
Because I've always been alone.
[PEACEMAKER]
So he failed.
You are more formidable
than I thought, Guardian.
It is we, the Purgers
of the Church of Mauser,
who will consign the
Scrapped Princess to oblivion.
We could leave these matters
to the Royal Forces,
but they do not comprehend
the state of affairs.
Prepare, for I shall now
bestow true power upon you.
Through the divine arts
of our god Mauser,
the almighty creator,
become ye now truly one.
In the name of Galil,
fourth Peacemaker,
and on behalf of
a humble servant
of our great lord Mauser,
I now bestow upon
you this miracle.
[footsteps]
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
Winia!
[PACIFICA] Thank goodness
you're all right!
I'm sorry that I
didn't tell you.
I thought it would
cause trouble for you
if I said anything, Winia.
But... I still wanted
us to be friends.
Come on, let's go eat something.
I bet you're hungry, right?
You, too, Shannon! We made
a lotta food last night.
I'm gonna get a little sleep.
[PACIFICA]
What?
But you're the one who told us
to have a meal waiting for you.
We'll leave after we've
eaten, don't worry.
[gasps]
Winnia.
Uncle...
Here, come with me.
[PACIFICA] I guess we
got Winia involved, too.
If only I hadn't thought
that we could be friends,
how silly of me.
[LEO]
Good morning, everybody!
Wow! What an amazing
feast for breakfast!
Please feel free to
help yourself, Leo.
Really? Can I?!
This will let me work
hard again all day today!
Wow! What is this? How're
you supposed to eat it?
Just shut up!
It's not my fault...
[LEO]
Huh?
[SHANNON] Hand-made by
Pacifica herself, it seems.
This dumpling is bite-sized!
I'll give it a try!
Once I finish breakfast...
it's off to my Mr. Soopie job.
[INNKEEPER]
About those people...
[WINIA]
They said they would leave
after they finished eating.
They know... They know they're
no longer welcome here.
[FEMALE OFFICER]
Chris?
My mission was a failure.
I completely failed.
[horse whinnies]
[CHRIS]
Major Sturm!
Why are you here, sir?
Does this mean that Blackhawk
is also making its move
to eliminate the
Scrapped Princess?
[STURM]
Yeah.
They've already
infiltrated the city
in order to gather
more intelligence.
And if worst came to worst,
we were supposed to eliminate
any and all witnesses
to keep word of this spreading.
We were to attack once
the Scrapped Princess
had left the city.
That was the plan, anyway.
I've received a private message
from the capital, however.
[CHRIS]
What is it?
The church has
unilaterally decided
to send Purgers into this city.
They sent Purgers?
[STURM] Plus, they're
carrying papal documents
telling them to
eliminate this town
along with the
Scrapped Princess.
Destroy the entire city?
They must be out of their minds.
Our mission has changed as well.
We are to abort
any direct action
against the Scrapped Princess
and simply observe
their activity.
I'll go and help relay
the change in orders.
I'll inform the men.
I appreciate it.
[PACIFICA]
Well, we're off.
Look, we're sorry, but we're a
little short on the room bill.
We'll send you the
money once we have it.
We apologize.
[PACIFICA] I'm sorry you went
through all that scary stuff.
Still, I had a lotta fun here.
She didn't...
even say goodbye...
[LEO] Once we're married,
I wonder if every morning...
...she's gonna make me...
...a breakfast as big as that.
Stay focused!
Is something wrong, Shannon?
We've got company. Get inside.
Huh?
We'll make a break for it!
I bring a priority message
from Major Sturm.
Code Crimson, 0037.
[SHANNON]
Hey, didn't I tell you
never to show your
face again, Axe Boy?
[CHRIS] Actually, I prefer
to be called Chris.
I'll smack you, you little brat!
Hey, Shannon?
More importantly, the city
is in serious trouble now.
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[RAQUEL] God or demon,
be ye here destroyed!
That's quite impressive.
Is this any time
for compliments?
Well, my orders are
simply to stand by
and observe what happens here.
Wait! Shannon!
Could this be what Zefiris
was talking about?
[VOICE] Hear me, humans.
Listen and obey.
By all that is holy,
I order you, destroy it.
Destroy the seed of destruction.
Its name is Pacifica Cassul.
Shannon?
[gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Raquel?
No... No way...
Shannon! Raquel, wake up!
[VOICE]
Destroy.
Shannon, no...
[VOICE]
Destroy.
Why are you doing this? Raquel?
Why are you listening
to what that voice says?
Why are you two obeying him?
[VOICE]
Destroy.
Big Brother.
[VOICE]
Destroy.
No...
[PACIFICA]
No... This can't be happening...
No!
[SHANNON panting]
[gasps]
I almost...
Big Brother..
...are you okay?
Yeah.
[VILLAGERS whimpering]
[GALIL]
Pacifica Cassul...
So, thou art truly the one.
Pacifica!
[GALIL] In that case, I shall
merely swallow up any and all
who know of thee.
[VILLAGERS screaming]
I can't attack now!
Not like this!
Stop it... Make it stop!
Chris!
If you don't take out the
core, you'll never stop it.
But... what about the people
who've been swallowed?
[CHRIS]
I told you before, didn't I?
If you wanna protect one person,
you have to be prepared
to kill another!
Regardless of what
you might believe!
[PACIFICA] No... I can't stand
this... I can't watch anymore...
This is all my fault...
This is all because of me...
Pacifica!
[SHANNON]
Hey!
[PACIFICA] I'm the poison that's
gonna destroy the world, right?!
If that's the truth, then
you should just kill me!
[CHRIS]
It stopped moving.
Raquel.
O chained creature,
be thou released,
for thou art the
rod of destruction!
[yells]
[GALIL]
The duty of Peacemakers
is to safeguard
order on this world.
They are meant to
be above humanity.
Pacifica Cassul...
[INNKEEPER]
It's okay.
[WINIA]
Huh?
[ZEFIRIS]
Well done.
That was most likely a proxy
sent by a Peacemaker.
I'm impressed you stood up to
that creature in human form.
That is the reason
you are the poison
that will destroy the world.
As well as the final hope
bequeathed to us by our lord.
[VILLAGER A]
That girl is really her?
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
[VILLAGER B] I hear she's got
the blood of the devil in her.
Ready to go?
Yes...
[VILLAGER C] She's dangerous
to have around...
[WINIA]
Pacifica!
[gasps]
[WINIA] We'll put your
room fee on your tab,
so come back to pay it someday!
You hear me?!
Winia...
You really shouldn't
say that, you know...
After all, I'm the--
I'll be waiting for you.
I mean, it's my fault
that the city was...
I'll be waiting.
[WINIA]
Shannon.
I'm sorry I couldn't
say it before,
but I wanted to thank you
personally for rescuing me.
Shannon.
Thank you for everything!
Thank you, Winia!
[WINIA]
Sure! I'll see you again soon!
[LEO screams]
Pardon me! Excuse me! Ah!
Oh no... They've left already.
Wait a sec. Huh?
Wh... What in the world
happened around here?
[SHANNON]
That girl is strong.
She's much stronger than us.
Shannon...
Raquel, do you really think
we'll be able to protect her?
Can we really keep her safe?
[PRINCE]
The Scrapped Princess is alive?
My sister?
[RAQUEL]
A flighty man with no name
appears before the
Cassul siblings.
Believe it or not, this man
who plays such dulcet tones
is actually an assassin
who is after a bounty!
Will Pacifica, who has collapsed
after a surprise attack,
ever wake up again?
Next time on Scrapped Princess,
"Lullaby of the Troubadour."
See you next time!