[PACIFICA]
Hey, Raquel.
If we hang around
here much longer,
I bet that Natalie's gonna try
to do something to us again.
I suppose.
[sighs]
I don't know what's
so interesting here.
Can you tell what
any of this stuff is?
[RAQUEL]
No, not at all.
But they said that long ago,
people fought the gods
using machinery like this.
It was supposed to
enhance the abilities
of people with psychic powers.
[PACIFICA]
Yeah...
And they also said something
about them being betrayed.
[RAQUEL]
From what Miss Eirote tells me,
all of this machinery works by
combining simple
calculation algorithms
in order to convey
complicated instructions.
Magic works exactly
the same way.
It's very interesting.
Really... I wouldn't know.
[intercom beeps]
[SENES]
Hey, you two, listen up.
We'll be reaching the
coast of Sauer soon.
I need you on the bridge.
[gasps]
[RAQUEL chuckles]
[PACIFICA chuckles]
Come on, Raquel, let's go!
If we're late, ol' tomboy Senes
will throw a fit and snarl.
[EIROTE giggles]
You know, I can still
hear you, you little brat.
What's wrong?
Feeling nostalgic about home?
Not really.
The village that you three grew
up in must've been a nice place.
[SHANNON]
You know our village?
No, it's just that
I get that feeling
when I look at you
and your sisters.
It must be nice to have a home,
a place you wanna go back to.
[PETERS-STAHL]
We are in a difficult situation.
The Giat Empire's
special weapon,
the Skid, is right
off our coast.
This is obviously an invasion.
We, the members of the
Leinwan Royal Forces,
must meet this imminent
threat with resolve
and smash it utterly.
[GENERAL A] That may be
the case, but this is the Skid.
It's a weapon built by the race
of evil during the Genesis Wars.
Wouldn't any attempt to take it
by force be extremely difficult?
That's true. We probably
can't destroy it
by simple cannon attack.
Which is why I
propose the use of
the strategic-grade
offensive spell, Ginnungagap.
[GENERAL B]
Preposterous!
[GENERAL C]
Why would we need to use that?!
[GENERAL D]
Ginnungagap?
The use of that spell
is banned by treaty!
[PETERS-STAHL]
Shall we uphold the treaty
and let our country fall?
This is an invasion.
Gentlemen, our first priority
is to destroy the Skid
and then, we should march
on the Giat Empire.
[BARONESS] A moment please,
General Peters-Stahl.
Something to add, Lady Bairach?
I have heard reports that the
Skid set out on its journey
after trading fire with its
own country's Second Fleet.
It is possible the Skid's crew
was seen as a rebel force
by Giat and they sent out
the fleet to pursue them.
It may be too early to
say this is an invasion.
[PETERS-STAHL]
What if that was a ruse
designed to confuse
and mislead us?
If their main forces arrive
and begin a joint
assault with the Skid,
it will be too
late for us to act.
Which is why it is crucial
to ascertain the
truth of the situation.
If we break the treaty now,
then a plunge into
all-out war is inevitable.
In the end, we will exhaust our
military forces for nothing.
You believe our forces will be
defeated by the likes of Giat?
Fortune can smile on the enemy.
[PETERS-STAHL chuckles]
Well, well. Those are hardly
the words I would expect to hear
from the woman who controls the
legendary Special Forces unit.
Justice is on our side.
Besides, that Skid is
harboring the poison
that will destroy the world,
the Scrapped Princess.
[GENERALS murmuring]
[PETERS-STAHL] For the sake of
peace, not only for our country,
but for the entire world,
we must eliminate her.
We are fighting a holy war.
Wouldn't you say that's true,
Cardinal Hogue?
Yes, of course, General.
[KING BALTERIC] I don't care
what you have to do to win.
There isn't a moment to lose.
You must destroy
the Scrapped Princess!
[BARONESS]
What do you intend to do?
[LUKE] I will standby
and receive my orders.
Of course, that's all
we really can do.
Yes, we are both soldiers,
after all.
[STEYR] What are you
afraid of, Cardinal?
[HOGUE gasps]
Lady Steyr!
[STEYR] Everything's going
according to plan.
The Scrapped Princess
will die soon.
But just to be on the safe side,
go ahead and keep
agitating the King
just as you've been doing.
Understand?
[HOGUE]
Yes, milady.
A strategic-grade
offensive spell.
It turned out just like
Jill predicted, didn't it?
Our country will be engaging
the special fortress
from the Giat Empire very soon.
You will probably receive
operation orders any day now.
Christopher?
I should report this
to Prince Forsyth.
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[footsteps]
Everyone seems all
worked up for some reason.
Yeah...
Well, there are a lot of people
living here in the Capital,
so maybe it's always like this.
Since we're here, let's hurry up
and go your friend's house,
shall we?
[WINIA gasps]
Right!
[FORSYTH]
Father, I beg of you.
Please reconsider
what you're doing.
We mustn't throw away the
lives of our precious soldiers
in a needless war!
[KING BALTERIC]
Silence!
[FORSYTH gasps]
[KING BALTERIC] Don't look
at me with those eyes!
Your eyes are just
like your mother's.
She disobeyed my command
and allowed our
daughter to escape.
I'm sure your sister must
have the same eyes as you.
[door clicks]
He wouldn't even listen
to me, just as I expected.
[CHRIS]
I see.
He's lost his mind.
He's going to start a war.
Countless numbers of
our people will die
just so he can kill
the Scrapped Princess.
I don't understand.
What in the world
is Father thinking?
[LEO]
What's the matter, Miss Winia?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just this house is huge.
[LEO]
You think so?
For a baronial family estate,
I think the design is
rather pedestrian, personally.
Still, it's odd for there to
be no guards manning the gate.
Um, Leo, do you know
a lot about nobles
and how they build
their estates?
[LEO]
Oh, I never told you before?
I'm the eldest son
of Baron Skorpus,
the ruling lord of
the barony of Takos.
I'm on a training tour
at the moment though.
Oh, I didn't know.
[LEO]
This is sorta awkward.
We can't simply
barge in unannounced.
I suppose I'll just have
to stand here and shout
until someone comes.
[WINIA]
Um... That's all right.
[LEO]
Huh?
Don't bother.
It's sort of rude for me
to come without asking.
Let's just go.
[LEO] Don't talk
like that, Miss Winia!
[WINIA gasps]
You came here to see someone
you really care about!
You can't just give up, not when
you're so close to seeing him!
Or at least, that's what I think
Miss Pacifica would
say if she were here.
[gasps]
It's Chris.
[sighs]
Um, I--
[gasps]
Baron Bairach!
[gate clangs]
Miss Winia...
[WINIA]
It's okay.
[LEO]
Uh--
It's fine. I'm sure
he has his reasons.
Or am I just trying to be
too optimistic about it?
No, not at all, Miss Winia.
You're right.
Yeah...
[WIZARD A]
Ginnungagap?!
They can't be serious!
[WIZARD B]
The ship may be offshore,
but the people on the coast
will be hit by the blast!
All I know is that this
is an official order
from His Majesty, the King.
Please begin with your stage
one incantations immediately.
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
[SHANNON]
There's no sign of activity.
[SENES] We're here now,
so what are they waiting for?
[PACIFICA hissing]
[RAQUEL]
Pacifica! Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm a little scared,
that's all.
You said earlier
that the Peacemakers
can't attack Pacifica directly,
am I right?
[EIROTE]
Yes, they will most likely
try to use humans to
attack her instead.
[PACIFICA] Maybe they just
don't know that we're yet.
Maybe we should try
to signal them or--
What are you, an idiot?!
They're Peacemakers;
they can detect our movements
whenever they want.
Yeah, I guess I am.
[SENES] Well, as long as the
Skid's defensive functions
are online, they could
fire a million
large-bore cannonballs at us,
and it still
wouldn't even dent us.
[ZEFIRIS]
Do not let your guard down.
The Peacemakers are aware of the
capabilities of this fortress.
We can assume that they are
avoiding unnecessary
combat for a reason.
I'm surprised you can show
your face in front of me.
Or don't Dragons possess that
kind of human sensitivity?
--[PACIFICA grunts]
--[SHANNON] Ah!
That hurt, you little twerp!
How can you talk
to her like that?!
She helped me save you!
If it weren't for Zefiris,
you'd still be brainwashed!
And I wouldn't have been
brainwashed in the first place
if she hadn't been working
in league with Natalie!
And that's not all.
She never bothered
to tell us the truth
and decided to use us, instead.
All right, already!
That might be true,
but you don't understand!
Zefiris has problems of her own!
Ugh, whatever.
There's no point in fighting
with you about this now.
What are the Peacemakers
after anyway?
[ZEFIRIS] Probably a
strategic-grade offensive spell.
[RAQUEL gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
Strategic-grade? What's that?
[RAQUEL]
It must be Ginnungagap.
[SHANNON] Is that the spell
Reynard was trying to cast
in the heretic village?
[RAQUEL]
The principle is the same.
However, if a group of
elite military wizards
were to cast such a spell,
then its power would be
immeasurable greater.
[SENES]
Hey, wait a minute.
Spells that powerful are
supposed to be banned by treaty.
Treaties mean nothing
in the face of
irresistible Peacemaker
mind control.
After all, that treaty
was originally designed
by the Peacemakers via
the Church of Mauser.
But still, incantations for
those kinds of spells
take a long time.
And you can't fire
them off very quickly.
I believe that the Skid's
defensive function
should be able to
withstand such an attack.
[ZEFIRIS]
They can.
However, the Peacemakers
are also very aware
of that same fact.
[STEYR]
This is taking forever.
We've got some time to kill,
so why don't we release a few
proxies inside the Capital?
[CZ]
Don't.
Tactics like that are pointless.
[STEYR]
Y'know, Cz, I think you may have
spent a little too
much time stuck in
that childish,
halfway uncompressed state.
[CZ]
What do you mean?
[STEYR] You'd like to avoid
human deaths if at all possible.
Isn't that what you're thinking?
[CZ]
We are Peacemakers.
We're programmed to
preserve the human race
in a stable state, so it's
natural to avoid bloodshed.
[STEYR]
Is it really?
I don't know; your thinking
seems awfully human to me.
Right, Socom?
[SOCOM]
Perhaps, so.
But nevertheless,
Cz's opinion does have merit.
The wizards have already begun
the spell's incantation.
There is no need for us
to resort to cheap tricks.
[STEYR]
Oh, come on.
You Artillery-types about
as subtle and nuanced
as a sledgehammer.
Brute force is
all well and good,
but doesn't a little cunning
give you more of a thrill?
[CZ] You're the one who
thinks too much like a human.
[SOCOM]
I would prefer to avoid
any direct intervention
on our part.
As we planned earlier,
suppressing the defense
and mobility functions
of the mobile fortress
should be sufficient.
[STEYR]
Here we are, three Peacemakers,
and we're resorting to parlor
tricks in order to win.
[SOCOM] I just want the job
done as efficiently as possible.
I'm not interested
in being flashy.
[STEYR]
Fine, fine.
[PILOT B]
Princess, Senes!
The defense system output
is dropping rapidly.
I can't maintain the shields.
What?! What's causing it?
[PILOT B]
I don't know.
But it doesn't seem to be
damaged from the outside.
Wait, is it Natalie?
[NATALIE]
I'm not the one doing it.
[ALL gasp]
[SENES]
You expect us to believe you?
As long as Pacifica Cassul
is aboard this ship,
I have no reason to want
to expose her to danger.
That's true.
The impression
I'm getting is that
the defense system is being
ripped apart at the seams
by some invisible force.
Invisible force? Are the
Peacemakers behind this?
Of course. It's being
controlled remotely.
You must get away from here.
Retreat, Senes Lur Giat.
I should what?!
If we were to take a direct hit
from a strategic-grade spell
with our defense systems
locked down like this,
none of us would survive.
[SENES]
Forget it!
Those Peacemakers
are here, right?
You want me to run away
when the ones who killed
my men are just outside?
[NATALIE] You would
be killed by the humans
that the Peacemakers control
long before you ever had
a chance to fight them.
Damn it.
Withdraw, full speed!
[PILOT A]
Roger.
[radar beeps]
[PILOT A]
Hm?
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
[PILOT A]
The helm's not responding.
What's that?
What do you mean
it's not responding?
Do something!
Big Sister...
We should abandon ship.
[SHANNON]
Why you little--!
You expect us to just let the
people in the Capital die?!
[ZEFIRIS] I believe I understand
how you feel about all of this.
But this fortress is now nothing
more than a large target
floating the water.
If you stay here,
Pacifica will die.
And the rest of you
will go along with her.
I expect that such an outcome
would be undesirable to you.
I'll go out and fight the
Peacemakers with the Dragoon.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
If I can manage to loosen
their grip on the fortress,
then we should be able
to move again, right?
Perhaps, my Lord, but three
Peacemakers have assembled here.
In terms of power, we are
completely outmatched.
So what else is new?
[ZEFIRIS] The Peacemaker Cz
is also with them.
[ALL gasp]
If you are going to fight,
you will not win
unless you are prepared to
utterly destroy your enemy.
Are you able to fight
Cz without holding back?
[SHANNON]
Yeah.
[SENES]
Shannon Cassul.
Don't do anything stupid.
Right.
[SHANNON]
Let's go.
Zefiris, I want you to
give me all the power
that you have access
to right now.
It's too dangerous
and you still have deep
misgivings about me, my Lord.
If the fusion is incomplete,
it will put such a strain
on your body that--
Now is not the time
to be holding back!
As you wish.
[grunts]
[SHANNON roars]
[ALL gasp]
[PACIFICA]
What is that thing?
That creature there is
a Dragoon's true form.
[STEYR]
Here they come.
[CZ] So, she's finally
taken physical form.
Can the two of you
maintain control
of the mobile fortress
by yourselves?
[SOCOM]
We can keep it from moving.
[CZ] In that case,
I'll handle the Dragoon.
[CZ] Second class
divine retribution
enforcement configuration,
engage.
[SHANNON gasps]
[ZEFIRIS]
It's Cz.
[SHANNON]
Cz...
[PILOT B] The defense systems
have recovered by 20%.
Divert all power to
engines and break away.
This is our chance.
Cz will be focused
on the battle.
All right, maximum output, now!
Roger!
[STEYR chuckles]
They're putting up a fight.
[SOCOM]
Futile.
[PACIFICA yelps]
[SHANNON]
Stop it, Cz! I don't want to--
[CZ]
Silence!
If you want to say
something to your enemy,
then make sure you do it after
you've crushed them underfoot
with overwhelming force!
[SHANNON gasps]
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
Huh? Huh?
[RAQUEL gasps]
Barrier, protect us!
[PACIFICA]
Big Sister...
[RAQUEL]
Pacifica!
[SHANNON]
No...!
[CZ]
Our mission is complete for now.
[MESSENGER] The strategic-grade
offensive spell, Ginnungagap,
has manifested above the
Giant Empire's special fortress,
the Skid. Half of the
ship has been destroyed.
We are searching for
survivors using magic,
but no life signs have
been detected as of yet.
We believe the threat from the
target has been eliminated.
[PETERS-STAHL]
Good work.
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
[MAN] They cast the spell
with no warning, huh?
They'll do anything for
the sake of a mission.
Even if the explosion
triggers a tsunami.
I'd say the military's
MO hasn't changed.
Uh... Excuse me,
but who are you?
[MAN]
When you meet someone new,
aren't you supposed to
give your own name first?
Yeah, you're probably right.
I just can't remember anything.
My name, my family, nothing.
You don't know who I am, do you?
[MAN]
Sorry, Kid, but I don't know ya.
Oh, too bad...
[MAN]
Later.
Hey, why are you
following me like that?
Because I don't know
anyone else here.
And if I follow you, I might
run into someone who knows me.
Suit yourself.
So tell me, what is your name?
The name's Furet.
[PACIFICA]
Hmm...
[FURET chuckles]
For someone who can't
remember anything,
you sure seem to
be in a good mood.
Ya think so?
Well then, maybe I'm better
off not remembering who I am!
[giggles]
[RAQUEL]
The Skid has been destroyed,
and the Cassul siblings
have been split up.
Shannon and Raquel frantically
search for Pacifica.
But Pacifica has no idea
that they're looking for her
and has been living a carefree
live with a boy named Furet.
It's important to kick back and
relax once in a while, isn't it?
Next time on
Scrapped Princess,
"Duet by the Riverside."
See you next time!