[COLETTE]
How horrible.
The demon that destroyed
the capital has returned.
No, you are mistaken Colette.
That is one of god's
divine messengers.
What?
[HOGUE] Please, Colette.
Let me confess my sins to you.
[COLETTE]
Cardinal Hogue!
[RAQUEL]
Pacifica.
Pacifica!
[SENES] Looks like you're
having some trouble.
[SHANNON]
Senes! You're with me.
Pacifica's been stabbed.
We don't have a second to lose.
She's what?!
[SHANNON]
Dammit.
Hurry! Let's take
cover by those rocks.
[SOLDIER A]
There they are!
[EIROTE]
Huh?
Uh?!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
You'll die if they sting you,
so please be careful.
[EIROTE]
Who are you?
The introductions can wait.
It looks like we should
get out of this place
while we still can.
[SOLDIER B groans]
How you doing?
[SOLDIER C groans]
We're holding our own.
Fafal!
Worthless rebel scum!
Don't let up!
Continue the barrage!
[RAQUEL]
Why...?
Why won't the bleeding stop?!
Somebody!
Somebody help her! Somebody!
[whimpering]
[RAQUEL]
Help her, god.
Devine Lord Mauser...
Please forgive my little sister.
Please forgive Pacifica!
--[SHANNON] Pacifica. Pacifica!
--[ZEFIRIS] Shannon! Calm down.
[ZEFIRIS] You can't kill
them with one shot.
[SOCOM]
What are you aiming at?
Is that all you've got?
[SHANNON]
I'm going to kill you!
[RAQUEL]
Pacifica... Pacifica!
Hey Raquel...
[gasps]
Where's big brother?
[RAQUEL gasping]
[RAQUEL]
No!
Why... Why?!
I couldn't do anything
to save her...
to save her.
Uh. What's that?
[WINIA gasps]
[BERKENS]
What the hell?
[gasps]
Pacifica!
Pacifica! Pacifica!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[SHANNON]
What's this? What's going on?
[ZEFIRIS]
I don't know.
It looks like we've been thrown
clear of the atmosphere.
[CZ] The sealed world has gone
into autistic mode... But why?
[SOCOM]
This was not anticipated.
I am unable to
contact the system.
I will therefore release the
restrictions on our powers.
[SHANNON]
What the hell...?
[SENES] Ruth! Drake!
Defend Shannon no matter what!
[RUTH, DRAKE]
Yes, ma'am!
[SHANNON] Zefy, give me
everything you've got!
[ZEFIRIS]
Understood.
[SHANNON]
Do it now!
Ruth, no!
Ruth, answer me!
[RUTH]
I'm okay!
[SOCOM]
Now.
[CZ]
Wait, Socom.
[SHANNON]
Dammit.
[CZ]
I'm sorry.
No, Cz!
[SHANNON gasping]
[SHANNON]
Dammit Cz...
[PACIFICA]
Shannon...
Raquel....
[PACIFICA]
Is this place... heaven?
[CELIA] This is a virtual
reality location
that's been created
within the free space
of the sealed world's
control system.
You've left the vessel of
your physical body behind you
and entered into the
heart of the system
that controls your world.
What the heck are
you doing here?!
Wait, does that mean
that you're dead, too?!
Who are you?
You can call me Celia.
I am Celia Mauser.
[gasps]
You're Lord Mauser?
[ZEFIRIS]
Hey Shannon. Are you all right?
[SHANNON]
What about Pacifica?!
What's happened to our world?!
[ZEFIRIS] It's functions have
been completely locked down
for some reason.
My links to Natalie have
been cut off as well.
[grunts]
Does that mean... you're god?
Me a god? No.
I'm just a traitor.
I'm the one who locked up
humanity in this world.
It's just...
[CELIA]
I know.
You were born for the sole
purpose of destroying me.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
Over the past 16 years,
your body has built up the
power needed to destroy me.
That immense power was
designed to be released
at the moment of your death.
Wait, so then I was supposed to
destroy you as soon as I died?
[CELIA] However, that seems to
have happened 10 hours short
of your power reaching its peak.
At this moment,
your powers and mine
are caught in
precise equilibrium,
and because of that,
the slightest nudge could
cause the balance to shift
in either direction.
That is why I want you to
make the final decision.
[PACIFICA]
Uh?
[CELIA]
Long before you were born,
back in the time
of the ancients,
humanity fought a terrible war.
The war dragged on
for years and years,
and many people died
because of it.
It was then, in the
midst of that slaughter,
that I received a
message from the enemy.
They wanted me to supply
them with information
on humanity's forces,
so they could end the war
and preserve the human race.
From the enemy's point of view,
human beings were a rare
and precious form of life.
[CELIA]
They were trying to find a way
to save a species that seemed
bent on self-destruction.
I did as they asked and
gave them the information.
I thought that if something
wasn't done soon,
I would eventually lose
my brother and sister.
After that, all of humanity
was locked away in
this sealed world,
and I was implanted
into the system's core
as their caretaker.
I have tended this
miniature garden
for more than 5,000 years now.
[PACIFICA gasps]
[CELIA]
My younger brother and sister.
All I wanted was to keep
the two of them alive.
I did all of this for them.
Even if humanity was
locked away forever,
it was enough for
me if they survived.
However, I was too late.
[BECKNAM] Zefy, please.
I want you to survive.
[ZEFIRIS]
Lord Becknam, no!
The enemy has discovered
our tactical patterns!
Zefiris! Gloria! Natalie!
All surviving units, retreat
into phase space immediately!
[gasps, yelps]
[CELIA] I just wanted my
brother and sister to survive.
Truly. That is all I wanted.
This is the body you possess
in the physical world.
[CELIA] The vessel that you have
inhabited for 140,150 hours.
I want you to make the decision.
Decision?
I'd like for you to decide
whether this world should
continue as it is.
I'm no longer certain
I made the right choice.
I don't know, either!
All this stuff about humanity
and the world is so...
[CELIA] Just tell me
what your heart says.
[gasps]
Do you honestly feel
what I did was wrong?
I'm not sure.
I think I understand
what you did.
I have a brother and sister
that I care about, too.
If there was something
I could do that would
keep the two of them
safe from harm,
I think I would have to do it,
no matter what it was.
I'd try to help them,
even if it took thousands or
tens of thousands of years.
[PACIFICA] And yet, even if
people could live safely
inside that closed-off
world like that,
I still think there would
be something wrong
about it somehow.
Even if someone
chooses the wrong path,
it was something
they chose themselves
and it's their responsibility.
That means you're free to make
your own decisions in life.
Having to live in a world
where you can't make
your own decisions,
that sort of a world is
just so wrong to me.
I suppose it is.
[laughs]
Does that answer your question?
[CELIA]
Thank you.
Now I can finally be set free.
Huh? Set free? But...
Hey, wait!
I'm sorry! I take it all back!
[CELIA]
It's all right.
I am finally free now to join
my little brother and sister.
But Celia...
Farewell to you,
Pacifica Cassul.
[gasps]
[RAQUEL gasping]
[CELIA] Hear me now,
humanity, and listen.
[CELIA]
I am Mauser.
Sheathe your restless swords
and withdraw your soldiers.
The seed of destruction
has passed you by.
The terrible poison you
have feared for so long
will never again wreak
its havoc upon your world.
The doors have now been opened.
Humanity...
I return to you
now your freedom.
I give you new lands.
And let you behold
the true sky above you.
[CELIA] There will be
no more revelations.
No more prophesies.
From now on, you will have to
walk hand-in-hand with others,
and choose your own destiny.
[CELIA] Mauser is not
in the heavens above you.
Divinity is within
your own hearts.
Now is the time for you
to weave your own future,
and decide your own fate.
[gasps]
Hey, big brother.
Pacifica.
[SHANNON groans]
[PACIFICA screams]
Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!
Pervert!
[SHANNON]
You little twerp!
I used to bathe you
when were a kid,
so who cares if you're naked?!
[PACIFICA] Well, you should be
able to look right at me, then.
[gasps]
See?! You can't even look at me!
You closet perv!
[SHANNON] How about a little
embarrassment with your anger,
you shameless princess!
[PACIFICA] How dare you
call me that, you pedophile?!
[SHANNON] Who are you calling a
pedophile, you exhibitionist?!
[BERKENS]
Look! His wound.
[gasps]
Um...
I'm back, Sis.
[FORSYTH]
But, I...
Come.
Please stand up, Prince Forsyth.
[gasps]
[LUKE]
General?
Are we stopping by the Cassuls'?
They said they're coming later.
[LEO]
Miss Pacifica!
Miss Pacifica?!
C'mon Miss Pacifica,
Prince Forsyth's coronation
ceremony is tomorrow.
Princess Senes and
her people are waiting,
and the Bairachs left
for Castle Sauer ages ago.
[PACIFICA grunts] Dragunov's
about to go into labor.
I can't just leave her
at a time like this!
Yeah, but--
Oh, tell Forsyth I'll make sure
to come to his next one, okay?
To the next one?
Pacifica, what's the
holdup over there?!
Please hurry up
with the firewood!
Sure! I'll be right there.
You better shake
a leg, Pacifica.
I know already! I heard.
Okay. Let's see here...
[LEO] Miss Pacifica.
Are you happy now?
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[PACIFICA chuckles]
I guess so.
It's peaceful, and every
day is lots of fun.
It's not all wine
and roses, but still...
It's not like I have
to form an opinion
on my whole life
right now though.
Maybe that's what really
matters in the end.
Being able to look
back over your life
when you're on your deathbed,
and say to yourself,
"You know, it wasn't half bad."
You know what?
I'm sort of glad I was born
as the Scrapped Princess.
I had to go through lots
of painful stuff, but,
I went to all kinds of places
and met all sorts of people.
And if I weren't the
Scrapped Princess,
then the two of us probably
would never have met.
[PACIFICA]
Hm?
[LEO]
What's that?
Oh.
Whenever I wear this,
I feel protected somehow.
Miss Pacifica.
I'm going to ask
you one more time.
Huh?
[LEO] Please do the
honor of marrying me.
Uh... Ah!
Ow. That hurt.
You are so out of your league,
you big loser! Hmph!
[LEO]
Huh?
Uh! Wait! Please, come back!
I mean it! Honest! I really
do love you, Miss Pacifica!