[SOCOM]
Greetings, my Master.
Now that we have lost the two
Peacemakers Galil and Steyr
to the enemy, the likelihood of
our being able to eliminate
the Providence Breaker is slim.
As such, I hereby request
authorization for the use of
class one divine
punishment configurations.
[CELIA] I cannot condone the
use of class one configurations
within the atmosphere.
You are authorized only
to continue using only
your class two configurations.
[SOCOM]
Understood.
[hammering]
Fafal, once you're finished,
go stand guard.
Sure thing.
[hammering continues]
Have any luck?
I'm still not sensing
anybody in the area
that could be the Royal Forces.
That's good.
[LEO yells]
[SUTTON grunts]
What's with this hippo?
He's actually a dragon.
His name is Mr. Soopie.
[SUTTON]
Don't you think he reeks?
[LEO]
No, not at all.
[PACIFICA giggles]
Come on, Pacifica.
You need to help out, too.
Go fetch some
water or something.
This is just like
we're camping out.
Except that we're fugitives.
Good work.
I feel better knowing
that you're here now.
Thanks, Eirote.
Well, it looks like the damage
is a lot worse than I imagined.
[SENES] We'll be
fighting the Peacemakers
and the Royal Forces again soon.
Work up a damage report
and tell me how long
they'll take to regenerate.
[EIROTE]
Yes, ma'am.
Then you still
haven't found her?!
Send the whole army if you must!
[LUKE]
But General...
We're busy with reconstruction.
Our search and rescue
teams are overloaded.
[PETERS-STAHL]
We can worry about that later.
We have to hand the girl
over to the Peacemakers
as soon as possible.
[footsteps]
[BERKENS]
Prince Forsyth?
I thought I'd bring
you some lunch.
Berkens, that's kind of you.
How are things in the Capital?
I've heard they started the
reconstruction work already.
And that they've even begun
repairing the castle itself.
However...
His Majesty is still missing.
I see.
And my sister?
The Scrapped Princess?
Apparently, they're still
searching for her.
[FORSYTH]
I see. So she's still alive.
Dinner is served!
[ALL gasp]
[PACIFICA] Now don't be shy;
there's plenty for everybody.
Where's Senes and her crew?
They said they'd
eat at their camp.
[PACIFICA] Oh! Hey, Zefiris!
You wanna join us?
Weapon systems like me don't
need to eat, so I'll abstain.
Who cares if you're a weapon?
Stop lurking back there.
Come here and join us, Zefy.
[PACIFICA]
Here!
It's just for appearances sake.
Yes, sir.
I never thought that someday
I'd be eating a meal
that was cooked by
the Scrapped Princess.
[DENNIS]
Let's dig in!
[ALL gag, wretch]
[SUTTON]
Oh... You gotta be kidding me!
[DENNIS]
Oh, man!
[FAFAL]
Unbelievable!
[SUTTON] Her poison's
gonna destroy my stomach
before it destroys the world!
Sorry about that.
We should've warned you first.
[LEO]
Nonsense! It's delicious.
[coughs]
[WINIA]
Excuse me.
I've just finished
cooking my dish.
[ALL gasp]
[SUTTON]
Wow, this tastes great!
[FAFAL]
It's delicious!
[DENNIS]
This is so good!
[SUTTON]
This tastes great!
[DENNIS]
We heard ya the first time.
Make me puke already.
Excuse me...
[PACIFICA]
Hmph.
[LEO]
Uh--
Here, Chris. Please have some.
[CHRIS]
Thanks.
None of you people
possesses the gene.
[CHRIS]
Huh?
[ZEFIRIS]
The Guardian gene.
Who's Jean?
[WINIA]
Guardian gene.
That's right. It was
seeded across the world
in order to protect
the Providence Breaker.
Apparently, Raquel and I
both have this thing.
Leo and Winia, too.
We're here because
we all want to be here.
There's no other reason.
Plus, we've got nowhere
to go back to. Not anymore.
Yeah, nobody ordered us.
We just came on our own.
Wow! I really hope
that more people
start to think like they do.
[PACIFICA] Still...
I guess it's all my fault.
If none of you guys
had ever run into me,
then everyone...
...would have avoided
being tortured
by your lousing cooking.
So, we're back on that, are we?!
Well, that's our most
immediate threat right now.
[PACIFICA]
Oh, what do you know?!
You wouldn't know good
cooking if it bit you!
Now, take it easy...
[PACIFICA] Still, it feels
good to be able to
eat with everybody like this.
It's really nice.
I feel happy!
[RAQUEL chuckles]
[PACIFICA sighs]
This feels so good!
Are your feet hurting you?
Shall I make some
Mr. Soopies to massage them?
Pass.
Really?
I've put out a blanket for you.
Oh, thank you, Winia.
[WINIA]
What is it?
Nothing... Thanks a lot.
I heard you the first time.
No, not for that.
I mean for coming all this way.
I'm sorry... that you're
mixed up in this.
That's okay.
I wanted to come along anyway.
To be honest,
you're not the only reason
I came out here, Pacifica.
Huh?
[WINIA]
I-It's nothing.
What is it?
There's another
reason you came here?
[WINIA]
I said it's nothing, okay?
Wait a sec.
Why are you blushing
all of a sudden?
Come on, tell me!
Pacifica, how long are
you going to wear that?
Why don't you change?
[PACIFICA] But I don't have
anything to change into.
I told you before, your outfit's
in Shannon's tent.
[PACIFICA]
Oh, you did?
Well, good night then.
[SHANNON grunts]
I get the feeling... you don't
want to share a tent.
[SHANNON]
Can't say I'm thrilled about it.
Besides, Leo, that thing
really stinks.
But I can't get to sleep
if I'm not wearing it.
Hey, Shannon, can I
get my clothes back?
[SHANNON]
Sure.
Thank you. Good night.
[SHANNON grunts]
[PACIFICA]
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just thought it might be nice
to sleep beneath the stars.
Oh! That sounds
like a good idea!
All those lights...
What do you suppose
they actually are?
I have no idea.
[PACIFICA]
You know, Leo.
They say that long ago, humans
used to be able to go up there.
[LEO]
To the stars?! You're kidding!
[PACIFICA]
No, honest!
[LEO]
Huh.
I wonder what they did up there.
[LEO]
Hm?
[PACIFICA]
What the heck is this?
[gasps]
What did you drop? What is it?
Miss Pacifica?
I sure wish I knew what
I was crying about.
It's kinda weird. I'm sorry.
[LEO]
What's the matter?
I don't know.
It's just-- I can't stop.
[sobs]
[LEO]
Um... I'm sorry, Miss Pacifica.
For what?
Why do you need to apologize?
[LEO]
Well, you're--
There's no need to.
I'm not crying
because of you, Leo.
[sobbing continues]
[SOCOM]
What are you doing?
[CZ]
Socom.
[SOCOM]
I petitioned our master.
But she denied the use of
class one configurations.
[CZ] There is one thing
that bothers me.
It concerns the
Providence Breaker.
[SOCOM]
What's that?
[CZ] I understand
the reasoning behind
why we must eliminate her.
She's a disruptive
element that could
destabilize the fundamental
principles system.
But as weapons go, doesn't she
seem to be too passive
to be effective?
[SOCOM] She does seem to
lack offensive capability.
Is there something else?
[CZ]
I just don't understand.
Is Pacifica Cassul really
that much of a threat?
Is it necessary for
us to obliterate her?
[SOCOM]
Don't trouble yourself.
It isn't our place to
make those decisions.
Steyr told me of
the circumstances
surrounding your decompression.
If this is going to cause
you to hesitate in combat,
request a memory wipe treatment.
It will only take seconds.
[CZ]
I can look after myself.
[SOCOM] We have very
little chance of success
without the use of the
class one configurations.
Perhaps I should
follow Steyr's example
and use a more cunning approach.
[PACIFICA]
Isn't this a beautiful day?
[giggles]
[LEO chuckles]
[RAQUEL]
Oh my! Look, it's Eirote!
And Makarov!
Good afternoon.
[PACIFICA]
Makarov!
You brought him all this
way for me? Thank you!
Don't mention it.
[SHANNON]
And the Gigases?
[EIROTE] It'll take two or
three more days to repair them.
[SENES] I just hope that no
one finds us here before then.
Dennis and Sutton are both out
reconnoitering the
Capital and the Holy City.
[SENES]
Who are you?
I'm Christopher, former member
of the Special Forces unit,
Princess Senes Lur Giat.
Huh. Special Forces, huh?
That's a plus for us,
right, Eirote?
Yes, ma'am!
I hate to bring it up,
but perhaps we should
work out a plan
for when this site is attacked.
Good thinking.
[footsteps]
[WINIA] Could you help out
with the laundry, Pacifica?
Forgive me, but... could I
trouble you to wash this
while you're at it?
What?!
Oh! Don't worry,
I'll take care of that one!
[PACIFICA]
Laundry time!
I gotta help, too?
[RAQUEL] Okay, you don't have
any more itchy spots, do you?
Back home,
we did our laundry like this
all the time, remember?
You mean I did it.
[RAQUEL]
What's wrong, Shannon?
[SHANNON]
This stain won't come out.
[PACIFICA]
Who cares about a stain or two.
[SHANNON]
I do!
[PACIFICA]
Hang these up.
[SHANNON]
I'm busy here!
[PACIFICA]
I wanna jump in and rinse off.
I mean, it's been forever
since I've had a bath.
Suck it up already.
Oh come on, I just wanna
clean myself off a little.
I can cast an illusion spell
to hide you if you like.
Thank you, Sis.
[gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Must be imagining things...
[gasps]
Who's there?!
[CELIA]
Isn't this a beautiful day?
Why yes, it is.
Uh... If you're here to swim,
feel free to go in first.
[CELIA]
Tell me something.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
A bird in a cage...
Does it long to fly
freely through the sky?
[SHANNON]
Hang those up properly, will ya?
[RAQUEL]
Yeah, yeah...
[SHANNON]
Three days to go.
Three days until
Pacifica turns 16.
I wonder what's going to happen.
Even if we do manage to
protect Pacifica for that long,
what happens afterwards?
[RAQUEL] No one can know what
the future may hold, right?
[SHANNON] Yeah, I guess
you're right about that.
Who knows, our names
might go down in history
as the people who
betrayed humanity.
We'll be the traitors
who sacrificed the world
to protect their little sister.
[RAQUEL] You're overthinking
things, Shannon.
It's a beautiful day outside,
the breeze feels
wonderful on your face,
and our laundry
is nice and clean.
I just can't bring
myself to believe
that this world will
simply be destroyed.
Not today, anyway.
Your optimism is
nothing short of amazing.
It always cheers me up.
[RAQUEL chuckles]
I'm sorry... but what
are you talking about?
[CELIA] Would you be willing
to listen to my story?
It's a story of the far
distant past, an ancient story.
Humanity had created wings that
let them soar higher
than the birds.
They took flight and left
the Earth behind them,
aiming for the stars.
But God frowned upon humanity
striving for the heavens.
[CELIA]
If left to its own devices,
the human race might've devoured
the very stars themselves.
Humans are like vicious birds
that not only destroy others,
but kill their own kind.
God decided to capture those
birds in order to preserve them.
By placing them inside a cage.
[CELIA] But humanity fought
back against God's will.
Many of those who
resisted perished.
I was worried that if
the fighting continued,
all of humanity
might become extinct.
And so... I helped God put
humanity in its protective cage.
Although they were caged,
we took precautions
to ensure that
humans wouldn't notice
they were captives.
As long as you are unaware
that there is a sky outside,
then your cage is
your entire world.
Even so...
What do you think about this?
Do you want to leave your cage?
Huh?
[PACIFICA]
W-What do I think?
I want you to tell me.
Please tell me.
What do you think,
Providence Breaker?
[gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Big Brother!
[SHANNON]
Pacifica!
What's wrong?!
[LEO]
Miss Pacifica!
[RAQUEL]
What happened?
[PACIFICA]
Just now, there was a woman.
[SHANNON]
What woman? Where?
[LEO]
But I don't see anybody here.
She was right there.
Didn't you see her?
There was a strange woman!
[SHANNON]
This one?
No, not me!
That's not funny, you jerk!
Can you describe her?
[PACIFICA]
She looked just like me.
She was really pretty.
Now I know for sure
you're hallucinating.
I believe Miss Pacifica!
She was telling me this story,
and then she called me
the Providence Breaker.
I believe you.
Wait a sec.
Hey, Zefiris.
Did you see her?
Negative.
I wasn't able to see her.
It was as if this whole area
was swallowed up by a fog.
[PACIFICA] So... I was
the only one who saw her?
A ghost?
I've never seen one of these
entities that you call a ghost.
Still, I'm glad you're safe.
What's the matter?
Don't worry about it.
It's nothing, really.
[CELIA]
It won't be long now before
everyone will come to kill you.
And then... what will
happen to this world?
[HOGUE gasps]
Prayer and supplication alone
will not solve anything.
There are three days
until the birthday
of the Scrapped Princess.
[HOGUE]
Yes, Lord.
[SOCOM] You still have
one more task to perform.
[HOGUE] Lord? How is it
that I may serve you?
[SOCOM]
Steyr had a favored saying.
"Fear and dread,"
she used to tell me,
"those are what drive humanity."
The Scrapped Princess used the
underground waterway to escape.
Which means the ones who
helped her flee were--
It's time for us to head out.
Ow!
Are you okay? You should
be more careful.
Yeah...
Maybe you should
learn how from Leo.
[PACIFICA] Wow, your training
is really paying off.
I sort of feel like I'm not
putting it to its proper use.
The Royal Forces have begun
marching in our direction.
[SUTTON]
It doesn't look like
they have a fix on
our position yet,
but we don't have
much time left.
--[wings flap]
--[birds chirp]
It's so strange...
That weird woman, was she trying
to tell me something
about this world?
[PACIFICA]
I mean, they did tell us once
that our world was
sealed off, right?
Pacifica...
Right, right.
[LEO sighs]
The sky...
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
[RAQUEL]
On the day before her birthday,
Pacifica wakes up in her camp
surrounded by the Royal
Forces' giant tank squadron.
After breakfast,
she does her laundry
at the nearby river with Winia.
Senes scolds her for
not being more careful.
But that's not the first
time she's been chewed out,
now is it?
Next time on
Scrapped Princess,
"Oratorio of the Mortals."
See you next time!