[LEO]
Let us out! Let us out of here!
[SUTTON] This guy is
getting on my nerves.
Hey! Shut up!
[LEO]
Do what you want with me...
But let Miss Pacifica go!
[DENNIS] If you don't stop
making all that racket,
I'm gonna kill you.
[BOTH gasp]
Excuse me...
I-I'm just wondering...
What's gonna happen to me?
Look, I don't really know
what's going on here,
but did this Scrapped
Princess person
really do such terrible things?
[SOLDIER A]
Get in!
[PACIFICA]
Huh...? H-Hey! Wait!
[yelps]
[groans]
Why'd you do that?!
What's that thing for?
They don't expect me to do
my business in that, do they?!
That's so mean!
It's like this is a
dungeon or something!
Oh... I guess this is a dungeon.
I can't even take
a bath in here.
Winia... Leo...
[PACIFICA]
Furet...
[chirping]
[tongue clicks]
C'mere.
[footsteps]
[door creaks]
[lock clicks]
--[WOMAN groaning]
--[PACIFICA gasps]
Um, excuse me, but are
you all right in there?
[WOMAN]
Y-Yes... Thank you.
Then you've captured
the Scrapped Princess.
[LUKE]
Yes, sir.
Very good.
[LUKE] However, she has
yet to admit that
she actually is the
Scrapped Princess.
That doesn't matter.
But, sir--
[PETERS-STAHL] An imposter
will do just as well.
Just the fact that
we captured her.
In the end, that's all
that's really important.
[SOCOM] They've captured
the Scrapped Princess,
so why aren't we doing
something about it?
[STEYR] We've got a
little more than a week
before the Princess turns 16.
Let's wait and see
how things develop.
These foolish creatures
will probably
put on an amusing show for us.
[SOCOM] Toying with the humans
like this is a waste of time.
It is a meaningless
act on our part.
[STEYR]
You find it disagreeable? Ha...
That's interesting since our
personalities were modeled
after those cruel,
foul-tempered humans.
Don't forget that.
[LEO groans]
[DENNIS]
You two are free to go home now.
We don't need anything
else from you, so scram!
What have you done
with Miss Pacifica?!
Just get outta here already.
[LEO]
Wait! Hey, hold it!
Open up! Open up this door!
[LEO]
Open this door...
Please... I beg you...
[LEO]
Open the door...
[WINIA]
Leo...
[LEO sobs]
I promised him...
I gave him my word.
I swore I would keep Miss
Pacifica safe no matter what.
I promised that to him!
[JILL]
You still think this is right?
[CHRIS]
Now we won't be disbanded.
That's all that matters, right?
Christopher... Jillian...
[JILL]
Huh?
Word's come down
that Prince Forsyth
is being sent away
to the Holy City.
What?!
[FAFAL]
He apparently scolded the King,
telling him that he should treat
the Scrapped Princess better.
Sounds like the Prince
has been trying to
convince his father
not to go to war.
And now, the King wants to get
rid of his trouble-making son.
What do you think, Christopher?
You know that all
of us will follow you
no matter what happens,
even if it means
losing the unit.
So tell us, what is it that
you really want to do now?
[SOLDIER B] Hey, did you guys
get that notice from the brass?
[SOLDIER C]
Yeah, just now.
[SOLDIER B]
I guess this means that
they finally caught
the Scrapped Princess.
[SOLDIER C] Yep, looks like
we can take it easy for a while.
[SHANNON]
Is that true?
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?
It must be or the guys
on top wouldn't have
rescinded our orders to
keep searching for her.
So where are they
keeping her now?
[SOLDIER C]
She's probably been executed.
After all, that little
girl's the poison
that's gonna destroy the world.
The guys who caught her said
she was ugly and evil lookin'.
[SOLDIERS laugh]
[Soldier B gasps]
[SOLDIER D]
Hey, you bastard!
[grunting]
[SOLDIER E]
You better watch where
you're puttin' that
right hand, Buddy.
[SOLDIER F] You ready
to deal with all of us?
This situation is dangerous.
You're so irritated that you're
acting completely haphazardly.
And you're one of the reasons
I've so damn irritated!
[SLEY]
What's going on here?!
Stand aside!
[LUKE]
Shannon Cassul, I presume?
And you are?
[LUKE] We are the Royal Forces
Special Intelligence Bureau.
So you're the Blackhawks then.
I am the squad leader,
Colonel Luke Sturm.
[SHANNON]
What do you want with me?
I'd like you to come with us.
We'd also like your companion,
the Peacemaker,
to accompany us as well.
[gasps]
[LUKE]
Let me make this clear.
At this point in time,
we have absolutely no intention
of antagonizing either you or
the forces of the Peacemakers.
Please think of this as
a request on our part,
not as a command.
[SHANNON grunts]
Your request is
pretty inconvenient.
All right, Colonel. Let's go.
They have Pacifica?!
[LEO]
I'm so sorry.
I knew that it was
going to be difficult
for her to escape the Capital.
But to be caught so soon...
And I still don't
know where Shannon is.
[LEO]
I'll do all I can to rescue her!
And how are you
going to do that?
I'll arrange a jailbreak
or set off a mass escape;
there are lots of ways!
[KEYDARF]
Those don't sound very feasible.
Then-- We'll use
Miss Raquel's magic.
[RAQUEL]
We can't do anything rash
until we know if
Pacifica's all right.
What about that inquisitor
friend of yours?
Might he know something?
It's possible.
He was just summoned
to the castle.
If I could find some way
to meet up with Mr. Berkens,
then maybe I could
learn something
about what's
happened to Pacifica.
[HOGUE]
Highness...
By order of His Majesty,
I have been charged
with escorting you
to the holy city of Grendel.
Those are Father's orders?
We are on the brink of war,
and the Capital's in turmoil.
So he believes this to be in
Your Highness' best interest.
I've heard the Scrapped
Princess has been captured.
Would it be possible for me to
at least see my sister
before I have to leave?
As to that...
I guess it's too much to ask.
[PACIFICA] Hey, are you sure
you're okay over there?
You don't sound too good.
[WOMAN] Yes... And you?
Are you all right?
Yes, I am. Thanks for asking.
[WOMAN grunts]
I may not look it,
but I'm mother to both
a daughter and a son.
How old are you, young lady?
I don't know.
[WOMAN]
Huh?
Well, you see, I sorta
lost my memories.
[WOMAN]
Oh, I see. You poor dear.
[PACIFICA] That's why I
don't really understand
what's going on.
I don't even know why
they took me prisoner.
They keep going on about how
I'm the Scrapped Princess,
but I don't get it.
Scrapped Princess?
It can't be...
[PACIFICA]
Uh, ma'am? Are you all right?
Y-Yes... I'm fine...
[PACIFICA]
Why did they throw you in here?
[gasps]
I secretly helped
a person get away
that everyone was trying
to hunt down and kill.
They tortured me, wanting to
know where this person was.
But that person's
been captured now,
so I suppose they don't need me.
Then that person must've
meant a great deal to you.
[ELMYR]
Oh, yes.
[PACIFICA]
But he got captured... Poor guy.
[gasps]
[WOMAN gasps, groans]
[PACIFICA]
Your hand... It feels so cold.
[ELMYR] Your hands...
They feel so warm to me.
[LUKE] I have a message
from General Peters-Stahl.
It reads as follows:
"I consider it an honor that you
have agreed to meet with me."
I don't have time to engage
in silly introductions.
Get to the point already.
[SLEY gasps]
You truly are a Peacemaker.
You may have taken
on human form,
but it looks like
everyday social matters
are still a foreign
concept to you.
You've got gall
calling us impolite.
Seems to me, inviting us to
come here and be insulted
is the height of rudeness.
Calm down, there's no
need for us to argue.
Shannon Cassul,
come with me, if you please.
[knocking]
You may enter.
[door clicks, clatters]
Excuse me, sir.
I have brought him to you.
Let me get right to the point.
I have a proposition;
let's join our forces.
What do you mean by that?
[PETERS-STAHL]
Our research shows that
these beings known
as Peacemakers
have meddled in our
world from the shadows.
manipulating and shaping
our history for millennia.
[SHANNON]
And?
Despite that fact, we intend
to march on the empire of Giat
with or without the permission
of the Peacemakers.
We will control our own destiny,
and in turn, become the
masters of the world.
Huh?
[PETERS-STAHL]
We still don't know why,
but the Scrapped Princess seems
to threaten the Peacemakers.
And that Scrapped Princess
is in our custody
at this very moment.
[SHANNON gasps]
You're planning to use my
sister as a bargaining chip?
Give her to me!
Please, calm yourself.
[SHANNON]
Where's Pacifica then?!
The Scrapped Princess
is unharmed.
Incidentally, I'm told that
you have combat capabilities
and resources that are on par
with those of the Peacemakers.
With your assistance, we could
easily defy the Peacemakers
and conquer the world.
You're serious? That's insane.
You think you can negotiate
with the Peacemakers?
You're going to demand that
they let you rule the world?
I'm doing it because I believe
it's the right course of action.
You think it's right?
Who exactly is this right for?
I gather you don't
intend to assist us then.
Not likely.
[PETERS-STAHL]
I have but one word of caution.
Your precious sister
is in our hands.
I hope you won't
forget that fact.
I'll ask you again
later for your decision.
Till then, weigh your
options carefully.
[LUKE]
This way.
[SHANNON]
I know already.
[LUKE gasps]
It's you again.
Is that girl a Peacemaker?
[SHANNON]
No.
In that case,
she must be a Dragoon.
Just give us a minute.
I'm not so stupid
as to try and escape.
In that case, I'll be waiting
for you in the antechamber.
[ZEFIRIS] Shannon, it appears
Pacifica is being held
in the castle's dungeon.
[SHANNON gasps]
It must be difficult for
you to feel so helpless.
Huh. Well, I never expected that
you would take my feelings
into account about anything.
I want to help you.
All you have to do is ask me.
Oh yeah, that's right.
I'm supposed to be your
master now, aren't I?
Yes, that is true.
But I want to help
you of my own free will,
not out of duty.
Do not forget, my Master.
Should you ever need me,
call my name.
I promise that I will be
there right at your side.
Eirote!
Ma'am?
How much longer before we
can begin activating them?
We're looking at another
30 hours or so.
[NATALIE] It's quite impressive
that you were able to
complete them in such
a short amount of time.
[SENES] If our ancestors
could design and build them,
then so can we.
You shouldn't underestimate us.
[NATALIE] I have just
received an important message
from Zefiris.
She said that Pacifica Cassul
has been captured
by the Royal Forces.
What?!
Report, Eirote!
Ma'am?
I want these Gigases
activated in three hours.
[gasps]
Yes, ma'am.
It's still no use.
I can't find Shannon no
matter how much I try.
Something is jamming my signal.
It's possible there might
be a Peacemaker nearby him.
[KEYDARF] I suppose all we can
do now is sit back and pray.
[RAQUEL]
No. Begging the gods for help
is nothing but a waste of time.
[KEYDARF]
Huh?
There's no point in
staying here anymore.
It's time for me to
do something about this.
[WINIA] I hope that Pacifica
is doing all right in there.
You think she's
okay though, right?
[cries]
What am I doing here?
What was I thinking?
I never should've
come to this city.
What's the point if
all we do is suffer?
I had such high hopes
when I left Taurus.
What am I doing here?
[crying continues]
[CZ]
What did you two speak about?
[SHANNON] Maybe what you
said earlier was right.
Humans are foolish.
And they're thoughtless.
And they're greedy, to boot.
I'm like that, too, so I
guess that makes me human.
If it were left alone, humanity
would eventually go extinct.
That is why we are here--
To see to it that humanity
continues to exist.
So, if Pacifica does turn 16,
what do you think is
actually going to happen?
Will this world
flicker and disappear?
Or will humanity be
all that's wiped out?
We still do not know for certain
what that system
is intended to do.
We are just carrying out the
mission that was assigned to us.
[PACIFICA]
And then after that,
I landed an acting
job at a theatre.
Guess who I got cast as?
I played a horse's
legs of all things!
I guess I can't expect
to play a princess.
But a horse's legs?
I mean, come on!
[ELMYR] Really? I wish
I could have seen that.
What? You'd like to
see horses' legs?
Not that. I would have liked to
have seen you performing a play
and living a happy life
surrounded by your friends.
[PACIFICA]
Oh, right.
You said you have a daughter,
didn't you, ma'am?
So you haven't seen
her for a while?
I haven't.
I gave up my daughter when
she was just a little baby
so that others could raise her.
[PACIFICA]
Oh...
[ELMYR] I didn't even
give the child a name.
I thought that if I did,
I'd never be able
to give her up.
But it was impossible for me
to keep my daughter with me,
so... I gave her away.
[PACIFICA]
What ended up happening to her?
[gasps]
[ELMYR] I heard
from those around her
that she grew up to be a
cheerful and carefree girl.
Really? Well, I'm glad
to hear that.
[ELMYR] Ever since then,
I've prayed that one day
I would be able to
see my daughter again.
Yeah! I'm sure that you will.
So am I.
[PACIFICA] I have someone
that I want to see again, too.
[ELMYR]
Oh?
[PACIFICA]
Well, he's... He's really gruff.
And when we go to the baths,
he always makes me wait forever.
And he's really bad at
drawing portraits, too.
But... I guess he is kind of a
nice guy every once in a while.
[ELMYR] Well, I suppose
you are at an age
where you're going to fall
in love with someone.
[PACIFICA]
What are you talking about?
Who said I was in love with him?
Say, ma'am.
I was wondering...
[PACIFICA]
Ma'am?
[groans]
[PACIFICA]
Hey, ma'am?
Are you really okay?
What's wrong?
[gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Hey! Somebody get over here!
Come quick! We need help!
Somebody get over here now!
[SOLDIER G]
What do you want?! Quiet down!
The lady next to me
is in a lot of pain!
Please, you have
to call a doctor!
[SOLDIER G]
Shut up already!
[gasps, grunts]
Hey, wait a minute!
Where are you going?
[ELMYR]
Please... Could you...
[PACIFICA gasps]
[ELMYR] Would you please tell
me your name, young lady?
What's my name?
My name is Pamela.
[ELMYR]
Pamela...
I'm sure you'll get
out of this place.
That's the spirit! Once you
give up, you've already lost.
So let's both hang
in there, okay?
[ELMYR]
Of course...
Hey, ma'am?
Are you okay?!
[ELMYR] Pamela... Would you...
do something for me?
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[ELMYR]
If you could, Pamela...
I'd like you to call me
"mother" before I die...
Before you die?
Come on, that's not funny.
Don't talk like that.
[ELMYR] Pretend that you're
my daughter, please?
[gasps]
I can't do that. I just can't.
Because once I do, I'm afraid
that you'll-- Don't die!
I'll come up with something!
Don't. You can't. Don't give up!
I'm so sorry... Pamela.
Don't die. You can't!
Say something! Talk to me.
Please, you have to hang on!
Please, Mother!
Mother?! Mother, no!
[PACIFICA]
Mother!
[RAQUEL] Pacifica is
taken out of her cell
and brought before the King.
He seems to be
afraid of her, though.
But General Peters-Stahl,
who knows no fear,
seems to be trying to make a
deal with the Peacemaker Cz.
It sure is audacious
to try to bargain
with beings who are
like gods, isn't it?
Next time on
Scrapped Princess,
"Prelude to the
Divinely-Ordered Collapse."
See you next time!