[CHRIS]
Major.
So I heard that you tried
to take on her guardians.
News travels fast.
I'm just saving myself up
for the real fight later.
[MAJOR]
How will you report this?
[CHRIS]
As the Baroness ordered.
I am to report
everything to her
regardless of the success
or failure of the mission.
And besides, it's not as if
they have any real chance
of escaping the
continent of Dustvin.
This goes without saying,
but don't let your personal
feelings get in the way.
What's the matter, Major?
Are you really that
concerned about me?
My assignment is
to kill the poison
which will destroy the world.
That's the only agenda
I have on my mind.
[horse whinnies]
[BANDIT LEADER]
Whoa!
Hi there, cute little girl.
Hi there.
[BANDIT LEADER]
And how are you doin'?
Fine, thanks for asking!
Hey, Shannon, some
bandits are here.
[SHANNON]
Okay.
What's the matter, Sis?
[PACIFICA]
Bandits, looks like.
Oh.
Hey, little lady.
You wouldn't have somethin'
nice to share with us, would ya?
Oh-ho!
How 'bout some pickles?
[BANDITS laughing]
You're a pretty sweet
kid, little lady.
Let's see...
You, the young man over there!
Yeah?
[BANDIT LEADER]
It'd be best
if you just leave your
stuff here and walk away.
Same goes for you.
[BANDITS laughing]
Not bad, boy, but don't come
cryin' to me if you get hurt.
[BOY]
You men down there!
I refuse to allow
any wicked behavior
to threaten the livelihood
of innocent people!
In the name of
our lord god Mauser,
I shall pass judgement
on you all!
Have at you! Charge!
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
What was that about?
Hey, is that guy
a friend of yours?
Why you--!
[BANDITS yelling]
[PACIFICA] Didn't you
check to see if it was wet
before you took it down?
A princess is only supposed
to wear dry clothes!
[SHANNON] It'll dry
while you're wearing it.
[PACIFICA] Hang up the
stuff that's not dry yet
inside the wagon.
But those clothes'll
make it stink in here.
[PACIFICA]
Then I won't wear it.
Suit yourself, then.
It's not like I care.
Huh?
[PACIFICA]
Are you okay over there?
[BOY]
Yes! I'm doing just fine!
In that case, take care!
Thanks! I certainly will!
Hey, wait! Wait a minute!
I noticed that you three were
in some trouble back there.
Oh, don't worry, we're all fine.
Are you injured?
Not a scratch.
Uh... Where is your
party headed now?
Um, well, we hadn't decided yet.
Maybe we'll go to a city.
[BOY] Oh, so you're
on a journey, then.
[PACIFICA]
Um... Sort of.
Well, in that case,
allow me to accompany you.
Huh?! I don't...
If only for a short while!
Won't you join me for a
leisurely conversation?
[PACIFICA]
Are you sure you're really okay?
Hello?
Anyone in there?
[PACIFICA gasps]
Huh?
[BOY]
W-W... Will...
"Will"?
Will you be my girlfriend
with the assumption that
we will marry one day?
[BOY yelps]
What the hell has gotten
into you, Casanova?
What do you mean? I'm just
trying to propose to her.
Huh?
[SHANNON]
Who are you anyway?
Oh, right. Where are my manners?
My name is Leopold Skorpus.
My father is the Baron.
I'm the eldest son of
the Barony of Takos.
Well, you're an awfully long
way from home, aren'tcha?
[LEOPOLD] I'm actually
on a training tour
as a knight-errant.
One day, I hope to join
the Amber Knights.
The Amber Knights? You mean
the order of courtly knights?
[LEOPOLD]
Yes! Yes, that's them!
[RAQUEL] The elite order
of Leiwan Royal Cavaliers?
Yes! That's exactly right!
[PACIFICA] The most powerful
knights in existence?
Wow, you know them so well!
So, are the three of you
going on a journey somewhere?
Well, something like that.
Huh...
[SHANNON chuckles]
I understand now.
If I abandoned a young maiden
with whom I had
exchanged marriage vows
in this lawless area, it would
disgrace the House of Skorpus
unto its last generation!
"Exchanged vows"?
[LEOPOLD] Until we reach
the end of this highway,
allow me to protect you.
No, thanks.
Now, now, my good man,
I absolutely insist.
I said no.
But why not?
He's a little bit strange, but
he seems like a nice guy to me.
Come, then! Let us be off!
Pacifica. What a lovely name.
Truly a name worthy
of your beauty.
Hear that?
People with a trained eye
know beauty when they see it.
[SHANNON]
Mm...
Hear me, god Mauser! I give
thee thanks for this encounter.
The thing is, Leopold...
Please, call me Leo, milady.
Okay, Leo.
But what're you supposed
to do when you're on tour
as a knight-errant?
[LEO]
Have you ever heard of a man
by the name of Doyle Barrett?
If I remember correctly,
he used to be second in
command of the Amber Knights.
Yes, that's right!
My errant quest
is to seek him out
so he can tell me
the Tales of Chivalry.
So you're networking to try
and get in the backdoor.
Do you have to look at
everything in the world
with such a cynical eye?
He seems to know you.
[LEO]
Sir Barrett retired from duty
quite suddenly 15 years ago.
No one really knows why,
but there is a theory.
They say he was involved
with the sealing of
the Scrapped Princess.
Something about his
health being ruined
from being cursed by
the Scrapped Princess.
What? A curse?
It's only a rumor, really.
Besides, I'm not
completely convinced
that this Scrapped Princess
ever existed in the first place.
Uh... Is something wrong?
Uh... Nothing!
It's nothing at all!
[ALL chuckle]
[LEO]
Wow...
Oh. How dazzling.
Your beauty is blinding...
Miss Pacifica...
Oh, I didn't notice you
standing there, Big Brother.
[SHANNON]
Uh. "Big Brother"?
Tell me something.
What do you like so much
about that stray cat of a girl?
Everything.
"Everything" isn't very
specific, you know?
But isn't that how love at
first sight is supposed to be?
Is that so?
Well, I suppose if I did
have to give a reason,
it would be her dignity.
Huh?
I would hardly call
her a stray cat.
On the contrary, don't you
think she has a sort of
cat-like resolute air about her?
I sense a fortitude
in your younger sister.
An ancient nobility that is not
to be found among commoners.
[PACIFICA] What're you two
doing sitting over there?
[LEO]
Hmm?
[PACIFICA]
Come on! Come swimming with me!
Uh, I really don't
think I should.
[PACIFICA]
Why?
Well, I'd rather not.
You can't swim.
No! Big Brother!
Help me, please!
Nobles and commoners, huh?
[RAQUEL] Why don't you get
cleaned up, too, Shannon?
[SHANNON]
Uh, sure.
Poor Leo went through all
that trouble to propose to her
and look at him now.
[SHANNON] She's already
turned the guy into a pet.
Shannon... I was thinking
maybe we should go with Leo
to see this Doyle man.
[SHANNON]
Hmm?
After all, the only information
we have about what happened
fifteen years ago comes from
what we read in Father's will.
This Doyle Barrett person
might be able to tell us
more about it.
[SHANNON]
Hm.
Oh, wait! Please!
You're fine! Don't worry!
The important thing is
to get used to the water.
[whimpering]
[PACIFICA]
Take this!
Miss Pacifica, look over there!
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
What's she doing?
[incoherent yelling]
Hi, there! How are you?!
I think she's trying
to tell us something.
[LEO]
Huh?
Hey, Grandma!
Are you trying to say
there's something out here?!
[PACIFICA, LEO scream]
[LEO screams]
Curse you, amphibian! Ah!
[LEO groans]
What do you think you're doing?!
That's the guardian spirit!
[LEO]
Huh?
[PACIFICA yelps]
Pacifica!
[GIRL]
Would you like a hand?
[SHANNON]
Huh?
Are you from around this place?
Do you know what
the heck that thing is?
I do believe it is what
your kind calls a dragon.
You're kidding.
That thing's a dragon?
[GIRL] She must be using frog
DNA for her basic morphology.
Huh?
This identification signal
is serial seven. It's Gloria.
I'm amazed that you're
able to function at all
in a state like that.
[GLORIA]
I must protect...
I have to protect the
world that he loved.
Even if it takes thousands,
or tens of thousands of years.
[GIRL]
Pacifica Cassul.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[GIRL]
Please, let her go to sleep.
You just have to
tell her one thing.
Tell her, "That is enough."
Our kind are unable
to sleep on our own.
We must be ordered to rest.
I beg you.
Okay... I guess...
That is enough.
[PACIFICA] You can go ahead
and rest now if you like.
I thank you...
Pacifica!
Who are you? Tell me.
What just happened?
[GIRL] You wouldn't
understand even if I told you.
What in the world
was that thing?
[SHANNON] Yeah, that's
what I'd like to know.
[OLD WOMAN]
You people,
what did you do to
the guardian spirit?
I did what that girl said to do.
I told her she could rest.
[OLD WOMAN]
Hmm...
I see now. The guardian
spirit is at rest.
So, are you folks supposed to
be on a trip or something?
[RAQUEL]
Yes.
What on earth brings you
out to these parts?
We're looking for a man by
the name of Doyle Barrett.
Huh? Are you really sure?
We've decided that
we'd like to meet
this famous knight
for ourselves.
Doyle, huh? Never heard of him.
He's best known as
Sir Doyle Barret.
Formerly a Royal Cavalier.
A Royal Cavalier?
Oh, that guy!
[LEO] She says we'll
find a mansion there.
I say. Isn't this so exciting?
Not really...
Hmm?
Hey, what do we do if it turns
out he really is under a curse?
Tell me, do you have
any powers like that?
No, I don't.
I guess the rumors
could be true after all.
Maybe you turn people
all fat and bloated.
You jerk!
Shall we go?
Farewell, then!
We'll be on our way!
Have a good trip!
[PACIFICA] That's quite
a mansion, all right.
[LEO]
Uh...
So, are you gonna knock or what?
Uh, right.
Can I help you?
Uh?
I'm sorry, are you...
Sir Doyle Barrett?
[DOYLE]
That's right.
Ah!
My ultimate goal in
life is to be able
to join the Amber
Knights someday!
To that end, I have come as a
knight-errant to beseech you
to teach me the
meaning of chivalry!
Chivalry, huh?
Yes, sir!
Hmm... Then you've
wasted your time.
[LEO]
Huh?
[DOYLE]
I'm a simple town doctor now.
If you've got time to go
searching for chivalry
and all that nonsense,
go plow a field or something.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Leo's idolized you
his whole life, and--
That was his decision, not mine.
[PACIFICA gasps]
Now leave me alone.
[PACIFICA] Oh! Now I get it!
So that's the kinda man he is!
That's too bad, Leo!
Boy, worrying that he was fat
was such a royal waste of time!
Let's go!
Uh, Miss Pacifica?
What're you waiting for?
We're going back!
Well, it's just that
there's a...
A what?!
[LEO]
A cliff over there.
[DOYLE] Well then,
that should do the trick.
[PACIFICA]
Thanks...
Now, if you wouldn't
mind, just go away.
I know you.
My parents told me stories about
you when I was very young.
They said you were
a magnificent knight
who knew the true meaning of
justice and righteousness.
That you understood chivalry
more clearly than any other man.
Tell me, have you ever
killed anyone, boy?
[LEO]
Uh?
[DOYLE] A person who didn't
or couldn't resist?
Well... No, I haven't.
[DOYLE] If you kill someone,
then you'll understand.
Kill someone that you don't
hate or even dislike.
Kill someone who's powerless.
Do that and you'll
know what I mean.
The whole notion of
chivalry is a sham.
There's no absolute justice or
righteousness in this world.
But, sir!
Come, boy, tell me what
you think chivalry is.
Tell me about justice.
I don't know them anymore.
Can you tell me about them?
[DOYLE]
Go home already.
I will come again, sir.
Welcome back.
We're back...
--[ALL gasp]
--[OLD WOMAN cackles]
Feeling hungry?
[PACIFICA] I think I'll
have some of these eggs.
[OLD WOMAN]
Go on, dig in.
It's the least I can do for
you for appeasing the spirit.
[SHANNON] Thanks, but I don't
think we had much to do with it.
[OLD WOMAN] There's an old
legend from around these parts
that says the guardian spirit
had been suffering under a curse
from the Dark Lord Browning.
For a long time,
I've wanted to try and
help that tortured spirit.
So maybe I really did
help her out after all.
[RAQUEL] Didn't you say
that she thanked you for it?
Then I'm sure that what
you did was a good deed.
You're right.
By the way, what about Doyle?
Were you folks able to find him?
Oh, yeah, we were able
to find him, all right.
It's just, I got
the impression
that he didn't wanna
talk about knights.
Is that a fact?
I bet it's 'cause he
gave up being a knight
after something bad happened.
What're you talking about?
[OLD WOMAN]
This was 15 years ago,
back at the time of the
Revelation of Saint Grendel.
Rumor has it that the princess
who had just been born
came into this world under
the star of an ill omen.
People say something
about a sickness or curse,
that she was the
Scrapped Princess.
That Doyle man was
charged with the duty
of disposing of the cursed baby
in order to save the world.
The problem for him
was that the child
didn't seem like an
abomination at all.
She was just a
sweet little baby.
[gasps]
[OLD WOMAN] Of course, there
are some rumors that say
she was secretly spared
from her deadly fate,
that the Scrapped Princess is
still alive somewhere today.
Old woman, that's enough.
Sorry. Did I ramble on
too long for you, sonny?
Well, there's always a reason
for everything that happens.
So now that you know,
just go easy on him.
[sighs]
[PACIFICA]
Guess who?
Hey, why the long face?
Well, because...
Since I was a boy, all I ever
wanted was to become a knight.
I wanted to become one of
the famous Amber Knights
and protect the people
of the kingdom.
That's all I ever dreamed of.
Miss Pacifica... What do you
suppose chivalry really is?
[RAQUEL]
The Cassuls get rooms at an inn
in a town named Taurus.
Pacifica tries to befriend
the girl who works at the inn,
but the girl doesn't
open up to her at all.
She must be the shy type, huh?
Next time on Scrapped Princess,
"Fanfare for the
Unforgiven Man."
See you next time.