[STEYR]
Well, well.
Who knew there were toys
like these still around.
[CZ] They're not strong enough
to make any difference.
[SENES]
Hey, Zefiris.
The three of us will
follow your lead.
[SHANNON]
Senes, is that you?
What are those things?
[ZEFIRIS] The Dragoon
Emulation System, Gigases.
Here they come.
[roars]
[TOWNSPEOPLE screaming]
Christopher.
This way.
Hey, Christopher, do you mind
telling us where we're going?
Is this some sort
of special mission?
Christopher?
[CHRIS]
We're going to the castle.
To the castle?
[CHRIS]
Let's go.
I call you down
from the heavens.
Come, thou moon-devouring wolf,
and let thy rage take
the form of destruction!
[gasps]
Raquel! Look out!
Stay close to me!
[gasps]
[RAQUEL]
Those Bugs are quite impressive.
I guess so.
That's the first time
I've ever tried that.
Someone help me!
Isn't anyone there?
Somebody protect me!
At once, do you hear? Please!
Appease the wrath of God!
[PACIFICA grunting]
Damn it! Why won't
this thing open?!
[explosion]
[gasps]
Please, be careful, Shannon.
[SHANNON roars]
[explosions]
[FORSYTH panting]
What are those creatures?
[HOGUE] Surely a clever
young man like Your Highness
already knows the answer.
What are you saying,
Cardinal Hogue?
Those lights come
from the divine beings
whom the Church of
Mauser calls angels.
What you see are the
messengers of God.
[FORSYTH gasps]
[HOGUE]
There is no point in trying to
hide it from you any longer.
For they have finally
come out of hiding
and revealed themselves
to all humanity.
Those lights...
Those are angels?
[HOGUE] If only we had moved
faster and been able to
kill the Scrapped Princess
while she was in our grasp.
What do you mean
by that, Cardinal?
You have to understand,
young Prince.
If the Scrapped Princess
had never survived,
if your sister
had been executed,
then this tragedy would
never have come to pass.
Sutton.
[SUTTON grunts]
[grunts]
[SHANNON]
Climb! Go higher!
Circle higher! Don't let
them fire towards the city!
[SENES]
I know; just shut up!
Drake, report!
[DRAKE]
My repair systems can handle it!
[SOCOM] You think
you can destroy us
with such pitiful toys?
Don't make me laugh.
[SENES]
Don't underestimate us, Monster!
[SHANNON]
This way! Climb! Climb!
[SENES]
All right, already!
[SHANNON]
Are those Dragoons, too?
[ZEFIRIS] Those were
produced late in the war.
Unlike me, they possess
no personality.
These were buried in Giat,
so Natalie helped us repair them
and get them ready for battle.
So tell us, Christopher.
What do you plan on doing
once you get to the castle?
What will you do when you
see the Scrapped Princess?
[CHRIS]
I won't force you to come.
If you have any doubts about
my actions, you can leave now.
[SENES] Hey, Shannon Cassul,
I want the red one.
Leave her to me.
[SHANNON]
She's yours.
Well, General?
[GENERAL A]
General Peters-Stahl!
[PETERS-STAHL gasps]
What is it?
[GENERAL B]
What are your orders, sir?
If the King is incapacitated,
then command authority is
transferred to you, sir.
It appears to me
that we may have
picked the wrong people
to negotiate with.
Lord Mauser wants this entire
matter brought to an end.
Execute the Scrapped Princess.
We will offer up her head to the
messengers of our Lord Mauser.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
Stop it, please.
Stop this already!
Why...? Why are you doing this?
--[banging]
--[PACIFICA gasps]
[SOLDIER groans]
[PACIFICA]
What's happening?
[clatter]
[DENNIS grunts]
Wait... You're that boy!
[CHRIS]
Just hold still.
[PACIFICA whimpers]
Huh...?
We'll explain later.
Pacifica Cassul, you're coming
with us right now.
Huh? What's going on?
[CHRIS]
Let's go.
[FAFAL]
Hey, Christopher...
I know it's probably a little
late to be bringing this up,
but we're in clear violation
of our orders here.
Explain something.
What is it you
hope to accomplish
by breaking her out of jail?
The Baroness once
told me something.
She said to never let
go of my own free will.
Twice, I attempted to
take this girl's life.
Then later, under the
Baroness' orders,
I researched the
Grendel Revelations.
Is this helpless girl
really the poison
that will destroy the world?
[CHRIS] All of you saw
those monsters, didn't you?
Do you truly believe those
are God's messengers?
I'm standing by
this girl's side.
So what about the rest of you?
Isn't it obvious by now?
Don't be silly; do you
even need to ask?
Uh... What if one of us said no?
Are you saying no?
I don't care either way.
Then just keep quiet.
Get with the program!
Let's go.
[FAFAL]
Get up.
[ALL gasp]
[LUKE] And where do you
think you're going?
I don't recall there
being any orders given
to move the Scrapped Princess.
Is this the Baroness' doing?
No, sir. We're acting
on our own initiative.
No one else ordered this.
[LUKE]
I see.
[gasps]
Suit yourselves.
The order has come down to
execute the Scrapped Princess,
but there's no order to
keep her from escaping.
Colonel...
[LUKE]
However, I assume you do realize
the position you'll be in after
taking this course of action.
Yes, sir.
So you're sure then?
[ZEFIRIS]
Are you all right, Shannon?
[SHANNON]
It's nothing.
We can't keep
wasting time up here.
We have to help Pacifica!
[roars]
[PACIFICA]
Um...
'Scuse me. Just where are
you planning on taking me?
[CHRIS]
Don't worry. You can trust us.
See, people who tell me,
"You can trust us,"
those turn out to be the same
people that I shouldn't trust
in the first place.
Most people don't go out of
their way to be nice to me.
[CHRIS] I'm taking you to
your brother and sister.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
[CHRIS] So could you please
be quiet for a little while?
I don't get it.
Why are you doing this?
[CHRIS]
I'm not really sure.
I don't know.
I guess I did it because
I just wanted to.
[CHRIS]
This is probably the first time
since being raised as a
Special Forces soldier
that I've ever done something
because it's what I wanted.
You see, for me, the thought
of being someone's friend--
of wanting to help them without
actually being ordered to help,
but simply because I'd
like to help them out...
It makes me feel--
How can I put it?
It makes me really happy.
Does that answer your question?
Thank you, Chris.
[gasps]
[SHANNON]
Senes!
[STEYR giggles]
They were awfully gung-ho,
but they sure didn't
put up much of a fight.
It's not too late. We're still
willing to spare you.
Surrender now and forget about
everything that's happened.
If you can turn a blind eye
to your sister's destruction,
we'll even leave you
and your friends alive
after we carry out
the reset process.
[SHANNON]
Just shut up!
You call yourselves
messengers of God?
You're just overblown puppets.
You bastards aren't divine.
Or even righteous.
You seriously expect
me to believe
a word you say after
all you've done?!
[SOCOM]
What foolishness.
Huh?
[SOCOM] Why do you
humans struggle so hard
to try and avoid your destiny?
Is it out of some mindless
obsession with heroism?
Truthfully, is your
sister's life
worth risking the future
of the entire world?
You say you believe that,
but haven't you just been
genetically engineered
to think that way?
[SHANNON]
I agonized over it.
I had my doubts.
There were lots of times
when I wanted to give up.
But then I realized
I was overlooking
one very important thing.
[SOCOM]
Oh? And what's that?
[SHANNON] Who said that
I had to choose between
protecting either
Pacifica or the world?
There's no way I can
choose one over the other.
Call it what you will,
idealism or heroics,
but I'm going to do whatever
it takes to save both of them.
[SOCOM]
So be it.
[STEYR] Then take your ideals
to the grave with you.
[CZ]
Forgive me.
[roars]
[SHANNON groaning]
[ZEFIRIS]
It's no good, Shannon.
I can't take any more.
[STEYR]
Shall I finish him off?
[SOCOM]
Suit yourself.
[groans]
[SENES]
Are you okay?
[SHANNON]
Thanks...
[SENES]
Drake, Ruth, you're with me!
[BOTH]
Yes, ma'am!
[SOCOM]
We're withdrawing.
Steyr is dead.
Abort the reset operation.
We need to regroup.
[CZ]
Understood.
[SENES]
The bastards ran away.
What happened to the red one?
[ZEFIRIS]
She was completely destroyed.
[SHANNON]
We've done enough.
Let's go back.
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmur]
[WOMAN]
What's going on?
[MAN]
Oh, look at that!
They're dissolving.
Quick, Miss Raquel! We have
to head to the castle!
Yes, of course. Let's go.
[JILL]
Raquel Cassul, I presume?
[RAQUEL gasps]
[gasps]
[SHANNON chuckles]
[WINIA]
Pacifica!
[PACIFICA gasps]
It's Winia... And Leo!
What are you doing here?
--[SHANNON] Huh?
--[RAQUEL gasps]
[PACIFICA]
Dragunov!
How did you get all
the way out here, Girl?
--[DRAGUNOV neighs]
--What are you doing here?
Can you believe it, Raquel?
It's Dragunov!
Miss Pacifica...
[sighs]
Thank goodness...
Thank goodness she's all right!
[SHANNON]
It must've been tough.
[PACIFICA]
Mm....
[SHANNON]
Was it hard for you?
[PACIFICA]
Yeah...
It was painful.
I'm still upset by it now.
So then... many people died,
didn't they?
That's what I've been told.
If not for me... If I didn't--
If I weren't around,
then they'd still be alive!
Pacifica...
[PACIFICA]
I know.
I know what you'd say.
But I keep thinking
that it's true.
I can't help but think
that's really the case.
If I died right here,
everyone would be better off.
[gasps]
Shannon.
Do you want to die?
Would you like to die now
and get this over with?
My sword exists to protect your
life or to take it from you,
whichever you want.
If you truly want to die now,
then I'll kill you
here where you stand.
But remember that no matter
which path you choose,
it won't change the fact that
someone somewhere will die.
I don't care what names
people may call you.
Whatever they might say
about you is irrelevant.
Why should I care
about them anyway?
They pass judgement
on total strangers.
They just repeat
their favorite rumors
without ever knowing
the truth about anything.
That's why I don't give
a damn what those
ignorant bastards
might say about you.
Not anymore.
But still... if you do accept
what they think of you,
if you believe that
you're the poison
that will destroy the world,
if you wish that you
could disappear forever,
or if you want to
die and end it all--
If that's true...
then I can't stop you.
Because the only person
who has the right to decide
who or what you're
going to be... is you.
[PACIFICA]
Big Brother...
Tell me, what is it
you want to do?
Yeah, but-- but so many people
have been hurt or killed
because of me--
[SHANNON] I'm not asking
about anyone else!
For the last time,
I'm asking you what you want!
If you want to die,
I'll strike you down now
in the blink of an eye.
But if you want to live,
I'll do whatever it
takes to protect you.
You have to make the decision.
Then I...
I want to live!
[PACIFICA]
I want to stay alive.
I don't wanna die.
I want to be with my
brother and sister
and everyone I care about.
Then let's live...
with everything we've got.
[RAQUEL] Pacifica and the others
arrive outside the Holy City.
Who knows when the
Royal Forces will attack.
If you don't wash your clothes,
they'll start to smell.
And it's bad for your health
if you don't eat right.
Pacifica decides to
cook for the group,
but is it a good
idea to eat her food
before fighting
the Royal Forces?
Next time on
Scrapped Princess,
"A Rondo that Transcends Time."
See you next time!