[GALIL]
Cardinal Garnest Hogue.
[gasps]
[HOGUE]
Lord Galil.
[GALIL] Thou hast heard what has
transpired in Taurus, I assume.
[HOGUE]
Yes, Lord.
[GALIL] Then I shall leave
the resolution to you.
Under no circumstances
can we allow rumors
of people defying the law to
spread amongst the masses.
[HOGUE] May the will of our
great lord Mauser be done.
I am told that the kingdom
has placed a bounty
upon the head of the
Scrapped Princess as well.
[GALIL]
Nevertheless,
I expect that I shall have to be
involved personally next time.
Would you please slow down,
just for a second?
What's wrong?
Why won't you tell
me what happened
in the city back there?
I get it. You're going to
act like you don't know me
even though we're friends.
We're friends? Since when are
we friends with you, Leo?
What? But, Miss Raquel.
That was cruel...
I guess we'll have
to say goodbye to Leo
a little sooner than we thought.
[music playing]
That's such a pretty song.
From his looks, I'd say
that he's a troubadour.
Greetings, lovely travelers.
Can I interest you
in a song or two
to comfort you
on your journey?
A song of joy to
pluck up your spirits?
Or maybe you'd prefer a sad
tune to call forth tears?
It all depends on what
you'd like to hear.
Wow...
Oh, beautiful blonde maiden, I
am completely at your service.
How I long to whisper songs
of love and devotion
in your delicate ears.
Huh?
[giggles] Since you
put it that way,
I think I'd like to
hear some of them.
[TROUBADOUR]
Of course, of course, milady!
You can pay me for
the song later.
But first, let's
start with the line
from an ancient
tune of sad lo--
We're not interested.
I think you'll have better
luck somewhere else.
Easy, now. You haven't
even heard me sing yet.
[SHANNON]
I said get lost.
What's wrong with you, Shannon?
He was just gonna sing to me.
Huh?
We're sorry, but we're in a
hurry, so if you'll excuse us.
Oh, I understand completely.
I guess it just isn't my day.
Well, I won't keep you
travelers waiting, then.
If we meet again somewhere
down the road,
I hope I can sing
my songs for you!
You think he was...?
[SHANNON]
Probably.
He was getting ready to
attack as he stepped closer.
[RAQUEL]
He didn't look like a wizard.
He wasn't carrying anything that
looked like a weapon, either.
That's exactly why the
guy was so suspicious.
[LEO]
What a roguish looking fellow.
If he ever comes near us again,
I'll make sure to get rid
of that troubadour.
[TROUBADOUR] A frontal attack
won't work then, huh?
Wow, these guys
are pretty tough.
Hmm...
[BARONESS]
Enter.
[CHRIS] I apologize for
being unable to attend
the commander's funeral.
[BARONESS] That's all right.
Still, this is most unusual.
Failure is not tolerated
in the Special Forces.
You understand that, I assume?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm willing to accept whatever
punishment you deem fit.
[BARONESS]
Instead of punishing you,
the new commander
of the Special Forces
is giving you another mission.
New Special Forces Commander?
You mean that you're...?
I want you to reopen a
certain investigation.
It concerns the
Scrapped Princess
and the Grendel Revelation
from 15 years ago.
[PACIFICA sighs]
[PACIFICA] This is so good!
Omelets are absolutely the best!
Don't eat too much,
or you'll make the cart
too heavy for the horses.
Oh, shut up! What would you
know? I'm a growing girl!
[SHANNON]
Appetite over appearance, huh?
[PACIFICA growls]
No, that's not true at all.
Miss Pacifica is
definitely attractive.
That's why you have to be
careful around roguish men
like that one we met earlier.
Oh, really, Leo?
Is that jealousy I hear?
[LEO]
What?! It's nothing of the sort!
A guy like that who acts
so familiar with you
when he's only just
met you is dangerous!
I seem to recall a certain
someone who proposed to me
when we first met.
I'm all done!
Time for me to wash the dishes!
[LEO] Wait a moment! Please
allow me to assist you.
Miss Pacifica!
Who'd have thought those
two brats could be so noisy?
I'm going to make sure that no
one suspicious is in the area.
Is that...?
[SHANNON]
What is it?
[RAQUEL]
The signal...
It feels like the
troubadour from earlier.
Is that guy headed
towards Pacifica?
Actually, he's in the
completely opposite direction.
I thought I told you
to get lost already.
Oh, I heard you the first time.
But a musician has to
make a living, you know.
You certainly have a short fuse.
You're not a soldier of
the Royal Forces, are you?
I guess that makes that busted
instrument of yours your weapon.
Oh, it's not busted, not at all.
In fact, it's making
sounds just fine.
Human ears can't
hear it, that's all.
What do you mean?
[buzzing]
Bugs, huh?
[TROUBADOUR] You'll die if they
sting you, so please be careful.
[SHANNON] I've heard
about a clan of assassins
who have the power
to control bugs.
And here I thought
it was just a rumor.
It's funny; these bugs
are mysterious creatures.
You might not think it,
but it actually takes a great
deal of skill to control them.
My name's Keydarf Gylot. I'm
master of the silent melody.
I'm also known as the Silencer.
It's nice to meet you.
[KEYDARF] Are you sure you
should be wasting your time
messing around with me?
What's that?
A brother of one of these
fellows should be reaching
the Scrapped Princess right
about now if I'm not mistaken.
[gasps]
[PACIFICA] Come on, Leo.
Aren't you done yet?
[LEO]
Just a moment, Miss Pacifica.
This bit of dirt
is rather stubborn.
[gasps]
Huh?
Are you all right?!
Ow, that really hurt.
What the heck was
that... anyway...?
Pacifica, no!
I was there with her, and yet...
I'm not fit to be a knight!
I think her condition
is getting worse.
She must need an
antidote to the poison.
Let's go back to Taurus and
find a doctor who can treat her.
I'm not so sure... After what
happened back there,
I don't know if the townspeople
would be willing to
do us any favors.
[LEO]
Shannon! Miss Raquel!
I've decided. I'm going
back to see Doyle Barrett.
Doyle Barrett? Why?
You mean that
knight who's retired?
Yes, exactly. You see, Sir
Barrett also works as a doctor.
I want to ask him to
help Miss Pacifica.
You're right. That old man
might be able to help her.
And if we take the highway,
we can make it to his place
and back again in half a day.
[LEO] In that case, I'll
make sure to hurry back.
[SHANNON] Wait a second,
I'm coming with you.
No, I'm going with him.
[SHANNON]
Raquel.
You're terrible at asking for
help. Please stay here with her.
[CHRIS] Baroness. Is this
uniform really necessary?
[BARONESS]
Of course it is.
And I must say, you look
very handsome in it.
I can't go to Sauer Castle
dressed like this.
I'll stick out like a sore
thumb when I get there.
I don't think that's
going to be a problem,
"Christopher Bairach."
I've pulled some strings
with the registrar.
Starting today, you
are my adopted child,
the heir of the
House of Bairach.
But, Baroness...
I think you meant
to say "Mother."
An official title will
prove very useful
during the investigation
I mentioned.
Then I understand completely.
Thank you, Mother.
[BARONESS] Good morning, Prince
Forsyth. A fine day to you.
Likewise. It's a pleasure
to see you, Baroness.
[BARONESS]
I'd like to introduce you
to my foster son Christopher.
He was originally raised
in the provinces,
but I would be delighted if
you would be gracious enough
to offer him your friendship.
[FORSYTH]
It would be my honor.
I'm very pleased to
meet you, Christopher.
[CHRIS]
You honor me, Your Highness.
Please, Christopher,
just call me Forsyth.
[CHRIS]
As you wish, Prince Forsyth.
[FORSYTH] Do you know
what's been happening
in the provinces recently?
Why yes, a little.
[FORSYTH]
Tell me, Christopher:
Have you heard of
a certain rumor?
The rumor that says the Scrapped
Princess is still alive?
Come now! You can't possibly
be serious, Your Highness.
Don't tell me the prince
of the royal family
actually believes
in such nonsense?
[FORSYTH]
Not long ago,
when the royal wizard
attended my aunt's funeral,
he apparently spotted a
blonde girl with blue eyes
who looked very familiar.
It was in a village
called Manurhin Town.
My twin sister, who was scrapped
right after she was born.
It seems impossible,
but somewhere out there,
my sister could be
alive and well.
[RAQUEL]
Leo! We have to go faster!
[LEO]
Yes, ma'am!
[DOYLE]
Hmm?
I told you, I'm not
a knight anymore.
You misunderstand.
We've come to ask for
your help as a doctor.
[DOYLE]
Bugs, huh? That's a tricky one.
[LEO] So then, is
that thing an insect?
Legend has it these things were
created by demons long ago.
But I don't know
much about them
other than they're
extremely dangerous.
If you're stung by them
directly, you die instantly.
Even if you're only
grazed by it though,
you won't live to
see the morning.
[LEO]
You can't be serious!
Please save my sister's life,
Sir Barrett. I beg of you.
Even if I wanted to,
normal antidotes don't have
any effect on bug poison.
You have to prepare a special
mixture of wild medicinal herbs.
Problem is, the herbs only
grow in special locations.
Where can we find them?
The only place they
grow around this area
is inside a strange cave
known as the Fortress.
The Fortress?
[LEO]
Let's go there at once!
There's a bug hive
inside the Fortress.
Without a military
wizard to help us,
we'd never get
outta there alive.
In that case, I will go.
[LEO] Huh? Wh...? Miss Raquel,
you mean you can use magic?
Why, yes. Just a little bit.
That's the Fortress?
[DOYLE]
Mm.
[LEO] I wonder... Was all
of this made by humans?
[DOYLE] They say it's a
relic of the Genesis Wars,
that it used to be
some kind of vehicle.
Nobody knows what it
is for sure, though.
Let's get going.
[LEO]
I'll protect you, Miss Raquel.
I have to admit it, you're
a very impressive woman.
[RAQUEL]
You think so?
[DOYLE]
This is a dangerous place,
even for a military wizard.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
But my sister's life
is on the line.
[PACIFICA]
Shannon...?
Huh?
You're finally awake.
What happened? I can't
remember a single thing.
[SHANNON] You must've picked
up something weird
off the ground and eaten it.
Leo and Raquel went out
to get some medicine,
so you'll be as good as
new after you take it.
[PACIFICA]
Shannon...
You still haven't
gotten over the habit
of covering your mouth
when you try to lie...
Oh, give me a break.
If I keep getting worse...
If I end up dying from
whatever this is...
...then you and Raquel will be
able to go back to Manhurin Town
and live your lives
like normal people.
[SHANNON]
Yeah, I guess.
Then... nobody else
will have to die...
[SHANNON]
Everybody dies... eventually.
[PACIFICA]
I can't help thinking sometimes
that I cause you
a lot of trouble.
Seems like everyone would be
better off without me, so--
[SHANNON] Will you shut up?!
Just be quiet and sleep!
What's with all this
"If I die" crap?!
Why don't you just
give this whole
"self-sacrificing and noble"
thing a rest already?!
That's the easy way out!
[SHANNON] Let someone
else spoil you for once.
Hey, Big Brother...?
[SHANNON]
What is it?
[PACIFICA]
Would you hold my hand, please?
[LEO] Why do you suppose
the walls glow like this?
It's strange.
Legend has it that this place
is still under the curse
of the Dark Lord Browning
after all these years.
Who taught you to swing
a sword like that, boy?
[LEO]
No one, sir. I taught myself.
Huh. Your swing is stiff,
but it's still very quick.
Thank you very much, sir!
It's truly an honor to be
complimented by you!
[DOYLE] I was just
making an observation.
[LEO]
Um, Sir Barrett?
I realize this probably
isn't the best time, but...
[DOYLE]
What is it?
[LEO] Well, I was wondering
if you made the decision
to leave the Amber Knights
because you threw the Scrapped
Princess into the gorge.
[DOYLE] That old woman should
learn to mind her own business.
But, Sir Barrett, wasn't
it your duty as a knight
to throw her into that gorge?
A knight wields his sword
in the name of justice,
and if need be, he takes lives.
And if many lives would
be saved by that act--
No matter how great you
think the cause may be,
there's no excuse
for taking away
the smile of an innocent child.
[LEO]
But, sir--
I've had enough of this!
It's time for you to drop it!
[LEO gasps]
Something just occurred to me.
We've been getting closer
and closer to the center,
but there haven't been
many bug attacks.
[LEO]
Hm.
Now that you mention it...
[KEYDARF]
Greetings, everyone!
Welcome to my charming palace.
You're the guy
from this morning!
One of my bugs didn't return,
so I had a feeling you
might show up here.
This means the little lady
is still alive, isn't she?
That's right. We came here
to get her medicinal herbs.
If it's herbs you're after,
there's plenty of them around.
But, will you be
able to pick them?
[LEO gasps]
People of the flames, dance!
That's amazing!
[KEYDARF]
I suspected as much.
Well, how about this, then?
[screeching]
[KEYDARF] I'm sorry, but it
looks like the reward
of five million cetme
is going to be mine.
[LEO] Reward? What're
you talking about?!
[KEYDARF] What? You mean
you don't know yet?
Oh, tis a strange and
terrible tale of woe,
of a suckling child spoken
of in god's revelation.
A poisonous young girl
who will usher in the
world's destruction.
In other words,
the Scrapped Princess who
escaped her deadly fate
is the young lady you're
now trying to save.
[gasps]
What did you say?
If you think I'm
making this all up,
why don't you go ahead
and ask the lady there?
It can't be!
[DOYLE]
Well? Is this true?
Yes, it's true.
[gasps]
No matter what it says
in the revelation,
she's still my precious sister.
Miss Pacifica is the
Scrapped Princess?
Then she's still alive?
[KEYDARF] So what this
means is if I kill Pacifica,
I'll be able to collect a huge
amount of money as a reward.
[RAQUEL]
Barrier, protect us!
That's a very nice
defense spell,
but how long can you keep it up?
Damn it. How could I have
fallen for such a stupid trap?
I swore an oath
that I'd protect her
no matter what happened.
[SHANNON]
Pacifica...
[KEYDARF] If you plan
on picking those herbs,
then you'll have to take
down that spell eventually.
Will you give it up and go home?
Or will you just die here?
Either way, the
Scrapped Princess will--
It pains me to take another
person's life unnecessarily,
but...
[KEYDARF]
Huh?
I have the power to
alter the size and shape
of the spell's barrier
to fit whatever situation
I find myself in.
You can what?!
[RAQUEL]
Now then, Silencer...
...will you die here like this?
Or are you going to call
off your little bugs..
...and hand over the herbs?
[chuckles] You must be kidding!
I don't believe you're really
capable of killing someone.
[grunts]
It seems that you
have chosen to die.
[KEYDARF] Wait! Wait a minute!
I give up! Stop! Stop!
[DOYLE]
The young plants are no good.
You have to make sure to
pick the thick, green ones.
Right.
We don't have much time!
Please, go faster, Sir Barrett!
I know, I know!
She's the Scrapped Princess...
Miss Pacifica...
She's the poison that will
destroy the world...
[RAQUEL] Doyle drives his
horse hard to save Pacifica,
and Leo, having found out that
she's the Scrapped Princess,
is completely at a loss.
But, just at that moment,
an unimaginable power
begins to stir around them.
Next time on Scrapped Princess,
"The Pied Piper's
Song of the Knights."
See you next time!