[ZEFIRIS]
What should I--
What should I do now, Pacifica?
Why? Is there something
bothering you?
Uh, well that's
kind of a surprise.
From our point of view,
we've always thought of
you as a god or something;
you seem to know everything.
[ZEFIRIS] I want to hear
your honest opinion.
There is something
I wish you to see.
The truth of our existence.
Huh?!
[NATALIE]
Where are you going, Guardian?
I have to do something
to help Princess Senes
get this strange
ship moving again.
They said they'd
kill 1,000 per day?
I'm troubled that such a
small matter upsets you.
Don't you understand?
[SHANNON] She could
never live with herself
if all those people in the
Capital died because of her.
But you'll die as well.
Emotions are quite
a nuisance, aren't they?
However, you don't
need to worry anymore.
[SHANNON]
Huh?
[gasps]
[SHANNON]
M-Mother...
[SENES]
Who are you?!
It's my father.
Your father?
Mjollnir, strike!
Pretty decisive, aren't you?
He appears and you
just take him out.
[RAQUEL] My father is no
longer among the living.
[gasps]
I was the one who washed his
cold corpse after he died.
And I was the one who
lit his funeral pyre.
My memories aren't so vague
that I can be taken in by
such an obvious illusion.
We have to hurry now.
If they've left the
two of us behind,
that means that Natalie
and Zefiris might be
planning to do something
to Shannon and Pacifica.
[SENES] While they save us
ordinary folks for later?
Anyway, let's head for the core.
Getting the Skid moving
again comes first.
Right, we ordinary
types will have to
assert ourselves
the best we can.
That's right.
We're headed for
Sauer no matter what.
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[LEO] Phew! Well,
here we are, safe and sound.
We finally made it here.
To the Capital.
[GUARD A]
Hey! You there!
[BOTH gasp]
What's this s'posed to be?
Why that's Mr. Soopie.
[KING BALTERIC] I can't
believe the Scrapped Princess
made it to Giat.
Neither can I, sire.
[KING BALTERIC]
I obeyed the Grendel Revelation.
I ordered that the newborn
princess be killed immediately.
[HOGUE]
The god Mauser knows full well
all that you have done, my King.
However, the day of
destiny draws nearer
with every passing moment.
The day the Scrapped
Princess will turn 16
and utterly destroy--
[KING BALTERIC]
Yes! I know!
We must hurry and find her.
Isn't that right?
And finally destroy her.
Yes, sire.
No matter the cost.
I assume all of you are aware
that the Giat Empire ship has
violated our territorial waters.
Of course.
We've also heard about
the Scrapped Princess
making contact with Scarlet.
There are persistent
rumors going around
that she might be conspiring
with Scarlet to attack us.
Pretty suspicious,
don't you think?
It sure sounds like
something's about to happen.
And our King has apparently
issued a direct order
to the Royal Forces
concerning this matter.
They're mustering troops to
kill the Scrapped Princess.
[DENNIS]
If she's killed by our forces
while under Giat's protection,
it'll start a war.
Right. And Jill has been seeing
some disturbing
things in her visions.
Tell them.
If the situation gets any worse,
the military might authorize
the use of that spell.
--[ALL gasp]
--Which spell is that?
The long-range, strategic-grade
offensive spell
that was banned by
treaty many years ago.
[gasps]
[PETERS-STAHL]
The empire of Giat...
If only I could get a hold of
their military technology.
[VOICE]
It's tantalizing, isn't it?
I'd want their territories, too.
[VOICE]
But of course.
You have to take what you
want when it's in reach.
Yes, that's true.
This is the perfect opportunity.
[VOICE] Besides, you've also
got your ace-in-the-hole,
the long-range, strategic-grade
offensive spell, right?
Ginnungagap...
[knocking]
[gasps]
Pardon me, sir.
Forgive me, but is something
the matter, General?
It's nothing.
[PACIFICA]
What is this?
[ZEFIRIS] This is an
illusion I have created
in order to explain
things to you.
This is the realm of the stars.
It is also called outer space.
At one time,
human beings possessed
enough power to
reach this realm.
[PACIFICA]
Oh.
[ZEFIRIS]
But one day, an enemy appeared
and threatened humanity.
They suddenly appeared
out of the depths of space
and began to attack the
Earth for reasons unknown.
[PACIFICA]
Oh, right!
Miss Eirote said something
about this before.
I always thought it
was a myth, though.
[ZEFIRIS] The enemy was
an intelligent life form,
but they were not human.
In our language,
they are called the HI.
The battle between humanity
and the HI dragged on.
And so, we Dragoons
were created by humanity
in order to fight the HI.
We are weapons of immense power
created to rival the
strength of the gods.
That is the reason
our kind were called
the Beasts of the Apocalypse.
[ZEFIRIS] Unfortunately,
there was a design flaw
in the artificial
intelligence that was
meant to control the
Dragoon's functions.
The AI was unable to
withstand complex programs.
This malfunction led to a series
of deadly mishaps in the field.
Out of 200 mass
production models,
174 became inoperative.
Heavy protection protocols
were implemented
in the 26 units that somehow
continued to function.
This protection included
a human pilot, a D-Knight,
who would oversee
our actions in combat.
Barring self-defense, we cannot
access 90% of our power
without D-Knight authorization.
[snores]
[ZEFIRIS]
Wake up.
[PACIFICA]
I'm listening, I'm listening.
In short, since we could no
longer function independently,
we were assigned to
fight in smaller battles.
It was then that the fully
autonomous Valkyrie-types,
an upgraded version
of a Dragoon,
were sent into combat.
But the Valkyries were
brainwashed by the enemy
and turned against us.
These are the Peacemakers.
Um...
[ZEFIRIS] The Peacemakers
once fought alongside us.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?!
But they turned on us.
It was their betrayal that
led directly to our defeat.
Afterwards, the Peacemakers
were given
the role of being
humanity's administrators.
And as for me...
[PACIFICA]
What?
Big Brother?
It's not him.
That man is Lord Becknam,
my former master.
[BECKNAM]
Zefy... I'm sorry.
But this is as far as I can go.
Thank you for fighting by
my side all this time.
And I'm sorry.
[ZEFIRIS]
But you can't!
The only reason that
I continued to function
was because you accepted me!
You aren't afraid of me.
You trusted me and that's why
I didn't break down
like my sisters.
If I lost you, I couldn't--
[BECKNAM]
Zefy... Please...
I want you to survive.
I know this will be hard for
you but I want you go on.
You have to survive, Zefy.
So that you can lend
your power to help
our children fight in
the distant future.
Lord Becknam! No! Don't go!
No! You can't die!
No... No...!
And so, I waited.
I have obeyed the orders
of my fallen master
and awaited the coming of the
ones I was meant to help.
But only because my
master wished it.
The being you encountered
at that lake earlier
was the pale shadow of a
Dragoon who had lost her master.
[ZEFIRIS]
I am unsure how to proceed.
I had thought of
you people as pawns.
You were merely tools
that I could use
to help me carry out my mission.
Even my brother Shannon?
However, for some reason, I
feel I am unable to ignore
the wishes of you
and your siblings.
I have no explanation for it.
But it feels as if that would
mean betraying my master.
I am a weapon.
My power is immense.
I am capable of annihilating
many lives in an instant.
But I cannot act solely
on my own initiative.
That is why I have never made
a single decision by myself.
I lacked the authority to do so.
My master always decided
everything for me.
But now... he no longer exists.
[PACIFICA]
But wait,
isn't Shannon your
master now, Zefiris?
I do not believe that Shannon
will ever be able
to trust me again.
Pacifica Cassul, even when
you learned what I was,
you did not fear me.
You treated me the same
way my former master did.
You trusted me.
That is why I need you
to answer this question.
What should I do now, Pacifica?
[PACIFICA]
What is it? What's wrong?
[ZEFIRIS] Natalie has begun
to brainwash Shannon.
[PACIFICA]
Brainwash him? But why?!
To transform him into
the kind of person
who would do whatever
it takes to protect you,
even if that meant
sacrificing the lives of
millions of innocent people
living in the Capital.
[gasps]
[CAROL]
She's adorable.
[CLAIRE] I was able to
save her with my magic
just before she fell to
the bottom of the valley.
[CAROL]
Well done, Claire.
I can see that you're a
full-fledged Court Wizard now.
But I'm nothing compared
to you, Lady Carol.
What is the child's name?
She has none.
You can leave
everything to us now.
You should hurry back
before you're missed.
[CLAIRE]
I'll be going then.
Carol...
[CAROL]
How could they not name her?
If I found out that Shannon or
Raquel were about to be killed,
I'd sacrifice everything
I had to protect them.
I know, but it's within
your power to do that.
The Queen is responsible for
more than just herself, however.
If they ever find out
she's still alive...
[CAROL] We have to give
this child a name,
a name that will make
everyone around her love her.
Yes, of course.
[giggles]
[CAROL]
Hello there, little one.
So tell me, what's your name?
Pacifica...
You know what this is?
Ancient language?
Yeah, except they called it
English or something like that.
"Use emergency
circuits to reconnect
main power to the
central mechanisms.
"Yes or no."
--Yes.
--[computer beeps]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Power's online.
Princess Senes...
[PACIFICA panting]
[ZEFIRIS] I can't believe
you're going through with it.
[NATALIE]
It's beginning to take effect.
We have to make it
clear to the Guardian
who it is that he
should truly protect.
[ZEFIRIS] We may be weapons,
but we are also servants.
These methods go against
our very reason for being.
[NATALIE]
I thought you said
he was nothing more
than a substitute.
[footsteps]
[PACIFICA]
Big Brother!
Big Brother...
[SHANNON]
It's all right now, Pacifica.
I promise I'll
always protect you.
Mother and Father want
to keep you safe, too.
Natalie, what have
you done to him?!
[NATALIE] I showed him data
from the past, that's all.
I need him to realize once more
that you are something
that is irreplaceable.
[rumbling]
They must have connected
the emergency circuits.
[RAQUEL]
Pacifica! Shannon!
[PACIFICA]
Big Sister!
[RAQUEL]
Are you all right?
[PACIFICA]
Something's wrong!
What's the matter?
Shannon?
[NATALIE] I'm going to make this
mobile fortress self-destruct.
[SENES]
You're what?!
This fortress is the vessel
for your personality.
If it self-destructs--
This is the best
way to stop this.
All of you need to evacuate.
Going to the Capital in this
vanguard for the sole purpose
of being killed by
Peacemakers is foolish.
[ZEFIRIS]
Natalie...
You are beginning to recover
your original strength as well.
You should get clear.
The Providence Breaker's
abilities will manifest
in 1,000 hours.
Understand?
[PACIFICA gasps]
Pacifica...
Let's run away together.
[PACIFICA whimpers]
We can't!
Lots of people might
be killed if we leave!
We can't just
abandon them to die!
Why did you mess around
with my brother's head?!
[ZEFIRIS]
Pacifica, assist me.
[PACIFICA gasps]
We will return Shannon
to his old self.
[SENES] We need to
get out of here first!
[ZEFIRIS]
It would be too late by then.
Once he leaves this
interference field,
the brainwashing
can never be broken.
You can forget about him.
Your brother is of
no use to us now.
You just shut your mouth!
[PACIFICA]
Zefiris, what do I need to do?
The only thing you can
do is dive into his mind
and persuade him to come back.
But if you fail,
your consciousness
will be unable to return.
I'll be the one to go.
[ZEFIRIS] The brainwashing
centers around Pacifica Cassul.
Only she can do this.
What about you?
[ZEFIRIS]
Even though we can dive into
the consciousness of a human,
we cannot tamper with it.
Don't do this, Zefiris.
Make one mistake, and we'll
lost not only the Guardian,
but the Providence
Breaker as well.
Zefiris...
I'll do it.
But Pacifica...
All I want is for
Shannon to go back
to the way he was before this.
I may be the Providence Breaker
and he may be the D-Knight,
but none of that
makes any sense to me.
And I wish I didn't
know anything about it.
I didn't ask to be born
as the Scrapped Princess,
but I had no choice.
Helping out around the house,
marrying someone,
having children...
That's all I've ever wanted.
To grow old and be surrounded
by my grandchildren.
I wish it could've
been like that.
I wish no one had ever
told me all the secrets
about this world.
That way, nobody would
have ever had to suffer.
You may say that we're
sealed in this world,
but I can't wrap my
head around that.
And when you bring up
stuff from 5,000 years ago,
it doesn't make any sense to me.
But you two wanting to carry
out your dead masters' wishes,
that I can understand.
I understand that just fine.
But even if I do understand,
what does any of
that mean to us now?
I'm going.
[SHANNON] I swear, only you
could pull a stunt like this.
Getting into a fight to
the death with the chickens
over an omelet.
It seems like you've
been losing a lot lately.
[PACIFICA]
Aww!
You mean I can't have
an omelet today either?
[gasps]
Thank you, Daddy!
[YUMA]
Mm-hm.
Here you go!
[chuckles]
[PACIFICA giggles]
Yummy!
[ALL laugh]
[PACIFICA sighs]
What's the matter?
I wanna ask you somethin'.
Tell me the truth, Shannon.
I'm not really you and
Raquel's little sister, am I?
I mean, I'm the only
blonde one in the family.
And I heard some people in the
village talking about it, too.
What difference does that make?
You're still my sister
no matter what they say.
If those people in the village
wanna talk, then let them.
You'll always be my
little sister, Pacifica.
[PACIFICA]
Mm.
[PACIFICA] I wish I could
stay like this forever.
I wanna stay here
with you, Big Brother.
Together with you forever.
Pacifica...
I promise I'll protect our way
of life... and you, as well.
Pacifica, it's time for
us to head home, okay?
I don't wanna go! I wanna
stay here with my big brother!
That's okay.
You can stay here a little
while longer with Shannon.
I'll keep you safe. Always.
Pacifica! It's time
for us to go home!
I don't wanna! I wanna
stay here with my brother!
That's okay, then.
[YUMA chuckles]
You can stay here with
Shannon if you want.
I will protect you,
my little sister.
Wow, that was cool!
You're so amazing, Big Brother!
What the heck?!
What is all this crap?
No, don't!
[BOTH gasp]
Will you two just
stop it already?
You're making me sick!
Big Brother, she's scary!
Who's this weird kid
supposed to be anyway?
[gasps]
Oh, no!
Wow, you're so amazing,
Big Brother! I love you!
[PACIFICA giggles]
[SHANNON laughs]
[PACIFICA grunts]
[SHANNON groans]
Didn't I just tell you that
this all creeps me out?!
Stop letting them
brainwash you so easily!
[SHANNON groans]
Come on now! We're going back!
We're going back
to the real world!
[SHANNON]
Uh... Huh?
[PACIFICA]
Don't give me that crap!
Pacifica...
[PACIFICA] I swear, Shannon,
you are so pathetic! Honestly!
Is that how you've been
seeing me all these years?
I don't understand.
How could she break the
brainwashing so easily?
It's just not possible.
Who is this girl?
[PACIFICA grunts]
Come on, get up already.
She is our little sister.
Now we are left
with no other option
but to travel to the Capital
and confront the Peacemakers.
[PACIFICA] Come on, stand up
straight already! Stand up!
[SHANNON]
Ow!
Well, full speed ahead.
[EIROTE] Set course for the
capital city of Leinwan.
Thank you.
We never would've been able
to get our old Shannon back
if it weren't for
you helping us.
I'm not the one
who saved Shannon.
You did that yourself.
That may be true, but still...
I am sorry.
[PACIFICA]
Huh?
What you said earlier
was absolutely true.
We have dragged all
of you into our fight
and left you little
choice in the matter.
Don't apologize.
It only makes it worse.
I suppose you're right.
[SOCOM]
Here they come.
[STEYR]
I've already made arrangements.
[RAQUEL] The Cassul
siblings return to Sauer,
ready to die if necessary.
But the harbor is
strangely quiet.
Convinced that their
fortress is an invader,
the country's generals seem
to have a nasty surprise
in store for them.
I wish they'd cool off before
something terrible happens.
Next time on
Scrapped Princess,
"Opera of Powers and Plots."
See you next time!