[AMON]
Glad to hear you're okay.
I assume you'll be discharged
in the next few days?
Yeah. Thanks for saving
me back there, Amon.
I was worried we'd lost you.
That sick bastard
was eating my Arata.
Lemme ask you.
Do you think the
Eyepatch is a kakuja?
That's a good question.
I've heard a ghoul can
transform into one
by repeatedly committing
acts of cannibalism.
But this guy? No.
He's more like a half-kakuja.
Amon. Watch your back.
He's dangerous.
[KANEKI gasping]
[KANEKI groans, yelps]
[KANEKI screams]
[INVESTIGATOR 6A]
Thanks, Investigator.
I'll be sure to discuss your
concerns with Development.
Let me know what they say.
And thank you for
your time, ma'am.
[AMON sighs]
[AMON]
What happened to these girls?
If they turned into ghouls,
then is it possible others
have met the same fate?
[HIDE]
Hey, thanks! See ya!
[AMON, HIDE yelp]
[HIDE]
Aw crap! Sorry about that, sir!
[AMON]
Nagachika, right?
Wow. You know my name?
I try to learn everyone's.
You're not hurt, are you?
Uh, no. Hang on.
Lemme help you, sir.
[gasps]
What's wrong?
Uh-- Oh, nothin'.
I was just thinkin' about
this "Eyepatch" guy,
I've heard a lot about him
in the news lately.
He must be a pretty
scary dude, huh?
Well, I'd better go.
Again, sorry about that.
No problem. You keep up
the good work.
[KANEKI whimpering]
I don't wanna eat anymore.
[AMON]
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
[AKIRA]
It happened, Father.
I came face-to-face
with the Owl.
[BOY 6A]
Aw!
[FATHER 6A] I told you
it was going to blow away
if you don't hold on tight.
[BOY 6A]
I tried, Daddy!
[FATHER 6A]
All right then.
I guess we'll just have
to get you another one.
[BOY 6A]
Really?
I promise I'll hold on
really tight this time!
[JUZO grunting, whimpering]
There you go.
So how'd I do, Mama?
Did I make you happy?
I tried really hard for you.
Yeah. I could see that, Rei.
Wanna know what your "good boy"
score was this time?
Sixty points!
I made you proud
today, didn't I?
[BIG MADAM] Why, of course
you did, my dear!
Now comes the fun part.
Lemme show you
what 60 "good boy"
points get ya!
[JUZO yelping, screaming]
[SPECTATORS laughing]
Kill the guy!
Rip his head off!
[MAN 6A yelping]
[JUZO panting]
[JUZO, MAN 6A grunt]
[MAN 6A whimpering]
No! P-Please, stop!
[giggles] I want
"good-boy" points!
Ten! Twenty! Thirty!
Forty! Fifty!
Don't make this harder
than it needs to be!
I've gotta make Mama proud!
[SPECTATORS cheer]
Just a few more!
Hang in there! Come on!
You can do it!
That's how it's done, Rei!
See? What'd I tell ya?
When it comes to killin',
the kid's a natural.
[MASKED MAN 6A]
To say the very least!
He's already become
quite an artist!
--[BIG MADAM giggles]
--[rumbling]
[MASKED MAN 6A, BIG MADAM gasp]
[SPECTATOR 6C] It's the Doves!
Let's get outta here!
[BIG MADAM]
Somebody help me!
I've fallen and I can't get up!
[INVESTIGATOR 6B]
There she is! Big Madam!
[INVESTIGATOR 6C]
Don't let her escape!
[BIG MADAM screams]
[SHINOHARA, CCG TROOPERS gasp]
--[CCG TROOPER 6C gasps]
--Stay back.
Uh...
[giggles]
[STAFFER 6A]
Impressive.
His agility and endurance
are off the charts.
There's no reason for us to
waste his time at the Academy.
In fact, I think we should
put him to work right away.
Are you kidding me? The kid's
a complete psychopath.
He has no concept of
morality whatsoever.
Ah, you've got a good point.
He has a long list of
psychological issues.
Everything from
aggressive behavior
to inflicting self-harm.
[STAFFER 6A]
I'm not surprised
but it's not like
he can help it.
I mean, he was raised
by ghouls, after all.
[STAFFER 6C] Exactly, we can't
expect him to live like a human.
It's not fair.
He's just a kid.
He simply did whatever he had
to do in order to survive.
If anything, I consider
him a victim.
[SHINOHARA] You know, we've
got pesticides to do that.
Huh?
My name is Yukinori Shinohara,
and as of today,
I'm your new partner.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Juzo Suzuya.
We're gonna make a great team.
[gasps]
Hm.
[CAT 6A meows]
[SHINOHARA] Getting in
some quality zoo time?
I'm sorry, Juzo!
I didn't mean to scare off
your furry friend.
What're you doing here?
You bust out of the hospital?
Not quite. They let me go.
You really like animals,
don't you?
[JUZO]
Yeah, I do!
It's fun to imagine
what they'd look like
in cross-sections.
[SHINOHARA]
Whatever makes ya happy, kid.
Hey, Shinohara,
the One-Eyed Owl
is strong, isn't he?
You bet. Stronger than me.
Ooh! I can't wait till
we get to fight him!
You know, if we face him,
there's a good chance
that I could die.
Well, if that's what
happens, then so be it.
Whether we live or die
isn't that big of a deal.
That's true.
But if you happen
to die before me,
I would be sad.
[gasps]
All right. Let's go.
You wanna get somethin'
to eat on the way back?
[JUZO]
That sounds delightful!
[SHINOHARA]
Hm?
[giggles]
[ROMA screams]
Oh, my goodness! I'm so sorry!
Geez. Not again.
[ROMA]
What should I do?
I'll get the broom!
Wait, where is it?
[growls] Roma!
Break one more cup and
you're out, ya hear me?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, like you have
any right to fire her.
Now play nice.
Somebody's gotta whip
this klutz into shape
or she's just gonna
keep breakin' stuff!
[KOMA chuckles]
[NISHIKI] Don't pick it up
with your hands,
you'll cut yourself!
Sweep it up!
[ROMA]
Okay.
Oh, poor Roma! You're
not hurt, are you?
Here ya go, I brought
you the broom.
Ooh, you're such a sweetheart!
I can't thank
you enough, Hinami!
As a result of
the recent attack,
the 23rd Ward has been placed
under heightened security.
Those who live or
commute to the area
are asked to report
any suspicious persons
to the authorities immediately.
Officials warn...
Awesome! When she said
"suspicious persons,"
I bet she meant
your friend, Kaneki!
Maybe, yeah.
That's, like, so cool!
I can't believe you're
friends with a guy
who's all over the news!
That makes you famous
by association!
[HINAMI] Um, I've gotta go
upstairs and feed Hetare.
[gasps] No way!
You can't leave until you
tell me what he's like!
I mean, is he really
as crazy as everyone
makes him out to be?
--[HINAMI] Well, uh--
--Aw, c'mon, you can tell me!
I promise I won't say a word--
[HINAMI, ROMAN, KOMA gasp]
What'd I say, Roma?
One more cup, and the
great Devil Ape's
gonna lose his patience.
Touka sucked, but at least
she never dropped anything.
Well, she's too busy
studying to work.
So Roma's just going
to have to step up.
I've got a novel idea,
why not give us a hand,
since you're here.
What, on my day off?
Keep dreaming.
Hey, Hinami. Stay strong.
I know Touka's not
around much now.
Let's just hope she passes.
Yeah.
[growling]
[sighs]
[STUDENT 6A]
You hear about the CCG?
They got their asses kicked
in the 23rd Ward.
Seriously? What the
hell happened?
[STUDENT 6A]
Remember that eyepatched psycho
who blew up the
prison bus? It was him!
Rumor has it, he took down the
whole branch office by himself.
[STUDENT 6B]
No way!
I mean, the guy'd have
to be some kind of monster.
He is!
Why do you think he wears
that creepy lookin' mask?
I bet his face is all
disfigured and gross.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Sorry, I can't concentrate.
[sighs]
[KANEKI grunting, groaning]
[KANEKI screams]
[KANEKI pants]
[sighs]
[SEIDO]
All done, Mr. Amon.
I finished and filed
the meeting reports.
Yeah? Good work.
Hey.
I was thinking about
grabbing some dinner,
you wanna come with?
[AMON]
Hm. Sure, why not?
I haven't been out in a while.
You ready?
[SEIDO]
As ever!
You wanna go back
to that kabob place
we tried last time?
Sounds good.
[SEIDO]
I love the sauce they use.
I don't know what's in it,
but man, is it tasty.
Don't just stand there.
Are you comin' or what?
[AMON]
Hm? Yeah.
Akira.
Uh... Something I
can help you with?
I was wondering if
you'd like to join us.
Well, it is only 8:18.
[sighs]
[AKIRA] I'll go if the place
is within walking distance.
Uh--
[SEIDO]
Pay attention, would ya?
C'mon, you're not
even listening to me!
Oh. Sorry, what?
Well, I said, I wanna work
hard so I can get promoted,
then find Aogiri, capture
those ghouls, and lock 'em up!
That was my plan,
till Akira showed up!
How'm I s'posed to move up
with her at our branch?
She got valedictorian and
stuck me with salutatorian!
--Isn't she mean?
--[AMON] Seido!
You know,
there are more important
things in life
than getting promoted.
Great, here we go!
It doesn't matter
what I say or do,
she's always gotta
contradict me!
Amon, would you please tell
her that I'm not a bad guy?
To be frank, I've always known
you had it out
for me, Takizawa.
You can try to play the
nice-guy-act all you want.
But deep down you've
got devil horns!
Right? Devil!
Wha--? Wha--?
--What did you say?!
--[phone rings]
Who the hell is this?
Can't you see I'm
busy right now?
And why are you calling me this
late at night, you bastard?
[HOJI] Well, hello. It's Hoji.
So, is this a bad time?
[SEIDO yelps]
I went over the meeting reports
you filed and
they're incomplete.
I'm going to need you to
come back into the office
and finish those up for me.
What's the matter?
Is everything okay, Seido?
No. I have to go
back to the office.
[AMON]
Uh-- Right now?
Guess I'll see
you guys tomorrow.
Be careful heading back, okay?
[sighs]
[AMON] You all right, Akira?
How are you feeling?
[AKIRA] Are you like
that idiot, Takizawa?
All he cares about
is being promoted.
Are you like that, too?
[AKIRA]
My father...
He had talent and a
perfect track record,
but he was never more than
a Senior Investigator.
My mother became an
Assistant Special Investigator
at a very young age.
But my father couldn't
get promoted,
no matter how hard he worked.
Most people blew him off,
calling him a
quinque-crazy old fool.
[AKIRA] But he didn't care,
he just wanted revenge.
As long as he had a purpose,
rank and status
meant nothing to him.
That's what he always
told me, anyway.
But I know that it
had to bother him.
I'm the one who held him back.
He had to look after me
while he was working.
I thought if I could
hurry and grow up,
maybe he'd finally get
that promotion he deserved.
[AKIRA]
He talked about you a lot, Amon.
He was proud to have
you as a partner.
[AKIRA] He'd go on and on
about how brave you are.
And he was right, we came
face-to-face with the Owl
and you didn't even flinch.
Meanwhile, I completely
fell apart.
Don't beat yourself up, Akira.
You were hurt.
[AKIRA]
In case you didn't know,
my mom was killed by the Owl.
All my father wanted was
to avenge her death.
[AKIRA] Where were you while
he was fighting the Rabbit?
You were his partner.
You were supposed
to be by his side.
He never should've faced
such a deadly ghoul alone!
Why the hell weren't
you with him?
I can't believe
they promoted you
to senior investigator.
If you had done your job
and stuck with your partner,
my father would still
be alive right now!
I'm sorry, I--
[AKIRA] My father is dead
because of you.
Kotaro Amon.
I loathe you with
every fiber of my being.
I'm sorry. I don't
know what else to say.
But you're right, I am
to blame. I know that.
I'm still haunted by nightmares
about what happened that day.
I play it over and
over in my mind,
thinking of all the ways
I could've saved him.
Why're you telling me this?
[AMON] So you know I won't
let it happen again.
[gasps]
I swear. I'll stand by you
and protect you at all costs.
We will avenge your
parents' deaths.
If you say so.
You okay? Hey, Akira!
Great, just my luck.
Akira. You're home now.
[AKIRA groans]
[gasps] Oh, it's just
a cat. A big one.
[meows]
You lead the way.
[AMON sighs]
[AKIRA gags]
Ah!
[AMON pants]
Akira. I got medicine for you--
[AKIRA moans]
[grunts]
I'll leave it here.
I also picked up a
bottle of water for you.
[sighs] Well, I'd
better be leaving.
Please don't go.
[gasps]
Stay here with me.
[AMON gasps]
Are you sure?
Don't leave me, Father.
[AMON gasps]
I can't believe I thought...
that I-- That she--
Get a grip, Amon!
You stupid rookie!
What's the matter with you?
You know better! Use your
head! Stupid rookie!
Two hundred 98! Two hundred 99!
Three hundred!
[AKIRA grunts]
[AMON grunting]
[grunting]
Oh... My head.
Maris Stella.
[MARIS STELLA meows]
--[AMON grunting]
--[gasps]
[AMON grunts]
Seven thousand...
...890.
[groans, pants]
What are you doing out here?
Oh, you know. Push-ups.
Just getting a work out in.
[AKIRA] You've got a long
list of accomplishments.
You were valedictorian of
your class at CCG Academy.
And as Senior Investigator
Kureo Mado's partner,
you defeated one deadly
ghoul after another.
You were promoted to
Investigator 1st Class
after less than three
years on the job.
You took down multiple
Aogiri-aligned ghouls
in the battle over
the 11th Ward,
including the infamous
Bin Brothers.
[AKIRA] You were promoted
to Senior Investigator
at just 27 years old.
It'd be a shame if anyone
ever found out the
truth about you.
That you're a pervy
investigator who's obsessed
with his subordinate
and push-ups, apparently.
[AMON grunts]
[AKIRA]
I'm just messing with you.
Now eat up.
I promise it's edible.
I had to take over the household
chores when Mom died.
I've actually become
a pretty decent cook.
Thank you.
[AKIRA]
Investigator Amon.
Thanks a lot. I appreciate it.
[AMON]
No problem.
[YOSHITOKI]
I singlehandedly picked
each and every one of you
for this special task force.
You are the CCG's new
Owl Suppression Unit.
From this day forward,
you will be working
under and reporting
directly to me.
[YOSHITOKI] We've got
a challenge ahead of us.
The Owl, who's undoubtedly
the leader of Aogiri,
is a formidable foe.
Once we locate the
organization's base,
we'll launch an
extermination campaign.
Both The Owl and Aogiri...
[YOSHITOKI]
...must be destroyed.