[SEIDO'S MOM]
I wish you had called, first.
I would've made your favorite.
No worries. This is delicious.
Well, I'm glad.
Someone has to make
sure you eat properly.
[sighs] Yeah. Thanks, Mom.
[COOKIE whines]
[SEIDO'S MOM] Still, it's
strange having you home.
Not that I'm
complaining, mind you.
Is work stressing you out?
No, not much.
[SEIDO] A mission to
exterminate the Owl?
Yes, it'll be one of our
largest ops to date.
You'll be there. I saw
your name on the roster.
But, before that.
You'll need to write
out one of these.
[gasps]
I don't know what
I'm supposed to write.
Aw, man, not another one.
[SHINOHARA]
Rules are rules, Juzo.
[JUZO sighs]
[JUZO] I know, but I don't
have anything "deep"
to tell anybody.
It doesn't have to be "deep."
Try saying something nice.
Maybe a "Thank you,"
to the friends you've made?
[JUZO]
Mm?
Here's mine, sir.
[KUROIWA grunts]
[sighs] Listen up.
[INVESTIGATORS gasp]
I'm goin' out there with you.
Seriously?
Really, Investigator?
[grunts]
[KURAMOTO] Did ya get yours
written yet, Captain Hirako?
[HIRAKO]
My testamentary note? Yeah.
[KURAMOTO]
Really?
I tried, but I don't have
any idea what to write.
[HIRAKO]
Don't overthink it.
Thank your parents,
that kinda stuff.
I bet Arima finished his.
Can't help but wonder
what he wrote.
From what he told me...
He doesn't write anything;
he leaves it blank.
Seriously?! That is so cool!
Not really.
[HIRAKO] He said he'd
stare at it for hours
trying to think up what to say.
[HIRAKO] I guess he couldn't
find the words, either.
I asked Dr. Chigyo for an
overhaul on the Dojima.
Even got a new trick for it,
thanks to my junior partner.
I hope to have it with me
when we hunt down the Owl.
[footsteps rustling]
[gasps]
Akira?
Investigator. Fancy
meeting you here.
[AKIRA] She was your
classmate at the Academy?
[AMON]
Yeah.
My Dojima was hers.
She died in the 24th Ward.
What a small world it is.
[AKIRA]
My parents worked in the 24th.
That was where their
investigative team
focused all of their efforts.
Under Captain Marude's command.
[INVESTIGATORS gasp]
[AKIRA] That's where
they ran into the Owl.
They gave it their all,
but against his exceptional
strength, there was no hope.
[AKIRA]
Investigator Marude realized it
--[MARUDE] Get out of here!
--and ordered a withdrawal.
[INVESTIGATORS grunting]
[MADO]
Let go of me! Let go!
[MARUDE]
Kureo! That's an order!
--I don't care!
--[MARUDE] Kureo!
[MADO]
Kasuka! Kasuka!
[AKIRA] My mother stayed behind
to cover their retreat.
Kasuka!
[AKIRA] Ever since then,
my father was obsessed
with hunting the Owl.
[AKIRA] Now his vengeance is
mine to bear. And I'll get it.
Even if I have to choke the
bastard with my bare hands.
He will die. I swear it.
[AMON]
Akira.
Just don't do anything reckless.
Don't mistake me
for your Dojima girl.
Hmph. I'm not her. I'm me.
If you need me to
prove it, I can.
[gasps]
You're too tall
for your own good.
[AMON gasps]
[AKIRA]
That's so like you.
So very like you.
[SEIDO sobbing]
[gasps]
[silence]
[gasping]
[NEWSCASTER 1A]
Tensions are at an all-time high
in the 20th Ward, where a
large-scale police force
has cordoned off the area.
The CCG reported the civilian
evacuation was completed
ahead of schedule,
and may move forward
with the operation as
early as this evening.
We'll have more as
the situation develops.
Commence the operation!
[CCG TROOPERS gasp]
[footsteps tapping]
[gasps]
[KOMA, IRIMI]
Welcome to Anteiku.
[CCG TROOPERS grunt]
[CCG TROOPERS gasp]
[CCG TROOPERS groan]
[CCG TROOPER 9I yelps]
[CCG TROOPER 9J groans]
[CCG TROOPERS groaning]
[CCG TROOPERS yelping, groaning]
Stay frosty! There's
only two of 'em!
[IRIMI]
"Only two," he says.
[KOMA] Apes and Dogs
run in packs, chump.
[CCG TROOPERS gasp]
I thought it was just the Owl
that was holed up in there!
I know them!
That's the Devil Ape!
[CCG TROOPER 9D]
And the other is the Black Dog!
[CCG TROOPER 9D] I don't get it.
They're sworn enemies!
Why are they teaming up?
[KOMA] You haven't gone soft
on me, have you, fellas?
[APE FACES]
Hell no!
[IRIMI] All of you,
lay down your lives for me.
[BLACK DOBERS]
Right!
[KOMA]
Go wild.
[CCG TROOPERS groaning]
[APE FACES grunting]
[CCG TROOPER gasps]
[SOLDIER 9A]
The first division has engaged!
We've got Ape Faces and
Black Dobers out here! [screams]
The Black Dobers?
Where the hell's Aogiri?
Orders, Chief Washu?
[YOSHITOKI grunts]
First Division, do what you can
to split up their forces.
Second and Third Divisions,
move in and kill any stragglers.
Investigator Marude
will command both.
Copy that.
[beeping]
[HACHIKAWA]
Hachikawa here.
What is it?
[HACHIKAWA]
Let me have the Black Dog, sir.
I've got a bone
to pick with her.
D'you hear that?
That means you've got
the Devil Ape, Mogan.
[MOGAN]
Mm-hm! Roger, boy.
And Hachikawa,
don't do anything dumb!
[HACHIKAWA]
Copy that.
[screams]
--[APE FACE 9C grunts]
--[CCG TROOPER 9Y yelps]
[CCG TROOPER 9AA groans]
[KOMA]
Who's next?
[CCG TROOPERS gasp]
Higher...
--[KOMA gasps]
--...Mind!
[APE FACES scream]
[KOMA] Careful with that.
Someone might end up dead.
[MOGAN]
Crawl back to your mountaintop.
You damn dirty ape.
[KOMA laughs] Hate to break it
to you, but this is my mountain.
[IRIMI gasps]
[BLACK DOBERS scream]
[IRIMI groans]
[HACHIKAWA] Hey. Long time,
no see. Black Dog.
[IRIMI]
Bow-wow.
[YOSHITOKI]
Divisions Four and above,
commence lock down!
Don't let a single one of
them get past our nets!
[CCG TROOPERS]
Yes, sir!
[YOSHITOKI gasps]
[YOSHITOKI]
There you are.
[CCG TROOPERS gasp]
[YOSHIMURA] To take from another
is tantamount to evil.
From the moment we are born,
we practice this art.
Perfecting the sin
we've inherited.
That's what life is.
A continuous series
of compounding sin.
[YOSHIMURA] It is life itself
that draws us into the darkness.
I have accepted my fate.
I know that I am evil.
As are each and
every one of you.
[YOSHIMURA] Now, let's
practice a different sin.
[TOUKA gasps]
[YOMO]
Where are you going?
Do you have to ask?
It's too late.
What?
[TOUKA]
So, that's it?
We sit here and do nothing?
We always said
that we'd help each other
out at Anteiku.
I want to fight with them.
Please, Yomo! I can't
let them die out there!
[YOMO]
I know this is hard.
But they've been preparing
for this day for a long time.
[YOMO] Koma and Irimi
have taken many lives.
Committed many sins.
It wasn't until
they met Yoshimura
that they finally understood
the magnitude of those sins.
[YOMO] They tried,
but no amount of goodwill
could change what they'd done.
[YOMO] And so, they
need to be punished.
Punished?
Yes, this fight is
their retribution.
And not just them, but all
of their followers as well.
What about me?
I'm sick with sin.
Don't I deserve to be punished?
I've killed people, too!
Not just because I had to eat,
but because I was
royally pissed off!
So, why not me?
Why am I the only one
who gets a free pass?
[grunts]
[TOUKA]
Why? Why?
[IRIMI]
You're lucky.
I always thought
school would be fun.
[TOUKA]
Why are they doing this?
[KOMA] If by "gross tie"
you mean "awesome tie,"
then I totally agree with you.
[TOUKA] Why does everyone
end up leaving me?
Good work today.
[TOUKA]
I'm gonna lose it all.
Hey, Kirishima, I made
a little extra for lunch
if you'd like to share it.
Have you decided...
[TOUKA]
My promises to Yoriko...
All the hard work
I put into studying...
[YORIKO]
What? Wait, you mean...
[TOUKA]
I'm losing it all.
My dreams. My friends.
It's all slipping away from me.
[TOUKA] Why won't it stop?
I can't take it!
[TOUKA]
I won't lose anyone else!
[NISHIKI] Would it kill ya
to crack a smile now and then?
[KANEKI]
What are you doing here?
Heh. Catchin' up
with an old friend.
[NISHIKI]
I got a message from Yomo.
He took Touka and
Hinami someplace safe.
They're out of harm's way.
[NISHIKI]
Damn.
Seems like such an
abrupt end, doesn't it?
Things got so relaxed I started
taking them for granted.
Now it's all gone to hell.
I can't say I'll miss
the old man's coddling.
The Codger'd probably wipe
your ass, if you let him.
Pompadour and Irimi
were just as annoying.
There was just
somethin' about them
that struck a nerve, you know?
Have you decided what
you're going to do next?
[NISHIKI]
Me?
Well, gettin' the hell
out of Dodge, for starters.
Sure, I could charge right
into that flock of Doves,
but then that'd mean the others
would die for nothing.
So...
I'm gonna see Kimi one
last time, and then I'm gone.
I don't want her sittin'
around waitin' for me
till she's old and gray.
[NISHIKI]
Besides...
A girl as fine as she is?
Gotta hit that one
last time, y'know?
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't brought you
to Anteiku, then, maybe...
I don't need you
driving the knife in
any deeper than it is.
I won't hold it against you.
So that mask of yours.
[NISHIKI]
There's no reason for
you to wear it
anymore, is there?
I won't let you do it!
[KANEKI]
Tsukiyama, I--
[pants]
There's too many
of them out there.
And, if I let you go, I would
never forgive myself.
There's nothing you
can do to stop me.
Is that so? Very well then.
Then you die!
Right here! Right now!
You're not leaving me
any choice, Kaneki!
Even my Tsukiyama family
blood couldn't save me
from a force of that size,
so how can you expect
to fare any better?
What else would you have me do?
What else?
Have you forgotten
that you're my prey?!
I've wasted so much time
waiting patiently.
Now no one can keep me
from my feast, got it?
Not even you!
[TSUKIYAMA grunts]
Kaneki!
[TSUKIYAMA yells]
[thud]
[CCG TROOPERS murmuring]
Now! Let's go--
[CCG TROOPERS scream]
[CCG TROOPERS gasping]
[YOSHITOKI]
Hm.
[yells]
[CCG TROOPERS yelling]
[CCG TROOPER 9A grunts] We're
screwed. He's Triple S rated!
How the hell are we
supposed to defeat him?
[SHINOHARA]
It's a real shame.
[SHINOHARA] Iwa here would've
loved a cup of your coffee.
I wish you'd had the chance
to share some with him.
[TSUKIYAMA sobs]
Have a heart, my sweet Kaneki.
I would give anything
if you'd only stay.
You know that I can't.
[KANEKI]
I'm sorry.
I appreciate that
you tried to stop me.
[KANEKI]
But...
I've always wanted to help.
It's time that I did.