[AMON] Every day, we lose
precious human lives
to the ghouls.
So many, in fact,
that the fate of humanity
has been forever changed.
And we will continue
to suffer those losses
unless we are willing to
stand up and fight back.
So, drill that into your heads.
And put everything you've
got into your training.
That's all I've got.
Thank you for listening.
[applause]
[KURONA]
Investigator Amon?
Shizuku. Ask him.
Uh. Well, sir, I wanted
to know if women
can become CCG investigators?
I mean good ones like you.
Of course.
Work hard, and I'd be honored
to serve beside you,
Shizuku Kawakami.
And the same goes for you, too,
Kurona and Nashiro Yasuhisa.
[GIRLS giggle]
It's so easy for people
to lose their lives.
[NASHIRO]
Hello, Rei.
[JUZO] Hm? Ah! If it isn't
Nashiro and Kurona!
What are you doing here?
You first.
Why didn't you come
to Shizuku's funeral?
Yeah, aren't you sad? At all?
Why should I be?
I mean, she only died, right?
[KURONA, NASHIRO grunt]
[KURONA] How could you
say something like that?
She was your friend.
[JUZO] Yeah, but how's being
sad gonna change things?
Dying's natural,
it's no different
than eating or sleeping.
[NASHIRO] Quiet, Rei!
How could you be so heartless?
I'm warning you,
quit bugging me!
Leave me alone!
Can't you see that I've got
better things to do? Now go!
[NASHIRO]
That's it!
[gasps]
[JUZO]
Dying's normal.
People do it every
moment of every day.
It just happened
to be her time to go.
Isn't this awesome?
It's like a class reunion!
[NASHIRO]
Rei!
[JUZO] The name's Juzo now!
And don't you forget it!
[KURONA, NASHIRO grunt]
[JUZO] So tell me somethin',
what made the two of you
decide to go "ghoul"
on the world?
Inquiring minds wanna know!
[NASHIRO]
You might get answers if you'd
shut up once in a while!
[KURONA] You're no better
than we are, Rei!
You gave up your
name to join them!
[NASHIRO] The CCG are monsters!
Why can't you see that?
[gasps]
[JUZO]
Uh-oh...
[KURONA]
Don't think poorly of us.
Do it!
[JUZO] I was about to
say the same to you!
[JUZO]
This is for your own good,
so please don't
think poorly of me.
[KURONA groans]
[NASHIRO]
Kurona!
[KURONA]
I'm all right! It'll heal.
You sure about that?
[gasps]
[laughs]
Because I'm not sure
you have enough... time.
[AYATO pants]
[SHINOHARA grunts]
[AYATO grunts]
[SHINOHARA] He's fast,
but he's gettin' weak.
[SHINOHARA grunts]
[AYATO grunts]
[SHINOHARA, AYATO grunting]
[AYATO groans]
Damn it.
[groans]
Hurts, doesn't it?
[laughs]
[JUZO] I've got 45 more
cuts and stabs just like it
for you to enjoy!
[JUZO laughing]
[growls]
[grunts]
Gotcha!
[groans]
[JUZO] I've been carving up
ghouls for a while now.
So, I've got a pretty
good idea how many slices
it takes to rip one
apart at the seams.
You shouldn't have
messed with me.
You're what's become of Rei?
[JUZO] For our next game,
I'm gonna take the one thing
you cherish most in
this world, Kurona!
[gasps]
[NASHIRO]
Damn you!
[JUZO]
You ready to play?
No! Stay back!
[JUZO]
Gotcha!
[gasps]
[gasping]
[JUZO] You're what she
cherishes the most, silly!
[laughs]
[AYATO pants]
[AYATO pants, grunts]
[AYATO, SHINOHARA grunt]
[SHINOHARA] Something's wrong.
My Arata's resisting.
I wonder why?
[AYATO grunts]
[AYATO yells]
[SHINOHARA yells]
[AYATO groans]
Shiro! No!
Ku... ro....
[KURONA gasps]
[gasping]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
It's your turn! Come on down!
[whimpers]
[NASHIRO]
Run.
Leave me here.
Please, save yourself.
Huh?
[JUZO]
Party poopers.
They didn't even bother to
tell me why they turned ghoul.
What a drag.
They've wiped out every
guard in the facility.
Stay back, Takizawa.
Looks like somebody's coming.
Huh?
[TATARA]
Hoji.
It's been a long time.
Not long enough. Interesting.
So you're a member
of Aogiri now?
[TATARA]
Fei and Yan. I want them back.
Sorry to disappoint you.
But I can't do that.
Not anymore.
[AYATO grunts, groans]
[AYATO groaning]
[AYATO grunts]
[SHINOHARA gasps]
[ARATA]
"The boy reached out his hand
and with a warm smile
on his face, he asked,
'Will you be my friend?'
Godot answered with
a triumphant 'Yes!'
And the two shook hands, sealing
their newfound friendship.
The end."
Well, what do you think?
Read it again!
Huh?
Come on, Dad, one more time!
Well, okay.
Pleasant dreams, Touka, Ayato.
[door rattling]
[lock clicks]
[AYATO]
Dad?
[rattling]
[SHINOHARA gasps]
[SHINOHARA] He's fast! I can't
make out his kagune!
Whatever it is, it doesn't
look completely formed.
[SHINOHARA]
Holy hell. It's a kakuja!
[AKIRA grunting]
[AMON]
Our reinforcements should be
storming the place
any minute now.
I'll have them get you
out of here. Stay strong.
[KURONA grunting]
[grunts]
[AMON]
Are you all right?
Yeah.
[KURONA grunts]
[gasps]
Tch.
[AMON gasps]
I know you two.
[KURONA grunts]
Wait!
They're ghouls.
[AMON]
Let's keep moving.
When I met Kurona and Nashiro,
they were human.
Now they're ghouls?
That's impossible! What in
the hell is going on?
[ETO humming]
[ETO giggles]
It's about that time.
[weapons crashing, clanging]
[SHINOHARA grunts]
[SHINOHARA groaning]
[SHINOHARA] My Arata's no
good against this guy.
Screw it!
[SHINOHARA]
How do ya like this?
[KANEKI groans]
I'm sorry kid, but my
family's not ready
for me to punch out just yet.
[SHINOHARA]
Huh?
[KANEKI gasping]
My fingers on the bench.
[KANEKI gasping] Centipedes,
crawling in my ears, in my head!
Son of a bitch!
How many kagune sacs
does this guy have?
[laughs] One thousand
minus... seven... is...
[SHINOHARA] I've put down some
crazy ghouls over the years.
[KANEKI]
Do you know?
But you've gotta be
the craziest of 'em all.
Bring it!
[SHINOHARA gasps]
[SHINOHARA screams]
[laughing]
[HOJI panting]
[TATARA grunts]
I've got you covered!
[TATARA]
Fei's kagune.
Run, Takizawa!
Get out of here, now!
[TATARA]
So he's one of yours?
[HOJI gasps]
[alarm blares]
[SEIDO yelps]
[TATARA]
I guess that's my cue.
They deployed the CRc gas.
Well, that should stop
Aogiri in their tracks.
[AKIRA]
Thank you.
Hey, what's the matter, Amon?
Did you hear something?
[cracking, roaring]
[AMON]
What the hell?
[KANEKI chomping]
[AMON]
Eyepatch?
[KANEKI chomping]
[AMON gasping]
[panting]
Damn, you!
[AMON grunts]
[AMON yells]
Okay, Eyepatch. I want answers
and you're going to give
them to me, got it?
Why?!
You had the chance to
kill me but you didn't!
Why did you spare my life?
[AMON]
You were crying that night.
I saw tears streaming
down your face.
Or was that... all a lie?
[KANEKI gasping, groaning]
[AMON]
I thought I'd get some answers
if I found you again.
But it looks like the ghoul
who spared my life is long gone.
All I see before me now
is a murderous monster!
[grunts]
[AMON grunting]
[AMON grunts]
[KANEKI grunting]
[gasps]
Y'know, it's a shame.
I thought you were different
from other ghouls.
But you're just another
heartless killer, aren't you?
[gasps]
[KANEKI whimpering]
[KANEKI]
I don't wanna eat anymore.
[AMON sighs]
[gasps]
[roars]
[AKIRA gasps]
Investigator Amon!
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
It's really him.
The One-Eyed Owl!
[AYATO grunts]
Huh?
[AYATO yelps]
[KANEKI grunting]
[screams]
The Owl's taking them.
[AYATO gasping]
[KANEKI screaming]
This isn't over.