[NAKI whimpering]
Boss... Boss...
[NAKI] Where are you?
I don't wanna be alone.
[AYATO]
Let's go.
[KANEKI grunts]
[CCG TROOPERS gasping]
--[gunfire]
--[CCG TROOPERS screaming]
[KANEKI, AYATO grunt]
[AYATO, KANEKI gasp]
[AYATO]
Who in the hell are they?
[AYATO gasps]
[KANEKI gasps]
[KANEKI grunts]
[NASHIRO]
Well, what do ya know?
[KURONA] He is strong.
Just like Papa said.
[KANEKI gasps]
[AYATO] Aw, shit! Get him
outta there! Hurry, dammit!
[KANEKI gasps]
[KANEKI]
One-eyed...
[NAKI]
I'm burning!
[AYATO]
Huh?
[NAKI] I'm on fire, Boss!
I'm burning up!
What should I do? I gotta hurry.
It's so hot. I might...
...explode!
Where's my boss? Where's Yamori?
--Take me to him!
--[AYATO] Hey!
--I wanna see my boss!
--We're saving you, dumbass!
[AYATO]
Screw this.
[NAKI groans]
[NAKI whimpers]
Oh, Boss.
My feelings are an inferno!
Take me to Yamori or I'll
incinerate you, too!
[AYATO]
You gotta be kiddin' me.
Of all the convicts we
could've busted out,
they chose this dumbass?
What'd you call me?
No one talks to me
like that and lives!
No one except for Boss Yamori!
And you ain't him!
So I'm gonna ground
you into a bloody pulp!
"It was almost as
though the people
had turned to candy.
Said the..."
..."the," uh...
whatever that is.
[TOUKA]
How's your new book? Is it good?
[HINAMI]
Mm-hm!
Some of the words are a little
hard, but it's interesting!
You can borrow it if
you wanna read it.
Nah, that's all right.
Hey, guess what I heard!
[TOUKA]
Hm?
[HINAMI] My favorite
author, Sen Takatsuki,
is having a book
signing tomorrow.
[TOUKA] All right.
What time do we leave?
You mean it? Thanks, Touka!
[NEWSCASTER 1A]
We interrupt this program...
--[HINAMI] In that case, let's--
--Moments ago,
an armored CCG transport
van was brutally attacked
by a gang of ghouls.
According to eyewitness reports,
the "Eyepatch", who is
currently wanted by police,
led the assault.
The CCG believes the attack
is part of an organi--
[HINAMI] "Eyepatch"?
That's him, isn't it?
I'm sure Kaneki has a
good reason for this.
He's not the kind of person
who does bad things.
[TOUKA]
Hinami.
Huh?
Can we please not talk
about this anymore?
[HINAMI]
Why not?
He's gone now.
And he doesn't have
anything to do with us.
Bedtime.
[IRIMI] You look upset,
Touka. Is everything okay?
Uh. Yeah. It's just Hinami.
[IRIMI]
Hm...
[KOMA]
What's up? You two have a spat?
That's easily fixed! Just leave
it to Koma the Devil Ape!
I'll smooth it out.
[IRIMI] Koma. Be a dear
and bus the tables.
As you wish.
[IRIMI]
Be patient with her.
But stay firm, remember
you're the grown-up.
That's a scary thought.
[HINAMI]
Good morning!
[IRIMI]
Go ahead.
Hey! Good morning, Hinami.
Tada!
Wait a sec,
are those my clothes?
They looked small for you,
so I borrowed them.
Is that okay?
I don't mind,
knock yourself out.
Don't you look fancy!
Are you going somewhere?
[HINAMI]
Mm-hm!
Sen Takatsuki is doing
a signing at the bookstore
in front of the train station.
[TOUKA] Just give me a minute,
and I'll be good to go.
I'll be fine on my own.
You're going by yourself?
I don't think that's safe.
It's really not far from here.
She'll be all right.
[TOUKA]
But, Irimi...
Keep to yourself.
If you see any doves, come
back to Anteiku. Understood?
Right! 'Kay, I'm off!
Ah--
Touka has enough to
worry about without
me distracting her
all the time.
No need to worry.
I sent Koma to keep
an eye on her.
Thanks.
Ah! My precious
Hinami is blossoming
into an independent flower,
right before my eyes!
[TOUKA] Quit talking like
you know anything! Idiot!
Whoa, there! Ha, ha, ha!
I guess I touched a nerve.
Jerk!
Nishiki. Shouldn't you
be in class right now?
[NISHIKI] Yeah, but I left my
notebook in my work locker.
[NISHIKI]
Hey, java head.
[TOUKA]
What is it?
[NISHIKI]
Wanna check out the campus?
[TOUKA]
Huh?
Wanna go to Kamii, right?
You should at least see it.
Help me out here.
Don't worry, I'll handle things.
The manager should
be back shortly.
There you have it.
Don't make me drag you out.
But, you...
Wait! Nishiki!
[NISHIKI] Here we've
got the admin building,
and next to that is science.
[TOUKA] They have a building
for every subject?
[NISHIKI]
No, not necessarily.
Some of them house experimental
tech, though, which I need.
And here we have the cafeteria.
[TOUKA]
Oh, wow.
With all these people around,
no one would notice
if I didn't eat.
[NISHIKI]
I suppose not.
You'll still have
to choke it down
when you're hangin'
with friends, though.
It's just so big!
My school doesn't hold
a candle to this place.
It's called a "Mega-versity"
for a reason.
Well, I'm supposed to
meet up with Kimi. Later.
You're leaving me?
Try not to cry like
a baby if you get lost.
Would it have killed you
to show me around?
[TOUKA] So this is where
Kaneki went to school.
I can see him now,
reading those ridiculous
books of his.
[gasps]
[TOUKA]
As long as these are posted up.
There's no way he can
come back here.
[HIDE]
Here we go!
This is the perfect spot.
[UNDERCLASSMAN 3A]
Hold it, Hide, you can't just
take that down!
[HIDE]
Whatever.
If we want people
to see our poster,
we need to put it where
it stands out. There.
[gasps]
[HIDE]
Uh--
What are you doing here?
[SEIDO sighs]
There's no end to these things.
What're you hoping to find
by digging through
six-month-old files?
Something started to bother
me after Akira's report.
If I'm right, the
answers are in here.
I wouldn't put too much
faith in her intuition, Hoji.
I worked with someone
like her, once.
A superior with
a sharp intuition.
Kureo Mado. Investigator
Akira's father.
The man spent every
moment on the job.
I think it's a safe bet
Akira's the same way.
Hm?
[HIDE]
Here! Nice and hot.
[TOUKA]
Thanks, Hide.
So, decided to go
to Kamii, huh?
Yeah. If I can get in.
Man, those entrance
exams are a bitch.
You'll do fine.
[TOUKA]
About Kaneki.
Huh?
I was wondering
what kind of person
he was as a kid.
Kaneki, huh?
He's been a serious book nerd
for as long as I've known him.
Whenever he'd get the chance,
he'd bury his face
in one of 'em.
After his mom died, he changed.
It was subtle, but I noticed.
He always seemed lonely.
Even in a crowd.
It sounds depressing,
but he found other interests,
and even had the lead
in a school play, once.
[TOUKA]
A play?
I know! He doesn't seem
like the type at all.
But he was so good on stage,
it actually gave me goose bumps.
Really?
He always shouldered
the weight of the world.
Didn't matter what
he was doing,
he'd don his mask and play
any role life threw at him.
Maybe that burden was
too much to carry.
Wherever he went,
I just hope he's happy.
[TOUKA] I'll bet he's
out there right now,
reading a book or something!
So, don't worry.
I'm sure he's safe and sound.
[HIDE] I don't suppose you ever
caught Kaneki's bad habit?
Habit?
Yeah! Whenever he was
trying to hide something.
He'd grab his chin
and rub it, like this.
But you didn't hear
that from me. See ya!
[ambulance alarm blaring]
[firetruck alarm blaring]
[HINAMI sighs]
I'm really sorry
for the hold up.
I'm sure she'll be here soon.
[SEN]
Late, late, late! So very late!
[gasps]
Ah! There you are!
[SEN] Look, coach!
I made it home safe!
No, you're out. Entirely.
[SEN]
Aw...
[SEN] Whew. Um. Sorry for
the wait. I overslept.
[giggles]
--[SEN humming]
--[EDITOR] Next person, please.
Goodness! Well, aren't you
a lovely young lady?
What's your name, dear?
I'm Hinami.
[SEN]
"To the lovely Hinami."
Um. Hold on!
Or do you go by
"Hina" instead?
No, ma'am. This is
going to be a gift.
[SEN]
Oh, I gotcha!
So, who would you like me
to make it out to, sweetie?
To Kaneki. Ken Kaneki.
Did you say Kaneki?
[HINAMI]
Mm-hm.
[SEN] All right.
And how do I spell that?
Oh, um,
It's the same characters as
"sweet osmanthus," and "shine."
Goodness. What a great
way to remember it!
To Ken Kaneki...
So, is he your boyfriend?
Uh... Oh, no,
nothing like that!
He's like family!
[SEN]
That's beyond adorable!
He must be one heck of
a guy for you to do this.
Uh...
Thanks for coming
to see me, Hinami.
No, thank you, Miss!
See ya!
Ken Kaneki, huh?
Yo! Got a delivery
for you, Seido!
What's up, Messenger?
[HIDE]
It's Nagachika!
Geez, would it kill ya to
remember my name at least once?
So, what's that
you've got there?
Huh?
Just reading up on
the Eyepatch ghoul.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but didn't that Eyepatch
dude first show up
somewhere in the 20th Ward?
You've done your homework.
That's right. He and
the Rabbit ghoul.
They're suspected of
killing an investigator.
So, who's this "Naki" guy?
A cross between a
dedicated underling
and a rabid fan-boy.
He worked for Jason.
Eyepatch freed him
on his way to Cochlea.
[HIDE]
Cochlea?
[SEIDO]
It's a ghoul internment center,
y'know like a jail,
in the 23rd Ward.
It's where the CCG houses
S and Double-S rated ghouls.
Wow. Sounds terrifying.
Yeah.
Working there isn't high
on my list of priorities.
Do you think Eyepatch
might've been
trying to help one
of his buddies?
Who can say for sure?
We don't even know if ghouls
have a sense of camaraderie.
Sounds like Aogiri,
and groups like it,
must be pretty rare, then.
Actually, they pop up
all the time.
When the Owl first
showed up ten years ago,
he had a little
posse of his own.
Then there were groups
like the Black Dobers
and the Ape Faces.
They were big back in the day,
but no one's heard
from them in years.
[AKIRA] I hope you're getting
paid for this information.
Otherwise, why would
you offer it up?
Hey, Akira! What's shakin'?
Nagachika, is that right?
Would you care to explain to me
why you're so
interested in ghouls?
Well, it's hard not to be when
they're all over the news.
And knowing is half
the battle, right?
Welp. I'll get out of your hair.
Enjoy the rest of your day!
[gasps] Look at the
size of it!
--This is CCG's main laboratory.
--Wow!
[SHINOHARA]
They handle everything in here.
From ghoul research, to Q-bullet
and quinque development.
Impressive, isn't it?
[JUZO]
Uh-huh!
[CHIGYO]
They'll let anyone in here.
[SHINOHARA]
Good to see ya, Chigyo.
Same to you.
You're not exactly what I
pictured, Investigator Suzuya.
But, if you managed
to take down Jason,
you must be stronger
than you look.
[JUZO]
It was nothin'.
I only finished what
somebody else had started.
[CHIGYO laughs]
Modesty. That's refreshing.
Sorry it took us so long.
But I can assure you that it
was worth the wait. Voila!
[gasps]
Well? It's a beautiful
piece, isn't it?
Huh? What are you doing?
[SHINOHARA]
Uh--
I wanna see how
sharp this baby is!
Hey, we need that
steel to make quinques!
[SHINOHARA groans]
[JUZO]
Hey, Mr. Shinohara? Am I allowed
to give my weapon a name?
[SHINOHARA]
Sure, as long as you promise
not to break anything else.
Good. Then I shall
call him Juzo's Jason.
[NAKI]
No way! It's a lie! It's a lie!
There's no way it's true!
Boss Yamori can't be dead!
Those pigs must
have tricked him!
Yes! That's the only way!
[NAKI sobs]
Boss Yamori!
Screw the CCG!
I'll pound them all
into bloody pulps!
Tch. I can't listen to this.
Come back, boss! I need you!
You're my divine leader!
If you're gone,
what's that make me?
[NAKI sobs] I wanna see you.
Even if it's just your name.
Boss Yamori... Yamori...
Boss Yamori, wait a minute.
Is that how it's spelled?
Maybe this way?
[NAKI]
No, that doesn't look right.
Boss Yamori.
So is that how it's spelled?
Yeah.
[NAKI whimpering]
[NAKI wails] Yamori!
I wanna see you again!
[NAKI]
Eyepatch!
You're a really
good guy, I mean it!
Thanks for helping me out, man.
[NAKI whimpering, sobbing]
[ETO]
Ken Kaneki. Thought so.
--[TATARA] Hm?
--[ETO giggles]
Oh, it's nothing.
[TSUKIYAMA]
So, have you heard?
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3B]
Huh?
[TSUKIYAMA] About the new
big shot, you know,
the Eyepatch?
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3B] I heard he's
some kind of power house.
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3A]
Yeah, I heard that too,
but have you heard the rumor?
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3B]
Rumor?
[TSUKIYAMA] Please, enlighten
us. If you'd be so kind.
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3A] Word is,
he took a bite out of Yamori.
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3B gasps]
No! For real?
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3A]
Straight up cannibalized him.
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3B]
I don't believe it!
No one could pull that off!
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3A]
Unless he's a monster.
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3B gasps]
[TSUKIYAMA gasps]
My sweet Kaneki, a cannibal?
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3B]
Your what now?
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3B groans]
[chuckles]
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3A gasps, pants]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Ce est incroyable!
Yes, Kaneki. Ah!
This spice you've added
is truly captivating!
Cannibalism! The taboo of
taboos! The forbidden apple!
Like Adam, you were drawn
to its promise of power!
To taste that apple...
To savor him for myself.
Over and over!
Every bite would
be a revelation!
It's my destiny!
Man, you are one sick bastard.
[AOGIRI SOLDIER 3A]
Get off of me, dammit!
[TSUKIYAMA]
Why don't you tell us
everything you've heard.
Oui, se il vous plait?
[HOJI] I've been chasing a gut
feeling the past few days.
Fill them in, Takizawa.
Right.
We went through files
from around the time
the Eyepatch ghoul
first appeared,
and we dug up an incident
that seems rather puzzling.
Can you be more specific?
Yes, sir. Four months ago,
in the 20th Ward,
some steel girders fell
and crushed a bystander.
Oh, yeah. He was in
pretty bad shape.
As I recall, they gave him
organs from the young woman
who was killed.
Right. Now, here's
where it gets weird.
They both went missing.
The young man and his surgeon.
There's been no sign
of them ever since.
[SEIDO] The young man's
name is Ken Kaneki.
He was a student at
Kamii University.
He went to Kamii?
[HIDE]
For crying out loud.
You know better than to make
a nice girl wait for you.
Star of the school play, huh?
That's hard to believe.