[KANEKI] I didn't come
here for a cup of coffee.
I wanna know about the Owl.
[YOSHIMURA sighs]
A long time ago, there was
a ghoul named Kuzen.
[GHOULS panting]
[INVESTIGATORS panting]
[screams]
[GHOUL 8C screams]
[GHOUL 8A whimpers, groans]
[GHOUL 8B yelps]
[YOSHIMURA] Like so many
of us, he was forced
to kill and eat humans
in order to survive.
But he didn't stop there.
He also slaughtered
his ghoul companions.
As a result, he found
himself alone,
cursing his fate in solitude.
[footsteps tapping]
[YOSHIMURA]
Tales of Kuzen's ruthlessness
began spreading far and wide.
It wasn't long
before an organization
set their sights on him.
They were determined to enlist
him, and they were successful.
[YOSHIMURA] Kuzen did whatever
the organization asked of him
without even batting an eye.
He had no qualms about
killing humans or ghouls.
Before he knew it, he had
become an assassin.
[YOSHIMURA]
But one thing never changed.
The loneliness he
felt in his heart.
In the end, he chose to
leave the organization
because it didn't
feel like home.
[YOSHIMURA]
Then one day,
his life was changed
thanks to a chance encounter
with a pretty, young human.
[UKINA]
Would you like another cup, sir?
[UKINA] You sit in the same
seat, drinking the same coffee,
day after day.
You take it strong
and black. Is that right?
[UKINA]
I never would've guessed
that you have trouble
reading kanji.
[UKINA]
Hm.
[KUZEN sighs]
Well, then I'll just
have to tutor you.
[KUZEN]
I shouldn't...
[UKINA]
You coming?
[YOSHIMURA] Kuzen had been
alone his entire life.
He'd never opened
his heart to anyone.
The young lady
caught him off guard,
and he became smitten
with her. But then...
[KUZEN grunts]
[UKINA gasps]
[KUZEN gasps]
[KUZEN grunts]
[KUZEN growls]
[KUZEN gasps]
Why'd you keep this
from me, Kuzen?
It doesn't change how I feel.
[gasps]
[YOSHIMURA]
She accepted him for who he was.
[clock chiming]
[gasps]
[UKINA]
You're telling me there could be
something wrong with the baby?
[KUZEN] Sorry, but unless
a miracle happens,
our child will be
born part ghoul.
It's going to need
nourishment, right?
[UKINA] Don't worry, my love.
A miracle will happen.
[YOSHIMURA]
She did the unthinkable
to nourish their unborn child.
[sobbing]
[YOSHIMURA]
When the child was born,
it was the happiest
day of their lives.
However, the new family's
happiness would be short-lived.
[KUZEN, UKINA panting]
[UKINA gasps]
[gasps] Ah!
[groans]
[KUZEN panting]
[KUZEN grunting]
Ukina, no!
--[UKINA grunts]
--[BABY coos]
[gasping]
[KUZEN grunts]
[KUZEN gasps]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[BABY coos]
[sobs]
[KUZEN grunting]
[YOSHIMURA] Kuzen went back
to the life he had known.
But he was haunted
by the memories
of the child he left behind.
[panting]
[YOSHIMURA]
Time passed and eventually,
a merciless ghoul made
its way onto the scene.
One who seemed to hate the
world and everyone in it.
[KANEKI]
The One-eyed Owl.
[YOSHIMURA]
Yes. My child.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[YOSHIMURA]
Snow, huh?
[YORIKO]
You're moving?
[TOUKA]
Yeah, I don't have any choice
'cause they're renovating
the whole building.
Geez.
You know you're more than
welcome to come and stay
with my family until
your place is ready.
I appreciate it,
but I've already
got it worked it out.
I'm gonna crash at
a relative's house.
Aw. You sure? I mean,
why would you stay there
when you could have home-cooked
meals by yours truly?
[laughs] I'll be fine.
[gasps] It's snowing.
Oh, how pretty!
Do you think it's gonna stick?
[TOUKA]
That's a good question.
[YORIKO giggles]
I sure hope it does! I love it.
[TOUKA]
Yeah. Me, too.
[KIMI] Oh, wow! Nishiki,
look! It's snowing!
[NISHIKI] Brr! No wonder
it's so damn cold.
Here, let me help warm you up.
I don't know why you insisted
on walking me to work,
it's freezing out.
I wanted to.
[NISHIKI] We don't have
much farther to go.
[KIMI] Good, I can't
wait to get back home
and bask in the
warmth of the heater.
[NISHIKI]
And the truth comes out.
You didn't have to do this.
[KIMI] I know, but it's
little moments like these
that count the most.
[NISHIKI]
I'll admit it has been nice.
[ROMA]
Oh, wow.
It's really starting
to come down now.
[HINAMI] You were smart to bring
an umbrella, just in case.
Damn it.
Why is this place so
busy all of a sudden?
Nishiki, why're you complaining?
Being busy's good, right?
Yeah, but he's lazy.
Listen, up.
We'll have to do the best
we can without Touka.
It'll be tough,
but we can manage.
Hinami, you man the counter
and I'll take care
of things out here.
'Kay.
Uh! What about me?
[NISHIKI]
Ugh.
Roma. Don't break any dishes!
[yelps]
Miss Irimi, we'd like to order
three Americanos, please.
No problem.
[MAN 8A]
Hey, Koma!
[KOMA]
Huh?
We're gonna need four blends,
on the double, okay?
Comin' right up!
[KOMA chuckles]
[IRIMI chuckles]
[HINAMI sighs]
[YORIKO] What do you wanna do
once you graduate from college?
Have you thought about it?
[TOUKA] Not really. I haven't
even made it in yet.
That's true. Okay, what if
I put it like this.
Have you decided what you
wanna be when you grow up?
I suppose I should
figure that out, huh?
I guess I've never really
given it much thought.
What about you?
A chef, of course!
Makes sense. You're the
best cook that I know.
[YORIKO giggles]
Why, thank you!
Enough about me,
what do you wanna do?
What, when I "grow up"?
[YORIKO]
Mm-hm!
I can't pick just one.
I mean, there's lots of
stuff that I'd like to try.
Oh, really? Like what? Tell me!
[TOUKA] Well, I wouldn't
mind being a teacher.
Or maybe running a coffee shop.
What? Wait, you mean
like Anteiku?
[TOUKA]
Mm-hm.
Oh, wow. You must
really love the stuff.
No, not really.
I just think
coffee shops are cool
'cause they bring
people together, y'know?
[YORIKO]
Mm-hm.
So, if I open one,
you'll always know
where to find me.
[YORIKO]
Yeah, of course I will,
because I'll be
working there with you.
[TOUKA]
Sounds good to me!
[door clicks]
[MARUDE] I read over your
report. Very interesting.
But do you have any
conclusive evidence?
Instinct?
That's great.
Last time I checked,
you're not Kureo.
[SHINOHARA chuckles]
I've got a nagging feeling
that most of our 20th Ward
investigators have been made.
So I've called in new recruits
and they're staking
out the place.
Leave it to you, Maru.
You sure work fast.
[MARUDE]
I don't have any choice.
[grunts] Man, this place
was packed all day;
I've never worked
so hard in my life.
[IRIMI] How're you holding up?
I know you must be tired.
[HINAMI] Nah, I'm wide awake!
I thought it was fun!
[NISHIKI]
Huh. Congratulations, Roma.
Huh?
This is the first time
you've made it through
your entire shift without
breaking any dishes.
[ROMA giggles]
Almost! I broke two!
Aw well, I say that's
still pretty good
considering how
ridiculously busy we were.
[ROMA] Whoa, did you just
give me a complement?
But you're never
this nice to me.
You're not trying to
flirt with me, are you?
Keep dreamin'!
Damn, I say one
nice thing to you
and it goes straight to that
big ol' head of yours!
I love when the shop's busy.
I don't know about you, Koma,
but it reminds me
of the good old days.
[KOMA]
Yeah, me too.
I was worried for a while there,
I thought we were gonna
have to call in
Anteiku's secret weapon.
I didn't know that
we had a secret weapon.
So, who is it?
[NISHIKI]
Mm?
You all know him.
[bell chimes]
Well, well, speak of the devil.
[NISHIKI]
He's our secret weapon?
You gotta be kiddin' me.
[TOUKA] No way. Does he
even make coffee?
[NISHIKI, HINAMI, TOUKA, ROMA]
Eh?!
Indeed, it's true.
Although it was a
very long time ago.
[TOUKA] Yomo doesn't
strike me as someone
who should work in
the service industry.
[NISHIKI]
You can say that again.
Believe it or not, he was
great at making coffee.
[KOMA]
Mm-hm.
But not so great with customers.
[ROMA, TOUKA, NISHIKI]
Ah...
Well, Touka? Have you
finished packing yet?
Oh, crap! I've still
got a little left to do.
Go finish up, we can
handle things down here.
[TOUKA] Thanks, I appreciate it.
Let's go, Hinami.
Coming!
[YOSHIMURA]
Is that right?
[YOMO]
'Fraid so.
What're you going to do?
I have some loose ends
that I need to tie up.
[YOMO sighs]
[YOSHIMURA]
Please, Yomo.
Promise me you'll
watch over the others.
[YOMO sighs]
I'll do my best, sir.
[HIDE]
Hey, what's up, Seido?
[gasps]
What's with all the
frenetic energy
in the office today?
Did somethin' happen?
Well, uh, I couldn't tell you.
They really haven't
told me anything.
Oh, yeah? Wonder why?
[SEIDO] Look, I'm sorry,
but I'm kind of in a hurry.
Whoa, check it out,
it's still coming down!
Yeah, looks like it
might stick, after all.
They're in your hands,
Yomo. Be careful.
Right.
[giggles]
[YOMO]
You ready?
Yeah.
I'll see you soon!
Let me know if you guys
need any help at the shop.
I'll help, too!
[bell chimes]
[SHINOHARA]
Oh, wow.
Looks like we're gonna get
some accumulation tonight.
Welcome back, sir.
Excuse me, would you mind
if I join you, Investigator?
Not at all.
[YOSHIMURA]
Here you are.
Thank you very much.
[YOSHIMURA]
No problem.
[SHINOHARA]
That's good.
I've had years of practice.
[SHINOHARA]
What makes one coffee
taste better than another?
Is it the quality of the beans?
[YOSHIMURA] Yes, that's
part of the equation,
but there are many
other factors involved.
Everything from the way
the beans are roasted,
to the water that's used for
brewing, can change its flavor.
[SHINOHARA]
Really?
[YOSHIMURA] I have my own
philosophy about it.
I've worked here a long time,
and I've noticed.
It's not the quality of
the bean that matters,
but rather, how you
approach them.
I don't follow.
Let me explain.
You have to approach each and
every coffee bean differently.
No matter how
expensive they may be,
carelessly brewed beans will
make a horrible cup of coffee.
[SHINOHARA grunts]
[YOSHIMURA]
The opposite is also true.
Even the cheapest beans
can become flavorful,
as long as they're
brewed with care.
It takes some work, but you can
bring out the best in them.
I see. That was profound.
[YOSHIMURA]
Not at all.
[SHINOHARA]
Delicious, as always.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
This one's on the
house, Investigator.
Thank you, but I
don't mind paying.
Very well. Then if
you insist, sir.
[SHINOHARA]
Good night. Thanks again.
[ETO]
Look at all this snow.
I'm starting to get excited.
[knocking]
It took us a while, but the
shop is spic and span, Boss.
And we also got rid
of all the documents
while we were at it.
Good. Thank you.
[KOMA chuckles]
[IRIMI chuckles]
There you go. Now, drink up.
I've been looking
forward to this.
[IRIMI]
Me, too. Thank you.
It won't be the
same without them.
Like it or not,
you're stuck with us
until the bitter end.
I hope it's the former
and not the latter.
[YOSHIMURA]
Ukina.
It's unfortunate, but in the
end, my wish did not come true.
[YOSHITOKI] We're prepared
to implement our mission
to exterminate the Owl.
Pending your approval,
of course.
[TSUNEYOSHI] If I may ask,
what is the target location?
Certainly.
Our first target
is a coffee shop
in the 20th Ward
called "Anteiku."