[IBA groaning]
Medic! Get over here!
[MADO]
Iba!
[SHINOHARA gasps]
[IBA groans] Forget about me!
I'm of no use anymore.
Just leave me here.
We can't do that!
[IBA] Mado! It's up
to you! Avenge Kasuka!
[whimpering]
[MADO grunts]
I'm with you. Let's get 'im.
Shinohara...
[ARIMA]
I'll need to borrow this.
Arima.
[OWL growls]
I don't suppose anyone's
heard from Arima?
I'm just wondering whether
he'll bother to show up.
Hm... Well, he better show!
It's not every day
the chief calls us in
for a meeting like this.
Do you think he gives a shit?
He's never been the
type to follow protocol.
I'd be surprised if he makes it.
Shinohara just got
out of the hospital.
If he can make it, so can Arima.
Luckily, Kuroiwa and I
can take a licking.
We're just glad
we could make it.
[grunts]
Sorry, Chief, but I'm afraid
Arima isn't here yet.
We'll start without him.
I now call this
meeting to order.
[ALL but YOSHITOKI]
Yes, sir.
[YOSHITOKI]
In addition to the 11th,
Aogiri has now seized control
of the 9th and 10th wards.
Unfortunately, the standoff
in the 11th Ward
left our forces so weak we
simply didn't have the manpower
to hold them at bay.
Mm... Boy.
You should've called on me,
Marude, old buddy.
I would've kicked those punks
outta there in no time.
Yeah, right. You're
nothin' but talk, Mogan.
[YOSHITOKI] According to
reports, the Aogiri team
who took control of the 9th
and 10th wards was led
by a ghoul wearing a
mask with an eye patch.
We have reason to
believe this ghoul
is somehow involved
with the murder
of Investigator Mado
in the 20th Ward.
Let me ask you this, Chief:
Do you think Aogiri could
have a base there, too?
And I'd like for you
to look into that
when you go back, Shinohara.
You can count on me, sir.
[NISHIKI] Aw man, this sucks!
My back is killin' me!
Whaddya say we take
a quick fiver, you guys?
You're far too young to
be asking for a break.
Yeah, quit bein' so lazy.
Y'know, you could learn
a thing or two from Hinami.
Hey, Koma. Think this'll
look good by the door?
Yeah! Good thinkin'.
[HINAMI]
Want some help with that, Irimi?
[IRIMI]
That'd be great!
If you'll wash this one,
I can move onto the next.
[HINAMI]
Sure thing!
[clears throat] Listen, Hinami.
I dunno about you,
but I could use a break.
[HINAMI] Me, too. But I'm
so close to finishing this.
Yeah, but I just wanna
take a little break,
and if you were to side with me,
they'd probably give in.
Pretty please with sugar on top?
[NISHIKI grunts]
Hetare! Hetare! Hetare!
[NISHIKI] Where the hell did you
come from, ya crap-a-tiel?
[HETARE]
Hetare! Hetare!
Ah! You really did crap on me!
That's right,
you better fly away!
--If I get my hands on you...
--Be careful, Nishiki.
Or the 'lil guy might
crap on your head.
Uh-- Speaking of
Touka, where is she?
She said she was going
to school to study.
Something about entrance exams?
So she decided, huh?
You happen to know
which school she picked?
Yeah. Kamii.
She chose my school?
There's no way she's gonna
make it through those exams.
I barely passed,
and I'm smarter than her.
She's made up her mind,
that's where she wants to go.
Maybe she could pass
if you help her study.
Yeah, yeah, I suppose I could
help her out a little bit.
But still. Why'd she
choose Kamii?
Uh-- You don't think...
With everything that's
happened lately,
I'm sure Touka could
use the distraction.
[YORIKO] Oh, wow!
The coffee shop's reopening?
That's great to hear!
Are you excited
to get back to work?
Yeah, but I need to study,
so I'll have to cut back
my hours a little.
Just promise me that
you'll be careful.
The criminals who robbed you
are still out there somewhere.
I don't wanna scare you,
but they could strike
the shop again anytime.
Yeah, right! I'd like
to see 'em try.
If they do, I'll give
'em summa 'dis!
There you go, trying to
be the tough chick
you know you're not.
[TOUKA]
I'm just kidding!
Hey. Tell you what.
If you get robbed again,
call me and I'll help you fight.
I'm totally joking!
I could barely say that
with a straight face.
[BOY 2A]
"Evacuation drills"?
[BOY 2B]
I heard the 9th and 10th Wards
have been taken over by ghouls.
[BOY 2C] What? Are you
serious? Talk about scary.
[GIRL 2A]
Do you think they're, like,
trying to eat their
way through the wards?
[BOY 2D] I don't get why ghouls
even exist in the first place.
[GIRL 2B]
No joke, they should just die.
Thanks, you idiot.
[YOSHITOKI] If I was a
betting man, I'd put money
on Aogiri's next target being
either the 3rd or 13th Ward.
If that's the case, do you
think they're planning
to take over the city by
moving in from the west?
I know it's just
speculation at this point,
but I'm requesting
reinforcements from each ward.
Excuse me, Chief,
but does that include
the 23rd Ward?
Yes, Cochlea is no exception.
[MISAKA] Mm. Well,
if you think that's best.
We don't have any choice.
We're going to need all the help
we can get in this situation.
We're facing a formidable foe.
And we have to be ready
to fight back.
I refuse to have a repeat
of what happened last time.
Our top priority
is to wipe out
both the Owl and Aogiri Tree.
[SHINOHARA] Did I think
the Owl looked smaller?
Yeah.
Maybe. Guess I didn't
really notice.
But it's been a while
since we've seen him.
Well, I could be wrong.
I dunno, it just felt like
something had changed.
[SHINOHARA] In what way?
What makes you say that?
I can't quite put
my finger on it.
I just remembered him as being
more imposing, and more vicious.
A lot of investigators died
during the first
Owl extermination.
You're right. This confrontation
was very different. There were
injuries; however, no deaths.
Eh, who knows?
Maybe the Owl's shrinking
in his old age.
Did his attacks feel like
an old man's to you?
Ha, ha. Not at all.
Shinohara.
I've got a theory I'd
like to run past you.
[elevator dings]
Listen, Iwa.
I think it's best if we
keep this between us.
[KUROIWA grunts]
Things are chaotic enough
as it is right now.
[HIDE]
Investigator Shinohara!
You've got mail.
Hey! You here on business?
Yes, sir! Mr. Seido needed
a gofer, so here I am.
Ha, ha! Well, tell him thanks.
Will do! Have a good day, sir!
Lemme guess, a new part-timer?
Yeah. From the 20th Ward.
He's got a good work ethic,
for someone his age.
--[LADY 2A] Bye, now!
--[HIDE] Take care, ladies.
[KANEKI grunts]
[DETECTIVE 2A whimpering]
--[DETECTIVE 2A gasps]
--[door slams]
[AYATO] You gonna stand
there all day, or what?
C'mon, let's go.
[gasps, pants]
[JUZO giggling]
That'll do it. All done!
Do you have any idea
how gross that is?
What's gross about it?
You're giving yourself
stitches for no good reason!
You're supposed to be
an investigator,
try to act like one for once!
Wow, you're so annoying.
How 'bout I sew up
that mouth of yours
so you'll stop
running it, Seido?
[SEIDO gasps] Step off, Juzo!
What, you think you're tough
now that you've been promoted?
I'm the boss! You hear me?
We might both be investigators,
but we're not equals!
[sighs] I see you're at
each other's throats again.
Play nice, boys.
Mr. Shinohara!
[JUZO] Good to see you
again, sir! Welcome back!
Thanks.
I'm surprised they
released you already.
I'm pretty tough, kid.
Takes more than that
to keep me down.
[HOJI]
The indomitable Shinohara.
You just couldn't stay away.
You know it, Hoji.
Heard you covered for me
while I was out. Thanks a lot.
No problem.
[SHINOHARA] Where's Amon?
I thought he'd be here.
He said that he'll be in
after he visits Mr. Mado.
Oh, I see.
Well, I guess I'll have to wait
to break the news to him.
I don't know how he's gonna
react to getting a new partner.
Progress report.
The binge eater's
still in hiding.
But I've got some solid
leads on the gourmet.
At this point,
I'm still investigating
the Rabbit and possible
ties to the eye patch.
One more thing.
I've been promoted, Mr. Mado.
I'm now a senior investigator.
[AKIRA]
Hey.
You certainly visit
my father a lot.
Eh, Kotaro Amon?
Who are you?
You don't know?
I guess you haven't
heard the news yet.
As of today, you have
a new partner.
That'd be me, Akira Mado.
Mado?
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Senior Investigator Amon.
Hello, I'm Akira Mado,
Investigator 2nd Class.
I look forward to working
with you gentlemen.
Please bear with me
as I get adjusted.
[SHINOHARA]
Don't worry, your partner'll
show you the ropes.
Right, Amon?
Yes, sir!
Why'd she have to be
assigned to my branch?
Hello, Takizawa.
It's nice to see you, too.
You two know each other?
Yeah, we went to
the Academy together.
[SHINOHARA]
They were in the same class.
Akira always ranked at
the top. Seido was second.
I see.
Hiya! My name's Juzo Suzuya!
Nice to meet ya, Miss Mado.
Wow, your stitches look so cool.
Put 'er there.
We're gonna get along.
[giggles]
[SEIDO]
Hmph!
During our special
investigators' meeting
at CCG headquarters,
we determined
that we need to
concentrate our efforts
on eliminating the
Owl and Aogiri.
One of their members,
codenamed "Eye patch,"
was first spotted here
in the 20th Ward.
We suspect he might be
one of Aogiri's captains.
If that's true, then it's highly
likely that the organization
has a base somewhere
in this ward.
Hey!
If this Eye patch guy
is a captain with Aogiri,
isn't it possible they've got
other members in this ward, too?
Like maybe the binge
eater and the gourmet?
No, they're not affiliated.
[grunts] And how
would you know that?
Don't tell me it's your
"intuition" again, Investigator?
Sure, you can call it that
if it makes you feel
better about yourself.
Let me explain.
I came across a number
of interesting facts
while scanning the 20th Ward's
predatory attack data.
Let's take a look at the
binge eater, for instance.
There haven't been
any signs of predation
in the last six months.
Therefore, it's fairly
obvious that--
They've moved onto
another ward, right?
[AKIRA]
Wrong.
[grunts]
I believe she's
probably deceased.
[SEIDO grunts]
Okay, sure.
That's one possibility, but,
hang on, what do you mean "she"?
[AKIRA] Well, seeing as all of
the victims were young men,
it's safe to assume the
binge eater is female.
[SEIDO grunts]
[AKIRA] While looking over the
data for the last three years,
I noticed that there's
a distinct point
where incidents of predation
start to decline dramatically.
Yeah, that's when our
senior investigators
marched in and kicked ass.
Please refrain from talking
until I'm finished, Takizawa.
I looked through the
CCG's data as well,
and there are no records
of increased personnel
in the ward at that time.
Now the 20th Ward is no stranger
to ghoul organizations,
the Black Dobers and En were
quite powerful in the past.
However, neither has
been seen or heard from
in over ten years.
These days, the number
of predatory incidents
have remained fairly low.
That is, until the
binge eater showed up.
Would you just get
to the point already?
The ghouls in the 20th
Ward are being regulated
by some sort of organization.
And the binge eater
broke the rules.
She committed so many
predatory attacks,
she began attracting
investigators.
Fearing they'd be discovered,
they dealt with her.
Wait, are you insinuating
the binge eater
was killed by this organization?
That's right.
[SEIDO] And you believe that
organization is Aogiri?
No, I never said that.
However, based on the facts, I'd
say it's a definite possibility.
How come you didn't
mention anything
about the gourmet, huh?
You need to calm down, Takizawa.
There's no reason to get upset.
[SEIDO grunts]
[SHINOHARA]
Hm...
A ghoul organization
regulating the ward.
Brilliant investigative
work, Akira, thank you.
As we move forward,
let's assume
this organization has ties to
Aogiri. I think she's spot on.
Wow, you did all that research
in such a short amount
of time? Nice job.
Don't complement her, Hoji!
Can't you see her ego
is big enough as it is?
Hey, Akira.
I realize that Takizawa's
not your favorite person,
but try to get along with him.
'Kay. No prob.
[clears throat]
Not to pull rank,
but I am technically
your superior.
Please speak to me with
more respect from now on.
I'm not fond of wastefulness
in any capacity.
Being polite is a waste
of both time and energy.
[gasps]
[AKIRA] As partners, we're
going to spend a lot of time
talking to each other.
It takes point nine seconds to
say "if you would be so kind,"
as opposed to "would ya,"
which only takes
point three seconds.
That's a whopping difference
of point six seconds.
Let's say I ask you for
something ten times a day,
using "would ya" will save me
as many as 2,000 seconds
over the course of a year.
Now, I don't know how
good you are with math,
but that's the equivalent
of about 33 minutes.
It might not sound like much
to you, but I can accomplish
an awful lot in that
amount of time. So please.
Let's not concern ourselves
with trivialities.
Our priority should be
the investigation,
Investigator Amon.
Well, she is Mado's daughter.
That being the case, I can't
really say I'm surprised.
I don't know if we're
going to get along, sir.
[SHINOHARA]
Here's a thought, why don't you
invite her to dinner? Once
you've both had a few drinks
it'll be easier to
talk things out.
Give it a try, you'll see.
I know it's not easy,
adjusting to a new partner,
Amon, but I've got faith in you.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Dinner, huh?
I'll try it!
[AMON]
Akira!
[AKIRA]
Yeah, what?
How would you like
to go to dinner
after we've finished
our reports?
Mine should only take me
about ten minutes or so.
Thanks, but no thanks.
[AMON]
Huh?
I'm sorry, but I make it a rule
not to eat anything
after nine pm.
Thanks for the invite, though.
And I've already finished
my report, it's on your desk.
Hey. You all right, Amon?
[AMON] Yes, sir.
Everything's just fine.
You sure?
[TOUKA grunts]
[YORIKO]
Hey, you walking home with me?
[TOUKA] Of course,
it's the least I can do
after keeping you out so late.
[YORIKO]
It's no biggie.
Seriously, you can
call me anytime,
I'm more than happy
to study with you.
Thanks, you're the best. 'Kay!
I've gotta work super hard
to make up for lost time.
[YORIKO] Why are you so
gung-ho about studying
all of a sudden?
Uh. Well, because...
Did you choose a college?
So which one?
I'm thinkin' maybe Kamii?
[YORIKO gasps]
You gotta be kidding!
You're gonna ditch me
for the brainiacs?
There's no way I could
ever get in there!
Why'd you pick that school?
[TOUKA]
Whoa, chill out!
[gasps] Huh...
Think you're a
sly one, don't'cha?
Hm?
[gasps]
[YORIKO] Hmph! I don't
blame you. It's cool.
Go with your boyfriend!
[TOUKA]
Don't be stupid!
I told you, he's
not my boyfriend!
[YORIKO giggles] There's no
need to get defensive!
[TOUKA] You've got the wrong
idea, Yoriko! No, it's not!
[YORIKO]
Bye-bye!
[AYATO]
Let's go, Eye patch.
[ETO]
Ah!
[giggles]
[inaudible]
Ken Kaneki. Huh.