[CCG TROOPERS screaming]
[OWL roars]
[JUZO gasps]
[SHINOHARA grunts]
[roars]
[gasps]
[JUZO whimpers]
[SHINOHARA grunts]
Shinohara...
[SHINOHARA sputters]
[OWL growls]
[JUZO gasping]
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO pants]
[growls]
[gasps]
[SHINOHARA]
That's true.
But if you happened
to die before me,
I would be sad.
[JUZO]
Shinohara.
[yelps]
[growls]
[gasps]
--[thud]
--[JUZO gasps]
[growls]
[gasping]
[screams]
[CCG TROOPER 11A gasps]
[CCG TROOPER 11B]
Huh?
[CCG TROOPERS scream]
[NAKI laughing]
[CCG TROOPERS groan]
[TATARA]
Let's get to work, Noro.
[KANEKI]
I'll only ask once. Let me pass.
Sorry. Can't do that.
--[AKIRA grunts]
--[AOGIRI 11A groans]
[AOGIRI 11B groans]
How many more of these
bastards are left?
It doesn't matter!
We cannot let them pass!
Yeah, no shit!
[MARUDE]
Holy hell.
All this time...
...there were two
of them out there?
[growls]
[JUZO grunts]
That tickles.
[JUZO grunting]
--[JUZO groans]
--[OWL growls]
[JUZO groans]
[OWL cackles]
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO yells]
[OWL grunts]
[JUZO grunting]
[JUZO yells]
[laughs]
Second and Third Divisions
are falling back.
We've got a problem!
I've lost contact with
the Fourth Division!
[grunts, pants]
[YOSHITOKI]
Investigator Mado.
Yes, sir?
[YOSHITOKI]
Division Four needs back up.
[AKIRA] But they'll break
through if we leave!
[YOSHITOKI]
That's an order. Now go.
Copy that.
[AMON grunting]
[AMON grunts]
This whole world has
gone straight to hell.
And it's your kind, the
ghouls, who sent it there!
[grunts]
[AMON yells]
[KANEKI grunts]
[AMON growls]
[AMON grunts]
[panting]
[KANEKI] Because when it comes
to the state of the world,
you can't point your finger
at ghouls or humans.
We're all to blame.
[KANEKI grunts]
Whoa. I thought
we were done for.
[AMON]
He saved them.
[sighs]
[AMON]
Just what is he up to?
[AMON] All this violence.
Is there any reason for it?
[KANEKI] If I had a choice,
I would choose not to fight you.
But I don't.
[AMON grunts]
[AMON groans]
[gasps]
[AOGIRI 11C groans]
Mado! Get your head
out of the clouds!
[AKIRA grunts]
My mistake.
[SEIDO] I'll take care of
things here, you get going.
Amon and the 4th
Division need your help.
But, Seido--
[SEIDO]
Shut up and go!
The chief ordered you
to assist them, didn't he?
[AKIRA grunts]
[grunts]
[AKIRA]
Let's go!
[AMON grunts]
[AMON pants]
Don't mistake me
for your Dojima girl.
I'm not her; I'm me.
If you need me
to prove it, I can.
[sighs]
[AMON] After all the work you
did redesigning this for me.
It'd be a shame to let
it get destroyed here.
[grunts]
[gasping]
[gasping, whimpering]
[TATARA] You're Hoji's
subordinate, aren't you?
[pants]
[TATARA laughs]
[panting]
[screams]
[gags]
[TATARA] Tell me where
to find him, or else.
[gagging] You won't beat him!
Hoji will rip you apart
and send you back to hell!
[TATARA]
Is that right?
[gasps]
Seido... No.
[JUZO panting]
I can't stop.
[JUZO grunting]
[growls, chuckles]
[OWL laughs]
[yells]
[KANEKI grunts]
[KANEKI, AMON grunt]
[KANEKI pants]
[KANEKI screams]
I thought you were different
from other ghouls.
But you're just another
heartless killer, aren't you?
[KANEKI panting]
[KANEKI grunts]
[AMON grunts]
[AMON yells]
[AMON grunting]
[AMON grunts]
[KANEKI wretches]
[AMON grunts, groans]
[AMON growls]
[yells]
[panting]
[KANEKI sighs]
[KANEKI]
I meant it.
I wish we didn't have
to fight each other.
[AMON] Me, too, but this
is how it has to be.
So what's your name?
If you don't mind me asking.
Amon. Kotaro Amon.
[AMON sighs]
[AMON] If only we'd met under
different circumstances.
I would've liked to sit down
and discuss all this with you.
[AMON yells]
[KANEKI yells]
[AKIRA gasps]
[AOGIRI 11D yells]
[AKIRA grunts]
[gasps]
[AMON] When the foe
is before you, fight!
Even if it costs you your life!
Never give up.
That's the best advice
Mr. Mado gave me.
[AKIRA grunts]
[AMON] Sorry, Akira.
I went and broke it anyway.
[YOSHITOKI]
Has he arrived yet?
[JUZO groans]
Come on.
[OWL]
It's you!
[OWL roars]
[sighs]
[MOGAN]
Mm.... Well, boys. It looks like
we're in quite a pickle.
Copy that. We'll hold 'em off.
[sighs] Arima just arrived.
Can you believe it?
Who?
[grunts] We can't afford to let
these bastards show us up,
now can we, boys?
[roars]
[OWL roaring]
[OWL screams]
[OWL growling]
--[MOGAN grunts]
--[AOGIRI 11E groans]
[AOGIRI GHOULS groaning]
[FURA]
Hmph.
[HOGI grunts]
[KURAMATO grunts]
What's up?
[AOGIRI GHOULS whimper]
[AOGIRI GHOULS yelp]
What the hell happened?
We had 'em on the ropes!
[CCG TROOPERS yell]
[AOGIRI GHOULS
yelping, groaning]
I've been waiting for this.
[OWL growls]
[OWL cackles]
[ARIMA grunts]
[growls]
[OWL grunts, cackles]
[ARIMA pants]
[OWL shrieks, giggles]
[CCG TROOPERS scream]
[KANEKI gasping]
Have to hurry... to Anteiku.
[KANEKI]
Yoshimura...
[KANEKI gasping]
[KANEKI]
Touka...
[KANEKI gasping]
[KANEKI]
Hinami and everyone else...
[KANEKI grunts, groans]
[KANEKI]
I will protect you all...
I will...
[KANEKI]
Promise... I'll save you.
[TOUKA panting]
[panting]
You're never gonna
learn, are you?
[AKIRA panting]
[panting]
--[door clicks]
--[bell rings]
[door clicks]
[footsteps tapping]
[clinking]
[KANEKI inhales]
[KANEKI gasps]
[KANEKI grunts]
[KANEKI]
Anteiku...?
[footsteps tapping]
[HIDE]
Tell you what, making coffee's
a lot harder than it looks.
[rustling]
Hey. It's been awhile.
[OWL cackles]
[OWL] That investigator doesn't
show any mercy, does he?
[OWL cackles]
Ah! That feels much better!
Eto...?
[giggles] Why, hello... Father.