[TOUKA panting]
[panting]
[KOMA yells]
[TOUKA]
Koma...
[panting]
[IRIMI, HACHIKAWA grunting]
[TOUKA]
Irimi...
[TOUKA panting]
[YOSHIMURA grunts]
[panting] I'm coming!
[AKIRA] Shoot them,
before they get too close!
Fire!
[APE FACES panting]
[CCG TROOPERS groaning]
Now, Misato!
[APE FACE 10A yells, groans]
[yells]
C'mon, Seido!
Hurry and take
that bastard down!
I'm trying!
Easy for you to say,
you're just standing there!
[pants] I gotta keep fighting,
or I'll let everybody down.
[KUROIWA groans]
You all right, Iwa?
[grunts]
[YOSHIMURA groans]
[SHINOHARA]
Thanks, Hoji!
[HOJI]
No problem.
[SHINOHARA grunts]
[SHINOHARA] I'd say his fire
power's only a level five,
but his regeneration rate
is easily an eight.
He is, without a doubt,
the CCG's greatest foe.
[MOGAN]
Higher Mind!
[KOMA]
What's with this fool?
He's not gonna hit anyone if he
yells every time he attacks!
[MOGAN]
Hm.
[KOMA grunts, yells]
Compress!
[KOMA grunts]
[KOMA]
What the hell?
[MOGAN]
Diffuse!
[KOMA groans]
Aw, shit!
[MOGAN] You dodged it?
I thought I had you.
I'm shocked. It's never
failed me before.
[KOMA] You and your buddies
are serious, aren't ya?
You're out for blood.
Go on, try me.
The Devil Ape's not
giving up without a fight!
[CCG TROOPERS scream]
[HOGI grunts]
[HACHIKAWA]
You're finally going to pay
for what you've done!
[IRIMI grunts]
[HACHIKAWA] You're nothing
but a rotten, little mongrel.
[IRIMI] Now, now, that's no way
to speak to a lady, is it?
Mind your manners,
you filthy man-grel!
[MOGAN grunts]
[MOGAN groans]
[KOMA] Looks like you're
outta luck! Now die!
[grunts] No, you!
Rot in hell, you filthy ape!
[MOGAN] I'm fighting for the
lives of my fellow homo sapiens.
We'll never give way to a bunch
of ghoulish primates like you.
[KURAMOTO grunting]
[IRIMI grunts]
Whoa, she's fast.
Is that why she's
Double-S rated?
[IRIMI] You've got a face
only a mother could love.
And you are overcompensating
with that big sword of yours.
What?
[IRIMI gasps]
Keep it down!
What's all the racket?
[IRIMI gasps]
Wait. Are you a ghoul?
It's a civilian! Captain Hirako!
[HACHIKAWA]
I'll blow her and the hag away!
Hachikawa, no!
[IRIMI]
Damn it! Bad timing, Granny.
[IRIMI gasps]
[IRIMI] Look what's become
of me. I've gone soft.
[MOGAN]
You put on quite a show.
Well, I don't know about you,
but I think it's time
for the grand finale.
What have you done to my angel?
[IRIMI gasps]
[IRIMI] I wish... I'd had
a second cup of coffee.
[HOGI, KURAMOTO grunting]
[yells]
[HIRAKO grunts]
[HOGI grunts]
[IRIMI] Life is a struggle,
and I'm well aware
that I haven't always
made the best decisions.
But, in the end, whether
the choices I made
were right or wrong
doesn't matter.
What's most important is what
I've learned along the way.
I can't change the past,
but I've been given the chance
to make up for what I've done.
I'm no longer running
from my sins,
I'm facing them head-on.
I'm liberated.
Today I will lay down my life
for those I care about,
and for that,
I'm eternally grateful.
[MARUDE] Yoshitoki.
The 3rd Division is reporting
that they've defeated
the Black Dobers.
[HACHIKAWA]
You have no idea how long
I've waited for this day.
I've dreamed of putting
that vicious bitch down.
[HIRAKO]
You better watch it, Hachikawa.
[HACHIKAWA]
Why's that?
Protecting the lives of
civilians is our top priority.
What you did back there?
It was inexcusable.
[HACHIKAWA] Then we've got
our priorities mixed up.
As far as I'm concerned,
taking out Black Dog
is more important than
saving some old hag
who's already got one
foot in the grave.
Ten years.
That's how long I've
waited for revenge.
She killed my teacher,
my fellow investigators,
and changed my life forever.
So I think my
actions are justified,
don't you, Special
Investigator Hirako?
I'll make a fine
quinque out of you.
I'll see you in Hell.
What? There is no afterlife
for ghouls, bitch.
[HACHIKAWA groans]
[KURAMOTO, HOGI grunt]
[KANEKI]
You sure there's one for humans?
[UI yells]
[SHINOHARA]
Ui!
[UI grunting]
[KUROIWA grunts]
[SHINOHARA grunts]
[SHINOHARA]
That do it?
Incoming!
[KUROIWA, UI grunt]
[SHINOHARA] We're gonna
need more men, and fast.
Hey, Maru, where's Juzo?
[MARUDE]
He's heading your way.
[JUZO singing]
How do you do, Owl?
[HOGI, KURAMOTO grunt]
[HOGI groans]
[KURAMOTO groans]
[IRIMI]
Now I understand, Kaneki.
[IRIMI] You had no choice
but to join them.
It was the only way
you could get this strong.
[IRIMI]
I'm sorry we ever doubted you.
[IRIMI] You sacrificed
yourself for us. Thank you.
[JUZO grunts]
Yeah!
[gasps] Juzo!
Quit darting around!
[laughing]
[SHINOHARA] Coordinated
attacks have never been
his strong suit,
but he's got to focus,
especially against the Owl.
He can't keep swinging wildly--
[MADO] He seems to be doing
just fine, if you ask me.
Wha--? Mado?
[MADO] Calm down. You're
overthinking it, as usual.
This is war,
not some intricately
choreographed dance routine.
[MADO] It's erratic, volatile,
and the balance of power
can shift in the
blink of an eye.
When it comes down to it,
there's no way to predict
anyone's movements,
be they friend or foe.
Don't waste your time
trying to figure out
what the enemy's going to do,
pay attention to your partner.
Get to know their thought
processes, behavioral patterns.
And you'll learn to trust them.
Then you can let them roam free,
always keeping a
watchful eye, of course.
At least, that's
what worked for me
back when we were
partners, Shinohara.
Thank you.
Ya just had to get one
last jab in, didn't ya?
[JUZO grunting]
[JUZO panting]
[SHINOHARA]
Juzo!
Huh?
[SHINOHARA]
Go get him, kid.
[gasps]
[IRIMI]
What'll we do with you?
We had the perfect plan, but now
thanks to you, it's ruined.
Aw, c'mon.
Don't be so hard on him.
I mean, he did rescue us.
[KOMA] Hey, Kaneki,
you're going back, right?
[IRIMI chuckles]
[KOMA chuckles]
[YOSHIMURA grunting]
[JUZO yells]
[YOSHIMURA grunts]
[SHINOHARA grunts]
[UI gasps]
Incredible.
I've never seen them use
a joint attack before.
It's pretty impressive.
[KUROIWA]
Mm-hm.
Here they come!
[SHINOHARA]
If only we had one more man,
we could clinch this.
[SHINOHARA] Where's Hirako?
Or better yet Mogan?
[UI] They're dealing
with the Eyepatch, sir.
[YOSHIMURA]
Hm?
[SHINOHARA]
How're they doing?
[UI] They're fine for now, but
their quinques were destroyed.
Don't let him get away!
I've never made coffee before.
I have to learn by experiencing
things for myself.
That's all I can do.
[YOSHIMURA pants]
[YOSHIMURA]
Kaneki.
[YOSHIMURA groans]
Silly Owl, you can't
run from me!
[CCG TROOPER 10F screams]
[CCG TROOPERS groan]
Bad news.
The 2nd and 3rd Divisions'
forces have been wiped out.
It was the Eyepatch, sir.
Send the 4th Division after him.
[CCG TROOPER 10G] Hurry!
Our target is the Eyepatch!
[CCG TROOPERS]
Right!
[TOUKA]
Kaneki's here?
[CCG TROOPER 10H]
This way, men! Let's go!
[JUZO grunts]
[SHINOHARA]
Juzo!
[JUZO] Don't worry, I'm fine!
Just throw me back in!
[SHINOHARA yells]
[giggles]
[YOSHIMURA grunts]
[YOSHIMURA groans]
[KUROIWA, SHINOHARA yelling]
[yells]
[YOSHIMURA groans]
I've always wanted to help.
It's time that I did.
[UI grunts]
[YOSHIMURA groans]
[TOUKA]
Go to school? I don't know.
I'm a ghoul, so why should I?
[SHINOHARA]
Charge him, Iwa!
On it!
[KUROIWA grunts]
[YOSHIMURA groans]
[YOMO sighs]
I'm sorry. I'm just not
cut out to work here.
Hoji!
[HOJI yells]
[YOSHIMURA groans]
You tryin' to start
something with me?
Y'know, I'm the Devil Ape!
[YOSHIMURA groans]
[yells]
Don't talk to me like
you know me, Gramps.
I'll kill you.
[yells]
[YOSHIMURA yells]
[JUZO yells]
[YOSHIMURA groans]
[yells]
[YOSHIMURA groaning]
[YOSHIMURA yelps, groans]
Ukina...
[SHINOHARA]
Shinohara reporting.
[MARUDE]
And?
We finally did it, Kureo.
Rest in peace, old friend.
Now, if you would.
Let's make it official.
Owl extermination complete.
[CCG TROOPERS cheer]
[cheers]
[MOGAN sighs]
[sighs]
[YOSHIMURA] You are both
human and ghoul, Kaneki.
Therefore, you are
the one and only person
who has a place in both worlds.
The way you've
handled everything:
I believe you have
the power to unite us.
Not only that,
but to save someone
who's all alone.
And perhaps, someday,
to save my own child.
[AMON]
This is Amon, 4th Division.
I've encountered the Eyepatch.
Carrying out my mission.
Roger that. Keep us
updated then. Be careful.
[gasps]
[ALL yell]
[SHINOHARA, KUROIWA gasp]
[OWL roars]
Two of 'em?
I knew it!
[SHINOHARA growls]
[roars]
[SHINOHARA]
It's only got one eye!
[OWL growls]
[growls]