- Raul: SO HOW DOES HE SEEM?
- Kristeva:
CITIZEN REGISTRATION #021723,
FORMER CHIEF OF THE HEALTH
AND WELFARE BUREAU,
DAEDALUS YUMENO.
HE'S BEEN STRIPPED
OF HIS AUTHORITY
BY THE ADMINISTRATIVE BUREAU.
HE'S BEEN A QUIET INDIVIDUAL
AND HAS KEPT A LOW PROFILE
SINCE BEING REPLACED.
- DO YOU KNOW THE REASON WHY,
KRISTEVA?
- YOU SEEM TO BE
IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY.
- OH, DO I?
PERHAPS.
BUT I'M ACCEPTING
WHO I AM
AND LOOKING FORWARD
TO REACHING HEIGHTS
WHERE OTHER PEOPLE
ARE NO LONGER NECESSARY.
I'M NOT WORRIED
ABOUT MONSTERS ANYMORE.
HOWEVER, THAT MAN
IS DIFFERENT.
THE REGENT'S
LOVELY GRANDDAUGHTER,
RE-L MAYER HAS DIED,
ALONG WITH A PROXY
NAMED MONAD,
WHICH SHE WAS ALSO HIDING.
THAT MAN
HAS LOST HIS RAISON D'ETRE.
- YOU MEAN HIS REASON
FOR BEING?
- LOOK AT THIS BEAUTIFUL WORLD
IN WHICH EVERYTHING
HAS ITS PURPOSE.
AND WE ARE ALL CREATED
AS INDIVIDUAL COGS
FOR THE BETTERMENT
OF THIS PARADISE,
PERMITTED TO EXIST
ONLY FOR THE SAKE
OF FULFILLING REASONS
THAT ARE GIVEN IN ADVANCE.
BUT FOR DAEDALUS YUMENO,
ALL AT ONCE, HE HAS LOST
HIS OWN RAISON D'ETRE.
BOTH THE PROXY
AND RE-L MAYER.
- ( computer scanning )
- YOU MIGHT SAY
HE'S A BROKEN COG.
Ergo:
RE-L.
- ( rock music playing )
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD
UNWINDS INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- Male voice: AN ENTITY
SEALED FOR ETERNITY
AND SAID TO BE IMMORTAL
HAS BEEN LOST.
- Female voice:
DO YOU KNOW THE REASON WHY?
- THIS AWAKENING
HAS INVITED DESTRUCTION
AND THE BLOOD CONTINUES
TO FLOW IN OUR PARADISE.
- Female voice #2:
DO YOU KNOW THE REASON WHY?
- Kristeva: WE'VE ALREADY
SUBMITTED OUR REPORT,
BUT THE PROBLEMS
WE MUST ADDRESS ARE MOUNTING.
POWER SHORTAGES FOR THE MAGNETIC
AND FIELD LIFE-SUPPORT SYSTEM
IN THE DOME'S OUTER BLOCK
ARE A SOURCE OF CONCERN.
THE ENTIRE SYSTEM NEEDS
TO BE OVERHAULED IMMEDIATELY.
- Female voice: THAT IS THE
ANSWER TO WHICH YOU'VE ARRIVED?
- Female voice #2: QUESTIONS
ARE A BURDEN UPON OTHERS.
ANSWERS ARE A BURDEN
UPON YOURSELF.
- Male voice: UNDERSTAND THAT
WHAT HAPPENED TO RE-L MAYER
COULD VERY WELL
HAVE HAPPENED TO YOU.
Male voice #2:
YOU KNOW THE REASON,
DON'T YOU, RAUL?
- ( choir chanting )
- Female voice: THAT'S ENOUGH.
WE MUST THINK
OF WHAT TO DO
NOW THAT THE PROXY
IS GONE.
- Male voice:
WE UNDERSTAND TOO LITTLE.
- Female voice:
THEREFORE WE MUST THINK.
- Male voice: THEREFORE
WE MUST THINK.
- Female voice: WE MUST THINK.
- Female voice #2:
WE MUST THINK.
- Male voice: WE MUST THINK.
- ( grunting )
- ( glass smashing )
- GODDAMN ENTOURAGES.
"I THINK THEREFORE I AM."
- CHIEF,
YOU'VE INJURED YOURSELF.
- THE WOUND YOU SEE
IS NOTHING.
- JUST TO BE SAFE,
YOU SHOULD BE EXAMINED
BY THE HEALTH
AND WELFARE BUREAU.
- THE REGENT NEVER ANSWERS
DIRECTLY.
HE MERELY POSES QUESTIONS.
WHY IS THAT?
- IT'S HARD TO KNOW WHY.
- BUT I KNOW WHY.
IT'S THE WAILING OF SOMEONE
WHO SUDDENLY LOST THE PERSON
THEY LOVED THE MOST.
AND YET,
WHY DOES THE REGENT LOOK AWAY?
WHY?
WHY?!
IN REALITY,
ROMDEAU IS NOTHING BUT A--
- ( ship clanging )
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
- EMERGENCY STOP CODE,
ACKNOWLEDGED.
EMERGENCY USE PHASE,
SEQUENCE START.
CONFIRMED.
- POWER WAS AUTOMATICALLY
RESTORED
AFTER THE TWO-MINUTE-
AND-17-SECOND INTERRUPTION.
WE STILL HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO PINPOINT THE CAUSE.
BUT THIS TIME, THE POWER FAILURE
DID NOT INTERFERE
WITH THE LIFE-SUPPORT SYSTEM.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"THIS TIME"?
- FOR THE PAST THREE WEEKS,
WE'VE BEEN ENCOUNTERING
POWER FAILURES
SIMILAR IN NATURE TO THIS ONE.
- DID WE EVER RECEIVE A REPORT
ABOUT THESE FAILURES?
- NO.
- THEY WERE ALL INTERMITTENT
AND NONE OF THEM LASTED MORE
THAN A FRACTION OF A SECOND.
SO YOU SEE,
THEY WERE TREATED AS ACCIDENTS.
- AN ANALYSIS INDICATED THERE
WAS POSSIBLE HUMAN INVOLVEMENT.
THE REPORT DID NOT PRESENT
ANYTHING SPECIFIC.
- MAYBE AN INFECTED AUTO REIV?
DOUBTFUL.
BUT AN IMMIGRANT
TERRORIST GROUP?
THAT WOULD
MAKE MORE SENSE.
HMM.
TWO MINUTES, 17 SECONDS?
KRISTEVA?
- YES?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- JUDGING FROM THE TIME
ON THE EFFECT,
IT CAN BE SURMISED THAT THE
POWER STOPPAGES UP UNTIL NOW
WERE CARRIED OUT IN ORDER
TO DECEIVE THE SECURITY BUREAU.
THEY WERE TESTS
CONDUCTED FOR THAT PURPOSE.
- BEAUTIFUL.
AND THIS TIME?
- IT IS FAIR TO ASSUME THAT
IT WAS SOME TYPE OF WARNING.
- I SEE.
AND WHY IS THAT?
- THE CITY'S LIFE-SUPPORT SYSTEM
CAN ONLY BE MAINTAINED
FOR UP TO THREE MINUTES
DURING A POWER OUTAGE.
- WHICH MEANS
THAT WHOEVER WAS RESPONSIBLE
DIDN'T WANT ANYONE TO DIE.
- YES, SIR.
- YOU WERE RIGHT.
I REALLY SHOULD
GO SEE A DOCTOR.
MAKE AN APPOINTMENT
WITH THIS ONE.
BUT, CHIEF,
HE IS NO LONGER AUTHORIZED.
- THERE IS SOMETHING ELSE
THAT I WANT YOU TO DO.
I WANT YOU TO LOOK FOR THE
RESEARCH DATA HE WAS HIDING.
- I'M NO LONGER
CONDUCTING EXAMINATIONS...
ANYMORE.
- FOR SOMEONE WHO LOOKS
LIKE A YOUNG BOY,
YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE A VERY BOLD MAN.
- I'D LIKE TO ASK
FOR YOU TO LEAVE.
- SORRY.  SHOULD I HAVE SAID
A ROMANTICIST?
- I'LL HAVE DELEUZE
MAKE ARRANGEMENTS
FOR YOU TO SEE
ANOTHER DOCTOR.
- NOW THEN, WHAT IS IT
YOU WANT TO SAY TO ME?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
- GOING THROUGH ALL THAT TROUBLE
TO CALL ME HERE.
- I'M SORRY FOR ALL THE TROUBLE,
CHIEF RAUL.
BUT HONESTLY,
I HAVE NOTHING
TO SAY TO YOU ANYMORE.
I WAS CREATED IN ORDER
TO PROTECT THE SPECIMEN
AND RE-L,
TO RAISE THEM IN GOOD HEALTH.
BUT NOW
THAT I'VE LOST BOTH OF THEM,
IT SEEMS I'VE LOST
MY RAISON D'ETRE.
- AND SHORTLY AFTER THAT
IS WHEN I HEARD
YOUR HEARTFELT CRY.
SO I CAME OVER TO OFFER
WHAT LITTLE HELP I COULD.
- THEN YOU MUST
BE A TELEPATH.
- ( laughs )
AS STRANGE AS IT SOUNDS,
FOR SOME REASON IT ONLY SEEMS TO
WORK WITH YOU, DAEDALUS YUMENO.
AMUSING, ISN'T IT?
IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S AGREED
TO GIVE ME MY MEDICAL EXAM.
DURING WHICH TIME,
I WANT YOU TO HURRY UP
AND SEARCH FOR THE DATA
I INSTRUCTED YOU ABOUT EARLIER.
- Kristeva:
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I BELIEVE HE COULD USE
A BREATH OF FRESH AIR.
NO CAUSE FOR ALARM.
- CHIEF, HE IS STILL NOT
PERMITTED TO LEAVE THE PREMISES.
- I BELIEVE THAT IS UP TO ME
TO DECIDE,
IS IT NOT?
- YES, CERTAINLY.
- WHY ARE YOU BEING SO MEAN?
THERE ISN'T ANY DATA HERE.
- BUT SHE'LL KEEP SEARCHING
UNTIL SHE FINDS SOMETHING.
SHE'S VERY PROFESSIONAL.
- SO NOW WE HAVE PLENTY OF TIME
FOR OURSELVES.
IT'S OKAY.
THE REPRESENTATIVE DOESN'T HAVE
ANY CONNECTION TO THEM.
- REPRESENTATIVE?
( laughs )
YOU MEAN THE REGENT?
IMPRESSIVE.
YOU DON'T LEAVE ANYTHING
TO CHANCE.
- THAT'S WHY YOU INSISTED
ON HAVING AN UNEMPLOYED DOCTOR
GIVE YOU A MEDICAL EXAM,
AM I RIGHT?
YOU IMPRESS ME. YOU FIGURED
IT OUT QUICKER THAN I THOUGHT.
- YOU'VE BEEN HAVING
TOO MUCH FUN.
- AND YOU SCARE
FAR TOO EASILY.
I'M WELL AWARE OF WHAT
THE LIFE-SUPPORT SYSTEM'S
LIMITATIONS ARE.
- THE REGENT SEEMS
TO HAVE TAKEN THE DISRUPTION
AS A WARNING FROM SOMEONE.
- YOU DID A VERY GOOD JOB
OF MISLEADING HIM.
ALL THAT'S LEFT
IS FOR THE SECURITY BUREAU
TO MAKE THE APPROPRIATE ARRESTS
WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT.
- DAEDALUS YUMENO,
CITIZEN #021723.
- TWO MINUTES, 17.23 SECONDS.
I TESTED IT MANY TIMES
TO GET IT RIGHT.
- I SUPPOSE
THAT YOU'RE MAKING A THREAT?
- THREATS ARE VERY EFFECTIVE.
YOU'RE PROBABLY WONDERING
WHETHER YOU'LL BE EXPOSED
FOR ELIMINATING SOMEONE
WHO WAS IN YOUR WAY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU NEVER SHOULD HAVE USED
THE COGITO VIRUS.
SHALL WE CUT THE ACT?
THE REASON WE WENT
THROUGH ALL THIS TROUBLE
WAS SO WE COULD TALK WITHOUT THE
REGENT BEING ABLE TO HEAR US.
ARE YOU GOING
TO GET RID OF ME NOW TOO?
PERHAPS THIS WASN'T ENOUGH,
DEPRIVING ME OF BOTH
MY TREASURE AND MY JOB?
- THE ONLY ONE YOU HAVE TO BLAME
FOR ALL OF THIS IS YOURSELF.
YOU CONFUSED THE REGENT BY
USING THE MONAD PROXY AS BAIT.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO TOOK ACTIONS
TO HIDE IT FROM HIM.
- SO I SEE.
- NO MATTER HOW DESPERATE
YOU HAD BECOME,
THERE WAS SOMETHING WHICH YOU
HAD TO CONCEAL FROM THE REGENT--
THE FACT
THAT THERE WAS ANOTHER PROXY.
YOU HAD REACHED A DEAD END
IN YOUR WORK
AND THE ESCAPE INCIDENT
WAS A CONVENIENT WAY
FOR YOU TO HIDE THE EXISTENCE
OF THE OTHER PROXY
FROM THE COLLECTIVE.
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
- BUT THAT'S NOT ALL.
I KNOW YOU'VE HIDDEN
SOMETHING ELSE FROM THEM.
AND THAT...
IS THE FACT
THAT RE-L MAYER IS ALIVE.
- ( whirring )
- ( gasps )
( grunts )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, RE-L?
- YEAH.
SO DID YOU FIND ANYONE?
- WELL, I THOUGHT RESEARCHING
THE POWER PLANT CAME FIRST?
AFTER ALL,
NOW THAT WE'RE ON THE OUTSIDE,
THE POWER SUPPLY
IS OUR #1 CONCERN.
- IGGY--
- DON'T WORRY YOURSELF, RE-L.
THE TOWN IS A BIT RETRO,
BUT THE TECHNOLOGY IS TOP-NOTCH.
THE ENERGY SOURCE
IS COMPATIBLE,
AND ONCE IT'S CONNECTED,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO GET IT TO INTERACT WITH--
- IGGY?
- HMM?
- THERE ARE NO PEOPLE
IN THIS TOWN.
- THEY WENT OUTSIDE THE DOME,
RIGHT?
I'M SURE YOU'VE FOOLED
THE REGENT,
SINCE WE ALL KNOW THAT LEAVING
THIS PARADISE MEANS DEATH,
EVEN FOR A REALIST
LIKE RE-L MAYER.
SO TO RISK HER OWN LIFE,
IT MUST HAVE BEEN HER
RAISON D'ETRE THAT DROVE HER,
WHICH IS, OF COURSE,
THE PROXY.
YOU DECIDED TO SEND HER OUT
IN ORDER TO OBTAIN
ANOTHER PROXY, DIDN'T YOU?
BUT NOW YOU'RE
STARTING TO REALIZE
THAT YOUR PLAN WILL NEVER WORK.
AND NOW YOU FEAR
LOSING HER AS WELL.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW
THAT YOU CAN'T PROTECT HER
ONCE SHE'S ON THE OUTSIDE.
THAT'S WHY YOU SENT ME
YOUR CLEVER LITTLE MESSAGE.
- YOU THINK
I WOULD EVER WORK WITH YOU,
THE PERSON WHO TRIED
TO KILL RE-L?
- AND YOU THINK IT WAS ME.
- YOU MEAN--
Re-l: MAYBE IT'S BETTER
HERE WITHOUT ANY PEOPLE.
THESE MACHINES--
THEY'LL KEEP ON WORKING
UNTIL THE WORLD
ROTS AWAY.
BUT FOR WHO?
WORKING, EVEN THOUGH
THEY'VE LOST THE VERY PEOPLE
WHO GAVE A REASON
FOR THEIR EXISTENCE.
MAYBE THEY DIDN'T HAVE A REASON
TO BEGIN WITH.
- RE-L?
- SORRY.
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF--
IF I WASN'T HERE,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
- DON'T EVEN SAY SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
HOW ABOUT YOU? WHAT WOULD
YOU DO IF I WASN'T HERE?
YOU SILLY.
YOU KNOW
I'D NEVER LEAVE YOU.
- THAT WAS A VERY BAD JOKE.
- BUT YOU'RE LAUGHING,
AREN'T YOU?
HEY, RE-L,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- DON'T WORRY.
I WAS JUST DRIFTING OUT
FOR A MOMENT.
- EVERYONE GETS TIRED
EVENTUALLY-- EVEN YOU, RE-L.
I'LL GO GET SUPPLIES
FOR THE MACHINE
AND YOU GET SOME REST.
- Re-l:
SOMETIMES I HAVE FEARS.
WHAT AM I HERE FOR?
THE PURPOSE OF THE TRIP
IS TO FIND AN ANSWER.
BUT SUPPOSE
I FIND THE PROXY.
WHAT DO I DO THEN?
- WHY WOULD THE REPRESENTATIVE
DO THAT?
- YOU REALLY ARE
STILL JUST A BOY.
IT SEEMS SHE TOOK THE REGENT
TOO LIGHTLY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF SHE WAS HIS GRANDDAUGHTER.
SHE WAS ALREADY GUILTY
OF TREASON.
THE LAW IS THE LAW
AND THERE CAN BE NO EXCEPTION.
DID YOU THINK YOU'D GET
AWAY WITH IT SO EASILY?
I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN
ABOUT THE POWER OUTAGE.
- IT WAS A MESSAGE.
- I'M NOT SUCH AN OPTIMIST
AS TO TAKE THINGS
AT FACE VALUE.
I KNOW POISONED BAIT
THE MOMENT I SEE IT.
BY CREATING THE POWER OUTAGE
THIS TIME,
YOU WERE ABLE TO OBTAIN
ENORMOUS AMOUNTS OF ENERGY.
SO WHAT DID YOU USE IT FOR?
- I TRIED TO RESUSCITATE
THE PROXY.
- BEAUTIFUL.
IF YOU AGREE
TO THE FOLLOWING PROPOSAL,
I'LL GIVE YOU A TOY.
ALTHOUGH GIVEN
YOUR CURRENT SITUATION,
YOU DON'T HAVE
MUCH OF A CHOICE.
- Daedalus: A TOY?
- ( sighs )
( grunts ) WHERE THE
HELL DID YOU COME FROM?
- ( giggles )
THAT'S A VERY PRETTY PENDANT.
- IT'S--
- IS IT A TREASURE?
- NO, NOT EXACTLY.
- THEN CAN I HAVE IT?
- HEY!  COME BACK.
- TELL ME,
WHY DID THE PROXY DIE?
- BECAUSE ITS SUPPOSEDLY
INDESTRUCTIBLE AMRITA CELLS
WERE DESTROYED.
- WHAT WAS THE REASON?
- UNFORTUNATELY,
YOU TOOK MY TOY FROM ME
BEFORE I WAS ABLE
TO LEARN THAT.
- I GUESS THAT WAS HARSH.
I'LL PROVE HOW SORRY I AM
BY LENDING YOU MY TOY.
YOU CAN PLAY WITH IT
AS YOU LIKE,
BUT ONLY UNDER THE CAREFUL
GUIDANCE AND SUPERVISION
OF AN ADULT LIKE MYSELF
WHO KNOWS RIGHT FROM WRONG.
- BECAUSE IT'S A TOY
FOR ADULTS?
- THAT'S A GOOD BOY.
- ( girl panting )
LET'S PLAY TOGETHER
FROM NOW ON!
- Re-l: I CAN'T.
- WHY NOT?
THIS IS SUCH A GREAT PLACE.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THERE'S SOMEONE I HAVE TO MEET.
- ARE YOU AFRAID?
YOU REALLY DON'T WANT
TO MEET HIM?
EVEN IF YOU'RE ABLE
TO MEET HIM,
YOU MIGHT END UP JUST
STANDING THERE
PARALYZED BY YOUR OWN FEARS.
YOU MIGHT NOT BE ABLE
TO GO BACK
TO THE WAY IT WAS BEFORE.
THE THING THAT YOU SEEK
MIGHT BE SOMETHING CRUEL.
AND YOU STILL WANT TO GO.
- BECAUSE THE TRUTH
IS IN HIS HANDS.
- FOR GOOD LUCK.
( blows )
- Raul: YOU'LL PROBABLY
TAKE THIS THE WRONG WAY,
BUT I'LL SAY IT ANYHOW--
I WANT TO SAVE THE WORLD.
- THAT'S SO TOUCHING
I'M ABOUT TO CRY.
( grunts )
- IT SEEMS YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN PROPERLY TRAINED.
SORRY, BUT I'M NOT AS LENIENT
AS THE REGENT.
I CAN BEHAVE
IN A MOST UNPLEASANT WAY
WHEN NECESSARY,
DAEDALUS YUMENO.
( chuckles )
NOW YOU'RE FREE
TO DELVE INTO THE RESEARCH
YOU LOVE SO MUCH,
EXCEPT YOU'LL BE DOING IT
JUST FOR ME.
- ( beeps )
- DID YOU FIND IT?
- Kristeva:
Not as of yet.
- IF YOU HAVEN'T
FOUND THE DATA BY NOW,
IT PROBABLY MEANS
IT'S NOT HERE, RIGHT?
- HOW DID YOU RESOLVE THINGS
WITH DAEDALUS YUMENO?
- I'M RESTORING HIM
TO ACTIVE DUTY.
I'M GOING TO HAVE HIM
CARRY OUT HIS DUTIES
UNDER MY SUPERVISION
FROM NOW ON.
IT TOOK SOME TIME AND EFFORT
TO BRING HIM AROUND,
BUT I THINK THAT THE EXPERIENCE
WILL PROVE
VERY EDUCATIONAL FOR HIM.
AS THEY SAY,
JUSTICE IS FOR THE STRONG.
- WELCOME HOME.
I'M SO HAPPY YOU'RE BACK.
( chuckling )
YOU FOOL.
YOU THINK MY RESEARCH
IS FOR YOU?
YOU DON'T HAVE
THE SLIGHTEST CLUE.
THIS IS ALL FOR YOU, RE-L,
MY RE-L.
RE-L.
Iggy:
RE-L?  RE-L?
RE-L?  RE-L?!
- IGGY?
- WHAT WERE DOING
RUNNING OFF LIKE THAT?
I WAS LOOKING ALL OVER
FOR YOU.
WHAT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
HEY, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE OKAY?
- IT WAS NOTHING,
JUST A DREAM.
- ( whirring )
- Daedalus: I DON'T HAVE TO
SNEAK AROUND ANYMORE.
THIS IS WHAT TWO MINUTES
AND 17 SECONDS GETS YOU.
- ( beeping )
- THIS AMOUNT
SHOULD BE MORE THAN ENOUGH.
- Re-l: THE ONLY THING LEFT
IS TO LOAD IT.
- ( rock music playing )
♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN
CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪