- Re-l: A DENSE PREDAWN FOG.
ANOTHER DAY
WITHOUT A GUST OF WIND.
I GET UP AS USUAL.
I TAKE AN HOUR
TO GET READY.
THE MORNING IS SPENT OUTSIDE
WITH THE ENTOURAGE
ASSESSING
THE SITUATION.
I CONFIRM THAT THERE'S NOTHING
WITHIN SIGHT.
- ( shouts )
- I CHECK OUR SUPPLY STOCK.
WE NEED TO FIND A WAY OUT
OF HERE.
- ( humming )
- RE-L.
- Pino: VINCENT.
VINCENT!
- ( laughs )
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD UNWINDS ♪
♪ INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL ♪
♪ MY PLACE ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- ANOTHER 2,000 MILES TO MOSK.
THE CALM OUTSIDE HAS SHOWN
NO SIGN OF LETTING UP.
THE ONLY THING THAT STIRS
IN THIS PLACE IS MY PATIENCE.
AND THEN THERE'S THE PROXIES,
A MYSTERY WHICH REFUSES
TO BE SOLVED.
IT IN FACT SEEMS TO DEEPEN
THE FURTHER IN I LOOK.
I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
EVEN THE BASE NATURE
OF THEIR POWER IS UNCLEAR TO ME.
AND THE BIGGEST MYSTERY
OF ALL
IS RIGHT NOW IS LYING
ON THE FLOOR
AT MY FEET.
- ( sneezes )
( yawns )
OH!
AND A VERY GOOD MORNING
TO YOU.
- ( laughs )
- THROUGHOUT THE DAY, I TRY
AND OBSERVE THE PROXIES' HABITS.
PATHETIC.
IS LEAVING A TOILET SEAT UP
THE ONLY WAY FOR A MAN
TO ASSERT HIS MASCULINITY?
VINCENT!
- ( playing tune )
- Re-l: I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE TO
REMIND YOU
TO LOWER THE TOILET SEAT
WHEN YOU'RE DONE?
- I KNOW.  I HEARD YOU.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T.
IN MY SPARE TIME,
I OBSERVE THE INFECTED AUTOREIV.
I GET IT.
- HUH?
- Re-l: LIFE IS OFTEN SPOKEN
OF AS A JOURNEY.
"A PINCH OF SALT?"
THOSE DIRECTIONS SOUND STUPID.
SOMETIMES I MAKE DISCOVERIES
IN THIS STRANGE NEW WORLD.
SOMETIMES THERE ARE SURPRISES.
OH, DAMN!
( gasps ) OH, NO!
HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?
WHILE PREPARING LUNCH,
I OBSERVE ANOTHER FACET
OF THE COGITO VIRUS.
ARE YOU LEFT-HANDED, TOO?
- LEFT MY HAND WHERE?
- HMM.
AUTOREIVS ARE DESIGNED
TO BE AMBIDEXTROUS.
BUT SHE STILL GOES OUT OF HER
WAY TO USE HER LEFT HAND.
COULD IT BE A SIDE EFFECT
OF HER ASSERTING HER WILL?
- DOES IT TASTE GOOD?
- IT'S STALE.
I PUT THE MYSTERY
OF THE SINISTER AUTOREIV
OFF TILL LATER.
AFTER THINKING IT OVER,
I REALIZE IT'S NOT
THE PROXY,
BUT VINCENT LAW HIMSELF THAT
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT.
WHAT NOW?
- I REALLY WOULDN'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
- FOUND IT.
( grunting )
( scoffs )
YOUR SOCK HAS A HOLE.
- HUH?
- IT'S NOTHING.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- BUT DO I REALLY NEED TO KNOW?
THAT IS THE QUESTION.
IN THE AFTERNOON,
A SUPPLY SHORTAGE QUESTION
I'D ANTICIPATED SUDDENLY CAME
TO THE FOREFRONT.
- TWO, ONE.  RE-L,
IT'S BEEN THREE MINUTES NOW.
I'M STILL WASHING MY HAIR.
- YEAH, BUT CONSIDERING HOW MUCH
WATER WE HAVE LEFT.
- I HAVE TO WASH MY HAIR TODAY.
- RE-L!
- TWO MORE MINUTES.
YOUR HAIR'S SHORT.
YOU ONLY NEED A MINUTE.
- YEAH, BUT--
- AFTER TALKING IT OVER,
WE ARRIVED
AT A TEMPORARY AGREEMENT
ON THE WATER SHORTAGE PROBLEM.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- EYE EXERCISES.  THAT'S ALL.
- OH.
- LEFT, RIGHT,
LEFT, RIGHT, LEFT.
- THERE WAS A MARKED DECLINE IN
THE CREW'S MORALE THIS MORNING.
IT'S BEEN THREE HOURS
ALREADY.
WHAT THE HELL ARE THEY DOING?
THE FOOD SHORTAGE CONTINUES
TO GROW WORSE.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
NOT BEANS AGAIN.
- I WAS THINKING THAT,
BUT WHY ARRANGE THEM
IN A PATTERN?
- WELL, I THOUGHT GIVING THEM
A NEW LOOK
MIGHT MAKE IT BETTER.
- WITHOUT A DOUBT THE ACT ITSELF
RAISES SOME SERIOUS QUESTIONS.
I CAN'T COMPREHEND WHY,
BUT STARING AT THE SERENE
EXPRESSION ON HIS FACE
IS BEGINNING TO IRRITATE ME.
( grunting )
THE AFTERNOON COMES.
NO CHANGE.
( sighs )
( gasps )
OH.
BRAND-NEW.
THAT IDIOT.
- ( yawns )
- WHAT'S THIS?
- ( vibrates )
- ON THIS JOURNEY SUCH AS THIS,
UNDER THESE CONDITIONS,
IT SOMETIMES DAWNS ON ME
THAT THERE IS A WALL,
A WALL BETWEEN
PROXIES AND PEOPLE.
A WALL BETWEEN PEOPLE
AND INFECTED AUTOREIVS
FOR THAT MATTER.  AN ESSENTIAL
LEVEL OF COMMUNICATION
CAN NEVER TAKE PLACE.
WE'RE EACH DISTINCTLY SEPARATE
FROM THE OTHER.
THERE ARE MOMENTS
WHEN THIS TRUTH RESONATES
TO MY VERY CORE.
WHAT THE HELL ARE THEY?
- WHAT THE--
- Pino: HEY, VINCE, LOOK!
- HUH?  NOT AGAIN.
SHE'S GONNA GET MAD, YOU KNOW?
- I'M GONNA DO YOUR MAKEUP NOW,
VINCE.
- STOP IT.
- HERE, TAKE A LOOK.
- I TOLD YOU TO STOP.
BUT SINCE YOU STARTED ALREADY,
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE MORE HERE?
- OH, RE-L'S BACK.
- HUH?
- LOOK AT VINCE.
HE'S PRETTY.
- LOOKS LIKE FUN.
- I'M SORRY!  RE-L!
- STANDING BEFORE THIS VAST,
ENDLESS LANDSCAPE,
IT OCCURS TO ME JUST HOW
POWERLESS AND INSIGNIFICANT
WE ALL ARE.
SO WHAT'S ARE YOUR THOUGHTS
ON OUR CURRENT SITUATION?
ANY IDEA HOW WE'RE
GETTING OUT OF THIS?
- I'M NOT SURE WHAT
YOU'RE EXPECTING ME TO SAY.
AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW HOW
TO MAKE THE WIND START BLOWING?
- AND?
- AND NOTHING.  THAT'S IT.
- JUST NOTHING?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S JUST NOTHING.
AND WHAT'S NOTHING SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
IS IT NOTHING BECAUSE
YOU'VE REALLY THOUGHT ABOUT IT?
OR IS IT NOTHING
BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T EVEN TRIED?
WHILE WE'RE ON THE SUBJECT,
WHY DO YOU INSIST ON DROWNING
MY FOOD IN THAT AWFUL DRESSING
WITHOUT ASKING ME?
OR IS THE DRESSING PART
OF YOUR PLAN
TO DESTROY MY SENSE OF TASTE?
- WELL, UM--
- IF YOU HAVE SOMETHING YOU WANT
TO SAY, THEN SAY IT.
I DON'T GET THE SENSE
THAT YOU CAN DEAL WITH ANYTHING.
LOOK AT THIS TRIP WE'RE ON.
YOU'RE JUST MAKING IT UP
AS WE GO.
HAVE YOU EVER ACTUALLY
MADE A PLAN?
- WELL, I THOUGHT IF WE JUST
MADE IT TO MOSK, THEN--
I'M SORRY.
- SORRY DOES NOT MAKE IT BETTER.
- I'M SORRY--
- ( both sigh )
- WHY CAN'T YOU JUST BE STRONG
ABOUT SOMETHING?
AND DON'T YOU DARE
TRY AND GIVE ME THAT
"HERE SHE GOES AGAIN" LOOK.
IT SICKENS ME.
- WELL, I JUST FIGURED
IF WE WAIT,
THE WIND WILL COME BACK, RIGHT?
- IS THAT SERIOUSLY YOUR PLAN?
THAT IS THE STUPIDEST--
( sighs ) FORGET IT.
I'M BORED AGAIN.
I DECIDE TO OBSERVE THE AUTOREIV
AS A BRIEF DIVERSION.
- OH, NO!
HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?!
DON'T YOU DARE TRY
AND GIVE ME THAT
"HERE SHE GOES AGAIN" LOOK.
IT SICKENS ME.
- THE BOREDOM PERSISTS.
MY REASON DETERIORATES.
( sighs )
ALL I SEE ARE PROBLEMS.
- RE-L.
- I'VE TRIED TO UNDERSTAND.
( sighs )
BUT IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
A PREDAWN SNOW.
OUR CIRCUMSTANCES
REMAIN UNCHANGED.
I GET UP AS USUAL.
I ASSESS THE SITUATION.
IT'S AS CALM AS EVER.
- ( exhales )
ON SUCH A BONE-CHILLING DAY,
EVEN WHEN IT'S TIME TO GET UP,
MY BODY JUST WON'T COMPLY.
- Vincent: WOW, IT'S COLD!
( laughing )
- Pino: SNOW!  RE-L!
THERE'S SNOW OUTSIDE!
COME PLAY WITH ME.
RE-L.
HEY.
- PINO, COME TAKE A LOOK!
THERE'S AN AURORA.
- WHAT'S THAT?
OH, WOW, IT'S SO PRETTY.
- ( laughing )
- Vincent: COME ON!
( echoing )
COME ON, YOU STUPID WIND.
COME AND GET ME.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M RIGHT HERE
WAITING FOR YOU.
- I DON'T GET HIM.
- DAMN.  COME ON.
COME ON, YOU STUPID BASTARD.
YEAH.  COME ON.
COME ON, DAMN IT.
( grunting )
- WE USE AS LITTLE ELECTRICITY
AS POSSIBLE
TO SAVE IT
FOR AN EMERGENCY.
- ( whirring )
- SHE'S WATCHING ME.
AND SHE'S SAYING SOMETHING.
I WONDER.
- SHAVE IT.  SHAVE IT.
- COULD SHE BE--
NO, SHE COULDN'T.
- MAYBE IT'S MALNUTRITION,
BUT MY MIND
FEELS LIKE IT'S ON THE BRINK.
MY NERVES ARE SHOT.
I DON'T THINK I CAN
TAKE MUCH MORE.
( exhales )
I SLEEP SOUNDLY FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN AGES.
I DREAM ABOUT IGGY.
- Both: SHH!
- ( laughing )
- ALL I HAVE LEFT IS MY WILL.
I NEED A CANDLE.
VINCENT.
- YEAH, SURE.
OW!
- ( laughing )
- WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
- IT WAS NOTHING.
- IT DIDN'T FEEL LIKE NOTHING.
- HEY, DON'T GIVE ME THAT LOOK.
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- OW.
- JUST HOPELESS.  OH!
- HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- OH!
- GOTCHA!
BYE.
- PINO, WAIT UP.
- Re-l:
COME ON, YOU STUPID WIND!
COME AND GET ME.
- RE-L.
- I'M HERE WAITING FOR YOU.
I FEEL A LOT BETTER.
- ( laughs ) I TOTALLY JUST
GOT YOU IN THE FACE.
- IT'S NOT FUNNY.
- COME AND GET ME.
- Re-l: FINDING A WAY OUT
OF THIS MIGHT BE EASIER
THAN I THOUGHT.
I REALIZED THAT OVER-THINKING
IT WAS A WASTE.
WHAT'S MORE,
FOR SOME REASON...
- PINO.
- FOR SOME REASON,
I FELT I COULD FINALLY SMILE.
- ( wind blowing )
- ( gasps ) THERE'S WIND!
- Re-l: 2,000 MILES TO MOSK...
...ON A STRONG SOUTHWEST BREEZE.
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING
TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
- Re-l: A MADNESS ROAMS
THE ABANDONED PARADISE.
A SHADOW STIRS AMONGST
THE FORGOTTEN RUINS.
OUR MUTUAL DESIRES NOW THUNDER.