- HMM?
A RABBIT!
- WHO SAID YOU COULD LOOK?
- YAY!
- PINO, I WANTED
TO SHOW THAT TO MY MOM.
- A RABBIT?
- HE'S NOT JUST A NORMAL RABBIT.
HE'S LIKE A SUPER RABBIT,
BUT NOBODY KNOWS
WHERE HE IS ANYMORE,
BUT HE'S SOMEWHERE OUT THERE.
AND WHEN WE FIND HIM,
WE CAN GO ANYWHERE.
- Both: FINISHED!
- HUH?  HUH!
- THEY MATCH.
- YOU'RE INCREDIBLE.
- ( laughs )
- ( wind howling )
- ( rock music playing )
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD UNWINDS ♪
♪ INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL ♪
♪ MY PLACE ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- ( mechanical whirring )
- THAT'S THE END OF THIS PLACE.
- Boy: OVER HERE.
MOM!
- TIMOTHY,
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN HIDING?
COME ON, LET'S GO.
- LOT OF PATROLS LATELY, HUH?
- YEAH, EVER SINCE A CERTAIN
SOMEONE ARRIVED.
- I WONDER WHY THAT IS.
- WHY DON'T YOU GO AWAY?
- COME TO THINK ABOUT IT,
WHY DID YOU COME HERE AT ALL?
- BECAUSE I--
- BECAUSE VINCENT
IS THE CHOSEN ONE, OF COURSE.
- ( grunts )
- THIS MAN IS WELL-KNOWN
AS A REVOLUTIONARY
THROUGHOUT ROMDEAU.
A FAMED WARRIOR
OF THE RESISTANCE,
VINCENT IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR DIRECTING MANY ACTIONS
AGAINST THE DOME'S ESTABLISHED
RULING PARTY.
- HEY, HOODY, COME ON.  JUST
HOLD ON A SECOND, ALL RIGHT?
- WE WITNESSED HIS
MAGNIFICENT GUNPLAY.
THEY CAN SEND AS MANY
PATROL FLIGHTS THEY'D LIKE
AGAINST OUR COMMUNE.
HE'LL DISPATCH THEM
AS IF IT WERE CHILD'S PLAY.
- ( murmuring )
- THE OF FALL OF ROMDEAU
IS ALMOST AT HAND.
CITIZENS TURNED REFUGEE ARE
JOINING THE COMMUNE EN MASSE.
THESE ATTACKS AGAINST US
ARE THE LAST DESPERATE ACTS
OF THE CITY GOVERNMENT.
THEY STRUGGLE
TO KEEP THE CITIZENRY
FROM ABANDONING THEM.
( sighs )
BUT THEIR VIOLENCE ONLY
URGES REVOLUTIONARIES
SUCH AS VINCENT
TO RETALIATE.
QUITE FOOLISH REALLY.
- THANKS A LOT, HOODY.
- REVOLUTIONARY?
( scoffs )
I COULD CARE LESS
ABOUT REVOLUTION
OR THE FUTURE OF ROMDEAU.
I WANT NO PART OF THIS.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
OUR FREEDOM HANGS ON THE SUCCESS
OF THIS REVOLUTION.
- WHAT THE HELL IS THE POINT
OF FREEDOM IF YOU HAVE TO DIE
TO GET IT?
- ( murmuring )
I GIVE YOU MY WORD THAT
NO MORE LIVES WILL BE LOST.
- HOW CAN YOU
MAKE THAT PROMISE?
- WELL, BECAUSE--
BECAUSE AN INSIDE SOURCE
HAS BEEN GIVING ME NOTICE
AS TO WHEN THE PATROL FIGHTERS
ARE GOING TO ATTACK.
- THAT'S HOW.
- ( murmuring )
- ( clears throat )
FINE.
I WAS HOPING TO KEEP IT A SECRET
TO AVOID A PANIC,
BUT I SUPPOSE I MUST TELL YOU
THAT I'VE BEEN IN NEGOTIATIONS
FOR OUR AUTONOMY
WITH ROMDEAU FOR SOME TIME NOW.
OUR ENEMY IS ANXIOUS
TO SETTLE THIS.
THEY PRACTICALLY CAME HERE
CRAWLING ON THEIR
HANDS AND KNEES
ASKING FOR OUR RETURN.
- I'LL BE DAMNED.
- IT'S A DREAM COME TRUE.
- ( laughing )
- THAT WAS A VERY CLOSE CALL.
IF I HADN'T HELPED YOU OUT OF
YOUR LITTLE SITUATION BACK THERE
YOU'D HAVE QUITE A MOB
ON YOUR HANDS RIGHT NOW.
- BUT STILL,
YOU REALLY DIDN'T HAVE TO LIE.
- I'D PREFER TO THINK OF IT
AS WORKING A CLOSE CALL.
AND IT WAS A CLOSE CALL,
A VERY CLOSE CALL.
- JUST LEAVE THINGS TO HOODY
AND IT'LL ALL WORK OUT
FOR THE BEST.
- MM-HMM.
- YEAH, QUINN,
YOU GOT SOMETHING YOU WANNA SAY?
- NOT REALLY.  I WAS
JUST WONDERING HOW EXACTLY
HOODY MANAGED TO GET IN TOUCH
WITH ANYONE FROM ROMDEAU.
JUST SEEMS STRANGE TO ME.
- ( gasping )
- YES, THIS IS THE COMMUNE.
ATTEMPTING COMMUNICATION
WITH ROMDEAU.  OVER.
CAN I HELP YOU?
- QUINN WAS WONDERING--
- WHAT WAS THAT?
VERY WELL.
IT SEEMS THAT THEY'RE READY
TO ADMIT THAT
THEIR BACK'S AGAINST THE WALL.
I THINK THEY'RE FINALLY READY
TO SEE THINGS OUR WAY.
THEY SOUND DESPERATE.
- IS SOMEONE FROM ROMDEAU
COMING HERE?
- LIKE WHO?  A NEGOTIATOR?
- A NEGOTIATOR.
- MAYBE THEY'RE FINALLY
COMING FOR US.
- WELL, I DON'T SUPPOSE
THAT'S COMPLETELY OUT
OF THE QUESTION--
- WE CAN GO BACK TO ROMDEAU?!
- WHAT GOOD LUCK.
- HOT DAMN!
- SO, HOODY,
IS THAT THE RADIO?
- HUH?  OH!
- ( all laughing )
- ALL THAT WORRY
FOR NOTHING.
- I TRIED TO TELL YOU.
WITH A GREAT REVOLUTIONARY
ON OUR SIDE, WE'RE INVINCIBLE.
- SPEAKING OF WHICH,
WHERE DID HE GET TO?
- FOUND YOU!
YOU'RE PLAYING HIDE AND SEEK?
ME TOO. ( laughs )
- SHH!
JUST GO PLAY SOMEWHERE ELSE.
- OH.  ROGER!
HIDE AND SEEK!  HIDE AND SEEK!
- SHH!  SHH!
- DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
HE'S AROUND HERE.
- YEAH.
- UGH!  SHH!
- FINISHED.
- ME TOO.
- HUH?
QUIT COPYING ME.
- ( laughs )
- WHY THE LONG FACE?
DON'T TELL ME OUR REVOLUTIONARY
HAS LOST HIS STOMACH.
- SORRY,
BUT YOU STARTED THIS.
- SO YOU'RE COMPLAINING
NOW, TOO?
THEY'RE ALL TOTALLY
DEPENDENT ON ME,
BUT THE SECOND THERE'S TIME
TO COMPLAIN.
( sighs ) I'M THE ONLY ONE
RUNNING THE COMMUNE.
WELL, DON'T WORRY.
IF WE RIDE THIS ONE OUT,
EVENTUALLY WE'LL FIND PEACE.
AND IF IT COMES TO IT,
WE CAN ESCAPE
ON THE CENTZON TOTOCHTIN.
- CENTZON?
- IT MEANS 400 RABBITS.
- 400 RABBITS?
- I FOUND THE RABBIT.
HEY!  WAIT!
- WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?  NO ONE'S
EVEN SEEN IT EXCEPT FOR HOODY.
I DON'T HAVE THE SLIGHTEST CLUE
WHAT KIND OF VEHICLE IT IS.
GIVING IT THAT UTTERLY
RIDICULOUS NAME--
"THE 400 RABBITS."
WHO KNOWS WHERE HE'S HIDING IT.
- WHY WOULD HE HIDE IT?
- HE MADE UP ONE OF HIS STORIES
ABOUT THE OUTSIDE WORLD
BEING DANGEROUS.  REALLY
HE JUST WANTS TO KEEP US HERE.
HE DOESN'T WANT
TO LOSE HIS COMPANIONS.
THE WHOLE THING SCARES ME.
LIES BEGAT LIES,
AND AT SOME POINT SOON,
THERE WON'T BE ANY TURNING BACK.
FOR BEING HUMAN,
SEEMS LIKE SUCH A TRAGIC STATE
FOR EVERY ONE OF US.
- SO WHEN'S
THE NEGOTIATOR COMING HERE?
- I'M SURE HE'S ON HIS WAY.
- FROM WHERE?
- I GUESS
FROM SOMEWHERE THAT WAY.
- WELL, IF IT WERE ME,
I THINK I'D CIRCLE
AROUND THE COMMUNE
TO MAKE IT LOOK I WAS COMING
FROM RIGHT OVER THERE.
- ( all shout )
- ( Pino and Timothy laughing )
- ( door opens )
- ( gasps )
- HOODY, HE'S HERE.
HE'S FINALLY HERE.
- WHO'S HERE?
- THIS WAY.
A NEGOTIATOR.
- HUH?
( gasps )
- I CAN'T HEAR A THING.
I WONDER WHAT THEY'RE SAYING.
- I CAN'T SEE
THE NEGOTIATOR'S FACE, EITHER.
- I WONDER IF HOODY
CAN HANDLE THIS.
- ( clears throat )
YOU DON'T LOOK AT ALL LIKE
THE NEGOTIATOR FROM LAST TIME,
BUT WHY DON'T YOU AT LEAST
START BY GIVING ME YOUR NAME?
THIS IS GOING NOWHERE.
COULD YOU AT LEAST TELL ME
WHAT YOU'RE HERE FOR?
ARE YOU TOO SCARED
TO CONTINUE NEGOTIATING?
SO YOU PLAN TO ATTACK US?
IN THAT CASE,
YOU'LL BE DEALING WITH HIM.
- UH, HELLO.
- Re-l: VINCENT, IT'S ME.
- RE-L.  WHAT ARE YOU--
- I'VE COME TO RETRIEVE YOU.
- WHAT?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- YOU'RE COMING BACK
WITH ME TO ROMDEAU.
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT'S NOT ALL THAT EASY.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
ONCE SOMEONE'S LEFT ROMDEAU,
THEY'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE ABLE TO RETURN.
WHY?  WHY JUST HIM?
- ( laughing )
- SHUT UP.
GO AWAY!
- OKAY.
- VINCENT, LET'S GO.
- NO, YOU CAN'T HAVE HIM.
- DO YOU WANT TO DIE?
- ( growls )
- Daedalus: RE-L, IT'S ME.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- CHIEF, WE'VE RECEIVED A REPORT
FROM THE SECURITY--
- RE-L?
- WHAT?
- OUT OF THE WAY.
- Re-l: WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
THERE ARE PEOPLE ALL OVER HERE
ON THE OUTSIDE.
- RE-L, I SPECIFICALLY TOLD YOU
NOT TO MAKE CONTACT
WITH THE PEOPLE OUT THERE.
- THEY WERE STANDING RIGHT IN
FRONT OF ME.
KIND OF HARD TO MISS.  WHY WERE
YOU HIDING THIS FROM ME?
- I JUST--
I JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO WORRY YOU.
- THIS IS ABOUT MORE
THAN THE PROXY NOW.
- PROXY?
THIS IS ALL STARTING
TO SOUND VERY SUSPICIOUS.
- DON'T TALK TO HIM!
DAMN!
- ALL RIGHT, WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE MONSTER?
- YOU THINK PROXIES
ARE MONSTERS?
YOU DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT ANYTHING.
- HE'S LAUGHING.
- HE'S COLD AS ICE.
PEOPLE HAVE CALLED THEM MONSTERS
OR DEMONS,
BUT THAT'S ALL
NOTHING BUT NONSENSE.
IN TRUTH,
PROXIES ARE MAGICIANS.
THEY HAVE THE POWER TO
CHANGE THEIR APPEARANCE
INTO ANY FORM THEY CHOOSE.
THEY CAN DISAPPEAR WITH EASE
LEAVING NO TRACE
THEY WERE EVER THERE.
THEY CAN ALSO ENTER HUMAN BEINGS
AND TAKE CONTROL
OF THEIR MIND AND BODY.
THEY CAN SUMMON LIGHTNING BOLTS
AND SCORCH THE EARTH
WITH THEIR POWER.
THEY CAN EVEN CONJURE UP
FLAMING PLANETS FROM THE SKY!
- ( playing tune )
- WOULD YOU KNOCK IT OFF?
- BOTH OF YOU,
GO OUTSIDE AND STAY THERE.
- TAG, YOU'RE IT.
SORRY FOR THE INTERRUPTION.
I WAS ABOUT TO TELL YOU
THAT THERE IS MORE
THAN ONE PROXY.
SIMPLY STEP INTO THE WILDERNESS
AND YOU'LL FIND THEM
CRAWLING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
I MYSELF HAVE PERSONALLY
SEEN AT LEAST...
- JUST FIVE?
- WELL.
- YOU'RE WASTING MY TIME.
COME ON, VINCENT.
- WAIT.  VERY WELL.
YOU LEAVE ME NO CHOICE.
IF THIS IS THE WAY IT HAS
TO BE,
THEN I'LL TELL YOU
WHERE THE PROXY IS.
OF COURSE IN RETURN,
I'LL BE EXPECTING
A LITTLE QUID PRO QUO...
- Daedalus: RE-L, IT'S ME AGAIN.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- YES, WHAT?
- FIRST, YOU RECOGNIZE
OUR RIGHT TO AUTONOMY...
- THE SITUATION HAS CHANGED.
RETURN IMMEDIATELY.
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I WAS PLANNING TO DO.
- YOU SEEM STRANGELY WILLING.
HAVE YOU RETRIEVED VINCENT LAW?
- YES, I HAVE.
- AND WE DEMAND THE RIGHT
TO RETURN TO ROMDEAU.
YOU'RE TOO LOUD.
GO SOMEWHERE ELSE.
- ( laughing )
- BUT THAT'S WHERE WE'VE
SEEN PATROLS.
- THEY WON'T FLY PATROLS
IN THE MIDDLE OF TALKS.
- I UNDERSTAND.  WE HAVE TO
GET OUT OF HERE, VINCENT.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
THE SECURITY BUREAU IS PREPARING
TO STERILIZE THE COMMUNE.
YOU'LL BE KILLED TOO,
IF YOU STAY HERE.
- STERILIZE US?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
WE WERE JUST ABOUT
TO ESTABLISH FRIENDLY RELATIONS.
- WE'RE LEAVING NOW, VINCENT.
- ARE SOLDIERS REALLY
ON THEIR WAY?
WHAT ARE THEY
GOING TO DO TO US?
WHAT ABOUT ME?
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- LET GO!
- YOU'RE JUST GOING TO
ABANDON US, AREN'T YOU?
YOU'RE GOING TO ESCAPE
EVEN AFTER I SAVED YOU.
- HEY, I SAID
STOP COPYING ME.
JUST TRY DRAWING SOMETHING
YOU WANNA DRAW YOURSELF.
- WHAT DO I WANNA DRAW MYSELF?
- DON'T ASK ME.
JUST DRAW WHATEVER POPS
INTO YOUR HEAD.
LIKE SOMETHING YOU WANT
TO EAT RIGHT NOW.
- BUT I DON'T EAT.
- OH, YEAH.
THEN JUST CLOSE YOUR EYES.
NOW REMEMBER SOMETHING
REALLY FUN.
AND ONCE YOU REMEMBER SOMETHING,
THEN YOU CAN TRY DRAWING IT.
- SO I GUESS WE'RE
ALL GOING BACK.
- I GOING TO NEED
TO PACK MY BAGS.
- WHAT?  A PATROL FLIGHT?
- I THOUGHT THEY
STOPPED COMING.
- THEY'RE HERE TO HELP.
- KEEP MOVING, VINCENT.
- IT'S JUST--
CAN'T WE BRING
THE OTHERS ALONG WITH US?
IT'S JUST NOT RIGHT
THAT I GET TO GO BACK.
NOT WHEN--
- ONCE YOU'RE BACK IN ROMDEAU,
YOU'LL FORGET ABOUT
THIS WHOLE EXPERIENCE.
THE PEOPLE, THE COMMUNE,
EVERYTHING.
YOU JUST NEED SOME TIME
TO GET BACK IN STEP
WITH YOUR REAL LIFE.
- BUT WHAT IF CAN'T GO BACK
TO HOW I WAS BEFORE?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I PROMISE I'LL TESTIFY
AS TO YOUR INNOCENCE.
- THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
I KNOW...
EVEN IF I GO BACK
TO ROMDEAU,
NOW THAT I FOUND OUT THE TRUTH,
NOW THAT I KNOW ABOUT
THE WORLD OUTSIDE,
I CAN NEVER BE
A FELLOW CITIZEN.
- THERE'S NOWHERE ELSE
YOU CAN GO EXCEPT ROMDEAU.
WHERE WOULD YOU LIVE?
THIS GARBAGE DUMP?
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
- I KNOW.  YOU'RE RIGHT.
I MEAN, WHERE COULD I POSSIBLY
BELONG NOW?
NOT HERE OR ROMDEAU.
SO I SUPPOSE I SHOULD JUST
RETURN TO WHERE I WAS BORN.
- BACK TO THE LOST DOME?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- LOOK OUT!
- STOP!
- ( screams )
- ( shouting )
- COOL.
SHE CAN DO ANYTHING.
- Pino: TIMOTHY!
Daedalus:
RE-L?  RE-L?
- DAEDALUS, THEY FRIED
MY ELECTRICAL SYSTEM.
I CAN'T MOVE.
- RE-L.
- DAMN IT.
- STOP!  YOU'LL DIE IF YOU COME
IN CONTACT WITH THE ATMOSPHERE.
- ( air hisses )
- RE-L, COME BACK!
- WHO ARE YOU?
( panting )
I NEED TO CONTACT
ROMDEAU IMMEDIATELY.
- IS THAT THE RADIO?
- ( stammers )
- ( playing tune )
- Hoody: NO, THE NOTE
SHOULD BE HIGHER--
- WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( clears throat )
- HAND OVER THE RADIO.
- QUINN, COME WITH ME.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- HURRY UP, HURRY!
- IF I DON'T CONTACT
ROMDEAU SOON.
- Hoody: SETTLE DOWN.
HERE, HAVE SOMETHING TO DRINK--
- SHUT UP!
( coughs )
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY WAS THERE A PROXY HERE?
( gasps )
TELL ME WHY DOES THE PROXY
ONLY APPEAR
WHEN YOU'RE SOMEWHERE NEARBY?
ANSWER ME!
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
WHO?
- RE-L!
- ( groaning )
- Pino: I TOLD YOU, TIMOTHY
WON'T GIVE ME MY BOOK BACK.
- ALL RIGHT.
- HE WON'T ANSWER ME, EITHER.
- ( gasps )
- ( rock music playing )
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING
TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
Re-l: A MAN STANDS IN
THE WAY OF OUR DEPARTURE.
WHEN THE BALANCE OF POWER
BETWEEN OPPOSING
FORCES COLLAPSES,
THE DOOR OPENS ON
A PLACE TO WHICH WE MUST RETURN.