- ( harmonica playing )
- ( gasps )
( panting )
- WHERE AM I?
- ( harmonica playing )
- PINO.
HEY, IS ANYBODY HERE?
HELLO?
PINO?
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- VINCE.
- PINO.
PINO?
WHO ARE YOU?
- WELCOME TO THE LAND
WHERE THE SUN
CALLS ITS HOME.
- ( rock music playing )
- ♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD UNWINDS
INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- I THOUGHT
I WAS IN CHAROS.
- THAT IS
WHERE I FOUND YOU.
YOU WERE LYING UNCONSCIOUS,
SO I BROUGHT YOU HERE.
- LYING THERE?
I'M SORRY.
- MY NAME IS
KAZKIS HAUER,
THIS TOWER'S MASTER.
YOU MUST BE
A BIT CONFUSED,
SINCE YOU JUST
WOKE UP.
- UM, WERE THERE
ANY OTHER SURVIVORS?
- WHO ELSE
COULD HAVE SURVIVED?
- ( Rino whimpers )
- HUH?
COME OVER HERE.
I'LL GIVE YOU
A TREAT.
- SHE'S AN INFECTED
AUTOREIV.
- AUTOREIV?
- UM, THEY'RE MACHINE-BASED.
- HMM, MACHINE.
- HUH?
PINO.
- ( door opens and closes )
- I'M SORRY.
LOOKS LIKE SHE'S FEELING SHY.
THEY SAY SHE'S GOT
THE HEART OF A CHILD.
BUT EVEN SO,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY SHE'S ACTING LIKE THAT
AFTER YOU RESCUED US.
BUT WHY DID YOU
RESCUE US?
- WHO WOULDN'T COME
TO THE AID OF A FRIEND?
- A FRIEND?
- THOSE OF US WHO KNOW
THIS FAR CORNER OF THE WORLD
ARE ALL FRIENDS.
- FAR CORNER
OF THE WORLD?
- FROM THE WORLD
THAT YOU HAVE SEEN
TO THE WORLD
THAT YOU NOW SEE,
THOSE EYES OF YOURS
ARE STARING AT DEATH.
- WELL, WHEN YOU LOOK
AT THINGS THAT WAY,
I GUESS
YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT,
SINCE SURVIVING MEANS SEEING
SO MUCH DEATH FIRSTHAND.
MY FRIENDS
ALL DIED TOO.
I'VE JUST BEEN
ON MY OWN.
BUT WHY IS IT?
WHY AM I THE ONLY ONE
WHO SURVIVES THESE HORRORS?
- ( glass shatters )
- I SUPPOSE YOU COULD
CALL IT FATE.
I'M SO GLAD
YOU MADE IT THIS FAR.
- HOP, HOP, STEP.
HOP, STEP, STEP.
OW, THAT HURTS.
- THE LAND
WHERE THE SUN CALLS HOME.
- ( Vincent's voice ) I HAVEN'T
SEEN SOMETHING LIKE THIS
IN A LONG TIME.
- PINO, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
LOOK, IT'S LIKE A MAZE.
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
- COME ON.
- WHAT IS IT?
ALL RIGHT. ( chuckles )
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
WHAT ARE THEY DOING HERE?
- LET'S GO BACK TO THE BOAT,
BACK TO THE RABBIT.
VINCE.
I DON'T LIKE IT HERE.
LET'S HURRY UP AND LEAVE.
IT'S SCARY.
WE CAN'T STAY HERE.
COME ON, LET'S GO
LOOK FOR THE RABBIT.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GO FIND IT
ALL BY MYSELF THEN.
- BUT HE SAVED US.
- JOIN ME FOR A DRINK.
- THANKS, NO.
- YOU HAVEN'T TOUCHED
YOUR PLATE.
- WELL, IT'S JUST
THE AUTOREIVS I SAW.
- HMM?
OH, YOU MEAN
THE KNIGHTS?
- THEY WERE THE ONES
FIGHTING IN CHAROS.
THEY KILLED AN AWFUL LOT
OF PEOPLE THERE.
- WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
WAR HAS ALWAYS BEEN
ABOUT WINNERS AND LOSERS,
ALWAYS A MATTER
OF LIFE AND DEATH.
NO WAR HAS EVER STARTED WITHOUT
PEOPLE KNOWING THAT FACT.
- PERHAPS,
BUT WHAT'S THE POINT
OF YOU CONTINUING
TO ATTACK CHAROS?
- WAR IS POINTLESS,
BUT BEING DESTROYED
IS NOT.
YOU SAW IT,
DIDN'T YOU--
THE END OF CHAROS?
YOU SAW SENEX
AS SHE APPEARED.
- SENEX?
DID IT DESTROY CHAROS?
- HMM.
WHY ARE YOU SO FIXATED
ON CHAROS?
THE WORLD IS BETTER OFF
WITHOUT THEM.
- IS THAT WHY
YOU KILLED THEM?
- YOU'RE JOKING.
- HUH?
- THEY WERE
LEFT BEHIND.
AND DURING
THE LONG SLEEP
THEY TRIED TO FIND
THEIR MEANING.
BUT THEY SHIED AWAY FROM THE
FACT THAT THEY'D BEEN ABANDONED
AND ONLY FOUND A WAY TO LIVE
THROUGH MUTUAL DESTRUCTION.
BEFORE LONG,
THE WORLD WAS IN CHAOS
AND EVEN DEATH HAD LOST ITS
MEANING IN THEIR FEEBLE MINDS.
SO PATHETIC.
YOU KNOW,
IT JUST ANGERS ME TO THINK
THAT THOSE INTENTIONS OF THEIRS
EVEN EXISTED.
TO THOSE
MISERABLE CREATURES.
PERHAPS WE SHOULD BE
BEGGING FOR FORGIVENESS--
BOTH YOU AND ME.
- WHY ME?
WAIT, HOLD ON A SECOND.
ARE YOU SAYING
THAT I DID SOMETHING?
I'VE DONE NOTHING BUT GET CHASED
ACROSS HALF OF CREATION.
THAT'S HOW I ENDED UP HERE.
- THERE YOU HAVE IT.
- HUH?
- IT'S HARD NOT TO DO ANYTHING,
NOT BEING ABLE
TO DO ANYTHING.
IT WAS THE SAME FOR ME.
- FOR YOU TOO?
- I WAS DISGUSTED WITH MYSELF
FOR NOT BEING ABLE
TO DO ANYTHING.
SHOWERED WITH
MY OWN INSULTS,
I COULDN'T FIND PEACE OF MIND
EVEN WHEN I SLEPT.
WITHOUT A PURPOSE,
I SIMPLY COUNTED THE MINUTES
AND SUFFERED AS MY LONG LIFE
DRAGGED ON.
I SUFFERED
JUST AS YOU DO.
- IT WAS THE SAME
FOR YOU.
- I FEEL
A LOVE FOR YOU,
NOT UNLIKE THE LOVE
I FELT FOR SENEX.
- ( door squeaks )
- ( wind whistling )
- YOU LOVED SENEX?
- IT'S TIME TO TELL YOU
ABOUT US.
IF MY ASURA
WERE THE SUN,
THEN CHAROS
WOULD BE THE MOON.
SENEX AND I EACH BUILT
COMPANION TOWERS
TO SERVE WITNESS
TO THE VOWS
WE WOULD EXCHANGE
WHEN WE AWOKE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M SAYING?
SENEX AND I BOTH CAME TO SEE
THE WAY OF GRIEF.
AND FOR THAT,
WE SUFFERED.
AND FOR THAT, WE CAME TO HAVE
AN UNSHAKEABLE LOVE.
BUT SENEX DIED
BEFORE WE HAD THE OPPORTUNITY
TO EXCHANGE OUR VOWS,
BECAUSE YOU KILLED HER.
- NO.
- BUT THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
VOWS HOLD LITTLE WEIGHT
IN THE EYES OF FATE.
HONESTLY, I FEEL
TRULY HONORED
TO HAVE MET YOU
IN THIS WAY.
LET US BE GRATEFUL
FOR YOUR POWER.
- WHAT?
ARE YOU INSANE?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I DIDN'T KILL HER.
YOU'RE WRONG.
I COULD NEVER DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SENEX WAS--
- PLEASE STOP.
- BUT YOU ARE--
- I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
- THIS IS A GAME
YOU'RE PLAYING, ISN'T IT?
- LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU THINK WE ARE.
- JUST PLEASE
TELL ME THAT I'M RIGHT.
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU?
- PLEASE STOP.
- HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT WHEN...
- WHY ARE YOU...
- ...WE SHARE THE SAME GRIEF?
- ...TORMENTING ME LIKE THIS?
- WHY?
- I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING!
- HE DOESN'T REMEMBER.
( screaming )
- ( glass shattering )
- ( laughs )
HE KILLED
MY DEAR SENEX
WITHOUT EVEN
REALIZING IT.
- ( Vincent panting )
WHY?
- THIS IS MY ASURA
AS IT REALLY IS.
- HUH?
- THIS IS WHAT YOU BELIEVE
TO HAVE SEEN, RIGHT?
IT'S JUST A MONUMENT.
THE CITIZENS BUILT IT SO THAT
FUTURE GENERATIONS WOULD KNOW
JUST WHAT ASURA WAS LIKE
IN THE PAST.
BUT IT WAS
A WORTHLESS EFFORT.
- WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE CITIZENS?
- THEY WERE
COMPLETELY WIPED OUT,
EXTERMINATED
BY THE KNIGHTS.
- YOU COULDN'T.
- CHAROS AND ASURA
ARE ONE.
THE CITIZENS ALL DIED
IN THE WAR
AND ONLY THE KNIGHTS
REMAIN.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE SOLDIERS IN CHAROS?
- THEY WERE SIMPLY
A FALSE PEOPLE.
IN DEATH, THE EXISTENCE
OF NOTHING
RETURNS TO NOTHING.
- BUT THEY WERE STILL
LIVING BEINGS.
THE LIVING HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO GO ON LIVING.
- THE LIVING?
NOW THAT THEY'RE GONE,
WE CAN CONSIDER THIS ALL
A BLESSING.
- WHY?  AREN'T YOU
THE MASTER OF THIS PLACE?
SHOULDN'T YOU HAVE PROTECTED
YOUR CITIZENS?
- IT SEEMS
YOU REALLY ARE A FOOL.
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR EYE FOR THE
TRUTH AS WELL AS YOUR MEMORY?
- I HAVE NO PROBLEM
WITH MY MEMORY.
- THEN TELL ME
WHO YOU REALLY ARE.
- WHAT?
- TRY AND TELL ME
WHO YOU ARE.
- I'M VINCENT LAW.
I WORKED AT ROMDEAU'S
AUTOREIV DISPOSAL UNIT FACILITY,
BUT I WAS FALSELY ACCUSED
OF THE CRIME OF TREASON
AND FLED FROM THE DOME.
- AND BEFORE THAT?
- I LIVED IN THE MOSK DOME.
I EMIGRATED FROM THERE.
- AND WHAT DID YOU DO
BACK IN MOSK?
- DO?
- YOU DON'T REMEMBER,
DO YOU?
DESPITE HAVING
SUCH LIMITED MEMORIES,
YOU'VE LIVED UNTIL NOW
WITHOUT ANY DOUBTS.
THAT ITSELF
IS THE GREATEST PROOF
THAT YOU INTENTIONALLY ERASED
YOUR MEMORY, IS IT NOT?
- MY MEMORY?
- YOU SAID YOU WERE IN MOSK.
- YES, IN MY HOMETOWN.
- I SEE.
BUT IT MUST BE MONAD.
YOU MUST HAVE TRANSFERRED
YOUR MEMORIES TO MONAD.
IT WAS TOO MUCH
FOR ANYONE,
BUT MONAD STILL ACCEPTED
THOSE MEMORIES
IN SPITE OF
THE REPERCUSSIONS,
BECAUSE MONAD LOVED YOU.
BUT IN THIS DISPLAY
OF UNREQUITED LOVE,
MONAD COMPLETELY
LOST YOU.
NO, NOT ONLY MONAD.
YOU LOST YOURSELF
AS WELL.
WE ARE THE SUM
OF OUR MEMORIES.
ERASING THE MEMORIES
ETCHED INTO ONE'S OWN SELF
IS THE SAME
AS LOSING ONESELF.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING TO ME?
- WHAT I'M SAYING IS THAT
YOU ARE A TRAITOR, VINCENT LAW.
- A TRAITOR?
WHO DID I BETRAY?
- YOU RAN AWAY.
THAT IS THE MOST SHAMEFUL THING
FOR A PROXY TO DO.
- A PROXY?
- BUT WHAT'S MORE UNFORGIVABLE
THAN ERASING YOUR MEMORIES,
EVEN RUNNING AWAY--
YOU MURDERED
MY BELOVED SENEX!
LOOK UPON
THE AGENT OF LIGHT--
KAZKIS PROXY.
ON MY HONOR,
I WILL ANNIHILATE
THE TRAITOR.
- ( beeping, whirring )
- ( yells )
- ( Vincent screams )
- VINCENT, EVEN THOUGH
YOU ERASED YOUR MEMORY
AND LOST YOURSELF, YOU STILL
HAVE YOUR INSTINCTS, DON'T YOU?
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IT'S THE ONES WHO'VE GONE MAD
WHO ARE THE MOST IN DARING,
LIKE MY DEAR SENEX
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN LET ME GO MAD TOO!
- ( gunshots )
- ( Vincent exclaims )
- OH, I'M SO SORRY.
DID THAT HURT?
( laughing )
- HOP, HOP, HOP.
RABBIT!
- ( moaning )
( coughing )
( screaming )
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
MY ARM.
HELP ME.
IT HURTS!
AM I A MONSTER?
NO, I'M A--
- YOU ARE A PROXY.
- A PROXY?
- AH, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M FEELING?
DO YOU?
I'M FEELING REVOLTED
AND I'M NAUSEATED.
- YES, THAT'S IT.
- ( moaning )
- IT'S BECAUSE OF YOU,
YOU BASTARD.
I'LL GIVE YOU ONE LAST CHANCE
TO TELL ME
YOU ARE THE AGENT
OF ONE.
YOU CAN'T ANSWER.
VERY WELL.
THEN YOU CAN DIE!
GO AHEAD AND RUN,
BUT YOU ARE IN A TRAP,
JUST THE SAME AS ME.
- 98 RABBITS, 99 RABBITS,
100 RABBITS.
FINE.
I'VE COUNTED TO 100,
SO I'M GOING TO LEAVE VINCE NOW.
I'LL COUNT ANOTHER 50.
101 RABBITS, 102 RABBITS,
103 RABBITS...
- ( screams ) NO!
- ( glass shatters )
- Kazkis: THIS ONE'S NO GOOD.
IT'S NOT FRAGRANT.
THIS ONE'S BAD TOO.
IT'S GOT A COARSE
AND SOUR TASTE.
NOT A DECENT ONE LEFT.
THEY'RE ALL
WORTHLESS PISS.
- YOU MUST TELL ME,
WHAT THE HELL
IS A PROXY?
- HOW DARE YOU ASK THAT AFTER
YOU WIPED OUT YOUR OWN MEMORY?
- THEN TELL ME,
AM I A PROXY?
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT
AGAINST YOU LIKE THIS.
- THEY WHY DID YOU
COME BACK?
BECAUSE YOU WANT
TO KILL ME NOW, RIGHT?
- YOU'RE WRONG.
- IT'S THE TIME
OF THE AWAKENING.
- I DON'T WANT
TO HURT ANYONE.
- ALL RIGHT,
THEN WHO KILLED SENEX?
IS SENEX THE ONLY ONE
YOU'VE KILLED?
- ( screams )
- YOU'VE LOST YOUR WAY
AND THE ONE YOU LOVE.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO LIVE
SO BADLY?
WHY NOT JUST DIE HERE?
- ( grunting )
- SENEX, I WANTED TO SEE YOU
ALIVE ONE LAST TIME.
BUT I PROMISE
I WILL AVENGE
YOUR DEATH.
- ( growling )
( screams )
TELL ME,
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
WHY?
- THEN I'LL ASK YOU
AGAIN:
WHAT ARE YOU
THE AGENT OF?
- MY NAME
IS ERGO PROXY
AND I AM
THE AGENT OF DEATH.
- REALLY?
( grunts )
GO AHEAD AND SUFFER.
ALL THOSE WHO WANDER IN
THE DARKNESS SEEK THE LIGHT.
BUT WHEN THEY REACH
THE LIGHT,
THEY TURN THEIR EYES AWAY
FROM THE BLINDING GLARE.
I CAN EVEN SENSE
THE PAIN.
THE TRUTH
IS LIKE THAT TOO.
SOMEDAY YOUR EYES WILL BE BURNT
BY THE LIGHT OF TRUTH
AND YOU WILL KNOW
ETERNAL DARKNESS.
THAT IS THE JUDGMENT
THAT AWAITS.
( laughing )
SENEX.
- IF I AM NOT HUMAN,
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO GO ON?
- 400 RABBITS.
( gasps )
VINCE.
- PINO.
- ARE YOU HURT?
- NO.
THAT'S NOT MY BLOOD.
- OH, THEN IT'S THE OTHER ONE'S.
NOT YOUR BLOOD,
BUT FROM THE OTHER VINCE, RIGHT?
WELCOME BACK.
- THEN YOU KNEW
ABOUT IT?
LET'S GO TO MOSK.
YOU WEREN'T
AFRAID OF ME, WERE YOU?
- AFRAID?
BUT YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO ALWAYS HELPS ME.
- IS THAT SO?
- ( Vincent's voice )
WE CAN'T SEE IT,
BUT FROM THE MOMENT
WE LEAPT FROM ROMDEAU
IT WAS ALL
SET INTO MOTION.
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU STOP
THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET
SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN
CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪