- Vincent: RE-L.
BUT WHY?
- I DIDN'T
TRAVEL ALL THE WAY HERE
JUST TO GIVE THAT
BACK TO YOU.
NO MORE GAMES.
TELL ME EVERYTHING YOU KNOW,
VINCENT LAW.
- RE-L...
I AM...
- IMPOSSIBLE.
DO YOU REALLY EXPECT ME
TO BELIEVE THAT?
THAT YOU'RE A--
- ( rock music playing )
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD
UNWINDS INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
Pino:
VINCE?
THE SCARY LADY,
IS SHE COMING WITH US?
- MAYBE.
DO YOU WANT HER
TO COME WITH US?
YOUR FACE LOOKS FUNNY.
- HEY.
IT'S JUST I--
- I CAN TELL
YOU KNOW SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING
ABOUT THE PROXY.
WHY DOES IT ONLY APPEAR
WHEN YOU'RE AROUND?
DO YOU CALL FOR IT TO COME?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU?
( grunts )
- I SWEAR I DIDN'T KNOW BEFORE.
I ONLY JUST REALIZED
I'M A PROXY.
- WHAT DO YOU--
- I'M NOT SUMMONING
THE PROXY.
I AM THE PROXY.
MAYBE SHE SHOULD GO BACK
TO ROMDEAU.
- I'M GLAD
WE CAUGHT UP WITH HIM
WHILE WE STILL
HAD SOME FUEL LEFT.
- HEY!
SCARY LADY!
OVER HERE!
- HEY!
- ( laughs )
WHOA, COOL!
- THAT AUTOREIV'S INFECTED
WITH THE COGITO VIRUS.
YOU STAY HERE.
- UH?  BUT RE-L!
- OH, IT'S HOT.
( sighs )
WHAT?
- IT'S JUST I REALLY WISH
I COULD EAT FOOD.
BUT I LIKE WATCHING.
IT'S SO COOL.
- JUST GO AWAY.
I DON'T LIKE YOU STARING.
- NYAH!
- SORRY ABOUT HER.
- I STILL THINK YOU'RE LYING.
- HUH?
- ABOUT YOU BEING THE PROXY.
- IT'S UNDERSTANDABLE.
I FIND THE SITUATION
PRETTY HARD TO BELIEVE MYSELF.
THAT'S WHY I NEED ANSWERS.
THE ONLY THING I DO KNOW
IS THERE ARE STILL
OTHER PROXIES OUT THERE.
- OTHER PROXIES?
YOU'RE SURE?
- I FEEL IT.
THERE ARE OTHERS.
I BELIEVE I'VE COME IN CONTACT
WITH AT LEAST TWO OTHER PROXIES.
BOTH TIMES I KILLED THEM.
- KILLED THEM?
- THE FIRST ONE WAS IN CHAROS,
THE SECOND IN ASURA.
AND THE SECOND TIME,
THE PROXY AND I TALKED.
IT TOLD ME
THAT I HAD LOST MY MEMORY.
WHATEVER I'M MISSING,
IT HAPPENED IN MOSK.
I KNOW I'VE
FIGURED THAT MUCH OUT AT LEAST.
IF I GO TO MOSK,
I MIGHT FIND ANSWERS.
FOR NOW, ALL I KNOW FOR CERTAIN
IS THAT I'M A PROXY
AND THERE'S NO TURNING BACK.
- OKAY.
- SO YOU STILL
THINK I'M CRAZY, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- HMM?
- IT'LL KILL THE PROXY?
- WELL, IT'S THE BEST DEFENSE
I CAN GIVE YOU,
AT LEAST FOR THE TIME-BEING.
I THINK I'VE COME UP
WITH SOMETHING
TO DESTROY THE PROXY.
THIS BULLET
HAS AN F.P. PAYLOAD.
HARMLESS TO HUMANS,
THE F.P. RAYS
SHOULD AFFECT THE AMRITA CELLS
WHICH ARE UNIQUE
TO THE PROXY.
AS LONG AS THE BULLET
MAKES CONTACT,
THE F.P. RAYS
WILL BLANKET THE TARGET,
MAKING ANY HIT
A CONFIRMED KILL.
AT LEAST IN THEORY, ANYWAY.
- HARD TO BELIEVE--
THIS IS ALL IT TAKES.
- ALL IT TAKES THEORETICALLY.
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE YOURS NOW.
SO IF IN YOUR TRAVELS,
YOU COME ACROSS THE PROXY--
- YOU WANT ME
TO TEST THIS OUT.
TRY TO KEEP IN MIND,
MY FIRST PRIORITY IS TO ATTEMPT
TO CAPTURE THE PROXY.
- OF COURSE.
IT'S MINE TOO.
WELL, I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
- Re-l: DAEDALUS AND I
BOTH THOUGHT
THAT IF WE COULD
CAPTURE THE PROXY,
THEN THE MYSTERY
WOULD BE SOLVED.
NOW I WONDER.
I'VE FINALLY SEEN
THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
AND IT'S BEDLAM.
ROMDEAU IS THE LAST REFUGE
OF ORDER
AGAINST THE CHAOS
OF THE GATE.
NO.
ROMDEAU'S FALLING AS WELL.
THE RAMPAGING PROXY,
THE RISING NUMBER
OF COGITO INFECTIONS.
AND EVEN THOUGH
I'M THE REGENT'S GRANDDAUGHTER,
I NARROWLY ESCAPED
AN ASSASSINATION.
EVEN IF HE IS A PROXY,
WHAT PROFIT IS THERE
IN TAKING HIM BACK
TO ROMDEAU NOW?
BUT I CAN'T LET HIM CONTINUE.
WHAT DO I DO?
- RE-L, ARE WE TAKING
VINCENT LAW INTO CUSTODY?
EITHER WAY,
IF WE'RE GOING BACK TO ROMDEAU,
IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
RE-L, DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
- I STILL DON'T BELIEVE HIM.
- HUH?
- BUT I NEED TO BE SURE.
- RE-L?
- Re-l:
HE SAYS HE'S A PROXY?
FINE.
I CAN FIND OUT WITH ONE SHOT.
IF HE LIVES,
HE'S A LIAR.
AND IF IT'S TRUE--
NO, HE'S LYING!
F.P. SHELLS
ARE HARMLESS TO HUMANS.
I'LL JUST SHOOT HIM
IN THE LEG.
( sighs )
VINCENT?
I BELIEVE THAT YOU
AND THE PROXY ARE CONNECTED.
THAT'S WHY I FOLLOWED YOU
ALL THIS WAY.
I-- I GUESS I FELT MYSELF
BEING STRANGELY DRAWN TO YOU.
I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU
MORE THAN A LITTLE
DURING THIS JOURNEY.
TELL ME, ARE YOU A PROXY?
EVEN IF YOU ARE,
IT'S STILL GOING TO--
- ( both gasp )
- Vincent: I LOVE YOU.
- HUH?
- I SAID I LOVE YOU, RE-L.
BUT HOW COULD AN IMMIGRANT--
I MEAN, A MONSTER LIKE ME
FEEL THIS WAY?
I TRIED TO STOP
FEELING THESE THINGS.
I TRIED TELLING MYSELF
IT DIDN'T MATTER
BECAUSE I'D
NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN.
BUT NOW YOU'RE HERE
AND I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT?
- ( rustling )
- ( sighs )
- Vincent: WHO ARE YOU?!
WAIT!
THERE ARE PEOPLE
EVEN OUT HERE.
- ( computer beeping )
- TELL ME.
- IT'S NO GOOD.
EVEN TAKING INTO ACCOUNT
THE POSSIBILITY OF REFUELING
ALONG THE WAY,
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS
TO GO ANY FURTHER.
YOUR PRINCE SAID SO HIMSELF,
DIDN'T HE?
HE TOLD US TO MAKE SURE
WE HAVE ENOUGH FUEL
TO MAKE THE RETURN TRIP
TO ROMDEAU.
YOU CAN'T FORGET THE WISHES
OF THOSE WHO CARE ABOUT YOU.
AND DON'T IGNORE THAT
HANDSOME BOYFRIEND OF YOURS.
- DAEDALUS IS MY DOCTOR.
- WHATEVER.
LET'S JUST GO BACK HOME NOW.
RE-L?
- IGGY,
YOU ALREADY KNOW
THE WHOLE SITUATION, RIGHT?
BACK IN ROMDEAU,
RE-L MAYER IS ALREADY DEAD.
- I'M SURE YOUR PRINCE
WILL MANAGE
TO TAKE CARE OF IT SOMEHOW.
- Re-l:
MY PRIDE WOULDN'T ALLOW IT.
IF WE TURN BACK NOW, THIS ALL
WILL HAVE BEEN FOR NOTHING.
- I GUESS, BUT--
- I KNOW.  IF WE CAN'T
KEEP USING THE U4,
THEN WE CAN USE HIS SHIP.
IT'S WIND-POWERED.
I KNOW IT LOOKS PRIMITIVE,
BUT WE WON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT FUEL.
- YOU'RE GOING
TO STEAL HIS SHIP?
- NOT EXACTLY.
- YOU WANT TO BE WITH HIM
THAT BADLY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT HE SEEMS
TO FEEL THAT WAY ABOUT ME.
- HUH?
- HE THINKS
HE'S IN LOVE WITH ME.
AND I'M NOT READY
TO RETURN TO ROMDEAU.
- RE-L?
- ARE YOU DONE?
- HUH?
OH, YEAH, YOU'RE ALL SET.
- I'M GONNA WORK THIS OUT,
NO MATTER WHAT.
- HEY, PINO!
HELLO?
DAMN.
I WAS REALLY HOPING
SHE MIGHT PICK UP A FEW THINGS
FROM RE-L'S ENTOURAGE.
( grunts ) OW!
- ( flute playing )
- AHHH!
HUH?
HMM?
HEY, YOU WERE
AT THE RABBIT YESTERDAY!
THE RABBIT BROKE,
SO VINCE
IS GOING BANG BANG ON IT.
IT GOT NOISY,
SO I WENT AWAY.
HEY, WHY WON'T YOU
SAY ANYTHING?
COME ON, DON'T YOU WANT
TO TALK TO ME?
MAYBE YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW TO TALK.
- ( growling )
- VINCE?
- ( gasps )
- ( shouting )
- AHHH!
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S HAPPENED?
STOP.
THAT AUTOREIV'S INFECTED.
YOU STAY HERE.
- BUT...
IT'S ALREADY TOO LATE.
HUH?
- ( groaning )
AHHHH!
- VINCENT LAW.
- SCARY LADY!
- ( growling )
- OH, VINCENT.
NO.
- AHHHH!
- VINCE!
- VINCENT.
- HEY, DON'T WORRY.
VINCE IS REAL STRONG.
HUH?
- Iggy: RE-L!
- IGGY.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
IT'S DANGEROUS.
LADY!
- RE-L.
- IT'S VINCENT, HE--
- I KNOW.
I SAW IT TOO.
- IT'S THE SAME EXACT PROXY
I SAW IN ROMDEAU.
IT'S THE ONLY THING
I'VE EVER SEEN
THAT TERRIFIED ME.
STILL,
I HAVE TO SEE
IF THE F.P. SHELLS WORK.
I HAVE TO KNOW IF THIS
WILL REALLY KILL A PROXY.
- Iggy:
YOU'RE GOING TO SHOOT HIM?
- ( grunting )
- ( gun cocks )
- CAREFUL.
YOU'VE ONLY GOT
TWO F.P. ROUNDS.
- YEAH.
- YOU WERE RIGHT.
THE MAN WE'VE BEEN CHASING
THIS WHOLE TIME WAS A PROXY.
WE CAN FINALLY GO BACK
TO ROMDEAU.
- AHHH!
- WHY DIDN'T YOU SHOOT HIM?
- IGGY!
- Iggy: VITAL SIGNS-- NEGATIVE.
- HE'S DEAD?  YOU SURE?
- RE-L.
- ( clicking )
- ( gasps )
- ( whirring )
- I'VE SEEN IT
WITH MY OWN EYES.
NOW I BELIEVE
YOU'RE A PROXY.
IN THIS GUN
IS THE ONLY WEAPON
THAT CAN KILL A PROXY.
VINCENT,
IF I PULL THIS TRIGGER,
I CAN KILL YOU TOO.
Vincent ( low voice ):
KILL ME?
DID YOU SAY
YOU'RE GOING TO KILL ME?
ME?!
- Vincent: STOP IT!
( Vincent grunting )
RE-L, PLEASE.
- FINE.
I WON'T KILL YOU.
BUT I'M COMING WITH YOU.
- RE-L!
- WHAT I CAME HERE TO FIND
WAS THE TRUTH,
NOT A DEAD PROXY.
JUST REMEMBER THIS--
SOMEDAY I'M GOING
TO PULL THAT TRIGGER.
SO CAN YOU STILL LOVE ME
KNOWING THAT?
THAT'S AMAZING.
DAEDALUS IS SURE
GOING TO BE HAPPY.
- I CAN'T
GO BACK TO ROMDEAU ALONE.
- I WANT YOU TO TELL DAEDALUS
ABOUT EVERYTHING
THAT YOU SAW HERE.
- NO!
I WON'T HEAR ANY MORE OF THIS.
YOU NEED TO COME BACK
WITH ME TO ROMDEAU.
HE'S A PROXY.
WHY WON'T YOU SEE REASON?
RE-L, I WANT AN EXPLANATION.
- IS THAT ALL YOU WANT?
EXPLAIN WHAT?
HOW COULD I EXPLAIN
TO AN AUTOREIV?
HOW DO I CONVINCE YOU
WHEN I DON'T EVEN UNDERSTAND?
- RE-L, I DON'T THINK--
- APPLICATION OFF.
FOLLOW YOUR ORDERS, IGGY.
RETURN TO ROMDEAU.
- ROGER.
RETURNING TO ROMDEAU.
PLEASE CONFIRM.
- CONFIRMED.
- Vincent: WHAT NOW?
- HUH?
- WHAT THE HELL
DO WE DO NOW?
- ( rock music playing )
♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN
CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
- THE COGITO VIRUS.
THE CHAIN OF SAD SOULS
THAT LOST ITS RAISON D'ETRE.
THE SHOT THAT ECHOED
IN A MAZE OF TREES
WHEN HE STOPPED
BEING WHO HE WAS.