- WHY DO YOU ALLOW HER
TO ACT WITH SUCH INDEPENDENCE?
- IF SHE IS MORE THAN
YOU CAN DEAL WITH,
THEN WHAT USE ARE YOU?
- SHE IS YOUR RAISON D'ETRE.
LOSE HER AND YOU
WILL LOSE YOUR MEANING.
- SUCH IS THE BOND
BETWEEN AN ENTOURAGE
AND ITS MASTER.
- ( cell phone rings )
- Re-l: Iggy, I need to head
over to the HJ District.
Come pick me up.
- BUT HJ DISTRICT IS OUTSIDE
OUR JURISDICTION.
- I REALLY DON'T CARE
ABOUT JURISDICTION.
I'M GOING ONE WAY
OR THE OTHER.
IF YOU'RE AFRAID
OF WHAT GRANDFATHER WILL SAY,
I'M FINE GOING ALONE.
- Man: WHY DO YOU ALLOW HER
TO ACT WITH SUCH INDEPENDENCE?
- Woman: IF SHE IS MORE THAN
YOU CAN DEAL WITH,
THEN WHAT USE ARE YOU?
- YOU'LL NEVER KNOW.
- Woman:
SHE IS YOUR RAISON D'ETRE.
LOSE HER AND YOU
WILL LOSE YOUR MEANING.
- Man: SUCH IS THE BOND
BETWEEN AN ENTOURAGE
AND ITS MASTER.
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD UNWINDS ♪
♪ INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL ♪
♪ MY PLACE ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- ARE YOU SURE THE SHIP WILL
BE ABLE TO TAKE OFF
WITH ALL THIS WIND?
I MEAN, LOOK AT THE STATE
OF THIS THING.
IT'S READY TO FALL APART.
HEY, YOU, MY LEG
IS REALLY STARTING TO HURT.
GIVE ME A MEDICAL EXAM.
- MEDICAL WHAT?
- YEAH.
SHE'S JUST A COMPANION MODEL.
SHE DOESN'T DO THAT.
- ( sighs )
SURE, A USELESS SHIP.
WHY NOT A USELESS AUTOREIV?
I'M AMAZED YOU'VE MANAGED TO
MAKE IT THIS FAR IN ONE PIECE.
OH.  IT MUST BE
BECAUSE YOU'RE A PROXY.
- RE-L.
- A PROXY WHO DOESN'T KNOW
HE'S A PROXY
OR EVEN WHAT A PROXY IS.
IT'S PATHETIC.
SHIT!
WHEN'S IT GOING TO LET UP?
- Iggy: PROXY.
IF IT HADN'T BEEN FOR HIM.
VINCENT LAW.
- ( loud bang )
- I KNOW THAT AUTOREIV.
DID IT COME FOR THE BODY?
- ( loud bang )
- WHAT?!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
HEY!
GO ON, TAKE IT.
IT'S NOTHING BUT TROUBLE.
WAIT.
WAS THAT YOUR MASTER?
YOU WERE LOOKING
AFTER THAT PROXY.
THIS IS--
THIS IS FAMILIAR.
OF COURSE.
THE WHOLE PLACE IS--
DID HE MAKE THIS?
WHAT THE HELL
ARE THESE PROXIES?
IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER.
I'VE GOT IMPORTANT THINGS
TO DO.
NOW THAT YOUR MASTER IS GONE,
WHAT WILL YOU DO?
- Vincent: OH.
- DID YOU REALLY THINK
YOU COULD TRY TO TAKE MY GUN
FROM ME WHILE I WAS ASLEEP?
- I THOUGHT
THAT YOU LOOKED COLD.
- FIX MY HAIR.
YOU AT LEAST KNOW HOW
TO DO THAT, DON'T YOU?
WELL, ARE YOU DEAF?
- NOT NOW.
I'M TRYING TO READ.
- ( grumbles )
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
- FINE, YOU DO IT.
- HUH?
- HELP FIX MY HAIR.
- I DON'T--
- JUST DO IT.
I JUST WISH
IGGY WERE STILL HERE.
- NO MATTER WHO THEY ARE,
THE MASTER IS THE MASTER.
ENTOURAGES CAN'T LIVE
WITHOUT A MASTER.
IT SEEMS EVEN MORE TRUE FOR ME
NOW THAT I HAVE A SOUL.
SO...
I DON'T REALLY
HAVE A CHOICE.
I HAVE TO KILL THE ONE
WHO TOOK MY MASTER AWAY.
YES, THAT'S GOOD.
IF I KILL HIM,
SHE'LL HAVE TO COME BACK.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, RE-L?
YOU'LL BE A GOOD GIRL AND COME
HOME WITH ME, WON'T YOU?
- YOU KNOW, THAT'S NOT BAD.
- REALLY?
- I'LL HAVE YOU DO IT
FROM NOW ON.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I'M WORRIED ABOUT THE SHIP.
- I'M GONNA GO TAKE A LOOK.
- BUT THE STORM.
- IF I KILL THE ONE WHO TOOK
HER, SHE'LL COME BACK.
- I THINK THE WIND HAS LET UP
ENOUGH THAT WE CAN TAKE OFF.
- RE-L.
- IGGY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
IN ROMDEAU.
- I TOLD YOU, REMEMBER?
I WOULD NEVER
LEAVE YOU BEHIND.
- COGITO.  YOU'RE INFECTED.
- OH, MY.  DID YOU REALLY
NOT NOTICE TILL NOW?
( laughs ) I WOULD HAVE EXPECTED
YOU TO BE SMARTER THAN THAT.
NO, YOU JUST WEREN'T PAYING
ATTENTION TO ME ANYWAY.
THAT HURTS, RE-L.
TO THINK OF ALL THE TIME
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER.
- WHEN DID IT HAPPEN?
- BACK IN ROMDEAU
WHEN THAT INFECTED AUTOREIV
ATTACKED ME.
- NO, YOU TESTED NEGATIVE.
I SAW IT.
- IT'S EASY TO CHEAT
IF YOU KNOW THE SYSTEM.
- SO ALL THIS TIME.
- YES, BUT I HAVEN'T
REALLY CHANGED.
- IGGY.
- YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
I'VE EVER OBEYED,
THE ONLY ONE
I'VE PROTECTED.
JUST YOU,
JUST RE-L MAYER.
BUT STILL, YOU INSIST
ON PRETENDING THAT
YOU DON'T NEED ME.
- ( grunts )
- WE'RE OUT OF WOOD.
HEY, PINO.
- NOT NOW.  I'M TRYING TO READ.
- COME ON, COULD YOU TRY
AND HELP OUT JUST A LITTLE?
- ( groans )
- LET ME OUT!
- FINALLY AWAKE,
ARE WE?
YOU'VE ALWAYS EXPECTED ME
TO FOLLOW YOUR EVERY WHIM,
HAVEN'T YOU, RE-L?
NOW WE'RE GOING TO TRY THINGS
MY WAY FOR A CHANGE.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M YOUR ENTOURAGE IGGY.
- NO, IF YOU'RE IGGY,
THEN IGGY IS DEAD.
- WHAT?
- IGGY WOULD NEVER
TALK TO ME LIKE THAT.
- DON'T BE STUPID.
MY VOCAL PATTERNS ARE
JUST AN EFFECT
OF YOUR CUSTOMIZATIONS TO ME.
- IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
ALL OF THIS.
THE REAL IGGY WOULD NEVER
THINK OF DOING IT.
IF THIS IS HOW THE COGITO VIRUS
CHANGED YOU,
THEN YOU MIGHT AS WELL
BE DEAD.
THE REAL IGGY WAS INFECTED
WITH THE VIRUS AND HE DIED.
- SHUT UP!
YOU ALWAYS WERE
A SELFISH BITCH, RE-L.
THIS IS NOT HOW IT WORKS
ANYMORE.
YOU DON'T GET
TO WRITE ME OFF JUST
BECAUSE I'VE GOTTEN COMPLICATED.
IF I'M DEAD, THEN TELL ME
WHO'S BEEN BY YOUR SIDE
EVER SINCE YOU LEFT ROMDEAU?
- THAT WAS--
- YOU'RE JUST AWFUL,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU'RE SAYING THAT WASN'T ME?
I WANT YOU TO TELL ME, RE-L,
WHAT AM I?
I'M YOUR FAVORITE.
YOU CUSTOMIZED ME
TO TALK THIS WAY.
- BASTARD.
- OH, MY, WHAT A FACE
YOU'RE MAKING.
YOU KNOW YOU SHOULDN'T DO THAT.
YOU'LL GET WRINKLES.
- YOU'RE A LIAR.  YOU'VE BEEN
LYING SINCE WE LEFT ROMDEAU.
- LYING?
- IT'S TOTALLY UNACCEPTABLE
FOR AN ENTOURAGE
TO LIE TO ITS MASTER.
THE LOYAL ENTOURAGE WOULD NEVER
BEHAVE THE WAY YOU'RE BEHAVING.
YOU LIED TO ME,
TO YOUR MASTER.
IGGY WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
IGGY IS DEAD.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
WHO THE HELL DO YOU THINK'S
RESPONSIBLE FOR ALL THIS?
SELFISH RE-L.
USELESS RE-L.
INCOMPLETE RE-L.
BESIDES ME, WHO COULD DEAL
WITH A WHINY BITCH LIKE YOU?
- WHAT ARE YOU?
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW INCOMPETENT YOU ARE?
YOU PREEN AND POSE AS SOME
HOT-SHOT CAREER WOMAN
ACROSS ROMDEAU.
WHO REALLY MADE ALL
THAT POSSIBLE?
WHO WAS THERE TO SUPPORT YOU,
YOU RECKLESS, ARROGANT BITCH?
YOU SAY MY LIE WAS UNACCEPTABLE?
IT'S YOUR LIE THAT'S
UNACCEPTABLE.
SO STOP PRETENDING
YOU DON'T NEED ME.
- WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING
TO DO TO ME?
- ( laughs ) LITTLE LATE
TO START WORRYING ABOUT THAT.
- TELL ME.
- WHAT I ALWAYS DO.
I'M GOING TO PROTECT YOU.
- ( gasps )
- RE-L, YOU SAID THAT
AN AUTOREIV LIKE ME
COULD NEVER TRULY UNDERSTAND YOU
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE A SOUL.
BUT I DO HAVE A SOUL.
HOW DID YOU NOT NOTICE?
WE CAN'T MAKE IT BACK
TO ROMDEAU IN THE U-4 ANYMORE.
BUT THERE'S STILL THE SHIP.
THAT WAS YOUR IDEA,
WASN'T IT?
- AND WHAT HAPPENS AFTER
YOU STEAL THE SHIP?
EVEN IF WE MAKE IT BACK,
YOU'RE STILL INFECTED.
THEY'LL HAVE YOU DESTROYED.
- ( gasps )
- VINCE!
- PINO.
- LOOK, I'M HELPING
BECAUSE I'M GOOD.  SEE?
- VERY NICE.
NOW FIND THESE.
- ROGER!
HEY, VINCE, LIKE THIS?
- YEAH.
- THIS ONE?
- YEP.
- ( humming )
- ( gasps ) IT'S YOU.
- I'M NOT GOING TO HURT YOU.
- PINO, THAT'S ENOUGH.
I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE RE-L'S--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH HER GUN?
WHERE'S RE-L?
- RE-L'S GOING TO
KILL YOU SOMEDAY.
SO WHY DO YOU NEED HER?
- RE-L'S NOT SAFE WITH YOU.
YOU'RE DESTINED
TO KILL HER.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- Iggy: I'VE SEEN IT.
A HIDEOUS MONSTER TORMENTING
RE-L AS SHE LIES STRUGGLING
IN AGONY.
YOU ARE THE MONSTER,
VINCENT LAW.
- THIS IS INSANE.
WHY WOULD I KILL RE-L?
- THAT FACE.
IT'S THE SAME WAY YOU LOOKED
WHEN RE-L PULLED
THIS GUN ON YOU.
YOUR FACE TELLS ME YOU WILL
INEVITABLY END UP KILLING RE-L.
MY BELOVED RE-L.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT HAVE YOU DONE
WITH HER?
- RE-L!
- IGGY.
WELL DONE, VINCENT.
NOW I CAN'T KILL YOU.
- RE-L.
- YOU BEAT ME.
- RE-L, I WAS--
- ( beeping )
- ( beeping faster )
- RE-L.
I THINK IT SHOULD BE
ABLE TO FLY.
- Iggy: RE-L,
LOOK WHAT
YOU'VE DONE TO ME, RE-L.
YOU WEREN'T WORTH
WHAT I SACRIFICED.
BUT YOUR DEATH WOULD HAVE
MADE MY LIFE MEANINGLESS.
- WHY WERE YOU MY MASTER?
WHY DID IT HAVE
TO BE YOU?
- ( sobs )
- RE-L.
PLEASE, I WANT YOU TO--
DON'T HATE ME, OKAY?
- IGGY.
- IT WAS SO HARD.
I WANTED TO BE WITH YOU
NO MATTER WHAT.
IT HURT.
YOU MADE IT HURT SO.
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO BE
SUCH A USELESS BITCH?
IT'S JUST--
PLEASE, DON'T HATE ME.
- OKAY.
I PROMISE, IGGY.
- RE-L.
RE-L MAYER!
RE-L.
- IT'S OKAY.
- ( playing tune )
- ( loud bang )
- I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
YOU'RE FEELING SAD.
- THE VIRUS.
- HUH?
- I MEAN, DOES IT MAKE
YOU FEEL UNHAPPY
KNOWING WHAT SAD IS?
- I THINK IT ACTUALLY
MAKES ME HAPPY.
- WHY IS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
ALL DONE.
I'M GONNA GO PUT SOME FLOWERS
ON THE OTHER GRAVE, TOO.
- IGGY.
AFTER YOU WERE INFECTED
WITH THE COGITO VIRUS,
YOU COULD HAVE LEFT ME.
YOU COULD HAVE BEEN FREE.
WHY DID YOU STAY?
- RE-L.
- ( crying )
YEAH, WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- WELL--
- IF YOU DON'T NEED ANYTHING,
THEN JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BUT WHY?
BECAUSE YOU SAID YOU WEREN'T
GOING TO SHOOT ME YET.
SO I'M GIVING IT BACK TO YOU.
WE SHOULD GET GOING, RE-L.
- VINCENT, I--
YEAH, SO THAT'S ALL
I CAME TO SAY.
- IGGY,
I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU REALLY WERE.
BUT I PROMISE,
I'LL UNDERSTAND SOMEDAY.
I'M SORRY.
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING
TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
Re-l:
MIRROR, MIRROR ON THE WALL.
A PHRASE FROM AN OLD FAMILIAR
TALE BECKONS US
TO THE FOUNTAIN OF ILLUSIONS.
THE FACE OF SOMEONE
WHO LOOKS LIKE YOU,
REFLECTED ON THE SURFACE
OF A WAVERING MIRROR.