- EVERYTHING IN HERE
IS UNNATURAL.
A MAN LIVING INSIDE
AN EMPTY ROOM.
VINCENT LAW.
WHAT DID HE THINK ABOUT
IN HERE?
WHAT WAS IT
HE WAS LOOKING FOR
THAT HE WAS WILLING TO DIE?
IS THIS ALL HE HAD
TO SHOW FOR IT?
- YOU LIAR! ( echoes )
- YOU WERE JUST AN IMMIGRANT,
BUT WHO THE HELL
WERE YOU REALLY?
( sighs ) LOOKS LIKE THIS
INVESTIGATION IS GOING NOWHERE
WITHOUT IGGY.
"PROJECTED ESCAPE ROUTE
FOR INFECTED AUTOREIVS."
WHY DID HE HAVE IT?
- ( rock music playing )
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD UNWINDS ♪
♪ INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL ♪
♪ MY PLACE ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- Man:
HEY, LET'S NOT DO THAT.
- Vincent: WHO ARE YOU?
- Pino: IT'S THIS WAY.
( laughs )
- Man: "NOTHING THERE WAS
A TOWN OR A CHURCH
OR A RIVER OR A COLOR
OR A LIGHT OR A SHADOW."
- IMMIGRATION I.D.
IN THE END,
IT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
- Vincent: WHAT IS THIS?
WHO ARE YOU?
- THAT'S THE ONE.
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE A SMART ONE,
AREN'T YOU, PINO?
- Vincent: PINO.
IT SURE IS HOT IN HERE.
DOROTHY, COULD YOU TURN
ON THE AIR CONDITIONER?
HUH?
- ( Pino laughs )
- YOU'RE HER.
THE INFECTED AUTOREIV.
- ( laughing )
- Man:
"I KEPT STILL FOR A WHILE.
AND FELT A PLEASANT SENSATION
AS THE INDESCRIBABLE
GREAT HARMONY,
THE BRIGHTNESS OF THE SKY
AND THE MELANCHOLY OF THE MOMENT
SPREAD THROUGHOUT MY BODY."
"IT WAS JUST A DREAM."
- IT'S NOT ME.
- AFTER ALL,
AN IMMIGRANT IS AN IMMIGRANT.
- ( screams )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HE'S BY HIMSELF.
- Vincent:
MAN, WHAT AN AWFUL DREAM.
THE SECURITY BUREAU
MISTAKENLY THOUGHT
I WAS THE ONE
WHO MURDERED YOU.
A PRETTY STUPID NIGHTMARE,
HUH, DOROTHY?
CAN YOU IMAGINE ME DOING--
- STOP RELYING SO HEAVILY
ON YOUR ENTOURAGE.
DOROTHY ISN'T HERE.
YOU'LL NEVER BECOME
A FELLOW CITIZEN NOW.
- Man: "I DON'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED INSIDE MY MIND.
NOR DO I HAVE ANY WAY
OF PUTTING IT INTO WORDS."
- I TRIED--
I TRIED HARD
TO DO MY BEST,
TO BECOME A FELLOW CITIZEN.
SO I COULD BECOME A PART
OF--
I--
- YOU CRIMINAL.
VINCENT LAW.
- IT'S NOT ME!
- Re-l:
THAT'S WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
- Vincent: HELP ME.
- "IT WAS A MOMENT
THAT DEFIED ALL WORDS.
WHEN I FELT SOMETHING
INSIDE ME FALL ASLEEP
AND SOMETHING ELSE WAKE UP."
"IN THE WORLD THAT WAS
BORN FROM HIM,
A PERSON COULD NOW
BECOME ANYTHING."
THE WORDS OF JOE BOUSQUET.
- Vincent: WHO IS THAT?
- JOE BOUSQUET.
- JOE.
- YOU'RE VINCENT LAW,
AREN'T YOU?
- WHERE AM I?
- THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
YOUR BODY FOUGHT OFF
THE VIRUS.
WELL, THANKS IN PART
TO MY TREATMENT, THAT IS.
EIGHTY PERCENT OF THE PEOPLE
WHO COME HERE BECOME INFECTED
WITH THE DISEASE
AND DON'T SURVIVE A WEEK.
- INFECTED.
- YES, YOU'VE BEEN ASLEEP
FOR TEN DAYS.
BUT YOU'RE ALL RIGHT NOW.
- TEN DAYS.
- DURING WHICH TIME PINO
TOLD ME ABOUT YOU.
QUITE A STORY.
- ( door opens )
- HELLO, PINO.  GOOD NEWS.
VINCENT IS AWAKE.
- VINCE, GOOD MORNING.
THANK GOODNESS.
VINCE.
- PINO.
- THE AUTOREIV ESCAPE ROUTE.
MY GOD.
THOSE GUYS AT THE SECURITY
BUREAU COULD NEVER FIND THIS.
- EXCUSE ME.  JOE.
- JOE?
- JOE.
( laughing )
JOE.
NO, NO, I APOLOGIZE.
ACTUALLY, MY NAME IS HOODY.
JOE'S A POET FROM CARCASSONNE.
( laughing )
- WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO KIND TO ME?
IT MUST HAVE BEEN TROUBLE
FOR YOU WATCHING OVER ME
FOR TEN DAYS.
- THERE ONCE WAS A TIME
WHEN OUR GROUP ENJOYED THE KIND
PROTECTION OF THAT PLACE
INSIDE THE DOME.
- THE WHOLE CITY IS ALL JUST
ONE BIG FAT ROTTEN LIE.
- UNTIL YOU KNOW THAT A LIE IS
A LIE, THEN IT'S THE TRUTH.
LEARNING HOW TO DISCERN
THE TRUTH FROM THE LIE
MAY BE THE RIGHT THING TO DO,
BUT KNOWING THE TRUTH WON'T
ALWAYS MAKE YOU HAPPY.
- LIES MAKE US HAPPY.
LIES MAKE US HAPPY?
- THAT'S ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
YOU'RE A CLEVER CHILD, PINO.
LET'S HAVE A GOOD LOOK.
IT'S AMAZING.
AUTOREIVS REALLY DO SEEM TO BE
BECOMING MORE AND MORE LIKE US.
I BET EVERYONE HAS THESE TYPES
OVER THERE NOWADAYS, RIGHT?
- OVER THERE?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- I'M TALKING ABOUT ROMDEAU.
ROMDEAU.  SAYING IT MAKES
ME FEEL NOSTALGIC.
- WAIT A MINUTE.  WE'RE NOT
IN THE IMMIGRANT DISTRICT?
HOW IS IT THAT
I'M STILL ALIVE?
- IT TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH.
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
YOU MANAGED TO ESCAPE OUTSIDE
THE DOME WITH PINO.
- OUTSIDE THE DOME?
- OH, I KNOW.  I KNOW.
PINO KNOWS THE ANSWER.
THE DISTANCE FROM HERE
TO THE DOME IS 1246.65 UNITS.
AND THE HEIGHT FROM
THE PLUG VENT VINCE LEAPT FROM
ALL THE WAY DOWN
TO THE EARTH'S SURFACE
IS APPROXIMATELY 517 UNITS.
I KNOW A LOT BECAUSE I
SEE ALL SORTS OF THINGS
AND ASK EVERYONE ABOUT IT.
I'M AMAZING.
DON'T YOU THINK SO, VINCE?
HMM?
VINCE?
- OUTSIDE ROMDEAU.
- ( gasps ) VINCE, NO!
- YOU DON'T LOOK WELL.
I WONDER IF MAYBE IT'S FROM
THE WOUNDS WE TREATED EARLIER.
IS IT BECAUSE THE ADMINISTRATORS
DISCIPLINED YOU?
I HEARD THEY CONFISCATED IGGY.
THAT MUST BE HORRIBLE.
- YES, BUT THAT'S NOT IT.
- SO THEN WHAT IS IT?
WON'T YOU TELL ME?
- I CAN'T.
I CAN'T SAY ANYTHING.
- OH.  IT'S DELEUZE
AND GUATTARI, RIGHT?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT THEM.
THE TRUTH IS
I'VE ALTERED THEM A BIT.
NO ONE'S GOING TO HEAR
A WORD OF WHAT YOU SAY.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT
IF MY GRANDFATHER--
- IT'S JUST BETWEEN
YOU AND ME.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
ON YOUR SIDE, RE-L,
EVEN BEFORE
I WAS YOUR DOCTOR.
YOU DO BELIEVE ME,
DON'T YOU, RE-L?
- YOU WON'T TELL ANYONE
ABOUT THIS?
- I WON'T.
- I FOUND WHERE IT IS.
THE DEAD BODY
OF THE PROXY.
THE SECURITY BUREAU STILL
DOESN'T EVEN KNOW.
IT'S THE MONSTER THAT RAUL
AND HIS PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
SEARCHING FOR WHILE KEEPING IT
SECRET FROM THE BUREAU.
I NEED A FAVOR.
EXAMINE IT
AND TELL ME WHAT IT IS.
MY GRANDFATHER'S IN
ON ALL OF THIS.
I NEED TO KNOW FOR MYSELF
WHAT THAT THING IS.
- EVEN IF I DO WHAT
YOU ASK OF ME,
YOU MAY NOT LIKE THE TRUTH--
- I DON'T CARE.
I'M BEGGING YOU, DAEDALUS.
- ( sighs )
ALL RIGHT, YOU WIN.
I'LL DO IT ONLY
BECAUSE YOU ASKED ME TO.
CAN YOU TELL ME WHERE IT IS?
- I DON'T KNOW HOW,
BUT I KNOW I CAME FROM THERE.
I WAS CHASED BY A MONSTER.
FALSELY ACCUSED OF A CRIME
AND DECLARED A TRAITOR.
- A MONSTER?
DID YOU ACTUALLY SEE IT?
- WHAT?
YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
- THOSE THINGS--
THOSE THINGS ARE DEMONS
BORN FROM THE ANGRY EARTH.
- THE AMRITA CELLS APPEAR
TO BE COMPLETELY WIPED OUT,
BUT THEY'RE INDESTRUCTIBLE.
- Re-l: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- WELL, I--
I WON'T KNOW MUCH
UNTIL WE TAKE IT BACK
TO THE LAB,
TO BE SURE.
- YOU KNEW.
- YOU'D BEST FORGET ABOUT
EVERYTHING YOU SAW HERE
FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY.
- THIS IS A PROXY, ISN'T IT?
AND THERE'S STILL
A SECOND PROXY ALIVE OUT THERE.
THE MONSTER THAT KILLED
THIS ONE.
IT MUST STILL BE ALIVE
IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
WE NEED TO FIND IT.
- RE-L.
- YOU KNOW ABOUT IT,
DON'T YOU, DAEDALUS?
I'M SORRY. I KNOW IT'S SOMETHING
YOU CAN'T TALK ABOUT.
- NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
- NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT, DAEDALUS.
LOOKS LIKE I MAY WELL HAVE
GOTTEN YOU
INTO SOME SORT OF TROUBLE.
- I WANT YOU TO TRUST ME
AND LET ME HANDLE THE REST.
JUST PROMISE ME
ONLY ONE THING.
YOU MUST TELL NOBODY
WHAT YOU FOUND HERE.
- HUH?
WHAT DID I FIND HERE?
IN FACT,
I'VE NEVER EVEN BEEN HERE.
- THAT IS PERFECT.
- WELL, I'LL LEAVE THE REST
TO YOU THEN.
WHY DON'T YOU FILE THE RESULTS
AWAY FOR ME WHEN YOU KNOW THEM?
I'LL COME BY TO PICK THEM UP.
- WHERE ARE YOU--
- I TOLD YOU, DIDN'T I?
I WANNA LOOK INTO THIS MYSELF.
THERE'S A SECRET PATH HERE
THAT ONLY THE INFECTED AUTOREIVS
KNOW ABOUT.
I'M GONNA TO TRY TO FIND IT.
- RE-L.
- SO YOU'RE AN IMMIGRANT.
I GUESS THE ROMDEAU AIR
DIDN'T AGREE WITH YOU, RIGHT?
I KNOW THE FEELING.
- IN THAT CASE, WELCOME.
YOU CAN STAY HERE AS LONG
AS YOU LIKE.
- THIS LAND IS WHERE
YOU'RE FREE.
IN EXCHANGE FOR LEAVING THE
DOME, WE GAINED TRUE FREEDOM.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- THEY THROW OUT THE THINGS THEY
DON'T NEED ANYMORE IN THE DOME.
BUT MOST ALL OF IT IS STILL
PERFECTLY USABLE.
- Pino: I FOUND THIS, TOO.
( playing tune )
- ( laughing )
- THE PEOPLE LIVING HERE EITHER
LEFT ROMDEAU ON THEIR OWN
OR WERE BANISHED FROM THE TOWN
FOR VARIOUS REASONS.
THAT'S WHY A LOT THEM FEEL
HOSTILE TOWARDS THE PLACE.
WHICH ISN'T TO SAY THERE AREN'T
SOME OF US WHO WOULD LIKE
TO RETURN.
- BUT SHE TOLD ME
THAT YOU CAN'T GO BACK
FOREVER.
- WHO SAYS WE CAN'T GO BACK?
- THE WOMAN THAT I MET BEFORE
OVER THERE.
- I WONDER IF
SHE MEANS THAT BITCH QUINN.
- SPEAKING OF WHICH,
DIDN'T THE OLD MAN SAY
THIS THING WAS THE LATEST
HIGH-END MODEL?
- I BET SOME HIGH-LEVEL CITIZENS
MUST HAVE OWNED HER.
THEY MIGHT COME LOOKING
FOR THEIR LOST POSSESSION.
RIGHT, YOUNG LADY?
- VINCE!
- ( laughs ) I'M KIDDING.
WHO WOULD EVER WANT TO GO
BACK TO THAT PLACE, RIGHT?
- YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
- ( laughing )
YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN!
- ( all laughing )
- ( sighs )
( sighs ) NOW WHAT DO I DO?
- Woman:
SO YOU'RE PINO'S COMPANION?
I'M QUINN.
AS YOU CAN SEE, I PICK UP THINGS
THAT FALL IN THE SEA.
IT'S A GOOD SPOT THAT
FEW PEOPLE KNOW ABOUT,
AND THE BAY'S WARM FROM
THE HEAT CAUSED BY THE WASTE.
- HEY, THAT'S A--
- OH, YOU RECOGNIZE IT?
IT'S AN AUTOREIV'S
CENTRAL SYSTEM.
IT'S WATERPROOF SO IT CAN SERVE
AS THE RABBIT'S
TRANSMISSION SYSTEM.
- RABBIT?
- YEP.
I'M NOT LIKE THE REST
OF THESE COWARDS
WHO'S GONNA STAY HERE FOREVER.
YOU MUST THINK I'VE GOT
A LOT OF NERVE
SPEAKING SO BADLY OF OTHERS
WHEN WE'VE JUST MET.
- I DON'T THINK THAT.
- WELL, YOU MAY HAVE
HEARD THIS FROM HOODY,
BUT I PASS FOR BEING A BIT
OF AN ODDBALL,
BUT IF YOU ASK ME,
THE BIGGER ODDBALLS
ARE FAR AND AWAY
HOODY AND HIS GROUP.
ALWAYS RANTING ABOUT
HOW FREE THEY ARE.
- ( chuckles )
- WELL, I DON'T PLAN
ON BEING A PARASITE
AND LIVING OFF THE SCRAPS
OF THE DOME LIKE THIS
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE,
YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT.
- YEAH.
- SO WHAT'S YOUR STORY?
- HUH?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE
CLUTCHING YOUR KNEES
AND WHIMPERING LIKE AN IDIOT?
- NOTHING REALLY.
- PINO SEEMS A LOT MORE
GROWN UP THAN YOU.
- THAT MAY BE TRUE.
- YOU'LL GET USED TO LIVING OUT
HERE BEFORE TOO LONG.
IN THE MEANTIME, YOU CAN THINK
ABOUT WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
WITH YOURSELF.  OH, SHIT!
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE.
- WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S A ROUTINE PATROL.
COME ON, HURRY!
- ROUTINE PATROL?
- A ROMDEAU UNMANNED
SPY AIRCRAFT,
VERY METICULOUS.
IT FOLLOWS A FIXED COURSE
AT A SET TIME EVERY DAY.
AS LONG AS IT DETECTS
NOTHING UNUSUAL,
IT WON'T GO LOOKING
FOR US.
AS FAR AS ROMDEAU'S CONCERNED,
THAT'S ALL WE ARE TO THEM.
NOTHING UNUSUAL.
- PINO, HEY, YOU IDIOT!
- WAIT,
THEY CAN'T DETECT AUTOREIVS.
- Vincent: PINO, GET DOWN!
- HUH?
- HEY, I THOUGHT THE ROUTINE
PATROLS DIDN'T FIRE
AT AUTOREIVS.
- IT'S THAT MAN.
- VINCENT LAW.
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO DO?
- HOW CAN HE STILL
BE ALIVE?
- SHALL I REPORT THIS
TO THE REGENT?
- NO.
I'M SURE HE'S NOT INTERESTED.
RATHER, STRENGTHEN
THE PATROL CRAFT DEPLOYMENTS.
- THEY'RE ALREADY STANDING BY.
- BEAUTIFUL.
SEND THEM OUT.
ISSUE A MOBILIZATION REQUEST
TO ALL BUREAUS CONCERNED.
- BUT, CHIEF,
WE STILL HAVEN'T DETERMINED
THE SPECIMEN'S WHEREABOUTS.
- THAT IS TRUE,
BUT IRRELEVANT.
EITHER WAY,
THAT IMMIGRANT HOLDS THE ANSWER.
OF ALL THE THINGS I KNOW,
THAT IS CLEAR.
- HOW UNUSUAL.
- HMM?
- THE SURPRISINGLY EMOTIONAL
TONE OF YOUR WORDS.
- I'M ACTUALLY SURPRISED MYSELF.
( laughing )
PERHAPS I WAS INFECTED
WITH THE COGITO VIRUS.
- I DON'T FIND
THAT JOKE VERY AMUSING.
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING
TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
Re-l:
AN ANONYMOUS WHISPER.
WHEN YOU CAN SEE THE UNSEEN,
YOU CAN NO LONGER BE
YOUR FORMER SELF,
BUT ANOTHER SELF.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT,
AS LONG AS IT'S MY TRUE SELF.