- Man: THIRTY-FIVE.
- ( machines beeping )
- THIRTY-SIX.
THIRTY-SEVEN.
THIRTY-EIGHT.
THIRTY-NINE.
FORTY.
FORTY-ONE.
FORTY-TWO.
- NOT HIM.
NOT HIM.
NOT HIM!
NO!  NO!  NO!  NO!  NO!
THEY'RE ALL WRONG!
- THAT'S EVERYONE
WE HAVE ON RECORD.
- IT'S SOMEONE YOU SAW
FOR A SPLIT SECOND
RIGHT BEFORE YOU BLACKED OUT.
MAYBE ONE MORE PASS,
BUT GO SLOWER.
- VERY WELL.
FROM THE BEGINNING.
- ARE YOU ALL IDIOTS?
I TOLD YOU HE'S NOT
ON THE LIST.
THE THING THAT ATTACKED ME.
- STILL INSISTING
ON THE MONSTER STORY.
- WHY DON'T YOU EXAMINE
THE CRIME SCENE CLOSELY?
WE CAN GO RIGHT NOW
IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME.
- WE EXAMINED IT.  WE WENT OVER
EVERY LAST BIT OF DATA RECORDED
BY YOUR HOME SURVEILLANCE SYSTEM
AND BY YOUR ENTOURAGE
TO SEE IF THERE WAS ANYTHING
TO SUPPORT YOUR STATEMENT
AND FOUND NOTHING.
- IT'S A CONSPIRACY.
THE SECURITY BUREAU MUST HAVE
ERASED DATA THEY DIDN'T LIKE.
THE INTELLIGENCE BUREAU--
NO, THE ADMINISTRATIVE BUREAU
HAS BEEN BETRAYED!
- VITAL SIGN REPORT.  HEART RATE
IS RISING TO STRESS LEVELS.
- MIND YOUR OWN DAMN BUSINESS.
- PLEASE UNDERSTAND
AND REMAIN CALM,
SINCE YOU ARE THE REGENT'S
GRANDDAUGHTER.
- DON'T PATRONIZE ME,
YOU BASTARD.
BEING HIS GRANDDAUGHTER MAKES
YOU A SUITABLE TARGET
BY IMMIGRANTS WHO LACK COMPLETE
CONTROL OF THEIR EMOTIONS.
- FOR EXAMPLE,
LAST NIGHT WE FOUND A MAN LYING
UNCONSCIOUS NEARBY YOUR HOME.
THIS ONE.
- What were you doing there?
Explain your reasons again
following standard procedure.
- Well, I was there
because I was told
that someone reported
an infected AutoReiv there.
- This report
was not confirmed.
- But I'm not lying.
If you take a look
at the facility's records.
- Man: VINCENT LAW.
WE'VE BEEN TOLD THAT HE
SUPPOSEDLY HAS DEVELOPED
PERSONAL FEELINGS FOR YOU.
PERHAPS HE COULD HAVE BEEN
YOUR STALKER.
- STALKER?  DO YOU THINK
HE WOULD HAVE THE GUTS?
THIS IS A WASTE OF TIME.
- ...from the start.
- Registration number 072...
- THE FACE OF A FELLOW CITIZEN.
THE FACE, THE FACE.
- My name is Vincent Law.
I work for the AR Disposal Unit,
FG Temporary...
- FELLOW CITIZENS,
THE TIME IS NOW TO CONSUME.
WHY SKIMP
WHEN YOU DESERVE MORE?
- Iggy: AND THEY SAID
YOUR NEW REPLACEMENT HOME
WILL BE READY IN SIX HOURS.
Re-l: IN THAT CASE, I WANT
TO STOP BY THE CENTRAL MALL.
I'LL GO ON A SHOPPING RAMPAGE
AND GET SOME SHOES, A BELT,
UNDERWEAR, SHAMPOO,
RINSE, MOISTURIZER
AND A TOOTHBRUSH.
- OH, NO.
YOU MUSTN'T DO THAT.
I KNOW YOU WANT TO FIND
AN OUTLET FOR YOUR FRUSTRATION,
BUT FIRST WE NEED TO GO
TO DAEDALUS' PLACE.
THEY SAID YOU NEED AN OFFICIAL
NOTE FROM THE DOCTOR
IN ORDER TO RETURN
TO THE INTELLIGENCE BUREAU.
- IT'S JUST A SCRATCH.
IT'S NOTHING SERIOUS.
- IT'S NOT JUST
YOUR PHYSICAL HEALTH.
YOU'VE HAD QUITE A SHOCK.
IT MAY HAVE AFFECTED YOUR MIND.
- GIVE ME A GODDAMN BREAK.
- HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT
WHEN THERE'S NOTHING
ABOUT THE MONSTER FROM LAST
NIGHT RECORDED INSIDE
THAT HEAD OF YOURS?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
RE-L, YOU SHOULD CHEER UP.
YOUR HOME LOOKS LIKE IT
WAS PRACTICALLY BLOWN UP.
IT'S A MIRACLE THAT YOU ESCAPED
WITH SUCH MINOR INJURIES.
I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
EVEN AFTER ALL YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH, YOU SURE ARE TOUGH.
- SO HOW'S THE MURDER
INVESTIGATION GOING?
- OH, ABOUT THAT.
- ( gasps )
HOW CAN YOU RELIEVE ME
FROM MY DUTIES?
- THE ORDER CAME FROM ABOVE.
THEY SAID YOU WERE
INJURED LAST NIGHT.
- ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT THIS SCRATCH?
- NO, IT'S FROM
THE SECURITY BUREAU.
- IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY,
THE REPORT STATED THERE
WAS A PROBLEM
REGARDING YOUR MENTAL CONDITION,
SOMETHING AS A RESULT
FROM THE SHOCK.
- A PATHOLOGICAL LYING EFFECT.
- Re-l: THAT SOUNDS LIKE
SOMETHING THEY'D THINK UP.
- Iggy: RE-L, SETTLE DOWN.
YOUR HEART-RATE IS--
- MIND YOUR OWN DAMN BUSINESS.
IN THAT CASE,
HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
WHAT HAPPENED
AT THE OLD IMMIGRATION BUREAU?
THOSE MARKS WE FOUND
WEREN'T LEFT BY AN AUTOREIV.
- YESTERDAY?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- ( gasps )
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THEY'VE EVEN ERASED HIS RECORD
OF THE INVESTIGATION.
- IN ORDER FOR YOU
TO RETURN TO WORK,
FIRST WE NEED TO SEE
A PSYCHIATRIC EVALUATION
FROM YOUR DOCTOR.
- DR. DAEDALUS, RIGHT?
HOW NICE TO HAVE THE HEALTH
AND WELFARE BUREAU'S CHIEF
AS YOUR PHYSICIAN.
- THE HEALTH
AND WELFARE BUREAU.
- THERE, YOU SEE?
YOU'LL RECEIVE A KISS
FROM THE PRINCE
AND THEN YOU'LL BE ALL BETTER.
- I GUESS SO.
VERY WELL THEN.
DO I HAVE AN APPOINTMENT?
- HE SAID YOU'RE
WELCOME ANY TIME.
- WAIT.  WHERE ARE YOU GOING
SO SUDDENLY?
- OH, TAKE CARE THEN.
- THE SECURITY BUREAU'S
GOING OUT OF CONTROL.
THE INTELLIGENCE BUREAU'S
SILENCE.
IGGY'S DATA BEING ERASED.
THEY'RE ALL CONNECTED
TO THE MONSTER.
THE POINTS ARE FORMING
A LINE.
THAT'S RIGHT, ISN'T IT,
GRANDFATHER?
- THIS WAS THE ESCAPE ROUTE
WE PREDICTED.
SO IT HAS GONE
COMPLETELY OFF-COURSE.
- IT CAME BACK TO THE CITY EVEN
AFTER MAKING IT ALL THE WAY
TO THE IMMIGRANT DISTRICT
IN THE OUTER BLOCK.
SO IT SEEMS THE PROXY
WAS AFTER RE-L.
- I WAS NOT EXPECTING YOU
TO SAY THAT.
ANY TRACES LEFT
BY THE PROXY AT THE SCENE
WERE ELIMINATED
AFTER WE RECORDED THEM.
WE'VE ALSO LIFTED
THE RESTRICTIONS PLACED
ON RE-L MAYER.
- I UNDERSTAND.
AFTER ALL, WE CAN'T ASK THE
REGENT FOR ANY ADDITIONAL TIME.
IF WE'RE FINISHED
WITH THE FORMAL QUESTIONING,
WE CAN RELEASE THE IMMIGRANTS
AS WELL
SINCE THEY AREN'T
REALLY SUSPECTS.
- CONFIRMED.  WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SEE THE GIRL'S STATEMENT?
- NO, SHE SIMPLY SUFFERED FROM
A CASE OF TEMPORARY INSANITY
AS A RESULT
OF THE STALKER ATTACK
AND WAS IN SO MUCH SHOCK
THAT SHE COULDN'T DISTINGUISH
BETWEEN REALITY AND ILLUSION.
- AS IS OFTEN THE CASE
WITH HUMANS, ISN'T IT?
FOR ADDED ASSURANCE,
I ARRANGED FOR HER TO SUBMIT
WRITTEN PSYCHIATRIC EVALUATION
FROM HER DOCTOR AS A CONDITION
FOR HER RELEASE.
- BEAUTIFUL.
- NOW NO ONE WILL BELIEVE
HER TESTIMONY
ABOUT WHAT SHE REALLY SAW,
WILL THEY?
- THE SECRET OF THE PROXY
TAKES PRIORITY ABOVE ALL ELSE.
- YES, A PSYCHOLOGICAL WAR,
ISN'T IT?
- SHE MAY BE
THE REGENT'S GRANDDAUGHTER,
BUT SHE CAN'T INTERFERE.
- VERY WELL THEN.
I'LL HAVE THEM CONTINUE
WITH THEIR SEARCH FOR THE PROXY.
- YES.
- DOES IT HURT?
- IT'S OKAY.  THANK YOU.
YOU'RE MAKING
TOO MUCH FUSS.
- IN ANY CASE,
I'M GLAD YOU'RE SAFE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WOULD DO
IF SOMETHING...
- IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
BUT IF YOU REALLY FEEL THAT WAY,
I WISH YOU'D BELIEVE ME.
HUH?
- HUH?
- "HIGHLY SUGGESTS A CASE
OF FANTASTIC PSEUDOLOGY"?
THEY GOT TO HIM.
ALL THE SAME, DAEDALUS,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
NOT HAVING ANYONE
WHO'LL BELIEVE ME?
- I SEE.
- I SAW THE MONSTER
WITH MY OWN EYES.
- I WANT TO BELIEVE YOU.
THAT'S WHY I'D LIKE TO EXAMINE
YOUR MIND A LITTLE MORE.
- IT'S NOT A DELUSION.
PLEASE, BELIEVE ME.
- RE-L!
ALL RIGHT, I UNDERSTAND.
- EVEN I CAN'T TELL ANYMORE
WHAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE REAL
AND WHAT'S SUPPOSED
TO BE A DREAM.
- YOU'RE CONFUSING
YOUR MEMORIES.
BEFORE WE CONSIDER COUNSELING,
I THINK WE SHOULD TRY
AND RUN A DETAILED BRAIN SCAN.
IT'LL TAKE SOME TIME FOR US
TO SET EVERYTHING UP.
WILL YOU BE ALL RIGHT?
- IF YOU SAY SO, DAEDALUS.
- WE'LL START SETTING IT ALL UP.
- "SPECIMEN.  PROXY."
- SORRY.  DIDN'T MEAN
'TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
- OH, NO PROBLEM.
- ( cooing )
- I CAN'T WAIT FOR YOU
TO MEET HIM.
HE'S COMPLETELY ADORABLE.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
I'LL GO ON AHEAD.
- Girl: EVERYTHING IS READY
FOR US TO LEAVE NOW.
- ( gasps )
YOU STARTLED ME.
APPLICATION ON.
- ( beeps )
- Iggy: HOW DID IT GO?
- Re-l: PHYSICALLY, I'M FINE.
MENTALLY, IT ALL DEPENDS
ON THEIR REPORT.
- WONDERFUL.
NOW LET'S GO TO THE MALL.
- BUT BEFORE THAT, IGGY, THERE'S
SOMETHING I WANT TO REFERENCE.
- GO RIGHT AHEAD.
CONNECT ME TO THE MAIN
INTELLIGENCE BANK.
- ( beeps )
- YOU ARE CONNECTED.
- ENTER THE WORD "PROXY."
- CONNECTION TERMINATED.
FORCED CUT OF TURING APPLICATION
FROM LANGUAGE FIELD.
UNRECOGNIZABLE WORD STRING.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO RE-ENTER?
- I KNEW IT.
TURING ON.
- SO, RE-L, WHAT WOULD
YOU LIKE TO LOOK UP?
- FORGET ABOUT IT.
- WHAT'S WITH YOU?
- ( beeps )
- HOLD ON A SEC.
IT'S AN EMERGENCY CALL
FROM YOUR GRANDFATHER.
- HE'S MONITORING IGGY.
- IT'S ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED YESTERDAY.
SHALL WE GO
AFTER WE DO OUR SHOPPING?
- LET'S JUST GO.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
- Woman:
WE WERE JUST DISCUSSING YOU.
- I'M VERY SORRY.
I APOLOGIZE FOR IGNORING
YOUR CALLS THESE PAST FEW DAYS.
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
HOWEVER, THE PROBLEM THAT WE
NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT IS--
- PROXY.
- YOUR NEGLIGENCE
IN FOLLOWING PROCEDURES.
- Woman: SOMETIMES COOPERATION
WITH THE SECURITY BUREAU
IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN YOUR OWN EGO.
- WHAT'S A PROXY?
- Woman #2: RE-L,
I CANNOT UNDERSTAND
IF YOU WON'T TELL ME ANYTHING.
- ARE YOU IGNORING ME?
IT'S BECAUSE I'M GETTING
TO THE HEART OF THE MATTER,
ISN'T IT, GRANDFATHER?
- Woman #2: IF YOU DO NOT WISH
TO ANSWER, THAT WILL BE ALL.
- PLACE HER UNDER THE AUTHORITY
OF THE ADMINISTRATIVE BUREAU.
- IT IS DONE.
- JUST A MINUTE.  HUSSERL!
BERKELEY!  YOU CAN'T JUST
DECIDE THIS.
LACAN.  DERRIDA.
GRANDFATHER.
- Woman: RE-L.
THEN PROMISE ME THIS.
THAT YOU WILL NO LONGER TAKE
THINGS INTO YOUR OWN HANDS.
AGREED?
- DERRIDA.
- IF YOU REFUSE,
THEN LIKE BERKELEY SAID,
FROM NOW ON, YOU WILL BE PLACED
UNDER THE SUPERVISION
OF THE ADMINISTRATIVE BUREAU.
- THEN I MUST AGREE.
- RE-L HAS GIVEN US
HER WORD.
- NOW GO.
- CAN IT BE?
- IT'S TIME
FOR YOUR APPOINTMENT.
- HUH?  IT ALREADY TIME?
- IS THAT A REPORT
FROM THE LAB?
WHY DON'T I TAKE OVER
FROM HERE?
- THAT'S NOT NECESSARY.
I'M ALMOST DONE,
BUT COULD YOU MAKE SURE
THAT A CAR IS READY TO GO?
- AS YOU WISH.
- THERE WERE TWO PROXIES.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
- I JUST LOVE YOUR NEW PLACE,
DON'T YOU?
AND YOU'VE GOT A GREAT VIEW
FROM HERE AS WELL.
RE-L?
- OH, I'M SORRY.
WERE YOU SAYING SOMETHING?
- SO DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
WITH THE PRINCE?
- IGGY, I KNOW YOU'RE
BEING MONITORED BY THEM.
I'M SORRY.
- RE-L, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I'M JUST GOING TO GO
GET A CHANGE OF CLOTHES.
- GO GET?  BUT I THOUGHT
YOUR PLACE WAS STILL UNDER
THE CONTROL
OF THE SECURITY BUREAU.
- I WANNA GO OUTSIDE
AND CLEAR MY HEAD.
BESIDES, I'VE BEEN WEARING
THESE THINGS SINCE YESTERDAY.
STARTING TOMORROW I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M GONNA DO ABOUT CLOTHES.
- WELL, WHY DON'T YOU TAKE THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO BUY A NEW OUTFIT?
YOU DON'T REALLY NEED TO GO
TO THAT PLACE, DO YOU?
- IT'S NOT ENOUGH FOR
GRANDFATHER TO KEEP TABS ON ME.
NOW HE WANTS TO GUIDE ME?
WELL, THERE'S NOTHING I LIKE
IN THE STORES.
- WHAT?  BUT JUST THIS MORNING
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT
GOING ON A SHOPPING RAMPAGE.
HOLD ON.
I KNOW A GREAT PLACE.
WE CAN GO THERE TOGETHER.
HOW ABOUT THIS ONE?
THE COLOR'S IN SEASON
RIGHT NOW.
RE-L?
- FELLOW CITIZENS,
DO YOUR PART AND MAKE WASTE.
LIFE IS EASIER
WHEN YOU LIGHTEN THE LOAD.
THE TIME IS NOW TO CONSUME.
WHY SKIMP
WHEN YOU DESERVE MORE?
- ( baby cooing )
- ( woman screams )
- ( man grunts )
- THAT'S--
- ( shouting )
- ( clamoring )
- CHIEF RAUL.
THE SECURITY BUREAU IS
AWAITING INSTRUCTIONS.
- REQUEST EMERGENCY DEPLOYMENT
OF ARMED AUTOREIVS.
SEAL OFF ROETHELIS PARK
AND THE SURROUNDING AREAS
COMPLETELY.
USE THE PARTITIONS.
- AS YOU WISH.
- ( snarling )
- ( panting )
- CURRENT STATUS REPORT.
- FORTY-TWO DEATHS INCLUDING
BOTH ADULTS AND CHILDREN.
FORTY-EIGHT PEOPLE INJURED.
ALL CIVILIANS WHO WERE
IN THE MALL ARE BEING KEPT
IN AN ISOLATED FACILITY.
- AND THE SPECIMEN?
- IT BROKE THROUGH THE PARTITION
AND REMAINS AT-LARGE.
HERE'S THE SURVEILLANCE MONITOR
FROM DISTRICT N-31.
IT IS NOW BELIEVED THAT
THE SPECIMEN HAS ALREADY
REACHED THE LOWER DISTRICT.
- ( gasps )
( steps on glass )
IT WAS NOT A DREAM.
THAT THING WAS IN HERE.
( sobbing )
- ( door opens )
- IT'S PAPA.
( gasps )
- ( grunting )
DAMN IT.
DAMN IT!
( grunting )
- IT WAS HIM.
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING
TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
- Re-l: WISE MEN FALLING
FROM EXHAUSTION.
INTERSECTING CLUES.
A MISSING IMMIGRANT'S FAILURE
TO APPEAR WHEN SUMMONED.
WHEN THE DRAMATIC CHASE
REACHES AN END,
THE PORTAL TO UTOPIA OPENS.