- Woman: QUESTION.
WHAT PHILOSOPHER REFERRED
TO MAN AS A THINKING REED?
- UH...
- ( buzzer )
- QUESTION.  WHICH ANCIENT
GREEK MATHEMATICIAN
DISCOVERED THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN THE LEGS AND HYPOTENUSE
OF A RIGHT TRIANGLE?
- UH...
- ( buzzer )
- QUESTION.  THE ENGLISH
NOVELIST LYTTON WROTE,
THAT THE PEN IS
MIGHTIER THAN THE WHAT?
- PEN IS-- SWORD!
- ( beeps )
- QUESTION.
THE PHENOMENON WHERE SOUND
APPEARS TO BE HIGHER PITCHED
AS IT IS APPROACHES AND LOWER
PITCHED AS IT IS LEAVES
IS CALLED?
- THE UH... SOMETHING EFFECT.
- ( buzzer )
- QUESTION.
- WATER IS
AT ITS HIGHEST DENSITY
AT HOW MANY DEGREES CELSIUS?
- DON'T KNOW!
- ( buzzer )
- QUESTION.
WHAT NUMBER QUESTION ARE WE ON?
- QUESTION NUMBER SIX.
- ( beeps )
- QUESTION.
WHO INVENTED DYNAMITE?
- MR. DYNAMITE.
- ( buzzer )
- QUESTION.  THE ASTRONOMICAL
UNIT IS A MEASUREMENT BASED
ON THE AVERAGE DISTANCE
BETWEEN WHAT TWO PLACES?
- ( buzzer )
- QUESTION.
WHAT IS THE TITLE
OF THIS SONG?
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD UNWINDS ♪
♪ INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL ♪
♪ MY PLACE ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- ( cheering )
- JUST INCREDIBLE!
YOU GET ALL THOSE ANSWERS WRONG
AND THEN NAIL THE SONG TITLE.
HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN THAT?
AMAZING.
HELLO, GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
THANKS FOR JOINING US TONIGHT.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY TO...
- All: Q-Q-Q-Q!
- IT'S THAT TIME AGAIN.
AS ALWAYS,
I'M YOUR HUMBLE HOST MCQ.
THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
REALLY, YOU'RE TOO KIND.
YOU'RE NOT TIRED
OF SEEING MY HANDSOME FACE?
NO, DON'T SAY THAT.
SO LET'S BEGIN.
AS ALWAYS, WE START BY LAYING
DOWN THE RULES OF THE GAME.
SO LET'S Q-Q-Q-Q!
- Woman: THE RULES
FOR THE QUIZ ARE SIMPLE.
THE CONTESTANT MUST SCORE ONE
MILLION POINTS IN 30 MINUTES.
IF HE ANSWERS
OUR QUESTIONS CORRECTLY
AND SAFELY REACHES
THE ONE MILLION POINT GOAL,
THEN HE WALKS AWAY
WITH THESE FABULOUS PRIZES.
AS A BONUS, WHEN THE CONTESTANT
REACHES ONE MILLION POINTS,
OUR HOST MCQ WILL DIE!
- YOU WIN AND I'M...
THAT'S RIGHT, FOLKS.
THE MOMENT A CHALLENGER WINS,
OUR SHOW IS OVER FOR GOOD.
SO FAR I'VE MANAGED TO GET THE
BEST OF 25 CONTESTANTS IN A ROW.
A VICTORY TODAY WILL GIVE US
A FULL TWO SEASONS ON THE AIR.
DO YOU FOLKS THINK WE CAN
MAKE IT?
WHAT HAPPENS IF OUR CONTESTANT
DOESN'T MAKE A MILLION POINTS?
LET'S HAVE OUR LOVELY ANNOUNCER
MELODY EXPLAIN IT TO US.
- IF HE DOESN'T REACH
ONE MILLION POINTS,
THEN I'M AFRAID
THE CHALLENGER DIES.
SO DO YOUR BEST
AND HOPEFULLY YOU'LL SURVIVE.
- I JUST LOVE THE WAY YOU LAY
OUT THE RULES EACH WEEK, MELODY.
ALL RIGHTY, LET'S GET STARTED.
"THE NIGHTMARE QUIZ SHOW!"
ONE MILLION POINTS...
- All: IN 30 MINUTES!
LET'S GET TO KNOW
OUR CONTESTANT.
WHO IS TODAY'S CHALLENGER?
THIS STRANGER WHO CAME TO US OUT
OF THE BARREN FROZEN WASTELAND.
- SAY HELLO TO VINCENT LAW,
FROM ROMDEAU.
- ROMDEAU, HUH?
YOU'VE COME QUITE A LONG WAY
TO BE HERE TONIGHT, RIGHT?
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- OKAY, GOT A GENIUS HERE.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE GOT HERE.
SAYS YOU'RE UNEMPLOYED
WITH NO FIXED ADDRESS.
- ( audience booing )
- HAD A BIT OF BAD LUCK LATELY.
AND YOU'RE LOOKING
A LITTLE THIN, TOO.
NO ONE EVER SAID LIFE WAS EASY.
HARD TO EVEN EAT WHEN
YOU'RE DOWN ON YOUR LUCK.
CHEER UP.
ON OUR SHOW YOU HAVE THE CHANCE
TO TURN THAT BAD LUCK AROUND.
SO DO YOUR BEST
AND TRY TO WALK AWAY
WITH THOSE FABULOUS PRIZES.
- YEAH, SURE.
- SO LET'S SEE HOW MANY
POINTS HE HAS.
- Melody:
A TOTAL OF 90,000 POINTS.
- JUST 90,000 POINTS?
NOT OFF TO A VERY GOOD START,
ARE WE?  ARE YOU GONNA BE OK?
- UH, YEAH.
- RIGHT.
NOT A TALKER, IS HE?
ARE YOU NERVOUS?
OR MAYBE YOU GOT SOMETHING
UNDER YOUR SLEEVE.
WELL, HE MAY BE UNEMPLOYED
WITH NO FIXED ADDRESS,
BUT HE DOES HAVE SOME FRIENDS
WHO'VE COME TO CHEER HIM ON
FROM OUR SUPPORTERS BOX.
I CAN'T TELL WHAT
THEY'RE SAYING,
BUT YOU CAN SURE SEE
THEY'RE ROOTING FOR HIM.
- DURING THE PROGRAM, WE'LL BE
HAVING OUR "CATCH THE MISTAKE"
QUIZ FOR OUR VIEWERS AT HOME.
SO KEEP AN EYE OUT.
- THEY GO BY QUICK,
SO MAKE SURE YOU STAY SHARP.
AND THAT GOES FOR OUR
STUDIO AUDIENCE AS WELL.
DON'T MISS YOUR CHANCE.
YOU MIGHT BE TONIGHT'S WINNER!
AND HERE WE GO AGAIN.
OUR NEXT QUIZ STARTS NOW.
IT'S THE "WHO AM I?" QUIZ.
TELL US THE RULES.
- THE WHO AM I? QUIZ.
IN A FEW MOMENTS,
THOUGHTS AND IMAGES RELATED
TO A CERTAIN PERSON WILL BE
REVEALED TO YOU ONE AT A TIME
IN THE PANELS ON THE SCREEN.
USING THESE CLUES,
YOUR JOB IS TO TELL US
WHO YOU THINK WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
THE SOONER YOU ANSWER CORRECTLY,
THE MORE POINTS YOU'LL GET.
- WOW, IF YOU GUESS CORRECTLY
AFTER THE FIRST HINT,
YOU GET A WHOPPING
600,000 POINTS.
BUT EVERY TIME WE HAVE TO
GIVE YOU A NEW CLUE,
THE PRIZE IS REDUCED
BY 50,000 POINTS.
AND IF YOU ANSWER AFTER
ALL THE CLUES,
AND YOU ONLY GET 50,000 POINTS.
IF YOU'RE READY,
LET'S GIVE IT A TRY.
WHO AM I?
THEY LIKE TO WEAR BLACK.
IS IT SOMEONE
WHO'S VERY FASHION CONSCIOUS OR
MAYBE SOMEONE WHO'S IN MOURNING?
I'LL BE AMAZED IF YOU CAN
GET THIS WITH ONE CLUE.
THINK ABOUT IT.
- WEARS BLACK.
- A MEAN LOOK IN THE EYES.
SOMEONE WHO HAS MEAN
OR SCARY EYES.
IS IT SOMEONE SCARY OR MAYBE
IT'S SOMEONE WITH POOR VISION.
COME ON, VINCENT.
YOU CAN DO IT.
THEY APPEAR TO BE YOUNG, BUT
THEY'RE OLDER THAN THEY LOOK.
HE'S GOT AN ANSWER.
IF HE ANSWERS CORRECTLY NOW,
HE'LL WALK AWAY
WITH 450,000 POINTS.
HE'S SMILING.
SUCH CONFIDENCE.
SO LET'S HEAR YOUR ANSWER.
WHO AM I?
- RE-L MAYER.
- ( buzzer )
THEY LIKE TO WEAR BLACK.
THEY HAVE A MEAN LOOK
IN THEIR EYES
AND THEY MAY BE OLDER
THAN THEY APPEAR.
YOU GUESSED RE-L MAYER.
INCORRECT.
NICE TRY.  WE HAVE RE-L MAYER
WITH US IN THE SUPPORTERS BOX.
HEY, RE-L, VINCENT THINKS
YOU'RE JUST AN OLD HAG.
JUST KIDDING.
NOW BACK TO THE QUIZ.
OUR AUDIENCE IS HANGING
ON THE EDGE OF THEIR SEAT.
WHO AM I?
THEY CAN WITHSTAND THE COLD.
THAT WOULD MAKE ME WONDER
HOW THEY DO IN THE HEAT.
MAYBE IT'S SIMPLY SOMEONE
WITH A LOT OF ENDURANCE.
THEY'RE SHY.
THEY'RE THE TYPE OF PERSON
WHO DOESN'T WANNA TALK
WHEN YOU FIRST MEET THEM.
IT TAKES TIME FOR THEM
TO FEEL COMFORTABLE,
BUT ONCE THEY DO,
WHO KNOWS HOW INTIMATE THEY GET?
OH, THIS PERSON'S GOT
THEIR EYE ON VINCENT.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
I THINK THAT'S A PRETTY
IMPORTANT CLUE, DON'T YOU?
THEY'VE GOT THEIR EYE ON YOU.
DOES THAT MEAN OUR MYSTERY
PERSON IS SOMEONE YOU KNOW?
- ( beeps )
- ALL RIGHT, VINCENT.
ANSWER CORRECTLY RIGHT HERE
AND YOU'LL RECEIVE
350,000 POINTS.
WHO'S BEEN THINKING
ABOUT YOU A LOT LATELY?
- PINO.
- ( buzzer )
- IT'S JUST WHEN YOU SAID
THEY COULD WITHSTAND THE COLD,
THE ONLY THING I COULD THINK OF
WAS AN AUTOREIV.
- SERIOUSLY?  TAKE A LOOK.
DOES THAT LOOK LIKE
A MEAN LOOK IN HER EYES?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
PINO DOESN'T LIKE
TO WEAR A LOT OF BLACK
NOR DOES SHE LOOK YOUNGER
THAN SHE ACTUALLY IS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS AIRHEAD
ACT USUALLY WORKS OUT FOR YOU,
BUT I THINK IT'S TIME
TO TRY SOMETHING NEW.
- I AM TRYING HERE.
- IF YOU SAY SO.
NOW BACK TO THE QUIZ.
- THEY KEEP QUIET.
- NOT JUST QUIET.
THEY'RE TOUTED FOR BEING
TORTUROUSLY TIGHTLIPPED.
- THEY'RE QUIET
AND TEARFUL.
- THEY ARE PRONE TO TEARS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT ON THE EDGE.
I CAN SEE IT.
PRONE TO TEARS.
THAT'S A GREAT HINT.
VERY TRUE.
A VERY GOOD WAY TO PUT IT.
DEFINITELY SOMEONE WHO LIKES
TO WORK BEHIND THE SCENES.
I MEAN, COME ON,
THEY WEAR BLACK.
- WINNER.
- THEY ALWAYS WIN.
COME ON, YOU KNOW BY NOW,
DON'T YOU?
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
I CAN TELL THE ANSWER'S
ON THE TIP OF YOUR TONGUE.
NAKED UNDER BLUE SKIES.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT NAKED,
BUT BLUE SKIES?
YOU EVER SEEN A BLUE SKY?
NAKED UNDER BLUE SKIES.
BLUE SKIES OVER THEM
WHILE NAKED.
TIME'S RUNNING OUT
TAKE YOUR SHOT.
THIS IS IT.
YOUR LAST CHANCE.
OUR MYSTERY PERSON
LIKES TO WEAR BLACK,
HAS A MEAN LOOK IN THEIR EYES,
IS ACTUALLY VERY OLD,
DESPITE HOW THEY LOOK.
THEY CAN WITHSTAND THE COLD.
SHY AROUND STRANGERS.
GOT VINCENT ON THEIR MIND.
PRONE TO TEARS.
KEEPS THEIR MOUTH SHUT
FOR SOME REASON,
BUT ALSO HAS A HIDDEN SIDE.
THEY'RE A WINNER
AND NAKED UNDER BLUE SKIES.
WHO AM I?
- IT'S ERGO PROXY.
- ( buzzer )
- ( booing )
- OUCH!
NO.  CLOSE, BUT NO CIGAR.
THE ANSWER WAS...
- Melody: THE CORRECT
ANSWER WAS PROXY ONE.
- WHAT?  WHO?
- McQ: I'M AFRAID
THIS ROUND WAS A SHUTOUT.
DON'T WORRY NOW.
'CAUSE WE'RE MOVING RIGHT ALONG.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GUESS THE
PICTURE IN THE "MOSAIC" QUIZ.
- Melody: THE MOSAIC QUIZ
OR GUESS THE PICTURE.
IN A MOMENT, A PIXILATED IMAGE
WILL APPEAR ON THE MAIN SCREEN.
USING THE PIXILATED IMAGE
AS A CLUE,
YOUR JOB IS TO TELL US WHAT
THE PICTURE IS OF
AS SOON AS YOU THINK YOU KNOW.
A CORRECT ANSWER WILL
EARN YOU 200,000 POINTS.
- WELL, SHALL WE START?
HERE'S YOUR VERY FIRST PICTURE
SO NOW TELL US WHAT IT'S
SUPPOSED TO BE.  Q-Q-Q-Q!
- IT'S I GUESS--
I CAN'T SEE A THING
THROUGH THAT--
- REALLY?
THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY
SQUINTING A LITTLE BIT, VINCENT.
SOMETIMES THAT CAN HELP.
KEEP LOOKING.  IT'S THERE.
PERHAPS IT'S SOMETHING
YOU RECOGNIZE, SEEN BEFORE.
HEY, THERE'S SOMETHING MOVING.
- IT LOOKS LIKE A BLOB TO ME.
- BUT LOOK, IT'S GETTING BIGGER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT'S BEING
BRED, BORN AND RAISED.
YOU CAN SEE IT'S GROWING.
SOMETHING THAT MOVES AND GROWS,
SO IT MUST ALIVE.
- ALIVE, HUH?
OH, YES, IT'S ALIVE.
ALTHOUGH NOT QUITE.
I DON'T WANT TO GIVE IT AWAY,
BUT IT'S NOT EXACTLY ALIVE.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S ALIVE,
BUT IT'S A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
- IT LOOKS ALIVE.
- YES, NOT THAT THE FACT IS
ANYONE'S FAULT NECESSARILY.
I MEAN THAT NOBODY COULD
HAVE POSSIBLY FORESEEN
WHAT EVENTUALLY HAPPENED.
IT TOOK LONGER FOR THE PLANET'S
ENVIRONMENT TO RESTORE ITSELF
TO THE PROPER CONDITIONS THAN
THE CREATORS HAD EXPECTED.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY THEIR
CALCULATIONS GOT SO MESSED UP.
HERE'S A HINT.
TO SURVIVE WHAT HAPPENED,
THEY NEEDED TO BUILD THEMSELVES
A HUGE DOME.
COME ON, THAT WAS A BIG HINT.
WHAT'S IN THE PICTURE?
- PEOPLE.
- ( buzzer )
- ( audience clamoring )
- OOH!  SORRY, VINCENT,
THAT WAS A NICE TRY.
SO CLOSE.
- MANKIND, HUMANS,
MEN AND WOMEN.
- GOOD GUESSES.
WE'LL REVEAL THE ANSWER RIGHT
AFTER THESE IMPORTANT MESSAGES.
- Melody:
The plan went into effect
in a much harsher
awakening environment
than had been
originally anticipated.
What proved to be the greatest
hurdle for the creators
under these harsh conditions
was the overabundance of data
that had been preserved,
particularly
"The Origin of Species."
Within the major cities,
the need to adapt
to an ever-changing
and fiercely harsh environment
was unnecessary...
- WE KNOW IT'S SOME SORT
OF BROADCAST SIGNAL
OF UNKNOWN ORIGIN.
AN ANALYSIS OF ITS SOURCE
CONFIRMS THAT IT IS
BEING TRANSMITTED VIA SATELLITE
OF TERRESTRIAL ORIGIN.
- YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT SOMEONE
PUT A SATELLITE INTO ORBIT
JUST SO THEY COULD
BROADCAST THIS?
- IT LOOKS THAT WAY, SIR.
WE'RE CURRENTLY WORKING
WITH ALL RELEVANT DEPARTMENTS
TO DOUBLE CHECK
THE DOME'S JAMMING SYSTEM.
- RE-L.
- Melody: But to admit failure,
the creators had to acknowledge
that the true failure...
- VINCENT LAW.
- ( audience cheering )
- McQ: IT'S TIME WE MOVED ON
TO THE "TRIPLE CHANCE."
FOR THIS QUIZ,
ALL POINT VALUES ARE TRIPLED.
AND JUST FOR FUN, WE'LL HAVE
THREE CONTESTANTS PLAY.
RIGHT OVER HERE.
NOW ALL OF YOU,
GOOD LUCK AND DO YOUR BEST.
- VINCENT, WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON?
- HEY, LET'S TRY AND STAY
ON THE CARDS, YOUNG LADY.
- ( audience laughs )
- WELL, IT'S TIME
TO GET BACK TO THE QUIZ.
LET ME DIRECT YOUR EYES
TO THIS VIDEO PRESENTATION.
Q-Q-Q-Q.
- Melody:
THE HISTORY OF THE EARTH.
BILLIONS OF YEARS AFTER
THE UNIVERSE WAS CREATED
IN THE BIG BANG,
A STRANGE LITTLE PLANET WAS BORN
ON THE EDGE
OF AN ORDINARY GALAXY.
THE NAME OF THE PLANET
WOULD ONE DAY BE EARTH.
POOLS OF WATER BEGAN TO FORM,
BECOMING A MIRACULOUS OCEAN
WITH SEAWEED AND FISH.
MANY STRANGE THINGS HAPPENED
OVER THE NEXT FEW HUNDRED
MILLION YEARS.  LATER ON DRY
LAND, DINOSAURS APPEARED.
THUS BEGAN THE LAW
OF THE JUNGLE.
EAT, BE EATEN OR RUN AWAY.
SOON WE CAME
TO THE AGE OF MAMMALS.
HERE, OUR ANCESTORS WERE BORN.
IN ORDER TO CATCH HIS PREY,
ONE OF THE ANCESTORS BY CHANCE
RAISES THE BONE
HE'S HOLDING.
YES! THIS IS THE MOMENT WHEN THE
FIRST TOOL CAME INTO EXISTENCE.
WAY TO GO, HUMANS.
- THAT WAS AMAZING!
- NOW WHILE KEEPING THE HISTORY
OF THE EARTH IN MIND,
PREPARE TO WRITE YOUR ANSWERS
DOWN ON THE BOARDS
WE'VE GIVEN THE THREE OF YOU.
NOW IT'S TIME
FOR ANOTHER MOSAIC QUIZ.
WHAT'S IT MAKING?
Q-Q-Q-Q!
THIS IS RELATED TO THE BONE
THAT MONKEY WAS HOLDING.
GIVE IT SOME REAL THOUGHT.  TIME
TO PUT ON THOSE THINKING CAPS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
HERE'S A HINT-- AN EVOLVED TOOL.
YOU'RE GETTING WARMER.
I CAN TELL.
IT'S THE LAST ONE THEY MADE.
IT'S A BIG ONE.
BUT IT WAS RUSHED.
NOT EVERYONE COULD USE IT
SO IT WAS A BIT USELESS.  IT
FOSTERED WIDESPREAD RESENTMENT.
YOU MUST KNOW WHAT IT IS BY NOW.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO WITH YOU?
HERE'S A HINT-- SOMEONE USED IT
TO TRY TO GET AWAY FROM EARTH.
ALL RIGHT,
THINKING TIME'S OVER.
LET'S SHOW THE AUDIENCE
HOW OUR CONTESTANTS DID.
FIRST OFF, LITTLE PINO.
- YAY!
OH, MY.  YOU DREW
THE PIXILATED IMAGE.
INTERESTING, BUT NOT WHAT
WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
NEXT, MISS MAYER.
- ( buzzer )
- OKAY, VINCENT.
WOW!  AND THE NAME?
- OH!  THE NAME?
I DON'T KNOW.
- ( buzzer )
- OUCH!  TOO BAD.
WELL, WHY DON'T WE PEAK
BEHIND THE MOSAIC
AND GET THE ANSWER?
WATCH THIS VIDEO
AND Q-Q-Q-Q!
- Melody: THE CORRECT ANSWER...
THE APOCALYPSE IS AT HAND.
THIS IS MANKIND'S LAST BEST HOPE
FOR ESCAPE FROM A WORLD
THAT'S HEADING FOR DESTRUCTION,
HUMANITY'S VERY OWN TRUMP CARD.
SCIENCE HAD MADE INTERPLANETARY
EMIGRATION POSSIBLE.
THIS WOULD BE THE LAST TOOL
MANUFACTURED HERE ON EARTH.
COMPLETED THROUGH
THE INFUSION OF ULTIMATE WISDOM,
IT WAS A SPACESHIP BUILT
IN GEOSYNCHRONOUS ORBIT
AND REFERRED
TO AS "THE EVACUATION SHIP."
- THAT'S SO COOL.
- McQ: SO THE CORRECT ANSWER
WAS?
- Melody: THE CORRECT ANSWER
WAS "THE BOOMERANG STAR,"
AN INTERPLANETARY SHIP BUILT
BY THE HUMAN RACE LONG AGO.
- SO THE NUMBER OF POINTS
VINCENT CURRENTLY HAS IS?
- JUST 90,000 POINTS!
- ( sighs )
NOW, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
IT'S TIME FOR OUR
"FINAL BUZZ FOR YOUR LIFE"
ROUND.
CAN VINCENT MAKE IT
TO THE MILLION POINT MARK?
WE'LL FIND OUT NEXT.
- AND WE'VE CUT TO COMMERCIAL.
- HEY, THAT CLOSE-UP ON
THE LITTLE GIRL WAS AWFUL!
SHE WAS MAKING A FACE.
- SORRY.  WE'LL TRY
TO BE MORE CAREFUL.
- DON'T WORRY, FOLKS.  I WAS
JUST TALKING TO THE DIRECTOR.
- EXCUSE ME.
- I'M NOT ANGRY.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
- EXCUSE ME, MISS.  I NEED YOU
AND THE KID TO COME OVER HERE.
OKAY, WE'RE BACK ON
IN EIGHT, SEVEN,
SIX, FIVE, FOUR...
- "NIGHTMARE QUIZ SHOW."
GET ONE MILLION POINTS...
- All: ...IN 30 MINUTES.
- NOW IT'S TIME
FOR OUR "FINAL DO-OR-DIE" QUIZ.
ANSWER QUICK AND Q-Q-Q!
- Melody:
FINAL DO-OR-DIE QUIZ...
ANSWER QUICK AND Q-Q-Q.
YOU'LL RECEIVE 30,000 POINTS
FOR EACH CORRECT ANSWER.
FEEL FREE TO PASS
ON ANY QUESTION.
ANSWER AS MANY QUESTIONS AS YOU
CAN WITHIN THE ALLOTTED TIME.
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO REACH ONE MILLION POINTS.
- AND IF HE REACHES
ONE MILLION POINTS,
NOT ONLY DOES HE WIN,
I GET TO HAVE A GLORIOUS DEATH.
BUT IF HE FAILS,
THEN HE DIES.
WHO WILL LIVE?
WHO WILL DIE?
- Melody: READY.  START.
- QUESTION.  IN THE SECOND HALF
OF THE 21ST CENTURY,
THE MOST PROMISING ALTERNATIVE
ENERGY SOURCE TO FOSSIL FUELS
AND NUCLEAR POWER WAS MADE
BY COMPRESSED METHANE GAS
IN SOLID FORM,
AND THIS WAS CALLED?
- I DON'T KNOW.  PASS.
- ( buzzer )
- Melody: THE ANSWER WAS
METHANE HYDRATE.
- QUESTION.
THE ACCUMULATED METHANE HYDRATE
EXPLODED IN A CHAIN REACTION.
WHAT PERCENTAGE
OF LIVING CREATURES
ON PLANET EARTH WERE WIPED OUT?
- 100%.
- ( buzzer )
- Melody: THE ANSWER WAS 85%.
- HOW COULD IT HAVE BEEN 100%?
IF THAT WERE TRUE, EVERYONE
ON THE PLANET WOULD BE DEAD.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
- QUESTION.
THE PLAN TO RESTORE
THE HUMAN POPULATION
HAD A DOUBLE LETTER ACRONYM.
THOSE TWO LETTERS WERE
DOUBLE WHAT?
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE.
JUST TRY SAYING SOME LETTERS.
- R, A, O, M, P.
- THE ANSWER WAS DOUBLE P.
- ALL RIGHT!
THAT'S THE WAY TO DO IT.
( snaps fingers ) QUESTION.
WHAT WOULD THE HUMAN RACE
NO LONGER NEED
ONCE THEIR NUMBERS HAVE BEEN
PROPERLY RESTORED ON THE PLANET?
COME ON.  THERE'S ONE SITTING
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
- YOU MEAN IT'S ME?
- THE ANSWER WAS PROXY.
- OOH, SORRY.
YOU WERE SO CLOSE THAT TIME,
BUT HOLD ON A SECOND.
IT WASN'T THE EXACT
RIGHT ANSWER,
BUT I'M GONNA GIVE IT
TO YOU ANYWAY.
HEY, I'M A NICE GUY.
QUESTION.
AS A RESULT OF THE "DOUBLE P
PLAN" OR "PROXY PROJECT,"
THE NUMBER OF PROXIES THAT WERE
RELEASED ACROSS THE PLANET WAS?
A-- 30?  B-- 300?
C-- 3,000?
JUST THREE CHOICES.
- C.
- 3,000?  WOW!  WE'D BE
IN A HECK OF A LOT TROUBLE
IF THAT MANY
WERE RUNNING AROUND.
- THE ANSWER WAS B-- 300.
- ALL RIGHT, QUESTION.
WHAT IS THE PULSE
OF THE AWAKENING?
COME ON,
I WANNA SEE YOU NAIL THIS ONE.
THINK ABOUT YOUR SITUATION.
- PASS.
- THE ANSWER WAS CONCLUSION
OF THE PROXY PROJECT.
- CATCH UP.  QUESTION.
CARL GUSTAV JUNG WAS KNOWN
AS THE AUTHOR
OF "PSYCHOLOGY AND ALCHEMY."
JUNG WAS ALSO KNOWN
AS THE KING OF WHAT?
- UH--
- ( buzzer )
- THE ANSWER WAS KING
OF THE SUBCONSCIOUS.
- QUESTION.  HUMANITY HAD
A SECOND PLAN INVOLVING
THE CURRENT OUTBREAK
OF THE COGITO VIRUS.
WHAT WAS IT CALLED?  IT WAS THE
ANSWER TO AN EARLIER QUESTION.
VINCENT,
THIS IS YOUR BIG CHANCE.
- IT WAS SOME KIND OF PROJECT.
- ( buzzer )
- THE ANSWER WAS
THE BOOMERANG PROJECT.
- OH!  NEARLY HAD IT.
CHEER UP, VINCENT.
YOU'VE ALMOST FOUND YOUR GROOVE.
QUESTION.
THE EGYPTIAN GOD RA-- KNOWN
FOR HIS EYE THAT LOOKED HUMAN
BUT WAS SACRED--
WAS THE GOD OF WHAT?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
- OH!
- THE ANSWER WAS THE SUN.
- QUESTION.  BEETHOVEN'S 5TH
SYMPHONY IS COMMONLY REFERRED TO
AS THE WHAT SYMPHONY?
- IT'S FATE.
- QUESTION.   A PERSON WHO
TRAINS THE MIND IS A TEACHER.
WHAT IS SOMEONE
WHO MINDS A TRAIN?
- PASS.
- THE ANSWER WAS CONDUCTOR.
- OF COURSE.
- THE ANSWER WAS FAILURE.
- THAT HURT.
YES, THE ANSWER WAS SCHISM.
- ESCAPE.
- THE ANSWER WAS CONTRACT.
- SUBSTITUTE.
- ( beeps )
- OBLIVION WAS CORRECT.
- ( buzzer )
- THE ANSWER WAS AWAKENING.
- FIGHT.  ENJOY.
NO!  YEAH!
- THIS IS THE MOMENT OF TRUTH.
ANSWER CORRECTLY, YOU PASS
THE MILLION POINT MARK.
SO DOES THIS MEAN OUR SHOW
IS FINALLY COMING TO AN END?
VINCENT, WHAT IS YOUR ANSWER?
- LABYRINTH.
- ( beeps )
- THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU GOT IT!
AT LAST, THE MOMENT HAS ARRIVED.
"NIGHTMARE QUIZ SHOW."  HE GOT
OVER ONE MILLION POINTS...
- ...IN 30 MINUTES!
- THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
THANK YOU.
HEY, I ALMOST FORGOT.
IT'S TIME TO ANNOUNCE THE NAME
OF THE AUDIENCE MEMBER
WHO WON LAST WEEK'S
"CATCH THE MISTAKE" QUIZ.
BUT BEFORE THAT,
LET'S SEE THE MISTAKE.
- Melody: THE RED COY STREAMER
WAS MISSING TWO SCALES.
- WHICH MEANS,
THE WINNER IS--
IT'S MR. BALANCING TOY, WHO
WISHES TO REMAIN ANONYMOUS.
- WE'LL BE SENDING YOU
YOUR PRIZE RIGHT AWAY.
INCIDENTALLY,
FOR OBVIOUS REASONS,
TODAY'S "CATCH THE MISTAKE"
QUIZ WINNER
WILL RECEIVE THEIR PRIZE
WITHOUT IT BEING ANNOUNCED
ON NEXT WEEK'S SHOW.
AFTER ALL, THE SHOW'S OVER!
- ( gasps )
- ( audience booing )
- ♪ THANK YOU SO MUCH, MCQ ♪
♪ THANK YOU FOR ALL THAT
YOU'VE DONE... ♪
- I HAD NO IDEA.
- YOU'VE BEEN GREAT.
- I SAID I WASN'T...
GONNA CRY.
- ( audience cheering )
- YOU NEVER KNOW
WHEN YOU'LL HAVE TO SAY GOODBYE.
BUT FOR ME,
THAT MOMENT HAS FINALLY COME.
THE CHALLENGER VINCENT LAW
REACHED ONE MILLION POINTS
IN 30 MINUTES.
YOU REALLY GAVE IT YOUR ALL.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- I'M FINE.
- RIGHT AND SO, TO ALL OUR
LOYAL AUDIENCE MEMBERS
WHO STAYED WITH US HERE
TILL THE VERY END
AND SINCE THIS IS OUR LAST
EPISODE, ALLOW ME TO PRESENT
TO YOU ALL THE PROXY WHO'S
THE TRUE CHAMPION OF THE WORLD.
LET'S GIVE HIM A HAND.
THAT'S RIGHT, OUR NEW CHAMPION.
MAKE SURE YOU REMEMBER HIS FACE.
THAT'S HOW IT GOES.
I GUESS PROXIES WILL FIGHT
THE WAY PROXIES WILL FIGHT.
- LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, LOOK FOR
A SPECIAL ANNOUNCEMENT WE THINK
YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE AT THE END
OF THE PROGRAM.
STAY TUNED
AND BE SURE NOT TO MISS IT.
- HOW DID YOU LIKE
OUR FINAL PROGRAM?
I THINK WE REALLY WRAPPED
EVERYTHING UP WELL.
I'LL BE DEAD SOON,
SO GOOD NIGHT ALL.
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING
TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
NOW THE ENEMY WE'RE
STRUGGLING TO DEFEAT
SEEMS TO HAVE
ORIGINATED FROM HERE.
WE NEED TO PUT OUR HEADS
TOGETHER AND THINK THIS OUT--