- Vincent: SAD.
INCREDIBLY SAD.
AGAIN.
IT'S THE DREAM AGAIN.
AM I CRYING?
IT'S HIM.
( grunting )
I'M SAD.
AND YET, I'M ALSO LAUGHING.
UGH!
WAS I HIT?
TODAY'S THE DAY I SEE.
I'M ALMOST THERE.
( groans )
THE DREAM.
DREAM AGAIN. ( grunts )
( cell phone ringing )
- ( beeps )
- Re-l: Vincent,
where are you now?
- ( rock music playing )
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD UNWINDS ♪
♪ INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL ♪
♪ MY PLACE ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- ( busy tone plays )
( sighs )
- ( sighs )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IGGY'S STILL BEING MONITORED
BY MY GRANDFATHER.
IT'S NOTHING.
- HEY, RE-L.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
THE INTELLIGENCE BUREAU'S
DATA BANKS HAVE BEEN
ACCESSED 74 TIMES.
- WHAT'S MORE IS THAT DURING
THE SHORT TIME THEY WERE ONLY
ACCESSED BY UNKNOWN ACCOUNTS.
STRANGE, ISN'T IT?
- YES, IT IS.
THEY LOGGED-ON WITH THE HIGHEST
LEVEL OF AUTHORIZATION.
I BET THEY WERE ACCESSING IT
FROM THE SECURITY BUREAU.
- YOU WANT ME TO DO THAT?
- SO WHAT WERE THEY LOOKING FOR?
WHAT THE HELL?
- ( cell phone rings )
- DOROTHY.
- Dorothy:
VINCENT, OVER HERE.
- DOROTHY, WHERE ARE YOU?
THAT'S--
( shouts )
DOROTHY.
- VINCENT, OVER HERE.
- NO!
DAMN IT!
WHAT THE HELL DID I DO?
DAMN IT.
- TARGET HAS BEEN LOST.
- CONFIRMED.
INPUTTING UPDATED ESCAPE ROUTE
PROJECTION.
- YOU STILL DON'T EVEN HAVE
A CLUE AS TO WHERE IT IS.
- WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU FAIL
TO MANAGE THIS?
- EVERYTHING LEADS TO US.
- I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR ANY EXCUSES.
- BEAR IN MIND, YOU WILL NOT
BE GIVEN EVEN A MOMENT'S GRACE.
- Woman: WE WANT
TO BE REASSURED QUICKLY.
- Man: WE CAN REPLACE YOU
JUST AS EASILY.
- Man #2: SINCE THERE ARE AS
MANY ENTOURAGE-TYPE AUTOREIVS
AS THERE ARE STARS
IN THE SKY.
- Woman #2: I UNDERSTAND.
- ( panting )
HE'S NOT THERE, CHIEF.
- SEARCH CAREFULLY.
HE'S NOT JUST ANOTHER
INFECTED AUTOREIV.
- THIS COULD BE MY CHANCE
FOR A BIG PROMOTION.
- OH.
- WHAT'S A COMPANION MODEL
DOING HERE?
ARE YOU LOST?
HMM?  YOU'RE THAT--
YOUR NAME'S PINO,
ISN'T IT?
- PINO?
- ( phone beeps )
- ( busy tone playing )
- VINCENT LAW, WHERE ARE YOU?
- UM... UM...
IS PINO REALLY PINO?
IS PINO SUPPOSED TO BE PINO?
WELL, YOU SEE,
PINO IS REALLY--
- DON'T TALK SO LOUD.
DAMN TURING APPLICATION.
THAT'S WHY COMPANION AUTOREIVS
ACT LIKE THAT.
PLEASE, JUST STAY THERE,
ALL RIGHT?
- HUH?
- ALL RIGHT, JUST STAY THERE.
CAN YOU--
CAN YOU DO THAT?
- ( mutters )
- HEY, THAT'S--
- THIS?
- ( beeps )
( rings )
- NO, DON'T!
- HELLO THERE.  WHO IS THIS?
WHO IS THIS?  HELLO.
- VINCENT, IS THAT YOU?
- Inspector Re-l.
- WHERE ARE YOU NOW?
- Dorothy was--
it was an armed AutoReiv.
It wasn't me.  They--
The whole thing was a trap!
- CALM DOWN!
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DID THIS HAVE TO
HAPPEN TO ME?
IF I DON'T GET OUT OF HERE.
PLEASE, YOU'VE GOTTA HELP ME.
I DON'T-- I DON'T HAVE ANYONE
ELSE TO TURN TO.
I'M BEGGING YOU.
- WHAT CAN YOU SEE FROM THERE?
- I'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- ( metal screeching )
- OH!  LIGHT RAIL CROSSING.
A LITTLE FURTHER
AND THERE'S A--
ARE YOU TRYING TO LEAVE
THROUGH THE PLUG VENT?
- I can't take it anymore.
If they're gonna kill me, I
might as well go to the outside.
- AND YOU'LL FIND DEATH WAITING
FOR YOU.
- I'm sorry.
Doesn't look like I'll be
becoming a fellow citizen.
- VINCENT!
- I'M GLAD I COULD HEAR
YOUR VOICE ONE LAST TIME.
- I'M GOING TO MEET YOU
AT THE PLUG VENT.
JUST WAIT FOR ME.
Vincent!
- DAMN IT!
DAMN IT!
- HUH?
- LET'S LOOK FOR ANOTHER WAY.
- YOU DON'T NEED IT?
- IT'S HEAVY.
- WAIT FOR ME.
- THE SECURITY BUREAU.
- CAN'T GO THIS WAY, EITHER.
- ( shouts )
IS THIS A MAZE?
LET ME HAVE THE BAG.
MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING IN THERE
WE CAN USE FOR A LIGHT.
PINO?  PINO!
- THIS WAY.
- COULD IT BE?
DOES SHE KNOW?
- AGENT RE-L, WHERE ARE YOU
GOING IN SUCH A HURRY?
I NOTICE THAT YOU DIDN'T BRING
YOUR ENTOURAGE WITH YOU, EITHER.
- I'M GOING TO INSPECT
THE CRIME SCENE
IN THE IMMIGRANT RESIDENT
DISTRICT.
AS FOR MY ENTOURAGE,
HE'S 15 MINUTES BEHIND ME.
- I'M SORRY FOR THE DELAY.
GO AHEAD
AND PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
ALL OF THE AUTOREIV'S INFECTED
WITH THE COGITO VIRUS
FOLLOWED THE SAME ROUTE,
DIDN'T THEY?
IT DOESN'T MATTER
NOW THOUGH, DOES IT?
- ( laughs )
- IT'S A DEAD END, ISN'T IT?
( grunts )
HEY!
- HER INTUITION IS FAR TOO KEEN.
- I WONDER WHO
SHE MUST TAKE AFTER.
- THE CITIZENS ARE ALL MODELED
ON PRE-ARRANGED INFORMATION.
LOCAL APPROXIMATIONS
ARE MEANINGLESS.
- I KNEW WE SHOULDN'T
HAVE ASSIGNED HER
TO THE INTELLIGENCE BUREAU.
- NO, FROM AN EDUCATIONAL
POINT OF VIEW,
IT WAS THE RIGHT DECISION.
THE DATA SHOWS
AT THE CITIZEN LEVEL
HER MAXIMUM SENSITIVITY
HAS BEEN MAINTAINED.
A MOST SPLENDID OUTCOME.
- BUT IT IS THE DYNAMIC ENERGY
DERIVED FROM THAT,
WHICH IS THE MAIN CULPRIT.
- SPEAKING OF CULPRITS, WHAT
ABOUT THE SECURITY BUREAU?
- Man:
THERE'S NO CAUSE FOR CONCERN.
WE'VE MADE OURSELVES VERY CLEAR.
- Woman:
HOWEVER, THERE'S NO DENYING
THAT OUR ROMDEAU
HAS BEEN SHAKEN.
- Man #2:
WE MUST TAKE SWIFT ACTION
TO RESOLVE THE SITUATION
IMMEDIATELY.  OTHERWISE...
- Woman #2:
ITS RAISON D'ETRE WILL COLLAPSE.
THAT IS OUR ONLY CAUSE
FOR CONCERN.
- I KNOW YOU'RE HERE.
AREN'T YOU, VINCENT?
I CAME HERE BY MYSELF.
I'M ALSO COMPLETELY UNARMED.
- Vincent: WAIT.
- HELLO THERE.
- COME ON OUT, VINCENT.
- INSPECTOR RE-L.
I--
- I NEED TO KNOW,
WHY IS THE SECURITY BUREAU
CHASING YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WHAT DID YOU SEE
IN THE BATHROOM?
TELL ME.
- THE BATHROOM?
- THEN HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN THIS?
- HOW?  WHERE WAS IT?
- THE MONSTER.
- YOU MEAN THAT THING.
- WHAT DID YOU SEE?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I WAS SUDDENLY ATTACKED
IN THE MALL
AND THE SECURITY BUREAU
CAME AFTER ME.
INSPECTOR,
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING
TO ME?
- YOU SAW THE MONSTER.
THE PROXY.
YOU KNOW.
- PROXY?
- VINCENT LAW,
STAY WHERE YOU ARE
AND DO EXACTLY AS I TELL YOU.
- THE SECURITY BUREAU.
- YOU LIAR!
- VINCENT, I DIDN'T CALL THEM.
- THEN WHO? ( gasps )
- OUTSIDE.
- STOP IT.
- ( grunting )
- Re-l: VINCENT!
IGGY, I HAVE TO SAVE VINCENT.
- DON'T BE A FOOL.
- VINCENT!
- IN MY DESPERATE ATTEMPTS
TO BECOME A FELLOW CITIZEN,
I'VE CONSTANTLY
SUPPRESSED MYSELF
AND TRIED TO BE THE PERSON
I THOUGHT THEY WANTED.
CONSTANTLY.  EVERYWHERE.
- Re-l: VINCENT!
- AND LOOK WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO ME.
I'M A FAILURE.
- VINCENT!
LISTEN, I'LL TALK
TO MY GRANDFATHER.
THE SECURITY BUREAU WON'T
BE ABLE TO TOUCH YOU.
- DOUBTING THE SYSTEM IS BAD.
ALWAYS OBEY.
THOSE ARE THE CONDITIONS
FOR BEING A FELLOW CITIZEN.
- DON'T DO IT.
- BUT I'LL NEVER BECOME
A FELLOW CITIZEN.
IT'S OVER.
- WHY ARE THEY CLOSING IT?
WE MUST CAPTURE HIM.
- KEEPING IT OPEN ANY LONGER
WILL EXPOSE THE ENTIRE CITY
TO DANGER.
- VINCENT, WAIT!
VINCENT.
- IT'S OVER.
MY LIFE.
IT'S ALL OVER.
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING
TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
- Re-l: A MAN MISSING WHO WENT
INTO THE DARKNESS.
THE LABYRINTHINE MYSTERIES
THAT STILL REMAIN.
ULTERIOR MOTIVES HIDE BEHIND
THE SCENES IN PARADISE
AND BECKON THE LOST
TO THE LAND OF HADES.