- ( Vincent's voice )
THE UNCERTAIN LIGHT
REFLECTS THE PURPOSE
BEHIND MY JOURNEY...
BACK TO MY BIRTHPLACE.
DOES THE THING
I'M TRAVELING TO MOSK TO FIND
ACTUALLY EXIST?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR.
I RAN OUT OF FOOD
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
IT SEEMS THE ONLY THING
I FOUND ON THIS JOURNEY
IS A LONELY DEATH.
I'M ALL ALONE.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR--
- Rino: VINCE!
THERE'S SOMETHING
SHINING OVER THERE.
MAYBE IT'S
A PLAYING CARD SOLDIER.
- ( groans )
THOSE ARE JUST FROM A BOOK.
- ( Vincent's voice )
I'M NOT EXACTLY ALONE.
I HAVE SOMETHING
RESEMBLING A COMPANION--
AN INFECTED AUTOREIV.
- THERE'S A LIGHT.
- ( helicopter blades whirring )
- WHAT?
- ( rock music playing )
- ♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD
UNWINDS INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- A TOWER.
MAYBE IF WE HIDE
IN THE SHADOWS,
WE CAN AVOID
ANY MORE ATTACKS.
- FROM MY PRESENT LOCATION,
THAT'S 558 UNITS
HEADING ALONG
THE X-AXIS
AND 832 UNITS
ALONG THE Y-AXIS.
- I COULD USE LESS TALKING
AND MORE HELPING OVER HERE.
( grunting )
- ( rapid gunfire )
- AUTOREIVS?
PINO.
- DON'T MOVE.
- OKAY.
- THE MOSQUITO'S DOWN.
KEEP SEARCHING.
- HEY, DOES IT
TASTE GOOD?
- SO IT'S THIS WAY:
THE DOME CITY
YOU KEEP TALKING ABOUT--
- IT'S CALLED ROMDEAU.
- ARE YOU
THE CARD SOLDIERS?
- ARE WE THE WHAT?
- WE SAW THE SHINING LIGHT.
THAT'S WHY WE CAME.
- SHINING LIGHT?
THAT'S THE SAME THING
THAT WOMAN WAS SAYING.
- THERE ARE STORIES
ABOUT A MONSTER
THAT SLEEPS UNDERGROUND
OUT HERE.
- THAT'S NOTHING
BUT SUPERSTITION.
IT'S NOT RELEVANT.
- OH.  CAN I ASK A QUESTION
ABOUT SOMETHING?
WHY ARE YOU FIGHTING
THE AUTOREIVS?
- WHY ARE WE FIGHTING?
ONCE YOU'RE ON THE BATTLEFIELD,
IT'S BEST TO STOP ASKING
THOSE QUESTIONS.
- I DON'T GET IT.
- MM.
- IS IT TRUE THAT ONCE THEY'RE
INFECTED WITH THAT VIRUS,
WHATEVER IT IS,
THAT THEY GET A SOUL?
- I'M VERY SORRY,
I CAN'T ANSWER THAT.
- BUT, VINCE, I--
- WE'RE JUST TRAVELERS
PASSING THROUGH.
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY,
FOR YOUR HOSPITALITY,
ESPECIALLY THE FOOD.
- AND YOU CERTAINLY
DID EAT.
YOU'RE WELCOME, SIR.
- CALL ME VINCENT.
MY NAME IS VINCENT LAW.
- I'M LIEUTENANT OMAKATL.
AND THIS IS
COMMANDER PATEKATL.
UM, MAY I ASK YOU SOMETHING
ABOUT YOUR SAILBOAT?
- MY SHIP IS CALLED
THE SENSAN.
- WHAT'S ITS POWER SOURCE?
I'D ALSO LIKE TO KNOW
ITS AVERAGE CRUISING SPEED
AND RANGE.
- I'M AFRAID
I DON'T KNOW THAT.
- DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I DON'T KNOW.
- DON'T WORRY.
OUR PEOPLE ARE ALREADY
SEEING TO ITS RETRIEVAL.
YOU CAN LEAVE
THE REPAIRS TO US.
- I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO THANK YOU.
- YOU CAN THANK US
BY HELPING US--
HELPING US WIN
OUR BATTLE.
- WELL, I--
- Man: NO SIGN OF THE ENEMY
NEAR CHAROS.
- HMM.  CASUALTY REPORT.
- Man: WE HAVE NINE
CONFIRMED DEATHS
FROM PLATOONS ALPHA,
BETA AND GAMMA.
ALL TOLD, OUR BATTALIONS
CURRENTLY STAND AT 43 SOLDIERS.
SHALL I UP PRODUCTION?
- LET'S NOT OVEREXTEND OURSELVES
FOR THE LONG GAME.
WE'LL STAY CONSERVATIVE.
NO INCREASE.
- YES, SIR.
- EVERYONE, MAY I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION, PLEASE?
( over speaker )
First off,
I have some unfortunate news
to report.
We lost nine of our brave
soldiers in this last battle.
However, this is not
the time for grief.
We must remember our enemy
has a singular goal--
they wish to overrun
the production room
and the heart of our fortress--
the very body of our parents.
- EVEN IF THEY ATTACK US
IN GREAT NUMBERS,
SO LONG AS THEY HAVE
THIS SINGLE OBJECTIVE,
WE CAN ALWAYS ANTICIPATE
THEIR ATTACK.
- AS SOON AS THE AIRSHIP
IS REPAIRED,
YOU MAY COMMENCE
ITS ARMORED RETROFITTING.
- HUH?
- THERE'S NO NEED
TO HOLD BACK IN WAR.
FOR EXAMPLE, YOUR SHIP'S
MOBILITY AND FUEL EFFICIENCY
WILL COME IN PLENTY HANDY
ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
- OH.
- I KNOW,
BUT HUMANS MUST WIN
THIS WAR.
I ASSUME, AS A HUMAN,
THAT YOU UNDERSTAND,
MR. LAW.
- ( Vincent's voice )
GREAT.
I THINK
I'M IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
- ( groaning )
- HMM?
( groaning )
- SORRY.
WHERE'S THE BATHROOM?
- HMM.
MM.
- SORRY.
- THIS IS BETA FOUR,
REQUESTING PERMISSION TO LAND.
- ( toilet flushes )
- THIS IS PATHETIC.
- VINCE?
- I THINK I ATE TOO MUCH
TOO QUICKLY
AND MY STOMACH
COULDN'T QUITE HANDLE IT.
BUT I'M ALL BETTER NOW.
- ALL BETTER.
- ( Vincent's voice )
FOR SOME REASON, NOW I FEEL
CLOSER TO THIS INFECTED AUTOREIV
THAN I DO TO THESE PEOPLE.
IT DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE TWO OF US
TRAVELING TOGETHER
AT THE TIME.
ALL I WANTED WAS TO SEE
ANOTHER HUMAN BEING.
- SOMETHING'S WEIRD.
- HUH?
- THE PEOPLE HERE--
THEY'RE ALL WEIRD.
- YEAH.
ONCE THEY FINISH
REPAIRING THE SHIP,
WE SHOULD LOOK
FOR A WAY TO ESCAPE.
- ( Vincent's voice )
I'D FINALLY MANAGED
TO REACH CHAROS,
BUT I DIDN'T
BELONG HERE EITHER.
- PINO?
WHERE'D YOU GO?
- THERE WAS
SOMETHING SHINY.
- AGAIN?
ARE YOU SURE?
- YES.
IT WAS TWINKLING.
- COME ON.
- I'M COMING.
- IT'S AN AIRSHIP,
ALTHOUGH I'VE NEVER SEEN
ONE LIKE THAT BEFORE.
- YEAH, IT'LL BE NICE NOT HAVING
TO WORRY ABOUT A POWER SOURCE.
( grunts )
- WELL, CONSIDERING
THE MOSQUITO'S FLIGHT RANGE,
WE COULD SURE USE
THIS THING.
HMM?
HEY.
- I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
CAN'T YOU JUST TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON?
JUST TELL ME--
- WHO ELSE IS WITH YOU?
ASURANS DON'T KILL
LIKE THIS.
THIS WAS PERSONAL
AND MESSY,
LIKE IT WAS FUN.
OUR MEN WERE TORN APART,
AND SOMEONE ENJOYED IT.
- NO.
WHY WOULD I?
- WELL, IN THAT CASE,
HOW ABOUT THE AUTOREIV?
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
- BE THAT AS IT MAY,
THERE'S ONE THING
THAT'S FOR CERTAIN:
NONE OF THIS STARTED
UNTIL AFTER YOU TWO CAME.
- WAIT.
IT WASN'T ME.
- ( Vincent's voice )
NOT AGAIN.
- ( person breathing heavily )
- ( woman yelping )
- ( Vincent's voice )
AM I THE ANGEL OF DEATH?
EVERYTHING I TOUCH
STAINS WITH BLOOD.
EVERYONE AROUND ME DIES.
RE-L.
- ( metal clanging )
- ( woman mumbling )
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THOSE TWO?
- THAT STUFF
ABOUT THE LIGHT.
- THE WOMAN MENTIONED
THE SAME SORT OF THING.
- YOU MEAN THE STORIES
ABOUT LIGHT
RADIATING FROM
AN UNSEEN MOON?
ANYONE STUPID ENOUGH
TO LISTEN TO SUCH NON--
- REGARDLESS, LET'S LOOK
TO HAVE NO FURTHER INCIDENTS.
- COMMANDER, THE ASURAN ARMY.
- HUH?
- BIT BY BIT
IT CAN'T BE SEEN.
BIT BY BIT IT CAN'T
BE HEARD.
BIT BY BIT
IT GROWS STRONGER,
HERE, THERE, EVERYWHERE.
THE LAST BEAT.
THE MASTER COMES.
RIDING ACROSS
THE MOONLIGHT,
IT HAUNTS THE SHADOWS
IN THE DARK PLACES.
HE TAKES HIS TIME,
BIT BY BIT,
BIT BY BIT, BIT BY BIT.
- Woman and Rino:
BIT BY BIT.
- BIT BY BIT,
- Together: BIT BY BIT,
BIT BY BIT.
BIT BY BIT, BIT BY BIT.
- ( Vincent's voice ) MAYBE--
- BIT BY BIT, BIT BY BIT.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
- MAYBE INSIDE OF ME--
- BIT BY BIT.
BIT BY BIT.
- SOMETHING--
- ( woman screams )
- Rino: BIT BY BIT,
BIT BY BIT.
- THIS FEELING.
- Rino: BIT BY BIT.
- Woman: I HEAR...
- BIT BY BIT, BIT BY BIT.
- ...THE PULSE...
- BIT BY BIT.
- ...OF THE AWAKENING...
...ALONG THE MOONLIGHT
THAT HAUNTS THE DARKNESS.
IT WILL WITH CERTAINTY
PROVIDE THE TIME.
THE PULSE
OF THE AWAKENING,
THE LAST BEAT.
THE MASTER RIDES
ACROSS THE MOONLIGHT.
- Rino: VINCE.
- Vincent: NO.
HELP ME.
I DON'T WANT
TO CHANGE INTO--
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT WAS THAT THING?
WHAT WILL I BECOME?
JUST STOP IT.
- WE FAILED TO STOP
THE ENCROACHMENT IN AREA 32.
ASURAN TROOPS NUMBER
APPROXIMATELY 30 PER PLATOON.
THEY'RE NOW ADVANCING
TOWARDS AREA 15.
- THEY WANT THE MOSQUITO?
ALL PERSONNEL
TO BATTLE STATIONS.
DEFEND THE MOSQUITO
AT ALL COSTS.
I WANT TWO PLATOONS DEPLOYED
TO DEFEND THE PRODUCTION ROOM.
EVERYONE ELSE, HEAD TO
THE HELIPORT IMMEDIATELY.
- ( rapid gunfire )
- ( alarm whooping )
- NO.
PLEASE DON'T.
- ( man over headphone )
Commander, Asuran forces
have infiltrated
the underground facility.
Sir, they're going to--
- IT'S OVER.
- YOU COWARD!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WE CAN'T ALL FIT
IN THIS THING.
AND WE CAN'T REBUILD
OUR UNIT,
NOT WITHOUT
THE PRODUCTION ROOM.
- DAMN YOU.
WHAT THE--?
WHAT ARE YOU?
- GET US OUT OF HERE!
- SIR, LOOK.  IT'S THE THING
THAT WOMAN WAS TALKING ABOUT.
- JUST LIKE
THE LEGEND SAID.
- GOTCHA, YOU BASTARD!
- MOVE!  COME ON!
WHAT ARE--?
- ( screams )
- Woman: SENEX.
AGENT OF THE MOONLIGHT.
- ( Rino screams )
- Woman: THE DRUMS OF WAR
ARE BEATING.
IT IS THE MUSIC
THAT BRINGS
THE BIRTH
OF A NEW WORLD.
THE MASTER COMES,
RIDING ACROSS
THE MOONLIGHT
THAT HAUNTS THE SHADOWS
IN THE DARK PLACES.
IT'S ALL SO BEAUTIFUL.
- ( creature moaning )
- Woman: WHEN THE BATTLE'S DONE,
HE WILL BRING
TO THIS WORLD
A GIFT OF DEATH.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU STOP
THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET
SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN
CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪