- ( sighs )
I GIVE UP.
PINO?
( sighs )
OKAY, A BOOKSTORE.
- ( door unlatches, creaks )
- HELLO?
IS ANYBODY IN HERE?
I AM REALLY LOST RIGHT NOW.
HELLO?
- ( rock music playing )
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD
UNWINDS INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- Man: WELCOME
TO THE CITY LIGHTS BOOKSTORE.
YOU MUST BE TRAVELING.
WELL, ALL RIGHT,
COME WITH ME.
LET'S JUST GIVE THE TEA
A BIT OF TIME TO STEEP,
GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
SOUND GOOD?
OKAY.
SO YOU'RE TRAVELING.
- ACTUALLY, I THINK I'M LOST.
- YEAH, I FIGURED.
WE GET THAT A LOT AROUND HERE.
- WITH THAT FOG--
- THAT REMINDS ME OF SOMETHING.
A MAN SAID THE FUTURE
IS AN OPAQUE MIRROR.
ANYONE WHO TRIES
TO LOOK INTO IT SEES NOTHING
BUT THE DIM OUTLINES
OF AN OLD AND WORRIED FACE.
- MY SHIP--
IT'S RIGHT NEARBY.
- THE ANSWERS YOU SEEK
YOU WILL NEVER FIND
UNTIL YOU START
TO LOOK WITHIN YOURSELF.
IT'S HOW IT WORKS
WITH THESE THINGS.
- HAVE YOU SEEN A LITTLE-GIRL
TYPE AUTOREIV AROUND HERE?
HER NAME IS PINO.
SHE'S ABOUT--
- YOU'LL GET NOWHERE
IN A HURRY.
TAKE THIS TEA FOR EXAMPLE.
NOTHING THAT YOU DO
WILL MAKE IT STEEP ANY FASTER.
YOU CAN'T JUST RUN AROUND
TRYING TO DO EVERYTHING AT ONCE.
SO WHY NOT TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THE BOOKSTORE?
- YEAH.
SORRY FOR BEING IMPATIENT.
I WAS JUST GOING
TO ASK YOU FOR DIRECTIONS.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVE
A PRETTY IMPRESSIVE SHOP.
I GUESS I'LL HAVE A LOOK,
MAYBE FIND SOMETHING.
- GO ON.
PULL A BOOK OFF THE SHELF
AND GIVE IT A ONCE-OVER.
- ( snaps )
OH, DEAR, IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE THE POOR BOY'S
FIGURED IT OUT YET.
WELL, WE'RE PERFORMING
ON A VERY SPECIAL STAGE.
WE ARE,
IF YOU'LL PARDON THE EXPRESSION,
IN THE THEATER
OF HIS MIND.
CONSIDER THESE BOOKS.
FOR THEM TO EXIST,
SOCIETY MUST EVOLVE
TO AN APPROPRIATELY
ADVANCED STATE.
BUT FOR A SOCIETY
TO EVOLVE,
IT WOULD NEED THE LINGUISTIC
TOOLS THESE BOOKS CONTAIN.
I KNOW-- A BIT OF
A CHICKEN-OR-THE-EGG DILEMMA,
ISN'T IT?
EACH ONE'S CREATION
REQUIRES THE OTHER,
SO WHICH CAME FIRST?
IN THE FACE
OF SUCH A PARADOX,
ONE COULD REASONABLY ARGUE
THAT LANGUAGE IS PERHAPS
NOT ENTIRELY
A HUMAN INVENTION.
IS IT TOO FAR-FETCHED
TO IMAGINE GODLIKE CREATURES
BESTOWING MAN
WITH THE GIFT OF LANGUAGE?
MMM, IT'S PROBABLY
A BIT FAR-FETCHED.
IT WAS ROUSSEAU WHO FIRST
PUT FORWARD THIS ARGUMENT.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S PROBABLY
ENOUGH PHILOSOPHY FOR NOW.
TIME TO GET BACK
TO THE DISSECTION
OF THIS YOUNG MAN'S
PAST AND FUTURE.
WHO KNOWS WHAT TREASURES
WILL BE UNEARTHED BY THE--
- Male voice:
--FICKLE HANDS OF FATE?
( chuckling )
- ( snaps )
- WHY IS MY NAME ON THE COVER?
WHERE'D YOU GO?
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
NO, THEY'RE ALL--
I'M DREAMING.
- Male voice: THIS IS NOT
A DREAM, VINCENT LAW.
COME, OVER HERE.
- WHO'S THERE?!
DOROTHY.
- Male voice:
I AM NOBODY.
EVEN IF I WAS SOMEBODY,
I AM BEYOND
YOUR COMPREHENSION.
AND EVEN IF YOU COULD,
YOU WOULD NOT HAVE THE TOOLS
TO EXPRESS THAT KNOWLEDGE.
- CHIEF.
- THAT IS THE WAY IT HAS TO BE.
YOU ALREADY KNOW THIS.
- ( grunting )
I'M STILL DREAMING.
Male voice: THIS IS NOT
A DREAM, VINCENT LAW.
FROM THE PERSPECTIVE OF OTHERS
I AM PART OF THE WORLD.
BUT WHEN I OBSERVE THE WORLD
FROM MY PERSPECTIVE,
I AM NOWHERE TO BE FOUND.
TO OBSERVE
IS TO CREATE PERSPECTIVE.
I CAN NEVER CEASE
TO BE THE POINT OF ORIGIN
FROM MY PERSPECTIVE.
I OBSERVE THAT
WHICH IS NOT MYSELF.
THIS IS THE FIRST PRINCIPLE
DEFINED!
- ( grunting )
- I AM NOBODY.
EVEN IF I WAS SOMEBODY,
I AM BEYOND
YOUR COMPREHENSION.
AND EVEN IF YOU COULD,
YOU WOULD NOT HAVE THE TOOLS
TO EXPRESS THAT KNOWLEDGE.
I DO NOT BELONG
TO THE WORLD.
THAT IS THE LIMIT,
THE BOUNDARY
BETWEEN ALL AND SELF.
- WELL, I WAS THERE
BECAUSE I WAS TOLD
THAT SOMEONE REPORTED
AN INFECTED AUTOREIV.
- INCORRECT.
IT IS NOT
"I THINK THEREFORE I AM."
- BUT I'M NOT LYING.
IF YOU TAKE A LOOK
AT THE FACILITY'S RECORDS...
- CORRECT.
THE ANSWER IS,
"I THINK THEREFORE YOU ARE."
YOU STILL DON'T REMEMBER,
DO YOU?
- HOLD ON.
YOU KNOW, DON'T YOU?
PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT THE PROXY IS.
TELL ME ABOUT THE MONSTER.
- YOU THINK PROXIES
ARE MONSTERS?
( laughs )
YOU DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT ANYTHING.
PEOPLE HAVE CALLED THEM
MONSTERS OR DEMONS, BUT THAT'S--
- RE-L!
- --ALL NOTHING BUT NONSENSE.
IN TRUTH, PROXIES ARE--
- YOU!
- THEY HAVE THE POWER
TO CHANGE THEIR APPEARANCE
INTO ANY FORM THEY CHOOSE.
THEY CAN DISAPPEAR WITH EASE,
LEAVING NO TRACE
THEY WERE EVER THERE.
- IT'S ALL ABOUT YOU.
- THEY CAN ALSO
ENTER HUMAN BEINGS
AND TAKE CONTROL
OF THEIR MIND AND BODY.
- IT'S WHAT YOU ARE.
- THEY CAN
SUMMON LIGHTENING BOLTS
AND SCORCH THE EARTH
WITH THEIR POWER.
- IT'S TIME TO REMEMBER.
- THEY CAN EVEN CONJURE UP
PLANETS FROM THE SKY!
- ERGO PROXY!
- STOP IT!
NO, I'M NOT!
I'M VINCENT LAW!
REGISTRATION #0724FGARK.
MY NAME IS VINCENT LAW.
- IT SEEMS
YOU REALLY ARE A FOOL.
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR EYE
FOR THE TRUTH
AS WELL AS YOUR MEMORY?
- MY MEMORY?
I HAVE NO PROBLEM
WITH MY MEMORY.
- WELL, THEN WHO ARE YOU?
TRY AND TELL ME
WHO YOU REALLY ARE.
( chuckles )
- I'M--
AFTER I IMMIGRATED
TO ROMDEAU,
I GOT A STAFF JOB AT THE
AUTOREIV DISPOSAL UNIT FACILITY.
- AND BEFORE THAT?
- I WAS LOOKING FOR WORK
IN THE F.G. TEMPORARY
IMMIGRANT DISTRICT.
THAT'S WHERE I FIRST SAW RE-L.
- AND BEFORE THAT?
- BEFORE I IMMIGRATED
TO ROMDEAU,
I LIVED
IN THE DOME CITY OF MOSK.
THERE WAS AN ACCIDENT.
THE CITY WAS DESTROYED.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
- AND BEFORE THAT?
- I WAS IN MOSK.
- AND WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
- IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- I CAN'T REMEMBER.
- YOU CAN'T REMEMBER BECAUSE YOU
STILL DON'T WANT TO REMEMBER.
LET'S SEE WHAT QUESTIONS
YOU CAN ANSWER.
- ( shattering )
- IF YOU CAN'T FIND
THE ANSWER YOURSELF,
THEN ASKING ME
IS POINTLESS.
YOU'RE NOT CAPABLE
OF UNDERSTANDING YET.
- WHY?
- I'VE TOLD YOU.
IT'S BECAUSE A PART OF YOU,
VINCENT--
OBSERVE.
- Vincent:
NO.  I'M--
- ( fingers snap )
- --DREAMING.
- THIS IS NOT A DREAM,
VINCENT LAW.
- Bookkeeper: THE MOST
IMPORTANT PART OF A BOOKSTORE
IS, OF COURSE, THE BOOKS.
THERE IS A MAGIC INHERENT
IN LANGUAGE.
OUR WORLD IS RULED
BY LOGOS.
SOME WORDS CONTAIN THEIR
OWN INTERNAL CONTRADICTIONS.
FROM THESE OPPOSITIONS,
GREAT TRUTHS CAN BE REVEALED.
BIOS, FOR EXAMPLE.
THE WORD "BIOS" CAN BE DEFINED
AS THE PROCESS OF LIFE,
OR AS THE ARCHER'S BOW.
THE BOW AND LIFE-- AT FIRST,
THEY SEEM QUITE UNRELATED.
BUT BOTH INEVITABLY RESULT
IN DEATH.
THE PHILOSOPHERS OF THE ANCIENT
WORLD COULD BE VERY CLEVER.
- YEAH.
- "ANAMNESIS."
THE WORD HAS TWO MEANINGS,
BOTH MEMORY AND RECOLLECTION.
- Male voice:
REMEMBRANCE.
WHO WAS VINCENT LAW?
WHAT WAS HE AFRAID OF?
WHAT DID HE DECIDE
TO ERASE HERE?
- ( snaps )
- I PRESENT A TIME
OF DESTRUCTION.
THERE IS MISFORTUNE
IN THE STARS.
THE SKY IS LOST
AND THE SEA IS FROZEN OVER.
THE CIRCLE OF LIFE
WHICH ALLOW BOTH MAN
AND NATURE TO FLOURISH
HAVE ALL BUT STOPPED.
THE MAIN PLAYERS OF OUR STORY
HAVE LONG SINCE LEFT THE STAGE.
WE HANG IN ANTICIPATION FOR
THE INEVITABLE FINAL CURTAIN.
AND YET,
EVEN AT THIS LATE HOUR,
TRACES OF THE GREAT CIRCLE
REMAIN.
THE CIRCLE OF LIFE
ONLY CONTINUES
BECAUSE YOU EXIST.
WE WAIT TO SEE THE FATE
OF YOU LAST SURVIVORS
OF THIS WORLD,
FOR IF YOU PERISH,
PERCEPTION IS REMOVED
AND EXISTENCE
COMES TO AN END.
A UNIVERSE WITHOUT PERCEPTION
IS MUCH LIKE AN ENORMOUS
STACK OF ROTTING BOOKS,
FOREVER UNOPENED
AND UNREAD.
- STOP IT.
PLEASE STOP.
- TO SURVIVE THIS DARKNESS,
THE UNIVERSE HAS THRUST ITSELF
INTO A NEXT PHASE
OF ITS LIFE CYCLE.
LISTEN.
CAN'T YOU HEAR THE PULSE
OF THE AWAKENING?
- THE PULSE...
- ( heartbeat )
- Bookkeeper:
STOP BADGERING THE BOY.
HE CAN'T TAKE MUCH MORE.
( snaps )
LOOKS LIKE I GOT HERE
JUST IN TIME.
A PULSE--
THE MEASURE OF A LIFE.
EVERY ANIMAL ON THIS PLANET
HAS A CIRCULATORY SYSTEM
IN SCALE WITH THE MASS
OF ITS OWN BODY.
IN FACT,
THE BEATING OF THEIR HEART
CAN BE USED
TO PREDICT LIFE SPAN.
IT'S CALLED KLEIBER'S LAW.
AND TO TRY TO GO FORWARD WITHOUT
GRASPING THIS ESSENTIAL LAW,
IT WOULD BE POINTLESS.
- THAT'S ENOUGH, OLD MAN.
- OLD MAN? I AM THE GATEKEEPER
OF MEMORY, YOU FOOL.
AND YOU'VE NO RIGHT
TO BE THREATENING THE CORE SELF.
- WHAT'S THE POINT
OF HAVING A GATEKEEPER
IF YOU NEVER OPEN THE GATE?
NOW IT'S TIME TO REMEMBER.
- ENOUGH!
- REMEMBER.
REMEMBER HOW WE SOMEHOW MANAGED
TO ALTER OUR OWN PULSE.
REMEMBER,
FEEL THE POUNDING IN YOUR CHEST
AS THE PULSE QUICKENS.
IT BELONGS TO NO ONE ELSE.
IT IS YOURS AND MINE.
IT IS THE FOUNDATION
OF OUR TRUTH--
PROOF THAT WE BELONG
IN THIS WORLD,
THAT WE ARE OF THIS WORLD.
FOLLOW YOUR INSTINCTS.
YOU'LL FIND THE ANSWERS
YOU SEEK INSIDE.
THE WHITE NOISE THAT BEATS
WITHIN THE WHITE DARKNESS
IS THE RHYTHM OF LIFE.
IT IS THAT PULSE WHICH
NEVER TRULY LEFT THE STAGE.
- IN MY DESPERATE ATTEMPTS
TO BECOME A FELLOW CITIZEN,
I HAVE
CONSTANTLY SUPPRESSED MYSELF.
I TRIED TO BE THE PERSON
I THOUGHT THEY WANTED,
CONSTANTLY, EVERYWHERE.
- IF IT'S INTERRUPTED,
THAT WHICH NEEDS TO BE EXPRESSED
WILL BE EXPRESSED.
OUR WORDS WILL CONNECT US
AGAIN TO SOMEONE ELSE.
- Vincent:
LOOK WHAT'S HAPPENED TO ME.
I'M A FAILURE.
- TO SECURE US
IN THIS CIRCLE,
TO BRING US INTO THIS
TETHERED SYSTEM WE CALL LIFE,
SOMEONE WHO IS NOT OF US
HAD TO CREATE,
TO BRING US INTO BEING.
- Vincent:
DOUBTING THE SYSTEM IS BAD.
ALWAYS OBEY.
THOSE ARE THE CONDITIONS
FOR BEING A FELLOW CITIZEN.
- CAN'T YOU HEAR IT?
THE PULSE OF THE AWAKENING
BEATING IN YOUR CHEST.
WE HEAR IT TOGETHER, JOINED BY
THE HEART BEATING IN OUR CHEST.
LISTEN.
ITS PULSE IS FOR BOTH OF US.
- BUT I'LL NEVER
BECOME A FELLOW CITIZEN.
- ( snapping )
- Both voices: VINCENT!
- Vincent: IT'S OVER.
MY LIFE-- IT'S ALL OVER.
- NOW YOU KNOW THAT I AM YOU.
AND YOU ARE ME.
- NO!  I--
I'M VINCENT LAW!
- VINCENT LAW,
TAKE A REAL LOOK AT YOURSELF.
THEN I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN--
WHAT ARE YOU THE AGENT OF?
- Vincent:
I'M--
AHHH!
- ( glass shattering )
- ( Vincent shouting )
I'M--
RE-L.
NO.
I DON'T REMEMBER HOW,
WHY,
ANYTHING.
BUT I KNOW.
NOW I KNOW.
I AM ERGO PROXY.
( sobbing )
- KEEP IN MIND, VINCENT,
YOU HAVE JUST CROSSED
THE THRESHOLD OF TRUTH.
IT'S TIME TO FIND YOUR WAY
TO KNOWLEDGE.
- ( sobbing )
- ( fingers snap )
- Bookkeeper: YEAH, I THINK
IT'S BEEN ABOUT THREE MINUTES.
THE TEA IS READY.
GO ON, DRINK UP.
SO WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
- UH, WELL,
ACTUALLY I THINK I'M LOST.
- YEAH, WELL, I SORT OF FIGURED
YOU'D SAY THAT.
WE GET THAT A LOT
AROUND HERE.
- WITH THE FOG--
- A MAN SAID THE FUTURE
IS AN OPAQUE MIRROR.
ANYONE WHO TRIES
TO LOOK INTO IT SEES NOTHING
BUT THE DIM OUTLINES
OF AN OLD AND WORRIED FACE.
- MY SHIP-- I KNOW MY SHIP
IS DOCKED SOMEWHERE AROUND HERE.
- THE ANSWERS YOU SEEK
YOU WILL NEVER FIND
UNTIL YOU STOP LOOKING OUTSIDE
AND START LOOKING FOR THEM
WITHIN YOURSELF.
- HAVE YOU SEEN A LITTLE-GIRL
TYPE AUTOREIV AROUND HERE?
HER NAME IS PINO.
- YOU MIGHT HAVE BETTER LUCK
LOOKING FOR ONE LOST
THING AT A TIME.
( chuckles )
- THE SHIP.
NO, I MEAN PINO.
HAVE YOU SEEN HER?
- SORRY.
I HOPE YOU CAN BE COMFORTABLE
IN YOUR ACCEPTANCE.
WANDERING LOST IN THE DARK
FOR SUCH A LONG TIME--
IT CAN BE REAL EASY
TO LOSE SIGHT
OF THE THINGS
THAT ARE IMPORTANT.
- MY ACCEPTANCE IS JUST FINE.
- THAT'S AN ACCOMPLISHMENT.
CAN YOU TELL ME
JUST WHAT IT IS
YOU'VE ACCEPTED?
- HUH?
- GO ON THEN.
- I'M JUST LOST, THAT'S ALL.
I GOT LOST.
- ( clapping )
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
THAT BEING THE CASE,
I'D BE HAPPY
TO POINT YOU IN THE
RIGHT DIRECTION.
GOOD LUCK, VINCENT LAW.
I MEAN, ERGO PROXY.
- WAIT!
- ( snaps )
- HMM?
( laughs )
VINCE?
- Vincent: I KNOW NOW.
I AM A PROXY.
- I FINALLY FOUND YOU.
- I'M DREAMING.
- THIS IS NOT A DREAM,
VINCENT LAW.
- ( rock music playing )
♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN
CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
- TELL ME EVERYTHING YOU KNOW,
VINCENT LAW.