- Man: PATROLLING FROM
LAST CONFIRMED SIGHTING
FOR DISTRICTS
E AND H.
- Kristeva: CONFIRMED.
OVERWRITE YOUR PROJECTED
ESCAPE ROUTES FILE
WITH THE UPDATED VERSION
AVAILABLE
ON THE SECURITY NETWORK.
REMEMBER THAT THE TARGET IS
A FORMER SECURITY BUREAU CHIEF.
- ( panting )
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
IT'S TOO LATE, SIR.
SORRY, REGENT.
I'M NOT A FELLOW
CITIZEN ANYMORE.
- THERE'S NO NEED
TO SHOW ME I.D., SIR.
- PROTOCOL MUST
ALWAYS BE MAINTAINED.
- MY APOLOGIES, SIR.
AND CHIEF,
PLEASE ACCEPT MY ADMIRATION
OF YOUR CONDUCT AS
A FELLOW CITIZEN.
- YES, OF COURSE.
- ( rock music playing )
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD
UNWINDS INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- Pino: WE'VE GONE ABOUT
140 MILES TODAY,
SO THAT MEANS
WE'RE AROUND HERE?
- VERY GOOD.
- ( giggles )
- Re-L:
WE'RE CLOSING IN ON MOSK.
BIRTHPLACE OF
VINCENT LAW,
AND...
THE CITY WHERE
THE MYSTERY OF THE PROXY
AWAITS.
- ( playing melodica )
- Vincent: WHO AM I?
REALLY?
- I DON'T KNOW WHY
I EVEN BOTHER ASKING.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
- DID I FORGET ON PURPOSE?
WAS WHATEVER HAPPENED
TO ME THAT HORRIBLE?
IF I--
IF I CAN'T BE ME ANYMORE,
I'D RATHER IT END.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
I'LL NEED YOU TO KILL ME.
- THAT'S THE PLAN.
I'M SAVING THIS
LAST BULLET FOR YOU.
BUT BEFORE I SHOOT YOU,
WE NEED TO GET TO MOSK.
COME ON.
- PINO!
PINO!
( panting )
( gasps )
- HMM.
- Daedalus: IT PROVOKES
THE SAME REACTION IN ME.
IT'S UNSETTLING,
ISN'T IT?
- NOT UNLIKE A COFFIN.
- SOMETIMES I IMAGINE
I'M A WALKING CORPSE,
BORN FROM A COFFIN WOMB.
- WHAT DID THE REGENT SAY?
- THE USUAL.
HE SAID TO IGNORE IT
AND WE'LL DEAL WITH IT LATER.
- THE CITY CAN'T GO ON
LIKE THIS MUCH LONGER.
- I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
THIS SORT OF POWER WOULD HAVE
SIGNIFICANT IMPLICATIONS.
- WE WON'T LAST LONG
WITHOUT A PROXY.
STILL...
IT'S NOT THE END OF THE WORLD.
NOT YET.
- MM-HMM.
( chuckles )
YOU'RE TOO EMOTIONAL
TO BE REASONABLE.
- AND YOU'RE TOO DETACHED.
CONSIDERING YOUR PRECIOUS
RE-L ABANDONED ROMDEAU
AND MALICIOUSLY
BETRAYED YOU.
- ( chuckles )
SHE STILL LIVES,
SO I HAVEN'T BEEN BETRAYED.
SO LONG AS SHE EXISTS,
I CAN MAINTAIN MYSELF.
- I'M JEALOUS.
- PERHAPS YOU'VE FORGOTTEN.
THIS MESS, IT'S ENTIRELY DUE TO
YOUR RECKLESS STUPIDITY, SIR.
IT WAS VINCENT LAW.
THAT IMMIGRANT
SHE WAS AFTER
TURNED OUT TO BE
A PROXY.
AND THE REGENT WANTS THAT
POWER HARNESSED FOR ROMDEAU.
IF YOU HADN'T CORNERED HIM,
IF YOU HAD BOTHERED
TO EXERCISE
THE SLIGHTEST SELF-CONTROL,
WHERE WOULD VINCENT LAW
BE RIGHT NOW?
HE'D BE CONTAINED.
YOU LET PERSONAL GRUDGES
GET IN THE WAY,
AND YOU LOST THE PROXY.
WITHOUT YOU, EVERYTHING WOULD
STILL BE THE SAME.
YOU RUINED EVERYTHING.
( grunts )
- EVERYTHING?
YOU THINK I RUINED EVERYTHING?!
- ( grunts )
- IF YOU DON'T
WANT A BULLET
THROUGH THAT
EXCEPTIONAL MIND OF YOURS,
I'D WATCH YOUR MOUTH.
- HER TRANSPONDER WAS FINE
LAST TIME I CHECKED.
SHE JUST VANISHED.
- VANISHED?
WHAT DO WE DO?
- Re-L: THE ACTIONS OF
COGITO INFECTED AUTOREIVS
ARE GOVERNED
BY THEIR EMOTIONS,
THEIR SOULS.
- Kristeva: THIS IS YOUR
FIFTH INSPECTION THIS MONTH.
- AS CHIEF OF SECURITY,
IT'S MY DUTY TO BE
WELL-VERSED
ON ALL ASPECTS OF
THE CITY'S DEFENSE SYSTEMS.
- BUT THE RAPTURE
IS A RELIC.
IT'S BEEN SEALED OFF.
- YES, IT HAS.
HENCE MY INTEREST.
- THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
HOW DO YOU LOSE
AN AUTOREIV?
AND WHY NOW WHEN
WE'RE SO CLOSE?
- WE COULD JUST LEAVE HER.
- WHAT?
- SHE'S A COMPANION TYPE.
ASIDE FROM HER SENSORS,
PINO'S USELESS.
SHE'D BE FINE
IF WE LEFT HER.
HONESTLY, IT MIGHT SAVE HER
FROM GETTING IN THE WAY.
- NO.
SHE'S ONE OF US.
WE CAN'T JUST WRITE HER
OFF LIKE THAT.
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO STUCK WITH ME
THROUGH THIS WHOLE MESS.
- I FEEL THE SAME.
- ( gasps )
- DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
LESS TALKING,
MORE LOOKING.
- RIGHT.
( grunts )
OW.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( both gasp )
- WINNER.
I COULD DO IT.
I COULD TAKE THIS
LITTLE WORLD
AND DROWN IT IN DESPAIR.
( sighs )
VINCENT LAW?
STOP THAT!
- Kristeva:
CHIEF?
IT'S TIME.
- YES.
THANK YOU.
- IS IT DEAD?
- YEAH.
AND THERE'S MORE
THAN ONE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN CREATURES
LIKE THESE BEFORE.
- RE-L?
- SHH.
DO YOU HEAR THAT?
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU LOOK WORRIED.
OH, THIS?  IT'S FINE.
THAT'S SWEET
OF YOU TO SAY.
THANK YOU.
- ( piano playing )
- ( gasps )
PINO!
- ( giggles )
VINCE!  RE-L.
I'M GOOD AT THE PIANO, RIGHT?
- WHERE ARE WE?
AND WHO--
WHAT IS THAT?
YOU DON'T SEEM TO BE
HAVING A REACTION TO IT,
SO IT'S PROBABLY NOT
ANOTHER PROXY.
AND IT DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE REACTING
TO WHAT WE'RE SAYING.
BUT LOOK AT THIS PLACE.
WHY DOES IT HAVE A PIANO?
- Raul:
I'VE BEEN THINKING,
MEDITATING ON THE NATURE
OF ROMDEAU.
WE'RE TRULY PRISONERS
MORE THAN CITIZENS.
- Derrida: WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "PRISONERS"?
- ROMDEAU IS A SAFE HARBOR
FOR MANKIND
AS THE OUTSIDE WORLD
RECOVERS.
WE CANNOT SURVIVE
OUTSIDE THE CITY WALLS.
- Berkeley: YES, OF COURSE.
- Lacan:
IT IS THE SEED OF HUMANITY
WAITING TO TAKE ROOT
ONCE AGAIN.
- SO...
THEN WHAT YOU ARE SAYING
IS THAT WE ARE
HELD PRISONER HERE.
- Derrida: IS THAT WHY
YOU'VE COME TO US, RAUL?
- Berkeley:
JUST TO SPOUT SUCH NONSENSE?
- Lacan:
CEASE THIS PRATTLING.
YOU ARE TO RETURN
TO YOUR DUTIES
AS SECURITY CHIEF.
- AND HOW DO I
PROTECT US?
TELL ME WHAT I'M
SUPPOSED TO DO.
- Derrida:
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THE OUTSIDE WORLD
HAS BEGUN TO RECOVER.
BUT WHY DOES IT STILL
REMAIN A WORLD OF DEATH TO US?
TELL ME!
- Derrida: DID DAEDALUS PUT
THESE IDEAS IN YOUR HEAD?
- ANSWER ME.
- Berkeley: DO NOT THINK
YOU KNOW EVERYTHING.
DO NOT THINK YOU MAY
CHANGE EVERYTHING.
- BUT I KNOW THE TRUTH.
I KNOW THAT WE ARE
INCOMPLETE CREATURES.
- Lacan:
SUCH FOOLISHNESS.
- THE TRUTH IS THAT YOU'VE
BEEN WORKING IN IGNORANCE
FROM THE VERY START.
- Berkeley:
RAUL, WATCH YOUR TONGUE.
- THEN TELL ME WHAT I'VE
BEEN DOING ALL THIS TIME.
- Proxy One: RAUL.
COULD YOU AT LEAST
TRY AND PRETEND
TO KNOW YOUR PLACE?
SHOW SOME MODESTY,
YOU SAD, PATHETIC
LITTLE ANIMAL.
YOU ARE POWERLESS.
- YOU THINK YOU'VE WON?
I WON'T ALLOW IT.
NEVER.
YOU ARE NOTHING MORE
THAN A COG IN THE MACHINE.
A GREAT DESPAIR IS
MOVING AMONG US
AND YOU REFUSE
TO DO ANYTHING
WHILE MANKIND MARCHES
TOWARDS ITS DESTRUCTION.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
ROMDEAU IS NOT YOUR EPITAPH!
THE FUTURE OF OUR FELLOW
CITIZENS IS AT STAKE.
WE CAN NO LONGER
AFFORD YOUR IGNORANCE.
GO TO HELL, REGENT.
- Derrida: KRISTEVA.
- MA'AM?
- Derrida: WE'RE PUTTING
YOU IN CHARGE
UNTIL A NEW CHIEF
IS APPOINTED.
- Lacan: CITIZEN NUMBER 039666,
RAUL CREED,
IS TO BE STRIPPED
OF HIS AUTHORITY.
- Berkeley:
IT ISN'T REALLY SURPRISING.
- Derrida: NO ONE APPOINTED AS
CHIEF OF THE SECURITY BUREAU
HAS EVER SUCCESSFULLY
COMPLETED THEIR TERM.
- Lacan: THEIR POSITION
TEACHES THEM THINGS
THEY SHOULD NOT KNOW.
THESE IDEAS FOSTER
FEELINGS THEY SHOULD NOT FEEL.
- Derrida: THEN THEY ALL
STRAY DOWN THIS PATH.
- Berkeley:
WE KNEW IT WAS INEVITABLE
FROM THE MOMENT
HE ASSUMED OFFICE.
THIS IS WHAT BECOMES OF
A TRUE FELLOW CITIZEN,
AN IRONY WORTH NOTING.
- ( gasping )
- IS THIS WHERE THEY LIVE?
- THEY SEEM AWFULLY WEAK.
- ( Re-L coughing )
- RE-L.
- THERE ARE TRACES OF
TOXIC GAS IN HERE.
- HUH?
- NO WONDER THEY'RE
ALL SO WEAK.
THIS PLACE IS
A TOXIC DUMP.
IT WAS BETTER OUTSIDE.
( coughs )
- ARE YOU GONNA
BE ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
( coughing )
- COME ON.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- ( Re-L coughing )
- ( playing piano )
- ( humming )
- PINO, LET'S GO.
- AWW, JUST ONE MORE SONG?
- PINO!
WE'RE GOING NOW,
WITH OR WITHOUT YOU.
- ( groans )
- PINO.
- Re-L: THIS PLACE MUST HAVE
BEEN CREATED BY HUMANS...
- Pino: BUT I WAS HAVING
FUN PLAYING PIANO.
- Re-L:
...WHILE THEY WAITED
FOR THE OUTSIDE
ENVIRONMENT TO IMPROVE,
THEY SUCCUMBED TO
THE POISON INSIDE THE CAVE.
I'M GUESSING THOSE CREATURES
DON'T HAVE MUCH LONGER.
- Pino: WAIT.
- WHAT COULD HE
BE THINKING?
EMOTIONAL AWAKENING REALLY DOES
LEAD TO SELF-DESTRUCTION.
JUST AS THEY SAID.
CITIZEN NUMBER 039666,
RAUL CREED,
YOUR TIME IS UP.
- Man:
WE'VE LOST THE TARGET.
- KRISTEVA?
- RUN A FACIAL PROFILE
SPREADING ACROSS
THE ENTIRE AREA.
- YES, MA'AM.
NO MATCHES.
SHALL I CHANGE
THE SEARCH HEADING PARAMETERS?
- RECONFIRM OUR
LAST SIGHTING,
THEN RECONSTRUCT
THE PROJECTED ESCAPE ROUTE FILE.
HE WAS A VERY CLEVER
SECURITY CHIEF.
ALWAYS ONE STEP AHEAD OF US.
WHERE WOULD HIS DESPAIR
BRING HIM?
- YES, IT HAS.
HENCE MY INTEREST.
- I KNOW WHERE HE'S HEADED.
BEGIN DELETION OF CITIZEN
NUMBER 039666, RAUL CREED,
FROM THE SYSTEM.
- CONFIRMED.
HIS DATA WILL BE
COMPLETELY DELETED IN...
- ( panting )
- ...14 MINUTES, 55 SECONDS.
- Man: PATROLLING FROM
LAST CONFIRMED SIGHTING
THROUGH DISTRICTS
E AND H.
- Kristeva: CONFIRMED.
OVERWRITE YOUR PROJECTED
ESCAPE ROUTES FILE
WITH THE UPDATED
VERSION AVAILABLE
ON THE SECURITY NETWORK.
REMEMBER THAT THE TARGET IS
A FORMER SECURITY BUREAU CHIEF.
- Man: YES, MA'AM.
- SEND AN ARMED
AUTOREIV UNIT
TO THE RAPTURE CONTROL FACILITY.
WE CAN PIN HIM DOWN THERE.
- YES, MA'AM.
- WELL, I WONDER WHAT
OUR FORMER CHIEF WILL DO.
EITHER WAY,
IT DOESN'T REALLY AFFECT ME.
HE MAY HAVE BEEN TOO EMOTIONAL
TO BE A FELLOW CITIZEN.
BUT HE WAS AN
ENDEARING IDIOT.
IS THAT CRUEL OF ME?
- NO.
YOU ARE THE PRINCE OF ROMDEAU.
- DON'T CALL ME PRINCE.
IT'D MAKE HER LAUGH.
- MODIFYING APPLICATION
SETTING CONFIRMED.
- I'LL ALWAYS
BE ON YOUR SIDE.
- Pino: ARE WE CLOSE TO
THE RABBIT YET?
MY BATTERY IS RUNNING OUT.
- Re-L: STRANGE.
THE POISON SHOULD BE
THINNING OUT THE FURTHER WE GO.
- Pino: VINCE!
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
- Reporter: THREE AUTOREIVS
WERE FOUND DESTROYED
IN THE E AND H DISTRICTS
LEADING TOWARDS RAPTURE.
FORMER BUREAU CHIEF RAUL'S
I.D. WAS FOUND AT THE SCENE.
- IDIOT.
RAUL CREED'S CITIZENSHIP WILL
BE REVOKED IN EIGHT MINUTES.
IN THE MEANTIME, HIS AUTHORITY
AS CHIEF OF SECURITY
IS STILL IN PLAY.
TAKE HIM INTO CUSTODY
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- ( groans )
- ( grunts )
PINO, STOP.
THAT HURTS.
- IT'S HIM.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- I KNEW IT.
- HUH?
- THEY CAN'T SURVIVE IN
THE ATMOSPHERE OUTSIDE.
EVEN THOUGH THE POISON
IS SLOWLY KILLING THEM,
THEY CAN'T LEAVE THE CAVES.
- YOU MEAN NO MATTER
WHAT THEY DO,
THEY'RE GOING TO DIE?
- IT SEEMS A FEW DON'T
ACCEPT THEIR FATE.
- HE FOLLOWED US
OUT HERE.
RIGHT, VINCE?
- ( sighs )
- ( groans )
- ( gasps )
OH.
THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
- Vincent: YEAH.
- BYE-BYE.
YOU'RE WITH YOUR DADDY NOW.
- THAT'S, UH...
THAT'S NOT HER DADDY.
- HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- NOT AGAIN.
- IT CAN'T BE.
- RAUL CREED,
STOP THIS IMMEDIATELY.
- ALL CLEAR.
HE'LL BE DELETED
FROM THE SYSTEM
IN 20 SECONDS.
- DID I OVERESTIMATE HIM?
NO.
- Man:
WE'VE LOCATED THE TARGET.
- WHERE IS HE?
- Man:
AT HIS RESIDENCE.
- HE IS?
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
- FIVE SECONDS TILL DELETION.
THREE...
TWO...
- CANCEL THE DELETION.
- ...ONE, ZERO.
IT'S NOT RECOGNIZING
THE FIRING SEQUENCE ABORT CODE.
- ( piano playing )
- REBOOT ALL CONTROL SYSTEMS
FOR THIS FACILITY.
- "COMMAND NOT RECOGNIZED."
THERE'S NO WAY TO
STOP THE LAUNCH.
- HIS DELETION HAS TRIGGERED
THE SYSTEM LOCKOUT.
WELL PLAYED, RAUL CREED.
- NOTHING BUT DESPAIR.
I CAN NO LONGER
RESIST THE FEELINGS
THAT DRIVE ME TO DESTROY.
IT WAS ALWAYS HIM.
HE STOLE THE LIGHT
FROM THIS GREAT CIVILIZATION.
HE STOLE THE DESTRUCTION
MY DESPAIR HUNGERED FOR.
HE STOLE EVERYTHING FROM ME.
PINO...
- Vincent:
YOU REALLY LIKE TO PLAY.
- YEAH.
I LOVE IT.
- WHAT?
- Pino:
WOW, IT'S SO PRETTY.
- ( rock music playing )
♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES
IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
- Re-L: LAST STOP, MOSK.
A MAN AND WOMAN
COME FACE-TO-FACE
WITH LOST MEMORIES.
THE SIGN THAT APPEARS
CAN ONLY BRING PAIN.