- Proxy One:
SO YOU'RE FINALLY HERE.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
A LONG TIME FOR THIS.
- ( Vincent gasps )
( stammers )
- WHO ARE YOU?
- WHO AM I?
I TOLD YOU.
I AM YOU,
AND YOU ARE ME.
- ( gasps )
- SO LET'S CELEBRATE.
IT'S YOUR LONG-AWAITED RETURN
AFTER YOU BACKED UP
YOUR LOVER,
ERASED YOUR MEMORY,
AND ABANDONED YOUR PEOPLE.
- STOP IT.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- RE-L MAYER,
YOUR SERVICES ARE
NO LONGER REQUIRED.
I THINK WE CAN HANDLE THINGS
ALONE FROM HERE ON OUT.
- ( gasps )
- AH, SUCH FOOLISHNESS.
- Re-L: DAEDALUS.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
- Proxy One:
HE'S HERALDING IN THE NEW AGE.
I'VE ARRANGED FOR HIM
TO INITIATE
THE DESTRUCTION OF THE DOME.
HE'S EMBRACED THE DESTRUCTIVE
IMPULSE WITHIN HIM.
IT'S IN ALL OF US.
- ( gasps )
- IT'S NO USE.
YOU CAN'T STOP IT.
ACCEPT THE INEVITABLE.
EVEN IF YOU SOMEHOW SURVIVE,
YOU'LL NEVER WIN THIS BATTLE.
- THAT IS NOT THE POINT.
AND I AM NOT ABOUT TO RUN AWAY
FROM WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE.
- ( gasps )
- BECAUSE EVEN IF
YOUR FUTURE IS INEVITABLE
AND NOTHING BUT PAIN
AWAITS ME...
- ( chuckles )
- ...I'M STILL DOING
WHAT I THINK IS RIGHT.
OH, AND VINCENT,
FIND ME.
- RE-L.
RE-L.
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD
UNWINDS INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- ( Monad screams )
- RE-L?
- Proxy One:  GOOD.
TAKE IT ALL IN.
THIS IS WHAT
YOU REALLY LOOK LIKE.
YOU WEAR THE MASK
OF A MAN
WHO WOULD DENY
HIS OWN FATE.
WHY DON'T WE GO
THROUGH THIS AGAIN?
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU LOST YOUR MEMORY?
OR IS IT POSSIBLE THAT YOU NEVER
HAD ANY MEMORIES TO BEGIN WITH?
PERHAPS...
YOU CONVINCED YOURSELF THAT
YOUR MEMORIES WERE SIMPLY LOST.
BUT THEN YOU END UP
RIGHT BACK WHERE YOU STARTED.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- NO!
THE JOURNEY,
THAT'S WHAT WAS NEEDED.
THE RUINS OF THIS WORLD
ARE SPRINGING BACK TO LIFE.
I SAW WHAT WAS HAPPENING
TO THE WORLD OUT THERE.
I HEARD IT, TOUCHED IT,
TASTED IT.
FELT IT TO THE DEPTHS
OF MY SOUL.
IF I HADN'T BEEN MOVED,
I WOULD HAVE NEVER
THOUGHT OF RETURNING HERE.
- THE ARK AND CRADLE
WILL NURTURE YOU,
BUT IT WILL NOT
EDUCATE YOU.
I IMAGINE FACING
THE WORLD OUTSIDE ON YOUR OWN
WAS QUITE THE EYE-OPENING
EXPERIENCE.
IN THE END, I'M GLAD YOU
MANAGED TO GET THE POINT
THAT I'VE BEEN
MAKING TO YOU.
- TELL ME, WHAT ARE WE?
WHAT ARE THE PROXIES?
- "WHAT ARE THE PROXIES?"
THE ANSWER IS IN
THE WORD ITSELF.
WE ARE THE AGENTS
OF THE CREATOR.
- THE CREATOR.
( gasps )
- FIND ME, VINCENT.
- Proxy One: THAT IS WHEN
EVERYTHING BECAME CLEAR.
- WHERE ARE WE?
- EVERYTHING ABOUT THE MALICE
IMPLANTED BY THE CREATOR.
AFTER A TIME OF SUFFERING,
THE AGENT OF THE CREATOR
WOULD COMPLETE HIS TASK.
HE WOULD BE TAXED
WITH FINISHING
THE RESTORATION OF
THE HUMAN RACE,
AND THEN CHANGE HIS FORM.
IT'S THE PULSE
OF THE AWAKENING.
THE PROXY ANNIHILATION
PROGRAM.
THAT MEANS THE WHOLE
HUMAN RACE...
- NO.  WE CAN NEVER TRULY DEFY
THE CREATOR'S PLANS FOR US.
IT'S AN ELEGANT SYSTEM.
THE IRONY IS,
EVEN THOUGH THE PROXY
IS THE CREATOR'S SERVANT,
ONCE HE HAS
CARRIED OUT HIS MISSION,
HE IS UNNECESSARY
TO THE WORLD
THAT HE HAS HELPED
TO BRING ABOUT.
IN FACT, HE'S LEFT
TO BE SOME OF MONSTER,
AN OLD WORLD DEMON
OF A NEW AGE.
- BUT WHAT IF AT SOME POINT
IN THIS ELEGANT PLAN,
DEEP WITHIN THE ARC,
A NEW SOUL STARTS
TO BECOME AWARE OF ITSELF.
ANSWER ME.
WHY DID THE CREATOR DECIDE
TO GIVE THE PROXIES SOULS?
WE WOULDN'T SUFFER
IF WE HAD NO SOULS.
- I THINK YOU KNOW
THE ANSWER.
- I DO.
I GUESS IT HAD TO
BE THIS WAY.
- AFTER ALL, WE WERE THERE.
WE LEARNED WHAT IT WAS TO BE
WORSHIPPED, LOVED, BETRAYED.
WE WERE DRIVEN TO
THE EDGES OF DESPAIR
BY THESE CREATURES.
PRISONERS OF OUR OWN
FLAWED CHILDREN.
WE DISCOVERED
THE TORMENTS OF A CREATOR.
- AND YET,
WE STILL LOVE THEM.
- THE CREATOR WISHES
TO BE LOVED AS WELL.
IT'S AS IF I CAN FEEL
HIS SOLITUDE AND DESPAIR
IN THE VERY DEPTHS
OF MY SOUL.
THAT DESPAIR AND PAIN
IS THE REASON
THEY MUST ALL BE PUNISHED.
- BUT IF YOU'VE RESTORED
THE HUMAN RACE
LIKE WE WERE SUPPOSED TO,
THEN WHAT ELSE IS LEFT
FOR US TO DO?
( gasps )
- PRECISELY.
THE TERRIBLE TRUTH
FINALLY DAWNS ON YOU.
YOU ARE VINCENT LAW,
THE EMPTY MAN,
THE CREATOR'S SHADOW,
BOUND IN BODY AND SOUL.
YOU'VE BEEN MANIPULATED,
BURIED UNDER THE BURDENS
OF FAILED CREATIONS
AND HAVE BROUGHT
THE DESTRUCTION OF MAN
AT THE CUSP OF HIS REBIRTH.
- YOU'RE SAYING
ALL OF MANKIND?
- THE SHADOW KNOWS.
IT KNOWS THERE'S
A PRICE TO PAY,
AND THE FATE OF THOSE
WHO WOULD DEMAND A GOD
FOR A GODLESS WORLD?
THE HUMAN RACE
HAD TO BE DESTROYED.
THEY BROUGHT
THIS WORLD TO RUIN
THEN RAN AWAY.
OH, HOW THEY RAN.
MUCH IN THE SAME WAY THAT
YOU RAN AWAY FROM ROMDEAU,
A WORLD OF YOUR OWN MAKING.
VINCENT LAW IS SIMPLY
AN AFTER IMAGE,
LEFT BEHIND BY
PROXY ONE'S DESPAIR.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT THIS MEANS?
YOU'RE A PUPPET,
A PHANTOM,
AN IMPOSTER.
- IMPOSTER?
- A WELL-MADE ONE
AT LEAST.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU FOUND YOURSELF OVERWHELMED
BY A CRUSHING DESPAIR,
SO YOU RAN AWAY FROM
EVERYTHING YOU KNEW.
ACCEPT THE TRUTH.
YOU AND I ARE THE SAME.
- SHUT UP.
- THEN FIGHT IT
IF YOU DARE!
- NUMBER FIVE, NUMBER EIGHT,
ALL SILENT.
RESERVE POWER HAS BEEN
SHUT OFF THROUGHOUT THE DOME.
THERE'S NO STOPPING
THE COLLAPSE.
( sighs )
( gasps )
DAEDALUS.
- ( grunts )
- YES.
FOLLOW YOUR INSTINCTS.
SET YOURSELF FREE!
- ( grunts )
- ( both grunt )
- Proxy One:
I UNDERSTAND.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS
TO BE REJECTED.
TREATED LIKE
YOU WERE NOTHING.
- ( groans )
( shouts )
- ( grunts )
- I NO LONGER CARE WHO I WAS
BEFORE I BECAME WHAT I AM.
I'M MYSELF,
AND THAT'S ALL I NEED.
THERE'S ONLY ONE TRUTH
THAT REALLY MATTERS TO ME.
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
- JUST ONE TRUTH,
YES.
THOSE HUMANS WHO
DESTROYED THEMSELVES
LEFT A MESSAGE,
AND WE TORE IT UP,
THREW IT AWAY,
THEN RAN OFF.
ISN'T THAT JUST LIKE US?
- YES, IT IS.
I MUST ADMIT,
YOU AND I ARE BOTH
DEFINITELY ERGO PROXY,
PROXY ONE.
- ( screams )
- Daedalus:
STILL HOPING?
IT'S POINTLESS.
YOU NEVER CHANGE.
IT SICKENS ME.
- ( gasps )
- DON'T YOU GET IT YET?
OUR ROLES IN THIS
ARE FINISHED.
ROMDEAU'S FINISHED.
IT'S TIME FOR
THE FAILED CITIZENS
OF THIS CITY
TO VANISH FOREVER.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
WE CAN STILL DO.
- NO.
THIS IS THE END.
OUTSIDE, THE GODS THEMSELVES
ARE FIGHTING.
THERE'S NO PLACE FOR
THE SUBHUMANS OUT THERE.
THE BEST WE CAN DO NOW
IS KEEP QUIET.
YES, LIKE DONOV DID.
- ALL MY GRANDFATHER EVER
WANTED WAS TO MEET THE CREATOR.
EVEN IF THAT WAS
THE ONLY REASON I WAS BORN,
I CAN'T BRING MYSELF
TO CARE.
DESPITE THAT,
I STILL LOVE MY GRANDFATHER
WITH ALL MY HEART.
I JUST WANTED FOR HIM
TO LOVE ME BACK.
IS THAT SO MUCH
TO ASK FOR?
- Daedalus: IT WAS MORE
THAN THE REGENT COULD DO.
- ( gasps )
- YOU TWO,
YOU COULD BOTH
ONLY OPEN UP TO VINCENT.
I MEAN...
BOTH OF YOU FOUND
A CONNECTION TO ERGO PROXY.
AND AS FOR ME,
I...
- DAEDALUS...
- ( chuckles )
IT'S KIND OF A SHAME.
THE PROXIES CAN'T
SURVIVE FOR LONG
UNDER BLUE SKIES.
THE AMRITA CELLS
WON'T ALLOW IT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- THEY ARE ALSO...
TO BE WIPED OFF
THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
HELP!
- IS THAT WHERE
YOU'VE BEEN HIDING?
COME DOWN FROM THERE,
MY LOVE.
RE-L TWO, REAL.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
YOU'RE COMPLETE.
I'VE CREATED A GOD!
MY RE-L...
COME EMBRACE ME.
NO, WAIT.
DON'T GO!
WHY DOES THIS
ALWAYS HAVE TO HAPPEN?
WHY DOES SHE
LEAVE ME BEHIND?
PLEASE, COME BACK!
- DAEDALUS.
- HUH?
( chuckles )
OH?
( screams )
- ( gasps )
- BUT YOU ARE NOT
VINCENT LAW!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
THEY MEAN NOTHING TO YOU
BUT FAILURE.
- WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU KNOW?
- I TOLD YOU.
I KNOW EVERYTHING.
I AM--
- ME, I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY YOU CAME BACK.
TO KILL ME, RIGHT?
- Proxy One: THIS WORLD
DOESN'T DESERVE...
- OVER THERE.
- Vincent:
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE?
HOW MANY MORE
NEED TO DIE?!
- ENOUGH.
THE PROXY'S PURPOSE
IN THIS WORLD IS OVER.
( gasps )
- ( grunts )
IS THAT YOU, MONAD?
YOU'VE COME BACK?
( groans )
- MONAD?
- HELLO.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FORWARD TO THIS.
WE FINALLY GET TO MEET.
- STAY OUT OF THIS,
MONAD.
THE WORK OF
THE PROXIES IS OVER.
( coughing )
I'VE WON.
I'VE DESTROYED
THIS PITIFUL ATTEMPT
AT A NEW HUMAN RACE.
I MEET MY DEATH
FOREVER VICTORIOUS.
- ( gasps )
WAS THIS PART OF THE PLAN?
- THIS WAS MY REVENGE.
THE REST IS UP TO YOU.
IT'S YOUR WORLD
TO SHAPE NOW.
- HOW DARE YOU.
- ( grunts )
- YOU EXPECT ME TO
BEAR YOUR BURDEN AGAIN?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SAVE THIS WORLD.
- ( gasps )
- I UNDERSTAND YOUR BURDEN,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
DO THIS ANYMORE.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU CAN STOP NOW.
- THAT'S ENOUGH, MONAD.
- IT'S ALL COME TO AN END.
WE DON'T WANT ANYONE
TO SUFFER EVER AGAIN.
- MONAD...
- YOU'RE RUNNING AWAY AGAIN?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO LISTEN
TO WHAT ANYONE ELSE SAYS.
YOU CAN CLOSE THE SACRED EYE
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO.
- PLEASE, MONAD.
DON'T DO THIS.
- WHOA!
AAH!
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY WERE TOLD
NOT TO LISTEN
TO WHAT THE PROXY SAID.
BUT...
I STILL WANT TO HELP VINCE.
I WONDER WHY I'M DIFFERENT
FROM EVERYONE ELSE.
- Kristeva: THERE IS NOTHING
DIFFERENT ABOUT YOU.
- KRISTEVA.
- WHEN THEY SAY COGITO
CREATES A FLEDGLING SOUL,
THEY MEAN YOU ARE ACTING
ON YOUR OWN WILL.
BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN THAT
YOU'RE NOT FOLLOWING THE PROXY.
- THAT MEANS YOU CAN
HEAR IT TOO?
- JUST LISTEN TO YOUR HEART
AND DO WHAT IT TELLS YOU.
- ( gasps )
WHERE'S MY PAPA?
- HE TOLD ME TO
GIVE THIS TO YOU.
- ( chuckles )
- WE HAVE TO HURRY, PINO.
- MM!
- Daedalus: THE COGITO VIRUS
WAS BUILT INTO THE PROXY SYSTEM.
IT WAS SORT OF MANKIND'S
SAFETY VALVE.
AUTOREIVS WERE NOTHING
BUT BIT PLAYERS.
THEIR REVOLT HELPED BRING ABOUT
THE SYSTEM'S RUIN.
( coughing )
- THAT'S ENOUGH, DAEDALUS.
- I'M SAYING BRINGING MANKIND
BACK THROUGH THE PROXY SYSTEM,
IT WASN'T SUPPOSED TO BE
THE FIRST OPTION.
- ( gasps )
- EVERYTHING THAT'S
HAPPENING NOW
IS AN OBSTACLE
TO THE FIRST OPTION.
EVEN YOU AND I
ARE OBSTACLES
DESPITE OUR PAIN AND LOVE.
OUR SOULS ARE
RUINING EVERYTHING.
YOU'RE IN THEIR WAY.
- DAEDALUS...
- GO ON, RE-L.
YOU HAVE TO GO.
THERE'S STILL A TRUTH YOU
HAVEN'T FACED YET, ISN'T THERE?
( sighs )
YOU'VE GIVEN ME
SO MUCH TROUBLE.
EVEN SO,
YOU WERE ALWAYS
MY FAVORITE RE-L.
- DAEDALUS...
- THERE'S NOT MUCH TIME LEFT.
GO STRAIGHT THROUGH THERE.
FOLLOW THE PATH DOWN ALONG
THE MAINTENANCE RAIL
UNTIL YOU COME TO
THE PLUG VENT.
HURRY.
- I'M SORRY, DAEDALUS.
- I'M SICK OF YOUR APOLOGIES.
- I'D BETTER GO NOW,
DAEDALUS.
- GO ON.
RUN, RE-L!
VERY GOOD.
- WHAT'S THAT LIGHT?
- IT'S SACRED LIGHT.
A SIGN OF RESURRECTION.
- THE SUN.
- IT IS, YES.
IT SHINES SO BEAUTIFULLY.
THIS IS THE TRUE BLUE SKY
THAT STRETCHES OUT
FOREVER.
- SEE?  YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING ANYMORE.
- YES.
- ( gasps )
- ( mechanical whirring )
FIND ME.
- WHAT IS IT?
WHY DO YOU LOOK SO SAD?
PLEASE JUST TRY
AND LET ALL OF IT GO.
- I'M SORRY.
- ( gasps )
BUT WHY?
- BECAUSE I CAN'T LET
MYSELF FORGET ANYMORE.
- ( panting )
- Vincent: I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
REMEMBERING THE MISSION
THAT WAS PROGRAMMED
INTO ME.
IT'S THE FACES I ENCOUNTERED.
THE CONFRONTATIONS WE HAD.
THE LOVE AND SUPPORT GIVEN.
THE LIFE.
- WHAT IS IT THAT
DRAWS YOU TO THAT EXISTENCE?
IT'S DARK.
IT'S COLD.
AND THERE'S NEVER
ANY KNOWING
WHAT HORRORS LIE AHEAD.
- Vincent:
BUT THAT'S IT.
THAT'S WHAT LIFE IS.
IT'S ALL THAT YOU SAID,
BUT SOMEONE'S
WAITING FOR ME THERE.
- YOU MEAN HER?
- MM.
MONAD, I THINK THIS
BELONGS TO YOU.
- ( gasps )
MM.
( sighs )
VINCENT...
- GOOD-BYE, RE-L.
THANK YOU.
- ( gasps )
GOOD-BYE,
MY BELOVED.
- NO!
YOU MUSTN'T FLY SO HIGH.
- OHH.
I NEVER REALIZED THE WORLD
COULD BE SO BEAUTIFUL.
BUT NOW,
WHICH SKY AM I
TO SEARCH FOR?
( gasps )
I HEAR IT.
( sighs )
THE CRADLE
AND THE ARK.
( gasps )
IT WAS YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONES
WHO WERE CALLING ME.
I UNDERSTAND.
IT'S THE FUTURE YOU CHOSE,
VINCENT.
LET US SEE OUR FATE,
CREATOR.
- Daedalus: NO.
DON'T.
THE SKY...
YOU'LL...
( exhales )
- SO YOU CAME BACK.
- YES.
- VINCENT LAW.
YOU REALLY ARE THE SHADOW.
I WAS IMMORTAL,
BUT STILL YOU'VE DESTROYED ME.
YOU'VE STOPPED
THE PULSE DEAD.
- SHE PLAGUED YOU,
AND YET SHE STILL LOVED YOU.
SHE OFFERED HER LOVE
TO FLAWED, BROKEN SOULS
AND IN THAT
WE FOUND FREEDOM.
- VERY WELL SAID.
THE WOMAN WHO MADE
THE FUTURE A REALITY.
THAT'S A FITTING TITLE,
ISN'T IT?
SHE CERTAINLY IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR YOUR REALITY, VINCENT.
THE PRODIGAL SON RETURNS.
AND THIS IS
THE WAY OUR WORLD ENDS.
EXCEPT...
YOU WILL LIVE, VINCENT.
IT WILL BE THE MOST
FITTING PUNISHMENT
FOR THE CREATOR.
- DAMN IT.
I'VE MADE IT THIS FAR.
( gasps )
( grunts )
SHIT.
NOW WHAT?
- Pino: RE-L, RE-L!
- ( gasps )
RE-L, RE-L1
- PINO!
I HAVE FAITH.
- HMM!
- AREN'T YOU RAUL'S
AUTOREIV?
- I'M PROTECTING PINO NOW.
IT IS WHAT HE
ASKED ME TO DO.
IT IS MY FINAL DUTY
AS HIS ENTOURAGE.
- YEAH, AND SHE FOUND
THIS FOR ME AS WELL.
- WHAT ABOUT VINCENT?
- DON'T WORRY.
HE'S OKAY.
I CAN HEAR HIS VOICE.
- ( gasps )
- ( giggles )
AND I CAN SEE HIM TOO!
DISTANCE, 1,107 UNITS.
- HE IS SUCH
A PAIN IN THE ASS.
SO WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO?
SHOULD WE GO
AND PICK HIM UP?
- UH-HUH.
- THIS IS THE WORLD
THAT STANDS BEFORE US.
THE WORLD WE CALL
OUR REALITY.
BUT WITH RE-L AND PINO
AND THE OTHER
SURVIVORS WITH ME,
I KNOW I CAN
FACE THIS WORLD.
A WORLD THAT IS FINALLY
READY TO HEAL ITSELF.
FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN THOUSANDS OF YEARS,
MANKIND RETURNS
TO MEET ITS EARTH.
AND NOW THE TRUE STRUGGLE
MUST BEGIN.
I AM ERGO PROXY.
THE AGENT OF DEATH.
- ( rock music playing )
♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES
IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪