- Re-l: AS A YOUNG GIRL,
I THOUGHT THE WORLD
WOULD END WHEN I DIED.
IT WAS A CHILDISH IDEA.
I JUST COULDN'T IMAGINE A WORLD
THAT COULD EXIST WITHOUT ME.
STOP HOVERING AROUND ME
IN THAT THING.
- HEY, LET'S NOT FORGET
THIS IS YOUR FAULT, RE-L.
BOTH YOURS AND PINO'S.
- I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
- YOU FELL IN ALL BY YOURSELF.
- THAT'S HARSH.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO DIE.
- IT WOULDN'T HAVE KILLED YOU.
I SEE THE DOME.
- I AM MYSELF.
NOT SOMEONE ELSE.
I KNOW HOW STRANGE IT WAS.
I REMEMBER.
I KNOW MY MEMORIES
CAN BE TREACHEROUS.
BUT OF THIS MEMORY,
I'M CERTAIN.
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD UNWINDS ♪
♪ INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL ♪
♪ MY PLACE ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- YAY, SHOPPING!
- A COMPLETELY ABANDONED
GROCERY STORE.
THIS IS GREAT.
- THIS PLACE IS LIKE
A SHELL.
EVERYTHING BUT PEOPLE.
- Iggy: RE-L! ( echoing )
- IGGY!
NO AUTOREIVS, EITHER.
I'M GETTING PARANOID.
- WELCOME TO OUR STORE.
- Vincent:
HEY, FIND ANYTHING OUT THERE?
- SAME NOTHING
AS EVERYWHERE ELSE.
- SO WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HAVE SOMETHING TO EAT?
- I TOLD YOU I WAS
SICK OF BEANS.
- YOU NEVER SAID THAT.
YOU WANT SOMETHING TO DRINK?
COFFEE, TEA?
- GINGER ALE.
- YOU DRANK THE GINGER ALE.
WE'RE OUT.
- I'M FINE THEN.
- WHY IS IT ALWAYS
LIKE THIS?
- HOW LONG ARE WE STAYING HERE?
- WHAT?
- WE SHOULD LEAVE ONCE
THE SHIP'S RESTOCKED.
- SHOULDN'T WE WAIT TILL
WE'VE TRIED ALL THE FLAVORS?
- THIS IS SUPPOSED
TO BE YOUR JOURNEY.
WHAT NOW?
- HERE YOU GO.
HELP YOURSELF.
- I THOUGHT THAT AUTOREIVS
KNEW HOW TO COOK.
- THE PINO SPECIAL.
AND IT'S VERY NUTRITIOUS.
- GO AND FINISH
STOCKING THE SHIP.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I'M GONNA STAND GUARD.
- WHAT ABOUT YOUR FOOD?
- I'LL EAT LATER.
- ( groans )
I DON'T EAT,
SO I GUESS YOU'LL GET
TO HAVE IT ALL BY YOURSELF.
- PINO,
I DON'T KNOW.
IT LOOKS GREAT!
( retching )
- DAMN IT.
I SWEAR THE TWO OF THEM,
THEY'RE GONNA DRIVE ME CRAZY.
YOU SHOULD TRY RELAXING
ONCE IN A WHILE.
- YOU CHEWED ME OUT
FOR NOT PACKING FAST ENOUGH.
WEREN'T YOU GONNA
STAND GUARD?
- I HAVEN'T FINISHED
EATING MY MEAL.
- WHAT IS WITH YOU?
- DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- NO, NOTHING.
OH, BY THE WAY.
GINGER ALE.
I FOUND SOME IN BACK.
- THANK YOU.
- HEY, VINCE,
WILL THIS WORK OKAY?
- WE'RE GONNA GO
COLLECT SOME WATER.
GINGER ALE.
I FOUND SOME IN BACK.
- THANK YOU.
- ( bottle opens )
- THIS DRINK TASTES FUNNY.
- WHAT IS WITH YOU?
- ARE YOU DONE PACKING?
- I WAS THINKING
MAYBE WE COULD STAY HERE
FOR A WHILE.
- WE'RE LEAVING ONCE
WE'VE RESUPPLIED.
- WHAT'S THE BIG RUSH?
HOW OFTEN DO WE GET A CHANCE
TO RELAX LIKE THIS?
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHY DO YOU TALK THAT WAY?
- HUH?
- WHY CAN'T YOU TRY BEING
A LITTLE NICER?
- IF YOU EXPECT ME
TO CODDLE THE TWO OF YOU--
- I THOUGHT YOU
HAD FEELINGS FOR ME, RE-L.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- COME ON, DON'T YOU LIKE ME?
- BACK OFF!
GET UP.
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
ENOUGH, VINCENT,
STOP FOOLING AROUND.
- SO WHAT'S LEFT?
- ( door opens )
- HUH?
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN HERE?
- ARE YOU DONE PLAYING
YOUR WEIRD LITTLE PRANKS?
- WHAT?
I'M PACKING THE SHIP.
- SPARE THE EXCUSES.
WHERE'S THE AUTOREIV?
- IF YOU MEAN PINO,
SHE WAS JUST HERE.
- HERE I AM.
- HEY!
- COME BACK!
- ( grunting )
- OPEN THE DOOR!
- NOT TILL YOU CALM DOWN.
NOW TELL ME WHAT PINO DID.
- IT WANTS TO KILL ME.
- WHAT?  NO, SHE DOESN'T.
- IT'S DANGEROUS!
- YOU'RE STAYING IN THERE
FOR A WHILE.
- Vincent: DID YOU DO SOMETHING?
- Pino: I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
- YOU MUST HAVE DONE SOMETHING.
- I THOUGHT SHE'D LIKE IT.
- IT'S OKAY.
JUST TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED.
- ALL I DID WAS TRY TO GIVE
HER ANOTHER BOWL OF FOOD.
- YOU MEAN YOUR FOOD.
THAT'S A FAR CRY
FROM TRYING TO KILL HER.
RE-L!
- WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
- WHO IS THAT?
WATCH HER.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- THERE'S SOMEONE UP THERE.
DID SHE JUMP FROM UP HERE?
WHY?
- DON'T MOVE.
- RE-L, IS THAT YOU?
- TELL ME EXACTLY
WHAT YOU ARE.
- WHAT?  YOU KNOW ME.
IT'S VINCENT.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I'M ASKING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
ARE YOU HURT OR SOMETHING?
- DON'T MAKE ANOTHER MOVE.
JUST ANSWER MY QUESTION.
WHAT ARE YOU?
- YOU KNOW I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO FIGURE THAT OUT MYSELF.
- IS THAT YOUR
ANSWER THIS TIME?
DON'T YOU DARE MAKE A MOVE.
- RE-L.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
- IS RE-L OKAY?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT HER.  NOW
WE JUST NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- VINCE, WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- NOT FAR.
DO YOU LIKE ME, PINO?
- YEAH, I LIKE YOU A LOT, VINCE.
BECAUSE YOU LIKE
TO EAT MY FOOD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, VINCE?
- WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE HER LYING
ON THE COLD HARD GROUND.
YOU SEE,
WE HAVE TO
GIVE HER A PROPER BURIAL.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
DID RE-L DIE?
- SHE HAD TO GO AWAY.
THIS IS HOW PEOPLE
LEAVE THE WORLD.
( panting )
RE-L!
PINO!
THE SHIP IS GONE.
THEY LEFT ME BEHIND.
I'M ALONE AGAIN.
- WHERE'S RE-L GOING?
- RE-L'S NO LONGER WITH US.
IT'LL BE EASIER THIS WAY.
- BUT THE OTHER
ONE'S STILL HERE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THERE'S ANOTHER ONE
OF YOU ALSO, VINCE.
- THERE'S ONLY ONE VINCENT.
I'M THE ONE YOU LIKE,
I'M THE ONE WHO EATS
YOUR SPECIAL FOOD.
- NO, THE OTHER VINCE
ATE MY FOOD.
THERE ARE TWO VINCES,
AND THERE ARE TWO RE-LS.
I WONDER WHY THERE'S ONLY
ONE PINO HERE-- HUH?
- ( grunting )
- YOU'RE NOT THE REAL ONE.
- YOU'RE AN AUTOREIV.
- NO!
- DAMN IT!
RE-L.
( gasps )
RE-L, PLEASE!
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
IF YOU DIE ON ME?
YOU STILL HAVE TO
SHOOT ME, REMEMBER?
THANK GOD!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE DEAD.
- YOU DID?
THEN MAYBE YOU HAVE
A LITTLE DEATH WISH, TOO.
- ARE YOU OK?
- DID YOU REALLY JUST SAVE
MY LIFE?
- YOU HAD ME WORRIED.
- WHAT ARE OUR COORDINATES?
- LET'S SEE.
WE'RE 12,183,728 POINT--
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU'RE THE REAL ONE.
THERE WERE TWO VINCENTS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU'RE A PROXY, TOO.
- NO MATTER WHERE WE GO,
WE'LL NEVER BE ACCEPTED.
THIS IS MY TERRITORY.
AN ETERNITY OF SOLITUDE.
WITHOUT COMMUNICATION.
WITHOUT UNDERSTANDING.
WHY AM I THIS WAY?
WHY CAN'T I BE SOMETHING WORTHY
OF LOVE AND ACCEPTANCE?
I FOUND IF I PRETENDED
TO BE SOMEONE ELSE,
I COULD BE LOVED.
BUT AFTER A WHILE I REALIZED
THE PERSON THEY LOVED
WASN'T ME.
I AM NO ONE,
THEREFORE I AM LOVED
BY NO ONE.
AND SO I DECIDED
TO END MYSELF.
BUT EVEN IF WE WANT
TO END OURSELVES, WE CAN'T.
SO WE ENDED THE OTHERS.
FOR IN THEM WE FOUND REFLECTIONS
OF OURSELVES.
IT DIDN'T WORK.
IN THE END, THE ONLY ONE
LEFT WAS THE ONE WE WISHED
TO BE RID OF.
THAT RADIANCE.
THROUGH YOU,
I CAN FINALLY END MYSELF.
LET'S US END IT,
YOU AND I TOGETHER.
I'M NOT THE SAME AS YOU.
WE'RE BOTH ALONE.
BOTH OF US HAVE
BEEN LEFT BEHIND.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING I NEED
TO KNOW BEFORE I'M FINISHED.
- WHAT DO YOU NEED TO KNOW?
- I NEED TO KNOW WHAT I AM.
WE SAY THAT, AND YET
WE STAY HERE.
WE STAY HERE
BECAUSE THE TRUTH SCARES US.
- YOU'RE WRONG!
- FROM BIRTH TO DEATH,
THE STORY EVOLVES.
THE COMPLETE PICTURE
OF WHO WE ARE IS ONLY CLEAR
ONCE OUR STORY COMES
TO AN END.
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL
TAKE THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO SKIP TO THE END.
- RE-L...
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- STAY BACK!
- DON'T WORRY.
IT'S THE REAL ME.
SO JUST ASK ME SOMETHING
THAT ONLY I WOULD KNOW.
- I'M NOT GOING
ANY FURTHER WITH YOU.
- BUT WHY?
- I'M SICK AND TIRED OF THIS.
- HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
- DON'T MOVE!
THIS IS GOODBYE, VINCENT.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA LEAVE,
PLEASE JUST KILL ME.
- YOU UNDERSTAND NOW,
DON'T YOU?
YOU DON'T GET TO BE
WITH ANYONE.
THE BEST THING WE CAN DO FOR
EVERYONE IS DISAPPEAR FOREVER.
- JUST SHUT UP!
- LOOK.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- OUR GRAVE.
- THEY'RE THE PEOPLE
FROM THIS TOWN?
- SO THAT WE'RE NEVER LONELY.
- I'M GLAD
I DIDN'T BECOME LIKE YOU.
- YOU'RE JUST LIKE ME.
YOU BRING MISERY
TO THOSE AROUND YOU.
THIS WAY IS BETTER.
THIS WAY THEY DON'T SUFFER.
- RE-L.
- STAY BACK.
- DON'T WORRY. IT'S THE REAL ME.
NO, WAIT.
THIS IS STILL HIS GAME.
I'M NOT FALLING
FOR THIS AGAIN.
- I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
- BUT I'M CONFIDENT THAT
VINCE AND THE OTHER VINCE
ARE BOTH IN HERE.
- WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON DOWN THERE?
- Pino: LOOK!
- Vincent: RE-L.
- STAY BACK!
- PLEASE, NOT AGAIN.
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
- ( choking )
- VINCE, STOP IT!
- NOW YOU GOT WHAT YOU WANTED.
NO, IT'S NOT--
IT'S NOT REAL.
- ( screaming )
- PINO!
THIS--
THIS WAS REAL?
- SO LONG AS WE EXIST,
WE BRING NOTHING BUT MISERY.
- YOU DID THIS.
- WE DID THIS.
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO ME?
- IT PLEASES US TO DO SO.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO IF I'M ALONE.
- WE NEVER HAVE TO
BE ALONE.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
- Pino: OVER THERE!
- I'M AFRAID OF BEING ALONE.
I'M AFRAID OF NOT KNOWING
WHAT I AM.
BUT WORSE,
I'M AFRAID OF FINDING OUT.
THE PEOPLE I WANT
TO BE WITH WILL DIE
BECAUSE THEY'RE WITH ME.
IF THAT'S WHAT I AM,
I MIGHT AS WELL DIE, TOO.
- VINCE.
- NO, DON'T GO!
YOU'LL DIE!
IS IT YOU?  OR IT?
ARE YOU JUST SOMETHING
THAT LOOKS LIKE VINCENT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE STILL WEARING THAT.
- IT'S NOT LIKE
I CAN HELP IT.
I MEAN, SOMEONE HAS
TO TAKE THE HELM.
( sneezes )
- WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU CAME BACK.
- HUH?
- PINO AND I COULDN'T HAVE
RECOVERED THE SHIP WITHOUT YOU.
- WELL, IT HELPED
THAT IT HADN'T DRIFTED
TOO FAR AWAY FROM US YET.
OH, AND THANKS A LOT.
- FOR WHAT?
- FOR HAVING FAITH
THAT IT WAS THE REAL ME.
- IT'S BECAUSE THE IMPOSTER
DIDN'T LEAVE A REFLECTION
ON THE WATER.
- HUH?
- YOU MUST HAVE NOTICED THAT,
TOO, RIGHT?
- THE PROXY HOPED TO FIND
ACCEPTANCE FROM OTHERS
BY CHANGING HIS APPEARANCE
TO FILL THEIR NEEDS.
I USED TO THINK ALONG
SIMILAR LINES TO THAT.
BUT THEN I MET RE-L
AND PINO,
AND THEY CAME WITH ME
ON THIS JOURNEY.
AND WITH THEM, I CAN MAYBE
CHANGE WHO I REALLY AM.
AND IF I CHANGE,
MAYBE MY UNDERSTANDING
OF LIFE WILL CHANGE AS WELL.
BECAUSE OF THAT,
I COULD NEVER LET MYSELF DIE,
EVEN IF I AM A PROXY.
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING
TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN ♪
♪ CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪
- Woman: NEXT TIME, DUE TO
CIRCUMSTANCES BEYOND OUR CONTROL
WE'VE CHANGED
OUR SHOW FORMAT DRAMATICALLY
TO BRING YOU A SPECIAL PROGRAM.
DON'T MISS IT.
ON MCQ TV.