- ( wind whistling )
- WHOA.
WHOA.
THANKS A LOT, VINCE.
- ( Vincent's voice )
HAVING BEEN DRIVEN FROM ROMDEAU
BY A MONSTER
CALLED THE PROXY,
I BEGAN MY JOURNEY
INTO THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
- ( playing harmonica )
- LOSING ALL ELSE,
I'M LEFT WITH ONLY MY DOUBTS
AND A SINGLE PATH
STILL OPEN TO ME.
SO WE TRAVEL TO MOSK,
MY BIRTHPLACE,
IN THE HOPES
OF FINDING SOMETHING,
ANYTHING.
WE'VE BEEN TRAVELING
FOR SEVERAL DAYS NOW.
OUR BODIES
HAVE GROWN WEAK.
THE CLOUDED SKIES
HANG HEAVY ABOVE US.
FROZEN DESOLATION
THAT STRETCHES ON FOREVER
TO THE ENDS
OF THE HORIZON.
THE DISMAL VIEW
CLOSES IN AROUND US,
CHILLING US TO THE BONE,
CHILLING US
TO THE VERY SOUL.
- ( rock music playing )
- ♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD
UNWINDS INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- Derrida: SO HOW IS SHE?
- Daedalus: FINE.  I KNOW
IT'S ONLY BEEN THREE DAYS,
BUT ADAPTATION RATES
FOR THE BIOMIMETIC AMRITA CELLS
SEEM TO BE PROGRESSING
FAVORABLY.
WE'RE STILL WATCHING FOR ANY
COMPLICATIONS THAT MAY ARISE
DUE TO THE INFECTION
AND HER WEAKENED IMMUNE SYSTEM.
SO FAR, THOUGH,
EVERYTHING IS LOOKING GOOD.
- ( beeping )
- Daedalus: BARRING
COMPLICATIONS,
I THINK WE COULD BE
SENDING HER HOME FOR BED REST
AS EARLY AS TODAY.
IF YOU LIKE,
I WOULD BE HAPPY
TO BRING HER BY LATER.
- I HAVE THE LATEST DATA.
- SHE'S ALMOST
COMPLETELY HEALED.
YOU NEVER CEASE
TO AMAZE ME, RE-L.
- CHIEF DAEDALUS.
- Husserl: THE PROXY
HAS VANISHED
FROM THE OUTSKIRTS
OF ROMDEAU.
THIS FACT
IS IMMUTABLE.
- Kristeva: IF YOU ARE
IN POSSESSION
OF ANY SOLID INFORMATION, WE ASK
THAT YOU PLEASE DISCLOSE--
- Derrida: DON'T FORGET,
WHILE WE ARE INDIVIDUALS,
WE ARE ALSO
A SINGLE ENTITY.
- IT'S JUST THAT
IF THE RESEARCH BUREAU
HAS DISCOVERED A SYSTEM
FOR TRACKING THE PROXY,
THEN THE SECURITY BUREAU
SHOULD--
- Husserl: WE ARE WELL AWARE...
- Lacan: OF THESE
INTER-BUREAU QUARRELS.
WE ARE WELL AWARE
OF THE ENTIRETY
OF ROMDEAU.
- Berkeley: OUR WORDS ALONE
SHOULD BE SUFFICIENT PROOF
AS TO WHETHER THE PROXY
IS PRESENT OR NOT.
- Husserl: THE PROXY
IS NOT IN ROMDEAU.
THAT MUCH IS CERTAIN.
- FINE.  THEN LET ME ASK
A QUESTION OF THE WHOLE ENTITY:
WHAT EXACTLY
IS THE REASONING
BEHIND ALLOWING A CITIZEN TO
RETURN FROM THE OUTSIDE WORLD,
WHEN IT HAS NEVER BEEN
ALLOWED BEFORE?
- Derrida: YOU ARE NOT
AUTHORIZED TO REQUEST DISCLOSURE
OF INFORMATION RELATED
TO THAT MATTER.
- Husserl: YOUR TIME IS UP.
- ( Re-L's voice )
I THOUGHT KNOWING THE TRUTH
WOULD MAKE ME HAPPY.
I WAS SUCH A FOOL.
I'M WEAK.
MY CURIOSITY WOULD NOT
ALLOW ME TO BE HAPPY.
ALL OF MY
GRANDFATHER'S LIES...
THERE'S A WORLD
OUTSIDE THIS CITY.
THERE ARE PEOPLE
I KNOW THAT NOW.
AND THERE IS NO ESCAPE
FROM WHAT YOU KNOW.
WHAT'S THAT DOING HERE?
DAEDALUS, SO YOU DID KNOW
AFTER ALL.
- ( beeping )
- ( elevator stops )
- ( gasps )
- Daedalus: THEY'RE LIKE
CLOCKWORK WOMBS.
- DAEDALUS.
- THIS IS THE BIRTHPLACE
OF TRUE CITIZENS OF ROMDEAU--
THE WOMBSYS.
- DAEDALUS, TELL ME WHY.
- I'LL BE TAKING MY SCALPEL
BACK FROM YOU NOW.
IF EVEN ONE OF THEM
GOES MISSING,
PEOPLE MIGHT START
TO ASK QUESTIONS.
BY THE WAY, WELL DONE.
YOUR CURIOSITY
IS QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
COME WITH ME.
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU.
FROM FUNCTION TO FORM,
THIS PRODUCTION LINE
IS FAR AND AWAY
THE MOST EFFICIENT BIOLOGICAL
AND MECHANICAL SYSTEM
THAT EXISTS
WITHIN THE DOME.
IT IS FROM THIS PLACE
THAT THE FOUNDATIONS
OF WHAT MAKES A GOOD
FELLOW CITIZEN
ARE PREPARED.
EVERY STEP CONTROLLED,
EVERY DETAIL SCRUTINIZED,
ALL BALANCE MAINTAINED.
POPULATION MANAGEMENT
AND SOCIAL STABILITY
ARE ESSENTIAL FOR MAINTAINING
AN ORDERED DAILY LIFE
WITHIN A CITY
LIKE ROMDEAU.
RE-L?
- I'M FINE.
IT'S JUST--
I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN
THAT PEOPLE WERE GROWN IN TUBES.
I'VE KNOWN ABOUT IT AND
I'VE ACCEPTED IT MY ENTIRE LIFE,
BUT-- BUT THE REALITY
OF IT IS--
- SEEING IT
CAN BE DISTURBING.
OPERATIONAL INTERVENTION
IN EARLY DEVELOPMENT--
ONLY BY OUR CONSTANT
INTERVENTION
DOES THE HUMAN RACE
CONTINUE.
- ARE YOU SO SURE?
ARE YOU?
THEN HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
THE WORLD I SAW OUTSIDE?
DAEDALUS, CAN YOU
JUST TELL ME,
IF THERE IS A VIABLE LIVING
WORLD OUTSIDE THESE WALLS,
THEN WHY DO THE CITIZENS
NEED THE DOME ANYMORE?
HASN'T ITS USEFULNESS
FINALLY COME TO AN END?
WHY KEEP IT A SECRET?
- I'M AN IDIOT.
I CAME VERY CLOSE TO LOSING
SOMEONE IMPORTANT TO ME.
I'M SORRY.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE
LET YOU GO OUTSIDE.
- IT'S TOO LATE NOW.
ONCE YOU KNOW THE TRUTH, THERE'S
NO ESCAPING IT EVER AGAIN.
- YES.
- YOU STILL REMEMBER
OUR PROMISE?
- YES.
BUT, FIRST OFF,
I NEED YOU TO HELP ME
SAVE FACE.
- I NEED TO SEE
MY GRANDFATHER.
- ( Re-L's voice )
HE'S RIGHT.
BEFORE I SET OUT
ON ANY JOURNEY,
THERE'S SOMEONE
I NEED TO SEE.
- ( Vincent's voice )
A WORLD WITHOUT A TRACE OF LIFE,
WITHOUT THE SLIGHTEST SCAR
OF HUMAN CIVILIZATION,
FAR FROM MOSK,
OUR HOPEFUL
FINAL DESTINATION.
AND PAINTED
ON EVERY FACE,
A PALLOR OF FATIGUE.
- GRANDFATHER, I'M SORRY
I'VE CAUSED SO MUCH TROUBLE.
- Lacan: RE-L, ARE YOU
FINALLY SATISFIED?
- Derrida: WHAT DID YOU SEE
IN THE WORLD OUTSIDE?
- Lacan: IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN SPEAK FREELY HERE.
- Husserl: WE WOULD HAVE YOU
SPEAK NOW.
- THERE WERE PEOPLE
OUT THERE,
REAL LIVING PEOPLE,
A WHOLE WORLD.
- Derrida: REALLY?
- WHY DO YOU HIDE
WHAT'S OUT THERE?
- Lacan: RE-L--
- WHAT ARE YOU SO AFRAID OF
OUT THERE?
- Husserl: YOU'VE SAID
QUITE ENOUGH.
- I'M TALKING
TO MY GRANDFATHER.
- ( Re-L's voice )
YOU WON'T ANSWER, WILL YOU?
- ( wind whistling )
- - ( Vincent's voice )
I WONDER HOW LONG IT'S BEEN
SINCE WE LEFT ROMDEAU.
EVERYONE LOOKS SO TIRED.
WE MOVE ON,
LEAVING ONE MORE MAN
SLEEPING IN THE DIRT.
- RE-L.
- RE-L!  RE-L!
- HE WAS SENT TO ME
FOR READJUSTMENT,
DUE TO INACCURATE
JUDGMENT VALUATIONS.
AND SO I PUT HIM HERE
FOR SAFEKEEPING.
I'LL GO SET THINGS UP.
- ( door opens )
- IF IT WASN'T FOR THE PRINCE,
I'D BE SCRAP BY NOW.
YOU'VE LOST SOME WEIGHT,
HAVEN'T YOU?
YOU LOOK PALE TOO.
YOU'RE A MESS WITHOUT ME,
AREN'T YOU, RE-L?
HEY, COME ON, RE-L.
WHY WON'T YOU
TALK TO ME?
- ( Re-L's voice )
BECAUSE EVEN NOW YOU'RE BEING--
- GOOD.
NOW IT'S MY TURN
TO KEEP MY PROMISE TO YOU.
- HOLD ON.
BEFORE THAT...
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I DIDN'T TELL YOU--
IGGY'S BEEN GIVEN
THE SAME PROCEDURE
AS MY ASSISTANTS.
- YOU CUT OFF HIS CONNECTION
TO THE SURVEILLANCE STRUCTURE?
- YES.
TAKE COMFORT
THAT IGGY'S EARS
NO LONGER BELONG
TO YOUR GRANDFATHER.
- SO I CAN SPEAK FREELY
ABOUT THE SECURITY BUREAU?
HMM.
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS.
SO I HAVE
THE AUTOPSY REPORT
ON THAT THING OF YOURS
FROM A WHILE BACK--
THE THING FROM DEEP INSIDE
THE OUTER BLOCK.
BUT BEFORE THAT,
I'D BETTER TELL YOU
EVERYTHING
RIGHT FROM THE BEGINNING.
- Raul: THIS ERA
IS COMING TO AN END.
- Kristeva: CHIEF?
- IT HAS BECOME APPARENT TO ME
THAT THE REGENT'S LIFE FORCE
IS GRADUALLY STARTING
TO DECLINE.
IT IS MOST CLEARLY EVIDENT
IN HIS COMPLEXION.
- I'M AN ENTOURAGE AUTOREIV,
AND THEREFORE I MUST RECORD
SUCH STATEMENTS.
- I WANT THEM
TO HEAR ME.
ANY SIGNS OF THE PROXY?
- NOW THAT IT'S NO LONGER
IN THE CITY,
OUR REMOTE FOLLOW-UP SYSTEM
IS MAKING TRACKING DIFFICULT.
- THEN LET'S SIMPLIFY.
I WANT TO PULL THE RELICS FROM
THE SECRET UNDERGROUND VAULTS.
- ( beeps )
- INTELLIGENCE RELEASE MODE
CONFIRMED?
- YES.
- YOU MEAN
THE LONG-RANGE CRAFTS
THAT WERE USED
FOR THE MOSK OPERATION?
- LET'S DWELL ON THE THOUGHT
OF THE DAY:
IF YOU'RE GOING TO EAT
THE POISON,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
EAT THE PLATE.
- Daedalus: WE CALLED IT
THE MONAD PROXY.
- MONAD?
- IT WAS PLUNDERED
FROM THE MOSK DOME.
IT WAS ALREADY HERE
WHEN I WAS FIRST ASSIGNED
TO THE FACILITY.
I WASN'T TOLD
THE REASONS
AS TO WHY
IT WAS KEPT SHACKLED
OR THE REASONS WHY WE WERE
FORBIDDEN TO AWAKEN IT.
BUT THERE ARE SOME THINGS
I DO KNOW.
FIRST, IT IS
IN NO WAY A PERSON.
FROM BOTH A THEOLOGICAL
AS WELL AS A BIOLOGICAL
PERSPECTIVE,
WE WERE UNABLE
TO IDENTIFY ANYTHING,
EVEN DOWN TO GENDER.
IN MY OPINION, AS FAR AS
ITS SIGNIFICANCE TO ROMDEAU,
THE PROXY SHOULD BE
THOUGHT OF AS--
AS MORE OF
A LIFE FORCE.
- SO IT'S NOT A MONSTER.
- NO.  IN FACT, IT'S REALLY
MUCH MORE LIKE A GOD.
IT'S THE KEY
TO SUPPORTING THE FIELD
NECESSARY FOR OUR SURVIVAL
ON THIS DEVASTATED WORLD.
- IT SOUNDS
ALMOST LIKE MAGIC.
- WE DO HAVE DATA
TO BACK THIS UP.
COME HERE, LOOK.
THIS SPECIMEN IS COMPOSED
OUT OF THESE CELLS.
THEY'RE CALLED
AMRITA CELLS.
AND THEY'RE, AS BEST
AS WE CAN TELL, IMMORTAL.
IF WE COULD DISCOVER
THEIR SECRET, WHO KNOWS?
- THE PROXY IS THE KEY
TO OUR SURVIVAL.
BUT NOW
IT'S BEEN LOST.
SO THEN,
ROMDEAU MUST ALSO HAVE--
- YES.  WE MUST
NEVER FORGET
WE HAVE OUR OWN
LITTLE SECRETS, DON'T WE?
- THERE'S MORE THAN ONE
PROXY OUT THERE.
- YES, THAT WOULD BE IT.
- HEY, DON'T TREAT ME
LIKE I'M AN IDIOT.
- ALL RIGHT.
THEN THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
I WANT TO ASK YOU.
TELL ME, WHERE DID YOU
EVER MANAGE
TO LEARN
THE WORD "PROXY"?
- YOU KNOW YOU LEFT ME ALONE
IN YOUR OFFICE.
- RE-L.
- TO BE HONEST, I--
I DON'T KNOW WHY I'M SO DRAWN
TO ALL OF THIS.
- COULDN'T HELP YOURSELF?
- IT'S NOT JUST THAT.
SUDDENLY SOMETHING
HAD CHANGED.
IF I HAD SIMPLY
DONE MY JOB
AND WALKED AWAY
FROM THIS MESS,
I'D STILL HAVE
MY LIFE--
MY LIFE BEFORE I'D RUINED
EVERYTHING WITH THESE QUESTIONS
AND THEIR
TERRIBLE ANSWERS.
BUT--
- BUT?
- I ASKED MY QUESTIONS
AND THEN I DISCOVERED
A WHOLE WORLD I NEVER KNEW.
THAT'S MY TROUBLE
WITH QUESTIONS--
I STILL DON'T KNOW
HOW TO TAKE THEM BACK.
- YES, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE YOU.
SEE, I'M KIND OF
THE SAME WAY.
I LIKE ANSWERS.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
- DAEDALUS.
- HMM?
- ( door opens )
- ( Vincent's voice )
IT'S JUST THE TWO OF US NOW.
NO, THAT THING'S
AN AUTOREIV.
I'M ALONE, AGAIN.
- VINCE, WE'RE GOING
TO WHERE YOU WERE BORN, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- WHAT KIND OF PLACE
IS IT?
- IT'S--
YOU'LL SEE
WHEN WE GET THERE.
- Iggy: RE-L!
- ( gunshot )
- IGGY.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
THIS IS A SECURED FACILITY.
- ( device beeps )
- CHIEF.
- ( gasps )
THE COGITO VIRUS?
IT CAN'T BE.
- ( gunshot )
- THE FOOLS.
- ( siren wailing )
- THEY'RE WEAPONIZING
THE COGITO VIRUS.
- LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE AFTER ME.
- RAUL-- HIS RECKLESSNESS
IS GOING TO GET US ALL KILLED.
- AT LEAST NOW WE KNOW
HOW FAR HE'S WILLING TO GO.
- HE WANTS THE PROXY.
- AND ONLY ONE MAN
HOLDS THE KEY--
VINCENT LAW.
- ( device beeps )
- RE-L, I'VE GOT
A RESPONSE
FROM OUR PLANT
INSIDE THE SECURITY BUREAU.
I'M STARTING A TRACE
ON THE TARGET.
RE-L!
- RE-L!
- ( Vincent's voice )
ALL ALONE,
THE LAST ONE STANDING IS LEFT
WITH NOTHING BUT TIME TO THINK.
THE MEMORIES
I CAN'T RECALL
EVEN IF I WANTED
TO FORGET THEM.
THAT UNRESOLVED THING
INSIDE MY MIND
THAT REFUSES
TO SIT STILL--
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT IS THIS THING
INSIDE OF ME?
EVEN IF I KNEW,
WHAT GOOD
WOULD IT DO ME NOW--
NOW,
WHEN THERE'S
NO ONE LEFT?
IT'S SAFE TO SAY
WE'LL NEVER MEET AGAIN.
THAT'S WHY
I MUST FORGET.
BUT HOW?
HOW CAN I FORGET
THAT FACE?
- ( computer beeping )
- ( music playing )
- Rino: GOOD THINGS,
COMING THINGS,
MOVING THINGS,
SAD THINGS, HAPPY THINGS,
SINGLE THINGS,
COUPLED THINGS,
SHINING THINGS.