- ( metal squeaking )
- ( people chattering )
- ( snoring )
- ( door opens and closes )
- TIMOTHY.
- ( woman panting )
- ( door opens and closes )
- HUH?
- YOU CAN COME OUT NOW,
TIMOTHY.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
- ( harmonica playing )
- TIMOTHY!
THAT'S WEIRD.
- ( rock music playing )
- ♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE WORLD
UNWINDS INSIDE OF ME ♪
♪ YOU COMPLETE MY FATE ♪
♪ THE HALO CRAWLS AWAY ♪
♪ YOU REFILL MY PLACE ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME ♪
♪ COME AND SAVE ME. ♪
- ( clock chiming )
- ( mechanical waltz playing )
- Husserl: THERE'S NO SENSE
INTERFERING
WITH THE DOME ESCAPEES.
- Raul: FORGIVE MY IGNORANCE,
BUT AREN'T WE OBLIGATED
TO PUNISH THOSE
WHO TRY AND ABANDON ROMDEAU?
- Derrida: STRICTLY SPEAKING.
- Berkeley: PEOPLE HOLDING
SUCH BROAD VIEWS OF THE LAW
TEND TO BE FAR AWAY
FROM ITS CONSEQUENCE.
- Lacan: YOU ARE CHIEF OF
THE CITIZEN SECURITY BUREAU.
KNOW YOUR PLACE.
- YES.
- BLOOD PRESSURE AND HEART RATE
ARE BOTH INCREASING.
- BREATHING IS IRREGULAR.
- HOW RIDICULOUS.
WHAT'S THE POINT
OF YOUR OBSERVATIONS
WHEN I OBVIOUSLY HAVE CONTROL
OVER MY EMOTIONS?
- Husserl: PRIDE GOETH
BEFORE A FALL.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
LET ME CHECK YOUR VITALS.
- ( grunts )
THAT HIDEOUS FACE.
( grunts )
I WILL NOT BE
DISGRACED BY IT AGAIN.
NOT AGAIN.
- ( Re-L laughing )
DAEDALUS.
( laughing )
- ( toy whirring )
- HUH?
( laughing )
- I'M COLD.
- YOU ARE RUNNING A HIGH FEVER.
YOUR CHILL IS
DUE TO A CONTRACTING
OF THE BLOOD VESSELS.  SOON
YOU'LL BEGIN TO HAVE CONVULSIONS
AND DEATH WILL FOLLOW.
- ( gasps )
VINCENT.
WHERE-- WHERE HAS HE GONE?
DON'T TELL ME
HE'S ALREADY--
- NO, I PROMISE
HE HASN'T LEFT YET.
BUT HE MAY BE GONE
BY TOMORROW.
- DAMN.
- NOW YOU SHOULDN'T STRAIN
YOURSELF IN YOUR CONDITION.
- Re-L: VINCENT LAW--
HE'S THE KEY
TO UNLOCKING THE MYSTERY
OF THE PROXY.
( moaning )
DAMN.
- Man: CAN'T SEEM TO GET
ANYTHING OUT OF IT.
- Older man: THAT'S A ROMDEAU
MODEL FOR YOU--
HIGH-MAINTENANCE.
- Man: OH, LOOK.
PERFECT TIMING.
YOU KNOW A LOT ABOUT MACHINES.
HOW DO WE GET THIS THING TO--?
- WHERE DID YOU FIND THIS?
DID YOU STEAL IT?
- YOU CRAZY?
OF COURSE WE DIDN'T STEAL IT.
WE TOOK IT FROM HOODY
AND HE STOLE IT FIRST.
IT'S QUINN'S IDEA.
SHE THINKS WE CAN USE IT TO LURE
THE NEGOTIATOR INTO COMING.
- Vincent: WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- Older man: QUINN'S BEEN
DOING SOME PLANNING.
SHE'S BEEN A LITTLE OUT OF SORTS
SINCE TIMOTHY DIED.
- Man: TO BE FAIR,
WE'VE ALL BEEN RATTLED.
- HMM?
- ( sighs )
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- TELL ME WHERE
VINCENT'S GONE TO.
- BEATS ME.
- SOMEONE HERE
TOOK MY A.H.D.
I BET IT WAS YOU.
- YOU WANT IT BACK?
( gasps )
- LISTEN TO ME.
I'M TAKING THAT MAN
BACK TO ROMDEAU.
I WON'T LET YOU
HAVE HIM.
- SO THEN,
WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE--
HIM OR THE VEHICLE?
YOU DON'T LOOK SO HOT,
PRINCESS.
- RE-L.
- VINCENT.
- Quinn: HOODY DOESN'T HAVE
ANY VACCINE.
HE RAN OUT OF THE STUFF
A LONG TIME AGO.
HE JUST HASN'T BOTHERED
TO TELL ANYONE YET.
- BUT HE HEALED ME
BEFORE.
- SO YOU THINK HE CURED YOU?
WELL, YOU'RE WRONG.
YOU JUST MANAGED
TO GET BETTER ON YOUR OWN.
- SO THE MEDICINE
IS ALL GONE?
- ALMOST.
- IS THAT IT?
- OUR LAST VIAL.
AND I'M NOT
GIVING IT AWAY FOR FREE.
YOU GET THE VIAL
IF YOU AND THE GIRL
JOIN US ON THE RABBIT.
DON'T MAKE THAT FACE
AT ME.
I'M OFFERING YOU
A CURE.
YOU'D BETTER SHOW
SOME APPRECIATION.
AND AS FOR THE TRIP,
WELL, THE MORE THE MERRIER.
- HOODY.
- YES, PINO?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M NOT DOING
ANYTHING, DEAR,
NOTHING AT ALL.
- HMM.
- YOU'RE LEAVING HERE.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, PINO?
- YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- DON'T YOU WANT
TO GO BACK TO ROMDEAU?
- NOT REALLY.
- WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO LEAVE VINCE.
OH, BUT PA--
- MM?
- HUH-UH, IT'S NOTHING.
HEY, HOODY.
- MM-HMM?
- DO YOU KNOW
WHERE TIMOTHY IS?
I'VE LOOKED ALL OVER,
BUT I CAN'T FIND HIM
ANYWHERE.
- HASN'T ANYONE TOLD YOU?
TIMOTHY IS DEAD.
- YES, I KNOW.
SO I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO FIND ANOTHER TIMOTHY.
- PINO.
WHEN A PERSON DIES,
THAT'S IT.
YOU DON'T GET TO SEE
ANOTHER ONE OF THEM AGAIN.
- WHAT?
REALLY?
- THAT'S HOW IT WORKS.
- OKAY.
BUT I STILL WANT
TO PLAY WITH HIM SOME MORE.
- ARE YOU SAD, PINO?
- AM I SAD?
- YES, DEAR.
WHAT YOU'RE FEELING
IN THERE RIGHT NOW--
THAT IS WHAT WE CALL
BEING SAD.
- SAD.
- DAMN.  AND AFTER
ALL WE WENT THROUGH
JUST TO GET HER TO SHOW HERSELF.
- JUST BE PATIENT.
WE'VE STILL GOT
HER VEHICLE SECURED,
SO SHE'S NOT
GOING ANYWHERE.
BESIDES, I'D STILL LIKE TO TRY
AND KEEP THE BOY HAPPY.
- Older man: REALLY?
THAT DON'T SOUND LIKE YOU.
- Younger man: WHAT, ARE YOU
AFRAID OF THE LITTLE SHRIMP?
- Quinn: I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE.
- I GOT THE STUFF, QUINN.
Men: WOW.
LOOK AT THAT HARDWARE.
- LOOK AT THAT.
- WHOA, CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
LOOK HOW MUCH
THERE IS.
- THE SEEDS
HAVE BEEN SOWN.
NOW THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
EXCEPT TO WAIT.
- ( Vincent's voice )
I HAVE TO TAKE YOU WITH ME.
THERE'S NO CHOICE.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- YOU'RE REALLY
GOING TO TAKE HER THEN?
- WHAT CAN I DO?
SHE'S NOT GONNA RECOVER
FROM THE INFECTION HERE.
- VINCENT, WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT YOU'RE--?
- SHE'LL DIE.  AND YOU SHOULD
KNOW THAT BETTER THAN ANYONE.
- SO YOU KNEW.
- IF SHE AND I GET ON THE BOAT,
THEN WE GET THE VACCINE.
- AND YOU THINK
QUINN'S GOING TO HELP HER?
YOU IDIOT.
THAT GIRL'S FROM ROMDEAU--
THE CITY THAT KILLED TIMOTHY.
ONCE THE RABBIT MANAGES
TO SET SAIL,
THE DOME IS CERTAIN
TO TRY TO CHASE IT DOWN.
IF QUINN USES THE GIRL
AS A SHIELD,
THE DOME WON'T ATTACK.
BUT ONCE THEY'RE ACROSS THE BAY,
THEN THE GIRL WON'T BE WORTH
ANYTHING TO QUINN ANYMORE.
QUINN IS LYING TO YOU,
VINCENT.
AND YOU ARE A FOOL
STUMBLING RIGHT INTO HER TRAP.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE VACCINE?
- WHAT IF THE VACCINE
IS A FAKE?
AND EVEN IF THE VACCINE
WAS REAL,
IT STILL WOULDN'T MATTER.
IN HER WEAKENED CONDITION,
THE COLD WOULD KILL HER.
- EVEN SO, I CAN'T JUST
SIT AND WAIT HERE.
- HER TIME'S RUNNING OUT.
- SO WHAT ARE YOU SAYING
I SHOULD DO?
- TAKE HER BACK TO ROMDEAU.
- TAKE HER BACK?
TO ROMDEAU?
- IF YOU DON'T WANT HER
TO DIE,
TAKING HER BACK TO ROMDEAU
IS YOUR ONLY CHANCE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU INSIDE THE DOME,
BUT SHE CAME OUT HERE
LOOKING ONLY FOR YOU, VINCENT.
THEY THINK YOU'RE SOMETHING
SPECIAL.  YOU CAN GO BACK.
THE MAN FROM ROMDEAU
MUST RETURN.
IT'S PROVIDENCE.
TO RESIST IS TO FAIL.
- SO WE RETURN TO ROMDEAU.
- Man: QUINN, TAKE A LOOK.
- Both: QUINN.
- NO, YOU CAN'T GO.
- TAKE IT.
GOOD LUCK.
- YOU TOO.
IT'S TIME TO GO BACK
TO ROMDEAU, RE-L.
- HOP, HOP, HOP, HOP.
HOP!
( laughing )
AIRPLANE!
- LET'S MOVE OUT!
- BYE-BYE.
- RE-L MAYER'S BACK?
- HER A.H.D. IS CURRENTLY DOCKED
OUTSIDE PLUG VENT NUMBER THREE.
THE HEALTH
AND WELFARE BUREAU
IS ASKING FOR PERMISSION
TO RECEIVE HER.
- I'M TOO BUSY
FOR THIS.
- CHIEF.
- LET HER WAIT.
I CAN'T APPROVE
THE RETURN OF SOMEONE
WHO LEFT THE DOME
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
FURTHERMORE, ANYONE
WHO ABANDONS THE DOME
THE WAY
THAT YOUNG MAN HAS
DESERVES THE HARSHEST
PUNISHMENT ALLOWED,
AND CERTAINLY
REASONABLE.
YES, HE MUST HAVE
HIS CONSEQUENCES.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE,
KRISTEVA?
- THERE ARE NO WAVES.
- ( coughing )
- HOW IS IT?
- YOU DO KNOW
I'M NOT ACTUALLY A MECHANIC?
- WE'RE NOT GONNA SINK,
ARE WE?
- IF I WERE GONNA DIE, I'D BE
WITH A BETTER MAN THAN YOU.
- NO KIDDING.
( laughs )
- IDIOT, SHE WAS
TALKING ABOUT YOU.
- WHAT?
- ANYWAY, REATTACH
THE BROKEN LINES.
WE JUST NEED A QUICK FIX.
- BUT QUINN--
- IT'S TOO QUIET.
THERE'S NO WIND BLOWING.
NO, IT'S MORE
THAN JUST THE WIND.
- QUINN, ARE THOSE
SCARY THINGS COMING?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- YOU'RE LIKE MY PAPA.
- HEY, YOU'RE TRYING TO SAY
I'M LIKE YOUR MAMA, RIGHT?
- HMM?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
- ( men shouting ) GET 'EM!
- Rino: HELP!
- HUH?
- Men: GET 'EM!
AHA!
- DAMN IT.  TOO SOON FOR THIS.
- Man: COME ON, YOU.
HURRY, WE CAN'T TAKE
MUCH MORE OF THIS.
- WHAT ABOUT CHIEF RAUL?
- STILL NO ANSWER.
- USELESS.
- I ASSUME IT'S TO DO WITH
CONTAINING RE-L'S INFECTION.
- THAT WHOLE THING'S
MAKING MY HEAD HURT.
- THE OTHER PASSENGER IDENTIFIED
HIMSELF AS VINCENT LAW--
THE MAN THE SECURITY BUREAU
WAS PURSUING BEFORE.
SHALL I REPORT IT?
- SHE BROUGHT HIM BACK
WITH HER.
HE'S WORTH OUR TIME.
INFORM THEM THAT THERE IS
ANOTHER PASSENGER,
BUT KEEP NAMES OUT OF IT
FOR NOW.
LET'S SEE HOW MUCH
WE CAN GET OUT OF HIM.
- WHAT?
- IS THERE A PROBLEM?
YOU DON'T SHOW YOUR HAND
UNTIL IT'S TIME
FOR ALL CARDS ON THE TABLE.
- ( phone beeps )
- GET THIS THING MOVING!
- ( exclaims )
- RINO, TAKE COVER.
- CHIEF RAUL.
- YES, WHAT IS IT NOW?
- YOU'RE AWARD OF OUR REQUEST
TO OPEN PLUG VENT NUMBER THREE?
- THE OUTSIDE AIR
IS FILLED WITH GERMS.
WHAT'S MORE, IT'S NOT
SUCH A SIMPLE MATTER
OPENING A PLUG VENT
FOR SOMEONE WHO'S INFECTED.
- YOU'VE HAD PLENTY OF TIME
TO DEAL WITH THOSE ISSUES,
SECURITY CHIEF RAUL.
WE ARE PREPARED
ON OUR END.
NOW AUTHORIZE THE OPENING
OF PLUG VENT THREE.
- VERY WELL, DOCTOR.
- GOOD.  THEN WE'LL TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY
FOR BOTH PASSENGERS.
- BOTH PASSENGERS?
SO SHE DIDN'T
COME BACK ALONE.
SHE FOUND VINCENT LAW.
LEAVE THREE VEHICLES
IN PURSUIT
AND HAVE THE REST HEAD FOR
PLUG VENT NUMBER THREE.
I'LL JOIN THEM SHORTLY.
- YES, SIR.
- I FOUND HIM.
HE'S NOT
ON THE AIRSHIP.
- WAIT, WHY ARE THEY
ALL LEAVING?
- ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S OUR CHANCE.
HURRY UP AND FIX IT.
- THAT IS A LITTLE ODD,
ACTUALLY.
I WAS NEVER INFORMED
OF THE OTHER PASSENGER'S NAME.
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE
IT'S YOUR MAN?
OR IS THIS
JUST SPECULATION?
- PERHAPS,
BUT I'VE GOT A FEELING.
- VINCENT LAW,
GUILTY OF TREASON
FOR DAMAGING AN ENTOURAGE.
HE'S AN IMMIGRANT.
HE MAY BE CONSIDERED A THREAT,
BUT I DON'T THINK HE WARRANTS
HAVING THE SECURITY BUREAU USE
ITS FULL FORCE TO CAPTURE HIM.
- YOU'RE CORRECT.
THE MAN IS INSIGNIFICANT.
SO WHY DON'T YOU PLEASE
STOP PESTERING ME ABOUT IT?
- MY APOLOGIES.
YOU HAVE YOUR REASONS.
- RE-L MAYER IS ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THAT PLUG VENT.
I WOULD HATE TO THINK YOU'VE
FORGOTTEN THAT, DR. DAEDALUS.
- ( clock chiming )
- ( mechanical waltz playing )
- YES, OF COURSE.
- THE OTHER PASSENGER,
VINCENT LAW,
IS TO BE EXECUTED IMMEDIATELY
UPON IDENTIFICATION.
- IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
RE-L IS OUR
TOP PRIORITY FOR NOW.
TELL HIM
THERE WILL BE HELL TO PAY
IF I FIND SHE HAS
SO MUCH AS A SCRATCH.
- EXCUSE ME, CHIEF.
MAY I OPEN THE PLUG VENT?
- YES, GO AHEAD.
- OPENING THE HATCH.
- SHOW ME YOUR FACE,
VINCENT LAW.
- ALL RIGHT!
WE'RE MOVING!  WE'RE MOVING!
- YEAH, THAT WAS
SOME GOOD WORK, KID.
- ( mechanical waltz
continues )
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
- ( two gunshots )
- QUINN!
- ( waltz stops playing )
- Kristeva: THE SHIP HAS MADE IT
ACROSS THE BAY.
THE PATROL CRAFT
CAN'T PURSUE IT ANY FURTHER.
- BURN THE COMMUNE
TO THE GROUND.
- Vincent: QUINN.
WHAT'S THIS?
- WHISKEY.
MY LAST SHOT.
IT'S FOR YOU.
DRINK UP.
- WE CAN STILL GO BACK
TO THE COMMUNE.
WE'LL GET YOU SOME FIRST AID.
- Older man: QUINN.
- PLEASE DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT BEING THAT STUPID.
LOOK, THEY CAN'T FOLLOW.
THEY'RE JUST FLYING
IN CIRCLES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE WERE AFRAID OF THOSE.
I MEAN,
IT'S FUNNY, RIGHT?
IT'S LESS
THAN YOU DESERVE,
YOU BASTARDS.
- Older man: QUINN.
- HEY, QUINN.
I FEEL VERY SAD,
QUINN.
- ♪ PLEASE COULD YOU
STOP THE NOISE? ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET SOME REST ♪
♪ FROM ALL THE UNBORN
CHICKEN VOICES ♪
♪ IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ WHAT'S THAT? ♪