It's dark and hard to walk!
Ugh!
Why are we even
doing this anyway?
It's not gonna take them
very long to find that car.
I'd like to avoid
any unnecessary danger.
You seem to have
gotten used to this.
The sea is on the other
side of this ridge.
Hang with us kid.
Well come on then,
let's keep it moving.
This is disgusting!
I can't help but wonder.
What do you think the ISDA
is going to do with
all of the Dragons?
I don't know, but think,
if they are able to
give life to a dragon.
We have to assume
they have the power
to take that
life away, as well.
The dragons are not safe.
No... wait.
I still...
[JIN] Why did things
have to be like this.
Gio?
So you still haven't
found out where they went?
The search party is
investigating a lead right now.
They should be
contacting me shortly.
They just keep running away.
I'm giving the two of
you a different assignment.
A new mission? Go ahead.
It's an operating
test with the Aegis.
Aegis?
Aegis huh?
Interesting.
Understood, sir!
We will begin
our mission at once!
[KAZUKI laughs maniacally]
[HOWLINGSTAR punches wall]
How long are they going to
keep us locked up in this place?
Hey, we're
getting bored in here!
You need to calm
down, Howlingstar.
I could break the walls
if I could Actualize!
[AMADEUS] Given the powerful
CSS field around us,
I doubt you will be
able to accomplish that.
I can understand how you feel.
While we're trapped
here in this prison cell,
Thanatos is moving closer
and closer to the Earth.
But that's not
the ISDA's priority.
It's their image,
they need to hunt dragons
to gain support
from the general public.
The Dragonauts used to
be treated like heroes.
Now we get
treated like criminals.
It's up to them.
They're the only ones left.
I'm sure she could use the
sleep after walking all night.
I'm not sleeping
I'm resting my eyes.
[YANOMINE]
Here it comes.
Right on time.
We'd be in trouble
if it weren't.
Jin.
We need to wait for Gio.
No we can't.
If the patrol boats see us
this will all be for nothing.
Gio will catch up. I'm sure.
It's good to see you all again.
I don't understand.
We thought you could
use some reinforcements.
You can't attack
Tartarus on your own.
We haven't given up
hope that humans
and dragons can still co-exist.
That's why we're
here helping you.
We have to prevent the ISDA
from doing anymore harm,
and rescue the dragons.
Our future depends on it.
Right!
Tell me, what happened to Gio?
Don't know,
he's gone missing.
He's gone missing?
I don't get it, why would he
wander away from us like that?
Well worrying about it isn't
going to help us solve anything.
If it comes down to it,
I'll think of something.
Now, let's get this
thing moving faster.
As you wish, young lady.
Gio.
Toa.
Look Jin. It'll be all right.
Let's go.
Widow!
Damn you.
Okay.
My business only
concerns the dragons.
Hey!
I want to know what
you're going to do with them.
Then ask the commander,
I cannot divulge
that information to you.
Commander Sakaki?
We should be
approaching Tartarus
in the next few moments.
You guys ready?
Yes we are.
Let's get started.
Alright, we're flooding
the container.
You know,
it's lucky you guys
had this
control gear with you.
Not really,
I brought it on purpose.
In case I needed to wear it.
You were planning to use it?
You don't think I could?
No of course not.
Have you even had
any training at all?
Well, no.
You couldn't
operate the controls.
Not with those things
getting in the way.
Jin... Toa...
We're counting on you.
Are you ready for this?
Toa?
We're doing this to save
our friends aren't we?
I have to protect the bond
between humans and dragons.
I do, too.
I want to do
whatever I can
to make sure that
bond is never broken.
I want you to see me
in my real form, okay?
I give myself to
you completely, Jin.
Will you fight alongside me?
Toa.
To be honest with you,
I'm pretty scared.
Although, as long
as I have you with me.
I know things
will be all right.
Toa.
Yes Jin.
Are we really doing this?
I think we need
something to occupy
our time
until we find Jin.
I know.
But why is it necessary
to use them in the Aegis test?
Don't tell me
you've decided
now is a good time
to develop a conscience.
That's not what I meant.
It doesn't matter.
I'll probably just end up
going to hell anyway.
Captain.
We've just received a message
that something is approaching
Tartarus at high speed!
Let's do this Toa!
Tartarus is surrounded
by a CSS field.
You shouldn't get
too close to that thing Jin.
Roger that.
Right.
We should get moving too.
[KAZUKI laughing]
Jin. It's him!
You've come to see me.
Haven't you?
Sir communications with
Tartarus have been cut off.
Isn't it dangerous to go there?
The attack is likely
a diversion. We'll be fine.
Send out the attack craft!
What? Who are you?
He just ran out into the open.
You're really getting
into this stuff, Yonamine.
Who are you?
A champion of justice!
You're ridiculous.
Hurry.
Nozaki what's in the case?
CSS field neutralizing devices.
80% of their power.
Once we find
Amadeus and the others.
We'll give them these.
When did you come up
with that idea?
You don't think we
were hiding out
in the electronics
district for nothing?
Funny, I can picture
you as an electrician.
Let's hurry.
[TOA roars]
Are you okay? Toa?
Jin, what happened to Gio?
Kazuki.
You're still alive!
I can't believe it!
You can't believe it?
You tried to kill me Jin.
Or did you forget?
[KAZUKI laughing maniacally]
There's no way I can die
until after I've killed you!
Every time I can
feel this scar aching.
I think back to that cold,
dark hell where I felt nothing!
You'll get to see
this place too Jin.
When you die!
Kazuki stop this!
Whoa.
Are you done with that yet?
Leave me alone.
I'm working.
Just hurry up.
Hey, all right.
Nice work.
There they are!
[KAZUKI scoffs] What, did
you just get tired of Gio?
And now you've
moved on to Toa?
You gonna dump
her like you did Gio?
Cause I would never do that!
[JIN yelling]
You okay Toa?
[KAZUKI tauntingly laughs]
[KAZUKI]
What's the matter Jin?
You're gonna die
if you don't fight back.
Or maybe you don't like
the idea of Toa killing anybody.
You're not taking
me seriously, Jin.
You don't understand
that I'm not out here
fighting to hurt anybody!
I'm only trying to preserve the
bond between humans and dragons!
Preserve?
You broke mine with... Gio!
[TOA roars]
Hey, you guys ready?
Yonamine!
What are you doing here?
I'll explain as we go.
Come on!
Where's Amadeus?
Where did Amadeus go?
They took him away.
Taken where?
The lower level.
That means...
they must be planning
to use the Aegis on them.
What's that?
It's an ultra high
output directional CSS field.
We developed
it with the hope
it would be strong enough
to immobilize Thanatos.
You mean they were
finally able to complete it?
A live dragon wouldn't stand
a chance against the Aegis.
They weren't meant to.
I suppose the team
we used to know
as the Dragonauts
doesn't exist any longer.
Let's get moving.
We're going to rescue them.
Well, at least this room's
a little bigger than the last.
[OTOHIME] What do you
think they want with us?
[AMADEUS] I have a bad
feeling about this.
Now commencing operation.
I feel so... heavy.
I know, but why?
It's no use this barrier's
completely independent,
it won't accept
any of my commands!
And the others
are just past it!
[EVERYONE grimacing in pain]
Professor.
I may have figured out
a way to save them.
All of the power on Tartarus
is supplied by a single
underground reactor.
If we can find a way
to take out that reactor,
all systems will be shut down.
Good point.
And the CSS
field surrounding
the island would
be gone as well.
And then if
that happens Amadeus
and the others will be
able to escape on their own!
Right. Let's go.
Look out!
Is that...?
Keep moving.
Professor.
Hold on you can't
do this alone.
Take care of her
for me, Yonamine.
Don't go dying on us.
I never imagined
I would actually
get the chance to use this.
What?
I'll admit I'm surprised ISDA
was able to come up with
a similar device on their own.
Hold on. It's you!
I need you to hurry Sieglinde!
Disgusting.
There are firewalls everywhere.
It's too much.
You have to keep trying,
the fate of the other
dragons is in your hands now.
But...
If you believe in yourself
it will all work out.
Remember, you are
the genius of the group.
I know that.
Increase the output.
[OTOHIME yells in pain]
[HOWLINGSTAR]
Hang on Otohime.
Sakaki is wrong about us,
I think it's very important
you understand that.
You saw them right?
They are risking their own lives
in order to save those
of the other dragons.
We didn't go through Resonance
with the humans so
we could hate each other.
[LAURA] I don't care.
What?
Please, stop.
Ko!
That hurt.
[JIN grimaces]
Toa... Toa!
Kazuki.
[KAZUKI laughs]
Output has
reached critical level.
Itsuki, I'm so sorry.
This is it, huh?
It's been good, young miss.
Amadeus!
Switch to emergency power now!
Sir I can't,
the backups are down too!
Dammit, we're going to lose
all of the test data
from the Aegis.
Guys. Actualize.
Okay, what just happened?
Don't move!
What is that?
Hello, young miss.
Amadeus!
Thank you,
for coming back to me.
No my lady.
It is I who should thank you.
It's time to end this, Jin.
You die.
Now what?
It sounds like they made it.
Professor.
You're safe!
Yes, I'm fine, thanks.
Wait!
Returning to Sakaki
isn't the answer.
It will only be
more painful for you.
Raum stop!
That's the Raum?
[LAURA] Here it comes.
Get the hell away from me!
Gio.
You came back for us!
Gio...
What are you?
Alright, nobody's around.
Now to do the preview
while I can.
No you don't Kiril!
Sakaki, when did you get here?
Hey now, don't forget about me.
Professor Nozaki,
you're here too?
Please let me do this.
I've always wanted it.
Oh no you don't.
Next time on Dragonaut.
It will return.
Why are you trying to
take our jobs away from us?
Saki where are your clothes?
Eh, hehe.