[girls screaming]
Please, stop!
Can't you
just let us go?
[men laughing]
Not when you
scream like that.
Pretty sounds
make me spin.
Makes me want to
touch you, woohoo!
No.
Don't touch me!
You think you can do whatever
you want with impunity?
You're never going
to get away with this.
We are going
to tell someone.
I'd really like to see
you give that a shot.
Who do you think
is going to come
to your rescue all
the way out here?
I don't care what
impunity means
but it sure sounds
like a lot of fun.
[men laughing]
ugh, ah!
Who left that garbage sitting
in the middle of the road?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm the nightmare
that makes you cry
for your momma
'cept I'm real.
Get outta here!
Time to bring the pain, the
hurt, and then the more pain.
He is like so
deliciously hot.
I'm calling
dibs on his junk.
Tall dark stranger can
you tell us your name.
I am known to all as...
The Howlingstar.
Umph!
Oof!
[JIN sighs]
Toa is so freakin' beautiful.
[AKIRA] Hey!
No more slacking off,
Jin Kamishina.
Thirty laps around the track.
Move it!
Oh no please don't make me run
around the track again, Akira.
Totally sucks to be
you today, huh, Jin?
You had better
get running.
Tachibana, Asim.
You guys get to take fifty laps.
[boys yelling in despair]
[NARRATOR] The crucible of
adolescence, Thanatos Academy.
[TOA] Thanks!
Can you toss me the ball?
[NARRATOR] The sexual
tension was palpable.
[FEMALE swimmers]
One, two, one, two, one, two.
[drooling]
Coach Otohime
is unbelievable.
She's so sophisticated
and charming.
[sighs]
[NARRATOR] The passion
of youth surging forward.
Sweat flying.
Chests heaving.
Chests swaying.
Chests! Chests! Chests!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
My plan worked like a charm.
[NARRATOR] A storm of intrigue
engulfs the academy.
An interesting wind has started
to blow mightily around us.
Are you certain
about this director?
If this keeps up then...
[AMADEUS laughs maniacally]
[bangs hands on piano keys]
Who am I kidding?
The piano has always
been a distant second
to my true musical love...
...Mandolin!
♪ A mandolin's not a mandarin ♪
♪ like a mandrill's
not an orangutan. ♪
♪ If you love music,
like I love music, ♪
♪ and I love music. ♪
♪ You have to play the... ♪
♪ Mandolin! ♪
[NARRATOR] Who is this
mysterious mandolineer?
And how did she acquire
the keys to the music room?
[TOA] You
don't understand.
Passion is
its own master!
[HOWLINGSTAR]
We can't get carried away
by a love that could be.
You were raised as a
mostly respectable woman.
Our paths should
never have crossed.
None of that
matters to me.
Not even reinforced titanium
armor five inches thick
with a Kevlar coating could
stop my armor piercing love.
[TOA cries out in despair]
If you insist.
[JIN] How could
she forget my love?
Toa.
This is my own fault!
Howlingstar!
[NARRATOR] Laser beam
youth love grenade.
I'm getting inside no
matter what you do.
That will be easier
said than done.
Today's the day you
die, Howlingstar.
Now, our Sensei.
I can't think of anything
more poetically justifying
than facing down my
rival in this place.
It can't be.
Gio!
It's really been far
too long, Howlingstar.
Looks like we can
settle the score
from five
years ago huh?
Gio.
Kick his ass, Howlingstar.
[GIO and HOWLINGSTAR yelling]
By order of my master.
I cannot let you
pass through here.
Don't go, I need you.
Please, look at me.
Who are you?
I have forgotten.
You're standing in your grave!
Super-secret
technique number seven.
I will have vengeance in
my master's name this day!
Or I'll die trying!
Demon dragon Gio
come forth now
into being by my
ultimate command!
[GIO roars]
[AKIRA]
These are my students.
I'll never let you
take them from me.
Go forth, Spirytus.
Toa!
You are the first to
ever make it this far.
I'm impressed, Howlingstar.
I should have guessed
it was the Ebony Witch.
You caused this, right?
I want you to swear.
Upon this evil ring.
[NARRATOR] A young girl's
secrets hold all the secrets.
Thanatos Academy
will now be laid bare.
Dual spear spear!
[HOWLINGSTAR]
Google our webisodes!
[NARRATOR] In a world where
shocking and desperate meet.
ISDA films is
proud to present
the heartwarming
family blood fest.
Travels of the Wandering Dragon:
The Hellish Thanatos Academy.
Coming soon!
[RAINA] Everything is
proceeding as was foretold.
The age of man is at an end.
The age of dragons has arrived.
[RAINA] Everything is
proceeding as was foretold.
The age of man is at an end and
the age of dragons has arrived.
[HOWLINGSTAR giggling]
Dude, that was so amazing.
They captured me perfectly!
Yes, I'm even more
wonderful than before.
If I were a chick
I'd totally hit that.
I'm king of the world!
[SIEGLINDE] Aw, man.
What is with this weather?
This vacation sucks big time.
All we've done is watch
the bathroom safety dvd
and prank call my father
but he's totally on to
us and now it's no fun.
That's it, I've got nuthin' man.
There's nothing we can do.
Until the storm passes through
I'm afraid we're
just stuck here,
unless we can fix the jacuzzi.
That's a rehab bath.
They likely used it to
keep their patients mobile
during their time at
this nursing home.
At least there's plenty of
abandoned food to eat.
Stale old folks home food rocks.
Who cares about that?
I want to know why
none of the Dragons
are able to actualize anymore.
Actualize!
It didn't seem to
have any effect.
[HOWLINGSTAR]
Materialize!
Dragon ho!
Do it!
You know Toa thought
there might be some
kind of CSS
field at work here.
[SIEGLINDE]
CSS?
Anything's possible I suppose.
We should definitely
check it out.
Where did the director
and the commander go?
Knowing those guys,
I would guess they're
down at their usual hang out.
Huh? Again?
Nothing yet, huh?
Nope.
You have to sit still
and be patient.
[fish reel spinning]
Ah the fish ate
my bait again.
You're pulling it in
too soon professor.
You have to put yourself
in the fish's position
and try to get inside
his psychology like me.
It's the bait-snatchers and you
know it you withered old fool.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
The bait-snatchers only
exist in fairy tales.
You have to become
one with the fish
if you ever expect to catch it,
kill it, and eat it for dinner.
It's bait-snatchers.
Liar!
Wrong!
I suppose you believe
in the tooth fairy.
You sound like you
want to kiss the fish.
Fairy Lover!
Fish kisser.
Things are gettin' ugly.
Inside and outside.
[ALL DRAGONS gasp]
About time Amadeus.
Is my cup of tea ready, yet?
[SIEGLINDE gasps]
The tea?
Why don't you get it
yourself for once.
You worthless babbling brat.
What's wrong with you?
Get off your butt and
go get me a cup of tea.
But... what's your problem?
You're... not
acting like normal.
Get used to it.
Any little girl who expects
to be waited on hand and foot
is going to grow up
to be good for nothin'.
Things are gonna be different
between you and me
starting right now.
And don't try crying.
It won't work.
From here on out
you start getting
your own hands dirty miss.
I'm done with it.
Amadeus, you
can't leave me.
I don't... know
what to do.
My ass is tired.
Nap time.
I think she's gone.
Well that was
completely unexpected.
[TOA in sexy voice]
Jin.
[AKIRA gasps]
[JIN gasps]
Toa. Cat.
Big. Hot.
Boo.Bies.
You want to play
with Toa, meow?
Okay.
What do you think, Jin?
Do you like my new dress?
I love the way it makes me feel.
Kitty needs some affection.
You better start telling me
that you absolutely
love the way I look.
Or you're going
to get a spanking.
You bad little boy.
[JIN gasps]
Quick. Is everyone present?
[TOA] Pet the kitty Jin,
pet the kitty!
Sorry.
Okay.
What's going on?
Well, we have no idea
but it's quite humiliating.
Have you noticed anyone else
acting strangely?
That's why I'm here.
Gio and the others have
completely lost their senses.
Then I really cranked
up the funny on 'em.
Hey there guy?
You can't push it so hard.
You're gonna make that dragon
hotter.
Gonna make that dragon hotter.
Dragon hotter? Dragon
hotter? Dragonaut!
[WIDOW laughing]
Oh Gio, you're killing me.
Gonna make that
dragon hotter, dragonaut!
That's brilliant.
[WIDOW laughing]
I'm confused was that
supposed to be funny?
Gio doesn't
really get jokes.
Don't let him touch me.
Gio's seriously
attempting comedy?
Widow thought his
jokes were funny?
And that's not even
the worst of it.
[thunder clap]
[HOWLINGSTAR yells in fear]
What's the matter Howlingstar?
Get a hold of yourself.
Noise go away.
I should go get
the video camera.
[MACHINA growls]
You can't back out
on our bet now!
[GARNET]
Can't I?
It's your turn to jump.
Either jump or I'll shake you.
You don't
have to hurt me.
I'll do it.
Like this, right?
Yeah, good, Just like how
I began one, two, one, two.
But then you made me take
it up a notch didn't you?
I think you told me
I had to get
some air and make them fly,
it'nt dat right?
Make yours fly, missy.
Right.
Like this?
Very good.
Double jumps!
Don't slow down.
Mine bounced higher!
[GARNET] I can't jump higher.
[MACHINA] Yes, you can.
Guys, that doesn't sound
like the Machina I know.
[MACHINA] Stop being a whiny
baby and finish the bet.
Double or nothing.
Trampoline.
Oh, my Garnet.
You are so... bouncy.
This can only result
in complete disaster.
We have to help them,
right after this.
[SIEGLINDE]
Here's our problem.
I found it by
looking at this map,
but ISDA has purged
its existence
from all official records
because it used to be
a research and development
center that ran
some pretty weird experiments
that always went terribly wrong.
My guess is that somehow
the facility is back online
and whatever they're up
to has seriously messed
with our little
dragons' personalities.
That makes perfectly
convenient sense
especially because that's
the only antique ISDA map
you have in your collection.
Well yeah.
I'm very impressed
that you were able
to come up with this on your own
in such short order, Sieglinde.
The movie preview ate
all our time.
No fair!
The only obvious
course of action
is for us to risk
everything for our friends
and take out
this facility at all costs.
Who's with me?
We just have to destroy
the facility, right?
Yes that's correct, and it
shouldn't be terribly difficult.
I wonder why
Otohime's personality
has been completely
unaffected by it.
You're right she's
completely normal.
Well, I feel
a little bit weird.
It's simple.
Her personality is so normal
it is completely devoid
of anything to
amplify or reverse.
I'm completely normal?
Okay.
Time to shut down the CSS and
get our weird friends back.
Let's go!
I'm not normal.
I'm deep and mysterious.
Dragonauts, ho!
It's okay, girl.
The world needs vanilla.
I'm tired of cheering!
We'll save you crazy people,
yeah!
Time to roll out.
Did you guys hear like people
yelling or something?
No, you ladies must
be imagining things.
I think you've got
a nibble, director.
You!
You tried to trick me
out of my happy place
but it won't work because
I know exactly
what it takes to catch
the perfect fish.
Unless you
become as peaceful
as the deep cool stillness
that is the fish's home
you have not earned the right
to chop off their little
heads and spill their guts.
That's not a fish.
We've finally made it.
Just as I expected.
The CSS antenna is operational.
Okay, this is for
you, Gio. Widow.
We'll turn you back
into your normal
dark and brooding selves
or else we'll die trying.
Kazuki wait.
There's something you need to
know about their defenses.
That area is protected by
genetically manipulated
super plants.
Why didn't you tell me before?
Why do you hate me!
Let's move out.
We can't let his sacrifice
have been in vain.
I'm not dead!
You can cut me down.
Where are you going?
So, I'm at this party
and this totally hot chick
gets right in
my face and says.
"I must be dead cause
you look like an angel."
[WIDOW laughs]
[HOWLINGSTAR]
Make the bad noises go away.
I want to clean.
That's wacky, right?
Ohmigosh, that's crazy.
Be careful Akira, you're about
to fall through a trap door.
Your death will be remembered!
Why didn't you stop me sooner?
I'm a vapid void of blah.
You're kind of a being a total
pain in my ass right now,
that's something, isn't it?
I want you to jump, faster!
You mean like this?
I was jumping twice that fast!
I can't go faster.
I'm starting to get sick.
[laughing]
Somebody please make it stop!
I want to go home to
my mommy now, okay.
I wet my pants
when I get like this
and don't like
wetting my pants.
We're running out of time.
Hurry up, Sieglinde.
Whoops, I've made
some kind of mistake.
How could I let
this happen to me?
Because you didn't listen to me.
Oh, hey there, Jin.
Do you want me to get a you a
nice cool glass of ice water?
And maybe a pair of handcuffs
while I'm up.
I finally made it.
Once I shut this
down, Toa, Amadeus
and everyone goes
back to normal.
I think it's time for
me to save some lives.
Kazuki, Akira, Captain Raina.
Your noble
self-giving sacrifices
will be remembered
by us forever.
You'll be missed.
I hope you can all
rest in peace.
Sieglinde,
we're not dead! So,
I was wondering.
Where did that CSS
field come from anyway?
A team we were
never aware of
was developing it
in parallel to ours
but it didn't work right
so they had to scrap it.
Theirs totally had better
funding than ours though
which kinda makes me pissed.
And the lightning
strike during the storm
caused it to start
functioning on its own.
Well, I guess if you think of it
as part of the entertainment
it wasn't really that bad.
Right, Amadeus?
Stop teasing him Akira.
He feels terrible
about what happened.
I'm not sure he's ever going to
be able to recover from it.
Oh, miss, of course I will.
Well, at least everyone
appears to have turned back
into their normal selves
for the most part.
Howlingstar sucking
his thumb on my lap
is an image I'd like
never to repeat if possible.
You're gonna have to stop
bringing that up
or I will kill you.
Gio and Widow are so much
more fun to be around when
they're not
quite so entertaining.
I think there's one
person here who wishes
a certain someone hadn't changed
back to her old self.
Look.
Uh.
Jin.
What's the matter?
Can you um, do that thing
where you were meowing
like a sexy cat
again for me, Toa?
It was so damn hot.
It was really really hot.
I don't know how.
Just try, now meow like a cat.
Like a cat?
Make the cat noise for me Toa!
Jin, what's the matter with you?
I want my old Jin back.
Where'd he go?
Come on, Meow!
I've never understood why
humans act so crazy sometimes.
Looks like it's
clearing up out there.
I have to say though.
We've caught nothing.