They were out of
control, is that right?
Yes sir.
When a Dragon's Master dies,
the Dragon cannot maintain
its human-like
Communicator form.
If this happens its natural
ferocity takes over
and it becomes
impossible to control.
The fact of the
matter is we need Dragons;
but we need
them to be obedient
so that we may
reliably control them
in order to achieve our goals.
It is my understanding
that that's what
the Resonance is for,
a formula that allows
humans and dragons
to conduct communication.
Continue with
your investigation.
Well then,
I'd better get back to it.
[ASIM laughing]
Do it! Yes!
Not good.
Machina!
[MACHINA screams in rage]
Watch out!
Her back!
Toa! What's the matter?
Are you all right?
Machina! Please, stop!
Machina!
Machina, why are
you doing this to us?
Gio you must all leave.
Run away.
What's happening to you?
Akira's gone so
the Resonance is coming undone.
Please just go!
What?
Run away.
Save yourselves.
I can't control what
I'm about to become.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
It can't be stopped.
You wouldn't understand.
I'm not free like you are.
Machina please.
It's coming back.
[MACHINA screams in agony]
[HOWLINGSTAR gasping]
What is it?
What's wrong Howlingstar?
[HOWLINGSTAR gasping]
It... It feels just like.
Machina!
Raina!
Please let me go to her.
I'm begging you to give
me your permission.
Something terrible has
happened on Mars hasn't it?
Just a moment Sieglinde.
Please don't
try to stop us.
Try to stop you?
Now why would I do that?
Raina.
Actualization readings
at hatch number six!
What? Who is it?
It's Howlingstar and Amadeus!
They're rapidly accelerating
away from the moon base.
Open up a com line immediately!
They're offline sir!
They're both refusing all hails.
Where do they
think they're going?
I just hope we don't get
there too late to help them.
Wait! Stop right there!
This is trespassing!
This had better be good.
You're a busy man so
I'll get right to point.
We'd like you to
remove Prince Asim
as the officer in charge
of your nation's military
as soon as possible.
Why would I do that?
It has come to our
attention that your noble son
has been playing with fire.
Only the flame he toys with
could very well
scorch all of humanity.
How dare you
march into my palace
and give me an order
in my own kingdom!
Forgive me your Highness.
We would never presume
to give you and order.
We're merely
making a request.
However, it would be in the
best interest of your nation
to comply as the entire
world may turn against you.
It appears to me that we
have reached an understanding.
Much appreciated. Good day.
Machina,
why are you doing this?
She's out of control!
Don't tell me that
you didn't know about this Jin.
A Dragon whose Master dies
is released from
humanity's oppression
and their true
nature is revealed.
What are you talking about?
When the human factor falls
away they become a pure Dragon.
Is it not the most incredible
thing you've ever witnessed?
You bastard!
Is that why you murdered Akira?
You're so naïve.
If only you could
see how disgusting it is
when Dragons are
contaminated by humans.
Contaminated?
That's right!
I must confess, the love
between you and the Album
is indeed staggering.
However, the truth
is that the Album
has merely been
defiled by your filth.
Now then, Album.
I intend to liberate you
from this wretched creature.
Leave him alone!
I have not been bound to Jin!
Oh is that right?
Then why do you wear such a
pained expression on your face?
You're in pain
because you're a slave to Jin.
I can release your heart
from that bondage!
Garnet!
Yes, Your Highness.
Get her!
Machina!
Over there!
He has an army.
The other side too!
Okay, Gio. Let's go.
Yeah.
I want to fight as well.
No Toa, let us handle
the fighting right now.
But.
Please try to understand it is
my sole purpose to protect you.
He's right.
You really should
let us deal with this.
Please. Be careful
Akira, Machina. Sit tight.
We'll be right back for you.
You will bow before me,
you insects! Bow!
All Agathion vitals are
within permissible levels
and there are no brain
stem core irregularities.
Releasing safeties
on all equipment.
All units ready for combat.
Attack!
[ASIM laughing]
Not bad, are you?
How does this amuse you?
What reason could you have to
cause so many casualties?
[ASIM] I could've sworn I
already told you this.
I just love beautiful things!
What's the matter?
Are you too much of a coward
to come over here
and fight me yourself?
Oh, I'm so scared!
Leave your shackles behind
and come back to me.
Free yourself from the
prison of his enslavement.
I will accept you as you are!
No! You don't know
Toa like I do.
Perhaps I should just tell
her that I like her,
or better yet that I love
her just like you did!
Oh yes! Darling!
I love you!
I love you madly my dear!
You've lost your mind!
Seems to me like you are
the ones who are insane.
The Resonance has worked
you up into a frenzy
with the pitiable illusion that
you're actually in love
with each other!
You're wrong!
Am I?
Then tell me why you cling so
pathetically to the Album?
Because I'm in love with her!
I love her with all of my heart!
Do you love her because she made
you forget your loneliness?
I don't think so!
You love her because she
said she loves you
and you fell for it!
You made a terrible mistake!
How could you be so stupid!
Do you even know
what love is? Do you?
Enough! Shut your mouth!
Shut your mouth!
What could common scum like you
know about a noble like me?
What an agonizing life
you must've led.
No one ever said
they loved you
so you were
consumed by loneliness
until it warped you
into what you are now.
Silence!
You insolent pest!
Someone to say
they love me, huh?
I don't need that.
How pathetic!
[GIO and GARNET growling]
Why you...
Okay Agathions, I want
you to rip them apart!
Your Majesty, we've sustained
far too much damage,
I recommend an
immediate retreat.
Don't tell me what to do!
Agathion control has
been reconnected.
[ASIM laughing]
That's better.
How could he?
He killed his own troops.
I'll do whatever I
please to my things.
It's no business of yours.
I've had enough of this
nonsense about love
between Dragons and humans,
you ignorant deluded fools.
Kill!
Hang in there Toa, kay?
This'll all be over soon.
Akira.
My my.
You're looking a little worse
for the wear, Jin Kamishina.
Die!
Machina!
You just don't know when to
lay down and die do you.
Machina!
Album!
I can tell that your death will
be so incredibly gorgeous.
If I can't have you,
then no one will!
Toa!
[ASIM]
Now die!
What is this? What's going on?
Wait.
Why are you running away?
The fight was just
getting started!
Synapse intrusion?
Why won't you do as I say?
What the..
That's impossible, the Agathions
don't feel
anything let alone fear!
Gio.
What are you about to do?
It isn't real!
You speak of the bond of
true love between
a human and a dragon?
Such a thing could never exist.
It's so beautiful.
Asim.
Hold on!
Wait a minute.
Gio, what are you doing?
Stop it!
Toa!
What is happening down there?
There's a high-energy
reading centered around
the northwest section
of the Tharsis plateau.
The EM signature is... Gio's.
[RAINA]
What?
It's growing exponentially
in size and power!
A distress signal?
Let's go!
It's Raina and Howlingstar!
What happened to
Akira and Machina?
[JIN] They didn't make it.
No.
[SIEGLINDE] Let's take
refuge outside the atmosphere.
[GIO roars]
Gio, no.
At long last we have a glimpse
at the true power of the Dragon.
Our greatest fear has come true.
All this time we had no idea
what we were dealing with.
I know that fate
brought us together.
But why...
Mars is burned over?
Traversing space,
destroying entire planets.
Is that the true nature
of these creatures?
It's too risky to keep these
abominations on Earth.
They are not entirely
under our control.
I suppose it's too late now.
There's only one way
to beat a Dragon.
And that's with another Dragon.
What are you drinking Megumi?
Oh Ryoko, this is all
the rage these days.
I'm on the "Melons Diet".
Hold on.
Where are you getting your info?
From this magazine.
This is from like a year ago!
Wow!
The year sure went by fast huh?
Yeah.
You know what they say,
time flies.
I'm not really sure I like
that flying time business.
Let's do the preview!
Next time, a new development
and a change of mind!