[JIN] There it is.
[Kazuki] You're gonna
ride in that?
Yep.
[CHUCKLES] Man, you're
getting ahead of me Jin.
I can't help it if
that's where my mom works.
I'm just lucky, that's all.
So your mom's an astronomer.
I won't lie to you,
I'm a bit jealous.
Yeah... it's nice.
Look man...
[FOOTSTEPS]
[EIJI LAUGHS]
Dad... hey.
[EIJI] It's almost time,
are you getting nervous yet?
Maybe a little.
Everyone gets nervous at first.
Trust me, once
you get into space
you'll forget you were ever
nervous about anything at all.
It's beautiful up there,
especially the
view of the Earth.
You could say that
it changed my life.
I just wanted you to
experience that for yourself.
Thank you, dad.
Captain Kamishina!
It's almost time!
Yeah yeah! Be right there!
I'll see you on the moon.
Dad, wait!
Jin.
You be careful okay?
I will and thanks for
coming down here Kazuki.
I should prob'ly go now.
Take a nice long look
at Earth for me would ya?
Sure.
[CABIN ANNOUNCER (F)]
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for boarding
ISDA Flight 029 today.
As we taxi to
the take off position,
please make sure your
seatbelts are securely fastened.
We will be experiencing
1.6 Gs as we accelerate.
[AI] Hey Jin, did your
girlfriend come to see us off?
No, shut up!
I'm teasing,
it's Kazuki isn't it.
Like any girl is ever
gonna fall for you.
Ah!
Mom help! He's being mean!
[MOTHER] I think you both
need to settle down,
the shuttle's going
to be taking off soon.
[CONTROLLER (M)] ISDA 029.
Hold your position on
the runway and confirm status.
Ready for departure.
[CONTROLLER (M)] ISDA 029
you are cleared to taxi.
The runway is clear.
Adjust countdown.
Starting the roll.
[BEEPING]
[GASPS]
[CROWD GASPS]
Oh, no!
[BEEPING]
Well, I'm off.
[COUSIN] I'm serious it's true!
[UNCLE] If you say so.
[AUNT] Alright finish
your food and get moving.
Don't be late.
[COUSIN] Fine.
[JIN] Ever since then,
I've been alone.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
And we're back.
Our guest in the studio
this morning is Raina Cromwell,
chief of the ISDA's
Lintverm Unit.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
Thank you for joining us.
[RAINA] Yes, my pleasure.
The topic on everyone's
mind is Thanatos.
What can you tell us
about its current status,
and do you have results
from the missile test
performed the other day?
Well Thanatos hasn't
shown any new movement
from its position
in Pluto's former orbit
so the situation
remains relatively stable.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
Does that mean the Earth
is safe from its approach?
Not necessarily.
But if the asteroid
ever continued
on its path toward
Earth, the ISDA is working on
a contingency plan
called the D-Project.
The missile test you mentioned
is part of this system.
These weapons are capable
of annihilating all asteroids
within a 15 kilometer radius
of the detonation point.
All of the missiles worked.
We will move the
D-Project into Phase 3.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
Thank you Mr. Cromwell.
Coming up next,
we have an update
to our report on
the recent serial killings.
Last night, shortly before dawn,
in Shin-Ogasawara Terminal City.
[YONAMINE] There he is.
Jin Kamishina.
Seen this?
I'm guessing you've read it.
Not very friendly, huh?
Look at you.
Only survivor of
the ISDA shuttle explosion,
son of the pilot who
made that fatal error.
And now you're not getting
along with the relatives
who took you in
and put a roof over head.
Leave me the hell alone.
Hey! Wait a minute!
Huh. Stubborn kid.
It's her.
[FANGIRLS YELLING]
[HOWLINGSTAR]
Aren't you Mr. Popular?
Howlingstar don't.
I'm jealous. I wish
I had adoring fans.
If that's how you feel you
should take my place next time.
I won't object.
No, I think I'll leave
all the press up to you.
We'd never be able to fit all
the presents for me
into this car.
Did you see it?
Yeah it was on the newsstand.
It's all about Jin.
We're at the school.
You gonna get off here?
So what do you think?
[KITAJIMA] It's just a blurry
picture of a girl.
There's no way to know if
she's the Album's Communicator.
We need to bring her in and
study every inch of her body.
Speaking of...
What?
There's no need to wear that
lab coat while we're having tea.
This is a complete
waste of time.
Contact me if you
find something useful.
That's cold.
You think it's easy
getting this information?
I'm putting my life in danger
every time I come to see you.
Let go.
And what would
you do if I said no?
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[ELEVATOR DOORS OPEN]
[ELEVATOR DOORS CLOSE]
I had a feeling you might
be in here Professor Nozaki.
We'll be conducting
a new Resonance tonight.
[NOZAKI] Good.
I look forward to it.
I can't help but think every
time I come to this place.
There must be a reason
for everything.
That no encounter
is meaningless.
You say that no
encounter is meaningless.
Interesting.
[INDISTINCT CROWD NOISE]
[ROCKET ENGINE]
[KID BRO]
That's so cool.
[THINKING]
Dad. Mom. Ai.
I'm so alone.
[AKIRA] What's wrong?
Don't tell me you're
getting nervous back there.
Leave me alone!
I've never done it before.
First time huh?
You want me to stop the car?
I'll show you
exactly how to do it.
[GASPS]
[LAUGHS]
You can relax
I'm just messing with you.
You should see
how red your face is.
[MACHINA] Leave the
boy alone now, Akira.
Yeah, yeah.
You only need to answer once.
Okay, okay.
[PANTING]
[HEART BEATING]
[NANAMI] We're beginning
the Resonance process now.
[YELLING]
Ma'am, the Resonance
is now complete.
Vital signs for both
have returned to normal.
Congratulations
Kazuki Tachibana.
Your Resonance was successful.
You are officially
a member of the Dragonauts.
Thank you!
My dragon.
[AMAGI] No, come on!
[GARNET] Come on?
Don't do this.
I want you to say, "please."
Please, all right? You win.
[GARNET LAUGHING]
[CREEPY CAT] Meow.
[SIGH OF RELIEF]
[WHIMPERS IN FEAR]
[GROWLS]
[GIRL SCREAMING]
[MONSTER LOUDLY EATING]
Hello? Is everything okay?
Um?
[GASPS]
[MONSTER GROWLS]
[JIN SCREAMING IN TERROR]
Go.
You're not real.
Hey.
Oh, so you're still alive.
Well then.
[JIN THINKING] Why?
Why is this happening?
It's the same.
It's just like before.
Yep. It's her. No doubt.
She's the Communicator.
It's Yonamine.
[SAKI] Sir, it's the Album!
Shin-Ogasawara Terminal City,
re-development district,
Point Alpha 107.
Commander Sakaki.
Requesting immediate
deployment of the Dragonauts.
[SAKAKI]
Request granted.
Sir, we need to catch her.
I'm counting on it.
Commander?
The Dragonauts were not
created to be a search team.
However.
Finding the Album is
a different situation.
[AMADEUS] They seem to
have gotten away, Miss.
[SIEGLINDE] I know.
What happened?
That thing attacked me!
And then.
It was you.
Who are you?
[TOA] My name's, Toa.
Toa.
That's when I realized it...
I'm not alone.
[RYOKO] This is
ISDA operator Ryoko!
[MEGUMI] This is Megumi!
And I'm Saki!
I want to make
sure of something.
What?
The three of us are
always together right?
So that makes us a trio,
sharing one body and one mind?
One body and one mind?
How would that even work?
That's only two things
and there're three of us.
That's not what I meant.
Well then explain it to us!
Oh! We're missing the preview!
Next time something
big's gonna happen!
Nice save!