I have to admit
that seeing it
up close like this
is pretty extraordinary.
It looks like something
that came out of a dream.
It's just so big.
Honestly what
were we thinking?
We believed we
could defeat that?
That look on your face
really doesn't suit you.
There isn't a
single soul up there
who will ever give up hope.
We've gotta stay
strong down here, too.
Ko...
Raina, I've got
an estimate for
the number of Ostrums
we're dealing with.
If my calculations are correct,
then Thanatos is sending
somewhere in neighborhood
of 6 billion Ostrums
down to Earth.
6 billion?
It's like it's planning
to force all of mankind
to go through Resonance,
so it can absorb them.
It's a human wave tactic.
Then again,
since they're Dragons
I guess I should say
a "Dragon-wave" tactic.
[SIEGLINDE] How can you be
joking at a time like this?
Well, we'll just have
to divide and conquer.
Each one of us will
take on 2 billion of them.
It'll be a piece of cake,
trust me on this.
[SIEGLINDE gasps]
Not. Funny.
It's crazy is what it is.
[RAINA] Is it?
Okay Howlingstar, I know
you've been waiting for this.
This is insane.
I can't believe
we're doing this.
[RAINA] Would you
rather turn back now?
Who? Me?
Running away from this
never even crossed my mind.
Let's go Amadeus!
Otohime! Off we go!
Howlingstar!
Are you suggesting we could
defeat Thanatos using the Aegis?
Yes.
If we reset it
to maximum output,
we might be able to buy
them a little more time.
Jin is still in
there somewhere.
And knowing him...
He's sure to come
through with something.
I'll do everything I
possibly can to support him.
[gasps]
What're you looking at?
[TOGETHER] Oh nothing.
Geez.
Don't give up Jin.
We don't stand
a chance against Thanatos.
Is there a way we
could change its mind?
I don't know yet, but it's
our only hope so we have to try.
This is our last opportunity,
to defend the Earth.
And make everything right
for Humans and Dragons.
Right.
[CROWD yelling in fear]
Look, Ma!
The Dragonauts!
[RAINA]
It's not safe here.
Get to an evacuation shelter.
All right then partner.
How does it feel to
make a hero's comeback?
How can this be?
Is this the final judgment
that will eradicate
mankind once and for all?
Sir!
It's too dangerous here!
Come to the
underground shelter!
Father!
You've got to
get away from here!
[JOHAN]
Young Miss!
Johan, please look
after my father for me.
You can count
on me, Madam.
I'm proud of you,
Sieglinde.
Let's go now, Amadeus!
I don't understand this.
What reasons could they have
to justify such
stubborn resistance?
Why would the humans reject
the opportunity
to merge with us?
Everyday we learn more about
how unique they really are.
There is no doubt
they are imperfect
creatures prone
to base behavior.
But they remain a fascinating
species nonetheless.
Abject terror.
Despair.
And hatred.
These are the
emotions they feel.
Those primitive
sensations are the result
of being locked inside
the feeble mental framework
of a human consciousness.
By merging they
can free themselves
of ignorance and suffering.
They can finally become
a part of the universe.
Why can't they simply
understand and accept that?
Perhaps it is
exactly because
their vessels and
the memories that fill them
are both individual
and finite that
the humans find
such inimitable worth in them.
That is a very
insightful point of view.
I was human.
And those memories
are useful now.
A great many of
them indicate that people
may appear weak, but
are actually quite resilient.
Damn!
There are too many of them,
we can't get close enough!
[NOZAKI]
Please allow me to help.
Professor Nozaki!
Toa.
Tell me something,
are you happy?
I am!
I always had doubts
about the things
I felt after going
through Resonance.
I wondered if
the emotions we felt
were brought
about by Resonance.
And if that's the case
then the adoration
we feel is manufactured.
Which would mean
the love we have
for our partners
is a lie, right?
Has our freedom of will
been taken from us?
Do our hearts no longer
determine who we love?
Otohime! Habaragi!
[NOZAKI] But at last
I realized something.
It doesn't matter
whether these feelings
for our partners
are the result of Resonance
or they come forth naturally.
The most important
thing is that the love
exists and you must
never ignore it.
Look inside yourselves
and trust what you feel.
Yeah. Okay.
I've come up with a plan
of action to protect Earth.
I've injected the
anti-Thanatos factor
from Laura into my own body
so that when I am absorbed
I will act as an Annihilator
and destroy Thanatos.
Why would you do
something so rash?
There's someone down
there I want to protect.
Does that sound strange?
No.
I always wanted to
see what the future held.
What path Humans
and Dragons eventually take.
But now only
the ties between you two
can answer that question.
Just remember this one thing,
make sure Mother understands
the feelings you share.
Professor!
Professor Nozaki!
[NOZAKI yelling]
Yuri...
Professor!
[YONAMINE]
What's wrong?
[KITAJIMA]
Just now...
No.
[JIN yelling]
Gio!
Current energy
levels are at 88%.
Now, targeting Thanatos' head.
Target lock acquired.
Prepare for Aegis irradiation!
No good! It had no effect!
This is bad.
Several of the Ostrums
are headed for the Moon.
The Moon.
The Aegis.
It's destroyed.
We've got Ostrums closing in!
Take evasive action at once!
Bastards!
Keep walking we'll see
Thanatos' mind up ahead.
Wait.
It appears you are
still alive, Ostrum.
I've been waiting patiently.
For you, Gio.
Wait how is this
guy still alive?
I thought we
already defeated him!
You two should
go ahead without me.
I'd like to handle him myself.
But, Gio!
Hurry up.
See you soon.
Last time we met,
you humiliated me.
Now I'll get my
revenge for that.
How very appropriate.
You sound just like the
beaten-down dog that you are.
I've had enough!
Okay one down and
1,999,999,999 to go.
Guess we'd better get
started on the next one.
Young Miss, are you all right?
Speak to me.
Don't worry about me, Amadeus.
Itsuki! Otohime!
Sieglinde! Itsuki!
Howlingstar!
Easy there partner.
What's with
the gloomy expression?
Get it together.
You look like
you're about to cry.
Don't be absurd.
Let's take a quick breather
then we can get back
to winning this battle.
What do you say guys?
Yes.
Sounds good.
Yeah I'm in.
What the?
Are all of those?
Ostrums!
[OSTRUM and GIO grunting]
Why the struggle?
Why not just give in
and follow Mother's will?
You are already
a part of Mother aren't you?
Garnet! You're back!
Why is it you're so attached
to the human being
standing next to you.
I want to know.
Because I love him.
That is indeed
a fascinating reply.
But now I have to question you.
To ascertain
if that feeling is real.
There is no
greater feeling
than to give all that you
are and merge with Mother.
Jin, be careful okay?
I will and thanks for
coming down here Kazuki.
I should prob'ly go now.
Take a nice long look
at Earth for me would ya?
Sure!
Kazuki.
Widow.
Looks like
somebody's got a hot date!
C'mon man you know
it's not like that!
Whoa there tiger!
Simmer down!
Knock it off would you?
[MACHINA] Toa,
it's there somewhere.
You've got to find
your seatbelt!
[TOA yelling]
Hey! Big Brother,
that's not very gentlemanly.
Oh gosh, I'm sorry.
[JIN stammering]
Oh, uh...
It's fine!
[AI giggling]
Toa, you've found yourself
quite a handsome seatbelt.
Not now Sis!
It's not like that!
Yeah!
Stop saying stuff
like that, please!
Okay.
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
No, it's me who
should be apologizing.
What's wrong?
Is there something the matter?
This isn't right.
What is it Big Brother?
What's going on?
You look upset.
Are you okay Jin?
No.
None of this is
actually happening.
My mother is long gone.
My sister too.
Big Brother.
Jin.
What's the matter?
Is everything okay, Jin?
This is some
sort of elaborate
fantasy world
created by Thanatos
of how I wish
things would've happened.
[TOA] Jin.
Jin!
[JIN yelling]
Jin, thank goodness
you realized it was a lie.
I heard your voice in there.
Thank you for bringing
me back to my senses.
Why?
Once you submit
to merging with Mother
you will instantly be released
from all of your suffering.
Why can't you understand
that that is not what we want?
I will only explain this once.
By going through
Resonance we have gained
something we
will never give up.
It has changed us
on a fundamental level
and that change is
coming upon you too.
I will never accept that!
I will never be like you!
We were changed
forever when we went
through Resonance
with humans.
We now have souls that
allow us to care for others.
Is that something we need?
Is that
necessary for our kind?
I'm fortunate that
I was born on this world.
Because now I have a soul.
I know of love,
and got to experience
life with Jin and Toa.
Could that be it then?
Could the only difference
between you and me, be a soul?
As humans we know
we aren't perfect.
We go through life
dealing with the
imperfections that we have.
And yes, sometime
it can be painful,
but that's what
it is to be alive.
I wouldn't have
it any other way.
Having all of that
experience taken away.
Then becoming a single entity.
That sure sounds an awful
lot like loneliness to me.
Like living in a void.
What do you mean?
With every fiber of my being,
I love the gentleness in
Jin's eyes when he looks at me.
And I love his voice,
I can't think of a better sound.
He's my everything.
I love him so much.
That feeling is
nothing but the result
of your Resonance
with each other!
No. It isn't.
I can feel it in my heart that
even without Resonance.
I would still love him.
And I love her, solely
because of who she is.
So neither one of us
has any need to merge.
We are not alone.
What's this?
Are you saying
that I'm all alone?
How could you have not known.
But, I'm...
What the?
Mother?
Are you Thanatos?
Victory is yours human.
It would seem
that I have spent
far too much time alone
in the emptiness of space.
I have forgotten the pure,
essential truth that
two hearts can share.
I will consider
what it means to love.
I think she's.
Mother, are you smiling?
What the hell is going on?
It seems pretty obvious.
Those two lovebirds up
there just saved the world.
Oh Young Miss!
Isn't that the most wonderful
news you've ever heard.
Thanatos is going away.
Someday, many eons from now I
shall visit this world again.
When I return, I don't know
whether it will be
you humans who greet me,
or those who have
inherited this world from you.
Only time will tell.
But if it is you,
and you nurture the hearts
you have beating
in your chests,
I know that there is no chance
I will be disappointed.
Jin!
Farewell Gio.
We are...
Not alone.