[ASIM laughing]
The power of love huh?
Fascinating. Truly fascinating!
[ASIM laughing]
[ASIM continues laughing]
Now, Major Maclaine!
[GARNET yells]
[GIO grunts]
Get outta here now!
What about...?
[GIO and GARNET
make fighting sounds]
How long are you going
to play games with him?
I think it's about time
you show him your true power!
Your Majesty?
You heard me!
[GARNET gasps]
What the...?
[GARNET grunting]
[EVERYONE gasps]
You... You're a...
Jin!
Stay there!
Hand over the Album!
You don't touch her!
Jin!
How pretentious of you.
The power of love huh? Too bad.
Too bad that's all a lie!
[GIO yells with rage]
[ASIM gasps]
Jin, where do we go
from here? Earth?
[JIN] I don't know,
Gio's hurt pretty bad.
Find someplace close
where we can set down.
It looks like there's
an abandoned Gillard
mining operation up ahead.
They'll have air
and water there.
[JIN] Good.
Hang in there just
a little bit longer, Gio.
[CONCUBINE ] A-13 through
A-28 have been sealed off.
The atmospheric pressure in
block B is now back to normal.
[CONCUBINE] The two
dragons are flying
toward sector one zero seven.
I'll bet they think they
made quite a fool of me.
[ASIM giggles]
How long are you
planning on lying there.
The time for games is over now.
Garnet, we're leaving.
We're now commencing
the final check on the Avenir.
Scheduled completion
time is 1430 hours.
Aw.
That look on your face tells
me the meeting was wonderful.
It was terrible, it's that king.
Anytime the slightest
thing goes wrong
he thinks he can
simply blame it on
Prince Asim acting
of his own accord.
They can't just have
their own way, forever.
I refuse to allow it.
Well don't forget
that they do control
half the world's
energy resources.
No one's really capable
of confronting them.
It's appalling isn't it?
[alarm beeping]
I'm reading three individual
Dragon life pulses on Mars.
Gio and Machina are here.
And the third one is unknown.
That can't be!
Call it a hunch,
but I'd say that Prince Asim
isn't quite done yet.
It's gonna be okay!
But you've
gotta be strong Gio!
Jin.
Maybe I can help him.
[TOA'S healing power]
[GIO grimaces]
Gio!
Jin.
Hey, you're alright.
Toa!
I'm fine. Just tired.
Relax, I just need to sit
and rest for a little while.
You saved me. Thank you Toa.
I suppose I did.
I'm just glad that I was
here to help you out Gio.
You've saved
my life so many times,
it's the
least I could do for you.
Well seems like
we've got no choice
but to rest here
until Gio and Toa get
their strength back.
Awesome. It's about
time we got a break.
Oh man wouldn't it be perfect
if there was a nice hot spring
in this place somewhere?
Akira.
There.
It can't be.
They thaw the ice
that's frozen underground.
That's how they get water.
This hot spring must be
some sort of by-product of that.
I bet they could even put a spa
in here if they wanted.
A spa huh?
The two of us
haven't been
in the water like this
since the moon.
Of course Toa was
with us on the moon.
Well she can't
really join us without her
bathing suit now can she?
Oh. So that's
how it is, is it?
Yep. That's how it is.
[AKIRA]
This is so cool!
Can you believe that we
just happened to find
a hot spring beneath
the surface of Mars?
This is paradise. Paradise!
Remember what we talked about.
Okay, okay.
I've told you many times
that it's not proper
to repeat yourself.
Okay, okay.
No.
Oh my bad.
We shouldn't use slang either.
I sure have come a long way.
Seems like yesterday that I went
into space for the first time.
Gio, if it wasn't for you
there's no way I could've
made it this far.
Coming here and rescuing Toa
wouldn't have
been an option for me.
You made all of this possible.
For that I am grateful.
Thank you for everything Gio.
Yeah.
I think we should always
look out for Toa together.
Trust me I would
never leave such a big job
to the likes of you.
Okay, fine.
Are you sure
you're feeling okay, Toa?
You don't look so good.
I'm fine.
Everything is just fine.
This water feels so good,
I'll be good as new in no time.
Okay. Um...
So I happened
to notice something earlier.
Well you know.
When you were
healing Gio,
parts of your back
were glowing bright red.
What exactly was that?
Those marks
looked really painful.
Oh that was
nothing Akira I promise.
It looks much
worse than it really is.
That's just what happens
every time I use that ability.
What you saw
were the stigmata.
The scars that mark her time.
Stigmata? What is that?
The end of your life
is approaching
quickly, isn't it Toa?
We Dragons have
extremely long lives
when compared to
the lifespan of a human.
But we are by
no means immortal.
When an individual's life
is finally coming to an end.
The stigmata will begin
to appear on the Dragon's body
and as death draws closer
the glow becomes brighter.
Oh my gosh.
Does Jin know
about any of this?
He doesn't.
Please don't tell him anything.
Why not? This is
kind of important!
It's okay.
I knew this would
happen from the beginning.
We Original Dragons are all
essentially living probes
that are a small part
of the greater entity
known as Thanatos.
When we succeed in our mission
of retrieving our kind
from the planet earth our
lives are destined to end.
That is our inescapable fate.
I can remember the exact
moment when I first saw Machina.
I was absolutely terrified.
Machina.
Akira. It's nice to meet you.
The instant I saw her
I thought she was beautiful.
She was my ideal.
She was everything
I thought a woman should be.
She was my exact opposite,
in every way.
Beautiful and sweet,
graceful and warm-hearted.
Her speech and movement
were so perfectly feminine.
And her body, well.
It's perfect.
She has everything
that I don't.
That's why at first I
was so afraid of Machina.
Oh Akira.
You see.
That was just the beginning.
We started to warm up
to each other right away.
It was just like
we were old friends.
It wasn't long
before I knew I loved her.
Despite the fact
that I could feel
this overwhelming love
in my heart for Machina.
A voice inside kept
telling me that it was wrong.
That you can't love a Dragon.
There was a conflict
raging inside of me.
Is it wrong for me to
feel this way about her?
And then,
I encountered Jin Kamishina.
I have to go and find her,
I've got to learn the truth.
Toa's the only one who knows.
He said that he was
going to see you
like it was a matter of course.
Like that was the only course
of action he could take.
I want to see.
They might be
able to change it.
Change?
The Dragon-human relationship.
I thought if I came with him.
That maybe I could see a new
way for us to live together.
When I saw the two
of you with each other
I knew the love in
my heart was real.
I had to come for you.
Thank you Jin.
It took me long enough
to learn this lesson,
but I'm grateful
that I finally did.
If two hearts share
the same beautiful feeling
then it doesn't really matter
if you're a dragon or a human.
I too learned something very
important from all of this.
Toa, you once told me
that everything was fate.
You said destiny
can't be changed.
But you also told me
in no uncertain terms
that your fate is something
that can be changed.
You and Jin have proven that
fact beyond a shadow of a doubt.
So you and Jin should
make the fate that you want.
Don't ever settle
for anything less.
Akira and Machina.
[JIN] Oh, I see you
guys are already out.
Are you feeling okay Toa?
[GIO] We should hurry up
and get out of here.
[JIN] Yeah this is
the Gillard's home base.
There's no telling
what might happen
if we stay here any longer.
Hold up!
Take a look around!
Doesn't all of this look like
some sort of church altar?
Look!
Now that you mention it,
I guess it does.
Jin, I think we should
hold a wedding.
But, for who?
The two of you!
The two of us?
You got it.
That's you. And you.
Together forever and ever!
C'mon, this isn't the time
to be joking around, Akira.
He's right we should
hurry up and leave.
I'm not joking around.
I'm being totally serious.
But why at a time like this?
Now is when we need it most.
You're so sweet.
But, what about?
You're better off not
sweating the small stuff.
You ready to be a man?
Jin, don't you want... me?
Of course I want you!
I'd love to be your
husband. Soon for sure!
But does it have to be now?
[JIN] I mean it's a little
soon don't you think?
You don't get married
running from a madman.
They want a wedding.
What is that?
A magic ritual
that changes fate.
Changes fate?
All right! You've got
more than enough witnesses.
Let's do this you two!
Jin.
Oh, Akira.
Thank you for this.
No prob.
Okay we're not done here yet.
You put on the ring next.
[ASIM clapping]
[ASIM] Enough with these
childish charades.
I wish you
wouldn't mock me so.
Asim.
[ASIM giggles]
[AKIRA gasps]
No!
[GARNET growls]
[AKIRA] Oof!
[EVERYONE gasps]
Akira. No!
Akira, my love!
Akira!
Please, Akira stay with me!
Please don't go!
[GARNET chuckles]
[JIN] Akira!
[MACHINA] Akira!
I didn't even
get a chance to see...
What will become of you.
Now both of you...
must create a new
history...
as human and Dragon.
Together.
Don't go Akira.
[AKIRA's dying breath]
Machina.
[MACHINA crying in heartbreak]
[MACHINA yells in rage]
Akira!
[ASIM laughs maniacally]
Here it comes!
Now it begins!
[MACHINA yells
in grief and rage]
[ASIM laughs]
Do it! Yes!
Not good.
Machina!
Saki, Ryoko,
what's this button for?
Button?
What's that doing there?
It has "don't push"
written on it.
It also has "danger"
in big letters.
If it says "don't push" it's
telling us to push it, right?
Look I know how you feel
but you can't push it okay?
Oooh!
But I wanna push it so bad!
Let me handle this!
I'll push it!
Things don't look
good around here.
I know! Both of you!
The preview!
Right! Next time.
The Gillard story finally
reaches it's conclusion!
Now I can push it!