Machina.
Akira.
It's nice to meet you.
Although we had
a hostile encounter
with the Gillard Army
on the return trip.
Our mission to capture
the Album was successful.
Major Maclaine is acting
like she can just do
whatever she wants
and then get away with it.
The Gillard Army is officially
contesting the whole incident.
And right now our
case looks pretty weak.
They're pursuing legal action,
like dissolving our contract.
We've got a lot
of material to cover today.
Let's go ahead and move
on to Kazuki and Jin.
Kazuki Tachibana
is at the medical center
being re-evaluated
for his fitness as a Dragonaut.
Jin Kamishina is being
confined inside the base.
Jin Kamishina huh?
So what do we do with him now?
That brat caused
all of this, didn't he?
[RAINA thinking]
Jin Kamishina.
Judging from his
quick-witted decisions
and the bold initiative
he displayed during the
shuttle's atmospheric re-entry
I'd say there's a
lot more of his father
in that boy than I thought.
What's the matter?
Continue with your report.
Yes sir, please
excuse me.
Next, we should probably
discuss the Album.
At the moment
she's being held
in a specially-designed
cell with guards posted
so that our research
team can collect data
on Original Dragons.
That leaves
Gio and Widow.
They're confined
on Tartarus.
Well, there's no
telling when those Dragons
might go on a deadly rampage.
At this point they're damaged
goods and protocol dictates
that the rogue Dragons must
be disposed of accordingly.
Keep in mind that Gio and Widow
weren't bound by Resonance.
They took up Communication with
people other than their Masters.
They are also quite
valuable for research.
Is it possible to temporarily
postpone the disposal process?
The Album alone
will be sufficient.
Can't you see that
more research subjects
will only speed
up our progress?
Just like I told you before.
Those who demand everything
always end up with nothing.
But sir.
Would you just stop it already!
Do any of you have
a shred of decency?
You talk like they're
some sort of product.
Machina's right here!
They're all right here.
It's okay Akira.
That concludes my report.
Good work.
Take it easy.
Otherwise you too
will be reevaluated
for your fitness
as a Dragonaut.
[GIO] I can't help but
think about something
that Howlingstar once told me.
He said the destiny
of Earthborn Dragons
who have undergone Resonance
is to protect their masters.
[WIDOW] Then I am
without a destiny
as I have already
lost my Master.
You on the other
hand still have yours.
You mean Kazuki Tachibana?
That's right.
Kazuki is your Master.
He is not mine at least.
Have I been so blind
that I couldn't see
my true destiny was
to be Kazuki's Dragon?
Changing one's
destiny is impossible.
But fate can be malleable.
A lesson you won't
live to learn.
What do you mean by that?
The island we're on now
Is for the disposal of Dragons.
This place is a top-secret ISDA
facility where Dragons
that are judged to be
unfit for whatever reason
are secretly disposed of.
This island is a graveyard.
Make no mistake we have been
brought here for one reason.
To die.
There is a powerful
CSS electromagnetic field
that completely
surrounds the island.
For us Dragons,
escape from this pit of death,
is simply not an option.
To hell with them!
Who do they think
they're dealing with?
[AI laughing]
C'mon Brother! Move it!
Hurry up would ya'?
I'll be right there!
Ai?
Where'd you go Dad?
Mother?
Hello?
Jin.
Toa.
I'm the one who
left you all alone.
It was my fault.
That's why I came back for you.
Toa.
All right you bastards!
Let me out of here!
Let me see Toa!
That all depends
on your attitude.
There now, I'm Yuri Kitajima,
head of the research team.
It's nice to meet you Jin.
What is he doing?
This is Resonance.
So this is it, Resonance.
Resonance is a harmonious
synergy between man and Dragon.
You could call it
a contract of sorts.
Now.
Communicators are born from
eggs that undergo Resonance.
That's Gio!
The person who goes
through Resonance
becomes that Dragon's Master,
and that Dragon
follows its Master's orders
with absolute obedience.
Absolute obedience?
Gio's Master was supposed
to be Kazuki Tachibana.
Now this is where
things get murky.
As you must know, Gio didn't
choose Kazuki to be his Master.
He chose you instead.
This is of great interest to us.
I don't know what
you expect me to say.
What's even more interesting
Is your relationship
with the Album.
Hold on!
Toa is someone else's?
Someone else's?
That doesn't make much sense,
think about it.
What?
No that's impossible.
It can't be because I never went
through a Resonance with Toa.
The evidence we found
in your body is irrefutable.
During the shuttle
accident two years ago
you went through
Resonance with the Album.
I did what?
So ,Toa.
Yes.
You see you've been chasing
the Album this entire time.
But what you didn't know,
is that you're her master.
Geez, I am beat.
[AKIRA yawning]
Sometimes I feel
like I understand
less and less every day.
Oh, man.
I don't know what I'm supposed
to believe anymore.
Here.
Take it, I peeled it for you.
Oh, thank you.
Akira!
So, takin' a break
and relaxing huh?
How can you be so laid back?
--[MACHINA] Here.
--[SIEGLINDE] Hey what're those?
Oh look at those cute
little apple bunnies.
How delightful.
I mean, quaint.
This is a gigantic mess.
Mr. Kiril was so
adamant about us
settling things by
the book with the military.
Then it turns out
that our beloved leader
was totally conned
by that Gillard prince.
Oh well, I guess we
should have seen it coming.
Come on now tell me
what's on your mind.
What do you mean?
You didn't really
come here to talk
about all that stuff did you?
Spill it.
Please...
Promise you'll stay.
Never leave us or betray us.
Amagi is dead, Kazuki
is pretty much useless,
and Jin's not an option.
Akira if you were
to abandon us now
it'd just be me and Raina.
And I don't know how
well I could handle that!
Yeah.
All right.
I promise you.
Hello Doctor!
Guess what it's
almost my birthday.
It's true!
I sure hope I get lots
of awesome presents this year!
Are you gift grubbing?
How childish.
What's wrong with that?
Fine think about what you
want and then let me know.
All right!
It can't be anything
too expensive though.
What? Oh man.
Well in that case.
[GARNET] I have failed
to bring you Gio, my lord.
I humbly beg for your
pardon in this matter
and hope that you will
overlook my shortcomings
yet again Prince Asim.
Please forgive me.
Never mind about Gio.
My Lord?
The Album.
I now desire the Album.
It's her beauty.
She alone is worthy of me.
My lord, by now the Album
is already in
a secure ISDA facility.
It may not be
possible to obtain her.
Think hard, Garnet.
Why did we have our spies
infiltrate the ISDA
in the first place?
Garnet, I believe
now is the time.
Sir!
So that's the Album?
Yes, I've compared
her to Gio and Widow.
Each one of those
Dragons has acted
in partnership with someone
that they didn't go
through Resonance with.
Coincidentally all
three of these Dragons
appeared recently
one after the other.
It's fascinating.
Don't you think so?
We're on the edge of something.
And I'm going to
find out what it is.
What is the Album's condition?
At the moment.
All of her vital signs
appear to be stable doctor.
It looks like the
sedative is working.
[alarm beeping]
The Album has escaped!
Catch her! Somebody! Anyone!
We have to find her!
The Album is escaping!
Sir should we mobilize
the special unit?
No way.
They don't even stand a chance.
Despite that angelic face,
she's really a demon.
Ryoko, have you ever tried
saying something encouraging?
Right.
Sorry.
But she's got a good point,
the Album is an Original Dragon.
How the heck are
we supposed to catch her?
Just do it!
Right!
We'll do our best!
[SIEGLINDE panting]
Wait!
Akira, are you sure about this?
I want you to know that
no matter what happens.
I'm staying with you.
But what you didn't know
is that you're her master.
Me? Toa's Master?
See, you're not alone anymore.
You have me now Jin.
How can that be?
What exactly is Resonance?
Jin! Get up, it's time to go!
What is this?
What's happening?
We don't have much time left.
Get up!
What are you doing?
But, Toa.
Toa's getting out
of here on her own.
So you'd better get going too!
Right.
I've come for you.
Don't move!
Please don't, I'm here to
take the little ones with me.
Take the little ones with you?
That is my mission here.
Excuse me!
I'm the one in
charge around here
And I won't
allow anyone to lay
so much as a finger
on these eggs.
You're just like...
Every last one of these
eggs is of the earth.
The parking garage is up ahead.
Let's take a car,
and get out of here!
Raina.
This was bound to happen.
Sooner or later.
You mean...
Spare me the lies.
I know that you've given aid
to this dangerous young criminal
on more than one occasion.
Then again you may have
tricked them into doing this.
Is that right, Jin Kamishina?
Well, I...
Raina!
He did no such thing.
Akira and I decided on this.
Machina!
Take another step and he'll be
dead before he hits the ground.
Make her stop this Akira.
And if I say no?
Machina! Think about this!
Maybe you should listen
to your own advice Howl.
Raina!
Keep away!
Everything'll be just fine.
Raina!
Every last one of these
eggs is of the Earth.
Why? Why would you?
You want me to stop?
That's right.
I want you to
discontinue the experiments.
I want to know why?
Give me one good reason!
Why discontinue this
when we've finally
gotten such a
perfect live sample?
What good can come
from examining her?
Plenty of good will come.
Just wait.
Don't get me wrong
Dr. Kitajima,
I'm not trying to
steal your chance
at recognition from
the academic community;
and I'm certainly not trying
to hinder this operation.
On the contrary.
Take a moment to consider
that we are tampering
with forces we
don't fully understand.
Perhaps it would be prudent
to leave them be for the moment.
There are many
things that are better
left to the realm
of the unknown.
I see. Then it's over.
You'll have your chance.
Just trust me.
Some day you'll be
properly recognized.
The whole experiment
got dropped just like that.
That's pretty high-handed
even for Professor Nozaki.
Listen Doctor.
Go to Tartarus?
I'm just saying
they've got the same
caliber of research facility
there as they do here, right?
But, Nozaki would never
allow that to happen.
You could get the Album out
there on your own Authority.
All you have to do is explain
the she needs to be quarantined.
I suppose I could do that.
It's gonna be okay.
And then when we
get those results back.
Even the professor
will give you some credit.
It's okay Doc, we're
gonna make it through this.
[RAINA coughing]
Why are you helping me?
We think that
you might be able
to change the relationship
between people and Dragons.
What do you mean relationship?
Like Machina.
No matter what,
she's always by my side.
The reason she's
with me isn't simply
because she's
some mindless puppet
that I have
complete control over.
You have to understand,
Machina and I are together
because we complete each other
in the truest sense of the word.
I love her.
It's ridiculous to even think
that they could be our property.
Both parties
share their existences.
I'm sure you get
it since you were with Gio
even though you
aren't his Master.
There are many things
that are better left
to the realm of the unknown.
It would be prudent
to leave them be.
Why would he tell me that now?
Doctor, I thought
super hard about my present.
What was that sound?
Something's coming for us.
It's headed right toward
us at a high velocity!
We got a match!
One of the two vessels is
a Gillard Army submarine!
The Gillard Army?
The other one is--
[EVERYONE grunting]
It can't be.
An Agathion!
This is a distress signal
from the ISDA submarine.
I think I'd like The Album.
Still recovering
from the wounds
of their battle at
the base of mount Fuji,
the Dragonauts fall
into a new foe's trap!
Hey
Meanwhile, in Istanbul,
the international bomb plot
by the evil General
Blackeye draws ever closer.
Minute by minute,
second by second
the countdown to
detonation approaches!
Hey! C'mon!
Next time on
Dragonaut: The Resonance!
Decisive battle
at 20,000 meters!
Roses blooming in the solar wind
have the fragrance of death!
The time-space dragon Red Gyao
appears and actualizes!
Oh man!