Static is clear.
Reacquiring image.
Image correction starting now.
Distortion compensation
rate is deviating
3.74% more than expected.
We are now recording
all radiation fluctuations.
Gamma rays are decreasing.
Gravitational lens
effect confirmed.
Recovering image.
[KIRIL] Magnify.
Maximum magnification.
[Girl singing in Japanese]
[TOA] I'll be waiting for you.
At that lighthouse.
You'll be waiting?
Toa!
[Car door opens and shuts]
Toa?
[SIEGLINDE]
You and I need to talk.
She's a kid.
[AMADEUS] I'm sorry young man.
How'd he do that? And why?
Let me outta this
place right now!
Hello? Answer me!
Tell me where I am!
ISDA.
ISDA? What am I doing there?
We have business with you.
Business? What are
you talking about?
Let me out now and
I might not report you!
This is about the shuttle
accident you were in.
Feeling a bit more cooperative?
You ready little man?
[KAZUKI] Ka-zu-ki.
Kazuki Tachibana.
Gio.
[KITAJIMA] Gio?
[NANAMI] Yeah, you're
not gonna believe
what this guy did,
it's too funny.
This doofus misread
the code number G-10
and thought it said Gio.
So now he's decided
Gio is its name.
Gio.
Hmm.
It's not half bad.
What do you think you're doing,
keeping me here like
I'm some kind of prisoner.
Do you have something to say
about the accident or not?
[SAKAKI] Your father
was not responsible
for the shuttle accident
that killed your family.
20 years ago Pluto was destroyed
by a free roaming
celestial body called Thanatos.
Right, but we were
told that Thanatos
wouldn't collide with the earth.
Currently it is holding
position in Pluto's old orbit.
However...
Eventually Thanatos
will collide with Earth.
We have already
started seeing the signs.
The shuttle accident wasn't
the result of pilot error.
It was caused... by this...
What is it?
An extraterrestrial
life form from Thanatos.
The ISDA calls them dragons.
You're serious. But I don't
understand how this--
Unfortunately
this being collided
with the shuttle
your family was aboard.
What is all this?
Extraterrestrial life forms?
Dragons?
What about the truth
concerning the accident?
Why didn't you tell
everyone that the accident
was caused by an
extraterrestrial from Thanatos!
Since that day my father
has been talked about
like some kind of murderer!
Do the right thing and tell
the public what happened!
I'm afraid we can't do that.
Who are you?
I'm the chief of the Lindworm
Unit. My name is Raina Cromwell
Now listen Jin.
I can only imagine
what you must be feeling
but try to think
about the big picture.
What if we told them the truth?
That the accident
was caused by aliens.
There would be consequences.
So what!
The Dragonauts may
be the only chance
humanity has against
an onslaught from Thanatos.
If you want revenge
for your family.
Then become a Dragonaut!
Revenge means nothing to me.
Just prove my father
was innocent.
And then we can talk!
Where do you think you're going?
I am going home, now.
Funny I didn't know
you had a home to go to.
Sorry I'm late!
Please forgive me.
Kazuki?
Jin.
[SAKI]
You'll be staying
at the ISDA facility
for a little while.
We've already
contacted your family
so you don't need to
be concerned about that.
It's okay.
Trust me, I'm not all
that worried about it.
Oh? I see. That's good.
It's great to see you,
it's gonna be be just
like old times. Right?
After the shuttle accident.
You dropped out of
the astronaut training academy
and I started to believe
that you and I would
never see each other again.
Think back, Jin.
Do you remember the promise
we made that night?
Up on the hill.
[YOUNG KAZUKI]
One of these days.
We should go into
outer space together. 'Kay?
[YOUNG JIN] Sure.
That sounds like a great idea.
Do you promise me?
Yeah.
Someday, for sure.
More than
anything else we wanted
to go into space together.
I don't understand
what's happened to you.
Why won't you join us, Jin?
C'mon! Be a Dragonaut with me!
Did you know?
About what happened
with the shuttle accident.
That it wasn't
my father's fault.
Well yeah. I guess I did.
But not until
I became a Dragonaut.
Before then I didn't
know anything about it.
Yeah, whatever.
Jin.
Did you mean what you said?
About making Jin Kamishina
a Dragonaut?
Is there a problem with that?
No, but...
If he had the Album
you would welcome him.
Is that what Dr. Kitajima said?
She didn't have to.
We are relatively
certain that Jin
will have contact
with the Album again.
When that happens,
use every available resource
to capture her.
Is that clear?
Crystal clear, sir.
The shuttle accident wasn't
the result of pilot error.
It was caused by this.
If you want revenge
for your family.
Then become a Dragonaut!
I can't believe
those selfish bastards.
I don't need them.
They can all go to hell.
Leave me alone!
I have to go.
To Toa.
Toa.
Jin.
You're here.
Um, about yesterday.
I don't remember
exactly what happened.
There is one thing...
I do remember falling.
You don't need
to worry about that.
The important thing about
yesterday is that I met you.
Contact with
the Album is confirmed.
Roger that.
Please continue
the surveillance.
You won't get away again.
Is something the matter?
Hey Toa? Have you ever
traveled to outer space?
Have you ever seen
the Earth from way out there?
Yes I have.
So what did it look like?
Well, I thought it
was a very pretty planet.
But, did it change your life?
You know, I think it did.
That was mean!
Currently the Album is out
of ISDA's observation network,
and is fleeing
with Jin Kamishina
through the mountains
northwest of the lighthouse.
All Lindworm Unit members,
link with your Communicators,
then, you are to
locate and secure
the two of them as
quickly as possible.
Also, in the event
that the targets
don't cooperate with you.
You may use force.
That is all.
I will now brief
you on your stations.
Akira, go with
the special forces
and cut off the
target's path of retreat.
[KAZUKI] Jin... why?
Amagi, you and Kazuki
take the islands west exit.
I'll close the net
at the north exit.
Now, as far as actualizing.
[HOWLINGSTAR] Now!
What is this?
Here.
Thank you, Jin.
All that running
sure made me thirsty.
Hey, Toa. What on
earth came over you?
Please. Promise me you
won't go near ISDA anymore.
What's going on here?
Who're you?
[AKIRA] Hey! Over here!
Do as I say, nice and easy,
and nobody gets hurt.
All right then.
Would the two of you mind
coming along with me?
What the hell
are you talking about?
What do you guys want from us?
Machina!
[MACHINA] Now I've got you.
Toa.
I promise that
I'll come back for you.
After her Machina!
Toa.
Whoa there!
That's far enough.
The Album.
Toa!
Jin!
Kazuki.
Why are you running away Jin?
You promised me long ago
we'd go into space together.
So why?
Kazuki. You don't.
Stay where you are!
Don't move.
Are you going to shoot me?
I don't want to shoot.
We're best friends.
Just come back with me.
We can talk about
all of this at ISDA.
Please Jin!
You say you're
my friend... my friend!
Then, you hunt me down,
ambush me,
and threaten me with a gun?
Friends don't do that!
Please Jin.
I truly am.
All alone in the world.
Your arm. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
See.
You're not alone anymore.
You have me now, Jin.
You won't get away!
Jin!
Amagi... what're you?
How could you?
[AMAGI] I did it.
I just shot another person.
Abnormality
detected in Spirytus!
The comm link with his master
is starting to fade rapidly.
If this keeps up
his communicator
can't be maintained!
This is impossible!
[YONAMINE] Where's Amagi?
More! Kill them!
I want to kill more people!
His resonance connect is.
Why?
Why would you do
something like this!
Amagi!
[AMAGI] Yes! Yes! Yes!
Destroy everything Spirytus!
Amagi!
What are you doing Amagi?
Get him back to
a Communicator now!
Amagi! Amagi has
been eaten by Spirytus!
He was what?
Disgusting.
What?
This can't be right.
Why are you actualizing here?
This is bad.
Now with his Master gone.
His Resonance Connect
will not function.
That's right,
and when that happens.
We won't have any way
to control the dragon.
Impossible!
This cannot be happening!
Spirytus will reach the
observation park any second now.
Massive casualties are expected!
Hey. Over there. Look.
What is it?
It doesn't look good.
It's burning!
Whoa. What's that?
My god.
That thing.
I see now. It's a dragon.
I won't let it touch you Jin!
Toa.
[JIN] Toa. Who are you really?
Please. Close your eyes.
Toa.
[Girl singing in Japanese]
Excellent work everyone.
This is ISDA operator Saki.
Today is a tremendously
auspicious day.
What?
[RYOKO] This is
the second time Megumi.
[MEGUMI] She just wants
to hog all the attention.
You two are both here right?
Just being here isn't enough.
Yeah, we don't get
to say anything!
We've still got a long way
to go so just bear with it.
The preview time is
running out, again!
Next time, there's a monster
battle and some other stuff!