I'd say we cut it pretty close.
Not a very subtle tactic.
Well take a moment to think.
There wouldn't be
any witnesses up here.
They can make up whatever story
they want to explain the fire.
But how did they know
about this place?
[YONAMINE]
If I was able to find you,
it was only a matter of
time before ISDA caught up.
They're bound to find out
that cabin was empty.
They'll be looking for us soon.
Where do we go now?
We're going to Tokyo.
[JIN] How can we really hide
with all these people around?
If you're trying to hide a
tree put it in the forest.
person put it in the city.
Sneaking around will only
draw their attention.
Trust me nobody's seen you.
You're way too self-conscious.
You should really
work on fixing that.
I'll get right on that.
[YONAMINE] There's another
reason that we came to Tokyo.
Right now, Tartarus is one
of the more heavily secured
facilities that ISDA controls.
It won't exactly be a cakewalk
getting in to that place.
We'll need to make all
sorts of preparations
to execute this
mission properly.
It's not like ISDA is
just going to let us
take their usual ferry
out to the island right?
You are so dumb,
little man.
What I mean is...
We'll come by more information
and the necessary illegal goods
where there are lots
of people around.
After all, it won't do any good
if we're not
completely ready to act,
and we wind up
getting caught.
So you know of
a hideout in Tokyo
where they won't
be able to find us?
It's going to be
extremely difficult
to keep ourselves completely
hidden from ISDA, even in Tokyo.
[JIN] So then...
In the event
that they do find us,
our only hope is to be
somewhere they
wouldn't dare strike.
Does a place
like that even exist?
Yes it does.
Wait a minute you're
not talking about...
This is the place?
This is the Baumgard
family home?
"Little man" goes for
that brain of yours too.
Geez you're dumb.
Do you honesty think that
my family estate is in Japan?
[YONAMINE] The Baumgards
are one of the oldest
and most powerful noble
families in Germany.
Your mansion is in
Nuremburg as I recall.
[SIEGLINDE]
That's right.
This is just the
vacation house
that we use when
we stay in here.
Vacation house?
I didn't stutter.
This isn't a house.
It's a castle.
Good to see you Young Miss.
Welcome home.
It's huge.
Hey.
Up there.
Is that Amadeus?
The name of the man in
the portrait is Alfred.
That gentleman was
the beloved grandfather
of Lady Sieglinde, sir.
That's her Grandfather?
I guess we're mistaken.
It's been a long time Sieglinde.
You seem so surprised to see me.
You do know you're not the only
person who uses this mansion.
He has a business
meeting here in Japan.
He arrived this morning.
That's the current head
of the Baumgard family.
The great Wilhelm Baumgard.
I guess that would make him
Sieglinde's father then.
So, have you eaten dinner?
Not yet.
But I don't feel
like eating.
I wasn't asking you I
was asking your friends.
You really must be
more considerate.
You should always offer
your guests refreshments.
Forgive me Father but
I must excuse myself
for remainder of the evening.
Hey.
If you leave now you'll
have nowhere else to go.
Just stay.
You and your friends
will be safe here.
Are you saying you will be
kind enough to hide us?
Of course I will.
You my dear are the sole
heiress to the Baumgard family.
I have no intention of
handing you over to anyone.
Especially those
reptiles out there.
The Baumgard family has
provided a great deal
of financial support to ISDA.
I assure you they won't bite
the hand that feeds them.
As long as you are
here you'll be safe.
But I'm afraid
that's all I can do.
You understand.
That's fine.
All we really need
is a couple of days.
We can manage the
rest on our own.
Yes I see.
I'm sorry to interrupt
your meal sir.
There was a call from Germany
and I was instructed to
notify you immediately.
If you'll excuse me.
There is some urgent business
that I really must attend to.
Did you know my father
would be in Japan
when you came up with this
brilliant hiding place?
Of course I didn't.
I have to admit I always knew
you and your family
were well off.
But I didn't know you were
rich enough to finance ISDA.
Yeah well they're not my family.
Sieglinde wait.
An anti-Thanatos factor?
Yes, and once we inject
this anti-Thanatos factor
into the cells we extracted
from the Raum, well.
Please see for yourselves.
Once within the Dragon host,
the anti-Thanatos factor
causes repetitive
irregular cell growth,
much like cancer.
This quickly undermines
normal cellular development.
This process is fatal
and soon the host dies.
Thanatos is a living being.
And as such this
disease will kill it.
That's all well and good but how
do we get this inside Thanatos?
We would use the Dragons.
Dragons?
Yes.
In order to effectively
utilize the disease
it's necessary that it
be in an active state
when it comes into
contact with Thanatos.
So the first step would
be to expose a Dragon
to the anti-Thanatos factor.
Then we would send the Dragon,
as a host, back to Thanatos.
This would be
a lot like sending
disease-ridden rats
into an enemy camp.
We would essentially be using
a primitive biological weapon.
I understand.
But I thought it
was already decided
that we were going to use the
Dragon Slayer against Thanatos.
We are still moving
forward with the operation
that makes use of the
Dragon Slayer as planned.
Why choose just one course.
Our goal is to destroy Thanatos
regardless of the methods.
Indeed it is certainly
to our advantage
to have multiple ways of
eradicating the enemy.
We have already begun
a preliminary round
of experiments with
Howlingstar and Amadeus.
When will you know the results?
We've scheduled our first
examination tomorrow.
Tomorrow is the day.
I can't fall
asleep Sieglinde.
Are you awake?
What is it?
What's it like to
have a father?
I mean how does it feel?
Where did that come from?
I'm curious because I was
created from Thanatos.
So I never had a father or
a mother, I thought I'd ask.
For one thing,
it's no big deal.
Sure if it wasn't for him
I wouldn't have been born.
But that's pretty much it.
We don't live
together or anything,
I mean I hardly
ever even see him.
If he were dead my life honestly
wouldn't change that much.
Just today I caught myself
wishing he wasn't here.
So you don't like
your father huh?
Well if that's what you
think that's fine with me.
What I think is that your
father cares about you.
He is giving you
shelter here Sieglinde.
He's only protecting me
because I'm the heiress
to the Baumgard family.
Are you certain
of that?
Believe me Toa, my father
has no feelings for me.
He only cares for
the family name.
I guess I just
don't understand it.
Well, I couldn't
explain it to you anyway.
All I know is that I don't
belong in this place.
Where are you going?
I think I'll
go for a walk.
The fresh air might
do me some good.
Toa.
Ah that felt nice.
You should hit the shower.
What the...?
I wonder where Gio went.
[OTOHIME roars]
What's that?
[ITSUKI gasps]
Hang on, Itsuki.
[KITAJIMA] Oh, so you're at the
Baumgard Mansion outside Tokyo?
[YONAMINE] Yeah,
we just had dinner.
I think we're through
the first part of this.
That must be nice.
To wine and dine
at a mansion.
I don't know if nice
is the right word.
Any new
developments at ISDA?
Itsuki Habaragi and Otohime
were taken into custody.
Both of them will be secure on
Tartarus a few hours from now.
So the only dragons left to
capture are Toa and Gio.
The science team has been
acting strange also.
What do you mean?
They've been moving
a lot of people and
equipment to Tartarus.
And that means...
That they must be planning
to use the Dragons
for something.
Well you know how
to contact me.
Wait, just a minute.
What is it?
I...
Does the lady want
a goodnight kiss.
Maybe...
How is Toa doing?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Is there anything
different about her?
Different? Not really.
Oh. That's good.
No. Don't hang up!
[phone busy signal beeping]
Good night beautiful, mwah.
Professor!
It's your back again!
I'm all right.
It'll pass soon enough.
But...
I said I'm all right.
[GIO] Are you sure you
don't want to tell, Jin?
Yes.
He'll find out
sooner or later.
I know he will.
It's just...
Not yet.
You don't have much time.
What is it?
What's going on?
Hey, Gio.
Gio.
What's the matter?
Everything's just fine.
I will protect Toa,
no matter what happens.
I wonder here could
he have wandered off to?
Is everything all right sir?
Yes.
Well no.
My friend Gio left our room
and hasn't come back yet.
I'm worried he's lost.
So, I was just walking
around trying to find him.
Um...
My father loved this country.
As you can imagine
he was a busy man,
yet he often made time
to visit this estate.
Wow, is that right?
After Sieglinde was born
he always brought her
along on his
Japanese vacations.
He was a very strict father.
I don't remember him ever
making time to play with me.
But he was constantly pampering
that granddaughter of his.
So um, is Sieglinde's
mother still around?
She died soon after
Sieglinde was born.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It was difficult.
I lied about having a business
meeting here in Japan.
When I heard that Sieglinde
was being pursued.
I thought she might come here
so I decided to wait for her.
If you're not here for business
then why are you here?
I want to help her.
Shouldn't that be reason
enough for me to be here?
So then why don't
you just tell her that?
Don't talk to her
about inheritances
or carrying on
the family name.
Just come out and tell her
that you're worried about her
and that you want to help
her in any way you can.
I would but I feel certain
that she loathes me.
The only ones she ever
opened her heart to
were my father and Amadeus.
Who is Amadeus?
That was a dog that
we used to have.
And now she doesn't have my
father or Amadeus to confide in.
Once we've made the
necessary preparations.
We're going to break
into the ISDA.
This is going to be
way more dangerous
than anything we've
ever done before.
I should tell you that
there's no guarantee
that any of us will
come back safely.
So please tell Sieglinde
how you feel about her.
You may never get
another chance.
True.
But can I ever repair the
damage that's been done?
I'm sorry to interrupt
but this is important.
We won't be able to
take as much time
to prepare for this
as I had hoped.
It sounds like Howlingstar and
the others are in trouble
so we've got no choice but to
move out as soon as possible.
Okay. When?
We'll leave tomorrow
at daybreak.
She's leaving tomorrow?
Itsuki Habaragi and Otohime
are now secured on Tartarus.
I'm on my way back to base.
Excellent work.
Here I was losing
sleep over how to dispose
of you once Thanatos
has been destroyed.
What a convenient tool
you'll turn out to be,
not to mention
you'll die on your own
without any help from me.
[monitor beeping]
Commander.
The anti-Thanatos
factor we injected into
Howlingstar and Amadeus
has been eradicated.
What happened to it?
The only thing we can
figure is that anti-bodies
within the two of them worked
to destroy the disease.
Their macrophages displayed
a remarkable resistance
to the infection.
You're telling me it was the
result of an Immunoreaction?
Yes sir.
But we didn't observe any
measurable immune reaction
in samples from
the Album or the Raum.
Their dysplasia is proceeding
according to our expectations.
It seems the
anti-Thanatos factor
is only effective
in Original Dragons.
What do you think?
I agree sir.
I think that's
probably safe to assume.
However now that
we've lost the Raum,
unless we capture the Album or
the Atrum and test it on them,
we can't really say for sure.
We still need to
run further tests.
Commander?
I'll decide on this later.
Then for now I wait.
So this disease will only work
on Original Dragons huh?
[laughing]
Well isn't that just perfect.
I'm asking that you
return home at once.
So you want me to come home
and take over the family.
I always knew
this would happen.
That isn't it!
Please listen Sieglinde.
I want you safe so I'm
asking you to come home,
not as the head of a family.
But as your father.
Do you really
mean that?
[YONAMINE] It's an
old story isn't it.
A girl who hates
her strict father,
but took to her
doting grandfather.
Ha.
I guess families
are all the same.
It really doesn't matter
if they're rich or poor.
For some reason,
I'm not entirely convinced
that Sieglinde
hates her father.
Yeah I think
you're right.
It's just that she
and her father
are both so unsure
of how to finally
patch things up between
the two of them.
Sometimes it's really tough.
It is tough,
but its worth it.
Let's get out of here.
Are we going to leave
Sieglinde behind?
Yeah.
But Jin.
I think Sieglinde should
stay right here at home
and live a happy life
with her father
[SIEGLINDE] bWhere do you
get off deciding that for me?
Stupid little man!
You don't wanna stay behind?
Are you saying the bond
between parent and child
is the most
precious thing of all?
You of all people
ought to know
there are a few things,
that are even more important!
And don't you
dare try to tell me
that deep down you
don't believe that too!
You listen to me.
I belong with the Dragonauts!
I'm coming with you
to get Amadeus.
I'm glad you said that.
Welcome!
I'd like one ShinOgasawara
sandwich, to go.
I'll have 12 of
the Dragon Burgers.
Wha?
You're gonna eat that many?
Why yes, yes I am.
I'm terribly sorry,
we discontinued the
Dragon Burger last week.
Hmm.
Ah, well then, one
preview please.
Right!
Next time, there's gonna be a
desperate rescue mission!
Dang!
I forgot my wallet!