Gio, what do you
think you're doing?
Give me a hand.
Here.
Yeah, okay.
Just stretch the
sheets out like this
to get rid of any
wrinkles from the wash.
Give it a try.
Sure.
Like this?
No, Gio!
You're just ripping it apart!
I'm sorry.
Aw.
Maybe laundry's
the wrong job for you, Gio.
[JIN and TOA laughing]
Jin.
Toa.
I know what I am now.
And I know what
I am supposed to do.
It's so cold.
I'm sorry, Sigelinde.
But I...
I'm going to die soon.
It's not fair.
None of this is fair, Toa.
Toa.
Idiot.
May I offer any
assistance, Young Miss?
--I'm fine.
--You're rubbing your eyes.
The sun is just too
bright for my eyes today.
I was about to steep
us a fresh pot of tea.
Unless of course, you prefer
coffee instead this morning.
I don't care.
Tea is just fine.
Anyway, where are the others?
Have you seen them?
I just saw Itsuki and
Raina down at the beach.
[ITSUKI]
Thanatos' successor.
I wonder what exactly
that's supposed to mean.
[RAINA] Howlingstar and
the others don't know, either,
which makes this whole
thing extremely interesting.
I would say
that Gio could be
in direct contact
with Thanatos' mind,
but that's nothing more
than an educated guess.
Do you think that
could be why
Gio's attitude
changed so suddenly?
Perhaps.
I know he lived peacefully with
Jin and Toa for about a year.
I honestly can't
think of any other reason.
The man's probably
a whole different Gio
from the one we knew.
I'll bet by now
he has transformed
into the something
we don't know.
Something that
can execute
the will of Thanatos,
without debate.
It's almost like he's
an animal in the wild.
All caught up in the concept
of "survival of the fittest."
I don't think that's
exactly what's happened.
I'd say this is more a case
of thinning the herd.
That's a terrible
expression.
And it also implies
that your opinion
is that in order to maintain
the species it's only allowing
the most superior
specimens to remain alive.
Who can tell?
We know over a hundred times
more about that hermit crab
you're holding in your hand
than we do about Thanatos.
And the Dragons
aren't that much different.
All mankind ever thought
about was how to exploit them
and use them as weapons
against each other.
Not once did we
earnestly try to consider
who they might be or what
they want in the first place.
We assumed the role of master
from the start,
not knowing a single thing
about what they might be, so.
[SIEGLAND]
Hey, you two.
It's too early in the morning
for that much doom and gloom.
How about a cup of tea?
Kitajima, I need you to listen.
I'm afraid that there's
something I have to tell you.
[SIEGLAND]
We're all falling apart.
It might be little by little,
but it's there.
It's like something's missing,
like we lack something.
I guess that's it isn't it?
We're all just people
who feel a void in their lives
and we're doing whatever
we can to figure it out.
Always wishing
to become complete.
But going through
Resonance with the Dragons
fulfilled that wish somehow,
and then gave it form.
I'm sure that
makes Thanatos angry.
Its children have
been contaminated
by the selfishness of mankind.
Now Thanatos is
trying eliminate
any of those
who've been tainted.
[RAINA]
That's absurd.
This is a creature that
wanders between stars,
devouring worlds as it goes.
Do you think maybe
you're making its principles
of conduct a little
bit too human?
Hmm, you're probably right.
It could just be my imagination
over thinking things.
I just take it to the extent
that my tiny human brain
is able to consider.
I guess I can't
help myself sometimes.
Pardon me, Young Miss.
What is it?
There's someone coming,
over there.
Laura.
[LAURA yelling in pain]
[SECTION HEAD] As I expected, of
course, the anti-Thanatos factor
has established itself
in an active state
within the subject's
cellular structure.
[SECTION HEAD]
I believe if we introduce it
into Thanatos in this state, it
will produce the precise effect
that we've been
seeking, gentlemen.
So is it the
Raum, or what?
Yeah.
At least that's what the
scientists are telling everyone.
Then do we have any idea where
the Raum that Nozaki dumped is?
That was the Raum, too.
However, they said it
was a cast-off shell.
What do you mean?
I'm sure you're aware of this
part, but, as Communicators,
you keep your Dragon
bodies in hyperspace.
But after the Raum went through
Resonance with Commander Sakaki,
that particular hyperspace
connection was severed.
And we still don't have
the slightest idea why.
Is that sort of
thing even possible?
All of this has
to do with you guys.
Don't tell me you know nothing.
[LAURA screaming in pain]
Daddy please help me!
Are you actually
going to launch her
into Thanatos as
the Annihilator's warhead?
The Raum is an Original sent
here directly from Thanatos.
Now with the
anti-Thanatos factor
taking hold, it will work.
[KAZUKI chuckles]
This is it!
This'll end everything!
From Thanatos
to Jin... everything.
It will all be over.
Over!
I'm afraid to
say that the time
that I have left is
about to come to an end.
Yes, I know.
And there's something
I want you to see.
[KITAJIMA gasps]
What is that?
It's a harbinger of death.
It appears on all Dragons
whose lives are running out.
But I thought Dragons were so
much stronger than human beings!
We're not special,
we're just probes.
Probes?
There was the Album,
now there's the Raum,
and then of course, there's me.
Since the day that
Thanatos sent us to Earth,
we have been living lives
that were limited.
When we were created it
was with only a single purpose.
Just one.
We were to find the Dragons
that remained here
and then were to bring them
all the way back to Thanatos.
I don't want to say it,
but other than that
one thing, we're expendable.
You're not!
What an awful thing to say!
Please, I ask you not to
judge the actions of Thanatos
with your anthropocentric
values, Kitajima.
Oh, Professor.
Thanatos is a being that
transcends human understanding.
Its emotions and
will are on a plane so
different from humanity,
that the species itself may
never be able to comprehend it.
[YONAMINE]
Right.
So we're not grown
up enough to say
"Oh, whatever,"
accept it and move on."
I hate to tell you this but
humans aren't like Dragons.
Toa's life will be coming
to an end very soon.
Your life does not
have to end so soon.
As the successor to Thanatos,
I now have the
power to save you.
Toa!
What can I do?
Please, tell me, what can I do?
Toa.
I need both of you
to get up right now!
What's going on?
Commander Sakaki?
[RAINA] So you
knew it was the Raum
that had taken
the form of your daughter,
who has been
deceased for years now.
But you kept on hiding her.
You kept the whole thing
a secret from everyone,
and went on playing
the Dragonauts' commander
like nothing at all
was out of the ordinary.
You have to tell
me why you did this.
I mean, to have
the Raum close at hand,
taking the place
of your daughter,
I can certainly
understand the feelings.
No, that thing is not Laura!
She is a counterfeit,
created by my mind.
And I swear, I am not about
to let Laura be a Dragon!
That Dragon killed Laura
and stole her form.
I simply wasn't
going to stand for that.
I'm okay.
So you were plotting
revenge against Thanatos.
You were going to
use the Dragonauts
as your instrument
of annihilation.
The signal from
Deep Eye has been lost!
Ryoko, what's the cause?
Analyzing now.
But just before we were cut off,
we recorded a massive
energy emission from Thanatos.
This pattern I'm seeing,
it looks like a Doppler shift.
You mean, Thanatos
has moved its position?
Well, where is it right now?
I can't find it.
Reading the instruments,
it actually looks to be
over an hour since
Deep Eye stopped functioning.
So Thanatos just vanished?
This is just great.
What if it's
headed toward earth?
For crying out loud,
that terrible sound is
echoing right through my head.
Captain!
Ryoko, I want you to
connect us to the deep space
whole-sky scanning
system as soon as possible.
Confirm Thanatos' position!
Yes, sir.
Saki, I need you to patch us
through to ISDA headquarters
top level priority clearance.
I'll get right on that.
Megumi.
Sir!
I want a black coffee.
I want it hot, I want
it tall, and I want it now.
Huh?
Yes, sir.
[SIEGLINDE[ It was only
after Gio went out of control
and leveled Mars that you
reversed yourself.
And then you tried
to capture the Dragonauts.
You became fearful
of the Dragons,
of the power they possess.
As a Dragon Laura possesses
these abilities as well.ß
Worst of all, she does whatever
you tell her to do.
So you decided to have
the Exford Force
set up just for her.
She couldn't have
been a more perfect tool
for hunting the
bunch of you down.
What a tiny, littlÎe man.
Right now,
the ISDA is implanting
an anti-Thanatos
factor in her body.
When they're finished with that,
their plan is to stuff her
inside a missile warhead.
It's kind of ironic
isn't it?
The one thing that
can defeat Thanatos
has been right next to me
this entire time
and I never had a clue.
Are you saying that
Laura knew all of this,
everything you've done,
and she was letting
herself be used?
That's right.
I don't want you
to worry too much.
Everything'll be just fine.
We're not alone.
You see our pain connects us.
She was absolutely desperate
to be of some use to you.
Any at all.
Look, I already told you,
she was merely a tool.
Don't you understand yet?
You lost your family
in that accident.
Surely you see.
Are you finally happy now?
What?
You're making the Dragon
that killed your daughter
suffer while it carries out
your revenge against Thanatos.
Isn't that what
you've always been after?
Absolutely, what else
is there for me anymore?
In that case.
In that case,
why do you sit
there looking so
bitter and lost?
When I found Toa, I finally felt
the sense that I had been saved,
which is exactly how you should
have felt when you found Laura.
Don't be such an idiot!
You don't know.
Run, Dad!
You need to get
away from here daddy.
I did try.
It was true for us, too,
Commander.
Howlingstar is my only partner.
Otohime is like another me.
Amadeus is a dear family member.
We want someone to turn to us.
We want to be needed.
Nobody can stand being alone.
In the end isn't that
what Resonance is all about?
It's Gio.
Dragon chosen to
be the successor.
Have you come here
to follow your destiny
and consign everyone
else to oblivion?
Its destiny?
Yes.
It's a trial, given to the one
who would succeed Thanatos.
Herd-thinning?
Yeah, that's pretty narrow
thinking, considering
his presence. Professor!
You alright?
Gio's power has
increased dramatically.
Thanatos has shared some of
its power directly with him.
Both of you, get out of here.
Gio is only after the eggs.
There's no reason for you to get
caught in the middle of this.
We can't.
Yeah, there's no chance
we'll make it, Professor.
What was that?
Stop it, Gio! Now!
Let's go!
Actualize!
I'm coming for you Jin!
It's not working!
I can't believe this is the
power of Thanatos' successor.
Gio!
Gio, listen, you have
to stop this, already!
There's no reason why
any of us have to fight!
We can figure
out something else!
Yeah, like you fighting me!
Jin!
Kazuki, wait!
You can't think that this is
the right time
for me to fight you!
Take him down.
If it weren't for you
this wouldn't be happening!
Toa!
Toa, get up! Toa!
If you hadn't gone through
Resonance with Jin.
Then Kazuki would
not have had to suffer.
Stop it!
Out of my way.
Jin!
Toa!
I want you to stand
there and watch
while I destroy all of them.
No, stop!
All those who
have hurt Kazuki.
Gio.
Look.
What is that?
I'm detecting an unusual
mass in the Moon's orbit!
Yeah, but what is it?
We're too late.
Is that Thanatos?
It couldn't be.
Not this suddenly.
It's finally come, has it?
Thanatos is here.
Jin, give Toa to me.
You must trust me;
it is the only way
that she can be saved.
Gio.
This is a bulletin from ISDA.
As a result of the huge blow
to specialty
industries caused
by the large-scale
destruction in Akihabara,
it is doubtful that
a certain upcoming manga
festival will be held.
What?
Then, no one will
read my manuscript.
Huh?
What manuscript?
Never, mind, it's nothing.
I guess I won't
go the second day.
What second day?
Next time, I'll just go to
the amusement park instead!
Ah, you tricked us!