Here they come.
[roars]
Hold on tight.
[tires screaching]
This is bad.
[TROOPER A] It's no use.
We'll never catch them.
I don't care what you
do but bring them back.
Now, bring them down.
[AMADEUS groans in pain]
That thing. Who is it?
That leaves Sieglinde Baumgard.
She has not been
located yet sir.
We'll keep looking for her.
That's not necessary.
What?
I said you can call
off your search.
We're done here.
Sir.
Your mission is over.
Return to the base.
Wait there for
further instructions.
[TOA] Okay, thank you
for waiting.
Here's your daily
lunch special, green beans,
and your soup and
sandwich combo, no mayo.
And the Alfredo pasta.
Please, enjoy your meal.
I'm beat.
Me too. Are you
going home Toa?
Mmhmm. Had the early shift.
Hey, is your man
picking you up?
It's so romantic.
I wouldn't say that, yet.
If it makes you that embarrassed
then, it definitely is love!
Well, Toa, give your
lovely man our best.
Bye.
Lovely man.
I guess it does kind of
look like that. Maybe.
Hi Jin!
Toa, you're right on time.
--Hold on tight.
--'kay!
I'll bet he's planning some
absolutely unforgettable way
of asking her to marry him.
You know that's not really
what guys think about.
[bell rings]
Back to work, right?
Okay fine.
Where'd they all come from?
He's gone.
The repairs appear to be
proceeding smoothly.
Between rebuilding the
installation and compensation
for those residents
who were displaced,
the Gillard's finances
for the next ten years
are more than a
little complicated.
They'll need to
be monitored closely.
Prince Asim
has been removed.
In the long run, I'd say
it's small price to pay.
Don't you think?
Yes, I suppose.
Although if I could
I'd go back in time
and make sure Prince Asim never
existed in the first place.
That's heartless sir.
There are any number of people
to take the prince's place.
It's not the sentiment between
father and son that's important.
It's how they'll succeed
me and claim their power.
One must think ahead in
matters of business.
Or there is no way for
your endeavors to thrive.
That goes for you too
doesn't it Sakaki.
We are not pursuing
Dragons for profit.
Our reasons are
different from yours.
Oh, is that right?
You are hunting down those who
were once your colleagues.
If you ask me,
I think it is you
who have no heart
in this matter.
Please put me down.
If I can just get
a little bit of rest
I'll be able to
heal soon enough.
That's just not possible.
We don't have time to rest.
Aw man, you sure are
a tough Dragon tamer.
[guns cock]
Former Captain Raina,
I'm not very good at
capturing people alive.
Next time I'll
have to kill you.
So please, stop running
away from me would you?
Kazuki.
I'm going to
make you really sad
you missed your
chance to kill me.
Easy, Howlingstar.
Considering the circumstances,
I think you should
be more patient.
I miss that about you, Raina.
You were always such
a wise captain.
And now, we all must
go to Tarturus.
The world was made quite aware
of the power of the Dragons
after they witnessed
the tragedy on Mars.
The Dragons are
extremely dangerous.
That's right.
But this project is new.
Fighting fire with fire, huh?
Thanatos and Dragons.
The world sees them both as
the same uncontrollable blaze.
But where would the world be
if it had never harnessed
the power of fire?
I think it would be good
if the ISDA and the Gillard
Army continued to cooperate
as business partners
from here on out.
Just business right?
We've received the scheduled
observation data from Deep Eye.
Acknowledged,
beginning analysis.
No changes in
Thanatos' orbital path.
It has left Pluto's orbit,
and is currently
proceeding toward Saturn.
Thanatos is
in its Heaven,
and so all's right
with the world, oh yeah.
Megumi, verify the data
link with headquarters.
Everything seems
to be working fine.
Ryoko, how's yours?
Who cares?
The captain's gone.
He won't leave his room.
We can't ask for orders
on everything or nothing
will get done.
It's supposed to be
a promotion for him
but in reality it's
a pretty big step back.
I can understand
why he'd want
to shut his brain
off a little bit.
We're caught in the middle
and forced to live in space.
I wish I could curl
up with a bottle.
Then again, it makes
me look so perky!
I love zero G.
Oh, yeah. Zero G.
Hooray.
[GIO growls in frustration]
Oh yeah. That tastes perfect!
[HOWLINGSTAR]
So, this Tartarus place.
It's is a sophisticated
installation for ISDA, right?
It's formal designation is
Disposal and Trial Island No. 2.
It's a Dragon graveyard.
So it's a Class A
garbage dump then, huh?
Amadeus.
They managed to capture you too?
I am so very
happy to see
that you made it
through all right, Raina.
And you too, Howlingstar.
It's almost like you meant that.
And what happened
to Sieglinde?
Do you know
where she is?
I believe she's safe.
I gave myself up as a decoy,
so she would be able to escape.
I see.
Well, as long as
she's alive, I guess.
[HOWLINGSTAR coughing]
It's like a four star hotel.
I'm back.
I managed to hack into
the ISDA network.
Thanatos's movement
remains unchanged.
It's headed for
Earth, all right.
Yes, so it would seem.
Do you still believe that
Dragons and humans can co-exist?
Even after all
that's happened.
Can they still live
together in peace?
I'm trying my best
to remain optimistic.
That's why I rescued
them from ISDA.
I can't say I don't
understand why
Sakaki wanted to get
rid of them all.
In light of the tragedy on Mars.
I hate to think
about the time bomb
waiting to go off inside me.
One can never be sure.
Professor that
will never happen.
Exactly what is it that Thanatos
is planning to do to us?
I don't know.
Thanatos' thoughts don't come
through at all anymore.
There's not much time left.
I can feel it.
[JIN] Well, that takes
care of the shopping.
So, do you want to go
anywhere else today?
I just heard about a new place
from the girls at work.
It's supposed to be
a great little bakery
that opened last week.
The croissants they have
there are to die for.
I love croissants.
Wanna take a look?
Yeah, let's check it out.
Hey Mom, look at that!
It's the first star!
That's not a star. It's Mars.
Mars?
Yes.
A year ago, there was
a terrible Dragon,
who ran wild and
destroyed the planet.
That's why Mars
burns bright red now
and you can see
it during the day.
Are Dragons bad?
Yes, they're very bad and scary.
Toa...
Thanatos continues to follow
its course towards Earth
and based on
recent observations
ISDA estimates that
we have seven years.
Thanatos will then be
in proximity to earth.
And now for the
financial update.
Gio, we're home!
Dinner will be ready
in a few minutes.
Tonight, we're going
have noodles and a soup.
Aw, if you could have
waited a little bit longer,
I would have
helped you out.
No thank you.
Why not?
You can't cook. I'm sorry.
You mistook
the boiling potpourri
for after dinner tea
and served it to all of us.
Just imagine what you
could do to our food.
Toa it's okay, it tasted great.
That's so sweet.
But someday I'll have
to learn how to--
Sieglinde?
Who cooked this stuff?
I'll bet you it was, Gio.
That's correct.
Way too much seasoning.
I can't taste anything
besides salt.
Is that bad?
Why're you here?
Oh please!
Why would a Dragon need glasses?
Is it a disguise?
That's pathetic.
I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
It's all the dust in here.
Gesundheit.
After covering up your
whereabouts on Mars,
I wondered what you
guys were up to.
It's sad.
I never would have thought you'd
be here playing house like this.
You disappoint me.
We haven't just
"played house."
[knocking on door]
Such a lovely reunion.
Yonamine.
Yeah. How's it going?
Kazuki.
I will grant your wish.
I will kill Jin for you.
Well, what else?
Looks like the three of you
are doing pretty
well for yourselves.
Um, Yonamine...
Have you been watching
over us this entire time?
Yeah for the most part.
You all should be ashamed.
Living up here like
there's nothing wrong with it.
Some hippie commune.
All alone.
What have you been doing anyway?
Nothing unusual.
Each one of us is
holding down a job.
And we take turns cooking for
each other in the evenings.
This time together has
been like a dream.
Hmm. Like a dream.
Must be nice!
Wake up, Jin Kamishina!
You drag everyone around you
into chaos and at the end.
You retire out to
the countryside
and live out your
little fantasy life!
That's what you call a dream?
You've got to be kidding me!
Your dream had a price,
Akira and Machina.
[RESEARCHER] Agathions
number 01 through number 07
show no irregularities.
Moving on to reconstruction of
their remote control units.
What've I done? I'm a fool.
What's wrong daddy?
The ISDA, they want to kill
off all remaining Dragons.
[EVERYONE gasps]
We rebelled against them,
and tried to run away
with our Dragons.
But Raina and Howlingstar
have been caught.
And Amadeus gave
himself up to save me.
Commander Sakaki is planning
to exterminate
everyone still alive.
But if they do that,
Thanatos might become angry,
and destroy this entire planet.
He's planning to kill Thanatos.
That's Sakaki's
only logical endgame.
But as endgames go,
it's less than satisfying.
Thanatos isn't even
the least bit interested
in the people here on Earth.
Once it has retrieved
the Dragons,
Thanatos will simply leave
this solar system quietly.
Then Earth is
nothing more than
a convenient place
for spawning dragons.
Of course, that's not going to
convince the rest of the world.
Look at you.
You've become
quite the little human
over this last year,
haven't you?
If this were a
three ring circus,
I think that would
make you the clown.
You may be right.
I think so too, sometimes.
Now what?
What do you want to do?
You can't just cling
to them forever
like a turd hanging
off a goldfish, right?
What's so great about Jin?
Why do you waste your life
hanging out here with him?
I just love him.
Isn't that enough?
But you wouldn't
feel that way at all
if you hadn't gone
through a resonance with Jin.
It's not something
you chose on your own.
Something that
I chose on my own?
Jin, I need you to
bring me a bath towel!
It better be clean and
fluffy, preferably blue.
What?
Why should I get you anything?
You've been nothing but
a little snot towards me!
Look twerp!
Amadeus would've had it ready
for me without a word.
I'm not Amadeus.
I'll just leave it here!
Wait, Jin!
Jin, the water's
getting cold!
Don't be so stingy with
the heat out there!
Boy, you certainly are a little
princess, aren't you.
Toa.
Jin. Let's talk.
You don't have
to say anything.
Jin.
I've enjoyed every moment.
Yes.
I'll hold on to this
moment forever.
Clown, huh? Right.
Thanatos.
We've worked this
whole year through.
I wish we got bonuses.
I know a bonus would be nice.
Hey, doesn't it still feel like
it's only been one week?
My pay went up $100 per hour!
You're working here part-time?
Huh?
Aren't you getting
paid in space food?
Free food?
Oh, right, they said if we do
the preview, we'd get a bonus.
On the next Dragonaut,
father-daughter discord!
Hey, stop fighting for it!