You're saying our forces
should infiltrate
the ISDA's military division?
Yes sir, I believe such
a strategy would demonstrate
to the entire world
the true power of the Gillard.
Well in that case,
we should begin to move forward
with this
operation immediately.
Very well your majesty.
Of course we'll need
someone to head it up.
I think that Prince Rasina would
be well-suited to the task.
Yes, I believe you're right.
[LADY ATTENDANT]
Something terrible has happened!
Prince Rasina
has been murdered!
Now Gio!
For the record, you owe
me big-time for that one.
And I intend to
pay you back in full.
Those guys just keep coming!
Don't worry Toa,
I'm coming to save you.
I don't care what obstacles
those bastards put in my way.
[OPERATOR] The second wave
has been completely wiped out.
The third wave is
moving in to engage the enemy.
On my mark dispatch
the Agathion squadron!
I'm sure there's
no need for all that.
Your Majesty,
we have to act immediately!
If we don't destroy
the Dragonauts now,
nothing will stop
them from coming here
to take back the Album!
Perhaps we should
simply invite them in.
Don't you think that idea
sounds far more entertaining?
Your Highness, this may
be our only opportunity to--
That's an order, Major.
As you wish.
[HOWLINGSTAR making
martial arts noises]
Hey. What gives huh?
Here I thought we were finally
making a charge at Thanatos
and now we're taking a break?
That doesn't
seem right does it?
We'll leave soon enough.
Take it easy, Howlingstar.
Why can't we go right now?
I've really got the itch
to fight in a good battle.
That's just what
I'm counting on.
Yeah!
[SIEGLINDE]
Hey.
How much longer do think
we'll be here on the moon?
We'll be here as
long as it takes
to complete the Avenir's final
inspection and load the Type-X.
Oh.
As a result of
the Ostrum's attack,
the threat posed by Thanatos
has suddenly become much more
tangible to the general public.
All the major highways
are completely
gridlocked with people
trying to reach the spaceport
so they can leave Earth.
And we've received
multiple reports of rioting.
Was there really nothing
that could've been done
about the destruction
of Shinogasawara City
by just one of
the Original Dragons?
You should know
that many are holding
the ISDA
responsible for this.
Now then Mr. Kiril.
How do you explain your
agency's failure in this matter?
Hold on a minute,
my agencies shortcomings?
If the Gillard Force
hadn't ignored our request
for assistance
this whole ordeal--
Are you saying we're responsible
for the city's destruction?
Are you saying that you aren't?
You'd blame someone else for the
consequences of your actions.
That is among the
most dishonorable things
a man can do.
You and your brainless
cronies allowed this to happen!
How dare you let us
take the fall for it!
Are you so blind
that you can't see
how much we have to tolerate
from the Gillard Army!
Mister Kiril watch your temper!
Keep in mind that
you are addressing
the sovereign of a nation.
Infighting among D Project
members is also to blame.
That being said, it's
important to maintain unity
both between and
within our organizations.
An excellent point.
On our end, the conflict
with ISDA was the result
of Asim and his officers
acting on their own.
We're having
trouble controlling him.
You can't control Prince Asim?
But doesn't he command
your entire military branch?
He most certainly does not.
I can assure you
that authority on all matters
ultimately rests with me.
I promise you that
from this moment on
the Gillard army
will support the ISDA
with every resource available.
Sure.
It isn't just us.
They've been divided as well.
How are you feeling
today, my dear?
The look in your eyes
is as precious as ever.
So full of sorrow.
From what I can tell
the ISDA is about to launch
an attack on your kind.
This'll be good.
An attack?
You can't let them go!
If they attack Thanatos,
there will be no turning back!
Please!
Let me out of here
so I can stop this!
Not a chance.
Why would I
release my property?
If I don't do something
Earth is going to be wiped out!
Wouldn't that
be entertaining?
It's not every day
that you get front row seats
to watch the death
of an entire planet.
Entertaining?
Earth is your home
world, isn't it?
How can you be so
callous about this?
Let's talk about you.
Why are you so
worried about earth?
You're a Dragon after all.
Well...
I couldn't care less
if humanity lives or dies,
so it makes absolutely
no difference to me
if the earth is destroyed.
What?
Human beings are only capable
of thinking of themselves,
mankind is nothing more
than a group of
loathsome, foolish apes.
How can you say
something like that?
Aren't you a human being?
Yes, very observant of you;
but I am a chosen human.
A being that stands alone at
the very peak of all humanity.
All life everywhere
is completely equal.
There are no lives of
greater or lesser importance.
And in my heart of hearts
I know that humans
aren't the foolish,
self-centered creatures
you think that they are.
Wow.
A Dragon,
speaking up for humans.
It's true that
sometimes people
let their worst
instincts dominate them,
but that doesn't mean
that all humans are all bad.
I have felt, in
the depths of my soul,
the pure love that
humans are capable of!
Love, huh?
Even in the most
difficult situations,
when they must protect
someone they care for,
they'll sacrifice themselves
without hesitation.
Love can redeem them.
And sometimes it gives
rise to unimaginable power.
Of course.
But it also drives good
people to do bad things.
Therefore even love is
tainted by man's ugly nature.
It does have an ugly side.
But it has beauty too.
Love must have both sides.
It's all a part of what
it means to be a human.
Sometimes it gives
rise to great power?
When you said that
you weren't talking
about Jin Kamishina
by any chance?
How do you know about Jin?
I'm gonna let you
in on a little secret.
He will be here very soon.
No, that's impossible.
There's no way that
Jin could know I'm here.
Your Highness.
The boy is almost here.
Are you ready?
Everything is in place.
Looks like he'll
be landing shortly.
Jin is actually coming here?
You told me that love
gives rise to great power.
Well I think that now
would be a perfect opportunity
to prove that
to your prince.
I'm picking up a guidance
signal coming from Mars.
This feels like some
sort of Gillard trap.
Yeah, that's exactly
what it feels like.
Whadaya think?
Should we turn around.
We're going in.
There's no way I'm turning back.
I was hopin' you'd say that.
Man! I'm so bored.
How long are we
gonna sit around like this?
I want to attack!
Howlingstar,
you've got to be patient.
But I'm starting to soften up.
I wonder.
Are those two
safely together yet?
Targets will be in
firing range momentarily.
They don't stand a chance.
They'll be space
dust after this.
The targets are now
within firing range.
Fire!
I guess they must've heard
about how much I like fireworks!
All right Gio.
Let's go!
Blocks 3 and 4
have been disabled!
Blocks 7 and 8 have
been disabled as well!
I want the Agathions sent now.
Jin! Incoming!
We're going
through them, alright?
Akira! That's how
we're doing this!
Alright!
Don't let them near the dome!
[alarm beeping]
Akira!
We'll be fine! Just go!
I know you will.
That's right.
Just keep going, Jin!
Guess it's now or never Machina.
Bravo, I'm impressed.
[TOA] Gio...
[ASIM smirks]
Activating emergency bulwarks!
The main lobby is damaged
and we've spotted two intruders!
Toa! I need your help now!
You've got to tell
me where you are!
I'm here!
Oh, I don't believe I've
ever seen that expression.
I must say. That is fascinating.
I can't wait to see what kind
of expression you show me next.
I wait with bated breath.
[GIO screams in agony]
CSS!
Gio!
[ASIM laughs evily]
Well hello there,
and welcome to my castle.
My name is Asim.
I'm the one in
charge around here.
Where is Toa?
The captive princess is
at the tippy-top of the tower.
If you want her back
you have no choice
but to come up here
and get her.
I sincerely hope
you make it in one piece.
[ASIM laughs maniacally]
[GIO roars]
Gio! Are you okay?
Yeah, I think I'll be alright.
[JIN gasping for breath]
Jin!
Oh. Look at that oaf.
Can't you see
how foolish he looks?
No Asim. You're the fool.
[TOA] You think
you're above it all,
yet you take pleasure
in causing people
pain and suffering?
You are the most
despicable creature of all.
[ASIM] Aw. You can make an
angry face too. How beautiful.
[GIO] Go on Jin!
Toa!
[JIN yelling]
Jin no!
[GIO]
Get out of our way!
Gio!
You, caught me.
Hang on.
Please! Make this stop!
When it comes
to Jin Kamishina,
you really do show a wide
variety of expressions!
Almost as though
you were a person.
Toa!
Jin!
I'm impressed
you made it this far.
The power of love.
Apparently it's not
completely untrue.
I want you to let
her out, right now!
Let her out yourself.
Jin!
You coward!
Stay away from His Majesty!
Outta my way!
Toa.
The power of true love
doesn't seem very powerful.
Asim! Please stop!
That's more like it.
Jin!
Isn't this just incredible?
Who could have possibly guessed
that the power of your love
would keep me so
thoroughly entertained?
Oh goodness.
It appears the brave lover
has lost consciousness.
Let her go.
Let her go right now.
Filthy dog.
Stop it now!
That isn't possible!
How is she breaking
reinforced glass in a CSS field?
Hang on I'm coming your Majesty!
Toa.
Jin.
You're here.
I had to come for you.
Thank you, Jin.
You did it.
[ASIM laughing]
The power of love, huh?
Fascinating. Truly fascinating!
Ryoko here.
Have you guys ever
found a stray kitten?
'Cause I just
found one myself.
Saki here.
I just found a stray puppy!
Oh yeah?
Both of you are such pushovers,
I found this guy.
Whoa, is that a giant crocodile?
Megumi, where did you find it?
He chased me here! Help!
Gah! Don't come over here!
Wait!
Do the preview
before you run away!
Huh?
Next time, who'd
have thought that such a thing
would be in such a place?
Run!