Begin.
Yes ma'am.
Commencing Resonance.
[yelling in pain]
Abnormality detected!
We've gone too far to stop it!
[yelling in pain]
Why is it that those
imbeciles at ISDA
can repeatedly
do what we cannot?
Why?
♪ opening song ♪
So this is where Toa is?
Yeah.
[Toa singing to Jin]
There's no doubt about it.
Toa's definitely here.
[kids laughing]
--Me next!
--Over here!
[remote control toy crashes]
Aww!
You forgot to recharge
it again didn't you?
Shut up jerk!
It doesn't matter now.
It's raining cats and dogs.
C'mon, let's go home.
You'll catch cold like that.
What is it?
The song it stopped.
So, you can't hear it.
Toa!
It doesn't look like she's here.
No she has to be here somewhere!
I know Toa's song was
coming from this exact spot!
And just how can you
be so certain about that?
It's just... well...
All I can tell you...
is that can I feel it.
Gio!
I meant what I said Jin.
I told you that if we
don't find Toa on the moon.
I'd leave you behind
to search for her on my own.
Wait a minute Gio!
Listen, I can feel it!
She was definitely here.
Please wait!
Quiet down!
I understand you'll have
questions about the events
that occurred yesterday
near Shinogasawara;
I intend to answer them
to the best of my ability.
But in order to understand
last night's events
there is something else
we must discuss first.
Does everyone
recall the appearance
of Thanatos at the edge
of our solar system?
What does that have to do
with what's happening now?
Yeah! Don't change the subject!
We want to know about
those monsters yesterday!
Thanatos isn't some
harmless drifting asteroid!
It's an extra-terrestrial
life form!
The first two giant creatures
that appeared yesterday
on the Shinogasawara bridge
are also extra-terrestrial
life forms.
In fact Thanatos
is their origin.
We call them Dragons.
The Dragons that
subsequently appeared
and battled the first
two are earth-born Dragons.
These were created by ISDA
to resist the eminent threat
of Thanatos coming to earth.
Now are there any questions?
Earth-born Dragons?
You're going to have
to tell us more than that.
Are you telling us that you've
been raising these
monsters in secret?
They are much more
than just monsters.
These creatures are Dragons!
It's critical that we
be proactive in our defense.
These earth-born Dragons
can destroy Thanatos!
Defending Earth is
the purpose of the D Project
and the true mission
of the Dragonauts!
But you told us the Dragonauts
were just the next
generation of astronauts!
You've been lying
to us this whole time!
Do you believe
this no good liar?
Thanatos is directly
threatening the Earth!
The only hope our planet
has to eliminate
this menace is the D Project!
You sure are getting worked up.
Calm down.
Jin Kamishina's ID has been
used in the city on the moon.
We'll find him
and his accomplices there.
Yes I'm on it sir,
I have already landed
and I expect to
retrieve the boy soon.
You are as quick
as ever aren't you?
Not as quick as you sir.
Mister Kiril.
I can't help but wonder
if holding a press conference
so soon was a wise decision.
I can assure you
that's what any reasonable
person would have done.
[laughing maniacally]
Am I to understand that
the capture and return
of the rogue Dragon is
now my responsibility?
Indeed.
I'm afraid ISDA
has too many irons
in the fire to deal
with this situation.
However...
I want to be perfectly clear
that he is to be returned to
us as soon as you catch him.
Roger that.
From this point on, The Gillard
Army is under contract
to capture the Dragon, Gio,
and return him to ISDA.
I'm sure it goes without saying
that all of this is
to remain secret, Major.
It's not going to be that easy.
Another low-grade counterfeit.
I can't believe I still
have to use garbage like this.
Since the press conference,
the truth about the D Project
is out in the open.
Now that we're
declassified those in charge
have decided to speed
up project development.
That means the Lindworm Unit
will be working harder than ever
for the early implementation
of the D Project's
ultimate objective.
Also, the task of
retrieving our lost Dragon Gio
has been assigned
to the Gillard Army.
I don't understand why
they're being brought in.
They don't have
anything to do with us.
Yeah Raina.
This is our problem.
We should be taking
care of this ourselves!
These orders are
not up for debate.
Is that clear?
Hey, d'you mind
if I sit with you?
I heard that you
and Jin Kamishina
were childhood friends.
You know Jin said something
to me before he left.
I have to go and find her,
I've got to learn the truth.
Toa's the only one who knows.
That's what he
told me right before
he and Gio left
earth for the moon.
The Album has got
to be on the moon.
You go on ahead.
Yes ma'am.
C'mon. Let's get going.
I don't understand why,
but it seems like Gio
needed to see the Album also.
What I'm trying to
say is that I don't think
Gio left because
he doesn't like you.
So he went to the moon
to see the Album?
Yeah.
So there's no
reason to be upset.
'Kay?
I need to know exactly
what happened with Jin.
Tell me everything you know
about the Album
being on the moon.
Toa is definitely
somewhere here on the moon.
I know.
I can feel it.
You don't have the right.
Who do you think you are?
Where are you
planning on taking me?
Silence!
The Gillard Army.
Line secured.
Good. Go ahead.
Here.
Go on, drink it.
It'll warm you up.
Oh great. Stupid TV.
This message is for
the Communicator, Gio.
We are broadcasting
at a special frequency
only you Dragons can hear.
You should know that we now
have Jin Kamishina in custody.
If you want him released,
then surrender to our
forces immediately.
I repeat.
We now have
Jin Kamishina in custody.
Jin!
Hey, is everything alright?
The city's southwest mining site
will be the location
for the exchange.
That is all.
CSS emission
carriage is on station.
The transmitter for the CSS
signal anchor has been set.
Very good.
Now all we have to do is wait.
Is there anything I can
get for you young man?
Don't play coy.
You're the Gillard Army right?
What do you expect
to get from all this?
If you must know,
you're going to be the bait.
With your help we're going
to catch a very big fish.
I can see what you're doing.
But it won't
make any difference.
Gio won't come.
He left me behind
and he's not coming back.
You're saying a Communicator
abandoned his Master?
You almost had me.
We know the Resonance
between a Master and
a Communicator is absolute.
Not that crap again.
What is this "Resonance"?
Look! I told you don't--
Stop lying to me!
I've had just about
enough of this. Now talk!
Uh-huh!
It's true! I swear!
Yeah? Are you kidding?
Nope! It's totally true!
Sorry.
Toa.
Has the Lintverm
Unit's punishment
for the Spirytus incident at
Shinogasawara been decided yet?
No not yet.
It was determined
that any punishment
would only
hinder the D Project.
I have to admit I'm quite
relieved to hear that.
Is that all you've
come here to discuss?
I heard that the Album
is most likely on the moon.
You could give the order
and dispatch
the Dragonauts immediately.
I've already told you,
from this point on
the Dragonauts' only mission
is to move forward
with the D Project.
What's the matter with you?
Do you want to catch the culprit
of the shuttle accident or not?
Of course, Gio will be
brought to the military
research facility
immediately after capture.
We will however need you to
clean up the mess with ISDA.
It is critical that we
get a live communicator.
All we need to do is crack
the Resonance formula.
Once we do that,
then the ISDA will finally.
Target sighted!
Gio is approaching the site!
Here we go.
Gio.
Well now it would seem to me
that he hasn't
abandoned you just yet.
But why?
Why come back?
That's it, come.
Target has entered the airlock.
He'll reach the trap point
in approximately 19 seconds.
Come on. Yes That's good.
Nine seconds
until trap is engaged.
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0.
Turns out if we flood your body
with CSS you can't actualize.
Isn't that just
the darnedest thing?
Men seize the Communicator!
I see you can
still move well enough.
Although I have to say it seems
like you're slowing down a bit!
No, I can't move properly.
Amazing.
Gio.
Settle down, Communicator.
No.
Oh man, that was close one.
How can you still fight back
after we raised the CSS levels?
His physical
abilities are so advanced
compared to those of
a normal Communicator.
You maggot!
The CSS! It's hit!
What?
You'll pay for that!
Gio!
Let's go, Jin.
Deploy the Agathion!
[alarm wailing]
Agathion, ready for deployment!
A Dragon?
Ready? Here he comes!
Gio!
Mayday! I've lost control!
Mayday!
The shock has severed my
connection to the Agathion!
[dragon roars]
Without a pilot,
that Dragon is out of control.
There's no way a counterfeit
Dragon could defeat him.
No matter.
I will get my hands
on the Resonance formula.
What's the matter with you?
Do you want to catch the culprit
of the shuttle accident or not?
Why did you come back for me?
I thought you said you were
going to leave me behind.
What I said was that
if Toa wasn't on the moon
I wouldn't hesitate
to leave you behind.
However.
If she was in fact on the moon.
I said we'd find her together.
Ah!
♪ closing song ♪
Working behind
the scenes is tiring!
We're always in
the command center huh?
Doesn't the command
center seem cold to you?
I'll bet the Commander thinks
it's super stuffy in there.
That guy's as serious
as heart attack huh?
Stop that! It's so rude!
It's okay, everything's fine.
Nobody's listening to us.
No, the mic looks
like it's turned on.
Eh? Um. Um.
Next time!
After missing each other
for so long the two finally.
Uh, I don't think you're
gonna smooth this one over.