On the 9th of this month,
ISDA Flight 029
took off from Sorajima
International Spaceport
and exploded in midair
shortly after takeoff.
48 passengers
and crew were killed.
Miraculously, there
was a single passenger,
Jin Kamishina,
who escaped with his life.
The government's investigation
recovered shuttle fragments,
which may prove
crucial in determining
the cause of the crash.
It's here. The Atrum.
♪ opening song ♪
Where am I?
This is goodbye, Jin.
Don't leave me come back!
Toa!
Is that?
Gio, let's go.
Gio.
Spirytus never said much,
but we got along well.
Makes no sense.
It's like he was
different somehow.
He was like a brother
and I killed him.
It's not your fault, Howl.
It was an order.
You only did what any one
of us would have done.
A Master's command
cannot be contradicted.
That is the way
it will always be
beginning the moment
Resonance takes place.
I could never give
the order to kill someone.
That's enough.
How did it end up
like this anyway?
Why would Spirytus
do all those things?
Was it because of Amagi?
The ISDA's investigation
is looking into that right now.
It's the only thing we can do.
Howlingstar, I'm so sorry.
Kamishina and the Dragon Gio.
We need to find
and capture the two of them
as soon as we possibly can.
Before matters become any worse.
Gio... why go with him?
Why Gio? Why'd you go?
Now, are you certain of this?
It's not me saying it.
See, like it or not, one of
the survivors came around.
I showed him a picture of
Spirytus and he said it was him.
Why would a Communicator
commit mass murder?
It shouldn't be.
How could this happen?
Continue your investigation.
Got it.
The Dragonauts are
spending all this time
searching for
Jin Kamishina and Gio.
I only wish they'd try
looking for the Album, as well.
Jin Kamishina is
the bait to catch her.
Whatever that's
worth at this point.
Have you heard
anything about Spirytus?
Mister Kiril believes the press
must not find out
anything about this.
He says the success of
the project depends on it.
Very well.
Then I guess there is only
one path left for us to choose.
There's no way we can go public
with the truth
about the D-project.
Telling mankind that we face
a crisis of
extraterrestrial proportions.
Would only serve to make
the populous more anxious.
After last night,
I'm not sure there's much more
we could do
to shake them up.
The government has to maintain
a certain level of
plausible deniability.
We cannot appear
to have sanctioned
this covert dragon project.
It's a little late for that.
Who knows how many
people have already
seen Dragonauts
riding their dragons.
There is no way
for us to deny it.
Yes, but...
Sakaki, why don't you
tell us what you think?
I'd like to hear your
thoughts on this matter.
If we need to
conceal his identity.
The perpetrator connected
to this string of murders.
If we're forced to keep
this incident secret.
Then I think it's time we
go public with the D Project.
I don't see what
choice we have.
I agree.
So nice clothes.
Humans wear this sort
of thing, don't they?
Gio, what are you to Toa?
I was born to be
the protector of Toa.
She needs protection?
Tell me what you are to Toa.
Me? Well...
What am I to Toa?
Wait, that singing.
It's Toa.
It's her, I'm certain.
Where? I don't hear anything.
I think she's singing to me.
The moon.
Toa's on the moon.
The moon?
What makes you think
she's on the moon?
I can hear her, singing.
You can?
Machina?
About what was said before.
I want you to know I'd never
tell you to kill anyone, either.
I just couldn't do it.
I know.
[gasps]
[tires squealing]
What the...?
Gio!
That's him?
Let go! Let me go!
Jin Kamishina and
the Communicator Gio, right?
That's right.
I was just using him.
You backstabber! Why?
I thought you wanted to see Toa!
Attention.
We've captured Jin Kamishina
and the Communicator, Gio.
Repeat, we've
captured Jin Kamishina
and the Communicator, Gio.
Gio!
Good for you, Kazuki.
That's one checked off the list.
So, you heard the voice
of the Album calling
and you claim you don't remember
much of anything after that?
Yes.
Take G-10 to
Dr. Kitajima immediately.
Here you go.
Don't be shy, drink up.
Tell me.
Why did you do
something so dumb?
So I could see Toa.
That's all there is to it.
Hey. What's the matter?
Keep walking!
Did you hear what he said?
I want to know what I am to Toa.
That's why I want to see her.
I need to find out.
She told me I wasn't alone.
[beeping]
Intruder in Area D3!
Bringing up surveillance
monitor imaging.
This isn't good,
what the hell is Gio up to now?
Oh no!
Don't tell me they've
been working together
from the very beginning!
Akira, what's wrong?
Machina, go! Stop Gio!
Right.
Damn, they got away.
Stop right there!
The moon?
What makes you think
she's on the moon?
I can hear her, singing.
You can?
Then why is it
I don't hear anything?
Toa is on the moon.
You have to trust me.
It's the truth.
Somehow I know it.
If Toa isn't on the moon,
then this is over,
and I will leave you behind.
Yeah, I figured that.
We must leave.
No, hold on a minute.
I can't just fly off into
space like this, alright.
We have to get something first.
[alarm beeping]
C'mon open up.
Yes.
Freeze!
I wouldn't do that,
Jin Kamishina.
No you don't.
Okay, now why don't
we try doing this again.
I have a few more
questions I'd like to ask you.
Please, let me go.
You're not even a master
so how did you ride a dragon?
How is it you
were able to ride Gio?
You haven't
undergone a resonance.
What are you talking about?
What does that even mean?
No good!
I'm not buying it. Talk!
Masters? Resonance? What?
I don't understand
what you're talking about?
I told you, don't play dumb!
I'm not playing dumb!
You're not making
any sense to me.
What is this place?
What is going on here!
I want to know right now!
So start talking!
Maybe he doesn't know anything.
But why is he with Gio, then?
I have to go and find her.
I've got to learn the truth.
Toa's the only one who knows.
No!
You're mine.
You have been through Resonance
with Kazuki.
Why are you refusing
to comply with his directives?
That's who I am!
I take orders from no one!
How is that possible?
Who knows?
You are very interesting.
But I'm not interested in you!
Machina!
[JIN] I have to go and find her.
I've got to learn the truth.
Toa's the only one who knows.
You don't have to go after him.
I want to see.
They might be able to change it.
Change?
The Dragon-human relationship.
I'm picking up G-10's
Actualization reading.
It's over the sea
near Shinogasawara.
Currently at Point Alpha-12,
rising at 2 kilometers
per second.
So that's Gio, huh?
G-10 is leaving
the stratosphere.
Radar signature fading.
G-10 lost.
Nowhere to hide.
You're going to the moon.
Prepare my transport ship.
I'm going after him.
That coward, he's taken my Gio.
I'll get him back, I swear!
Well, well, well...
if it isn't the Dragonaut
rookie without a dragon.
Are you sure you
can risk being here?
You never know when they
might order you to deploy.
Get off!
But that's kinda tough to
do without a dragon, right?
It's blue up there especially
the view of the earth.
You could say that
it changed my life.
There it is Earth.
♪ closing song ♪
Ready, set.
We're your ISDA operators,
Saki, Ryoko, Megumi.
The good part got all messed up!
Ryoko, you're one
who said we should all
say them together so
there wouldn't be any arguing.
Well, you agreed to it,
didn't you?
Don't argue about it.
Next time, we'll do it better.
Next time?
We have to do the preview!
Right!
Okay then, I'll do it!
Let's see.
Next time, all sorts
of people will attack!
Aw, I thought it was my turn!
How rude!