Why is it that
women lose the ability
to make a simple decision every
time they go out shopping?
Don't start.
The only reason I'm
here in the first place
is because you said
I should wear perfume.
Don't get technical.
We've been doing
this for three hours.
At this rate,
our entire date
will consist of me
watching you smell stuff.
Hey, I can't help it.
I've never had to
wear perfume before.
I don't even know which
one of these I should get.
Why don't you try this one?
Wow. That's great.
I know, right?
I think your boyfriend will
like this one too, Dr. Kitajima.
Wait. You're the...
Yup! My name is Nanami Hoshi
and I've been assigned
to be your graduate
student assistant, Doctor.
I'm really
looking forward to this.
What's going on?
I don't understand
why you're doing this?
Tell me why?
Shut your mouth.
This is Nanami, come in.
I've taken control
of their submarine.
We're right on schedule.
[GARNET] Very good. We'll
retrieve the Album shortly.
Roger.
That gun.
It's Gillard issue right?
We'll be taking
the Album along with us.
Nanami...
Tell me why.
This is stupid!
What reason did they give
for us to sit and do nothing?
I thought Akira and
Machina were our friends.
Take it easy, Sieglinde.
The commander says
he has some sort of plan.
We just have to
follow his orders.
I shouldn't have
said that you were the one
who gave me clearance but,
there was no other way.
I'm sorry.
Gio's too important for me
to give him up without a fight.
It seems only
the young are allowed
to get away with
behaving so foolishly.
You are off the hook for now.
But I am ordering you not
to act on your own again.
Yes, sir.
You have my word.
Of course, if you succeed well,
then no harm done.
The order stands.
We are to remain at
our current status. Understood?
[AKIRA]
Well? See anything?
[MACHINA] Yes.
The special forces unit
has sealed off the bridge.
But, I don't see Raina
and the others with them.
That means
they're just trying
to keep an eye on
us, nothing more.
But why?
Well...
If they really
meant to catch us,
Raina and the others
would be coming after us,
not just
the special forces.
That makes sense.
Well, there's no point
in us hanging around
here anymore, right?
I think I know
a place where we can go.
[JIN] Really?
Yep, it's just a big
old haunted house.
[JIN gasps]
It is?
[AKIRA laughing]
I'm only teasing.
When they built
up the new city
nobody wanted to stay
in this area anymore.
Now all these houses
are completely empty.
All right, the lights are on!
The water seems
to be running, too.
[AKIRA gasps]
Know what that means?
Ah, feels good.
[AKIRA sighs]
That was refreshing.
[JIN gasps in embarassment]
Sorry!
I forgot that you're a guy.
So, what should we do now?
There's no going back for me
and Machina, that's for sure.
[JIN] The only
thing I want is Toa.
There's nothing
else for me.
Yeah, I guess there's not
much else for you, is there?
There's one more thing.
Could you put
your panties back on?
Oh yeah, right, sorry.
Time to go, Doctor.
The Album!
Stupid girl.
This is Kitajima!
ISDA, please respond!
Is anyone there?
[KITAJIMA gasps]
It's no use.
Maybe there.
[OPERATOR A]
Detached from submarine.
[OPERATOR B] Agathion 1,
Agathion 2, all clear.
[GARNET] How is
the Album doing?
She's still sleeping.
I see.
Why did you decide to
let those people all live?
You didn't order
me to kill them.
[GARNET chuckles]
Next time I'll have to be sure
not to forget that part.
[OPERATOR A] Major,
we're ready to get underway.
Right, move out.
[OPERATOR A] Roger.
Now engaging the Chariot.
How long do you suppose they
are planning to isolate us here?
What's that?
[KITAJIMA panting]
I have to...
I have to contact
the base at once!
The Album.
What?
Here you are, Kazuki.
Where am I?
What do you mean
the Album has been taken?
Yes.
We just received an emergency
message from Dr. Kitajima.
Nanami Hoshi was a spy
for the Gillard Army.
There's more Commander.
Our radar has picked
up an unknown ship
taking off from the sea near
Shin-Ogasawara Terminal City.
I don't think
there can be any doubt
that it was a Gillard spaceship,
with the Album aboard.
Understood.
Stay in contact with me.
I'll be there shortly.
Laura. Go to bed.
I have to go into
work for a while.
Okay.
Are you ready, Otohime?
[OTOHIME roars]
[alarm beeping]
Okay. Fire!
Very nice, Otohime.
Just make sure you're as
good when we do it for real.
Don't worry, Itsuki.
Right. We should get
to the briefing room.
This is the Type X warhead also
code named as the Dragon Slayer.
Now, pay attention
to its effectiveness.
This missile has quite a nasty
kick to it when launched,
and even with
your Dragon's abilities,
it will be difficult to
maintain attitude control.
Even though this missile
can be overwhelming,
you must strike the exact
center of the target core
or it is
completely worthless.
We have no idea how an unknown
life form like
Thanatos will react.
We have to assume that we will
only get one shot at this.
Only one chance. Remember that.
That is all.
Hey, sis.
Hey, Yuya.
It's almost time.
Yes, it is.
Guess it's too late.
I wish there was
enough time for me
to become a real member
of the Vritra Unit.
That way I could go out on
the raid with everybody else.
[ITSUKI laughs]
Well, isn't that cute.
When you do, you'll have
to start working out you know.
What?
I do work out.
See this?
[OTOHIME and ITSUKI laugh]
Nice. But first you
have to perform a Resonance,
and then convince
someone to be your partner.
Shouldn't be hard.
Right.
So I can't be a Dragonaut until
I get a dragon that was helpful.
Your Highness, the item you
are expecting has arrived.
She's here?
We bring you the Album,
your highness.
You did well, Nanami.
Yes, sir.
She is exquisite.
Where am I?
Where is this place?
Who are you?
My name is Asim.
You have been brought to
me in my palace, on Mars.
On Mars!
You can't. Oh no.
I'm here, Mother.
Can you hear me?
Please listen.
Answer me, Mother.
It's no use. She can't hear.
You have to let me go right now!
Take me back to Earth!
Take me now!
If you don't
things will get bad!
Please!
Sorry, but I can't do that.
You should
try to forget about Earth.
I'm keenly interested
in seeing what you are.
It's not that difficult.
Show me your true form.
What d'you mean?
The Album shouldn't be
such a modest creature.
Incoming message.
Tell me.
Just seconds ago,
a surveillance satellite
detected a Dragon of unknown
affiliation headed
directly toward Earth
from the Pluto region.
Are you certain?
This is an image of Thanatos
from five hours ago.
Our calculations
indicate that this unidentified
Dragon is headed
directly this way.
[TOA gasps]
Interesting.
That means a fourth
Original, if true.
Jin, you have to
get out of there.
The Earth is finished.
Thanks for the other day.
We wouldn't have made it
through without your help.
Well, I guess
I'll never cease to be amazed
again as long as I live,
an actual compliment from
Lintverm Unit and from you.
You're teasing me.
How about I say
thanks over dinner, huh?
I'll treat you to
whatever it is you'd like.
I'm not going
to get my hopes up.
No fair.
I'm a man who
keeps his promises.
Especially promises made
to beautiful women, right?
Stop, you're going
to make me blush.
What is it?
I don't know, but it's...
[ITSUKI gasps in fear]
Hey!
What's the matter, Habaragi?
Habaragi!
[alarm beeping]
Emergency alert!
Lintverm Unit.
Please report to
the command center immediately!
Commander, we have
an emergency alert.
Sensors have identified
a hyperthermic heat
source on L-3 Base.
It's some kind of explosion.
What? What caused it?
We're trying to
find that out now.
Understood.
Call me when you know.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir!
What's going on?
It looks like there was
an explosion on L-3 Base.
We're verifying that now.
This is bad.
What happened?
Apparently, there was
an explosion at L-3.
[SIEGLINDE gasps]
Have we established
communication?
No, sir. I've been
trying since we lost them.
Commander! We're receiving
an emergency
transmission from L-3 Base.
What? Oh, no!
What is it?
Sir there's an unknown dragon.
It attacked the L-3 base.
The entire Vritra Unit's
been wiped out.
That can't be.
[alarm beeping]
What was that thing?
[OTOHIME]
Itsuki!
Otohime.
Are you all right?
Yes.
D'you know what happened?
We were attacked
by a Neo-Original.
We have to get out of here, now.
It's not safe.
But, the others.
We have to help them.
They need us.
There's no time.
This place is about to explode.
Let's go!
[alarm beeping]
I have to get out.
What's that?
[DRAGON roars]
[YUYA gasps in fear]
Dragon!
[ITSUKI gasps]
Oh no! Yuya!
Yuya!
Commander, sensors are picking
up Otohime's pulse signature!
Captain Habaragi is with her.
Are you certain?
They're entering the atmosphere.
Image coming up.
Here they come.
What is that light?
The other dragon, it's here!
And closing on them!
No!
Otohime?
[MACHINA gasps]
What is it?
[DRAGON roars]
Saki here!
Megumi here!
Ryoko here!
And now, it's time
for the ISDA annual
year end tongue-twister contest!
Annual?
Year end?
What's wrong?
You're wearing
a summer uniform, aren't you?
I'm sensitive to the heat.
Um, we should
probably do the preview.
Okay we have to talk fast!
Take it, Megumi!
On the next episode
of Dragonaut: Shin-Ogasawara
reels when a giant
Dragon appears!
What will be the fate
of Jin and Gio!
And don't tell me
there's another dragon, too!
That was fast!