- ( theme song playing )
- I AM AN EXECUTIVE OFFICER
IN ROLAND'S ELITE
TABOO-BREAKER SQUAD.
SERGEANT LUKE STOKKART
AT YOUR SERVICE.
I'VE COME HERE TONIGHT
BY ORDER OF HIS MAJESTY.
HOW DO I PUT THIS?
I'VE COME TO KILL YOU,
RYNER LUTE.
- BEFORE WE DELVE INTO THAT,
PERMIT ME TO ASK A FAVOR
OF SOME IMPORT.
I WOULD LIKE TO ASK YOU
TO ELIMINATE RYNER LUTE
AS PER THE LATELY PENNED
ROYAL EDICT.
- ( smirks )
- I MUST RESPECTFULLY DECLINE.
- LET THERE BE DARKNESS.
- ( wind blowing )
- ( gasps )
- ( choking )
IT CAN'T BE! NO!
WHAT IS THIS?
- ( smirks )
- TOUCH A SINGLE HAIR
ON MY CAPTAIN'S HEAD, DEAR SIR,
AND IT WILL BE
THE LAST THING YOU EVER DO.
IS THAT CLEAR?
OUR FAMILY DOES NOT SUFFER
MEDDLERS LIKE YOU GLADLY.
NOD ONCE IF YOU UNDERSTAND.
- WELL PLAYED, SIR.
I SHALL RELEASE
YOUR DEAR CAPTAIN AT ONCE,
NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
DYING DOESN'T SUIT ME
AT THE MOMENT.
- UNTIL I AM ASSURED
OF HER SAFETY,
YOUR LIFE HANGS BY A THREAD.
- QUITE THE CAUTIOUS FELLOW,
I SEE.
IS THAT A SO-CALLED
HERO RELIC YOU WIELD?
- LET US SAY I STUMBLED
UPON SOMETHING
RYNER LUTE OVERLOOKED
IN HIS RESEARCH.
THE THREADS OF THIS
NEEDLE WEND THEIR WAY
TO THE REACHES OF INFINITY.
THREADS ONLY, PERHAPS,
BUT IMPOSSIBLE TO SEVER.
- THE MIND REELS AT THE DAMAGE
SUCH AN INNOCUOUS LOOKING WEAPON
COULD DO, IF, SAY, IT
WERE TO FALL INTO THE HANDS
OF ROLAND'S ENEMIES ABROAD.
- GASTARK? AM I RIGHT?
- AH. SOMEONE'S HAD THEIR EAR
AT A FEW DOORS, HAVEN'T THEY?
I PRESUME YOU'VE ALSO KEPT
A CLOSE WATCH ON RYNER.
WHAT'S YOUR OPINION OF HIM?
DO YOU THINK HIS EXISTENCE
IS NECESSARY TO US?
TO ROLAND AND HIS MAJESTY,
I MEAN.
IS HE VITAL TO THE KINGDOM'S
HEALTH, OR MORE OF A NUISANCE?
SURELY THIS WHOLE
IDYLLIC CONCEPT
OF A PEACEFUL, HARMONIOUS WORLD
WHERE NO ONE MEETS
A VIOLENT END
APPEALS TO YOU ON
A PERSONAL LEVEL AT LEAST?
BUT CAN NOT THE MORE
EXPERIENCED PART OF YOU
HELP BUT SEE IT AS A FANTASY?
- I'M AFRAID IT CAN'T.
- HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
CAMOUFLAGING THE EXTENT
OF YOUR MAGIC?
- YOU ARE A DESERTER,
RYNER LUTE!
AGAINST ALL PLEAS
FROM HIS MAJESTY,
YOU FLED FROM HIS FRIENDSHIP!
- AND NOW YOU'VE COME
TO CARRY OUT HIS ORDER!
- YOU'RE A KIND SOUL, I KNOW.
IT'S EASY TO SEE HOW CAPTAIN
MILK CAME TO BE SO FOND OF YOU.
IF YOU WERE TO PERISH,
SHE WOULD BE INCONSOLABLE.
BUT EVEN SO,
THE PATH BEFORE ME IS CLEAR.
YOU, SIR,
DO NOT BELONG AT HIS SIDE!
- Tiir: LAFRA.
LAFRA, WAKE UP.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WE HAVE AN INTRUDER
- TAKE MY WORD FOR IT,
THIS BATTLE IS ALL BUT DECIDED.
FIGHT ME AND DEATH'S ICY
GRIP WILL ONLY WRAP ITSELF
AROUND YOUR THROAT
ALL THE TIGHTER!
- TRAPS ON EITHER SIDE,
BUT A WEAK SPOT IN THE MIDDLE.
( grunts )
- YOU SAW THROUGH THEM.
- FOR FUTURE REFERENCE,
YOU TALK TOO MUCH!
- SO YOU BELIEVE.
WHAT THE HELL?
- CHECKMATE, MY FRIEND.
( grunts )
- WHY NOT JUST LET HIM DO IT?
HE'D BE DOING YOU AND
EVERYONE YOU KNOW A FAVOR.
YOU KNOW IT'S TRUE.
( groans )
AH, CRAP!
( screams )
- HMM? OH, I'M SORRY.
- DAMN YOU!
ONE OF THESE FRIGGIN' DAYS!
- HMM? YOU'LL WHAT?
I'LL GET TO THE BOTTOM OF
WHATEVER THE HELL
YOUR PROBLEM IS...
- YOU'LL HAVE TO SPEAK UP.
- OKAY, YOU'VE GOT EVERY RIGHT
TO BE PISSED AT ME,
BUT CAN'T YOU JUST LET
ME MAKE IT UP TO YOU
WITH A PACK OF DANGO
OR SOMETHING?
- PERHAPS. BUT FIRST
YOU'LL TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON.
WHY IS THIS MAN
TRYING TO KILL YOU?
- UNBELIEVABLE! YOU'VE BEEN
TAILING ME, HAVEN'T YOU?
- WERE YOU AWARE OF MY PRESENCE?
- ( Pueka screams )
- ( explosion )
- ( children crying )
- Girl: BROTHER TIIR! NO!
- RUN. ALL OF YOU.
RUN AWAY.
I'LL HANDLE THIS.
- ( scoffs )
OH, C'MON.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
THERE'S A FEAST FIT FOR
A KING RIGHT NEXT TO YOU
AND YOU JUST STAND
THERE AND BLEED?
THINK ABOUT IT, MAN.
HOW ELSE YOU GONNA KILL ME?
- WHAT THE...
- Lafra: RYNER!
- LAFRA?
- GASTARK HAS FOUND
OUR HIDING PLACE...
- ( all screaming )
- PUEKA!
- LAFRA.
- Lafra: PLEASE, RYNER,
YOU HAVE TO SAVE THEM.
- ( crying )
- ( laughing maniacally )
- OH GREAT! ANOTHER ONE.
- LIKE HELL!
NOT ON MY WATCH!
( screams )
- RYNER!
- Lir: LET THAT BE
A LESSOR, FREAK.
DON'T GET IN MY WAY
- ( laughing maniacally )
- ALL RIGHT, SPUNQUEL,
DO YOUR THING!
NOT A BAD START, HUH?
- ( children crying )
- ( laughs )
COME ON, YOU LITTLE FREAKS.
GET ON WITH IT AND LOSE
CONTROL ALREADY.
I DON'T HAVE ALL NIGHT.
- ( heart beats )
- Lafra: LOOK AT TIIR,
AND THE CHILDREN.
THINK ABOUT ALL OF OUR FRIENDS
SCATTERED TO THE FAR CORNERS
OF MENORIS.
MOST OF ALL, CONSIDER YOURSELF.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHOSE GIFT FROM GOD
COST HIM HIS FAITH IN HUMANITY.
- GASTARK!
- WELL, WELL, PRETTY QUICK
ON THE DRAW, AREN'T YOU?
LIGHTNING BEASTS!
- ( yells )
- ( explosion )
- RYNER!
- YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
- ( shouts ) DAMN YOU!
- Lir: WHAT DID I JUST SAY
ABOUT GETTING IN MY WAY?
- WHAT I SEEK ARE
THE BURNING FIELDS! KURENAI!
- HEY.
LIGHTNING BEASTS.
- ( girl screams )
- UGH! DAMN IT ALL TO HELL!
I'VE KILLED ONE OF THE FREAKS
BEFORE IT WAS READY
TO BE CRYSTALLIZED!
FANTASTIC!
- HOLD ON!
- YOU SON OF A BITCH.
- RYNER! DAMN YOU! WAIT!
- ( yells )
- LIGHTNING BEASTS!
- WHAT I SEEK
IS THUNDER! IZUCH...
DAMMIT, FERRIS! WHAT THE
HELL'S WRONG WITH YOU
RUNNING OUT IN THE MIDDLE...
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
IDIOT! IF YOU'RE REALLY
SO OBSESSED WITH DYING ALONE,
JUST DO IT.
IF SEEING YOURSELF AS A MONSTER
TRUMPS SEEING YOURSELF
AS MY FRIEND,
THEN JUST VANISH
AND BE DONE WITH IT.
IF YOU REFUSE TO
SEE YOURSELF AS MY VALET,
MY TEA-DRINKING COMPANION,
OR MY ALLY,
I CANNOT CONVINCE YOU OTHERWISE.
BUT DON'T EXPECT ME TO
SHARE IN THAT OPINION,
I WILL NOT SEE YOU AS A MONSTER.
AND THERE IS NOTHING YOU CAN DO
TO CONVINCE ME OTHERWISE.
YOU CAN DENY HOW LONELY YOU ARE,
BUT IT'S OBVIOUS TO ME
THAT YOU'RE MISERABLE.
AND I WILL NEVER THINK OF YOU
AS YOU THINK OF YOURSELF.
- Lir: WOW!
IMPRESSIVE LITTLE PEP TALK
YOU JUST IMPROVISED.
HELL, IF THIS WERE
A FAIRY TALE I'D BUY IT.
THE BRAVE DAMSEL
HOLDING OUT HOPE THAT
BENEATH THE FEARSOME BEAST LURKS
THE HEART OF A HUMAN BEING?
NOT IN THE
REAL WORLD, SWEETHEART.
MONSTERS LIKE THIS GUY
WILL ALWAYS BE MONSTERS.
- WHAT DOES THAT MATTER TO ME?
MONSTER OR NOT,
THERE'S NO REASON I SHOULD CARE.
HE'S MY FRIEND FIRST.
- THAT'S A VERY
SENTIMENTAL VIEW,
BUT WHETHER YOU CARE
ISN'T THE ISSUE.
THERE'S A WHOLE WORLD OUT THERE
WHOSE VERY EXISTENCE
IS THREATENED
EVERY MINUTE FREAKS LIKE
YOUR FRIEND DRAW BREATH.
FOR THE GREATER GOOD, HE HAS TO
BE PUT DOWN LIKE A RABID DOG.
- IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO IMPRESS ME?
- YOU DON'T CARE.
YOU REALLY DON'T CARE.
YOU JUST WANT TO KNOW...
YOU...
YOU JUST...
FERRIS...
IS IT REALLY OKAY
FOR ME TO LIVE?
- IDIOT, WITHOUT YOU AROUND,
WHAT DO YOU THINK I WOULD DO?
- WE'RE GONNA FIND OUT
REAL SOON, SWEETHEART.
SEE...
YOUR FRIEND'S ABOUT TO DIE.
- ( groans )
- FERRIS!
- RESONATE!
- PLEASE, NO.
DON'T DO THIS TO ME.
- FIGHT IT!
- Ryner: I CAN'T GO
THROUGH THIS AGAIN.
- Alpha Stigma:
WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
- SHUT UP!
- Alpha Stigma: NOTHING MATTERS!
- NO! YOU'RE WRONG!
- Alpha Stigma: THIS IS WHAT
YOU REALLY WANT.
TO DESTROY.
TO OBLITERATE. TO END.
- THIS IS NOT WHAT I WANT!
- LIFE, DEATH, JOY, PAIN.
NONE OF IT AMOUNTS TO ANYTHING.
- SHUT THE HELL UP!
YOU'RE WRONG!
- WHY DENY IT?
THERE'S NO POINT.
AS MUCH AS THIS WORLD HURTS YOU,
USED YOU UP, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
NOTHING DOES.
- STOP TALKING!
- COME ON.
LET'S BRING THE WHOLE THING
TO ITS KNEES.
EVERY CORNER OF IT IS YOURS
TO DO WHATEVER YOU WANT WITH.
OPEN UP. DECIMATE IT.
KILL UNTIL THERE'S
NOTHING LEFT!
REVEL IN SEEING IT ALL
GO UP IN FLAMES!
- ( screams ) NO!
- Ryner: DEEP DOWN,
I'M A MONSTER.
ONLY GOOD FOR SOWING
DEATH AND MISERY.
BLOODSTAINED HANDS
CAN'T HOLD ON TO A DAMN THING.
I KNOW THAT.
BUT...
I STILL WANT TO HELP PEOPLE!
I WANT TO REACH OUT AND TRY TO
SAVE THIS WORLD FROM ITSELF!
EVEN A MONSTER CAN
FEEL DESPAIR!
THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING I CAN DO!
- WHAT THE HELL?
- ( screaming )
NO! YOU DON'T GET A SAY!
( breathing heavily )
- HOW THE HELL DID YOU DO THAT?
YOU... YOU STOPPED IT!
WHAT ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
- JUST SOME FREAK.
- LIKE HELL YOU ARE!
THE LATSEL THREAD?
- AH, IS THAT ITS PROPER NAME?
I HAD NO IDEA.
I'D BE HAPPY TO DELIVER
YOUR HEAD TO GASTARK PERSONALLY.
IN FACT I'LL SHOW YOU ALL
ROLAND'S HOSPITALITY.
I'LL BRING THE FIGHT
TO THEIR DOOR.
- NOW, SPUNQUEL!
- WHAT I SEEK
IS THUNDER! IZUCHI!
TIIR!
I'LL KEEP THE BASTARD AT BAY.
YOU SAVE THE CHILDREN.
- THANK YOU.
GASTARK, WE ARE NOT
FINISHED YET.
I WILL BE THE LAST
THING YOU SEE.
GET AWAY FROM HERE, RYNER.
THIS ISN'T YOUR PLACE.
- WHOA THERE, FREAK.
I DON'T THINK SO!
- SORRY TO DISAPPOINT YOU.
BUT I'M THE ONE YOU'RE
GONNA FIGHT TONIGHT.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
ALL THAT B.S.
FOR ONE LOUSY CRYSTAL?
THE SOLVER OF ALL FORMULAS.
IMAGINE YOU CROPPING UP
IN A BACKWATER LIKE ROLAND...
- Ryner: SOLVER? WHAT?
- REALLY? YOU MEAN
YOU DON'T KNOW?
YOU'RE STANDING RIGHT HERE,
AND YOU DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE?
( laughs )
WOW. THAT'S JUST SAD.
GUESS THE HERO'S GOT
A LONG ROAD AHEAD OF HIM
BEFORE HE'S COMPLETE, HUH?
( laughs )
- WELL, I THINK IT'S SAFE TO SAY
THAT OUR SITUATION HAS
ALTERED CONSIDERABLY.
- HEY!
- FERRIS IS DUE TO WAKE
ANY MOMENT NOW.
SHE'LL BE FINE.
SHE ONLY HAS A
SLIGHT CONCUSSION.
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
YOU'RE NO ORDINARY MONSTER.
WHICH MEANS THE QUESTION NOW IS
JUST WHAT EXACTLY THAT IMPLIES.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- OF COURSE.
I'M FINE.
SO, BE COMPLETELY
HONEST WITH ME.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW
YOUR DESERTION EFFECTED SION?
IF YOU'D SEEN THE LOOK
ON HIS FACE,
YOU'D KNOW BEYOND
A SHADOW OF A DOUBT
THE LAST THING HE WANTS
IS TO KILL YOU.
- THE MAN'S GONNA WORK HIMSELF
INTO AN EARLY GRAVE.
HE'D TAKE THE WHOLE WORLD
ON HIS SHOULDERS IF HE COULD.
A FLEA CAN'T DIE ON HIS WATCH
BUT THAT HE BLAMES
HIMSELF FOR IT.
I ALIGN MYSELF
TO THE MAN PROUDLY
BECAUSE IN THE WORLD
HE INTENDS TO BUILD,
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US MATTERS.
AND HERE I AM FEELING
SORRY FOR MYSELF.
PRETTY NARROW-MINDED, HUH?
- WELL, IT'S IN KEEPING
WITH YOUR CHARACTER.
SO TO BE FAIR, NONE OF THIS
CAME AS A SURPRISE.
- YEAH.
AND CHASING DOWN
A LOST CAUSE LIKE ME
IS IN KEEPING WITH YOURS.
SERIOUSLY, THE TWO OF YOU
ARE SOME PIECE OF WORK
NO ONE ELSE WOULD EVEN
WASTE THEIR TIME.
I WAS AFRAID OF BEING HURT.
AFRAID OF HURTING OTHER PEOPLE.
SO I DID WHAT I
ALWAYS DID. I RAN.
BUT I HAD NO RIGHT
TO FEEL ALONE.
HOWEVER BAD THINGS GOT,
HOWEVER SCARED I WAS,
I WAS WRONG TO THINK THAT.
I WON'T RUN ANYMORE.
PROMISE. I'M COMING HOME NOW.
WITH THE SHADOW OF GASTARK
GATHERING LIKE IT IS,
CHANCES ARE, ROLAND'LL NEED ME.
- THANK YOU.
- BUT I'LL ONLY COME BACK
ON ONE CONDITION.
AND IT'S A BIG ONE.
IF I WIND UP LOSING
CONTROL OVER MYSELF,
I WANT YOU TO BE
THE ONE WHO KILLS ME.
ALL THIS TIME,
I'VE BEEN RUNNING FROM THE TRUTH
ABOUT WHAT I REALLY AM.
MORE THAN THAT,
I WAS TERRIFIED THAT
I MIGHT END UP KILLING YOU.
NOW, KNOWING THAT, I WANT YOU
TO SHOW ME THE COURAGE...
- COURAGE?
- TO SEE THIS THROUGH TO THE END
AND NOT RUN LIKE I DID.
- FINE. IF YOU COME BACK
HOME WITH ME.
- THANK YOU.
- Luke: "RYNER LUTE IS RETURNING
TO ROLAND OF HIS OWN FREE WILL.
"IN ADDITION TO THIS,
A NUMBER OF MAGIC EYE
BEARERS ACROSS MENORIS
"HAVE JOINED FORCES
TO FIGHT AGAINST GASTARK.
"WITH RYNER LUTE ACTING AS
OUR LIAISON TO THESE CREATURES,
"ROLAND POSSESSES THE MEANS
TO CONFRONT ITS GREATEST ENEMY
"WITH THE ELEMENT OF SURPRISE."
- WHAT GOOD WOULD IT DO?
THIS IS ALL MEANINGLESS NOW.
IT MATTERS NOT HOW USEFUL
RYNER MIGHT BE. NOT ANYMORE.
WE GRASP AT STRAWS.
- TRUTH BE TOLD, YOUR MAJESTY,
HAD LUKE STOKKART
CARRIED THROUGH WITH THE ORDER
TO ELIMINATE RYNER LUTE,
THINGS WOULD HAVE FARED FAR
BETTER FOR YOU THAN NOW THEY DO.
IS THAT NOT WHY YOU ISSUED
THE DECREE TO BEGIN WITH?
- I WON'T...
I WON'T KILL MY FRIEND.
- YOU REFUSE TO PUT DOWN
A MONSTER, THEN?
- I DO.
- ( laughing )
THAT RESOLVE SETS YOU
ON A FAR, FAR CRUELER PATH.
CAN YOU NOT BRING YOURSELF
TO SEE THE MERCY IN
KILLING HIM SWIFTLY?
HE IS, AFTER ALL,
YOUR MAJESTY'S VALUED FRIEND.
BUT FAR BE IT FROM ME
TO SWAY THAT RESOLVE,
EVEN HAD YOU ELECTED
TO KILL HIM NOW,
SOON ANOTHER WOULD HAVE
COME TO TAKE HIS PLACE.
JUST AS ANOTHER
KING WOULD STEP IN
TO TAKE YOURS SHOULD YOU FALTER.
I SUPPOSE ONE NEEDN'T
SACRIFICE FRIENDS.
BUT ONE PATH LAYS
BEFORE YOU NOW,
AND THAT PATH REQUIRES
THE STRENGTH
TO RUTHLESSLY CRUSH UNDERFOOT
ALL ONE HOLDS DEAR,
SHOULD THE NEED ARISE.
FRIENDS. LOVED ONES. EVERYTHING.
THIS IS WHAT NATURE REQUIRES OF
ONE WHO WOULD DREAM AS YOU DO.
I PRAY YOU HAVE
NO REGRETS, YOUR MAJESTY.
MY KING...
MY HERO.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: OKAY, ENOUGH WITH
ALL THE CRAP.
I KNOW I AGREED TO
COME BACK HOME, SURE,
BUT I HAVE LIMITS, YOU KNOW!
THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
WAY TO BURY ME UP TO MY NECK
UNDER A MOUNTAIN OF PAPERWORK,
SION! VERY MATURE!
FRIGGIN' SLAVE-DRIVER! UGH!
I KNEW THIS WAS GONNA SUCK!