- Ryner: IMPERIAL NELPHA.
AN OLD, SPRAWLING PROVINCE
JUST TO THE WEST OF ROLAND.
RELATIONS BETWEEN THE TWO
KINGDOMS HAVE BEEN STRAINED
FOR GENERATIONS.
BUT NELPHA'S CURRENT
EMPEROR PARTS COMPANY
WITH HIS PREDECESSORS
BY PREFERRING TO ENRICH
HIS KINGDOM,
NOT WITH
THE SPOILS OF WAR,
BUT WITH CULTURE.
THE PLACE IS HOME
TO MANY ANCIENT RUINS.
AMONG THEM, A GENEROUS
PORTION OF SITES
THOUGHT TO BEAR A
CONNECTION WITH HERO RELICS.
THERE'S TOO MANY.
I GIVE UP.
I'M TIRED. I'M HUNGRY.
I'M CRUELLY OVERWORKED.
- I DON'T SEE
ANY DANGO SHOPS.
YOU, DOG, SNIFF ONE OUT.
- Ryner: GIVE ME A REASON.
- BECAUSE YOU DON'T WANT
TO SEE ME IN A FOUL MOOD.
- YEAH, TOO LATE FOR THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SAVE YOUR BREATH,
I REFUSE TO DO ANYTHING.
SHORT OF FINDING AN INN
WHERE I CAN HAVE A GOOD NAP.
- HA, HA. SO, THAT'S YOUR
MODUS OPERANDI, HUH?
I'VE READ
ALL ABOUT THAT RUSE.
A MAN INVITES A GIRL
TO AN INN. PHASE ONE.
"DON'T WORRY," SAYS THE MAN,
"I ONLY WANT TO GET SOME SLEEP.
I WON'T TRY A THING, I PROMISE."
PHASE TWO, THE GIRL ACQUIESCES.
PHASE THREE, WHEN THEY'RE ALONE,
THE MAN PROVES HIMSELF
A WILD BEAST.
PHASE FOUR, THE GIRL'S HONOR
IS DEVOURED.
- WOW. YOU'VE GOT QUITE
AN IMAGINATION, HUH?
- HA! IMAGINATION
IS WHAT PROTECTS
VIRTUOUS DAMSELS LIKE ME
FROM THE LECHEROUS INTRIGUES OF
SEX- CRAZED LUNATICS LIKE YOU.
- I'M GETTING REALLY
SICK OF THIS GAME.
- WHAT A COINCIDENCE,
PLAYTIME IS OVER.
WE'VE GOT BOOK- STACKS
TO POUR THROUGH.
- PLAYTIME? SO, STANDING
ON ME IS YOUR IDEA OF FUN?
- YEAH, WELL I'M
STILL SICK OF IT.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: ( chuckles ) NOW,
THIS IS A PROPER LIBRARY.
THIS PLACE OUGHT TO BE
BRIMMING WITH HEROIC LORE.
- GOOD. JUST DON'T TAKE
ALL DAY FINDING IT.
- OH, COME ON!
WOULD IT KILL YOU TO OFFER
A WORD OF ENCOURAGEMENT
EVERY NOW AND AGAIN?
THERE DOES COME A POINT
WHEN JUST LOOKING AT YOU...
UH, WIELD A SWORD IS REALLY
ALL THE INSPIRATION
I NEED TO HUNKER DOWN
AND HIT THE BOOKS.
SHE WILL BE THE END OF ME.
- HALT! NO BARBARIANS!
- BARBARIANS?
- THIS IS A SACRED FONT
OF KNOWLEDGE,
A SHRINE TO THE HALLOWED
ARTS OF SCHOLARSHIP,
NOT A HOSTEL FOR UNRULY SAVAGES.
- LOOK, I KNOW SHE DOESN'T
EXACTLY DRESS THE PART
OF AN ACADEMIC, BUT STILL...
- Ferris: ( sighs ) I DRESS
THE PART OF A BELEAGUERED WOMAN
FENDING OFF THE ADVANCES
OF AN ACADEMIC.
- NOT EXACTLY A TONE
THAT'S GOING TO ENDEAR US
TO THE LIBRARY GUY HERE.
- WELL, I HAVE OTHER WILES
WITH WHICH TO ENDEAR.
- JUST KIDDING.
- I'VE SEEN ENOUGH.
SHE'S ALLOWED.
I SPOKE A BIT TOO
HASTILY BEFORE.
BESIDES, WHEN BEAUTY PROMOTES
ERUDITION, EVERYONE'S A WINNER.
- WAIT, YOU'RE ALLOWING HER IN
BUT NOT ME?
- STUPID BRATS.
- ( child screams )
- THEY'RE CHILDREN.
LEAVE THEM ALONE.
- YEAH?
WELL, FOR YOUR INFORMATION
THESE LITTLE BASTARDS
ARE THE ONES
WHO RAN INTO ME.
NOW THERE'S GRIME
ALL OVER MY SHIRT.
- YOU, MY FRIEND,
OWE US COMPENSATION.
- TOALE.
- LET GO OF MY BROTHER.
- IBEL, TELURA.
MAKE A RUN FOR IT.
- GET OFF OF ME.
- ( screams )
- Thug: STUPID LITTLE...
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE, HUH?
HEY, LOOK AT THAT.
THE BOOK YOU'RE HOLDING
JUST HAPPENS TO BE ONE
I'M ON THE HUNT FOR.
- IT'S FUNNY HOW THINGS
WORK OUT, HUH?
- HEY, YOU!
- NOT IN FRONT OF THE CHILDREN.
- ( thug screams )
- SO ANYWAY,
ABOUT YOUR BOOK...
- ( groans )
- ALWAYS BEWARE
OF THE CHARMING BEAST.
HE HAS MANY TRICKS WITH
WHICH TO LURE THE UNSUSPECTING.
- I'M GOING TO KILL YOU.
- FORGIVE ME,
BUT WHO ARE YOU TWO?
- Gainel: LORD TOALE.
- ( panting )
- WE'VE HIT THE MOTHER LODE.
HEY, TOALE, ALL THE ONES
ON THE TOP SHELF, IF YOU WOULD.
- MY PLEASURE. COME ON.
- ALL RIGHT. LET'S DO THIS.
- ( grunts )
HEY, KNOCK IT OFF!
- WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE,
CASUALLY BARKING ORDERS
TO HIS LORDSHIP?
FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
LORD TOALE JUST HAPPENS
TO BE NOT ONLY THE GRANDSON
OF EMPEROR GREAD,
BUT QUITE POSSIBLY
NEXT IN LINE TO RULE.
- THE BIG BLACK ONE
UP TOP OVER THERE, TOO.
- WITH THE FRAYED EDGES?
- YEAH, THAT'S THE
ONE. THANK YOU.
- HAVE YOU HEARD
A WORD I'VE SAID?
- PLEASE, UNCLE GAINEL,
IT'S NO TROUBLE TO HELP HIM OUT.
- HE'S NO ONE.
FETCHING ODDS AND ENDS
FOR A MISCREANT LIKE HIM
WILL ONLY BRING SHAME
TO THE AUGUST HEAD
OF IMPERIAL NELPHA!
- NO. WHAT WILL TRULY BRING
SHAME TO IMPERIAL NELPHA
IS SHIRKING GRATITUDE.
AND BESIDES, I'M THE FRUIT
OF MY FATHER'S INDISCRETIONS.
A DISCARDED ONE AT THAT.
HARDLY A MAN OWED DEFERENCE.
MY SIBLINGS AND I WERE
CORRALLED TO A MINOR ESTATE
BECAUSE OUR MOTHERS HAD
THE MISFORTUNE TO BE LOWBORN.
I AM SIMPLY ONE OF THE RABBLE.
- DON'T SPEAK SO.
YOUR FATHER'S AN IMBECILE.
NOT A SOUL IN THE REALM
PREFERS STARNEL AS HEIR
TO THE THRONE OVER YOU.
- PURSUE THIS NO FURTHER,
PLEASE, UNCLE.
I'VE NO ROMANTIC NOTIONS
OF KINGSHIP.
SO, WHAT ELSE
CAN I HELP YOU FIND?
- WELL, IN THAT CASE,
THAT SHELF OVER THERE.
- I'M HAPPY TO.
- I CAN'T REACH THIS ONE.
- SURE YOU CAN.
- YOU SEE.
- THANKS.
- WHAT A NICE GUY.
IT'S LIKE HE AND SION WERE
CUT FROM THE SAME CLOTH.
- AND YET, FATE LEFT HIM
TO FEND FOR HIMSELF.
HE AND HIS SIBLINGS
ARE ALL ALONE,
A BROKEN FAMILY.
- ( sobs )
- I WOULDN'T SAY THAT.
FAMILY IS WHAT YOU MAKE OF IT.
- ...WHEN WE'VE FOUND IT?
- I CAN.
- AH, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
- I'VE GOT A BETTER ONE.
JUST WHAT THE HELL DO YOU KNOW?
- TARIFF EXEMPTION
IS MEANINGLESS
UNTIL THE FLOOD VICTIMS
CAN RECEIVE AID.
OF COURSE, THE QUESTION
OF EXPANDING LORD BERYL'S HOL...
- Fiole: YOUR MAJESTY.
- WHAT IS IT, FIOLE?
- MUST I SPELL IT OUT FOR YOU?
YOU'VE BEEN GRINDING AWAY
FOR HOURS WITHOUT SO MUCH
AS TOUCHING YOUR MEAL.
YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
- YES, I KNOW. OH, WHILE
I'VE GOT YOU HERE, THOUGH,
WHAT'S THE STATUS
OF KRIADE'S DEBT?
- I'VE DRAWN UP
A FULLY DETAILED REPORT
OF THEIR FINANCIAL STATE.
BUT YOU WON'T SEE THE FIRST
QUILL STROKE OF IT UNTIL YOU
PUT SOMETHING IN YOUR STOMACH.
( laughs )
DOESN'T LOOK AS THOUGH
I HAVE A CHOICE.
EVIDENTLY I WAS QUITE
RIGHT TO APPOINT YOU.
- LOOKING OUT FOR THE MAN
WHO SAVED MY SISTER
IS THE LEAST I COULD DO.
IF YOU HADN'T BEEN
SO COMPASSIONATE
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT WOULD'VE BECOME OF US.
THAT A LOWBORN ORPHAN LIKE ME
COULD EVER BE WORTHY
OF SUCH GRACE
IS UNTHINKABLE.
- BITE YOUR TONGUE.
OF COURSE YOU'RE WORTHY...
WORTH IS NOT A FUNCTION
OF CLASS, WE'RE ALL OF US
FELLOW TRAVELERS.
OF COURSE, THIS WORLD BEING
WHAT IT IS, OUR BASER NATURES
IGNORE THE FACT.
AND YET, WE MUST LET HOPE
SPRING ETERNAL THAT THE WORLD
CAN BE TRANSFORMED.
- LET HOPE SPRING ETERNAL?
- WE MUST NEVER ALLOW
STATUS TO DICTATE
OUR ESTEEM
FOR HUMAN BEINGS,
BECAUSE WHOEVER YOU ARE,
NO MATTER HOW LOWBORN,
THERE ARE ALWAYS THOSE WHO
WILL LOOK UP TO YOU, ALWAYS
THOSE WHO WILL CARRY YOUR TORCH.
- WELL, I FOR ONE WILL ALWAYS
CARRY YOUR TORCH, SIR.
AS LONG AS I'M ABLE.
- HUH, NOW, I AM UNWORTHY.
- ENOUGH OF THAT.
EAT A LITTLE SOMETHING
AND REST FOR A WHILE.
YOU'LL NEED YOUR WITS
ABOUT YOU FOR THE BANQUET.
- ALL RIGHT.
BUT ONLY ON CONDITION
THAT YOU TAKE
THE WEEKEND OFF.
- UH, BUT SIR...
- YOUR SISTER MUST
MISS YOU, FIOLE.
GO PAY HER A CALL.
- OF COURSE, YOUR MAJESTY.
- COME ON, IS THIS A BANQUET
OR A FUNERAL, YOUR MAJESTY?
- I'M SORRY?
- YOU'RE ALWAYS SO DILIGENT,
WHY NOT THROW YOURSELF
INTO PLAYING HOST?
- ( chuckles )
COME, YOU JUST WANT
AN EXCUSE TO MINGLE.
- YOU'LL HAVE TO FORGIVE
THE CHARADE, YOUR HIGHNESS.
CLAUGH IS FRAIL BEFORE
THE FAIRER SEX.
- THAT'S RICH. FUNNY YOU'RE
CHATTING HERE WITH US, THOUGH.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
CHATTING UP LADY PEARL.
- PIG!
- BOTH OF YOU, PLEASE.
GO SOCIALIZE.
- Both: SIR.
- ( both laughing )
- MY, WHAT SUBTLETY.
WISH I HAD THEIR SPIRIT, THOUGH.
- HIGHNESS,
WON'T YOU DO US THE HONOR
OF EMERGING FROM THE SHADOWS
TO TAKE CENTER STAGE?
- LORDS BERYL AND PEARL.
I TRUST YOU ARE ENJOYING
YOURSELVES, YES?
- DAZZLED, AS ALWAYS,
BY THE UNPARALLELED OPULENCE
OF YOUR MAJESTY'S SOIREES.
- YOU CERTAINLY DO HAVE
A TALENT FOR POMP, SIR.
- ( chuckles )
- GENTLEMEN, EXPENSE
IS NO OBJECT
WHEN PANDERING
TO COSMOPOLITAN
TASTES SUCH AS YOURS.
- ( all laughing )
- KLAUSBERR AND STEARIED
LEER AT ME FROM THE WINGS,
DARING TO VEIL THEIR
ANTI-MONARCHIST LEANINGS
BEHIND EMPTY SMILES,
EVEN AS THEY SEND
THEIR LACKEYS OUT AGAINST ME.
- SIR?
- YES? WHAT IS IT, CLAUGH?
- I JUST RECEIVED WORD
FROM THE GUARDSMEN.
- IT'S FIOLE. HE'S BEEN
FOUND MURDERED.
- Beryl: FIOLE?
AH, YES, OF COURSE,
THE COMMONER YOUR MAJESTY
RECENTLY APPOINTED TO BE
HIS PERSONAL SECRETARY.
- HE'S BEEN MURDERED, YOU SAY?
WELL, AT LEAST THERE'S SOME
SOLACE TO BE GLEANED
FROM THE FACT
THAT HE'S A COMMONER.
- QUITE SO. HAD A NOBLE BEEN
SLAIN WITHIN THE CASTLE KEEP,
WE'D HAVE QUITE THE SCANDAL
ON OUR HANDS, WOULDN'T WE?
- ( laughs )
- SION.
- TRAGIC, THOUGH.
THE LAD WAS QUITE EXCEPTIONAL
AT FORGING MY SIGNATURE.
- ( all chuckling )
- MONSTERS.
- I MIGHT AS WELL HAVE SLIT
THE BOY'S THROAT MYSELF.
MY WEAKNESS SLEW HIM.
- STOP.
GET A HOLD OF YOURSELF.
- THANK YOU, CLAUGH.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- Fiole: ESLINA, SORRY FOR
TAKING SO LONG TO WRITE BACK.
I'M PLEASED TO HEAR YOU'RE
DOING SO WELL FOR YOURSELF.
A LETTER FROM YOU ALWAYS
INSPIRES ME TO REACH
A LITTLE HIGHER
THAN I THINK I CAN.
MY SUPERIOR MAKES ME FEEL
THE SAME WAY, IN FACT.
ASIDE FROM YOU, HIS MAJESTY
IS BY FAR THE GREATEST PERSON
I'VE EVER KNOWN.
HE BELIEVES IN DEALING
WITH PEOPLE, EVEN COMMONERS
AS EQUALS.
HE USES HIS POWER
TO PROTECT THE DOWNTRODDEN.
- CLAUGH, ARRANGE
FOR HIS INTERNMENT
CALNE, ATTEND TO ESLINA.
BEFORE THE NOBLES DO.
- Both: SIR.
- SENTIMENTAL, FOOLISH BOY.
YOU WERE WRONG TO PRAISE ME.
I DIDN'T HAVE THE POWER
TO PROTECT YOU.
ONLY TO BURY YOU.
- ( sobs ) FIOLE.
- Lucile: SHOCK,
BITTERNESS, HATRED,
ANGER, REPENTANCE, MISERY.
- ( chuckles )
TELL ME, SHOULD REVENGE
COMPLETE THE SEQUENCE.
IF SO, I AM HAPPY TO BE
THE LAST THING A
CORRUPT NOBLE SEES.
- NO. NOT YET.
I WILL PICK MY MOMENT.
- CAN YOU ENDURE THE WAIT?
- PERHAPS.
IF NOT, I'M SURE YOU
CAN BE COUNTED ON
TO REDRESS THE IMBALANCE,
BY ARRANGING IT SO YOU'RE
THE LAST THING I SEE.
- AS INDEED I WOULD.
A MAN WHO CANNOT RULE HIMSELF
HAS NO BUSINESS RULING A PEOPLE.
- RYNER LUTE,
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
YOU AND FERRIS HAVE
A KING'S ENVY AT YOUR BACK.
- Girl: NO FAIR!
MAKE STUPID-HEAD GIVE
ME BACK MY SUPPER.
- ( boy crying )
- SHUT UP.
- STOP WITH THE BICKERING
AND EAT. HEY, SLOW IT DOWN.
- SORRY ABOUT THIS.
HAVING TO IMPOSE
ON YOU AND EVERYTHING.
- TRUST ME, YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU SEE HOW WE ARE HERE.
TWO EXTRA HOUSEGUESTS
ARE NOTHING WE CAN'T HANDLE.
HANG ON, WHERE'D
THAT COME FROM?
- THE NICE LADY AT THE
GENERAL STORE GAVE IT TO US.
IT'S FOR GOOD LUCK.
SHE SAYS SHE HOPES YOU WIN
AGAINST THE CROWN PRINCE.
- ( chuckles )
- Ryner: SEEMS A LOT
OF PEOPLE FEEL THAT WAY.
- WELL, I GUESS EVERYONE
HAS THEIR OWN OPINION
ON THE SUBJECT.
BUT I THINK I'M FAR MORE
USEFUL HERE THAN I'D EVER
BE AS AN EMPEROR.
- BETWEEN SION AND TOALE,
CROOKED NOBLEMEN EVERYWHERE,
MUST BE TREMBLING
IN THEIR BOOTS.
- ( screams )
- PREPARE TO DIE, BEAST!
- WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- I'LL RESCUE YOU, SIS.
- ( grunts )
- Ferris: EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
- FERRIS!
- IRIS.
- I GOT SO WORRIED WHEN YOU
LEFT WITHOUT SAYING GOODBYE,
THAT I JUST HAD TO FOLLOW
YOUR TRAIL AND TRY TO SAVE YOU
FROM THE JAWS OF
THE VICIOUS BEAST
WHO'D SNATCHED YOU AWAY.
- I SEE. MY APOLOGIES.
- DON'T TELL ME.
THIS IS YOUR LITTLE SISTER.
- YES. ISN'T SHE ADORABLE?
- WHEN I ASKED HIS HIGHNESS
WHERE YOU WERE, HE SAID
A WILD BEAST TOOK YOU.
AND THAT YOU WERE ON A QUEST
TO FIND THE GREATEST DANGO SHOP
IN THE WORLD.
AND IF I COULD FIND YOU,
HE'D DEPUTIZE ME AND MAKE ME
HIS OWN SPECIAL ROYAL MESSENGER.
- SO, BASICALLY
THIS LITTLE HELLION
IS NOW OUR MAIN POINT
OF CONTACT WITH SION?
- YOU GUESSED IT.
NOW, TELL ME I'M GREAT.
- COME NOW, SWEETIE.
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
- WAIT, SEE? A WYNNIT DANGO
COMBINATION SET.
- ONE- HUNDRED POINTS.
- YAY! ONE- HUNDRED POINTS.
NOW TELL ME I'M GREAT.
- UH, SURE. JOB WELL DONE.
- OH, NO. I TALKED TO A
WILD BEAST. NOW, I'M RUINED.
- FEAR NOT, CHILD.
THE RUIN IS MINE.
FOR I SPOKE
TO THE CREATURE FIRST.
- ( sobs )
- NO. YOU WILL PAY FOR THIS!
FOR MY SISTER'S HONOR.
- ( groans )
- Sion: A GOODWILL MISSION
TO NELPHA?
- Stearied: YES, YOUR MAJESTY.
LEST OLD TENSIONS
BE REKINDLED
BY WHAT OUR NEIGHBORS
MIGHT CONSTRUE AS ALOOFNESS.
IF I MAY, IT IS PARAMOUNT
THAT WE ALIGN OURSELVES
TO EMPEROR GREAD.
HIS PLAN FOR NELPHA IS ONE
IN WHICH PEACE WITH ROLAND
IS CENTRAL.
THEREFORE THE INTERESTS OF
EVERYONE WOULD BEST BE SERVED
BY A SHOW OF SUPPORT.
- THERE ARE FIRST A NUMBER
OF INTERNAL ISSUES THAT
BEG MY ATTENTION.
I CANNOT GIVE YOU
AN ANSWER RIGHT NOW.
- WELL, I FOR MY PART,
AM SATISFIED THAT YOUR GRACE,
BEAR IN THE MIND THE
IMPLICATIONS OF TOO MUCH DELAY.
- IT'S A TRAP.
AS A FISH OUT OF WATER,
YOU CAN BE PICKED OFF
WITH RECKLESS ABANDON.
- I TAKE IT THERE
ARE THOSE IN NELPHA,
WHO SUPPORT OUR HOME- GROWN
ANTI- MONARCHIST CONTINGENT?
- NO DOUBT OF IT, SIR.
THEY DON'T DARE MAKE
AN ATTEMPT ON YOUR LIFE HERE,
SO AN OFFICIAL VISIT TO NELPHA
IS JUST THE PRETEXT THEY NEED.
- AND YET THEY KILL FIOLE.
- PARDON ME.
THERE WAS NO ONE HERE,
SO I THOUGHT I'D MAKE MYSELF
COMFORTABLE WAITING FOR YOU.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- MIRAN FROAUDE.
SON OF MARQUIS KARLAL FROAUDE.
CURRENTLY, I AM A
LIEUTENANT COLONEL
OF THE ROLAND IMPERIAL ARMY.
- AND WHAT DOES A NOBLE'S SON
WANT OF THE KING?
- I WOULD ENQUIRE AFTER
THE SMALL, CLANDESTINE FACTION,
WITH WHICH HE HOPES
TO OUST THE LANDED GENTRY.
- HOW DARE YOU?
- HOLD ON.
- YOUR REPUTATION PRECEDES YOU,
MIRAN FROAUDE.
YOU WERE MADE
A LIEUTENANT BY SEVENTEEN.
YOUR CONSIDERABLE GIFTS
LED TO A SWIFT PROMOTION.
BUT WHILE YOU ARE
THE MARQUIS'S SON,
IT IS BY ADOPTION
RATHER THAN BLOOD.
- I TAKE IT YOUR GRACE'S LATE
SECRETARY DID HIS JOB WELL.
DOUBTLESS, HE TOLD YOU
OF MY RUTHLESSNESS.
I AM A MAN FOR WHOM
RAW AMBITION JUSTIFIES
ANY MEANS AT MY DISPOSAL.
- THIS I KNOW AND YOU SEEK
AN AUDIENCE WITH ME?
- PRIVATELY.
- CLAUGH, PLEASE LEAVE US,
WILL YOU?
- SIR.
- I WOULD SPEAK
TO HIM IN PRIVATE.
- YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO HEAR
EVERYONE OUT, DON'T YOU?
- THANK YOU.
- JUST WATCH YOUR BACK.
- THERE, I'M ALL ATTENTION, SIR.
- AH, BUT IT IS I SHOULD
BE ATTENTIVE TO YOUR NEEDS,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
- WHAT?
- MY SOLE PURPOSE HERE, LIEGE,
IS TO ANSWER A NEED AND QUITE
A DESPERATE ONE AT THAT.
A GREAT MANY LIGHTS
ARE DRAWN TO YOU.
STRONG, DAZZLING,
RADIANT LIGHTS.
LIGHTS THAT WOULD SHINE
ON A WORLD TRANSFORMED.
AND YET TO SEE
THEIR HOPES FULFILLED,
YOU MUST DEAL IN SHADOW.
AND ENSHROUD YOURSELF
IN MIDNIGHT.
CAN A MAN LIKE YOU ENDURE
THE WEIGHT OF SUCH
A FUNDAMENTAL DISPARITY?
I THINK NOT, SIR.
YOU ARE THIS LAND'S KING.
YOU MUST EMULATE THOSE LIGHTS
SO DRAWN TO YOU. TO WHICH END?
WHY NOT SIMPLY DEFER
THE BURDEN OF SHADOWS
TO ONE WHO IS MORE ACCUSTOMED
TO THEIR RAIMENT THAN YOU?
SUCH AS MYSELF?
- HOW DO YOU DARE
SUCH PRESUMPTUOUSNESS?
TO SPEAK AS ONE
WHO KNOWS MY MIND.
- I SPEAK AS ONE
WHO KNOWS YOUR HEART.
- OH? THEN PLEASE LAY BARE.
- IN THE ANNALS OF HISTORY,
ROLAND HAS BEEN LITTLE
MORE THAN A RECALCITRANT
CUB AMONG LIONS.
YOU WOULD DRAPE IT'S BANNER
PROUDLY ACROSS THE WHOLE
OF MENORIS.
SUBJECT THE ENTIRE CONTINENT
TO YOUR ROYAL WILL.
- ( chuckles )
- IS MY HEART REALLY
SO GRASPING AS ALL THAT?
NOT TO DISAPPOINT
BUT WARFARE ISN'T MY AIM.
QUITE THE OPPOSITE. I SEEK
ONLY TO RULE PEACEFULLY.
- BUT OF COURSE, YOUR GRACE,
A KING DARE NOT MAKE IT PLAIN.
DISCRETION IS THE BETTER PART
OF VALOR, AFTER ALL.
I ASK AGAIN, APPOINT
ME TO THE SHADOWS.
USE ME AS YOU WOULD A SWORD.
AND NOT EVEN MY FATHER'S LIFE
SHALL STAND IN THE WAY
OF MY DUTY TO YOU.
THUS, I PLEDGE MY FEALTY.
- THE LIFE OF THE MAN WHO
RAISED YOU CANNOT BE SO CHEAP.
- ( chuckles )
A MERE FIGURE OF SPEECH.
- VERY WELL THEN. I ACCEPT
YOUR OFFER OF LOYALTY.
- I SHALL ENDEAVOR TO BE WORTHY.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: SINCE WHEN AM I
QUALIFIED TO BE A SENTRY?
WELL, I GUESS A RULER
LIKE SION HAS SO MANY
ENEMIES TO BE WARY OF,
HE CAN'T LOOK JUST ANYWHERE
FOR PEOPLE TO PROTECT HIM.
BUT STILL, THOUGH.
WHY ME?
THIS IS SO
INCREDIBLY NOT COOL.