( students chattering )
- Student 1: WHAT CLASS
IS SHE IN?
- Student 2: SHE IS CUTE!
- Student 3: YEAH, BUT SHE LOOKS
KIND OF INTIMIDATING.
- ( yawing )
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
- UH, MY BAD. SORRY.
- HEY, IF YOU DON'T WATCH
WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
SOMEBODY'S GONNA
GET HURT, BUDDY.
- ( theme song playing )
- Instructor: All right! Begin!
- ( yawns )
- WHAT IS THIS?
ARE YOU TRYING TO MAKE ME LOWER
MY GUARD? TAKE THIS, THEN!
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( Ryner snores )
- Student 4: LET'S GO.
- RYNER! WAKE UP ALREADY,
WE'RE MOVING!
- Student 4: OL' RYNER'S
SLEEPING AGAIN.
- Student 5: HE'S HOPELESS,
KIEFER, JUST LEAVE HIM BE!
- DOESN'T THE OPINION OF YOUR
CLASSMATES MEAN ANYTHING?
- NOT AS MUCH AS BEING FORCED
TO ATTEND TRAINING CLASS TODAY
BECAUSE OF ONE OF 'EM.
- OH, BOY.
WHAT AM I DOING?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
- ( exclaims ) I WANT THAT ONE!
- JUST DON'T WASTE MONEY, OKAY?
- RIGHT!
- SO, KIEFER, DO YOU SEE
ANYTHING YOU'D LIKE?
YOU ARE A FOURTEEN-YEAR-OLD
GIRL, YOU KNOW,
IT'S OKAY FOR YOU
TO WANT THINGS.
DON'T BE SO HARD ON YOURSELF.
- WELL, IT'S JUST...
I DON'T KNOW.
- LOOK! I GOT SOME FOR YOU, TOO!
TAKE ONE.
SEE? THEY'RE PRETTY,
AREN'T THEY?
- THAT WAS SWEET.
- I WOULDN'T BE LAUGHING
IF I WERE YOU, GIRL.
WE DON'T FIND
ESPIONAGE TO BE HUMOROUS.
- KIEFER! TAKE LEMILE
AND GO NOW!
- RIGHT!
- WHAT I SEEK IS
THUNDER! IZUCHI!
- HURRY! GET OUT OF HERE, NOW!
I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT TO BEAR
THE WICKED SPIRIT BEAST
THAT SLEEPS WITHIN THE EARTH!
- IS NAIA GONNA BE ALL RIGHT?
SHOULD WE GO BACK AND GET HER?
- SHE'LL BE JUST FINE.
WE'LL MEET UP WITH HER
AT THE BORDER, OKAY?
- ( laughs )
OH, NOT TO WORRY, LITTLE ONE.
YOUR SISTER IS ALREADY HERE.
SHE SAID SHE'D DO ANYTHING
TO SAVE YOU,
EVEN IF IT COST HER LIFE.
I GUESS SHE WASN'T KIDDING
AROUND AFTER ALL, WAS SHE NOW?
- ( sobbing )
- BASTARD!
I WILL END YOU!
- I LOVE IT!
( laughing )
- SISTER!
PLEASE LET HER GO,
YOU'RE GONNA KILL HER!
JUST STOP IT!
- SHUT UP!
- NO, DON'T!
I CAN'T BREATHE, PLEASE.
- ( sobs ) PLEASE STOP.
NOT MY SISTER.
LET HER GO.
I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU SAY.
- AH, IS THAT SO?
EVEN IF THAT PLEDGE MEANS
FORSAKING THE SOIL OF YOUR
NATIVE LAND AND
TURNING ON YOUR FRIENDS?
- I LOVE THE WAY THIS FEELS.
CARING ABOUT SOMEONE SO MUCH.
BUT I HAVE NO RIGHT...
NO RIGHT TO THINK SUCH THINGS.
BECAUSE IN THE END,
I MUST BETRAY HIM.
I HATE THIS. I DON'T WANT
TO KILL ANYONE ELSE.
PLEASE, RYNER, HELP ME.
- OH, WOW,
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
- I BET,
YOU DO ENJOY YOUR NAPS.
- I'M TIRED.
- SLEEPING WHILE AT THE REIGNS
IS FORBIDDEN!
- OH, COME ON,
CUT ME SOME SLACK, WILL YA?
I HAVEN'T SLEPT A WINK!
- OUR FRIEND. IT SEEMS HE'S
SLEEPING FOR THE BOTH OF US.
- PRIVATE KIEFER KNOLLES!
GET OUT OF HERE!
THIS WHOLE PLACE IS DONE FOR!
- YES, BUT, CAPTAIN,
THERE ARE STILL SO MANY
INNOCENT PEOPLE HERE!
- JUST FORGET ABOUT THEM.
THE ENTIRE GASTARK ARMY
IS ON ITS WAY!
- STOHL'S BY FAR THE STRONGEST,
BEST ORGANIZED MILITARY FORCE
ON MENORIS.
IT'S ODD THAT THEY DIDN'T
DO MORE RESEARCH
ON RYNER'S ALPHA STIGMA.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THANK YOU.
- NO WAY AM I GONNA DIE HERE,
NOT WHILE I STILL HAVE
BREATH IN ME!
NOW, I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT
TO UNLEASH THE BEAST OF LIGHT
THAT DANCES THROUGH
THE NIGHT SKY!
NO WAY!
MY MAGIC DIDN'T WORK!
HOW IS THIS POSSIBLE?
- Lefahl: A STOHL SOLDIER, HUH?
WHAT, DO YOU HAVE A DEATH WISH?
STOHL ABANDONED THIS VILLAGE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
ACCOMPLISH ON YOUR OWN?
- LOOK, YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT ME!
I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO
ABANDON THEM!
- WHAT'S WITH YOU?
A SOLDIER WITH A BLEEDING HEART,
THAT'S A NEW ONE.
- WHAT, SHOULD I REJOICE IN WAR?
WHEN ALL IT BRINGS IS DEATH,
DESTRUCTION AND PAIN!
- ( Lefahl laughs )
YOU'RE KEEPING ME TALKING SO
YOU CAN WAIT FOR A CHANCE
TO DISH OUT A LITTLE PAIN OF
YOUR OWN, AREN'T YOU, GIRL?
THAT MAGIC YOU USED ISN'T NATIVE
TO STOHL, THOUGH.
WHICH MEANS YOU'RE
PUTTING YOURSELF
BETWEEN THEM AND GASTARK,
RISKING YOUR OWN NECK TO SAVE
THE LIVES OF FOREIGNERS
WHO CARE NOTHING FOR YOU.
SOUNDS LIKE A
BLEEDING HEART TO ME.
HOWEVER, LUCKY FOR YOU I FIND
THAT SORT OF THING ENDEARING.
- PREPARATIONS ARE ALL IN ORDER,
MY KING.
- AND THE SECURING OF CIVILIANS?
- HAS BEEN COMPLETED.
A MASS INVOCATION FROM STOHL
FORCES IS ALMOST FINISHED.
WE MUST WITHDRAW, YOUR MAJESTY.
- YOUR MAJESTY?
SO HE'S...
- SIR! PLEASE!
- MY HEART IS AKIN TO YOURS.
IT HUNGERS FOR PEACE.
BLOODSHED, TEARS
AND MISERY, I ABHOR.
I ABHOR THE DEATH
OF A FELLOW SOLDIER.
I ABHOR THE
DEATH OF A CHILD.
AND IF A SWEET, KINDRED SOUL
LIKE YOURS WERE TO DIE,
ABHORRENCE WOULD BE
ALL THAT REMAINED OF ME.
BUT AS LONG AS NATIONS EXIST,
WARS WILL BE WAGED,
MEN WILL PERISH.
I SUFFER GREAT PAINS TO DIMINISH
CASUALTIES AS MUCH AS I CAN,
TO SOFTEN THE EDGES
OF THE WORLD.
NOT JUST FOR GASTARK,
BUT STOHL, TOO.
INDEED FOR EVERY SOUL
THAT CALLS MENORIS ITS HOME.
TO SAVE THEM ALL
AND TO ELIMINATE WAR,
THAT IS MY DREAM.
- ONE CANNOT PLEDGE TO ELIMINATE
WAR BY SEEKING TO WAGE IT.
YOU'RE A HYPOCRITE!
- YES, I SUPPOSE I AM.
WHAT CAN ONE MAN DO?
THERE'S ALWAYS THIS!
- Spectral Female Voice:
CONTRACTOR, I HEAR THEE
AND ANSWER THY CALL.
COME, OFFER THY COMPENSATION,
AND IN DOING SO
UNLEASH MY STRENGTH.
- I HEREBY OFFER YOU
MY LEFT EYE!
I NEED YOUR POWER!
- Spectral Female Voice:
THE CONTRACT IS SOLIDIFIED.
- NOW GIVE ME YOUR STRENGTH.
HEAR ME, GLOUVIL!
I UNLEASH YOU!
I WILL NOT LET THIS SACRIFICE
BE IN VAIN.
I BRING DESTRUCTION TO ALL!
I BRING CHANGE!
COME NOW!
AND SEND THESE BASTARDS TO HELL!
( Lefahl yells )
( screams )
- YOUR MAJESTY!
- Lefahl: LEAVE ME BE.
AND TELL STOHL:
UNLESS THEY WOULD SEE
ANOTHER SUCH ATTACK,
THEY WILL SURRENDER.
- YOUR EYE, IT...
- IT'S MY SACRIFICE.
FOR USING THE
SACRED SWORD, GLOUVIL.
- HIS MAJESTY HAS ALREADY
MADE MANY SACRIFICES.
HIS SENSE OF SMELL,
HIS RIGHT LEG.
- THAT'S AWFUL.
- IT'S NOT. I ENDED A
STAGGERING NUMBER OF LIVES, YES.
BUT BY DOING SO,
SPARED COUNTLESS MORE.
A SMALL PRICE TO PAY.
A SACRIFICE WELL WORTH IT.
TO SAVE LIVES.
- YOU REALLY DON'T REGRET IT?
- I'D BE A MONSTER IF I DIDN'T
DESPAIR OF KILLING WHEN I MUST.
IF YOU TRULY DO DESIRE PEACE
AND WISH TO SAVE LIVES,
STAND BY MY SIDE.
MY NAME'S LEFAHL EDEA.
THE GREAT HERO KING OF GASTARK.
- NOT JUST YET.
BUT SOMEDAY, YOUR MAJESTY,
I WILL STAND PROUDLY
BY YOUR SIDE.
- SOMEDAY, YOU SAY?
AH, WELL, SEE YOU THEN.
- GOODBYE, KING OF GASTARK.
KEEP ON TRYING
TO SAVE THE WORLD.
- Lord 1: SO D'YOU HEAR
ABOUT THE RECENT PURGE?
FROM WHAT I'VE HEARD,
LIEUTENANT FROAUDE IS BEHIND IT.
- Lord 2: IMPOSSIBLE!
YOU'RE SAYING HE RAISED A HAND
AGAINST HIS OWN FATHER?
- HOW LONG DO YOU PLAN TO
KEEP ME ON AS A FIELD MARSHAL?
- FOR AS LONG AS IT TAKES.
- I DIDN'T ASK FOR THIS!
AND I DON'T WANT IT, SIR.
I'M BEGGING YOU,
DEMOTE ME, PLEASE!
- WHY WOULD WE DEMOTE YOU?
A MORE APPROPRIATE PERSON
THERE IS NOT.
- I SEE.
YOU'RE MAKING SPORT OF ME.
- NO. I SPEAK TRUE.
- IS THAT SO?
WHY DOES THAT MAKE IT
MORE UNBEARABLE?
- YOUR SIMPLE MIND
DOESN'T COMPREHEND
THE SUBTLE WENDING
OF MORAL AMBIGUITY.
IN THAT SIMPLE MIND DWELLS
YOUR MILITARY GENIUS.
IT ENGENDERS LOYALTY
FROM THE MEN,
WHO ADMIRE YOU FOR
YOUR STEADFAST 'MORALS.'
- BASTARD! YOU MOCK ME!
- Sion: ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH!
WE MUSN'T FORGET, WE ARE ALL
ON THE SAME SIDE, YES?
FIELD MARSHAL KLOM,
I'D LIKE YOU TO PAY
A VISIT TO ESTABUL.
- ESTABUL, SIR?
- THE ESTABULIAN FORCES
MUST BE REFORMED
AND CONJOINED
WITH THE ROLAND ARMY.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
THE MAJORITY OF ESTABUL'S
SOLDIERS AND CITIZENS
FEEL RESENTMENT FOR ROLAND
AND FOR YOU, YOUR MAJESTY!
WE CAN'T FORCE THEM
TO JOIN WITH US,
IT WILL ONLY
MAKE THINGS WORSE.
- NO. TIDES ARE TURNING
FOR ROLAND.
GAINING ALLEGIANCE FROM
THE ESTABULIAN MILITARY,
THIS MUST BE OUR PRIORITY.
GIVEN LADY NOA'S REPUTATION AS
A BEACON OF HOPE FOR HER PEOPLE,
AND YOUR OWN AS HER
CLOSE PERSONAL FRIEND,
YOU ARE THAT
PRIORITY'S WARHORSE.
- YOU'RE SUGGESTING I TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF A WOMAN I ADMIRE?
- YES.
- WELL, YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT IT!
- IT IS NECESSARY
FOR THIS NATION.
- THE NATION OF WHICH
YOUR HIGHNESS SPEAKS.
TELL ME THIS. DOES IT INCLUDE
THE INNOCENT WOMEN AND CHILDREN
OF ESTABUL, TOO?
- YES, OF COURSE.
EVERY ONE OF YOU.
YOU'RE ALL MY VALUABLE CITIZENS.
THERE IS NO DECEIT
IN MY PLANS FOR ESTABUL.
I WISH TO FORGE PEACE, AND
CROSS SWORDS WITH THEM NO MORE.
I ONCE HAD A FRIEND,
A DEAR COMPANION NAMED
KIEFER KNOLLES.
I ADORED HER.
BUT SHE BETRAYED US
AS AN ESTABULIAN SPY.
A GOOD MAJORITY OF
MY FRIENDS WERE KILLED.
- SIRE, DO YOU MEAN TO INTIMATE
THAT YOU RESENT ESTABUL?
- I DON'T.
EVEN NOW, DEEP IN MY HEART,
I CONSIDER KIEFER A DEAR FRIEND.
YOU SEE,
SHE HAD NO ALTERNATIVE.
ONE SISTER WAS KILLED BY ROLAND,
ANOTHER TAKEN HOSTAGE,
SHE WAS FORCED
TO BECOME A DOUBLE AGENT.
BUT STILL, HER FACE NEVER ONCE
BETRAYED HER TRUE INTENT.
UNDOUBTEDLY, OF COURSE,
HER HEART MUST'VE WRITHED
IN TORMENT ALL THE WHILE.
BUT FOR MY LIFE
I NEVER KNEW...
AS LONG AS I RULE THIS LAND,
THERE WILL BE NO MORE WAR
BETWEEN ROLAND AND ESTABUL.
SO, FRIENDS.
I REQUIRE YOUR ASSISTANCE.
- AND YOU SHALL HAVE IT.
AS LONG AS IT IS WITHIN MY
POWER, I SHALL DO ANYTHING.
- YOU'LL USE LADY NOA'S
INFLUENCE TO REVITALIZE
THE ESTABULIAN FORCES
AND STRENGTHEN ROLAND.
AT THE SAME TIME, YOU'LL
ENGENDER LOYALTY
BY HONORING THEIR
MILITARY PERSONNEL.
IT'S BRILLIANT.
- LET US ALL HOPE IT HAS
THE DESIRED EFFECT.
- I SHALL TAKE MY LEAVE.
I WILL BE HEADING
FOR THE RUNA EMPIRE.
- RUNA?
- IT SEEMS DUKE STEARIED,
THE RINGLEADER BEHIND THE PLOT
TO ASSASSINATE YOUR GRACE,
WAS IN TALKS WITH RUNA NOBILITY.
I AM GOING TO ASCERTAIN
THE FACTS.
- BE CAREFUL, PLEASE.
YOU ARE OF NO USE TO ME DEAD.
- THY WILL BE DONE.
- Ryner: AW, MAN...
RESCUING KUKU'S
GOING TO BE A PAIN, ISN'T IT?
- THINK OF IT THIS WAY.
IF WE DO NOTHING, WHAT THEN
BECOMES OF OUR DREAM
TO HOLD CELEBRATORY TEA?
COME NOW,
LET'S DO THIS FOR KUKU!
- HEY, CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
WHY DO YOUR DREAMS BECOME
MY DREAMS BY EXTENSION?
JUST KIDDING, LET'S MAKE
ALL OUR DREAMS COME TRUE, HUH?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- THIS DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT,
THERE'S NOBODY INSIDE THERE.
- YEAH, I DON'T SENSE
ANY PRESENCE.
- DAMN. THE BOTH OF YOU!
- Ryner: WELL, THIS SUCKS.
- Sui: IF IT ISN'T OUR DEAR
FRIENDS, RYNER AND FERRIS.
WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE
RUNNING INTO YOU AGAIN.
- WERE YOU WAITING FOR US?
- YES. WE ARE BOTH
EXTREMELY INTERESTED IN YOU.
YOU OWN A UNIQUE ALPHA STIGMA,
AFTER ALL.
AN ENORMOUS POWER, INCOMPARABLE
TO ALL OTHER BEARERS.
YOU ARE ONE LUCKY FELLOW.
EVEN MY OWN RULE FRAGMENT,
THE ELEMIO COMB,
WAS ESSENTIALLY RENDERED
USELESS UP AGAINST YOU.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
EVEN AFTER AWAKENING
AND LOSING CONTROL,
YOU HAVE RETURNED TO NORMAL.
BEGGING THE QUESTION:
WHO ARE YOU?
- IF I KNEW THAT,
I WOULDN'T BE HERE.
- THAT LITTLE CHILD YOU TWO
MANAGED TO SECURE,
HE BEARS THE
ALPHA STIGMA, AS WELL.
WHERE HAVE YOU HIDDEN HIM?
- HOLD ON,
YOU KNOW ABOUT ARUA?
- WHY, YES, OF COURSE.
YOU SEE, RYNER, WE'RE
INTERESTED IN THE ALPHA STIGMA,
NO MATTER WHAT FORM IT TAKES.
- KUU...
- I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT
TO BEAR THE WICKED SPIRIT BEAST
THAT SLEEPS WITHIN THE EARTH!
- THERE'S NO ESCAPING KUU,
MY FRIEND!
- Ryner: NOT GOOD.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S SPLIT UP!
LEAVE THIS TO ME AND
GO TAKE CARE OF ARUA!
- RIGHT!
- OH, YES! RYNER!
BEFORE WE PART WAYS,
ALLOW ME TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOUR LITTLE FRIEND KUKU,
SHE IS BEING CONFINED
IN THE MANOR
OF A NOBLE
OF THIS TERRITORY.
WE'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU THERE.
- I WILL MAKE YOU REGRET THIS.
- Miran: TELL ME,
WHY IS THE KING OF RUNA
NOT PRESENT?
- MY FATHER, OR RATHER,
THE KING IS VERY ILL.
I'M SORRY.
HE IS UNABLE TO ATTEND YOU.
- Miran: OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
PARDON MY INTRUSIVENESS,
PRINCESS, WHERE DID HE GO?
CASSALA? OR IMPERIAL NELPHA?
- WELL, I'M AFRAID
IT'S NOT MY PLACE TO SAY.
- AGAIN, I BEG YOUR PARDON.
IN POLITICS, WOMEN ARE NEUTRAL.
SUCH IS BRED THE MIND OF A LADY
BORN TO THIS COUNTRY.
FORGIVE ME. IN THE FACE
OF SUCH BEAUTY
I SIMPLY FORGOT
MY STANDING, YOUR HIGHNESS.
YES, I SEE.
IT IS THE KING OF RUNA.
IT SEEMS HE HAS BETRAYED
HIS ALLIANCE WITH ROLAND.
HE'S JOINED HANDS WITH GASTARK.
A FOOLISH PLAN.
YES, THAT DOES EXPLAIN
WHY HE WAS UNABLE
TO MEET WITH ME TODAY.
FURTHERMORE,
THE KING OF RUNA WAS THE PERSON
WHO ORCHESTRATED
THE ASSASSINATION PLOT.
HE WAS BEHIND IT ALL.
- I'VE TOLD YOU EVERYTHING!
SPARE ME!
THESE MONSTERS!
PLEASE GET RID OF THEM!
- GASTARK MESSENGERS.
THEY SLAUGHTERED ALL
THE RUNA SOLDIERS IN AN INSTANT.
I CAN'T LET THIS GO
UNCHALLENGED, CAN I?
I SUPPOSE I'LL HAVE TO
DISPOSE OF THEM, TOO.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: MAN, WHY IS IT ALWAYS
ONE CRAPPY THING AFTER ANOTHER?
WHAT DID I SAY?
ALL YOU NORTHERN PEOPLE,
JUST STAY WHERE YOU ARE!
THIS SUCKS AND I DON'T WANNA
DEAL WITH IT ANYMORE!
THIS WHOLE REVENGE THING,
IT'S JUST...
IT'S NOT ME! YOU KNOW?