- UGH. COME ON, FERRIS.
WHAT IN THE WORLD COULD
BE TAKING YOU SO LONG?
AT LEAST THE LITTLE
GUY'S STILL ASLEEP.
- THAT BOY IS OUR
RESEARCH SUBJECT!
TAKE HIM AND YOU'LL BE
CONDEMNED AS HIS ACCOMPLICE
AND STRUCK DOWN BY
THE WRATH OF HEAVEN!
- RAT BASTARDS...
GO ON, KID...
NAP AS MUCH AS YOU WANT...
SURE BEATS DEALING WITH
THE REAL WORLD. MOSTLY.
- Ferris: STAND ASIDE!
- ( groans )
DAMN IT! WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT ONE FOR?
- DON'T PLAY INNOCENT...
YOU WERE FILLING THE POOR
BOY'S HEAD WITH WICKED IDEAS
THROUGH OSMOSIS.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- SO, DARE I ASK
YOUR STRATEGY?
- MY STRATEGY?
- FOR RAISING THE CHILD...
CLEARLY THE FRUIT OF SOME
LONG FORGOTTEN TRYST
YOU THOUGHT YOU
LEFT TO ROT YEARS AGO
HAS COME BACK TO CLAIM HIS
RIGHT AS YOUR OFFSPRING.
- BY NO STRETCH OF
THE IMAGINATION IS HE MINE!
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT LIKE I'M
THE ONLY ONE BEING PURSUED...
THE LONGER YOU STAND
AROUND CRACKING JOKE...
- BEHIND YOU.
- UH...
- FORTUNE LED ME TO THIS
EXQUISITE ABANDONED CARRIAGE...
- CARE FOR A LIFT?
- ABANDONED?
OH, YEAH. SURE...
I'LL BELIEVE THAT STORY...
ABANDONED BY THE NOBLES
YOU FORCIBLY PINCHED IT FROM!
- OH, BE QUIET...
JUST HURRY AND CLIMB ON...
BEFORE YOUR PERVERSION STARTS
TO RUB OFF ON THE LAD.
- KNOCK IT OFF!
MIGHT AS WELL, I SUPPOSE...
CAN'T HAUL THE KID LIKE A RUSSET
SACK ALL THE WAY TO REGIT.
I HAVE TO ADMIT,
I'M PLEASANTLY SURPRISED.
IT ISN'T LIKE YOU
TO BE SO THOUGHTFUL.
- HI-HO, SILVER!
- ( neighing )
- EASE UP ON THE WHIP!
I'M NOT IN THE STUPID
CARRIAGE YET!
- FULL GALLOP, BOY!
FLEE FROM THE LASCIVIOUS
BEAST AT OUR BACKS
LIKE A FOX FROM A HOUND!
- COME ON!
WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS!
HEY! I KNOW YOU CAN HEAR ME!
- SORRY, I DIDN'T QUITE CATCH
THAT. YOU'RE TOO FAR BEHIND.
- OH, YOU ARE SO GOING TO GET IT
WHEN I CATCH UP WITH THAT RIG!
DAMN IT, FERRIS!
- ( knock on door )
- Sion: COME IN.
- YOUR LUNCH IS SERVED,
YOUR MAJESTY.
- THANK YOU.
JUST SET IT THERE, PLEASE.
- MAY I SUGGEST YOU TAKE A
MOMENT FROM YOUR WORK
TO EAT BEFORE THE
MEAL GETS COLD?
- I'LL EAT THE SECOND I'M DONE
WITH THIS MOUNTAIN OF PAPERWORK.
- PLEASE, SIR,
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS.
- AH, SEE, HERE'S A PERFECT
EXAMPLE OF THE MISSIVES
I RECEIVE FROM DAY TO DAY.
- THANKS FOR SADDLING ME
WITH THIS RIDICULOUS
FIELD MARSHAL POSITION...
I'M ON TO YOU...
SADISTIC BASTARD!
YOU EXPECT ME TO DIE OF BOREDOM!
- ( giggling )
- THIS REPRESENTS THE BACKLOG OF
REPORTS SUBMITTED BY THOSE
APPOINTED TO CABINET POSITIONS
DURING MY TENURE AS KING.
- EVERY ONE OF THEM CHOSEN
FROM THE LOWER CLASS.
- WELL I REALLY DIDN'T INTEND
TO SHIRK THE NOBILITY
WHEN ASSIGNING POSTS.
IT JUST SEEMED TO
WORK OUT THAT WAY
WHEN I DECIDED TO FAVOR
PERSONAL MERITS
OVER THE ACCIDENT
OF ONE'S BIRTH.
SO FAR, EVERY PERSON SELECTED
HAS DRAFTED A PROPOSAL
WITH THE GREATER
GOOD IN MIND...
WHICH WAS THE IDEA.
YOU SEE, ESLINA,
NEW BEGINNINGS THRIVE
ON OUR THINKING
FROM THE GROUND UP.
- I COULDN'T AGREE MORE.
JUST AS LOFTY PRINCIPLES THRIVE
ON A WELL-FED IMAGINATION, SIR.
AND KINGS ON A HARDY LUNCH.
- SO THEY DO.
- I'LL LEAVE YOU TO IT,
YOUR MAJESTY.
- NEW BEGINNINGS AND
LOFTY IDEALS...
WELL, IN THIS QUIET
THEY SEEM TO THRIVE AT LEAST.
THE STORM WILL BREAK
BEFORE LONG...
- ( knocking on door )
- COME IN.
TROUBLESOME NEWS?
- I'VE JUST RECEIVED WORD
THAT THE NOBLES OF ARKMEL
ARE CLAMORING FOR YOUR
REMOVAL FROM THE THRONE.
- YOU DON'T SAY.
- IN THE REGION OF
HOUSE FROAUDE.
- HOW INTERESTING... I SHOULD
HAVE ANTICIPATED AS MUCH.
- ( chattering )
- Miran: FATHER.
- YES? WHAT IS IT?
- THE GUESTS HAVE GATHERED
IN THE RECEPTION HALL.
- AH. GOOD.
- IF I MAY, SIR.
IT IS A REMARKABLE FEAT.
AT YOUR BEHEST, NOBLES FROM
EVERY CORNER OF THE REGION
HAVE GATHERED UNDER ONE ROOF.
- COME, MY BOY...
THE ACCOMPLISHMENT
BELONGS MORE
ON YOUR HEAD THAN
IT DOES ON MINE.
- NOT SO, FATHER.
I MERELY MAKE A STUDY WHERE
YOU ARE THE CONSUMMATE MASTER.
- SUCH SILKEN WORDS YOU WEAVE...
YOU ARE YOUR FATHER'S PRIDE JUST
AS MUCH AS YOU ARE HIS WEAKNESS.
EVER WISE. EVER BEAUTIFUL...
MIRAN. MY LOVELY, MIRAN...
- YOUR OWN SWEET WORDS WEAVE
A THREAD TO EQUAL YOUR CARESSES.
YOUR PRIDE IS MY WEAKNESS, SIR.
- ( laughs )
- BUT LET THE TWO OF US NOT...
BECOME ENTANGLED JUST YET...
WE HAVE GUESTS TO SEE TO,
AFTER ALL.
- ( chattering )
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR PATIENCE.
BUT MY THANKS, MOST OF ALL...
TO YOUR AUGUST EARS...
LET US FIRST GIVE CREDIT
TO WHERE IT IS DUE...
THE BANQUET'S ORGANIZERS,
DUKE STEARIED, THERE AMONG YOU,
AND OF COURSE YOUR HOST,
THE ILLUSTRIOUS KARLAL FROAUDE.
- ( crowd cheering )
- LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THAT
SUCH EXCELLENT PEOPLE
WOULD SEE FIT TO ENDURE
THE WHIMS OF AN OLD MAN
IS SPLENDIDLY MOVING.
NO DOUBT, SHREWD AS YOU ALL ARE,
OUR PURPOSE HERE TODAY IS PLAIN.
IF I SPEAK TRUE, BY ALL MEANS
LET ME HEAR YOUR
BRAVE VOICES GIVE ASSENT.
- Man 1: WE'RE HERE TO PUT
A CALLOW, UPSTART KING
IN HIS WELL DESERVED GRAVE!
- Man 2: HIS BLOOD MUST BE SHED
FOR FLOUTING OUR GOOD NAMES!
- Man 3: HIS POPULIST IDEALS
WILL BE THE END OF US!
- Karkan: JUST SO, MY FRIENDS.
THE TIME FOR HIS REIGN TO END
IS UPON US!
ROYAL BLOOD OR NOT,
ASTAL IS A LOWBORN MONGREL...
THE LONGER WE LET HIM SPIT
AT US FROM ON HIGH,
THE MORE CERTAIN IS OUR DOOM!
HE MUST BE CRUSHED!
MADE AN EXAMPLE OF!
THE MEANS TO DO
SO ARE WELL IN HAND...
THE EMPIRE OF RUNA HAS
ALIGNED ITSELF TO US
IN THIS SENTIMENT...
THEY TOO WOULD SEE
AN END TO THE BASTARD...
ALLOW MY SON MIRAN
TO DESCRIBE THE PLAN
THIS ALLIANCE HAS WROUGHT.
WHY DO YOU HESITATE?
- BEFORE THE REALM CAN PROSPER,
I MUST FIRST ASK THAT ALL OF YOU
PRESENT HERE THIS AFTERNOON...
DIE.
- Man 1: WHAT'S
THE MEANING OF THIS?
- BOY, THIS IS NOT
THE TIME FOR ANTICS!
- DARKNESS, DESTROY.
- ( people screaming )
- NO!
WHAT IN HEAVEN'S NAME
HAVE YOU DONE?
DEAR GOD!
NO! SHOW ME MERCY!
- OH, BUT I'VE AWAITED
THIS DAY LONGER
THAN YOU CAN
POSSIBLY IMAGINE...
EVER SINCE, IN FACT,
I WAS FIRST PRESENTED TO YOU.
YOU SEE, AN AMBITION HAS
BURNED IN MY BREAST
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
AN AMBITION TO WHICH YOU,
DEAR FATHER,
HAVE BEEN LITTLE
MORE THAN A PAWN.
- BUT, MIRAN, YOU WERE
ONLY FIVE YEARS OLD
WHEN FIRST PRESENTED
TO ME FOR ADOPTION...
- QUITE SO, AND IN THOSE DAYS
YOUR ELDER BROTHER
WAS THE PATRIARCH
OF THIS HOUSE...
UNTIL, THAT IS, HE AND HIS
IMMEDIATE SUCCESSORS ALL MET
WITH UNFORTUNATE ACCIDENTS
ONE AFTER THE OTHER.
SUCH A PITY THAT WAS.
BUT SOON THEREAFTER,
ALL OF HOUSE FROAUDE
WAS YOURS, WAS IT NOT?
- YOU MEAN...
YOU MASSACRED THE CLAN?
MY WHOLE FAMILY? EVERY LAST ONE.
- COME NOW, SIR...
THAT'S HARDLY TRUE
SO LONG AS YOU LIVE.
- PLEASE, MY SON!
I BEG YOU. DON'T!
- HEARING YOU BEG IS A PLEASURE
THAT QUICKLY WEARS ITSELF THIN.
A FOND FAREWELL...
LORD KARKAL.
- YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
YOU CAN'T...
( screams )
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR
COOPERATION.
IT IS MUCH APPRECIATED...
THUS YOU SEE
MY PREFERRED METHOD
FOR DEALING WITH
POLITICAL DISSENT.
RECALL THIS SCENE SHOULD THE
URGE EVER TAKE YOU TO BETRAY ME.
- Stearied: MAKE NO MISTAKE,
I SHALL...
AFTER WITNESSING THIS...
A MAN WOULD HAVE TO BE A FOOL
TO TRY AND CHALLENGE...
( gasps )
- WHAT IN THE...
( Miran laughs )
YOU MANAGED TO ESCAPE
MY SHADOWS, I SEE...
WHO DO I HAVE THE PLEASURE
OF ADDRESSING?
- Lir: THE FACT THAT I'M HERE
MUST MEAN I'M A MEMBER
OF ROLAND'S NOBILITY...
- Miran: YES, VERY DROLL.
YOUR HAIR IS TELLING, THOUGH.
THE SOUTHERN REGIONS AREN'T
KNOWN FOR CROWNING NATIVES
WITH PEACH-COLORED LOCKS.
- NICELY DONE...
YOU'RE A MAN WHO PAYS
ATTENTION TO DETAIL.
- FROM WHAT COUNTRY
DO YOU CRAWL?
- DO I LOOK LIKE THE SORT OF
CHUMP WHO'D ANSWER THAT?
- AS A MATTER OF FACT,
YOU DO NOT.
- I'D LOVE TO TRADE QUIPS,
BUT I HAVE A JOB TO DO...
'COURSE I WAS HOPING NOT TO
HAVE TO USE MY FULL POWER
IN THESE DIGS...
BUT I GUESS YOU DO
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
- DARKEST NIGHT...
- BEASTS BORN OF HORIZON'S FIRE.
- COME FORTH!
- JUST AS I SUSPECTED. YOU CARRY
A WEAPON SIMILAR TO MINE.
- FUNNY. MOST FOLKS REACT TO MY
FRIENDS HERE A LITTLE MORE,
UH, ENTHUSIASTICALLY.
YOU MIGHT BE THE ONLY PERSON
WHOSE FIRST INSTINCT
ISN'T TO TURN TAIL AND RUN.
- Miran: OH, MAKE NO MISTAKE.
I AM FASCINATED.
YOUR VERY EXISTENCE
RAISES QUESTIONS.
SUCH AS WHY YOU WOULD
TROUBLE WITH DUKE STEARIED.
CLEARY HE WAS A VITAL PIECE
IN SEVERAL GAMES AT ONCE.
GAMES FOR HIGH STAKES...
PRESUMABLY AT LEAST ONE
OF WHICH IS BEING PLAYED
BY A FELLOW
COUNTRYMAN OF YOURS
WHOSE SIGHTS ARE SET ON ROLAND.
- Lir:
OH, I SHOULD'VE DUCKED OUT
BEFORE YOU PIECED THAT TOGETHER.
BUT, YOU SEE... YOUR LITTLE
TRINKET CATCHES MY EYE.
- WHAT I SEEK IS
THE BURNING FIELDS!
- LIGHTING BEASTS, ATTACK!
I'D SAY WE'RE EVENLY MATCHED...
NOT MUCH POINT IN
US CARRYING ON LIKE THIS...
- I'M SORRY... I'M AFRAID
THAT'S NOT QUITE THE CASE...
SEEMS YOU'VE A BIT OF A
DILEMMA ON YOUR HANDS.
ALL ELSE BEING EQUAL,
IT IS I WHO HOLD
THE ADVANTAGE HERE...
YOU CANNOT RECITE A PROPER
INVOCATION WITHIN EARSHOT OF ME
FOR FEAR OF EXPOSING
YOUR PLACE OF ORIGIN...
BESIDES WHICH...
- YOU REALLY LIKE TO TALK.
- EVERY DOOR AND WINDOW IN THIS
HALL HAS BEEN SEALED SHUT...
YOUR ONLY HOPE OF GETTING OUT
WOULD BE TO SET YOUR LIGHTNING
BEASTS TO WORK ON AN EXIT...
DURING WHICH INTERVAL
MY SHADOW BEASTS
WILL HAPPILY RIP OUT
YOUR INSIDES.
NOT A STRATEGIC POSITION
TO BE ENVIED, I SHOULD SAY.
- WOW, MAN...
BET EVERYONE LOVES YOU, HUH?
- SHOULD I FEEL INSULTED?
WHAT WILL YOU DO?
SURRENDER, OR RISK CERTAIN DEATH
FOR THE NARROW CHANCE OF ESCAPE?
- THINK I'LL PASS ON BOTH
THOSE OPTIONS...
I'M A GUY THAT LIKES
TO MAKE HIS OWN WAY.
A LINO DOUE CRYSTAL...
WITH THIS THING...
I WIN!
- OH DEAR...
DIRECTING MY SHADOW
BEASTS AT THE DOOR
WEAKENS MY DECOY PROJECTION...
I MISJUDGED YOU...
TO THINK THAT I WOULD
MEET MY END HERE,
IN THIS HOVEL.
- Claugh: GET DOWN!
- FIELD MARSHAL CLAUGH?
- ON YOUR FEET!
- WHY ON EARTH
ARE YOU EVEN HERE?
- SAVE THE TALKING FOR LATER.
- LET THERE BE DARKNESS!
WHAT'S THE PLAN
FOR GETTING OUT OF HERE?
MY SHADOW BEASTS WILL ONLY
SHIELD US FOR SO LONG.
- I'VE GOT THIS.
( grunts )
- DOES THIS PUT US ON
GOOD TERMS?
FORGIVE ME...
NOT TO SOUND UNGRATEFUL,
BUT WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- LOOK, DON'T GET ANY IDEAS.
IT'S NOT LIKE I WANTED TO COME.
I WAS JUST ACTING
ON ORDERS FROM SION.
- ACTING ON ORDERS?
BUT WHY NOT THEN ARRIVE
WITH A FULL COMPLIMENT
OF SOLDIERS?
- I BROUGHT A HANDFUL
OF INFANTRYMEN...
SION WOULDN'T HAVE IT OTHERWISE.
HE SAID I'D PROBABLY
MEET RESISTANCE,
SO COMING ALONE
WAS OUT OF THE QUESTION...
BUT, I...
WELL I KINDA RAN OUT
AHEAD OF THEM A BIT, SEE...
ONLY SO I COULD HAVE THE
PLEASURE OF PUNCHING YOU
WITHOUT ANYONE
AROUND TO HOLD ME BACK...
I GUESS SEEING YOU IN
TROUBLE DISTRACTED ME.
- YOU DIDN'T COME
HERE BY CHOICE.
AND YET YOU RUSHED OUT
SEVERAL LEAGUES AHEAD
OF YOUR OWN ENTOURAGE...
A BIT UNUSUAL, DON'T YOU THINK?
- I TOLD YOU, I WANTED
TO GET HERE FIRST
SO I COULD PUNCH
YOU IN THE DAMN FACE.
- YET HERE I STAND RESCUED
WITH NARY A WELT OR SCRATCH...
WHY NOT RAISE A FIST TO ME NOW?
I'D CERTAINLY DO
SO IN YOUR SHOES.
- HEY, IT'S NOT
TOO LATE FOR IT.
- YOU HAVE MY
GRATITUDE NONETHELESS...
I WOULD'VE BEEN DEAD IN MOMENTS
LEFT TO MY OWN DEVICES...
I AM IN YOUR DEBT, SIR.
- SO WHAT IN THE HELL WAS THAT
BLUE FLAME ALL ABOUT?
IS IT SAFE TO SAY
THERE'S A STORM BREWING?
- I COULDN'T SAY...
BUT IN ANY EVENT...
IT WOULD SEEM THAT
THE WINDS OF WAR...
ARE CLAMORING TO BLOW
OBSTACLES IN OUR PATH.
- ( wind blows )
- FIELD MARSHAL CLAUGH AND
LIEUTENANT GENERAL FROAUDE
ARE EN ROUTE TO THE
PALACE GATES, YOUR MAJESTY.
- EXCELLENT NEWS...
YOU MAY BE DISMISSED.
- Messenger: SIR.
- Sion: YOU'RE WASTING
YOUR TIME.
- Lucile: A VERY INTRIGUING
MOVE, ALL THINGS CONSIDERED.
LIGHTNING BEASTS IS IT?
GHASTLY AS THEY MUST
APPEAR TO A NOVICE,
NOTHING SO OBVIOUS
WILL WORK AGAINST ME.
TO WHOMEVER SUMMONS
THESE FAMILIARS
IN HOPES OF EMPTYING
ROLAND'S THRONE, KNOW THIS...
YOU ARE NOTHING.
RETURN TO YOUR MASTER
AND TELL THEM...
HIS MAJESTY'S PROTECTOR...
IS NOT IMPRESSED.
THE PRESENCE HAS DIMINISHED...
SEEMS THEY'VE FLED.
- SHOULD WE NOT HAVE TRIED
TO ENSNARE THEM, THEN?
- THAT DECISION IS THE
PROVINCE OF THE KING...
IF YOU WOULD LIKE, SIR...
I WOULD BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO TRY AND GIVE CHASE.
- I WOULD NOT SO DIGNIFY THEM.
- AH, SPOKEN LIKE A TRUE KING.
TORN BUT NOT IN TATTERS...
YOU MAY YET WEATHER
THE COMING UPHEAVAL NICELY...
PERHAPS WITH ONE SO
DECISIVE AT THE HELM,
THE KINGDOM ITSELF
CAN HOPE TO SURVIVE.
- AND IF I CANNOT PROTECT
THE KINGDOM AS DEFTLY AS MYSELF?
- I'LL DIVEST YOU
OF CROWN AND LIFE
WHILE SOMEONE WHO
CAN TAKES YOUR PLACE...
UNTIL THAT DAY,
YOUR MAJESTY MAY DO
AS HE PLEASES.
- AS I PLEASE...
SOMETHING STIRS THUNDEROUSLY
OVERHEAD... SOMETHING BIG.
- Lir: A SWORD FAMILY...
THIS WHOLE DAMN KINGDOM'S
A BREEDING GROUND FOR FREAKS.
AND I DIDN'T EXACTLY PULL
THAT ONE OFF LIKE A PRO...
- Runa king: WHO IN HEAVEN'S
NAME ARE YOU WRETCHED PEOPLE?
- Sui: OH, DIDN'T I MENTION IT?
WE'RE GOODWILL AMBASSADORS.
- Kuu: IF IT HELPS AT ALL,
THINK OF US AS A PAIR OF HANDS
OUTSTRETCHED TO RUNA
IN FRIENDSHIP.
ON BEHALF OF
OUR KING, NATURALLY.
- Runa King: THE RUNA EMPIRE
HAS ALWAYS BEEN
A STEADFAST ALLY TO ROLAND!
- YES, A VERY STEADFAST
ALLY INDEED...
SO MUCH SO, YOU CONSPIRED
WITH THE NOBILITY
TO DISPOSE OF
THEIR CURRENT KING.
BUT, I'M AFRAID TO SAY
THAT YOUR UNOFFICIAL
CONTACT, DUKE STEARIED...
IS, COURTESY OF
OUR COUNTRYMAN, NO MORE.
- SUCH A TRAVESTY...
TO HAVE ONE'S MAN
ON THE INSIDE NEUTRALIZED.
- NOW THEN, LET ME PUT
THE QUESTION TO YOU BLUNTLY,
YOUR HIGHNESS,
WILL YOU OR WILL YOU NOT JOIN
FORCES WITH THE GASTARK EMPIRE?
WELL, THERE'S NO NEED
TO MAKE A RUSH DECISION...
WE HAVE AN IMPORTANT JOB
TO GET ON WITH AS IT IS...
WE DO LOOK FORWARD
TO YOUR RESPONSE, THOUGH...
OH SISTER, DEAR...
REMIND ME WHERE WE'RE HEADED?
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
MUST I ALWAYS LEAD YOU
BY THE SCRUFF
THROUGH EVERY TINY LITTLE
DETAIL OF OUR SPECIAL MISSION?
I MEAN, WHEN... ARE YOU GOING
TO STAND ON YOUR OWN FEET?
- SORRY, I JUST FORGOT.
- WELL I'M GIVING YOU FIVE
SECONDS TO UN-FORGET
BEFORE I PUMMEL YOU!
FIVE, FOUR...
- WAIT, HOLD ON, I...
BELIEVE WE WERE BOUND
FOR A VILLAGE, PERHAPS?
- THE TOWN OF REGIT!
WE'RE TO FIND
THE ALPHA STIGMA CHILD!
- MAN, THESE GUYS JUST DON'T
KNOW WHEN TO QUIT, DO...
( screams )
- HOP TO, RYNER.
THEY'RE GAINING ON US.
- YEAH, WELL IMPALING ME'S
NOT GONNA HELP...
- ON THE CONTRARY,
IT'S WORKING LIKE A CHARM.
PLUS I LIKE IT WHEN
YOU DANCE FOR ME!
- DEMON!
ABERRATIONS FLEE FROM THE
WATCHFUL EYES OF HEAVEN IN VAIN!
- THE EYES OF HEAVEN?
GIMME A BREAK.
- I IMPLORE THE GODS ABOVE
TO ENDOW THINE SERVANTS
WITH THE
DEMON-PIERCING ICE BLADE!
- I OFFER UP A CONTRACT TO
UNLEASH THE MAGIC BEAST OF LIGHT
WHO DANCES THROUGH THE SKIES!
- WHAT?
- HOW'S ARUA?
- STILL SOUND ASLEEP...
ARE YOU SERIOUS ABOUT TAKING
US BACK THROUGH REGIT?
- YEAH, IT'S BETTER
FOR EVERYONE
IF ARUA'S LITTLE
FRIEND COMES WITH US.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- AS LONG AS THE TWO
OF THEM STAY THERE,
THE TOWNSPEOPLE WILL
GIVE THEM NOTHING BUT GRIEF...
I WANT TO TRY AND HELP THEM FIND
A PLACE WHERE THEY CAN LIVE
IN SOMETHING LIKE PEACE.
( screams )
- THEN THERE'S NO TIME TO LOSE!
ANOTHER ROUND OF PURSUERS IS
CLOSING THE GAP BETWEEN
AS WE SPEAK!
DANCE, OUTLAW, DANCE!
- OW! DAMN IT, STOP!
THAT REALLY FREAKIN' HURTS!
KNOCK IT OFF!
( yells )
- Woman 1: I HEAR PASSING
THE ENTRY INSPECTION HERE
IS PRETTY TOUGH.
- Man 1: 'CAUSE STOHL
TROOPS GET PAMPERED
LIKE YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE.
- Man 2: KEEPS 'EM HAPPY
WHILE THEY SCRAP SHIELDS
WITH GASTARK.
- Man 3: BUT I HEAR THAT
LITTLE NORTHERN BACKWATER
IS KIND OF A DARK HORSE.
- Man 4: PLEASE. THEY'RE
NOT EVEN A REAL COUNTRY.
STOHL'S GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
- Kiefer: ROLAND... CASSLA...
ESTOLIA... STOHL.
- Soldier: NEXT!
- HERE!
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: OKAY, I'M GETTING
REALLY SICK AND TIRED
OF STUPID CRAP JUST
FALLING OUT OF THE SKY AT US
WHEREVER WE GO.
GASTARK'S NEXT?
SCREW THAT,
I'M NOT GOING UP NORTH!
LIKE IT'S MY FAULT THE DUMB
BASTARDS CAN'T STAY PUT!
UGH, THIS TOTALLY SUCKS...