Ryner: I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT
TO BEAR THE WICKED SPIRIT BEAST
THAT SLEEPS WITHIN THE EARTH!
THERE'S NO ESCAPING
KUU, MY FRIEND!
( Ferris screams and
swords clash )
- OH, YES! RYNER!
BEFORE WE PART WAYS,
ALLOW ME TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOUR LITTLE FRIEND KUKU...
SHE IS BEING CONFINED IN
THE MANOR OF A NOBLE
OF THIS TERRITORY.
WE'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU THERE.
- I WILL MAKE YOU REGRET THIS.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( birds chirping )
- FERRIS IS SURE TAKING
HER SWEET TIME.
- I WONDER IF KUU HAS
BEEN GIVING HER ANY TROUBLE.
YEAH, WELL...
I GUESS IT'S NOT LIKE SHE
CAN'T HANDLE HERSELF
IF IT COMES DOWN TO IT.
- THAT'S HOW AN ALPHA
STIGMA IS CONTAINED.
DIDN'T YOU KNOW?
CAN ONE TRULY BE SO IN THE DARK
ABOUT HIS OWN POWERS?
- IF THERE'S ANYTHING
TO THAT METHOD...
I WONDER WHETHER OR NOT
IT'D SAVE YOU.
I MEAN, YOU HAVEN'T
REALLY HURT ANYONE YET.
I'D GOUGE IT OUT OF
YOU MYSELF IF I COULD.
BEFORE YOUR MIND
BECOMES SO DAMAGED
THAT EXTRACTION IS POINTLESS.
- ( grimacing )
WHERE AM I?
( gasps and screams )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHERE HAVE MY MOTHER
AND FATHER GONE?
I SAW THEM... THEY...
( screaming and sobbing )
THEY'RE DEAD AND
IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
EVERYONE... EVERYONE I
KNOW IS... I...
YOU... YOU MURDERED MY
PARENTS TO GET AT ME,
DIDN'T YOU?
I'LL KILL YOU!
- GET A HOLD OF YOURSELF, KID.
- WHY ME?
IT'S NOT FAIR!
TELL ME ONE THING I
EVER DID TO DESERVE THIS?
JUST STOP IT!
I NEVER WANTED THIS!
I NEVER WANTED ANY OF THIS!
AND NOW MY MOTHER AND
FATHER ARE DEAD BECAUSE OF ME!
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE!
- YOU CAN RUN AWAY.
OR YOU CAN LAY THERE AND DIE.
I'LL LEAVE IT UP TO YOU.
FAR BE IT FROM ME TO DISPUTE
WHATEVER FANTASY
YOU HAVE OF SALVATION.
- I WASN'T BORN
YESTERDAY, CREEP.
YOU INTEND TO KILL ME,
DON'T YOU?
MONSTERS LIKE ME
DON'T DESERVE TO LIVE.
- YEAH.
ABOUT THAT.
- ( gasps )
- I'VE BEEN GIVING THE MATTER
A LOT OF THOUGHT.
- IT'S A HELL OF A THING
WHEN THE MERE FACT
OF YOUR EXISTENCE MEANS
PEOPLE YOU LOVE GET HURT.
GET KILLED.
WORSE STILL, THAT THE PEOPLE
LUCKY ENOUGH TO SURVIVE
SHUN YOU AS A DEMON.
TENDS TO MAKE YOU START
ASKING QUESTIONS,
MOST OF WHICH BEGIN WITH "WHY?"
WHEN FOLKS EITHER RECOIL
FROM YOU OR WIND UP DEAD
FOR THE EFFORT OF
TRYING TO GET CLOSE,
HELL, WHAT SANE PERSON
WOULDN'T JUST WANT
TO CURL UP AND DIE?
THAT WAS THE CRUX OF
MY THINKING FOR A LONG TIME.
BUT...
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT
THAT WAS IT FOR ME,
SOMEBODY GOT THROUGH.
A NAIVE WOULD-BE KING WHO
SOMEHOW SAW A LITTLE GOOD IN ME.
A SCARED YOUNG GIRL WHO
TRIED TO CONVINCE ME
I WASN'T A MONSTER...
AND... MORE RECENTLY...
A SWORD-WIELDING
PSYCHOTIC ICE NYMPH
WHO TREATS ME
LIKE A PINCUSHION.
BUT IT DOES MAKE ME WONDER
IF I JUDGED MYSELF TOO HARSHLY.
IF MAYBE, I DON'T KNOW...
LIFE CAN WORK.
THESE DAYS WHEN I DREAM,
I DREAM I'M BUILDING A WORLD.
ONE WHERE THE PEOPLE
I CARE ABOUT CAN THRIVE,
WHERE LIFE MAKES SENSE TO ALL,
WHERE I DON'T RAMBLE
ON LIKE A TOTAL LUNATIC.
- THAT'S WHERE YOU AND
ME PART WAYS, THEN.
EVERY LAST PERSON WHO
CARED IF I LIVE OR DIE IS GONE.
- WHAT ABOUT YOUR OLD MAN?
WHAT WAS THE LAST THING HE SAID?
- DON'T DARE BLAME YOURSELF
FOR MY DEATH EITHER, SON.
YOU LIVE.
YOU HAVE TO GO ON.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
THERE IS SOMEONE LEFT.
WE DIDN'T JUST FALL OUT
OF THE SKY TO RESCUE YOU.
A LITTLE GIRL NAMED KUKU WAS
DESPERATE FOR US TO INTERVENE.
- SHE WAS?
- AT THE MOMENT,
SHE'S BEING HELD HOSTAGE
BY A COUPLE OF BAD APPLES
WHO INTEND TO LURE
YOU INTO A TRAP.
OF COURSE THE
NOBLE THING TO DO
WOULD BE TO TRY
TO SWOOP IN AND GET HER.
- BUT, I MEAN, COME ON...
- BUT NOTHING!
THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO!
- BE REALISTIC, KID.
YOU CAN'T EVEN FIGHT.
- THAT'S NO EXCUSE FOR
LEAVING MY BEST FRIEND TO ROT!
JUST TEACH ME WHAT
I NEED TO KNOW.
- Ferris: LOOKOUT!
- WELCOME BACK, FERRIS.
- DON'T BE TAKEN IN
BY HIS WILES.
NOT ONLY DOES HE SPEND
THE BETTER PART OF HIS TIME
SLUMBERING WHILE
THE WORLD LIMPS ON,
HE'S BEEN THE RUIN OF SO
MANY VIRTUOUS YOUNG WOMEN
THAT VICE'S MOST STALWART
CHRONICLERS HAVE LOST COUNT.
ALAS, CONSCIENCE
FORBIDS GREATER DETAIL
WITHIN EARSHOT OF A CHILD.
YOU DON'T REALLY DO
THOSE THINGS, DO YOU?
DON'T PAY ATTENTION TO FERRIS.
SHE... IS A MASTER
OF EXAGGERATION.
- IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU, MA'AM.
- WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT
WHAT HE'D HAVE TO LEARN
IN ORDER TO HELP US
RESCUE HIS LITTLE FRIEND.
- WE DON'T DARE RISK
THE BOY'S PURITY
BY LEAVING HIS
INSTRUCTION TO A PERVERT.
- COME, FOLLOW ME, ARUA.
- I WOULD BE HONORED TO,
MISS FERRIS.
- ( yawning )
GOOD OL' FASHIONED
MARTIAL ARTS.
BETWEEN THAT AND
HIS ALPHA STIGMA,
KID MAY HAVE A SHOT.
HELL, HE MIGHT BE A
FORCE IN HIS OWN RIGHT
BEFORE IT'S ALL SAID AND DONE.
- ( Arua screaming in pain )
- IF HE SURVIVES
FERRIS, NATURALLY.
- Ryner: ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S WHERE SHE'S BEING HELD.
NOW WE DEFINITELY WANT ARUA
TO BE THE KNIGHT IN
SHINING ARMOR OF THIS STORY.
THAT IS, OF COURSE,
IF YOU'RE SURE.
YES, I'M MORE SURE
THAN I'VE EVER BEEN.
SO LET'S GO.
IT'S THE LEAST I CAN DO
FOR KUKU AFTER WHAT SHE DID.
- YOU MAY NOT SURVIVE.
STOP TRYING TO
TALK ME OUT OF THIS!
I'M GOING IN THERE, OKAY!
- RUSHED THOUGH IT WAS,
YOU'VE BEEN TRAINED EXPERTLY.
I TAKE FULL CREDIT
FOR YOU NOT IN ANY WAY
RESEMBLING THE FILTHY OLD MAN.
- OLD MAN? I HOPE THAT'S
NOT A JAB AT YOURS TRULY.
- IF THE SHOE FITS,
WHEN IT COMES TO VILE,
LASCIVIOUS NE'ER-DO-WELLS,
YOU'VE HELD THE HIGHEST
RANK FOR SEVERAL CENTURIES.
- I HAVEN'T BEEN ALIVE
FOR SEVERAL CENTURIES!
- ( footsteps shuffling )
- Ferris: YOU'D THINK
THEY'D BE WAITING IN AMBUSH.
- NOT IF GIVEN HALF A CHANCE
AT MAKING FOOLS OF US.
- OH, DON'T FRET.
WE HAVE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
THE AILECRONE SCYTHE
IS TERRIBLY FAMISHED.
I INTEND TO GLUT IT.
- IT MUST BE SAID,
YOU CERTAINLY TOOK YOUR TIME.
- IS THE GIRL SAFE OR ISN'T SHE?
- YOU DON'T THINK WE'D HARM
SO VALUABLE A HOSTAGE?
- WE DON'T TYPICALLY
RESORT TO USING LIVES
AS BARGAINING CHIPS,
BUT MY DEAR BROTHER INSISTED
THAT THIS SITUATION
WAS DELICATE.
- YOU TWO CAN'T HOPE
TO WIN AGAINST US.
HAVE YOU ALREADY FORGOTTEN
WHAT HAPPENED LAST TIME?
- INDEED. YOUR POWER
IS ALL THE MORE REASON
FOR US TO HAVE
CALLED YOU HERE.
AT THE RISK OF
SOUNDING FORWARD,
WE'D LIKE TO ASK THAT YOU PUT
THAT POWER TO EXCELLENT USE
IN SERVITUDE TO THE
GREAT KINGDOM OF GASTARK.
- YOU KIDDING ME?
- VERY SOON THE WHOLE WORLD
WILL STAND IN THE SHADOW
OF GASTARK'S BANNER.
A WORLD UNITED UNDER THE
AUSPICES OF A VISIONARY KING,
FREE OF DISCRIMINATION,
FREE OF STRIFE,
WHERE TEARS FLOW NO LONGER
AND HAPPINESS IS
THE ORDER OF THE DAY.
SUCH IS THE MIND OF
LEFAHL EDEA, OUR KING,
WHO POSSESSES
NOT ONLY THE DESIRE
BUT THE MEANS
TO SHAPE THAT WORLD.
- ( amused chuckle )
TO HEAR YOU PUT IT LIKE
THAT, HE DOESN'T SOUND SO BAD.
IT'S EXTREMELY TEMPTING...
- GO ON.
- I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORD IT.
"A WORLD WHERE HAPPINESS
IS THE ORDER OF THE DAY. "
IF THAT REALLY IS YOUR
KING'S ULTIMATE GOAL,
MAYBE JOINING YOU GUYS WOULDN'T
BE SUCH A TERRIBLE IDEA,
WHICH IS TO SAY YOU DO
PAINT A VERY COMPELLING PICTURE.
- ( whispering )
ARE YOU MAD?
- DO YOU TAKE OUR HAND
IN FRIENDSHIP?
- NOT SO FAST.
IF WORLD PEACE IS REALLY
WHAT ALL THIS HAS BEEN ABOUT,
WHY DOES "ALL THIS" LOOK LIKE
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO ABOLISH?
YOU DIDN'T EXACTLY COME
BY THOSE HERO RELICS
BY SOWING HAPPINESS
IN YOUR WAKE.
HELL, YOU ROUSED
AN ALPHA STIGMA
JUST TO TRY TO
HARNESS HIS STRENGTH.
FOR PEACE-MONGERS, YOU'VE GOT
A LOT OF BLOOD ON YOUR HANDS.
IF THAT'S THE KIND OF
THING I CAN LOOK FORWARD TO
BY "USING MY POWER IN
SERVITUDE TO GASTARK,"
YOU CAN TELL YOUR PRECIOUS
KING TO KISS MY ASS.
YOUR COUNTRY WILL
NEVER BE MY HOME.
NOT SO LONG AS IT TREATS
ALPHA STIGMAS LIKE OUTCASTS,
OR WORSE, AS WEAPONS IN SOME
HYPOCRITICAL MISSION OF PEACE.
- HOW DARE YOU?
- IT'S EASY ENOUGH TO HURL
CLICHES AND PLATITUDES
AT US FOR WHAT WE DO,
BUT THE REALITY OF OUR SITUATION
DOESN'T ADMIT OF SIMPLICITY.
COLLATERAL DAMAGE AMASSES
IN REVOLUTIONS OF ANY SCALE.
IT'S NOT AS THOUGH WE
ENJOY HAVING TO KILL.
THE LIFE OF EACH HUMAN BEING
WE'RE COMPELLED TO SNUFF OUT
WEIGHS ON OUR CONSCIENCE.
- NOT A FRACTION AS MUCH
AS IT OUGHT TO!
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW
MANY PEOPLE I'VE KILLED.
HOW MANY INNOCENT LIVES
I'VE "SNUFFED OUT"
IN THRALL TO THIS DAMN CURSE.
I USED TO THINK THAT
CLINGING TO LIFE WAS EVIL,
THAT I WAS DEATH INCARNATE.
BUT DEATH, ARUA IS NOT.
HE HASN'T KILLED ANYONE YET.
AND WITH LUCK I CAN KEEP HIM
FROM EVER CROSSING THAT LINE.
THE ONLY THING YOU SEE IN HIM
IS EITHER SOMETHING TO HARNESS,
OR SOMETHING TO ERADICATE.
NEITHER OF YOU
SEE IN HIM WHAT I DO.
NAMELY THAT HE'S HUMAN.
- AS NOBLE AS THE
SENTIMENT IS IN THEORY
YOU COULD SEARCH
THE ENTIRE WORLD
AND NEVER ONCE
HEAR IT ECHOED.
- AH, BUT THE PLACE
I CALL HOME
GIVES THE LIE TO YOUR WORDS.
THE KING OF ROLAND
ISN'T LIKE YOUR KING.
HE DOESN'T JUST PAY LIP
SERVICE TO THE IDEA OF PEACE.
HE ACTUALLY BELIEVES
THE MEANS AND ENDS
OUGHT TO RESEMBLE
ONE ANOTHER.
AND WHEN I TALK ABOUT ENDS,
I MEAN A PEOPLE'S REVOLUTION
THAT WILL MAKE EVERY ROCK,
EVERY PEBBLE IN
THE REALM, QUAKE.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, HE'S
DELUDED ENOUGH TO THINK
IT CAN BE ACHIEVED
WITHOUT VIOLENCE.
A FLEA CAN'T DIE ON HIS WATCH
BUT THAT HE'S
RACKED WITH GUILT
AND BLAMES HIMSELF FOR IT.
THAT WHY, FOR ALL HIS AIRS, I
ALIGN MYSELF TO THE MAN PROUDLY.
BECAUSE IN THE WORLD
HE INTENDS TO BUILD,
EVERY LAST ONE OF US MATTERS.
- YOU'RE NOT SO NAIVE
AS TO THINK HE NEEDN'T
CRACK A FEW HEADS
IN THE PROCESS?
KINGS DON'T CARRY THE WEIGHT
OF THEIR VISION LIGHTLY.
THE ROAD TO PEACE IS
FRAUGHT WITH DILEMMAS, YES?
- TRUST ME, IF HE STARTS
FOLLOWING YOUR KING'S EXAMPLE
I'LL MAKE SURE THE FIRST
HEAD CRACKED IS HIS OWN.
- ( Kuu sneers )
- SO NEGOTIATIONS
HAVE BROKEN DOWN?
- I HATE TO BREAK IT
TO YOU, PAL,
BUT WE WERE NEVER NEGOTIATING.
WE'RE HERE TO GET
THE GIRL BACK.
ARE YOU READY?
- HIS WORDS DID HAVE ME
ENSNARED THERE FOR A BIT.
A WORLD WITHOUT STRIFE
WOULD BE A LOVELY ONE.
- DON'T RULE ANYTHING
OUT, PARTNER.
- PLEASE. NOW'S NOT THE TIME.
LET'S GO.
- OF COURSE. RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- NOW, KUU!
( screaming )
HONESTLY, THIS ONE
I WILL ENJOY.
- I OFFER UP A CONTRACT TO
BEAR THE WICKED SPIRIT BEAST
THAT SLEEPS
WITHIN THE EARTH!
- ( explosion booms )
- IT ISN'T TOO LATE TO
CHANGE YOUR MIND, YOU KNOW.
COME NOW, WON'T YOU RECONSIDER?
- LIKE HELL.
WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER!
- I HOPE YOU'RE NOT OPERATING
UNDER THE ASSUMPTION
THAT A RULE FRAGMENT CAN
BE TAKEN DOWN SO EASILY.
- IZUCHI!
- ( Sui gasps )
- ICE WALL.
- BURN HER!
- NO, YOU DON'T!
- FROM THE WEST I CALL
THE EMPTY, THE FORMATION,
- WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER!
- Sui: THE YANG!
- Ryner: IZUCHI!
- I BRING FORTH THE BRILLIANCE.
( screams )
WHAT IN THE...
I'VE LOST.
- Kuu: THEY'VE AN ALLY
IN HIDING.
- WELL CRAP, THERE GOES
THAT PLAN.
I THOUGHT WE'D GET 'EM
BEFORE THEY FIGURED IT OUT.
OPERATION SURPRISE ATTACK
HAS OFFICIALLY FALLEN FLAT.
CALL THE BOY DOWN.
- ARUA!
- Arua: YES. SIR!
- MEDDLING WITH THE VERY
STRUCTURE OF YOUR SPELLS.
AN INTERESTING MOVE,
HAVING THE BOY STRIKE
FROM OFFSTAGE
WHILE YOUR OWN INVOCATION MERELY
DIRECTED THE PATH OF HIS ENERGY.
- BIT OF A CHEAP TRICK, GRANTED,
BUT WAS IT THAT OBVIOUS?
SHEESH. MAYBE I REALLY
SHOULD RECONSIDER.
- IMAGINE A PAIR OF ALPHA
STIGMAS BANKING ON DECEIT.
I'M RATHER
DISAPPOINTED WITH MYSELF
FOR NOT HAVING PIECED TOGETHER
YOUR INELEGANT
LITTLE RUSE SOONER.
IT WAS TERRIBLY DISORIENTING
AT FIRST, I'LL ADMIT.
- SO SHOULD I FEEL
HONORED OR INSULTED?
- I DO BELIEVE I'VE REACHED
AN EPIPHANY IN THIS BATTLE.
I UNDERSTAND WHY YOUR KIND
ARE IN SUCH DISCORD
WITH HUMANITY.
FOR MOST, YOU'RE THE STUFF
OF MIND-SHATTERING NIGHTMARE.
BELIEVE ME, WE DON'T
NEED YOU TO TELL US THAT.
BUT BETWEEN LIVING IN FEAR
OF HARMING OUR LOVED ONES
AND THE CONSTANT
WORRY OF BEING HOUNDED
LIKE ANIMALS BY STRANGERS...
- I'M GONNA GO OUT ON
A LIMB FOR A SECOND
AND SUGGEST THAT
MAYBE THE LARGER SHARE
OF THAT NIGHTMARE IS OUR OWN.
- THEN WHY NOT BE
KIND ENOUGH TO DIE?
HAVING TO FIGHT YOU
AGAIN IN THE FUTURE
IS NOT A MERRY PROSPECT.
- I'VE GOT A BETTER IDEA.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GO THE HELL HOME?
- KUU?
- KUKU!
- YOU DIRTY SON OF A BITCH.
- YOU WERE RIGHT ABOUT OUR
HAVING NO HOPE AGAINST YOU.
SADLY, THAT LEAVES US NO CHOICE
BUT TO BRING THIS
MEETING TO A FINISH.
ALONG WITH THIS SWEET
LITTLE THING'S LIFE.
- PLEASE, NO!
- DAMN IT!
- TOO LATE FOR THAT, I'M AFRAID!
- LEAVE HER ALONE!
- ( claw slashing )
- (Sui screaming )
- ( Sui grunting in pain )
( panting )
- IMPOSSIBLE. IT CAN'T BE.
( gasps )
- ( Sui grunting )
- THIS CANNOT BE HAPPENING.
ONLY A RULE FRAGMENT
LIKE BROTHER LIR'S
COULD'VE CAUSED SO
MUCH DAMAGE SO QUICKLY...
- Miran: RULE FRAGMENT?
ANOTHER TERM TO GROUP
WITH "HERO RELICS"
I ASSUME.
INTERESTING.
TWO CONCEPTS ALTOGETHER
FOREIGN TO ME.
- IT'S HIM.
THE MAN WE FOUGHT IN NELPHA.
- WHAT THE HELL
IS HE DOING IN RUNA?
- Kuu: SUI! SUI, GET UP!
- JUST GET OUT OF HERE.
LEAVE ME.
- SO, YOU TWO ARE
THE TROUBLEMAKERS
WHO'VE INCITED RUNA TO DISSENT.
AMBITIOUS... BUT FOR NAUGHT.
LET THERE BE DARKNESS!
- WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER!
IZUCHI!
- YOU IDIOT.
WHY ON EARTH WOULD
YOU HAVE DEFLECTED THAT?
- CALL IT A FAVOR,
PAY ME BACK ANOTHER TIME.
NOW GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE!
- Miran: I MUST CONFESS
THIS SITUATION
DOES NOT SIT WELL WITH ME.
I HAD THE PLEASURE
OF OVERHEARING
THE BULK OF YOUR
IDEOLOGICAL EXCHANGE.
I'M AFRAID THERE'S
NO ROOM FOR DOUBT.
THE TWO OF YOU CERTAINLY
HAIL FROM ROLAND.
WHICH MAKES YOUR BOLD
DEFENSE OF THE INTERLOPERS
DISTURBINGLY SUGGESTIVE.
- THE THREE OF YOU SHARE
MORE IN COMMON THAN WE DO.
WE'RE NOT ASSASSINS.
WE DON'T MOW DOWN
WHOEVER'S IN OUR WAY.
- ALPHA STIGMA.
HERO RELICS.
WHAT TANGLED WEB
DOES HIS MAJESTY WEAVE
BEYOND MY KNOWLEDGE?
- ER, HEY. HOLD ON.
YOU'RE JUST WALKING AWAY?
- THERE'S NO NEED
FOR ME TO STAY
WHEN OUR BATTLE CAN JUST
AS EASILY BE POSTPONED.
- IF I MAY BE SO BRAZEN AS
TO OFFER YOU BOTH MY INSIGHT,
WOULD YOU SCOFF AT ITS
TAKING SHAPE AS A WARNING?
- I DON'T GUESS SO?
- GOOD.
I'M SO GLAD TO HEAR IT.
- YOU JUST SUGGESTED
THAT I MOW DOWN
THOSE WHO STAND IN MY WAY.
BUT ASK YOURSELF ONE QUESTION.
"WHAT SORT OF WORLD WOULD
BE LEFT WERE I TO HAVE MY WAY?"
- THE SIMPLE ANSWER TO WHICH IS
A WORLD PEOPLED ENTIRELY BY
THOSE WHOSE LIVES I DEEM
CONVENIENT TO MY PURPOSES.
YET...
IF AN ALPHA STIGMA
WERE TO HAVE ITS WAY,
WOULD NOT THE
LANDSCAPE LEFT IN THE WAKE
OF SUCH UNQUENCHABLE BLOODLUST
RESEMBLE IN MOST PARTICULARS
MY OWN IDEAL WORLD?
THINK ABOUT IT.
HUMAN BEINGS SUSTAIN THEMSELVES
ON THE BLOODIEST OF CONFLICTS.
ALWAYS HAVE. IT'S PART OF
THEIR ESSENTIAL NATURE.
HAPPINESS WILL NEVER
BE THE ORDER OF THE DAY.
HARDSHIP AND UGLINESS RULE. AH.
FORGIVE ME, I DO LIKE
TO PRATTLE ON.
OF COURSE YOU KNOW ALL
TOO WELL THE SALIENT FEATURES
OF THE HUMAN RACE.
IF IN SO DOING I HAVE
SPOKEN OUT OF TURN,
I IMPLORE YOUR INDULGENCE.
- I SHOULD OFFER YOU
OUR GRATITUDE.
WITHOUT YOU, WE COULDN'T
HAVE RESCUED KUKU.
- YOU DON'T SUPPOSE THAT I
CAME HERE TO LEND YOU MY AID?
- WELL NO, I'M NOT THAT
MUCH OF AN IDIOT.
EVEN SO, THE TIMING OF
YOUR ATTACK WAS...
WELL, LET'S JUST CALL IT A
VERY HAPPY COINCIDENCE.
- SUCH A PITY.
BUT, YOUR EXISTENCE
PRESENTS MORE QUESTIONS
THAN I'D LIKE TO ANSWER.
IT MAY JUST PROVE EASIER
SIMPLY TO KILL YOU.
- ( gate clangs shut )
- KUKU! WAKE UP!
- ARUA!
( crying )
- SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
- WELL, ONE THING'S FOR SURE.
IT'S FAR TOO
DANGEROUS FOR US
TO BRING THEM
ALONG ON OUR QUEST.
THAT'S IT!
I KNOW JUST THE PLACE
TO TAKE 'EM!
- Ryner: YEAH. PERFECT.
( chuckles smugly )
- IT'S HIGH TIME
TO SET OUT A LIGHT.
- IS THERE NOTHING SO TRIVIAL
THAT YOU WON'T AGONIZE OVER IT?
- TOO MANY THINGS HAVE
BEGUN TO CHANGE.
RUNA IS BEHAVING STRANGELY.
RUMOR HAS IT THAT NELPHA
STANDS ON THE PRECIPICE
OF A VIOLENT REVOLUTION.
TOO MANY THINGS CONVERGE
IN FAVOR OF A CONFLICT.
WAR FAST APPROACHES THE
CONDITION OF INEVITABILITY
DESPITE OVERWHELMING
POPULAR OUTCRY AGAINST IT.
- WAR IS WAR. PEOPLE ARE
PEOPLE, FOR THAT MATTER.
POPULAR OUTCRY MEANS NOTHING.
HUMANS DESPOIL ONE ANOTHER.
THEY FIGHT TO ESSAY
THEIR IDEALS.
AND THOSE,
REGARDLESS OF SHAPE,
FOUNDATION OR SUBSTANCE,
CONVERGE IN THE PERSON
THE KING.
- AND I WOULD ANSWER
THOSE IDEALS,
FULFILL ALL THEIR HOPES
AND THEIR DREAMS
BY FORGING A WORLD IN WHICH
THE LOWLIEST PERSON
MAY THRIVE.
WHERE WAR NEEDN'T BE
THE MEANS TO BRINGING
SUCH IDEALS TO FRUITION.
WHERE, IF ONE SO CHOOSES,
AFTERNOON NAPS CAN
BE TAKEN AT LEISURE.
- YOU STILL CLING
TO THE FANTASY?
EVEN KNOWING IT TO BE
THE DREAM OF A MONSTER?
EVEN KNOWING AS YOU DO
THE VISION'S INHERENT FLAW?
- Sion: IT SHOULD STILL
BE IN SIGHT.
I REFUSE TO ACCEPT THAT
THE GOAL IS AN ILLUSION.
AND YET...
YET...
I'VE A PROMISE TO KEEP.
ONE I DARE NOT
THINK OF FORFEITING,
NOT AND LIVE WITH MYSELF.
IT IS HIGH TIME
TO SET OUT A LIGHT.
YES. A LIGHT.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: YOU KNOW, I JUST
REALIZED SOMETHING.
ALL THESE ROYAL
PAIN-IN-THE-ASS SITUATIONS
I KEEP GETTING THROWN
HEADFIRST INTO ARE JUST THAT.
ROYAL. DAMN YOU, SION!
I SWEAR TO YOU, ONE DAY
YOU'LL KNOW FIRSTHAND
JUST HOW MUCH ALL THIS CRAP
YOU'VE PUT ME THROUGH SUCKS!