- ( footsteps approaching )
- AH, EXCELLENT.
SO YOU SURVIVED, THEN.
- WONDERFUL TO SEE YOU, TOO.
IT SEEMS I'VE RETURNED A HERO.
IF ONE HAS A MIND
TO PAY CREDENCE
TO RUMORS AND HEARSAY, THAT IS.
- I DON'T.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- A SUMMONS FROM HOUSE OF ERIS
IS IGNORED AT ONE'S PERIL.
- HE COMES AT MY BEHEST.
- Ferris: BROTHER.
- I DON'T BELIEVE WE'VE HAD
THE PLEASURE
OF A FORMAL
INTRODUCTION AS OF YET.
MY NAME IS LUCILE ERIS, I AM
THE HEAD OF THE ERIS FAMILY.
MY PURPOSE HERE IS SIMPLE.
I MERELY INTEND
TO SCRUTINIZE YOUR FEELINGS
AND JUDGE YOUR RESPONSE.
- FEELINGS?
TO WHAT END?
- I WILL ASK
A VOLLEY OF QUESTIONS.
EACH ONE AFTER ITS OWN MANNER
FOLLOWING THE SKEIN
OF A COMMON THREAD.
ANSWER SINCERELY.
BEFORE WE PROCEED, HOWEVER,
I REQUIRE YOUR CONSENT
TO THE FOLLOWING CONDITION.
SHOULD YOUR ANSWERS STRIKE ME
AS UNSUITABLE, I'LL KILL YOU.
- ( gasps )
- AS A COURTESY, THOUGH,
DEATH WILL COME QUICKLY.
THAT SPLENDID HEAD WILL SCARCELY
FEEL ITSELF LEAVING THE CRADLE
OF YOUR SHOULDERS.
JUDGING FROM YOUR FACE,
YOU ARE A BIT PUZZLED.
SEE, THE FORTUNES OF ROYALTY
ABIDE WITH THIS HOUSE.
- I UNDERSTAND.
THE ROYAL PROTECTORATE FAMILY
WOULD TEST THE FITNESS
OF ROLAND'S KING-TO-BE.
- Lucile: SUCH IS THE TRIAL
ALL DESCENDANTS OF THIS REALM'S
FOUNDER MUST ENDURE
WHO SEEK TO ATTAIN THE THRONE.
ESPECIALLY LOWBORN USURPERS
LIKE YOURSELF.
- OH? THEN I AGREE TO THE TEST.
ASK OF ME WHATEVER YOU DESIRE.
- GOOD. I DIDN'T ANTICIPATE
YOU'D RESIST.
COME WITH ME, PLEASE.
- YOU WOULD BRAVE THE HORRORS
OF BATTLE ONLY TO FORFEIT
YOUR LIFE IN CLOSE QUARTERS?
- MY LIFE WAS FORFEIT LONG AGO.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( kids laughing )
- STAND ASIDE! EVERYONE CLEAR
A PATH FOR HIS LORDSHIP!
- ( people chattering )
- SO I DON'T IMAGINE
YOU'LL BE HOME EARLY, HUH?
- BELIEVE ME, I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I'VE GOT TO STICK AROUND
AND MAKE THE SURE
THE NEW PRISONER
GETS SETTLED IN RIGHT TODAY.
- NATURALLY.
NO MATTER WHAT HE DID,
IT'S A PITY HE
WOUND UP IN THERE.
- Guard: YOU SAID IT.
STEP THROUGH THOSE DOORS
AND A BODY CAN BID THE SUN
A FOND FARE-THEE-WELL...
UNTIL THEIR DYING DAY.
- HOW OLD IS HE?
- YOUNG YET. NOT EVEN TWENTY.
- Ryner: GUARD?
HEY, GUARD?
- Guard: GOOD MORNING.
SO, WHAT'LL I HAVE
THE PLEASURE OF FETCHING
FOR OUR ESTEEMED GUEST TODAY,
A GOOSE DOWN PILLOW?
AN ERMINE LINED CLOAK?
- I'M GOOD.
- SERIOUSLY, SO LONG
AS IT'S WITHIN REASON,
YOU SHOULD JUST
FEEL FREE TO ASK.
- PAPER AND PENCIL THEN.
AND YOU'RE FAMILIAR
WITH THE ROYAL SPECIAL
MILITARY ACADEMY, RIGHT?
I'D LIKE TO BORROW SOME BOOKS
FROM THEIR LIBRARY
IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND GOING THERE
AND PICKING THEM UP FOR ME.
- BOOKS, HUH? SEEMS LIKE A
FAIRLY REASONABLE REQUEST.
- REALLY? EVEN IF I HAPPEN
TO HAVE A LIST
OF SAY 30 TITLES, OR SO?
- THIRTY? ARE YOU KIDDING?
- HUH...
YOU KNOW, UH, FLIES IN HERE,
THEY MIGHT BE KIND OF
HARD TO COME BY.
THIS CELL KEEPS OUT
JUST ABOUT EVERYTHING.
SO...
OKAY. MAN THIS IS TOUGH.
OH, COME ON!
( grunting )
HUH. GUESS WE'RE SHARING.
- Guard: I'VE BROUGHT THEM.
- AH, THERE'S A SIGHT
FOR SORE EYES.
- LOOK, I UNDERSTAND
YOU'VE GOT TO PASS THE TIME,
BUT THIS IS STARTING
TO GET OUT OF HAND.
- ABOUT THAT...I HATE TO ASK,
BUT WOULD YOU CURSE MY NAME
IF I ADDED ANOTHER TEN BOOKS
TO MY LIST?
- HUH? HOW DO YOU STILL
NOT HAVE ENOUGH?
SOMEBODY'S UP
WAY PAST THEIR BEDTIME.
- HMM? UH, YEAH.
- DON'T TAKE THIS
THE WRONG WAY, KID,
BUT MOST FOLKS WOULD JUST
CURL UP AND STARE BLANKLY
AT THE CEILING ALL DAY
AFTER A FEW MONTHS
STUCK IN A SITUATION LIKE YOURS.
HELL, I'VE SEEN GUYS TWICE AS
ENERGETIC GO QUIET AFTER A WEEK.
BEING LOCKED IN A DARK CELL
DOES SOMETHING TO A MAN.
POINT IS...KEEP IT UP
YOU'RE GOING TO HURT YOUR EYES.
HERE'S TODAY'S LOT.
- PERFECT. THANK YOU.
- I'LL HAVE TO PLUNDER THE ROYAL
COLLECTION BEFORE LONG
AT THE RATE
YOU'VE BEEN READING.
IF I DIDN'T KNOW BETTER
I'D THINK YOU WERE
TRYING TO TURN THIS CELL
INTO A HALL OF RECORDS.
- YOUR LITTLE GIRL EVER GET
OVER HER CASE OF SNIFFLES?
- OH, YEAH, GOOD AS NEW,
AS A MATTER OF FACT.
AND JUST WAIT'LL YOU HEAR THIS.
THE STINKER TOOK HER
VERY FIRST STEPS THIS MORNING!
- OH, SO THAT'S IT.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE BEAMING.
- YOU CANNOT IMAGINE THE JOY
OF SEEING YOUR LITTLE PRINCESS
CROSS THE THRESHOLD
INTO WOMANHOOD.
THEY GROW UP SO FAST.
( sobbing )
- YEAH. I DON'T THINK
HER CHILDHOOD'S
PASSED YOU BY JUST YET.
BUT YOU KNOW,
IF THIS IS HOW YOU ARE
WHEN SHE LEARNS TO WALK,
IMAGINE THE WRECK YOU'LL BE
WHEN SHE GETS MARRIED.
- ( grunting )
I'M NOT LETTING HER MARRY!
YOU'RE TRYING TO STEAL HER
AWAY FROM ME, AREN'T YOU?
OVER MY DEAD BODY!
- GET A HOLD OF YOURSELF.
TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
NOBODY'S STEALING ANYONE.
BUT THAT TEMPER'S GOING TO
COST YOU YOUR HEALTH SOMEDAY
IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL.
AND YOU DON'T WANT
YOUR BABY GIRL GROWING UP
ON A BATTLEFIELD, AM I RIGHT?
- WHAT KIND OF QUESTION
IS THAT TO ASK SOMEONE
WITH A KID?
OF COURSE I DON'T WANT HER
TO GROW UP ON A BATTLEFIELD.
- NO ONE DOES.
BUT IT HAPPENS MORE OFTEN
THAN YOU'D THINK.
- ( shivering )
( grunting )
WOW. SOMETHING
REALLY SMELLS GOOD.
- OH, YEAH. GOOD NOSE.
TODAY'S A CHEESE AND GARLIC
KIND OF DAY.
THOUGHT I'D PAMPER MYSELF.
- THAT'S A VERY CRUEL THING
TO WAVE IN FRONT OF SOMEONE
WHO LIVES ON SOUP.
- IF MY WIFE'S BUSINESS AFFORDS
ME THE OCCASIONAL LUXURY,
THAT'S MY CONCERN.
YOU'VE GOT MEAT!
- SO, UH, THE TWO OF YOU
WORK TOGETHER?
- YEAH, I HELP HER
SELL VEGETABLES
AT THE MORNING MARKET MOST DAYS
BECAUSE I DON'T REALLY CARE
TO HAVE HER
WORK IN THE STALL ALONE
WHEN SHE'S GOT
OUR DAUGHTER IN TOW.
HUH, SOUNDS LIKE
A HARD LIFE, I KNOW.
I'D CHOOSE IT OVER
BEING A SOLIDER ANY DAY.
I'VE HAD MORE THAN MY FILL
OF MILITARY LIFE.
I WATCHED SOME OF MY BEST
FRIENDS DIE IN THE LAST WAR.
NO TELLING HOW I CAME
THROUGH IT ALL INTACT.
- I'M SORRY.
- THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
I TURNED DOWN A CAREER OFFICER'S
PAY TO TAKE THIS JOB.
IT'S FAR FROM GLAMOROUS,
BUT I HAVE NO REGRETS.
- I'LL BET.
- ( birds chirping )
- ( both chuckling )
- WHO'S MY GIRL?
- (Ryner snoring )
- Sion: INTERESTING.
THIS IS THE LIFE
YOU'VE CHOSEN, IS IT?
GET ALL THE REST YOU CAN,
MY LETHARGIC FRIEND.
CHANGE IS IN THE WIND.
- ( yawning )
( sighs )
- DON'T THINK I'LL EVER
FIGURE YOU OUT, LITTLE BUDDY.
THERE'S A WHOLE WIDE
WORLD OUT THERE
TO MAKE A PARADISE OUT OF,
AND YOU KEEP SPINNING AWAY
IN THIS LITTLE DUMP.
IT'S JUST NOT HEALTHY.
YOU'RE FIXATED.
( scoffs )
( Ryner yelling )
( panting ) OKAY, MY LIFE
JUST FLASHED BEFORE MY EYES.
IF I DON'T CLEAN THIS PLACE UP
I'LL BE BURIED ALIVE.
WELL, MAYBE I'LL TAKE
A NAP FIRST.
I'LL GET STARTED
AFTER BREAKFAST.
WELL, SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
SO WHAT'S ON THE MENU TODAY?
HEY, WHAT'S WITH
THE GRIM MOUTH?
THAT'S NOT YOUR
USUAL EXPRESSION.
WHAT, DID YOU AND THE WIFE
HAVE ANOTHER ONE
OF YOUR FAMOUS SPATS...
OR DID DADDY'S LITTLE GIRL
BRING HOME HER FIRST BOYFRIEND?
- OH, FOR CRYING OUT LOUD
SHE'S BARELY EVEN
THREE YEARS OLD!
- HEY, TIMES AREN'T WHAT
THEY USED TO BE, BUDDY.
THREE YEARS OLD IS THE NEW 14.
- LOOK, WHATEVER SICK WORLD
YOU CALL HOME,
MY DAUGHTER IS
NOT A PART OF IT.
- EVERY PARENT TELLS
THEMSELVES THAT.
- ENOUGH!
ANYWAY, THAT'S NOT
WHY I LOOK GRIM.
- SO WHAT IS EATING YOU, THEN?
AND SPEAKING OF WHICH,
WHERE'S BREAKFAST?
- ( keys jingling )
- IT'S OKAY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY IT.
MY EXECUTION WAS PRETTY MUCH
AN INEVITABILITY.
THE POWERS THAT BE WERE BOUND
TO FIGURE KEEPING ME LOCKED UP
WAS TOO RISKY.
I CAN'T SAY I BLAME THEM.
TWO YEARS WAS GENEROUS.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO.
I DON'T SUPPOSE YOU COULD
HELP ME CARRY THE RESEARCH PAPER
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON?
- I HAVE STRICT ORDERS TO SEE
TO IT THAT YOU LEAVE THE CELL
EMPTY-HANDED.
- OH. RIGHT. WELL, I SUPPOSE
WHERE I'M HEADED I DON'T
EXACTLY NEED ANY OF THIS STUFF.
- ( sighs )
- COME ON, WE BOTH KNEW
THAT THIS DAY HAD TO COME.
LET'S GET IT OVER WITH.
- ( sobbing )
- GOODBYE, THEN.
BEST OF LUCK.
- ( girl humming )
- HEY! WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- BYE!
- BYE-BYE, BAD GUY!
- ( chuckling )
- Ferris: RYNER LUTE?
- WELL, IT'S BEEN REAL NICE.
TAKE CARE, BUDDY.
AM I ALLOWED TO
ASK A QUESTION?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO KNOW, PERVERT?
- HUH?
UH, OKAY, THAT MAKES
TWO QUESTIONS...
THE FIRST BEING WHERE THE IDEA
OF CALLING YOURS TRULY
A PERVERT COMES FROM?
- YOUR COUNTENANCE.
THAT AND THE PERSONAL HISTORY
I'VE BEEN ABLE TO UNEARTH.
SORRY TO HAVE ASKED.
THE SECOND QUESTION IS
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF I MADE A BREAK FOR IT?
- I TAKE IT
THAT'S NOT RHETORICAL.
- SORRY, NO.
I HAVE A PROMISE TO KEEP.
WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER!
IZUCHI!
- ( both grunting )
- WOW. THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
BETTER FOCUS.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE
THIS ONE A BIT MORE SERIOUSLY
THAN I THOUGHT.
- OH, SO ALL THAT JUST NOW
WAS A PRACTICE RUN?
- YEAH, JUST FEELING OUT
MY OPPONENT.
- AH, YES. I CAN SEE
WHY HE WANTS YOU.
- HUH?
- EN GARDE!
- WAIT, HOLD ON!
I OFFER UP THIS CONTRACT
TO BEAR THE WICKED BEAST
THAT SLEEPS WITHIN THE EARTH!
WHATEVER MAGIC YOU'RE USING
TO KEEP UP WITH MINE,
IT'S VERY UN-SPORTSMAN LIKE!
- ( grunting continues )
- OKAY, NEVER MIND.
SHE'S NOT USING MAGIC!
WAIT!
WHAT I SEEK IS THE WATER CLOUD.
MIZUCHI!
- TELL ME.
WHY DID YOU HOLD BACK?
- WHO SAYS I WAS
HOLDING BACK, HUH?
- DON'T PLAY DUMB.
ANY MAGICIAN WORTHY OF THE NAME
WOULD HAVE DEPLOYED FIRE MAGIC
IN THAT SCENARIO.
I'D HAVE HAD NO COUNTERATTACK
FOR IT AND YOU WOULD HAVE WON.
- YEAH, AND THERE'D HAVE ALSO
BEEN AN EXCELLENT CHANCE OF YOU
BEING SCORCHED TO CINDERS.
YOU CAN FORGIVE ME
IF I CAN'T BRING MYSELF
TO MAR A PRETTY FACE.
- AH! THAT'S IT, IS IT?
- YOUR TWISTED,
SEX-OBSESSED LITTLE MIND
COULDN'T BEAR THE THOUGHT
OF RAVAGING ME
WITHOUT ENSURING THAT I WAS IN
ABSOLUTELY PRISTINE CONDITION,
AND SO YOU SURRENDERED
THE VICTORY. VERY NOBLE OF YOU.
- UH, YOU'RE READING
WAY TOO MUCH INTO THINGS.
- QUIT DAWDLING. WE HAVE
AN AUDIENCE WITH THE KING.
- YEAH, SURE. I'LL JUST STROLL
WILLINGLY TO MY OWN EXECUTION.
THAT SOUNDS FUN.
- STAY BEHIND IF YOU LIKE.
YOUR REGRETS MAKE NO
DIFFERENCE WHATSOEVER TO ME.
- RIGHT.
DAMN IT!
- ( echoing )
- ( Ryner exclaims )
WHAT IN THE WORLD'S
COME OVER THIS PLACE?
- TO BID YOU A FAIR WELCOME
IN THE COURTLY MANNER, HI.
- OKAY. THAT'S IT. WAKE ME
WHEN THIS MAKES SENSE.
GOODNIGHT.
- I REMIND YOU, YOU'RE IN
THE PRESENCE OF ROYALTY.
- GOOD A PLACE TO SLEEP AS ANY!
- SO, THEN...
I TRUST HE BEHAVED WELL?
- I'M AFRAID
HE'S QUITE DEPRAVED, SIR.
I WOULD NOT SET HIM FREE,
BUT THEN I AM NOT OF A MIND
TO BEAR HIS FUTURE CRIMES
ON MY CONSCIENCE.
- BUT...
- IT MUST BE SAID THAT HE DID
TREAT ME RESPECTFULLY
IN THE COURSE OF OUR BOUT.
- EXCELLENT.
ON YOUR FEET, RYNER.
I HAVE NEWS ABOUT KIEFER.
- HOW EXCITING FOR YOU.
- Sion: SHE'S NO LONGER WITH US.
- ( gasping )
- BUT NOT DEAD.
- SNEAKY RAT.
- SHE TOOK HER
LEAVE OF ROLAND
AND BECAME A
CITIZEN OF THE WORLD.
ASKING THAT I KEEP AN
EYE ON YOU IN HER ABSENCE.
BUT I DIDN'T ARRANGE YOUR
RELEASE TO KEEP YOU ABREAST
OF KIEFER'S EXPLOITS.
- ( gasping ) THAT'S MY THESIS!
- "HOW TO BUILD A KINGDOM
OF AFTERNOON NAPS"
A RATHER AMATEURISH TITLE
IF YOU DON'T MIND MY SAYING SO,
BUT THE IDEA APPROACHES GENIUS.
"WHAT BETTER GUARANTEE
OF WORLD PEACE
"THAN THE SHADOW OF MUTUALLY
ASSURED ANNIHILATION?
"AND WHAT BETTER MEANS
OF CASTING THAT SHADOW."
- YOU KNOW,
IF I HAD INTENDED FOR YOU
TO READ THAT THING...
- ALAS, READ IT I HAVE,
OLD FRIEND.
- I'M INSPIRED.
TO YOU I ASSIGN THE SACRED TASK
OF UNCOVERING WHAT YOUR THESIS
REFERS TO AS HERO RELICS.
- YOU'RE OUT OF YOUR MIND!
- I WON'T TEMPT FATE
BY SENDING YOU ALONE, THOUGH.
TO ENSURE
THE MISSION'S INTEGRITY,
FERRIS WILL JOIN YOU.
- I REQUEST THIS OF YOU
FOR THE SAKE OF PEACE.
- I JUST WROTE THAT STUPID THING
TO OCCUPY MYSELF!
IT'S MEANINGLESS!
- I SUPPOSE YOU'D PREFER...
EXECUTION?
- ARE YOU ACTUALLY
THREATENING ME?
- WITH ALL DUE REVERENCE,
YOUR MAJESTY,
I ANSWER ONLY TO
THE HEAD OF HOUSE ERIS,
NOT ROLAND'S KING.
MY BROTHER WILL NOT BE PLEASED.
- YOUR BROTHER GAVE ME
LEAVE TO SEND YOU.
"REFUSE AND THE
WYNNIT DANGO SHOP
WILL BE REDUCED
TO ASH AND RUBBLE
IN THE TWINKLING OF AN EYE."
HIS WORDS, MY DEAR.
- Lucile: YOU HAVE
TWO MINUTES TO SET OUT.
- WHAT THE HELL?
WHERE'S THAT COMING FROM?
- HE'S DEADLY SERIOUS.
WE'RE WASTING TIME.
MOVE IT.
YOU'VE THREE CHOICES HERE.
ONE, LOOSE YOUR HEAD.
TWO, LOOSE YOUR TORSO.
THREE, DO AS I TELL YOU.
WHICH DO YOU PREFER?
- ( grunting ) I SWEAR YOU WILL
LIVE TO REGRET THIS, SION!
- THE SOONER YOU DEPART, RYNER,
THE SOONER YOU CAN FULFILL
THAT OATH.
- DAMN YOU!
- Lucile: ONE MINUTE.
- SOMEONE TELL ME
WHOSE VOICE THAT IS!
- GOOD AFTERNOON, YOUR MAJESTY.
- TAKE CARE OF YOUR CHARGE.
- LET GO OF ME!
- QUIT STRUGGLING, PERVERT.
- STOP CALLING ME THAT!
- ( door closing )
- TELL ME, IS THIS THE ROAD
DOWN WHICH I MUST TRAVEL?
- Lucile: NOT NECESSARILY.
SEVERAL PATHS
YET LAY OPEN TO YOU.
- I DON'T SUSPECT A SCEPTER
WILL BE THE LAST WEAPON
YOU BRANDISH.
THAT SAID, AN OLD KING
WEARIES OF HIS DIGNITY
SWIFTER THAN A NEW.
HENCE YOU STILL DRAW BREATH.
- Sion: MANY PATHS
YET LAY BEFORE ME.
HOW MANY LAY BEFORE
THE RELUCTANT SEEKER?
GOOD LUCK, RYNER AND THANK YOU.
- Ryner: IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
WE WOULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN VERY FAR
IF DEEP DOWN, PEOPLE WEREN'T
JUST AS LOATH TO KILL
AS THEY ARE TO DIE.
WAR FORCES THEM
TO CHOOSE ONE OVER THE OTHER.
HIGHBORN OR LOW,
NO ONE WANTS TO SOW MISERY.
NOT REALLY.
THEY JUST DON'T SEE AN OPTION.
WHEN OUR BACK'S
AGAINST THE WALL,
THE BEST OF US SEE THINGS
IN BLACK AND WHITE.
I'VE NEVER PUT MUCH STOCK
IN CHANGING THE WORLD.
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT,
THINGS CAN'T CONTINUE
THE WAY THEY ARE.
IF KILL OR DIE
IS THE ONLY CHOICE,
ITS TIME TO EXPAND OUR OPTIONS.
SO FAR, I'VE SPARED MYSELF
THE PAIN OF TAKING A GOOD,
HARD LOOK AT MY PAST.
BUT IF PAIN AND BITTER TRUTH
ARE WHAT'S NEEDED
TO RESHAPE
MANKIND'S DESTINY,
THEN SO BE IT.
A WORLD THAT HURTS KIEFER,
THAT KILLS TAHILE AND TONY
AND FAHLE.
A WORLD WHERE SION
CAN DO NOTHING BUT BROOD,
IS BEST SWAPPED FOR A WORLD
WHERE PEOPLE CAN
JUST CLOSE THEIR EYES
ON A LATE AFTERNOON...AND NAP.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: YOU KNOW,
I ENJOY A TREK
THROUGH PARTS UNKNOWN
OR HIGH ADVENTURE AS MUCH
AS ANYBODY,
BUT HAVING A FRIGID,
SWORD-WIELDING, PSYCHO-VIXEN
WITH A CHIP ON HER SHOULDER
DRAG ME AROUND BY THE SCRUFF
IS NOT EXACTLY MY IDEA OF...
OH, WAIT. WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
I WAS JUST KIDDING! DON'T...
( yelling )