- ( maniacal laughter )
- AND, THE FINAL
TETHER HAS SNAPPED.
- ( continues laughing )
- I TOLD YOU. THE COMB
NULLIFIES YOUR STRENGTH.
THERE'S NO POINT
IN TRYING TO RESIST US.
AAH! WHAT IN THE HELL?
( screaming )
- ( Ferris screaming )
- BURN IT!
WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE, KUU.
WHATEVER HE IS, WE'RE TRUMPED!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( breathing heavily )
- Ferris: WHO OR WHAT ARE YOU?
- MONSTER. DEVIL. GOD. HERO.
CALL ME WHAT YOU WILL.
YOU'LL CEASE TO EXIST
SOON ENOUGH, WORM.
- ( explosion )
- WELL, YOU CERTAINLY TERRIFIED
THE PINK-HAIRED FELLOW.
BUT THE FACT THAT THERE
IS MORE TO YOUR POWER
THAN MEETS THE EYE
ISN'T, TO ME, ALL THAT SHOCKING.
I MEAN, AFTER ALL
IT STANDS TO REASON,
GIVEN HOW EXCEPTIONAL
YOU ARE IN OTHER RESPECTS,
PARTICULARLY THE FIELD
OF GENERAL IDLENESS
AND WANTON SEXUAL PERVERSION.
- ( explosions )
- I'VE NEVER TOLD YOU,
BUT I ACTUALLY HAD THE CHANCE
TO PORE OVER
YOUR LITTLE TREATISE
AFTER SION HAD IT
SECRETLY COPIED.
A SPECIFIC PASSAGE STOOD
OUT TO ME, AS I RECALL.
"WE WOULDN'T HAVE
GOTTEN VERY FAR
"IF DEEP DOWN PEOPLE WEREN'T
JUST AS LOATH TO KILL
AS THEY ARE TO DIE.
"WAR FORCES THEM TO CHOOSE
ONE OVER THE OTHER.
"HIGHBORN OR LOW,
NO ONE WANTS TO SOW MISERY."
ONLY AN IDEALISTIC SIMPLETON
COULD'VE SCRIBBLED
TRIPE LIKE THAT.
LOATH OR NOT,
PEOPLE KILL, PEOPLE DIE.
THAT'S THE WORLD.
IF SOMEONE LIVES, YOU CAN BET
IT'S BECAUSE SOME POOR FOOL'S
TAKEN THEIR PLACE
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
OF COURSE, I CAN SEE WHERE
A TIMID LITTLE
PRETTY BOY LIKE YOU
WOULD STRUGGLE WITH SUCH
A PAINFULLY OBVIOUS FACT.
I FIND IT IRONIC THAT YOU'D
HARBOR SUCH REMORSE OVER KILLING
WHEN CLEARLY YOU'RE
NOT MUCH OF A KILLER.
SEE. LOOK AT YOU.
I HAVE INSULTED YOU TO YOUR FACE
AND STILL YOU STAND THERE.
NO MONSTER WORTHY OF THE NAME
WOULD TAKE SO MUCH ABUSE.
YOU PINE ABOUT HOW MUCH
DEATH AND DESTRUCTION
YOU'VE SOWN, AND YET HERE
I'VE DODGED YOUR ATTACK
NO LESS THAN FIVE TIMES.
I'LL MAKE A DEAL
WITH YOU, THOUGH.
YOUR NEXT ATTACK,
I WON'T DODGE.
- ( explosion )
- THE LAST THING YOU'RE CAPABLE
OF DOING IS HURTING ME, RYNER.
DO YOU HEAR ME IN THERE,
MR. RUN AWAY?
I DO NOT PARTAKE
OF DANGO, DRINK TEA,
OR CAVORT WITH THE LIKES
OF HOMICIDAL DEMIGODS.
YOU'RE NOT WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
LED TO BELIEVE YOU ARE.
- ( pulsating )
- OPEN YOUR EARS
AND LISTEN TO ME!
- NO.
ALL OF YOU
SHUT THE HELL UP!
EVERYTHING GOES BACK TO NOTHING.
YOU'RE TIME IS DONE.
- RYNER!
- ( explosion )
- ( screaming )
- FERRIS, I'M SORRY.
YOU HAVE TO CLOSE MY EYES.
I CAN'T DO IT.
- ( groaning )
( gasping ) RYNER, STOP.
YOU HAVE TO LISTEN.
YOU ARE NOT...
A MONSTER.
YOU ARE NOT A MONSTER!
( Ferris breathing heavily )
- Ryner: I WAS THIS CLOSE TO
SNUFFING YOUR LIFE OUT
LIKE A CANDLE.
YOU SEE WHAT I AM.
PEOPLE ARE RIGHT TO DESPISE ME.
MY ONLY TALENT IS
FOR WREAKING DEVASTATION.
I'M TIRED OF MURDERING PEOPLE
WHO'VE HAD THE MISFORTUNE
OF GETTING CLOSE TO ME.
THAT'S WHY I WANT YOU
TO GO BACK HOME.
THE MISSION IS
NULL AND VOID NOW.
I THINK SION WILL UNDERSTAND.
- Ferris: IF YOU REALLY
INTENDED TO KILL ME,
YOU'D HAVE DONE IT. PERIOD.
BUT I'M STILL VERY MUCH ALIVE.
WHAT KIND OF A MONSTER
LETS A WOMAN
HURL INSULTS AT HIM? SERIOUSLY?
I'LL BE JUST FINE.
NOW, UNLESS MY MEMORY FAILS ME,
WE WERE ABOUT TO HAVE TEA.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT I STILL HAVE
SOME OF THE DANGO LEFT
THAT IRIS BROUGHT ME.
- ( Ryner crying )
- SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- I SAY
I'M HOME.
Ryner: "IN A FOREST
ON THE OUTSKIRTS OF NELPHA,
"TWO PEOPLE OF UNKNOWN
ORIGINS, ONE MALE, ONE FEMALE,
"ASSAULTED US USING
THE DOLUELI SWORDSCALE.
"THEY HAD IN THEIR POSSESSION
TWO OTHER HERO RELICS,
"WHICH I BELIEVE POINTS
TO THEIR BEING
ON A MISSION SIMILAR TO OURS,
"THOUGH ON WHOSE ORDERS
WE DON'T KNOW.
"THEY DISAPPEARED
IN THE MIDST OF OUR SKIRMISH.
"WHETHER THEY SURVIVED
OR NOT IS NOT CLEAR."
- ( knock on door )
- THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
HOW MANY HOURS DO YOU INTEND
TO WORK WITHOUT TAKING A BREAK?
FOR HEAVEN'S SAKE YOU HAVEN'T
EVEN TOUCHED YOUR MEAL!
- SORRY, ESLINA.
AS SOON AS I COME
TO A DECENT STOPPING POINT,
I'LL EAT SOMETHING.
- NOT A DAY GOES BY
WHEN YOU DON'T PROMISE THAT.
- YEAH. OR SIT THERE MOPING
WITH THAT LOOK ON YOUR FACE.
WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
- NOTHING ANYONE NEED
CONCERN THEMSELVES WITH,
I ASSURE YOU.
- THERE YOU GO AGAIN,
THINKING YOU CAN SHOULDER
THE WEIGHT OF THE WORLD
ALL BY YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE GONNA
DRIVE US ALL CRAZY.
- ESLINA, WHEN THE KING
SHACKLES HIMSELF
TO THE WORKLOAD,
UNLESS HE'S PHYSICALLY STOPPED
HE'LL BURROW THROUGH
THE WHOLE PILE.
THAT'S WHERE YOU STAGE
AN INTERVENTION.
- DON'T WORRY. I'M ON IT.
- I AM SITTING RIGHT HERE.
- DON'T BELLYACHE, YOUR MAJESTY.
WE DON'T WANT FIOLE TO FEEL LIKE
HE HAS TO COME BACK DOWN HERE
TO SET THINGS STRAIGHT.
RIGHT, MADAM SECRETARY?
- EXACTLY! DON'T DISTURB
MY BROTHER'S REST!
TAKE A BREAK FROM WORK
THIS INSTANT AND EAT SOMETHING!
- ( chuckling )
- I SEE ROLAND'S KING
IS WELL LOOKED AFTER.
IT'S VERY HEARTENING TO FIND
YOUR SUPPORTERS SO PASSIONATE.
- AH, WELCOME, LADY NOA.
I HOPE ADJUSTING TO LIFE HERE
HASN'T PROVED TOO DIFFICULT?
- OH, NO. NOT IN THE SLIGHTEST.
I ASSURE YOUR MAJESTY I'VE HAD
A VERY PLEASANT STAY THUS FAR.
ADMIRAL KLOM TAKES
GREAT PAINS TO SEE
THAT I AM MADE COMFORTABLE.
- ( Claugh chokes )
- WELL, HE DOES ENJOY HIS WORK.
- IT APPEARS YOUR
MAJESTY'S INSTINCT
FOR ASSIGNING ADMIRAL KLOM
TO HER LADYSHIP HAS PANNED OUT.
- I'M INCLINED TO AGREE.
- HEY, THAT'S ENOUGH
OF THAT TALK.
- UH, THE LADY HAS
PRESSING BUSINESS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I HAVE NO BUSINESS TO SPEAK OF.
YOU AND I MADE DINNER
ARRANGEMENTS THIS EVENING,
DID WE NOT?
- DINNER, YEAH, RIGHT.
- Calne: REALLY? I THOUGHT
YOU SAID YOU HAD
A RECEPTION TONIGHT.
- ACTUALLY IT GOT POSTPONED!
THEY DECIDED TO HOLD IT
TOMORROW NIGHT
INSTEAD 'CAUSE OF
THAT OTHER THING.
- Calne: AH! OF COURSE,
OF COURSE.
- SO, UH. YEAH. I WAS GOING TO
HAVE TO CANCEL, BUT THEN...
- ( giggles )
IT'S PERFECTLY FINE.
YOU'RE A VERY
BUSY MAN, ADMIRAL.
I DON'T EXPECT YOU
TO KEEP ME APPRISED
OF EVERY SINGLE
LITTLE ENGAGEMENT.
- NOW, CALNE, YOU, UH...
AREN'T TELLING HER LADYSHIP
ANYTHING SHE DOESN'T
NEED TO KNOW, ARE YOU?
- MY GOODNESS, ADMIRAL,
WHAT EVER ARE
YOU KEEPING FROM ME?
- ( chuckles nervously )
NOTHING!
- ( Calne groaning )
- WELL I'LL BE VERY INTERESTED
TO HEAR ABOUT THIS "NOTHING"
OVER DINNER TONIGHT, THEN.
FOR WHICH PURPOSE, SIR,
I DO HOPE THAT YOU DON'T MIND
MY BORROWING HIM.
- HE'S ALL YOURS, MY LADY.
- Calne: THERE WAS NO
CALL FOR THAT.
- ( clears throat )
- ( sighs )
- GOOD THING FOR HIM,
THERE'S NO ACCOUNTING FOR TASTE.
- LADY NOA HAS BECOME
AN UNWITTING HOSTAGE
OF THE ILL-CONCEIVED
ESTABULIAN UPRISING.
I THOUGHT HAVING CLAUGH
AT HER SIDE,
MIGHT OFFER HER LADYSHIP
A MEASURE OF HOPE.
- WELL, SIR, SHE SEEMS
RATHER CHEERFUL.
- ( knock on door )
- ( scoffs )
Miran: HAS YOUR GRACE YET
HAD A MOMENT
TO READ THROUGH MY PROPOSAL?
- Sion: I HAVE. YES.
AND IT WOULD SEEM
THE NORTHERN TERRITORIES
ARE IN DIRE STRAITS INDEED.
- IMPERIAL STOHL BOASTS
FORMIDABLE FORCES
IN THE REGION, AS YOU KNOW.
BUT THE NEWLY EMERGENT
ROYAL FAMILY OF GASTARK
IN THE NORTHERNMOST TERRITORY
HAS SPEARHEADED
THE ANNEXATION
OF NUMEROUS VASSAL
KINGDOMS AS OF LATE.
WITH PREDATORY SWIFTNESS,
ONE MIGHT SAY.
THE DELICATE EQUILIBRIUM
OF MENORIS HAS BEGUN TO STAGGER.
FULL-SCALE WAR IS
ALMOST CERTAINLY IMMINENT.
IN WHICH CASE
OUR FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS
IS TO SOLIDIFY THE HOME FRONT.
IF WE CANNOT MANAGE TO BIND
THE COUNTRY TOGETHER INTERNALLY
BY HOLDING THE
ERRANT NOBILITY IN CHECK,
WE SHALL FALL
AND THE RAVAGING VORTEX
OF UNREST WILL CONSUME US.
TO THAT END,
WHAT IS CALLED FOR,
IS A POLITICAL PURGE.
THAT WOULD BE
THE SUREST ROUTE
TO THE KINGDOM'S
STABILIZATION, YES.
- SUCH AN EXTREME MEASURE...
- A MEASURE YOUR LEGACY AS
A RULER WILL COME TO ECLIPSE.
KEEP YOUR OWN HOUSE IN
ORDER AS THE MAELSTROM
RAGES WITHOUT, SIR...
AND THE COMMON STOCK OF
MENORIS WILL FLOCK
TO ROLAND'S HOLDFOR SHELTER.
BUT ONLY OF COURSE
IF BY THAT TIME
ROLAND ITSELF HAS NOT
SUCCUMBED IRREPARABLY
TO THE MAELSTROM RAGING WITHIN.
AGAIN, SIR, IF I HAVE VENTURED
TOO FAR TOO SOON,
I'M DUTY-BOUND TO STOP
AT YOUR COMMAND.
DUKE STEARIED.
- Stearied: ONE CANNOT TRAVERSE
A HALLWAY ANYMORE
WITHOUT HEARING TELL
OF YOUR ACCOMPLISHMENTS.
I WISHED TO SPEAK
WITH YOU IN PERSON,
TO REASSURE MYSELF THAT
NOT EVERYONE
IN HIS MAJESTY'S CABINET
HAS BEEN PLUCKED
FROM THE LOWER CLASSES.
I HOPE YOU WILL
FORGIVE MY CANDOR.
- I APPRECIATE THE VOTE
OF CONFIDENCE, MY LORD.
I HAVE DESIRED TO SHARE
WORDS WITH YOU AS WELL.
- HAVE YOU INDEED? EXCELLENT.
MAY I THEN ASK YOUR OPINION
OF THE YOUNG KING'S
STATESMANSHIP?
- Miran: WELL, TO BE HONEST,
HIS TENDENCY TO
DISREGARD THE OPINIONS
OF THOSE MORE EXPERIENCED
IS A BIT DISPIRITING.
HIS MAJESTY IS ONLY YIELDING
WHERE IT SEEMS MOST
PERILOUS TO BE SO.
- I THOUGHT AS MUCH.
NO DOUBT THEN, SIR,
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE TO WHOSE
BULWARK IT WOULD BE
MORE ADVANTAGEOUS
FOR YOU TO ALIGN.
THERE'S A GALLING DEARTH
OF MEN LIKE YOU
AMONG OUR ILK
IN THE NOBLE CLASS.
AGREE TO PART COMPANY WITH
HIS MAJESTY AND JOIN OUR RANKS.
AND WHATEVER PRICE
YOU CARED TO NAME
WOULD BE OURS
TO HONOR, LEST WE...
- IF THERE IS, AS YOU SAY,
A GALLING DEARTH OF MEN
LIKE ME IN YOUR CLASS,
YOU CERTAINLY PROVE THE RULE.
WHATEVER PRICE I CARE TO NAME?
YOU CANNOT AFFORD ME.
WHAT I REQUIRE IS SOMETHING
I HAVE FAITH ONLY IN
SION ASTALL TO GIVE...
YOU EGREGIOUSLY MISINTERPRET
MY RESERVATIONS
AS AN OVERTURE TO BETRAYAL
BECAUSE YOU, SIR,
ARE AN IMBECILE.
AN IMBECILE MY KING
IS TOO WILLING TO ENDURE.
HE WOULD SPARE THE VERY INSECTS
CRAWLING BENEATH HIS FEET.
WHICH IS WHY I AM HERE
TO ACT ON HIS BEHALF.
TO GRIND EVERY LAST ONE OF THEM
INTO THE COBBLESTONES.
SO, I BELIEVE
THE PROPER QUESTION IS,
TO WHOSE BULWARK
WILL YOU ALIGN, SIR?
- ( gasps )
- THE OLD POWERS THAT WHITTLE
THIS KINGDOM AWAY TO NOTHING,
OR MY KING?
- Noa: IT'S GETTING
RATHER LATE, ISN'T IT?
- Claugh: I HOPE YOUR LADYSHIP
ISN'T CROSS WITH ME
FOR THE CHARADE EARLIER?
- CROSS?
COME NOW, ADMIRAL KLOM,
DO I TRULY STRIKE YOU
AS THE SORT OF WOMAN
TO WAX PEEVISH OVER
SUCH TRIFLES?
- NO, NO.
IT'S JUST THAT SOMETIMES
A WOMAN MEANS ONE
THING AND SAYS ANOTHER.
- OH? YOU SEEM
ALARMINGLY WELL-VERSED
IN THE WAYS OF THE FAIRER SEX,
MY DEAR ADMIRAL.
- AGAIN WITH
THE "ADMIRAL" THING.
LOOK YOU CAN DROP THE
FORMALITIES AROUND ME,
ALL RIGHT?
CLAUGH WORKS JUST FINE.
- ( giggling )
HOW COULD ANY WOMAN
EVER BE CROSS WITH YOU?
I PROMISE I'M NOT UPSET
IN THE SLIGHTEST.
I'M SIMPLY NOT ACCUSTOMED
TO BEING OUT-OF-DOORS THIS LATE.
CERTAINLY NOT BENEATH
SO LOVELY A NIGHT SKY.
- IS IT REALLY
ALL THAT STRIKING?
I MEAN IT'S THE SAME SKY
OVER ESTABUL, ISN'T IT?
- WELL, THE VIEW IS SIMILAR
FOR EVERYONE, I SUPPOSE.
BUT THE SENSE OF IT CHANGES,
DEPENDING ON WHOM
ONE VIEWS IT WITH.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- HUH, SURE. WHY NOT?
- YOU ARE A CREDIT TO THE
KINGDOM YOU SERVE, ADMIRAL KLOM.
- I AM PLEASED TO KNOW YOU.
- HMM?
- UH, BY THAT I MEAN ONLY TO
EXPRESS MY GRATITUDE.
I'VE HAD SUCH FUN WITH YOU.
MY APOLOGIES FOR STAYING...
( gasps )
( whimpers )
- YOU'RE A CLEVER WOMAN,
MY LADY.
I THINK YOU CAN APPRECIATE
THE POSITION THIS PUTS YOU IN.
- IF I SCREAM,
YOU'LL MURDER ALL OF US?
IS THAT HOW
THE SITUATION STANDS?
- EXACTLY.
OR IF YOU'RE HEADSTRONG ENOUGH
NOT TO COMPLY WITH MY DEMANDS.
NOW STRIP!
- UGH! MAYBE ONE OF THESE DAYS
I'LL UNDERSTAND
A WOMAN'S THINKING.
- Noa: CLAUGH!
- DRIVER, STOP!
DAMN IT!
NOA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
( groaning )
- ( man groaning )
- ( Noa crying )
- WHAT HAVE YOU BASTARDS DONE?
- NOTHING, YET.
- NOTHING?
THEN WHY IS HER LADYSHIP CRYING?
- PRETTY NASTY WOUND YOU'VE GOT.
YOU SURE YOU WANT TO
PUSH THIS RIGHT NOW?
- MY WOUND IS NOT
THE ISSUE HERE.
I ASKED YOU WHY IN THE HELL
THE WOMAN IN MY CARE
IS ON THE FLOOR CRYING!
WHAT I SEEK IS THUNDER!
( grunting )
- I'D SAY ONCE WE'VE MADE IT
OVER THE SUMMIT
THE MOUNTAIN PATH
SHOULD GIVE A GOOD VIEW
OF OUR NEXT DESTINATION...
RUMOR HAS IT THE TOWN OF
REGIT IS DEMON-HAUNTED.
AND WHERE THERE'S
A WHISPER OF DEMONS
A HERO RELIC CAN'T BE FAR...
RIGHT?
- HMM.
( screams )
( groans )
- ON YOUR FEET, PRETTY BOY.
- HUH?
- THE FATE OF THE WYNNIT TEA
HOUSE IS IN OUR HANDS, RYNER.
I HOPE YOU APPRECIATE THAT.
FORGING WORLD PEACE
MAY BE A PIPE DREAM,
BUT PRESERVING THE INTEGRITY
OF DANGO IS NOTHING TO SCOFF AT.
- YOU AND YOUR
OBSESSION WITH DANGO...
INSPIRES ME TO BECOME
THE CAUSE'S FOREMOST CHAMPION.
- ( chuckles )
WOULDN'T KILL US TO
SLOW DOWN A LITTLE THOUGH.
- ( girl screaming )
- GET BACK HERE YOU LITTLE BRAT!
- DON'T BE STUPID!
YOU'RE ONLY MAKING THIS
HARDER ON ALL OF US!
- LET GO! STOP IT!
NO! SOMEBODY HELP!
- KNOCK IT OFF!
- ( girl screams )
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW MUCH
TROUBLE YOU'VE STIRRED UP?
- IS BEATING UP
A DEFENSELESS LITTLE GIRL
REALLY THE FIRST IMPRESSION
YOU WANT TO MAKE
ON A TOTAL STRANGER?
- WHO ASKED YOU
TO GET INVOLVED...
( groans )
- ( groans )
- THOSE GUYS DIDN'T
HURT YOU, DID THEY?
- I CAN'T DO IT ALONE!
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME!
- JUST CALM DOWN.
- LISTEN TO ME!
WE HAVE TO RESCUE HIM!
PLEASE, MISTER... ARUA'S
NOT BAD, HE'S JUST DIFFERENT!
- ARUA?
- HE'S NOT A MONSTER.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
( crying )
IT'S NOT HIS FAULT
THAT HE'S THE WAY HE IS.
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME RESCUE HIM
BEFORE THEY DO SOMETHING!
- Sion: ATTACKED?
WHAT HAPPENED? HAS SHE
BEEN INJURED IN ANY WAY?
- THANKS TO THE FORTUITOUS
INTERCESSION OF ADMIRAL KLOM,
WHO HAPPENED TO BE NEARBY,
LADY NOA IS SHAKEN,
BUT UNHARMED.
HER PRESENCE HERE HAS BEEN KEY
IN SETTING ROLAND AND ESTABUL
ON THE PATH TO RECONCILIATION.
HAD SHE BEEN KILLED
IN TONIGHT'S ASSAULT,
THE NEWLY HEALED SCHISM
BETWEEN OUR KINGDOMS
WOULD HAVE REOPENED.
YOU, AS HER PROTECTOR,
WOULD HAVE BEEN THE FOCAL
POINT OF POPULAR REVOLT.
- I SHOULD HAVE
EXPECTED THIS OF THEM.
SHE WAS THEIRS FOR THE
PICKING, AND I KNEW IT!
THE NOBILITY HOLDS NOTHING
SACRED IN THEIR WAR AGAINST ME
SAVE WHAT INCREASES THEIR
LANDS OR LINES THEIR PURSES.
- IF THEY CANNOT BE
CIRCUMNAVIGATED,
WHAT PATH THEN
LAYS BEFORE YOU?
- THE PATH THAT
YOU HAVE SHOWN ME?
- FOR YOUR HIGHNESS
TO FOLLOW THAT ROAD,
YOU MUST FIRST
BREAK BREAD WITH THE ENEMY.
INGRATIATE YOURSELF TO
THE NOBILITY
YOU SO VEHEMENTLY
AND RIGHTLY DESPISE.
LET THEM NOT SUSPECT YOUR HEART,
EVEN WHEN A LIFE IS AT STAKE.
ERODE THEIR DEFENSES
WITH CHARM, AND THEN...
- SLAUGHTER THE LOT OF THEM?
- IF IT COMES TO IT, YES.
- WHAT OF THE PEOPLE?
IN THE TIME IT TAKES ME TO WIN,
TO BEAT THE NOBLES
AT THEIR OWN GAME...
HOW MANY WILL STARVE TO DEATH?
- WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
EVERYTHING IS IN READINESS,
YOUR GRACE.
I HUMBLY AWAIT
YOUR PLEASURE TO UTILIZE ME.
- ARE YOU RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE INDIGNITY ON LADY NOA?
- WHILE I FIND IT ENCOURAGING
THAT YOUR MAJESTY THINKS
SO CUNNING A
CROSS-PURPOSE WORTHY OF ME,
I MUST SADLY CONFESS TO HAVING
NO HAND IN THIS AFFAIR.
- LEAVE ME.
- SIR.
- ARUA'S BEEN
MY BEST FRIEND FOREVER.
AND FOR A LONG TIME
EVERYTHING WAS FINE.
THEN OUR LORD
RAISED TAXES SO HIGH
WE COULDN'T AFFORD
TO PAY THEM AND EAT.
HE SENT A BUNCH OF SOLDIERS
INTO THE VILLAGE ONE DAY.
MY MOTHER AND FATHER
WERE BOTH KILLED.
WHEN I SCREAMED AT THEM TO STOP
THEY TRIED TO KILL ME.
BUT THEN ARUA
SHOVED IN BETWEEN US.
HE USED MAGIC.
I'VE KNOWN HIM MY WHOLE LIFE.
HE'D NEVER USED MAGIC BEFORE.
AND HIS EYES! HIS EYES!
THEY'RE CALLING HIM A MONSTER.
THE LORD AND THE SOLDIERS
TOOK HIM AWAY,
AND SAID THEY WERE GOING TO
DO ALL KINDS OF EXPERIMENTS.
PLEASE...
YOU'VE GOTTA SAVE ARUA!
- Ferris: RIGHT.
LET'S GET GOING.
- WHAT?
- WE CAN'T LEAVE AN ALPHA
STIGMA ON THE LOOSE.
I'VE SEEN WHAT KIND
OF HAVOC ONE CAN UNLEASH.
- BUT? I MEAN?
- FORGIVE ME, SHOULD WE WEIGH
THE PROS AND CONS FIRST?
- ( sighs )
- WHERE IS YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
BEING HELD CAPTIVE? SHOW US.
- UH, I THINK HE'S PROBABLY...
- VERY WELL THEN.
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE HEADED.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryner: DEMON'S EYES. GREAT.
JUST WHAT I NEED TO HEAR.
YOU KNOW, IF PEOPLE ARE
GOING TO DRAG ME INTO THEIR CRAP
THEY OUGHT TO AT LEAST BE
A LITTLE MORE SENSITIVE!
I DIDN'T CHOOSE TO HAVE EYES
THAT FREAK EVERYBODY OUT
AND THERE'S NOTHING I CAN
DO ABOUT IT, OKAY?
UGH! THIS SUCKS!